[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [
Music]
no  de
[Music]
Hum
さえ
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
[Applause]
hi
[Music]
o y
[Music] [Music
]
y [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [
Applause  hand]
[Music]
w
finally
3D
how come the anime isn't really noisy
y'all put it down first
yeah it's
heavy OK then
B Okay let's do a vlog next time okay borrow it
first  cameraman Okay guys
welcome back to my channel Don't forget to
like Subak and comment and give give
k i mean e join kabolus let's go okay
here I show you on my small island,
yes, it's just a small hut,
there's a boat there, right there?  there's a boat
because Kobo usually moves from island to island,
because there's a lot of Kobo merciswar,
not just on this island, look at
it, it's really high, but yes,
you saw it at the beginning, just e
Is it really
really tall? So it's a bit of a chili there.
So, Kobo will show it to
you guys later, okay, okay, then outfit check
OTD, check okay, that's shoes shoes shoes Look
at my shoes Look at my shoes uh the
details uh uh there are details uh uh you
can  see
[Music]
no, no, it's normal, yes, there's a
jacket, gocap, get three at the
night market, just modify it a little, give it the
brand name Shan range, it's really cool,
so it looks like it's expensive too.  You know, it looks
expensive all the time. Yes, the rest is just trifting.
sor Soror sor hang on a minute I have to go to
school first ah a cilus Please help
cilus I cilus help ah moto daddy am
I scared I am  I don't want to be late Ah, Hurry up, paint my
father's eyes, draw a picture Ah, I'm afraid I'll be
late, hurry up, I hope I'll be able to
finally get to class, is there anyone who's
stuck, is there anyone who's Ril,
who's in love, it feels like it's
blooming,
how do I feel like it's
not tickling
my heart?  when
your scent passes my nose
my eyes widen when I see you pass by
[Music]
in front of me, just an ordinary person. Is it worth it
to be
with you overing but don't want to
bother because I'm not you,
it's better to win  Oh
Asmara
says I'm near you Oh
Asmara hear the whispers of love
your eyes hit
my heart
[Music]
Asmara
feels that these
days still can't get close to you
uh
How to melt
your frozen heart it's better to give up Oh of course
not for the sake of our dreams we must continue to
learn to understand
your Love Language Oh
Asmara  I'm praying
it feels like I'm near you Oh
Asmara hear the whisper of love in
your eyes Oh
Asmara respond to the signal of
my wishes just once
Oh
Asmara is there no room in your heart
H  left
[Music]
for me that afternoon it was
a bump you were the first to come
to me, come to me Oh
Asmara
I feel like I'm near you Oh
Asmara hear the whisper of self-love
[Music] in
your eyes Oh
Asmara hear
it feel like I'm near you Oh
Asmara hear the whisper of Love Five
Oh
[Music  ]
Love
Hi, congratulations, congratulations, R, wait a minute, that's
why there's this cardboard board. What are you
doing? Meet your
new girlfriend, whose name is this?
Uh, who is this? No, I don't know, but I
don't know how handsome I am. I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, bro, are
n't I?  I don't know what to do, but it's normal for
guys to be like this. Hello, guys who
are like this usually have something to do, what do they want, do
they want it or not, don't listen to
him, darling  Don't listen to him, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!  So
it's so sprawled out that it's the same, it's
so hard to wait for Rid's debut, it's still a problem
to be flattened again, that's enough, there's no need  There's
no need to make a fuss when you're just making a fuss about cardboard, it's
not
cardboard, that's enough, that's enough, that's enough, that's enough, that's enough, okay?
Eh, I'm sorry, for your sake,
it's better for you to focus on Rimu, I'll take this
first, OK, bye
bye, cheer up,
R, no, don't let my girlfriend aniani
suisui
[Applause]
[  Music]
[Music]
て
k
[Music]
Yi
iss Yeah
[Music]
Yeah I love you
love love love love
love love love love love
you love love love love love
[Music] [
Music] love love
baby love baby
[Music]
loveab love [Music]
for [Music] [Music] [Applause] [
Music]
love you love you love you
Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love Love [Music] [Applause
]
Love I love
you
[Music]
yeah
oh ah so son son What's going on why are
you crying are you so sad  We  just sang a
great song together come
on your heart Hurts but why my boyfriend
sit it on me he goes for zetta wait wait
hold on a moment you have a you have a
boyfriend tell me who He is tell me
where He is and I will take  care of
everything Dad will take care of
everything for you coule I don't know I
don't know his name but I love him Um
What Um I don't really think I
understand but it's okay it's okay son
looks sometimes things in life  Just They
just don't go your way but  it's all
right You'll be okay I promise no no no
I I can't I can't take this
anymore here Kids Man
here Gun K I can't I can't do that I
can't do that you're my
sonak  all right right Well it's my job
after all So I guess I'll do it if you insist
doing my
job What happened here KY What did  you
do Oh I mean I I didn't do anything all
right look all right Hold on I know what it
looks like Look I shot I shot her
with a water Gun all right with with a
water Gun Look it's not Lethal or
anything she De She  just
playing You should be teaching her stuff
like this you know Kids kar look
only Come
on we fail his parents I wonder Come on
[Music]
live come on Yes come back to me
come Mommy yes yes yes sorry mommy It's
Okay It's okay oh Kobo  it Took you long
enough  Come on get up before Dady Gets
in
trouble Oh my
God I'm back mother
father well thank God what happened Kobo
What happened My boyfriend on
me Who's your boyfriend Where is he I
Said Uh I don't know his name but I love
him  listen here you little [ __ ] forget
about him Mommy is here Let's just have
fun together Okay have fun let's
go yeah let's go Sounds like fun you
guys Um I'm coming too right I'm invited
right you go buy milk milk really for
breakfast milk  yeah again we  need it
yeah byebye by
whatever co come on
[Music]
I want to be
president so I don't get php guys
[Music]
anymore
[
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Applause  ]
ST
SH p p
[Music]
p thank
you
yay I'm good now Thank you oh oh I'm
happy to hear that but you know Mommy
has to go home now and rest but I will
sleep and dream about
you let's go
so I you I you
bye Okay she now So m does know that I'm
not home yet Ok I w show you guys
something I want to show you something really
cool, really cool, really cool, a trick
using my R
power at
this
ah uh ah  am am
am Wow
H Weh it's raining really Crazy cool yeah
lenanoarata Isn't the water really cool
then it starts
raining ah this is also the first time you
guys see my jelly fish Umbrella
right By the way  every
time you send a super
chat,
it will give more power to the
ya
It's only the power of the
sound of a kobok that can
make rain like this, bro, eh. We thank
you for the super chat. It's
arrived. It's calf-length. It's quite a while,
guys. I haven't showered yet. I'll
wash it at the same time.  nice face thank
you
aatoah
eh how come there are more and more yes
thank you thank you But I can't swim
Eh I can't
swim just a moment slowly send super
chat Okay relax
frog like kok
[Music]
k
Thank you Thank you
for Thank  you for this love thank you
okay thank you
[Music]
you
my P
hur finally went
home ah luckily wearing Jan luckily my
outfit is waterproof oh by the way
welcome welcome to my
light this is inside Mer suar aku
Oh, I'm a little bit, okay, let's go do a
quick room tour. Okay, so there are
stairs here because MIRC, my voice is
really high, actually, that's all. Yes, never mind, let's just stay
here, L, okay, just on this floor,
we'll go upstairs later, OK, okay.
Then usually after school I go
straight to bed and go straight to bed, but yes,
because I brought guests here,
I'll just do a room tour, right?
Oh, this is called ayamaadas, right?
OK?  Continue e. This is the usual place where
food is picked up and
if you want to relax, I'll go with my
friends who I usually loot with. Well,
what else is there? There are
lots of dolls. Sorry, yes, then there's this,
there's Fajri Kipli Kupli, OK?  Come on, let's take a break. Yes,
there's Rio, there's Rai, there's Ryu, yes, there are lots of
them, guys, and there are several
instruments in my collection, like
one of them is a piano, a keyboard, the same keyboard and
then there's e. Where I usually stream
is here, what's there? There's a monitor.
At first I was just using the TV, so I was
relaxing for a while and then I saw that there was a
catfish tree and then there was a refrigerator and there were
two instruments that I often played,
namely electric guitar and acoustic guitar,
or not, I played acoustic guitar more often,
well, that's the one I played earlier.
This one, guys, is the
electric guitar, yeah. And whether it's the Violin, it's
rare, it's rare, right? There's
this plant. Hm, the pitcher plants have already
reproduced a lot.  the
cute lights on the top,
wow, they're
cute, the lights keep going. Isn't
that the ceiling really cute? How,
how, how, isn't it beautiful? My room looks like
the owner is an idiot. I saw Kak
Kobo. Please try playing
the instrument [Music] I'm kind and not
I'm arrogant, luckily I'm not loud, okay? I'm
fine. I'm fine. That's fine, you guys are
here, okay, let's go to the design. I'm going to
take that guitar. OK, I'll just play the guitar
and take off my jacket. Wait a minute.  OK,
wait here for a moment,
OK,
OK, I'm going to request buculbucul k
play guitar k guitar,
this is a melodious song,
OK, what do you think about it? Yes, you guys
definitely know how to sing together. Yes, those who know
the song, we sing together, OK
[Music]
[Music  ]
bir h
[Music]
h
i
[Music]
せ
men
[Music]
si
mこ 忘
[Music]
[Applause]
て
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
та
to
Han
[Music]
Kim
k
[Music]
n
a little wrong, it's okay l
yeah a little wrong sorry sorry I Made some
mistakes because I'm so nervous This is
my first time in 3D life singing singing
with active guitar the pressure is
different from from the US karaoke you
know  you know sorry sorry
That's it
with me, okay, so earlier I
showed you how my room looks
and what's in it, but there's still one
there's one more thing you guys don't
know and I want to show you guys
now now right here Yes still  there's one
thing you don't know yet, look at it
eh eh eh why is it broken Woi is it
Wii
t leave my private Le di verrobo OK e
just a moment I have something I
have to
use [Music] Now ready let's go to the
[Music]
sky
W how about it Cool new feature  merchar
me Wow, it's really attacking, the cameraman is here, the
cameraman, look here, it's
really high, so high
[Music]
ah, the cameraman is flying, guys, it's
really cool, even though the plane is really small,
we have to cross it.  Let's go there first,
yes, you know, later you will
know what I'm going to do. But
now I don't know if the rainbow can be
stepped on or not, like I'm afraid
of falling through, isn't it funny, guys, so
let's just jump, okay, I'll jump long, Friday,
okay, okay
[Music]
bismillak one two
three
Yes your scam I'm a scam Wi okay okay for
real this one for real okay this time it's
real
one two
three
Wow wuh wuh
Crazy really cool I  Let's
[Music]
gomite there's a really cute rainbow there's three
1 2 3 then there's clouds it's cloudy
now it's raining but yeah later it can change
again isn't it raining Yes it's easy,
this problem is the weather and there's
balloons there's stars I guess  It's
really funny There's a floor there's a bird
can you see who the bird is
[Music]
let me go hi
I come on
[Music]
when with me
any to [
Music]
goodp
thep
the
[Music]
thep of
the
best
[Music]
time I'm the one Who you've been waiting
for [
Music]
me sen k [Music
]
h [Music
込
[Music]
sung
hau top  of the top top of the world to
the
Topp
[Music]
the
[Music] [
Music] [Applause] [Music]
ina
you
[Music]
music
hah How cool or
not
? Isn't that cool enough but you know what's
cooler
like the stage? That's crazy cool, when
will you see Kowo
Idoro
like that for a second?  barar
[Applause]
[Music]
cameraera this
you guys
[Laughs]
f okay yeah they're already here so let's
invite something next time ya wan take the stage
for
Spin
okay
that's perform together Okay perform per okay okay okay
okay first sit down Please
OK
sit
I
have to put on your head
Okay
here don't move don't move
okay
[Applause]
girl
[Music]
[Applause]
group OK let's
go position position  post okay
[Applause]
[Music]
所
йй
[Music]
[Applause]
W J
bye bye go  go go away go go go go go away go
away go go fly
F go go next next next Go What's that Bye
Bye byee Bye Bye by by
by Thank you
very much, I've been expelled for a long time,
really
[Music]
okay, I don't feel it  It's already at the end of the
event. Yes, maybe someone is
interested, yes,
rice field fishing modding agencies, yes, I want to
show you something
OK, that is,
ee, Cang my business card, OK? So that's
really possible, ladies and gentlemen, if you're interested, you can
contact me.  this way, OK, here
you go, hm, what is this, what is this, Kobo, what is this, Oh
yes, this is a card case, this is a card
case, so that's why Kobo keeps
name cards in that card case, OK? Oh, you
want one too, because it's really cool. Ah sumpil,
yes, that's really cool, right?  that's
all  You can
find it. Yes, I've bought it. This is
really cool. It can be used to protect KTP cards,
student cards, SIM cards, STNK cards, ee
cards, all card A, basically it's okay,
okay, great, then next. I want to
inform you tomorrow, hello.
Funny hero, isn't it? Crazy, really cool, okay, not
note down the date  alright note down the
date OK, guys, take notes, OK, OK, Nice Nice
Iko Iko Iko Iko, OK, last but not
least, I still have another important announcement.
What is it? What is it?
Yes, let's look at it together.  Just what is
the video,
what is
universal, what does it mean, ma'am
Oh, I don't
know either, I don't know what is that, just
be patient. Ok, coming soon, really, really
soon,
okay, hah,
yes, yes, thank you, guys.
If that's the case, finally, I want to show you
Gigi
[Music]
I'm having a hard time having a hard time yeah that's it then
bye guys bye bye KBU has to
leave you now bye Bye Bye
everyone bye bye miss me
okay
but
it's a lie Thank you everybody for here
tonight yo spell rain  Ladies and
gentlemen, brothers and sisters, anyone at any age,
let's be together.
Minak the shining spell, the
world is sunny. It's lonely in a vacuum.
Problems come and go. It's
normal to be alone. I'm reluctant to take a
step. I open my eyes and look up at the sky. The
raindrops echo. The
raindrops sound like they're going to whisper. Let's explore.
the world is dreamy
and various dreams will not solve
problems. Have the courage to step
through all
obstacles, even though the rain won't
stop. I'll accompany you here.
Recite Mandra to bring light
to
your days.  Get rid of all the doubts that
cover your heart, thoughts and emotions, smooth out the
mtra, bring light, open
new things, everyone is still enthusiastic,
it doesn't matter, type one if you are enthusiastic,
huh, one one, one one, one,
ready for another one, yes, let's go,
what is the mantra, Shine of light, Shine
the World, huh, it's hard  I slept
all night, my heart was
pounding, I couldn't wait to
have fun on stage,
together with
you, the sad ones here, there,
happy sunsets, giving
warmth to the hearts of the guests, I
painted beautiful smiles
your night, various dreams will not
solve
the problem, dare yourself to break through,
break through
what
[Music]
obstacles, if the rain doesn't
stop, I'll accompany you here,
send a spell to bring succinar light
[Music] for
your days, get rid of all the doubts
that cover your heart, thoughts and emotions
spell out the mantra, bring the magic, open the
new symbol
[Music]
I remove all
the doubts that surround
my heart, think about it, come Jan, no, the
new Pronouncement, no
New prohibitions are not
new Wow, congratulations,
congratulations,
congratul JAT
Oh, don't
do it, you can't do it at this height, you can't do it at this
height, you don't have to be
arrogant, darling, you can do it, it's easy,
hold on, hold on. Yes, you don't have to
talk about it, okay, okay, let's just
mute it later, okay?  y show it come on let's do it
[Applause]
what's up Oh my
God nice glowing cuy nice oh
okay okay
okay
Go eh Hello Boss  don't be shy
Sinia
[Music]
Okay okay then
S
guys sungkemngkem first
ah okay okay
to be polite Bi polite
[Music]
take bye
[Laughs]
muah