foreign
[Music]
hello
honey can you hear me
I have oh
honey
can you hear us I have a very very
special guest with me today
are you ready
I'm ready
hello everybody and welcome to mornings
with Fox Mom I have a very special gay
with oh yes with me today I wanted to
say cake
sorry I'm a little nervous I have a very
special guest with me today she is a
gamer
CEO entrepreneur
so sorry
reduce yourself
and yeah well I just want to say first
off you know this is Andrew with whole
life uh collabing so you know we we use
different programs Etc so I look like
but this is totally fine okay this
isn't as good as it gets and we you look
so appreciate the effort that was put
into this in the first place oh my God
belly button when when you go back like
that I could spot a belly button
[Music]
I'm gonna blush well yeah oh yeah so I
didn't I mean say properly who I am I
I'm from Whole Life English the first
generation myth and I'm a phoenix and I
am uh potential like an owner of a fast
food franchise yeah this and that thank
you for having me here in this lovely
room today thank you for taking the time
out of your very very busy day you have
a freaking concert tomorrow and it you
still made time to come here thank you
this will actually help me calm my
nerves because I just want to be
distracted to be honest I got you baby
So for anybody who is tuning in who's
never watched this uh this is not a
podcast all right I'm just warning you
all the whole reason I started this show
was to have an excuse to talk to people
I just wanted to have an excuse to get
to know somebody because I'm sure you
know you've collabed with a lot of
people when you have a collab you don't
really get to kind of get to know the
person and talk to the person if it's a
game right because you're kind of
focused on the game but this way we have
each other for an hour and we can just
talk and get to know one another I think
honestly people keep on telling me to
like you wanna do more that's done like
chit chatting streams because we want to
just hear you guys talk so I think this
is what people want anyway this is what
the people want and we're giving it to
them you
give it to them I feel with zatsu's
sometimes even your most die-hard fans
have a chance to learn something about
you that is new because for example I'll
be asking you questions about stuff that
I might not know and that's always my
favorite part is seeing people go you
know I never knew this about that person
I love looking at you by the way thank
you I love your like whole Generations
new outfits you know
I am so sorry girls looks so so damn
I know the designs are so cool they are
all a little bit jealous of uh one area
of my outfit in particularly
maybe the ears the fluffy ears
definitely definitely Millie did have
some fluffy ears but mine are just a
little longer a little bigger a little
bouncier my ears you know look at them
my ears they wiggle
but thank you so much I feel so I am so
sorry to all cosplayers and artists I
feel that etherea we were already so
difficult to draw yeah we've got worst
yeah ethereal please why but did you
girls like put like the these new
outfits to do like decide on the theme
together
we had a choice of a few themes and we
ended up pushing for one theme uh we had
a few kind of themes that we could go
for and basically for the initially it
was just kind of a queen concept but
then Millie came up with the idea for
each of us to represent a suit of cards
and okay I like this I feel like I'm the
one getting interviewed hold on I I
don't think you're ready for this in my
blood I don't think you're ready for
this hold on um I this is
it's so much
it's so good though holy so much
everything so much effort put into it I
love it my mama is uh the manga cup for
a really really famous manga called
Overlord
so my mama subin is just incredible
it's insane right man can I ask you
about outfits because you have oh I feel
like this could have been also your
debut outfit you know I love my my I
love my you know I think this outfit's
amazing but the more I
see this new outfit I realize how
perfect my debut outfit was
perfect both I want to ask you questions
I am so honored and flattered that
you're asking me questions but miss
interview sit down it's your turn to be
interviewed
since we're talking about outfits can
you run me down some of your outfits
because you have the amount of
hairstyles and outfits that you have can
we have like a timeline of the kiwawa
outfits does he even have a frog one oh
it's not really official but I I made it
happen she is official in my heart right
now is the first one I got after my
default
um but I got this new hairstyle just
yesterday I got something added to it
but this is the first one we had a
casual theme yeah
and then in the same year soon after we
had a a fancy like party dress theme I
remember that yes that's my my red dress
where I have actually also a mask like
yeah not like yours but I do have them
it's similar I love that outfit of yours
so much thank you and then after that I
guess was kimono at like new year the
New Year's one yeah kimono outfit and
then after that was probably my 1
million subscribers uh like request
outfit because we could request like
something and I requested for an outfit
which I asked for a German diendo dress
okay okay am I missing I don't remember
that one hold on let me let me look at
that up though your 1 million outfit I
think if you type in Kiara diondo d i r
n d l and Chicago oh wait I see it
yeah okay in between I forgot actually
before the Casual one was a joke outfit
for April the first the first April
after hour debut uh we got the those
Mimi little small
um like to these oh my God wait I've
never seen this this outfit oh
oh my goodness
I am sorry I need a minute oh
ah well thank you
oh my God
have you seen a dandel before no I it's
I I've seen I know what like Oktoberfest
is and stuff like that so I've seen
those outfits but yours is so spring you
look like the mother of spring oh my God
thank you I love the hats going to the
mouth it's ironic because you know this
is kind of our our traditional sorry I
can't get over it I can get over it I'm
just wow
I am but yeah this is my first time
wearing a dandel because I never had the
money to get an actual one so oh
my little jacket over it you have a
little blazer and the K-pop part
I'm sorry I believe I've never seen this
before thank you I have too many you
know I never know what to use oh my God
I love so sorry you've never had the
money before to afford one of those and
now you have yeah yeah because I mean
the good quality ones are pretty
expensive I guess I could have maybe
like gone for a really really cheap one
before but yeah I never got one and it
was kind of sad because all my friends
had one and you wear them for like in
summer we have like you know Oktoberfest
and yeah and similar like just like
carnivals and amusement parks or
whatever you would wear this but or even
in school for like graduation or so but
I never had it so can I ask you more
questions about it so the outfits that I
have seen I've typically seen like the
mar the bar made outfit the Oktoberfest
outfit yours seems to be a lot more
spring inspired and even the chokers and
stuff like that is very flowery is that
kind of part of it or did you add those
yourself
it's totally like original I mean you
can like always accessorize your dandel
and in terms of colors there's legendals
come in every color you can literally do
every color so I've only ever seen them
in darker colors I've never seen
something so pastel and minty like yours
so pretty she exists oh definitely oh my
God you look like a when you have the
jacket on I'm sorry I'm still watching
the video
you have the jack
ET
thank you it's supposed to be kind of a
leather jacket because you don't often
combine the dandel with a leather jacket
it looks awesome and I love the
background with the with the amusement
park and the the castle is also looking
very very European thank you thank you
nobody knows this looks like to be
watching stuff in there I don't know
what you're watching but yeah sorry
everybody so I uh this is the video I'm
watching it's because I did not know
that you had this extra outfit I've seen
your other outfits but this one uh I'm
sorry I think this is my favorite it's
just so thank you
just telling me to explain one thing to
you talk to me there's like this apron
right and the ribbon um depending on
which side it is oh it's a statement of
like whether you're taken or yes or
married or widowed and or or a virgin I
guess oh not necessary
um and well my papa my artist is uh
Japanese so there was a misunderstanding
oh no he put the ribbon on the wrong
side making a statement of saying are
you a widow and I'm married I'm married
apparently oh no oh no
no it's okay no one really takes it
seriously I feel like that happens in a
lot of different cultures because I know
for example in Orthodox Churches you'd
have to cover your hair if you are of
marryable a so you have to leave your
hair uncovered if you're of marryable
age and you know looking to get married
and if you're taken married all that you
hide your hair away you put a little you
know you know the little babushka kind
of uh style that everybody always says
where you just put the scarf on your
head yeah
because I am a single mom of very many
kids I found them in cabbages and here I
am
aren't you in a memorable age I'm a
paste
it is too late I have decided I just
want to be you know the best wine Aunt
the best wine mom the best everything
oh being the mother of so many has made
me realize that I'm all right I can just
you know live in a cabin by myself and
have a good time oh man okay so going
back to the office after this outfit so
we're at what five outfits and then yeah
I guess uh that was my last one yeah
last one and then actually I was
supposed to get or we were supposed to
get one another one last year but it's
been so delayed the one that I should be
getting last year I'm still working on
um I'll be getting it maybe before
summer I think I'm excited
biggest like image change ever I would
say oh my God I can't wait I can't wait
I can't wait I'm gonna be there I'm
gonna be there watching Waiting Wishing
thank you
oh when's your new one coming up come on
I want a new one I just got mine
honestly I'm okay if I got to you know
play around with my next one I would
love to have my hair up something uh do
you know Bayonetta I would want like
those type of glasses maybe a casual
outfit maybe not a casual outfit I don't
know
especially for all the artists and
cosplayers and even just a pajama right
like keep everything give me a little
sleeping mask a pajama I'm good I would
want I would love a onesie but of my
fans the honey bunnies just like a big
onesie of a honey bunny
like honestly I I don't mind something
very very soon
yeah that would be nice I want to see
like what kind of casual outfit you
girls would go for what style me too I
think uh the next outfit is going to be
individual because usually we get like a
team outfit but then everybody has
individual stuff so I think everyone's
gonna go theme too and then we split
ways so I think it's fun I think it's
fun having your own kind of outfit
because what if somebody wants oh also
I'd love an army outfit I love love love
military style
oh but even that I feel like they could
Implement in a casual one time exactly
pushing for a casual one please I want a
casual one too trust me that is like my
next my next move hair up glasses casual
outfit please please I cannot wait
speaking of uh casual
you are not a Casual Gamer you are a
very serious gamer
yeah somebody has given to you okay so
when I made the list right I said you're
a CEO Idol gamer and everyone in chat
was like um she's not a gamer are you
kidding me she's been playing fire
emblem for hours I looked at your game
list you played places I am not a gamer
who said that I will not reveal their
name
hmm
I will not reveal their name
but somebody said she's not a gamer and
I I defended you I said she is a gamer
thank you
I am the gamer of whole life English you
are the gamer so I want to talk to you a
little bit about games right right now
you're playing Fire Emblem yes tell me
more tell me about what kind of games
you play what kind of games you've
played I thought yeah
it's like I feel like my game choices
are not the most popular game choices
but I just want to play like when I
stream so much I want to play things
that I actually enjoy you know so I
don't play like
um I don't I can't I can't get into FPS
and horror games which seem like it
seems like those are the very popular
game choices uh streaming choices and I
wish I could get into that but I can't
so I just usually for the past two and a
half years I've been streaming a lot of
RPG games long series and then in
between like some fun stuff uh like
shorter one-off games yeah but
Fire Emblem but in the past I've played
very Niche other Niche games like yeah
until your Risa have you heard about
that actually Niche I feel like that's a
pretty well known jrpg no
that's only Horizon I would say is maybe
in Japan pretty well known but outside
of Japan I guess actually Ariza made the
whole Atelier series quite a bit more
well known but before at delay Ariza it
was just a very very Niche okay um yeah
somebody said it's niche in streaming
that makes sense right there's a lot of
games that people might know but that
don't get streamed for example near
automata a lot of people know about that
series but it doesn't really get
streamed as much see that's another one
that I completed I streamed the whole
game how did you like it it was
did you play it yeah well okay spoilers
for near automata um how many endings
have you gotten
I don't I don't remember
um I think I was like in the beginning I
was like yo this is a long game I'm only
gonna do one and then people were like
you should do more and then around the
end of the game I was like wait I do
want more so I think I did more than one
for sure I don't know how many okay
they're saying you got all of the
endings okay I got them all they I got
them all I think the core ones at least
how dare you say she's not a gamer huh
yeah
yeah but there's like one thing that um
really really triggered me in this game
um I had a problem with the gameplay in
what way which was it was a totally
self-induced
um handicap
I love those we take those
um you know how you know do you have you
got to do hacking in the game right I
barely remember go on go on and there's
like little hacking that's like a mini
game within the fight you have to hack
into the enemies and it brings you to a
different like layout where you're just
like it's like a little mini game yeah
inside the game yeah like a block game
shooting shooting and I had troubles
until the end of the game until we
realized I had vsync on oh how did that
change the gameplay how did that affect
it once I turned it off or it was the
other way around I don't know but once I
turn it off suddenly
rocked that section suddenly it was like
a million times easier and something in
your brain
it feels your power level I love that
like I literally realized that on stream
and we saw the difference because they
were oh I don't know why we didn't like
why my viewers didn't tell me earlier
that something is really wrong when I
play the game oh people are saying it
was just really sped up
yeah yeah
it was so difficult to play before but
in general I I just really love this
kind of long story games you know I want
to be told the story and at the end of
this long journey it's just nice to like
look back on it at the end and we're
like wow we come so far this was so
beautiful yeah that's something I I'm
trying to get better at I don't really
play a lot of story games and I'm trying
to play more of them but I feel kind of
guilty if
people kind of come in in the middle of
the journey so I tell myself all right
baby I'll give people a week so that way
if they miss the VOD do you have any
advice for you know streaming really
long games and kind of just
what I do is usually I play it only once
or twice per week and I know there will
always be people who don't watch it
because a they want to play it
themselves in the future or B they just
don't wanna they don't have time or then
they don't want to watch long streams
like that
so that's all right but you just gotta
make sacrifices if you want to have fun
streaming now that's what I think if you
want to enjoy your your job but yeah so
if you don't like stream it like every
freaking day of the week I think it
should be fine people will catch up yeah
I feel like like you said once a week is
a really good time because then if you
did Miss let's say part one of the game
you have a whole week to catch up to it
and yes everyone gets busy but then
maybe after that you'll have two weeks
to catch up on and somebody said how did
you discover 144 Hertz I want to ask you
that after this
but what I got
wait but I do want to say like once a
week is maybe the best for the viewers
but I do I do want to say two two times
per week is more recommendable because
I've noticed like when I play so many
different games uh that I forget the
controls yeah until the next week or
even the story I'm playing I don't know
if you've ever played this game I so
recommend it it's called Uh outer Wilds
I am recommending do not watch a lot of
like don't spoil the game for yourself
it is amazing the story is incredible
but it's kind of like a mystery in the
space I think uh that's just Zeta just
played it not long ago I think
I think I think I'm a maybe maybe play
it or did play it I'm not sure maybe but
it's I think you'd love it but there is
a mystery in the game right and I find
whenever I take too long
I just I forget the clues I forget the
mystery I forget you know everything
yeah it do me like that so
too much time in between would be
recommendable but then it's hard because
I also want to do is that's a DOT I also
want to do collabs I also want to I feel
every week when I look at my schedule I
just go there's not enough days in the
week
yeah yeah that's that's true well you'll
find your rhythm
I think you should give it a go it will
be fun to have an ongoing Series yeah I
have a few but you know uh we can talk
about that later tell me about the 144
Hertz how does that work for you
uh this was last sometime last year I I
don't quite remember how this happened
but I guess I just changed some settings
or whatever I didn't realize but I was
playing I think this was when I was
playing tunic have you ever heard of
tunics yes oh the little fox it looks so
cute
this was my favorite game of 2022 I'm
telling you okay okay I played the whole
thing it's incredible like it's
mind-blowing but was it a long game
Sorry to interject was it a long game
it was as long as Fire Emblem well how
many streams like how many hours would
you say 20 hours Upstream
oh wait tunic game time Tunica but the
thing is you and I we love to talk so
that's why I want to hear from you how
long it took so if you wanna play it
through properly like me 100 then normal
people who don't stream I guess take 20
hours but I probably did more than that
also because it's pretty difficult
sometimes so you struggle a little bit
so maybe 30 hours oh I'm excited I've
had a lot of people recommend me that
game too
but yeah so
um
I realized apparently the what hurts is
that how you say it hurts I think yeah
yeah they when you make them higher on
your monitor it means that you're kind
of playing the game in higher FPS I
didn't know that and
I just randomly changed no wait this
wasn't even with tunic this was with um
cult The Cult of the lab another great
game
I love it another great game and I
suddenly went up from like what 25 fps
to 60 FPS oh my god of gaming experience
gamer girl
like what um how did I play like this
until now incredible it's like it's the
v-sync story all over again yeah exactly
I'm A Whole New World opened up to me
it's because you're too good that's why
every game gives you an automatic
handicap always yeah yeah so for real
for real I want to ask you so you've
mentioned a few of these games what
would you say have been some of your
most memorable games that you've
streamed or moments that you've had with
games I want to know okay well tunic is
100 one of them that was like I went in
there with not so many expectations I
just knew it was a cute uh Indie it's an
indie right yeah in Indie
um cute Fox game that is inspired by
Zelda games heavily inspired and that
was just life-changing and then
um I think near automata also I I'm so
glad you got to experience that oh
yeah and also um there's this like
[Music]
um
I really enjoyed playing for all of GTA
5. you played wait
you're real yes okay only whole life
English member who played all of GTA 5.
I have never gotten into GTA because I
don't really drive and then I remember
on on the twitch television it was huge
everybody was doing role playing but
they weren't playing the game
do you genuinely think like it's a game
I should I should play incomplete
I think so like for me it was so out of
character too but it was so much fun to
play with this the story is just so
ridiculous and I asked like what you
thought was fun about it because when I
looked at GTA it just seemed like you
just drive a car all the time
the fans like I would go out of my way
to drive the car more even when you were
able to teleport no nothing oh yeah I
think you could call it like travel
right yeah but I would want to drive
around because I didn't give a
about cars before that but then I I got
so into the game that I also was so
excited about seeing muscle cars because
that was the first time I found out what
a muscle car is I love that but but the
main thing about this game I wouldn't
say it's driving at all so don't worry
it's just like this fun little like you
know I saw the driving Parts as a good
opportunity to tangent yeah and to talk
you got me a good story because lately
because of Pomo I got into Metal Gear
Solid and yeah I so I played a lot of
games I was a little bit of a gamer girl
gamer Fox mom and I have this problem
where I feel like I've played a lot of
really famous story games so sometimes
it's hard for me I don't want to replay
a game that I've already played because
it's not the same you know I wouldn't do
that
but now you're saying okay I'll have to
I'll give an honest look to Grand Theft
Auto
V so good it's so good that's I was not
expecting that answer out of you I love
this I love this too yeah I think but a
lot of or yeah a lot of kfps say that
like my fans say that this is what
number one or in their top three of
their favorite playthroughs of mine
because it was just a hilarious the
whole time there's a game I heard about
I think it's called L.A Noir it's kind
of from what I gathered it's kind of
similar to GTA except with a little less
driving and a little bit more Detective
L A and then Noir n-o-i-r-e
oh I don't know if you've heard of it
Noir
it's the same developers that made it
every game we mentioned everyone's like
almond Planet oh yeah yeah yeah I wanna
I wanna play more of these kind of games
actually now yeah I just need the perms
of course of course that's always you
know that's always uh sometimes when
people like hey Nina when are you gonna
play that game I'm like I'm waiting I'm
waiting
struggle I'm sitting there twiddling my
thumb yeah
[Music]
is a good thing about playing like these
long jrpgs for me though because like I
I see other whole live English members
like struggling to like you know find
something to play sometimes because
they're waiting on the perms and they
played everything already like all these
shorter games and I'm just like sitting
here on my 25th part time of tales of a
fries having a good time and not just
that but when I look through your vods
you also have a lot of zat Sudan you
have a lot of talking streams so it's
like what am I doing this week talking
talking talking uh I tell you rise uh
Fire Emblem we're good yeah I also like
to do a lot of hand cam streams actually
a close ironing stream oh my God how do
you come up with that
a little more hand can streams than I I
am running out of ideas but this was one
of the genius ones I would say I've had
an idea for a handcam stream hold on
hold on I'm gonna run it by you I want
but I'm not sure if I want to do it with
livers or with the chat so let me know
oh do you know bingo
yes so I can go so for example if I go
on a website I can create Bingo cards
and I was thinking maybe of doing them
with like different libraries and
different outfits because I think we're
30 livers and on a bingo card there's
24. so to randomize them I would add
other outfits and stuff like that and I
would actually want to have my like
print them out the cards and you know
use the little marker what do you think
what would that
what would the game be so basically the
way it works is I'll have a card right
that's randomized of pictures and so
with the audience and then you just pick
a b 24 like be a lira Pandora and then
I'm like do you have a lyric and door on
B then you press it yeah everybody yeah
yeah that's the whole point right
because then whoever wins first
oh yeah that sounds cool right but I
feel like I kind of want to do that
against my audience because it's kind of
fun oh yeah you should right but they
might be cheating
no because all right but then I'd have
to ask them to tweet their card at me oh
wait no actually if I what if it's just
two cards
one card for me one card for the
audience
probably rigged I have really turning
into a grandmother maybe you could do
that in a member stream oh look at you I
haven't actually done anything yet that
was all my member streams I just talk
and drink what about you see more
variety now yeah yeah you are this is
why you're a CEO entrepreneur
yep yep yep what do you do in your
memory stream
so there's a little taste give us a
little tease the problem was that until
like maybe a year ago we didn't really
have perms for any games to play in
member streams at except for like two so
everybody would like repeat those right
which way again guys talking to you in
the member stream honey
but then I was like I'm sick of this I
want more variety so I started like
requesting specifically for uh member
streams games and now we have like this
huge library that we can choose from oh
that's cool
Aspire was one of them
don't worry we are going to talk about
slate Aspire I have almost a thousand
hours in slay the spire
my God like what the yeah okay uh
we're gonna talk about that in a minute
uh but for the member stream all I do is
I just okay I have 894 hours okay it's
not that much it's not a thousand eight
nine four it's not that much
you have 894 hours of members no no no
of slay the Spire sorry sorry I sent you
a screenshot I think
oh my God no I said I did not send you
the screen I sent you so many things and
I did not send it
wow
wow I'm kidding I'm kidding of course
okay uh so I used to play this game so I
have this problem where there's a lot of
games that I played during quarantine so
when sometimes people ask me to play a
game I'm like I can't I
played it so much
so would you say it was was all these
hours to 800 whatever hours are these uh
off sleep outside of niji Sanji these
are just me having nothing okay I have
do you play games outside of streaming
not really no no time me neither no
motivation no motivation either me
neither
I just recently shared a screenshot with
my community where I haven't been very
um streaming a lot in the last two weeks
and that's because I have 180 hours in a
game called Crusader Kings 2 in the last
two weeks so I've had
It's a grand strategy game so you have
to like you have your Empire you have
your cultures and you like take over
other I thought it was one of those
shitty phone games no no no no no no no
no no no no no it's actually like a
grand strategy game but if you think
about oh my God what
isn't like AOE it looks like AOE kind of
similar no I'd say it's closer to
civilization than Egypt Empire
but basically like you have your family
tree as well so it's also like a family
simulator where you uh so at some point
right when you become really strong your
family can be let's say beautiful or
genius so at some point you can marry
your son to I don't know somebody for an
alliance or you can marry your son to
his cousin because she's also beautiful
and genius and then their babies will be
beautiful genius
wait I think I'm interested because I
love like actual medieval history oh my
God okay I'm gonna link you if you look
up Nina Crusader Kings I did a challenge
where I went from Iceland to India
um because I played this like there's
this special uh there's a special
ability for Vikings where you can do a
varangian conquest which means you leave
your lands behind and you conquer new
lands
um oh yeah you can take a look at it but
if you want any help if you want to feel
like real life history references or is
it completely made up okay so
it's real which is why I
tried to play away from all like major
religions all major areas you know
wait can you do the two
she was actually there's there's the car
links there's the Holy Roman Empire
usually in uh near Germany there's a
really crazy start because you have gold
mines around there I think it's in hold
on it's like uh
[Music]
thing like that
yeah there's like a county there where
you can have crazy like Maps there's if
you have if you settle in cold or
coloring you can build like the
cathedral there yeah this is what a map
looks like hold on speaking of code I've
been to kill and I love it and I have a
friend I know you're gonna love I have a
friend she lives in Austria and every
time I've told her she's like Nina
Austria is
but better you have to come
she's like everything you love about
cook you'll love it in Austria
interesting wait so wait oh wait oh my
god look how can we only do this in one
hour I know I know it's okay so yeah
I've been since we're neighbor Neighbors
Foster and Germany I've been to Germany
many times but I've never actually been
to Chrome early okay what do you like
next time all right well first of all
it's really easy everybody's super sweet
everybody has I speak French for example
so it's easy for me to go to France uh
hot lady I said sorry I have to buy food
for my cat
[Laughter]
oh let's go what I loved about Germany
yeah I speak French and Russian
fluently but I'm no I'm gonna talk to
you later because you gotta tell me
about learning languages
we only got an hour how are we gonna do
this and I have like a question possible
we're gonna have to do this again no
worries
okay let's let's talk how about this
let's talk very quickly so we can talk
about more things all right yes yes what
I love about shooting gun talk what I
love about Germany is that uh I can get
around even though I only speak English
and French it's fine uh I love the food
I love the people I think it's such a
beautiful walkable City in there's when
I went it was like four Christmas
markets within walking distance
I love that I love that I went in
December yeah
Germany Austria like we have like
Christmas markets all over in December
oh that makes me so happy oh my goodness
okay this game
please if you need any help or advice or
anything it could be a little
intimidating to get into it I will help
you I will guide you this is such the
amount of role playing that can happen
so for example
I attacked another like you know Empire
I took over their castle and when I did
that I kidnapped you know when you take
over a castle you take um hostages I
hostage a a little boy I was like all
right and he's the son of the count so
I'm like all right I took him in I
raised him in my own culture and then
when he was older I made him go and
attack I made him Dakota war against
this father
some of the events I had an event where
it's like you find out that like your
children are doing stuff or like you
have oh my goodness there's there's a
lot of stuff in that game that you can
do I think oh my God oh my God
I love that you're creating history
you're creating drama history I love it
but there's there's also it's basically
like a lot of real religions a lot of
real stuff uh cool I had to you know do
a little disclaimer like hey if you know
if I am Christian and I have the and I
become accountable sorry that's you know
that's just that's just my gameplay
cannibalism is a great perk okay
definitely you know the tutors is like
my favorite thing ever and Berlin is my
Oshi uh my history
why
I eat everything up that has to do with
like European history like because the
tutors have so much connections also
outside of you know they they go to
France and Germany Spain everywhere so I
love hearing about ocean and watching
why don't you have a necklace that has a
k on it huh
where's your choker with the k
need one for anybody who doesn't know on
boy Lynn was very very famous for having
a necklace was it a beer and a I forget
it was either oh there we go so then
[Laughter]
okay why do you love the tutors so much
what the heck
I don't know okay okay this is probably
the okay I'm ready I'm pretty cute for
this but I got into it by the show the
tutors okay okay I don't blame you I see
it on my Tick Tock feed sometimes and
I'm like um
hmm yeah and while I was watching that
like every time during the episodes I
would go on not to Wikipedia and like
read more about everything because I
needed to know the background of these
people and all that and then you go and
dig dig deeper deeper deeper and then I
started watching all these like related
movies and shows everything the whole
like family line also like 100 or like
200 views before and after everything
I'm so like I love it also I feel the
actress really makes her come alive it's
the same it's the Marjorie Tyrell right
yes
what is her name
um does anybody know the uh Natalie
Dormer there we go yes she's hot she's
so hot and her acting oh my goodness
okay you don't even understand like I
love her so much she also played in The
Hunger Games where she was also really
hot like she's just always hot that's
her constant state being hot and she was
Marjorie Tyrell in the game of the
throne
yes you don't even understand how happy
I was when I saw her in there but then
these yeah
spoiler alert killed her off so early
I'm like
away from me I saw a meme that says
Natalie Dormer Smiles like she knows a
secret like she kind of yeah right she's
always kind of like hmm she does but
what does she know about us
yeah you can start in England too the
only thing is when you start in England
there's two starts there's like eight 67
which if you start in England it's going
to be a lot of Viking conquests and a
lot of hard times but if you start at
1066 it's a different start because then
it's you know castles all that stuff
it's a little different oh my god oh
look at your flushing what I'm talking
about history I love it
please I want more if you looked at this
game and you need any help or anything
okay no before that I need help with
slay the spider okay
at all on any character like I mean how
many streams have I done maybe like I've
finished uh I finished every character
right okay when you get to slay the
spire and I've also tried like different
techniques different Builds on several
characters it's like a lot of fun
um and I would I would just say that the
I only had one try until now to slay the
Spire oh and that one only went bad
because the build the the cards I got do
you remember your build at all like what
character you were and what cards you
had or not really
uh what what was I does someone remember
what I was going for for that one brand
and do you have a favorite
uh your favorite character
oh it's been a while but I think I like
the one there's a little guy oh yeah I
love her
I love the block build yeah yeah and I
just I I like them all like they all
have a charm a fun mechanic oh yeah
somebody's saying you had a poison build
with too many Shives yes that was the
problem
I feel yeah slay the Spire it's one of
those games where
it's really really fun and it's easy to
get into but you do need to the easiest
way to get better at slay the Spire is
to
I'm you basically have to memorize what
the enemy does so for example when you
start your deck you I know you have to
build for the final boss but something a
lot of beginner players don't do is they
don't look at their first boss so for
example if you're playing let's say
Ironclad you look at your first boss who
is it okay how do you deal with that
first boss
that's always kind of how you should be
building your deck it's always like you
have to beat the next boss and you also
have to start preparing your deck for
the final boss yeah always try to have
like most most of the time having a
small deck is always better and uh also
remembering so for example second act
has some of the hardest fights in the
game yeah so you should try to be
avoiding a lot of fights in second act
because they're really really hard
unless you're but it's stuff that yeah
sorry I love this game so much
no but like was it it was wasn't there
enough
en member who likes latest buyer Millie
I told her about the game she's obsessed
yeah so I I feel like I talked about
this before but like there is a um like
multiplayer it's like a spider
oh my God we we need to get into that
would be so much fun and play it
together oh my God yes but yeah if you
ever like want any advice even offstream
I feel like a lot of slate Aspire what's
gonna make you better is just knowing
what the enemy does so a lot of enemies
have a really predictable pattern for
example if you know in act two there's
the little thieves right you know that
they attack you three times and then
they're gonna try to run away oh yeah
yeah stuff like that uh there's some
enemies where it's like the hand for
example the little boss you know it's
like a book with a hand coming outside
he'll that he'll do like one big attack
and then you'll buff himself and then
you'll do like three small attacks so
you kind of have to yeah oh yeah sorry I
love this game so much good thing is
like when I was streaming that you know
the viewers they tell me about it and
you know it helps and I've been getting
to know it more and more I would say
that I just got really effed by the
cards that was dealt and I was just so
committed to it because I wanted to slay
the Spy
I think also um when people give you
advice they're giving you advice based
on their knowledge but it's really
important that you understand why you're
building that card so something I think
that's going to help you in card games
is if you actually take the time to ask
your audience okay you want me to add
this card why or you want me to do this
bill why because if you you kind of have
to understand how it works too
I think I've been doing that it's just
uh you know I was still kind of a noob
but it was I just came out of like
finishing every character once like
doing a full full run with every
character once yeah so yeah I think I'll
get it eventually if I go back into it I
should play Slayer the Spire again you
should oh my God I'll be watching and
again don't I feel like it's so
intimidating right to be a beginner at
something in front of a large audience
of people yeah it could be so much info
and you know like I I read the cards on
stream but I don't know do you have this
like concentration problem sometimes on
stream and you bring something it just
doesn't do your brain of course yeah and
then somebody comes in you're like hi I
missed you how have you been and then
you know of course yeah
it's very different I think you're doing
amazing and yeah I have good news and
bad news oh
I really want to go for the question
round it's funny I have a whole document
that I sent yada
questions but we had
people ask so many questions that I
really really want to go through some of
them
um and again the reason this is only an
hour is because I feel like it should be
bite-sized I feel like these kind of
streams are best enjoyed you know when
I don't know just an hour and also also
it's okay I've been told to go to sleep
after this for the concert tomorrow so
yeah and I want to talk about your
concert a little longer yep sorry
everybody this is it this is worth but
you know what now they're gonna want
more
and then we can tell them that um
in one minute and we can quickly tell
them uh uh we're gonna have maybe
another club coming up soon what okay
yeah question this one is from memer and
Globe question for the both of you what
makes you push yourself to be a great
content creator is there an end goal or
just a Target or is it something more
arbitrary
would you like to start with that sure
uh what pushes me to be a great Creator
is to create memorable moments at some
point I find myself thinking back to
certain streams and just going wow that
was such a fun streamer that was such a
fun event uh there's so much
pain and suffering and problems
everywhere and for me to just Escape all
of that with my community to have fun
moments to have like for example I
played this game called kenshi it's such
an ugly little game I love it and there
was free it's just so funny there's so
much stuff happening and I just I love
having those moments that
even though there's a lot of them they
all feel very Unforgettable oh
my turn yeah
so it for me it's like uh I think the
reason why I put so much effort into
what I do into my content and so on is
because it's a once in a lifetime chance
that was yeah to me yeah I feel that way
yeah I've been like a content creator
for my whole life not my whole life but
like many many years like at least 10
years uh actually more but yeah roughly
and it never really like I felt like I
never really got back what I wanted from
it like and but now it's like as much as
um or roughly the amount that I put into
it the effort that I put into it I will
be giving back with results
um I mean sometimes there's times where
I feel like hmm maybe I I should get
back a bit more from this uh it's not
going as smooth like not everything is
like happy and perfectly going like
rainbows everybody is allowed to have
hardships of course yeah but in general
I feel like I've I've I have this once
in a lifetime chance opportunity I need
to make the most of it because yeah it's
just my last chance it feels like my
last chance you know you know it's funny
when you say that because a while ago I
kind of had this I had a really hard
time streaming last year with a few
things that happened but at one point I
kind of realized like oh my goodness if
I told me five years ago that I was
gonna have you know over a thousand
viewers watching me play Crusader Kings
or
um kenshi or anything like that I would
be streaming 15 hours a day and yeah you
know I'm a little bit older now I need
to you know take care of my health
things like that but yeah it's just it's
amazing it's the best and knowing that
we get back what we get like I think
that's so hard when you're a content
creator because
I feel so many people work so hard and
it's just how can I not work hard when I
get so much love back
and I get so much support and you know
for me for example I just started
singing and the I've been doing
karaoke's and people are so excited to
hear me sing even though I'm such a
beginner
it's an amazing feeling and I yeah give
so much motivation I really think I told
the story kind of before but like one
example is in the past uh I I performed
in like on on the stage and there was
like
one one person in the audience one wow
like I'm not like under exaggerating
like the opposite of exaggerating but
one and and I still had to like
perform you know it was so heartbreaking
and soul-wrenching and this like
continued for many many years in many
ways like also in in other ways like you
know videos Etc but yeah now finally I
have so many people who come to see me
and it just changed everything finally
my Outlook and you know for that one
person that's why I always feel like no
matter what I do I have to focus on
doing the best I can like for example
maybe I could I could work on things
behind the scenes right let's say I have
a Content idea it didn't work well maybe
I could have prepared more maybe I could
have been on time maybe I could have
those things don't matter once the
stream starts and for you once you're
performing and there's one person in the
audience give them an unforgettable show
they came out they were there I feel so
many people worry about bringing in new
fans and you know growing bigger it's
always like we gotta get more fans we
gotta get bigger you know your best fan
is the fan of your already have yeah
what about giving them the best
oh sorry I agree I walk in something
inside of me
no I agree I also try to like you know
he always want more new people to come
in but at the same time you should
always try to give your current viewers
the best time they could have and put
much effort as you can into your streams
I want to be careful with how I say this
because I don't want people to
misunderstand
if new people find me that's great but I
am worried and I am focused on the
people who are here and the people who
showed up and the people who love me
right yeah like if if there's 40 spots
in the audience and 25 people are there
I'm not worrying about the 15 spots not
filled I'm worried about giving those 25
people a reason to come back I'm missing
yes I ended up going on a tangent oh my
goodness okay this one is from mental
Jedi we know Nina loves wine and Cara
doesn't drink what's your favorite
non-alcoholic drink when you're with
people who drink like me
what was I drinking when we met oh I
think just Cola I think yeah
probably
like not much interesting stuff you
don't like the menu off it or anything
like that
you know like iced tea or anything like
that I love iced tea very much but the
thing is in Japan when I order iced tea
all a lot of the time what they bring
out is just iced tea yeah
[Laughter]
yeah yeah
my name is praying like the normal
straight black tea but iced and that's
just I want something sweet baby you
know when I asked for a peanut butter
sandwich they brought me a peanut butter
sandwich I don't know how to you're so
cute
okay so everybody's saying orange soda
is that something you really love
that is like the
um
this is a whole situation you know Cali
from my gen she thinks she knows me when
she apparently doesn't because she was
boasting a long time ago she was
boasting about how she knew my favorite
drink was orange soda and I was like
girl I don't drink orange soda ever
maybe I drank it once when I was with
you but I don't that's not my drink oh
my God this is like a mom you know you
say one time to your mom that you love I
don't know uh the Batman and then your
mom's like I got you the Batman because
you love the Batman you're like yeah
when I was five
so kind of like that yeah do you have
any soda you like for example I like Dr
Pepper
oh I love talking it's so good it's kind
of medicinal tasting
yes but Dr Pepper is just not that
common usually where I'm around so it's
a bit hard to find do you like the chili
soda like a lot of sodas I I uh my it's
just not my first choice wouldn't be
Fanta okay yeah oh you guys well you
guys have Orangina too in
Europe that one's really good I like
that I do like mocktails by the way
right when they have mocktails I do
always order a fun mocktail any favorite
flavors raspberry lychee mojito
I think often uh go for something like
either berryish or Citrus ish oh my God
good choice good choice okay two more
questions quickly quickly this one is
from jar mod question from Kiara when
will employees get a raise
next question please okay next question
uh this one is from nagu 838 what do you
eat for breakfast I would be happy to
hear your breakfast recommendations
oh
um when I'm in Austria
um I have this breakfast routine once I
realized that the supermarket sells of
like finished flat um Austrian style
pancakes you know they're really thin
they're kind of like a crepe but a
little bit thicker than the crab so I
buy those because I'm too lazy to cook
in the morning so and then I slap like
some chocolate cream on it and then
strawberries oh fresh cut strawberries
yes oh that sounds amazing that sounds
so good every day every day I love that
I love having the same breakfast what do
you eat for breakfast usually a coffee
I'm really bad but I love Greek yogurt
with fruits or not that's always a
really easy one to eat it tastes sweet a
day oh chia seeds
oh that's very healthy damn girl we have
time for one more question and then tell
me about uh all your stuff happening
tomorrow so what's the one item of
clothing you can't live without from
restroom Flores
one item of clothing you can't live
without favorite item of clothing
I mean if you think logically it would
probably be uh like panties
right wearing it
but but but
[Music]
um
that's so difficult a very specific one
or a type I would say if it's a type
then I I I I it it's something called
man but I like the Rays oh really oh my
God you're so cute you are the cute
collection of Berets please please next
time I already told you next time we
meet we are going to karaoke until five
in the morning
so separate so early last time okay all
right we have to start wrapping it up
because she has a bedtime okay I'm sorry
everybody bedtime can you believe it
young lady I can't believe it you have
to be well rested poor yes Mommy sorry
Mommy why do you have to be well
arrested for baby sorry Mommy sorry
Mommy sorry sorry
yeah but let's talk more soon please
um what do you have to be well rested
for wink wink oh well yes well on this
weekend there's a big whole life
festival happening in Japan and uh it's
like at makuhani big big venue we have
Expo and a concert oh my God this year
I'm like way more involved than last
year last year I only had like one song
you know can I ask you what stages
you're gonna be on where can we find you
oh I'll be on day one like in the
concert and but also in Expo there's
some stuff to see there's like a program
uh called Hollow spy and then also
there's a they they made kfp real it's
like yeah you can get actual Fried
Chicken from kfp oh my God I can't wait
to see the photos of my design on it
yeah I'm excited and then on day I won't
be on day two but before day two days
like this we have this collaboration
concert with Deco Nina Deco 27. I saw
that called holo27 and I'll be there to
yes I'm so excited much to do this
weekend
I hope you have an amazing night again
sorry everybody yeah I can't wait to see
oh my God I thank you again for taking
the time to come and see me
I told you I told you how quickly an
hour passes didn't I yeah I know I know
I know you don't understand everybody we
barely covered anything we wanted to
talk about yeah so true but you know I
may have the bedtime in terms of
streaming but we can continue talking oh
yeah that's why that's why my next
stream is so late
we talked for 45 minutes before this and
I didn't even see the time go
that's also one of the reasons I love
doing these streams is because it kind
of gives me an excuse to stay up and
talk to the person
all right nice we gotta end any Last
Words My Darling before I end
um thank you to the ninja girls for like
you know welcoming me so we love creamy
and sweetly and treating me as one of
their own you know we love you you're my
baby from another cabbage
bubble
bye especially
we're ending you think about it
everybody thank you so much for watching
uh look forward to something happening
soon with us bye-bye bye
[Music]