[Music]
Mr. Orange and the idol Vtuber
interview interview
It's Takanashi Phoenix's character from Horror Men Gush It's
Orange
It's Orange
[Music]  I'm
late.
Excuse me.
There's a reason. I was busy. I
wonder what they were doing. I
wonder what the two of us were doing while we were standing there. I'm
so excited right now.  I
'm asking you to come to Ne's house
. Hey,
this is not okay. It's
Benetinchin. Yes,
Nechinchin is fine. It's
dangerous, it's dangerous. Yes, it's
m ahead. Well, that
's right. I had
Nekirari-chan take a look at the family.
What was it like? Are-chan was
so cute.  Well, everyone, it
's not that bugs are that bad,
but they are
really that big of a deal.When I
saw them up close for the first time in real life, I was a
bit put off
[laughter]  It's about as
long as the palm of my hand.It's
long.I wonder what it is called a flower flower.It's
crazy, but I took a photo.I
want to post it on Twitter after this,
so it's cool.It looks
like it's a geo-guesser today.Wait
for the popular one.  Wait, wait, yeah, I
gave the bug a name
[Music]
Hey bug, it's
going to die soon, so why not give it a name?
Well,
when I say soon, it's
like 3 months.  You
have a name, right?
In order to live a life with more meaning.
Well, I guess we should be able to give that hairy one a name. That
's right.
Mofurun Mofurun is cute.
Then I'll make it full already. When I saw the bath. That's
crazy.  I thought it was a cloud, but it
turned out to be a giant spider with really fluffy legs.And
when I opened the box, it smelled a bit bad.
But, well, that's just the way it is, those bugs. I
felt like they were coming out. It's so
funny. They really have that kind of hobby. I
thought my house was interesting. I was a little
hesitant, but I thought it was interesting.
[Music] The
humidity I felt was like that.  When I think about it, the
smell of insects
is somehow better than that of dogs.Oh yeah, it
smells like nature.It's a
correction, right
?
[Music]  The
insects
leave it like this and
don't try to meet the dog.What
happens if you put it on the floor?
It flies, yes, it flies, and it
flies somewhere.It
has wings and wings, and it flies.Even
in that small case at night, it will
bump into you a lot.Outside.  I
feel sorry for you.Or
rather, I'd rather have a bigger box.I
love those two bugs all year round, right?If you're an
insect-loving psychologist, then there's no box anymore.Let's
talk.Let me
be free.
While flying, the bugs don't
regret it, so they scatter them all
over the room.It's not a good idea to do that all over the room.While flying, they freak out.Well,
if you do that, you'll see.There's a room for the bugs, right?It's a
forest or something.I
guess it's nice, or something like a house.
In a hidden place in the forest, there are
trees and other trees that don't look very happy if you live in such a place.
Well, I guess that's
possible too.
Hurry up and play the game.
It's a free showdown today, but when I
look at those Japanese members, I feel like they're only looking at Japan. I
don't know.
Today I'm
going to take Neji overseas on a
world trip,
but the
screen is only in English, so it's
already possible because it's Pore's account,
but
please leave it to me.
[Music]
Honestly, where in America will it be?
So America is serious, I
don't understand, I
really don't understand, I really don't understand It's
a little bit like this When I'm in America or somewhere like that, I always have that
mouse in my house.It's
okay, but if you're curious about something, just let me know.First
of all, where are you going?  Hey,
more
. It's where there are signs and stuff. First of all, you
can see it here, but that's all.
Well, this is the name of a street. It's a
scalpel injection, I know. It's Massachusetts embroidery, but that's it.  It does
n't necessarily have to be in Masteel.
I see.
[Music] It's pretty
wide, the road is a little bit.
Let's walk.
What kind of place is it? Yeah, it
doesn't feel like it's flourishing, right?
It's rural, rural.  It's not a big deal, but it's nice to see a
dog on a swing in the house.There
aren't any shops.This is a
residential area.A
lot of Americans have come here, but most of the American fans
have cars.  If you do
n't live in a city, it's that thing.And you
park your car on the road, right?You don't park it at your house.America is so
big, it's so
big, that's why even if it's America's free finals, you'll
understand right away, Rain-chan.  But
I don't know. I made a mistake. Oh,
and this is
a school. Ah,
it's a pea clinic. I see.
The name of the store
is Domino's Pizza. The
name of that place is often used in Mizuno.
By the way, this is the phone number, but it's probably
Savenate, which
is the area code? Yeah, I'm sure
there are English viewers. Oh
, what, what, what is this store
? Looks like a goal. Red line card. They say it's somewhere in America.
Yeah, that's right, give me more hits.
But wait, I'm back around here.
[Music]
I see.
[Music] I've
never had tacos.
Taco Takahashi. It
's American soul food.
Heh.  There
are a lot of sports shops and sports shops.
[Music] It's
become a mountain. It's a
mountain.
If you're an American, you probably already know that.
Eh,
hint, hint, it's
not just American food. I know that.
Tacozo is not American food.  But I
feel like everyone is eating soulfully. It's
so
spacious.
Wait, this is the phone number. I can't get the phone number anymore. I
guess I'll just have to back off a little more.  It's
gone,
it's gone
It's a photo that was taken at a different time, so it's okay.
Wait, where is it? It's
blurry and blurry, but I can see it a little. It's a shame. It's
okay to have sex with me.
[Music]
Wait and find out. Wait,
America. That's it. Looks
like Montena, but
Montena.
The question is, where is the antenna? This is the first time I heard about it, but I wonder
how close it is. It's a
big, wide, wide camera.
OK, I'll take a walk around here.
This is also important here. It
says 15910, so I have to remember it
as the name of a road.
It's Surface. That area code is the same.
So I've already got a rough idea of ​​what's going on there,
but I do
n't understand anything.
But Mt.  It's along the side of the mountain.
It's close to the mountain. I wonder if
Yamato is
home.
JS I don't know what this is, but it seems
like a sport. It's not skiing.
Hey, it's true, it's
snowing.  It's
pretty far north, in the north of America
. Yeah, the weather is really bad. OK, what?
[Music]
[Laughter] It
's a shop. Somewhere, the name of this place has changed. Wait, it's really becoming a big city.
Back  Really, let's go to the city a little more and
check it out.
Wow, the
gas station looks nice. I
haven't written anything about this area. Hmm, I haven't written anything about it.
Hmm. The one
on the left is
[Music]
Well, I already know that it's popular, so give me a
little more
detailed address
OK, it's a
little blurry, but I
guess it's okay.I don't know, but, but, it's perfect.It's a
batch battery.It's
a bit like the
name of a place.Wild
vegetables
[Music]
Look, even if you don't know anything about it, you can still get there if you look for it.
But I walked quite a bit, so yeah, I think it's a bit
far, but let's just stay around here.
OK,
that's nice.
Wow, this is about 800 meters away. It's
really close.
Donpicha. Wow, you can go here. It
's square, isn't it? It's a city. Yeah,
that's right, America. That's how it's mainly made
.
OK, let me show you how to do it a little earlier.
[Music]
Good luck! It's a little more
like that. It
looks like a forest.  I've come to this place
[Music]
There's nothing, so I
have to look for something. I'm
aiming for something big. Oh Cyfresh, what does that
mean?  That
's the name of the road. This is the store. Let's go to the store.
ok. Let's aim for the big one. Okay, that's terrible. First of all, I do
n't understand this.
[Laughter]
[Music] Looks
good. Hmm.
[Music]
Zoom in.  That would be
helpful, but I haven't written anything.
[Music]
Please zoom in a little bit.
[Music] Eh, it's better not to do it now. [Music] There
's a little bit of that. If you said the price, you would have cropped it out. Ah, that's
right.  Is
n't he there? It's okay, I protected you, I
protected you, I'll protect you After the
auto shop
[Music] I
look at that sign in the back
Yeah, I think I should look at it, but it looks like I've changed my phone number.
Should I look for the phone number? It's
written
there.
[Music]
Hey, America, it's really
big.
[Music]
I do
n't understand that, I don't
understand it too much. Can I
see it? If I can see it, it's here, here, here
. It's the seaside. This time, it's the
North Color Liner's surfer.  It's
like a phone number that's not used at all. It's
better, it's better. By the way, what does this
mean? Eh, well,
this is probably
someone's photo, but when I
translate it,
let's mute the microphone for a moment.
[Music]
I see.
That's the name of the store. I
don't know why they chose that name, but it's
slow. Maybe it's a
gas station.
[Music]
Even when I get closer, it's still fur. That's all.
Hmm.Noooo
[Music] The
car is
in there, isn't it? I wonder if it's Doro. I'm
still working on it.
[Music] Just
a little bit. You
should look at the details.
Dangerous spanion
Espanol Spanishon can talk. Ah,
uh, that's it, Kaito-kun, go home.  Give it to me,
oh, be kind. Wow, if you were an
American, I wouldn't be able to find a store or something.
Also, the type of money, the
type of fire.  It
depends on the location, so
there are some stores that don't have a store, and I can
understand it quite well even if it's a tree,
but I don't know what it is, but I don't know what
kind it was yesterday.Oh yeah,
what,
Hint Please, Hint Pudding, it's okay, there's
one here and there that's not rock.  You
know, the authentic Mac is different from the American Mac.The
taste is so
healthy.I
guess it was the Japanese healthy one.I don't think it can be called healthy, but it doesn't seem to
be as filling.  I
think they put a lot of sugar in there, but there
are a lot of traffic lights. There are so many traffic lights. I'm from here.
[Music] It
might be true, but it seems like there's more to it than that. It's
Karpasage size. That's
crazy. Are hamburgers big in America?
If you order a small-sized drink, you'll
get something like this.The
small size in America is the large size in Japan.Hmm, that's
right, it's a good deal.That's what I
think.  That's
helpful. It's true that there is a KFC, so it's not KFP. Please change the name of the store that is not written there. Just to confirm. I wonder why. I want you to write it down. This is difficult. This is a big drug store.
[Music]
This is a
battery
store.Mr. I
think it's the one from earlier.Hmm, then let's
go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.Teleport
Oh, wait, but there's a lot I want to do.
Hmm, no, I don't understand this, really. It
was just like a sign with that speed.
That's the way it is. But
even if it's written here, I wonder how far it is. Well, I don't
think it's that far, but
then I
can't see the surf. Ah,
no.  Or
so, but I haven't seen the ocean, so it's
true. It's
in the city, so I think it's nice to be down here. Maybe
it's not
right, but I think it's close enough
.
I wonder what everyone is doing.What do you think of this number? Oh yeah, it's probably erased somewhere on the road, but 87 is climbing.There is 87.When I looked at it from a distance, I think it was 70.That's true,
too.
Where did you go
earlier?
Okay, it's a
long way,
isn't it? It's 70 years long. It looks like a crane over here.
In Japan, I think of it as being on the seaside.
That's right, it's
like they're lifting something out of the ocean. That's
amazing.
This one is really facing the ocean. There's
a little bit more written like this. This
is this. This is this. This is that factory.
[Music]  ]
This is a
cute in-store politician's advertisement Ah, that's right. Apparently they
're stabbing it on the roadside. They're
not pasting it on the wall. After all, it's 87 again.
If it's true,
that hole
is basically 87.
[Music]
This one is OK, so it's
perfect. I don't think it's necessary to make it clear,
but it's a bit of a winter scene.
There are 41. It's
41 along 70 Street, so I think I'll do it
around here for a little while. Let's
go, like this.  When I
look at it, it looks far away, no, it's
real, it's true, it's actually below the Fireout version, oh
yeah, it's true.
Someone wrote something in the chat. I'd
like to try bangs.
Somehow, I
went to Enoshima, and on this beach with bangs, there
was a sign that said, ``It's in Enoshima.''
[Laughs] You
can think of this as being worth it.
Hihiro:
Yeah, but maybe it's not a school. Just go around and
look.
Victory is building Pringus. I wonder what this is. This building is right now
in a large area of ​​mud, so I looked at it properly.
That's better.Isn't there
something written on it?You
can really tell me.Isn't there a
building name for this and that?Hmm, it's
not really listed.Look
here and there.OneWay
DonotenterThat
doesn't help.I'm
bored.38
yenThis
is it.  I don't need this, I don't need this
[Music] I
don't see it very often Ah,
Quick High School, I see.
This is the first time I've heard of you clicking somewhere. Hey, but it seems like a
peaceful place. It's
calming.  The
tree is beautiful. The
baby fainted and died. The
unconsciousness has changed. Wait,
414. I got the phone number, so I'll get it soon.
414. I
don't know, but I'll look for it.
This will help. I'm
infected with a virus. The
ocean is not the ocean, but it's serious.  There are
so many ponds, it's such a
nice
place
[Music]
Wow, it's so
loud
Okay, oh, but that's the high school
from earlier. Yes, Scott Card.  It's
so good, it's so American.
Even if you go alone, you can do some sightseeing on your own.
Yeah, it's really good. You won't get lost.
[Music]
You know,
that Morita
has S and MVBA written on it. That's right,
that's it.
Adolescence is something I want to see to study [Laughs] It's nice when I'm going abroad - it's kind. Hey, it's not a kindergarten. It's not a kindergarten. It's a park. [Music] A signboard, an invasion.  I
wonder if it's a place called ``Ray''.It has the name of a town, but it doesn't have the atmosphere of being on the coast.Hmm, tennis is on the right, and the American Denny's in Japan and Tennis isn't tasty at all. [Laughs] That's right, it's delicious.  Denny's is
delicious even when it's delivered to your home.
That's pretty good.
There's a store
in America, too. I've heard that the ones in America are pretty bad.
Heh,
but 7-Eleven in America is
[ __ ]
. [Laughs]
It's poop. I want to go to Starbucks. There are quite a few
hotels here, so I haven't written down a few photos. I
wonder if this is
n't a phone.
Hunting, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
look here. I
don't see any hmms, but I haven't written anything.
Hey,
[Music] I can't
use 88. I ca
n't use it. I'm
making that free call.
Wait, that number is 200, isn't it
713?
Wait, wait, I wrote Hüssen on a
sticky note
I know, I know, it's
here OK
stop I've
heard it before
[Music] I
don't know, it's like America It's
shaped like that It's pretty
similar It's almost the same
Texas is amazing
Unique  I went to this place that looks so big
. It's true. I've just discovered this place, but it
has an interesting shape.
Texas. I've heard of Texas before.
Houston
is on the ocean.  It
says good, right? If you're a nice person,
this is it. It's
right by the sea. I
need some hints, but I've already
figured it out. I wonder if I
can't find a park or something. It looks like a park earlier,
but it's
small, so I guess it's a bit impossible. If that's all there is,
then it's already
[Music]
People  I don't think they're walking around, or
rather, I wonder if they're being photographed that much.They're all in cars, after all.There
's a lot of phone numbers that I don't think will be deleted
[Music]  Let's make
some more Checker PVs. What's
Texas? Have you ever heard of it?
Texas,
oh well, let's
penetrate
French
[Music] Osmosis City,
Jachintou, Jachintoh,
wow,
this is good, isn't
it? That's all I understand.  Wow, that's
amazing. Seriously, Mango is
good. By the way, it's the 5th and last in America. Let's
go squid.
[Music] Is it
completely
okay? There's a cover. It seems difficult here.  You ca
n't go there
unless there's a road.It
's like a campsite.Let's find a big road.It's
nice.Each house is big.It looks
a little peaceful.Do your best.It's a
world I've seen in Icarly.I
see.That's true.  It
seems like it often appears in dramas like those American shows,
comedies and dramas.This is the
big road.I
went back and said I'd leave it to you once, but
this is a school bus.  It
's Kenchi, May is a place, right?
Money is definitely a place.
MA was
supposed to leave it to you. Let's
go here,
mamams. It
's a novel. Okay, I'll leave it to you from here. Okay,
can you find that? The name of this place
is Canyon Findy.
in
K, maybe K?
[Music]
No, it's like a different place, Kin-chan. [Music] No, I don't think so. If it's a
small town, I'll zoom in a little more.  You
might not be able to see it if you don't do that, but
then it's a little hard to see, so I
think this is different. Hmm, I think you can look around the blue one more time and then look
around you a little more. Let's look for a
hint. Hmm, I
like the big mom on the road.
Or something.  Yes, it
's quiet. Yes, it's quiet. Do you
have a phone number? I don't need it
anymore. I've already figured it out.
Even with a phone number, I only know about interviews.
Ah, it's all massachu embroidery right here
[Music]
Well, maybe I
should force myself to look for Venus. On the map, yeah, there
's a pop-up somewhere. I'll help you find Venus.
Hmm,
help me, this is correct.  Right OK OK
[Music]
[Music] It's
true,
Berlin. I sometimes repeat my name. Hey,
Yo, but it doesn't feel like this in the middle of the city,
right?
It's definitely greenish.
I know it. [Music] It's green, I guess. [Music] It's H. It's a reply. It's not a look, it's a reply. It
's a reply, but I haven't seen any negatives. It's
okay to be a reply.  It's from H,
but I can't find it.
I know it's
Harvard University,
but it might not be this one.
Maybe they're just in the same place. The
same name doesn't mean it's there, but it
seems like it's there.
Harvard University.
Which
elementary school is Harvard Elementary School? Harvard Elementary School.  I think I should join. You
're too old.
No, I'll skip a grade and go back soon. Shun-senpai
went there, right? You're a second-class
graduate. You
graduated from elementary school, so the university will be different.
Well, Shion-chan, I'll give you the university.
Ah, what's the best place? It
wasn't in the middle of town, so I guess it's somewhere around here.
OK
A
OK, where is it? Ah, you
were playing a really naughty game, weren't you?
That's how I tried it.
[Laughs]
There are so many other things you can do.
Back button Where is the back button?
[Music] It
was my first time playing such a naughty game. Why in my life did I want to
try it? It
was New Year's Day, so how was
it? Yes, it was naughty, so I played something so naughty.  It seems like
everyone was happy watching it.
[Music] Even
though it was night, there were a lot of people, and
everyone was in a naughty mood.
That's right. It
's in the middle of the city. I'm
not from Germany, but...  I
can speak German,
so I think I understand the basics pretty well, so let's go and check it out.
This looks like a parking lot.
Wow, Germany is quite
like a big city, but again, I'm looking for a phone number. Hmm, I
don't need it.  I wonder if there are any other
hints?
S. I feel like it's S, but I can't read it at all, but this looks like
Essen. S5 Essen is amazing. The
image quality is terrible, but it looks
like S. Hmm.  The
gas on the left is bad. Oh,
that
[music]
is bad. I
know, but
the location is close to Loaf.
By the way, it's the
place where the most Japanese people gather outside of Japan. Oh
yeah, I guess there's a reason why.  However,
since many Japanese people have lived here for quite some time, there are many restaurants
, Japanese restaurants, Japanese shops, and Japanese
hotel chains, so I
can understand the Japanese language.  I
wonder if there's a place where a lot of Japanese people gather.There's an area that seems like a mature place, but I think we'll be able to get along pretty well there.Hey,
don't look for it, let's do this.It's a white
birch tree.There's a
guy there.There's also a dog.It's
cute.It
's amazing.
Well, in Germany you can park your car on the road.
Well, if there was no parking, it
would be pretty normal [music]. There's
no big road. I'll still look for it. It's still peaceful
.  I
guess it's a park. It's a nice place. There are a lot of people. Yeah, I don't know what's going on. I want to draw some graffiti. [Music] There's a lot of graffiti overseas. I'm used to it, but I
came to the store.
Wait, wait, what's going on now?  Here,
over there, it's a
little too detailed. I
don't really understand, but sometimes I
write concert hall names on posters like this.
[Music]
Can't you see? The image quality is terrible here.
Another
map is better. I can't
read it. I wonder
who it is, so I'm writing the city on it. I'm
sorry. Ah, it's
amazing. It's artistic. It looks like it's actually
writing something here,
but the
image quality
has no choice but to improve.  But this is the main street,
right? Hey, I don't understand Coca-Cola. I
want something that I can clearly see.
[Music] I
can't see it. Oh, by the way, there
was something going on next to me when I was sleeping. I
want to go to that place in Europe.
There's a country, right? It's
Spain, right? I want to go to Pei. I'm going to go there after this. I'm going on a
trip around the world today. What
store is this?
[Music] It's
too difficult to even do it.
Ah, but I don't
understand. The
game is a bit over here.  It's small.
Hello.
Name of the place.
Name of the road. It's a one-person car. It's
cute.
There's one in Japan. Micro or Micro. It's
cute. I
want to ride
. I want to ride. You know, Germany. It's common in Germany.
Especially when it comes to
buildings. I do
n't want to get on it. I don't want to be exposed. I
went back here, right here, right here. Hmm, I didn't go home, so I
went back. The traffic
light is a little different again. You're fluent, licking.
What language?
What's going on
[Music] I
wonder
if I change it into a car, it's Berlin. It's
a bit of a wind-up window in Berlin. It
seems like it's around here,
but it doesn't mean it's really there, so I
'll drive a little carelessly. OK.
Take me
[Music] It's a
car.
This looks good. Bus stops here and there. Ah,
the signs. It's been
4 years.
[Music]
Looks like something has been cut here.
No, but I'm starting to understand.
[Music]
Spare version of Poop,
Bell Berlin.  I get it, it's
over there at Veronie, but I wonder
if it's really that weird. I want it on a signboard or something, not on a car.
[Music]
There's something posted there, advertising a bath.  It
's a public bath van, right in front of me, it's huge and it
's moving in an instant.
[Music]
Ah, but it looks like there's something here. Yeah, it's
really big. There
's a road. [Music] There's also a phone number, but this time...  I'm not going to look into it.
[Music] There
are a lot of cars. I
feel like it's
a bit different compared to America. It feels like a
town. I
thought there was a little less nature here.
Yes, there's nature too. Oh wait, I
think this is the name of a city. I've
never heard of it. I've
never heard of it. I don't
know. I don't know. Some
people say it's 100% Berlin. Seriously, it's
finally here.  I wonder if it's
inside Berlin.
Even if the city feels like Europe, and it's free
, don't think this is Europe.
There are better things out there. It's
really different, it's a little
different. I want to see it.
sGOOK
[Music]  That's
enough. It's already a drumstick. What is this? It's really busy. Is this Europe? I
guess I can guess it just by doing so. What's the
name of this forest? It has to be hard pack. I
can't get it, but
it's only the front and back.  So, I
couldn't go anywhere and was locked up. Well, on
Friday, I did
n't know anyone, so I asked them. They didn't
know.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Well then, I
came to see you. It
was in Frankfurt.
FrankfurtFrankfurt food
here
Apparently Frankfurt is the
name of a place.Eh, it's kind of
like that.It's
both a political name and the
name of a place.Hmm,
next time I'd like it to be in a more proper place.
Poi Poi Poi
Popi Ah I
know, I know,
as expected, it's really popular.Thank
God, it's a member of English English.As expected,
not everyone understands it.  The
boys in my class used to sing happily.It's
so hot here,
but it looks like a big match.Germany
has a lot of big towns, right?
Unlike Austria, there's only one
place.
Yeah, that's right.
[Music] You know,
what if we were Austria's free guest at Ospa?
The place is not fixed, it's
limited, so it's the same.
[Music] I'm
kidding. It
's a famous piano.
Classical music
artist Mozart was born
in Lenovo Computers and Reactions
[Music] I wonder if
this is a
tourist spot. It doesn't seem like a tourist spot, I don't think so, but it
seems like it's a pretty central part of the city. I wonder if it's by the seaside.  [
Music] I'm
making it. I
can't go here. It's so small. It's a
terrible
hat. It's a knitted hat. It looks
like this is written on the advertising page. There
's a bug. It's fluent.
Let's go that way, because we can't go there
[Music] It's
black, okay, hard mode
or
hard mode, right? There's
no hint, there's no hint - that's the only thing we have
[Music]
Something like this is the
name of a road overseas
[Music]
For
example, Japan's strengths are
completely different, and I think it's written in a different system,
but
for example, Hanopas is just a
street in Tokyo.  It
means something like that, but it does
n't necessarily mean it's Tokyo. It has a meaning. It's true. It
doesn't. Hint
[Music] Is it
too rough? It's not too rough. It's just
that my current analogy has landed. I was trying to get into it.  Runaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
know  I imagine
a hospital with the name of a town written on it
.
This place has
been erased. It has been erased.
Hard mode Hard mode Can I pass
through here?
Please
let me go. I can pass through there. I wonder if I can pass there. There are so
many people here.  Summer is
here [Music] It's a flower shop.
[Music] There's
a lot of bicycles parked up. It's
not going well in America, so
it's difficult for Germany, but for some reason it's that way. It's a bit like
Japan, isn't it? There are a
lot of buildings.  There are a
lot of cars, so
let's go with everyone, Berlin,
Berlin again.Eh, that's Berlin.A pharmacy uptake
means a pharmacy.But if it's a pharmacy in Berlin, it
's Berlin.I guess that's
it.
That's okay, okay
then, let's go. It's close. It's a stupid thing. It's
such a road.
Okay, then just keep going for a while and leave it to me.
[Music] You
know that? Yeah, that
German highway. Yeah,
that speed is
freedom.  It's
okay even if it's early. There's no limit. Hey, this is ah, that's helpful. It's helpful, but it seems like I went too far. Let's watch it again. Zoom2's Humberschbeck is the closest one. Ok, okay. I have to find it, Rube. Eh,
um,
the sea.  It's close to O, but it's 2000m from there. I wonder
if this is
possible. Leave it to me. 65 I'll see if I can
kill it.
65 It's quite far, but half of it.  It
might be a force, oh yeah,
what do you mean by refuting it? It
doesn't mean anything. It's like driving a car,
but it's still a road, so let's go and check it out. Eh, I
want a number. It's
a mud number.  It's not the 25 I want. I
didn't see it. It
's 2524. It's been
25 days since then.
There's a rainbow here, but it's
still along the road.
[Music] There's
already 5 things going on.  Looks like it's
over.
[Applause]
[Music]
OkOk
NEXTisSpain's
exciting, but Spain has no
choice but to do its best.
Go here, go here, go here, go
here, let's
Stain.
[Music] It
's natural now.
Hmm
LINE voice  Turn off OK. Looks
like it's hot. I'll
take a look. Which one is
it? It's cute. There's nothing natural about it. Is
there a tomato? Tomato or olive?
There's a nice tomato,
all the way,
all the way, I'm still going all the way.
[Music] It must have been
spawned in a place like this. I wonder if it's going
to be a too-suitable animal.
Just look at it, but it won't stop at this type of leaf.
It's on the ground, isn't it? On the ground. Huh.
Is this really a forest?
How far is it going?
I'm
not really serious about it, but there's something like that. I can't
read the sign. [Music] I can't read it.
Something must
have ended here.
What if it's an insect?
I guess this
means a good trip.
[Music] It's a
good trip. It's like I've completed one city. So I
guess I'll just have to do my best from here. [Laughs] No, I don't understand Spanish, but it's pretty much like that.  When you're in Europe, you hear
Spanish a lot, and it's quite similar to Italian, so I
guess
Sorry is OK, so it's probably something
like this, probably in a place like this, and I
already know what it means.There
's no main street.  That's right
[Applause] We've
lost the concept of the main street. And the
houses too.
But if we've come this far, we'd better go over here. We'd
better go straight.
Believe it. Let's go.
There's a building. It's coming, it's coming.
Come on,it
's a cow.
[Music]  ] Skirt
steak is
n't a noise, it seems
like it's a secret, but I just learned about it for the first time yesterday. I
've heard that skirt steak can be found anywhere, but
somehow the person at the restaurant...
When I say entwined, it's like skirt steak.That
's what I mean.It doesn't matter
what part of the restaurant you're in.If you
decide it's skirt steak, you can serve it as skirt steak.I've
heard that, but it could be a lie.It's a
scam, even my
boyfriend.
I told her, Wow, you can call it Calvin for anything.The
person at the recommended restaurant decided that this was our place, and it
was Calbi.
[Laughs] I wonder if it's
Main Street Boulevard
or this ranch.  Let's
move on. There was a building after all. Look, there we go. Go
forward until you find a sign.
[Applause]
Maybe it would have been better to go left or right over there,
but oh, there are
n't any houses around here.
There are cars.
Only cows.  No, I don't
know. [Music] I don't know. I've
been to Spain once, but I
wouldn't go there the first time. I probably went here once, but I don't know. It's
not in the city.
Where are you? I can't connect to Wi-Fi here. I
can't see the map.
There's also a horse.
This is a small horse.
[Music]
Oh, look to the left again. It's
taking a cute break. It's looking at me.
It's a signboard. I
don't know.
What do you mean?  I wonder what it means. I
don't think it means much, but it seems like
there's someone who knows where it is. Even if you're a genius, you're
not a cheat.
There's a basketball goal.  Sounds like
something interesting. What's the hint?
There's a town in a certain place where people don't speak Spanish, but it's
so far away that they seem to have
figured it out.
[Music]
Is this your brother here? You know,
your brother has
been coming here recently from around here in Austria.
From around here,
through Switzerland,
Ryoko, or rather...
[Music] I've been
walking this far. The
three months I've been walking have been amazing.  You
can walk in 3 months, but on the other hand, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right,
this is a pilgrimage standard, and it
's a work where you walk through a tunnel.
Apparently it was difficult.
[Music] I
was just saying what the name was.  But
[Music]
That's the only
place I've heard of it.
Actually, that's all I've
heard of it. It
seems to be somewhere nearby,
but I said something like it's probably
above that. I didn't say anything like, ``I wonder if it starts from the north,''
or if I see Calcyon.  It
starts with G.
[Music]
Hello, where are you?
[Music] They
don't seem to speak Spanish over there, which is weird. I
wonder what language it's in. It's
probably
not Portuguese, but something similar, so it's probably
Spanish.  I wonder if it's something mixed with Portuguese and
Galician, which seems to be the name of the region.Oh, it
looks like Court.It wasn't
written there.I looked, but it
was written there.It was written over there.  It's
not on the map, it's not,
but there are quite a few owners. Eh, I can't even find the region.
Galician
If it's a region, it's changed a lot.
[Music] It
's not difficult. I don't
understand it too much.
Just say yes. I've
given up. It's not that bad.
More  I want you to put it in a good place, in a place where it's easy to understand.This
time, it's better than the last one.Here, let's
go.Okay,
let's go.This time, the
trees are interesting.This
one is
a little different.I wonder if it'll
end.  It looks like
it's warm, isn't it? It's warm, isn't it? I wonder
what kind of field it is. I wonder what kind of field it is. Eh, I do
n't know. I'm
moving on. I wonder if it's
grapes.
[Music]
Really? The
futon looks like it's a little bigger. It's a
different shape.  I feel
like [Music] The letters came out of the words Pearl Spider.
I don't know.
Is this just the name of a building? I
don't understand it at all,
but there are some fancy letters.
That's nice
[Music] I
want a bicycle,
but walking is definitely
not enough.
Left or right,
right, left
,
left,
all the way,
Spain. It's on a
different level. They're
always plowing something.
Hmm, this is just speed.  This is it.
[Music]
Done. This
seems like the name of a place, but the shape of the sign
means that I can't understand it at all even if you say it like this.
[Music]
Española
No, seriously, it might be
worth it to guide you to Spain.By the way,
this is the place where I've been before:
Venice Valancia. I
think it's Manesya. Valencia. I
went here and there and
was playing alone in the sea around here.
Steam.  I
want to go again.
No, I don't know. I'm seriously going to Spain. I
'm going to Japan.
I don't know. It's too difficult.
Yes. Yes, it's a bus, but it seems like it's close. It's true.
Hmm, I don't know.
If it were here, it would be a little crazy. There
's a
possibility. There's a
possibility. If there's a possibility,
by the sea, by the
sea.
Besides, it doesn't look like a small town.
Christmas
tree
[music]
In front of the place, this is,
uh, this
garden.  It's like an
island
called Canary Islands. It
's an island, but it's not like this one. Is there another
island in Spain?
It's Tena
[Music]
Wait,
wait, wait,
this
is probably an island.
Santa, after all
, it's over there. I
wonder if this is the right place.
Where should we go?
Hmm, it's by the sea, so let's go somewhere somewhere. Around here,
around here.
No way.
Wow,
this is an amazing 5 km This
is surprisingly a popular place for vacations. I wonder
how big all the islands around here are. Should I
go home? Let's go to Japan. Japan felt great.
Now it feels amazing.
Well, as
expected, but if it's Japan.
I don't
know, please do that.
[Music] I
tried it too, but it
seems difficult and I always end up in Okinawa.
[Music]
Let's just say it out loud.  I'm
still
talking about this and that on LINE! Japan is here. There are quite a few mountains in every prefecture. The prefecture behind me is Akita Prefecture. Where is it?  Generally speaking, the
top is the bottom,
so I don't know yet.Even
if you ask me to give you a dome run, I
don't know what you don't like about it.Where
is Michimura?
Akita prefecture?Let's take a look.  I can
already feel the humidity It feels like an
experiment It's
stuffy But it looks cool
[Music]
Oh, it's a
doll sign. I
can't really understand it, but I can read road signs. I
have a driver's license.
Why are you so surprised? Do you
really have a paper?  But
since when
did you go on a drive date with me as soon as you graduated from Goldway High School? Ah, I'm
going to drive Nene.
When was the last time you drove?  It
was about 3 years ago,
no, I do
n't like it.It's not like I don't trust Route 105.I haven't driven
for about 3 years,
but if I suddenly start driving again, I don't
think I'll be able to do it or not.I
want to go to the driving school again,
but just in case.  Yes, there are
places like convenience stores,
but I wonder
if there are any Japanese people who can drive well even if they haven't gone out for a long time.I don't
think they have a car.
If you don't have an image, please let me know.
Everyone, I
want you to take me. I'd like to go for a drive in my car.
Normally,
Klee-
senpai is like that, and so are my seniors. I see that you're a senpai, and you're so excited. It seems so
weird. There are people who say that they can drive a Cicillon car.  I
have a lot of dreams of
Ryu's seniors, but I'm sure he can do it. Seriously, he's the one who
gets driven. He's not always the
one who rides in the back, so he
probably drives himself because he has free time.105
[Music] It's
confirmed that it's going to be on the line, so it's around here.
Yeah, let's
push the pit and see if it's in this room.
No, no, no,
next
[Music] That's
right. It's
not Tokyo, it's not Osaka, it
's not Nagoya.
[Music]  ]
Hey
, I don't understand.
[Music]
Kirara
Let's ask the people at the local house. Excuse me,
where is it?
Stop Asahikawa.
Hokkaido.
Asahikawa is probably.  It's
supposed to be in Hokkaido, it's called Asahikawa, right? Here, yeah, probably, probably. Amazing. [Music] I feel like Asahikawa is in Hokkaido,
seriously. If it's in Hokkaido, it's really cold. It doesn't move.
Wait, it felt cool, didn't it?
Toko
Toko Town I wonder if it
's there?
[Music]
[Laughter] I
want to interject a little more. It's
pronounced ``Otoko.'' It's
written in Roman letters at the bottom.
Talk,
talk, it's
really big. The
Japanese garden in Hokkaido is amazing.
[Music] Eh, I've
never
heard of it.
[Music]
The name of the area is a little more
general. Hmm.
Post [Music] I wonder
where I'll find it. It's probably very detailed.  I
think that's it. Is
there someone who said it looked like cheese everywhere in the post? It's the
house around where I saw it.
[Music]
Oh, what's that? 17.
[Music] It's
nice weather, it's nice weather. 16's, oh, it's
so detailed.
[Music]
21 tablets, 19, they
're coming.
[Music]
6th graders are
wide.
[Music] Where's
101213, 14?
Where's 15?
15 is 167  If it's 17, you'll
get a lot of points.
Let's identify it.
[Music]
Only 16 and 17 are missing.
5  It's
already locked.
Hey, 1616th Street.
[Music] If you
go down the road, it's
just 17 and 16.
[Music]
Hey,
uh
. [Music] Yeah, um, I don't know. 1617 Wasn't
it something?
Early respawn, I think 17. I do
n't remember.  There's a bus stop just now.
This guy is a genius. 17 I
want to find him. It's
like Kirara. There was a
killer
there.
[Music]  It doesn't matter how long you
want to go here
Ah, that's amazing Yes, that
's great This is totally suitable for collaboration
Game-chan, this
is a city, it
could be Tokyo It's a really
big city
[Music]
Wait a minute, I'll tell you when I'm done with the hints.
Yeah, I have to go, but maybe
along the highway.
[Music] If it's in the city, ah, I
think I'll
understand even if it's a tiara.
[Music] What's on
Bookstore Street? I've
never heard it before, but I've heard it before.  I feel like
there's a word that makes me think,
Tokyo, I guess. It's
not Osaka. I've
lived in Baking Soda, and I've
lived in Eisaku. I know
a lot more about it than I do. I
liked that
blue one.
Ah, that's nice. Who
came with the hot water? Shrimp to Fukushima.
Shrimp
Fukushima. Oh, and the fish. Was there a Fukushima nearby? I
wonder if there was one. I feel like there were two of them in
Fukushima. I don't know if it's Fukushima.
Wait, but it smells
like Osaka. I think it's Kanto.
[Music] I've
heard something before. Let's go a little further.
Let's go.
[Music]
Please tell me something. It's
small. The letters are small. It looks like
there's a station. It looks like it's in front of the station. Is that
wrong?  Hey
[Music] I'm serious
about 7-Eleven's Doria Ski
After all, it's Fukushima somewhere I
wonder if Kushima is a warlord
[Music]  It's
not the Loop Line. It's
not the Loop Line. It's not Osaka. I searched and searched.
Loop Line. There was an
expressway
there, so maybe Fukushima was around here. What if Fukushima was around here? I wonder if
Osaka city is that close.
Ah, it's definitely Japan.
Wrench's chat  Everyone here is very knowledgeable. That's
right. As
expected, everyone here will help. Osaka also has Fukushima, after all.
[Music] That's
great. I want to go to Osaka. Let's go!
Let's go!
Block  I
want to defeat it. It's
gone too far.
I don't know. I can't
see it either. But I think I saw something like that when I went to fish. I want the train to Fukushima. It's
looking at me so much. It's
so over here.
Good posture.
Okay, where should we go?
Where should we go?
This is juice.
Fukushima 7-chome. It
's cool and detailed. It must be Osaka. I wonder
if it's in Osaka city, right on the left on the way home.
Nae, it's so fishy. I want to
go every time
. I don't know where it is. I don't know where
Osaka is. It's
cute.
It's near Osaka station. It's so Osaka. So where is Osaka station?
Fish and vegetables
[Music]
Umeda, oh
Umeda,
Umeda? I don't know about that Shinkansen in Ueda.
Answer
: It's along the road, right? Is it around here?
Yes, that's good. I'll go there.
Don, you
helped me a lot, but
you know, the
best, the best. There's still
more. This is the countryside of Koi Ah 4. Even with this, it's all too easy. I've
been looking for that neglected person here before. I've
looked for it before.  I wonder
if I have to give up on dollars like this for a while
Yes, why is it like this? It's like
when we were in the city. It's
scary and scary. I'm alone with people.
Oranges, here there are oranges. I'll grow oranges
here.  I don't
think I'll have any fans. They won't come to the concert. It'll be held in the mountains. [Music] They couldn't let me into the venue, so maybe it's a spin. I guess Pin doesn't have this kind of feeling. It's already very
humid
[Music]  [Music] It's
humid. It's
really deep in the mountains. There are
no signs.
Well, well,
well, well, well, well, is there anyone else here? You
must be a genius. Locals number 3. [Music] I'll just have to go back and zoom. Huh?  there were
What do you read? Nishitani The bottom is Nishitani, Kumangu Tahara. Ehime is Ehime. [Music] It's not great. It's easy to understand just from that. It's Ehime, a little more Ehime. I still don't know how to grow mandarin oranges. It's too early, it's too early, why? It's
scary, scary,
local.  Is it easy to identify Japanese? It
's a scary world. Is it Ehime? What prefecture is Ehime?
Ehime Prefecture  It's
this way, right? But I listen to it often. I listen to it often. Ehime [Music] Aichi Aichi Prefecture Aichi Prefecture I don't think it's Ehime. That's wrong. [Music] Over here. What is
Shikoku, Shikoku?  It
's Shikoku. I've
come to Shikoku.
[Music]
Ehime, let's look for a little bit.
Coach
Okayama
Himeji
Ehime.
Only the princess is in Roman letters. I
see, so I look for a little more detail.
After all, I'm particular about it. Let's get down to it.
Ruu Yamashita, I really like Amelia-chan here. Yes, you're right. There's
too much nature.
[Music] It's
dark, it's dark.
There's a snake that I can't answer at all.  Yes, we have been
walking in the same place for 10 days now, not drinking water, not meeting anyone,
after getting lost.  I
wonder if there are still people who came here earlier. I wonder if it's all over. Are we the only ones left? I
shouldn't think about that. I
think there are still more people left. If I
don't keep walking,
this brain will go crazy.  It's
crazy. I'm going crazy.
[Music]
People, are they all still there? Are they still alive?
What's the address from the moment I thought it was over?
It's in Ehime. Yeah.
Nishitani: Well, I
could see Nishitani in detail.
Wow,
there's a place with Nishitani. That's how I
read it.
[Laughs] I
was actually in the mountains. It's still Kuma Plateau. It's
white. The
next one is
n't that far away.
[Music]  See
you again, toy Mt. Takasui. Maybe I'm wrong about Mt. Takasui. I
guess I'm addicted to perfume. I'm
going to go down the mountain again, Yon-
chan. There's an amazing but beautiful view. Wait, just normal Japan.  I
'd like to go to a place like that.It
definitely looks like Japan.I
want to go to the mountains.So
let's go to the drive rate.It's
true that it's tough without a car.I remember it, and I remember it again.I
think it was Gifu, a
place called Jigokudani.  There
was a monkey in the hot spring, and
Yame-chan really wanted to go there.That's
right, it was a really nice place.The monkey was
left to roam.I
didn't say that, but it
happened before.  I wish I had
told you the truth, Jigokudani.I wanted to
go there alone.Going alone is
lonely, and it takes 40 minutes without a car.04
Area code:
Well, it's
Tokyo, so maybe
Kanto
or something?Can you
tell me?
Saitama, Okutama,
Kanagawa-san,
Chiba  I still don't know which one is Saitama.It seems like I
can't figure it out just from 04. I'll have to
come to a bigger city.
Basically, the car license plate number is
too simple, but it's true. I
watched a video last year
of a solo trip to a hot spring in Hakone.
Pyramizodori
Hiramizo Dori Reimizu Dori
[Music]
Tiramizo Dori The locals are
very detailed.  Komaki, I think it will
come out when it rains, but
don't google it.
Just raise your hand if you're local.
If it's local, you'll probably be happy.
Orange is my hometown.  I
just came
to Hiramizu Street. It's the free finals, but I feel like I recognize the smell. It's like the same air. It's amazing, isn't it? Skeen, it feels so good to suddenly find a hot spring in a place like this. Yeah, it's kind of close. Oh, I live on a rural road in the middle of nowhere.  It's
really good
. It's not like I'm working. I see.
Everyone's okay. That orange is Japan's
all-around tour. I'm going to do a live house tour.
That's nice. [Music] I've been feeling sorry for you lately.  I
saw a professional girl on TV and there was a really cute girl,
right? I
heard that someone said they wanted to see Ikusabata station as much as they wanted to see it. I'm
going to Ikusabata just to see it.
Stop early.
[Music]
Tokyo,
Tokyo. It's not in Tokyo, it
's in the countryside.  The
country girl is
actually
in Ome City.I'm
not sure if you've
seen it,
but it's
probably
better than Kanagawa.
It's definitely a place with greenery. It
's on the left side, so
people
can get powder in there. I think it's on the
top left. I
wonder if it's in Hachioji or something like that. There's more greenery around
here. In Hachioji, there's a
lot of greenery. [Music] There's a lot of greenery over there.
[Music]
Yes, yes, it
's
true. It's amazing, but I don't know how far it is.
[Music]
Well, I'll go there. I
guess I'll do that.  I do
n't even know the name of the street on Hiramizo Street.
[Music]
Mountains, they chose mountains because they were named in the mountains.
Maybe they're all too naive. Eh, Mizuyama wasn't even
mentioned. Eh,
should I do this there? Or should I
go here?  OK,
then
[Music]
Let's go
for the last one. It's the last one. It was the
last one. It was amazing. I was able to travel the world so much.
Japan was the best. Congratulations. I was
able to see America and Spain.  Well, I was able to
see Germany, and I want to go there too.
Yes, Germany is
good. Hmm, but there are some good things about it. The
more English you
speak, the more you speak German. I'm good at English, I can do it. In
general, if you can speak English, you can communicate. Everyone can
speak English, so
English is good.
Even if it's not my native language, I speak English, so it
's English. But I'm forgetting one
important thing. My
role is over. I'm
definitely
crying through my earphones.
That's English.  I
thought I could do things like memorize words on my own, but the other day I
was listening to Ame-chan and Keala-chan talking, and I
thought, ``Listening'' is really difficult when you're in Japan.  I
guess I can do it. I can
talk every day.
[Music]
I wonder if there's something like English conversation,
like going to class or that
English program with Japanese subtitles on Everyday.  You
should just watch it on the Internet for free.Once you
get used to it, you can
watch it in English with English subtitles.If you
watch it while reading the subtitles, you'll become
better at both listening and reading, so
it's better to listen while reading.  It also
becomes easier to hear
[Music]
Recently,
for example,
when I watch English, it's always in Japanese,
so I watch it with Japanese subtitles.
[Music] I've
seen it quite a few times.
Okay, so I know the gist of what's going on.Okay,
now go ahead and
watch it with English subtitles.Oh, I see.I've already
got the Japanese content in mind, so yeah, I
see.So I see, you should just watch something like Disney or something like that
with English subtitles.  Let's try it,
please go ahead. Your
English will probably improve a little.
Listening. But one thing is still
important. The important thing is that there aren't many Japanese people in Japan.
But be
confident. They
say you can't speak English.
You know, after all, you have to get over that and try something after all.Well, it won't get better, so I think it's important to just talk and see it.Come on, I want to see the beautiful scenery of Austria and other places. [Music] Personally, I recommend Greece.
But that
cheap and beautiful person was
so kind.
When I went to Spain, I
had a little trouble with only English, but
in Greece.  I didn't have any
trouble,
but I read an article on the internet that said there are a lot of easy-going people.They're
really helpful,
open
and friendly.I still think they're friendly with Spanish people, but somehow I didn't have
much luck with English.  Hey, I'd
like to go to the Netherlands, too.
[Music]
Hungary, well, there's Hungary.
Just
come over here and
take a plane or train from Austria. You can go to Hungary by train,
like before, or something like that.  I
can go to the Netherlands in an hour's flight
, and then I can
go there in an hour or two.I've
said it many times, but I'm scared to go.I'm
actually going to get my passport.I've already got it.  Well then,
come around autumn, it
's not early, so it's not like that, so it's January now. It's
warm and cold in autumn too.
If you want to go on a vacation, then you can
come later.  It's
better to go in September.
Hmm, September is the time to go to the sea. Yeah,
September is good. I'll be waiting for you.
So today, Chiara-chan came to my house. Well, we're going to eat
delicious food now.  We're going out to eat some delicious food.
Well, I guess
there's something I wanted to do. Let's
do it at home. Let's go on a date now.
Ah, see you guys
[Music] See you
soon
[Music]
[applause]
Now that it's on, I'm a little
nervous
[Music]
It
's already happened,
but there are times when I'm frustrated, but I'll be okay today too,
please
[Music]
There's a fog
[Music] It's
funny, but
[Music]
[Music]  ]
[music]