[Music]
to
n
[Music]
hey
oh
[Music]
to
scky
there I'm
my everybody everybody's
here o o oi we've got we've gathered the
whole crew the whole
crew everyone's here
assembled except oh are we we hear
everybody is there a mic check we get a
mic check in the lethal company oh yeah
we can get a mic check H might be a good
idea no get get we can't I can't hear
GAA can you guys hear
GAA I can oh you can't hear that's cuz
oh right okay I see that makes
sense yeah
um you even though you
watcham it's fine guys just everybody in
the chat go watch somebody else's POV
I'm sitting out the first round so so so
I can't hear gooda but I'm haunting
her like a ghost oh wait what if uh what
if you watch gura but also watch
my Discord as well does that work oh I
hear girl but will you get double audio
I'm not too sure yeah maybe like don't
worry about it I'll figure it out you
guys you know you're going to get fired
you know have to make a well we can we
can also use Discord audio but I guess I
don't know when someone dies I would
mind this is fine this is proximity is a
lot funner but that's okay it's just
something that we're going to have to
deal with I guess because you know
I know a lot of people have been
mentioning mods we can't use those we
can't yes no can't we yeah it's not
allowed it's it's not allowed guys so
we're going to do what we can with what
we have that's what we've always done
that's what we'll keep doing
dance
[Music]
dance surely we can afford one soon
right well we did just begin this
journey the quot is pretty small the
first
day accessing terminal enter favorite
animal going to be our obviously
describe your role in a team Dynamic
thing a lot of
buttons
Tye
help
moons I time mons
moons mons
moons
exper it's so clicky I love this you
like have the
system that's above my B grade the AO we
are orbiting the
moon which moon there are multiple ah oh
we already
experimentation experimentation okay
experimentation let's
go just just go you going to Mo me I gu
crank it
Captain
crank who's the
captain be Captain hi oh am I the
captain oh that's right I sure am
selected as Captain ah I see
great big difference but you know what
that's fine ladies I can lead the charge
here company a few times who has play
lead the way play yet uh is the only one
who can play yet oh cons the content but
I've not played the game new
employee her new
employee I'm knew no we just just go and
take stuff scraps yeah main entrance is
R dead ahead ladies just find a
ladder no no please no start of the
game to avoid the bees you have to SP
three times okay is that a real thing or
you just pulling my
leg it's real look the chat says it's
real right right
guys hey Chad I know what you're trying
it worked for good it worked for her you
want what you believe
a sounds like a lie I'm I'm getting
mixed reviews from the chat right
now what do you mean no
it's at five it's like Five Night at
Freddy's if you're on the ship and
you're looking at the
cameras
exactly um we have nothing we have no
flashlights just find metal things and
get out of here and if we
[Music]
stay is brave
boy
[Music]
moves
all
right oh nice one I
feel you can do it
GAA nice one Ena
nice close that door in case there's a
mock bottles collected I'm going to be a
great asset to the company lock there's
the lock door here oh good I can't hear
you by the way nobody can hear you
you're
alone no I
do hang
up I feeling alone right up here
upstairs see what we can
find there wouldn't be a monster in here
right cuz like why would you got to
right click got to right click that's
how you scan stuff and you can see stuff
from the dark and it'll show you the
value of items no it's okay I'm going to
go too Ena don't leave
me Marco
hello there's really nothing over there
that's some stuff guess that this is the
exit who what what is
this and of don't really remember where
we came from got' be great assets this
place pretty big for like a first area
wait where is
more hi I muted myself on Discord so I
can talk to chat without messing up the
coms yes yes I'm listening to ena's
audio and Good's audio at the same time
I know it's scuffed and yes if we had
mods we could get around the problem we
don't have mods for various reasons
headphones
anymore are big meaty
footsteps whose big meaty footsteps are
those big meaty
[Music]
claws you got to jump five times that's
how you avoid
it I don't know where I
uhoh where's the
exit Okay mind
now nobody can hear you you're
ghost help me did you jump five times in
a row that's how you get away from this
one two three four see I told
[Music]
you I feel all Dan
I'm like kind of I I see a blurry vision
yeah cuz we were we were hit oh okay we
surv I think died what cost rip G was e
eaten or die consumed you're speaking
into the
void I can totally hear you yeah I dead
ah how that
happened
foot then death I mean I definitely
wasn't there you know I don't know if
you noticed but I'm a big old deserter
you guys only got one
item I brought I brought the bottles oh
oh
nice yeah fine we're not going in
anymore are we are we are we are we me
unless you guys someone should stay
behind
regardless a button is stuck I mean I
don't know if there was anything else
any other rooms yeah I didn't see
anything it was hard to see hold on
there we go
fixed do you want to get the
bees be collect the bees be but you
got them yeah the be
get do I at
theot I'm being up here hold on a sec
gra it can you spectate Callie so I can
watch don't
die pressure's on
huh I can scan
maybe anyone know where it is uh yeah
it's on the way or you doofuses are
going to tell me to go grab the hive and
not tell me where it is oh I just see it
from here it's it's like wait I I'll
I'll leave you it's over here basic you
have to help that way this way yeah I
think I oh oh there they
are wait did you grab
it somebody need to distract them e you
have to get pretty close and press e
be your
timeout
die going to
diek she probably um not so alive I see
her corpse I see her corpse can you
bring her a corpse guys if you want to
hear good now you can go to Callie's
stream and you can hear her on Callie
stream yeah but her body is so close to
the
bees hey you could it was you okay I'm
getting
late ah I'm watching you some Metroid
[\h__\h] if you
[Music]
die try to
bring we don't need the
bees oh my God the dogs where it spooky
where it spooky did she not know that at
night time she played this before this
is like that movie where that kid
di where's
my what
that where the kid dies death there you
go
Kiara she's one of our buddies do I
still have time to
bring don't you got
go how do I even get this I'm going hear
you tell p the l p
[Music]
well the bees had to be
abandoned I
could already hit so probably can't see
the name it's just the body
now yeah
just well I'll take
that
most paranoid makes a lot that was her
end
game
meast yeah thanks for trying
[Music]
to oh we pretty much reached the quota
we just need like one more metal scrap
so let's try and save to get to this far
away moons
ladies honestly we can sell like the
clipboard and stuff apparently it's
worth something if you're desperate but
I think we can definitely be
over over
the quota you know become employee of
the month wait who here is anybody here
part-timer or is everybody intern unpaid
intern I'm I'm
intern interns get
paid no um you're intern
[Music]
want
who pleas what are you Ty shovels or
flashlights I don't know Warrior
yeah flashlight no there's lots of stuff
if you go to the computer and type in
shop yeah flash would be good all right
I got this leave it to
me stop one shovel confirm we have to go
grab it
okay store and then we'll do
flashlight have like a little bit of
money oh I should do flashlight and then
a certain number okay
store um let's see box I don't think we
can afford anything
else how many flashlight just
one single flashlight and a dream we can
get more
later like that shall we go I can pickle
so
ship floting
SE yeah
I believe we
right is it Hol Fest time already true
oh no time wait guys it's a CLI watch
out yeah look for the
bridge bridge someone almost went off
the edge I
saw that was I haven't done that before
me neither me
neither very
scary there goes GAA somebody needs to
hold her hand we need to put a leash on
her ice
cream
[Music]
oh oh you bought a
shovel no do you want it no no you take
it my survival rate
is is run do you want that
flashlight I can carry the
flashlight things oh de I Eed so they
can't hear me doesn't it sound like ASMR
you know you're like one person just in
one ear
ooh I have private
ASMR
switch you guys forgot
to yeah I know someone's going to have
to be I thought you were for real now
was bait last time I recommend Ena be
bait this
time she come
out attack what's in there hey you want
to go in there girl attack oh wait where
do you have the things from did you pick
it up from the what's in
there the present there's a present in
the front
room I shov can you beat
him is it possible to hit that thing
with the
shovel back to the ship someone's got to
be bait and it might have to be me oh
she's not coming out that's what got me
last time man I tell them you can hit it
hit
it okay
okay
pressure blushy blushy
blushy we shall play with
it
we shall go more
aggressive we should go all in different
directions and then
[Music]
[Applause]
later
intercept here I don't
know well I don't think he can get
through the door if you guys just close
the door can you trap him in here close
the door he can't open the door but he
has arms he's there's nothing the other
way
no time for baby cows yeah we can lead
him into the other room all right I'll
have him follow me and you guys look for
scrap he's
gone who's got the flashlight I do no
we're
not
protect
hey again
again kill kill kill beat him kill
him oh
no you got it there's a casualty uhoh I
think gooda hit her by accident it's all
right girl you did what you had to do I
will take up her flashlight in
herstead I didn't I got it yeah feels
more noble that way hey that was sick
though
I
tell you can stay here take a
nap it's on a
place wait was that this room where's
Ena is Ena
alive where's
Ena en's got the flashlight Oh I thought
I saw a flashlight yeah yeah flashlight
oh okay there's another
Flashlight
[Music]
nice
anyway it's starting to get it's close
to
uhoh this is a big area I think good is
this
is a
fish holy what are the
odds that's amazing it's meant to be
wait does it do anything like does it
fake
swim not a fish this is really
heavy it's made of
tungsten wait
Marco
[Music]
fish okay okay hi hi yo let's
go she left you I got you don't worry
fireman's
Carri this seems like a different door
it's probably the same door anyway let's
get out of here before the the dogs come
and the Forest Giant they're not very
friendly oh what is the Forest Giant oh
he eats
you it's big treatment he got like
orifice face it looks kind of
weird and then he puts you into it and
you hear a munchy
noise where where is it know I know
should be around here she's
Dead's dead dead I don't know actually
lome s hey look we found the
ship nice one BR right again
all glut for
punishment
let's go oh is that ena's
body is this ena's body well it's not
mine I thought this was you I was
carrying the whole time you kill entire
I was bitten by the monster but I
quickly run away and survived somehow
coward my a button's a little stuck
again every time I go to the ship it
ends up that way anyway I got the kettle
nice they did do the uh switch of Maru
then sorry en you rest in peace look I
found AAL
bnk H fish that's a heavy boy oh
plastic still got value we're killing it
exit time yeah let's go everyone keep
your hands and feet on the
ride oh
she like yeah inside when the door
closes one big fish I sustained the most
injuries I think Ena sustained the most
injuries cuz she died no she's lazy she
didn't do anything can you be injuries I
can't you can't
[Music]
be me I'm a
part now
yeah part what does that part it just
means take the most risks in the next
Expedition anything until we sell all
right uh let's see access terminal all
right yeah uh let's see how about vow
let's go to
vow
yeah
wow the V or with the yeah with the V
what
other on
my have some um announcements at the end
okay let's go I'm just trying to
entertain myself I know I'm going to be
intern forever and I'm just entertain
why forever intern are you are you
injured whatever flashlight who's
turning off the lights you think it's my
second sh seen
many employes of the group they got
promoted and
level it's all right Ena OHA we got to
go it's all right Ena you can prove
yourself now
yeah all right
um I'm a little right now was anything
order nope nope not this time okay I'm
pretty sure this one is either straight
forward or to the
right
forget bird oh I don't think he'll hurt
us thankfully let's try going to the
right oh there's the friend get is
running off into the
unknown uhoh is running off into the
unknown she'll find her way
G
Marco Polo see Marco Polo
again screams we're getting lower
now all right well girl can use either
Bridge maybe I bet she'll find it
that'll be entrance oh I'm not a dummy I
knew it was there never seen this before
oh he jumped is there fall damage in
this
game kind of I I'm not going to find out
dark it
is ooh bottles nice you guys had a
flashlight but it's gone
now Goa dropped it I think so it must be
in the last
[Music]
area
no now going
to going to grab the
core
no
what wait is this
bad you're not going to believe what I
found was a CL
it's a it's a light
bulb where is
everybody wait why the lights but the
lights go gra grabed the
generator
wow wait is that what that was I thought
that was just like
a oh can I put it back in a forbidden
light bulb I don't think so where's and
Kiara probably
dead probably dead that's to say can we
go
back
can did you guys get any more loot maybe
it' be good to get we got we got some
bottles and then the generator so I
think you guys are fine you guys already
made the quota you can go back
yeah this one's more expensive you
grabbed a life bulb life bu question
marks
question mark that means that means
special
prize stupid
prize
hopefully I
[Music]
don't's
another can you throw me a
rope you have to climb I have some
beer I think I think my leg is
broken oh no wait there's H maybe you
can climb through there there's some
bees there though don't worry I'm Skyrim
teing oh
no I'm a covered
[Music]
in just
gaming you're going to have to go around
I
think Trust n
nice
just yes no okay
going I'm going
around
pleas the ship oh oh oh you made it so
fast no I thought I lost you
forever I just just heard scream and
turned around and you were gone she was
jump that thing she jump on a bed it was
bouncy I saw the play I was like H this
looks like the're
running no I don't really
here Callie and I'm just going to take a
while get and
see did I make it they
died I wonder
why but they do
huh wait oh they're lost alive they're
lost inside just lost oh no Kiara's dead
oh no she's alive oh no it's the monster
carrying it her around
oh Callie might be
alive did she make it
out I think I think she's
alive Call's in the backr SC is I don't
know didn't I make it maybe she's
outside now did you go pick her up is
that the edge of the map oh she made it
out alive oh she's crossing the
bridge jump on
[Music]
it wait
what it's becoming
dark somebody has to go back for wait
did we yeah she I think she's dead
moners are like oh look at this new doll
we got
oh oh she's
making look at all my
trinkets ooh a
trinket a drink it okay stay
here I'm here oh you guys are alive
let's go I
[Music]
thought
nice's
gone she bravely walked before me and um
and took a bug to the face and we
invaded a Bracken I can't believe that
happened there you shouldn't be alive
after that okay let's go well we made it
all you guys good work we were pretty
useless but I like to think we lured the
monsters away from you guys maybe we
were we were pretty shallow when the uh
when it happened I broke a bridge with
her big ah yeah that happens too fish
with my big butt yeah butt too big all
to it butt too
massive know I thought the tungsten fish
was stop jumping it turns out I'm the
tungsten fish hey stop jumping just not
jump button isn't even oh hold on sorry
it's just my jump button stuff there we
go door
open no no no no no
d
be oh we're leaving okay goodbye oh the
bees almost I mean I feel like if you
want to be safe before we leave the
atmosphere yeah you choke and die you
can die like that no unnecessary Death
yeah it's like space for science yeah
yeah
probably I can see that why am I the
laziest
[Music]
employees to intern I went back to
intern because of that what
F my time to go be to the company all
right I'll take us
there o what do I
[Music]
bring cool we're on the
way well I think we all know I think we
all know what happens when somebody
rings the bell right so
let's
yeah
what you get a you get a sticker when
you ring the
bell you ring the
bell like a bunch of times not just once
you get a
lollipop yeah something kind of neat
happens how do I hold
on
no
leave it leave it just leave
it
oh maybe the counter was kind of full
mhm give another sh it wasn't
taken
was sells for a lot too and the fish
fish
no the fish anything no I didn't I a
personal token lost it wait one more
thing one more thing I lost
[Music]
it
did you bringing it over my shoulder you
know
myness
no what a deal what a
deal not the fish not the fish you're
going to lose the
fish can weell to post it oh no she's
ringing the bell and running away I feel
like we have so much more money though
more than 146 we barely met the quota we
barely met the yeah when I scamed it was
like 24 something or another he ripped
us off rip off no
yeah huh
no oh we have enough money went back
into the
ocean she went
home wait fish oh this I think throw in
there yeah car we might find the fish
over
there oh [\h__\h] what is this
Flor what
this I don't know I kind of forget what
is you
me sound behind the wall there was a log
a journal
entry was a
will not
here I think I think she went
home all right well
I into the ocean
see well I got her
journal nice all
right yeah that would be a good idea
okay that was Min is the Min is the
quoda um probably
by something
Wy
talkies should
we switch members
or I wonder if someone left would I be
able to invite someone again in
here I'm should I'm should be able to
play next round this
round is that how it works let's see if
we
can't kind look like a
sculpture recreate a room it would be
better or not if we did not do that we
can't go to the rooms I wonder can can
we invite from here you can make it
saves an orbit oh yeah that's right you
can true yeah look I have a save file so
if we quit out of it it saves your
progress so I'll quit out of it and
reinvite people okay is that going to
work
okay yeah let's do that okay
save and then close
lobby go to orbit and then save yeah
okay so we we save and then we exit and
then invite people again somebody sits
out I see again fish all right so who
going to sit
out he in the deep deep darkness of the
waters so dark I can't see
anything gar will sit out so no but
you're new to the game everybody else
has played it did
you oh maybe I'll sit out for I don't
know if I in the game right now you
can't cuz you're the you're the host
true maybe I'll sit out the last game I
don't want
the
new okay well I'll go ahead and quit out
then we're in orbit now
quit
okay oh me a
coach you guys can't hear me or I can't
hear you guys right now that's
okay how did you did you show the
Discord share yeah yeah I just had um
like somebody's main POV and then
somebody else cuz you can watch two
streams at once and then I had both
audio playing at the same time and it
wasn't that bad it's kind of echoey but
it's not that
bad
okay uh
uh wait am I not sitting this one out I
can sit out I don't mind I'm sitting out
Choice has already been
made okay on welcome great asset I guess
I
should who
who wow now go to explain what were you
doing at the
end uh can one more person also stream
there I can I can I can see will
play okay I can do it I can do
it
uh wait just buying some stuff you guys
can
hear maybe I should buy one more walk
maybe two more walkies look who taught
you those dances huh
you
famar to me have you cheated on me by
going to a different dance
teacher Y no I would never do that you
kidding
me never I don't know those dance moves
they look unfamiliar to me I didn't
teach you those it's okay it's just your
old age you're you're forgetting things
you've gone CA that's
fine a little gas lighting here and
there good just a little bit
good fun bonart that's probably yeah I
did Watson you stin you guys can't even
get
out I'm going to light a match on
blowing this place
[Music]
up
Moon
Moon let's go to um Moon the Moon Moon
let's go to Insurance
again the moon seems good off we go
ladies I'll follow your lead I want to
see the powerful skills of ailia
Watson colle I'm like pretty
good Master TR
collector your trinket I'll take you
can't catch
meard Level D Stu easy list for
Christmas cribo
music Dad this is my
PO you want
this where is it yeah keep your eyes the
cowys there it is it's on it's draing
the
battery oh
[Music]
Santa what is it I got a present from
Santa
[Music]
Claus
flashlight
[Music]
break break follow the
light this is Big Fish over this is
Watson over I'm looking for the
entrance I'm staring right at it stupid
over I mean come back one two three
Niner ner
cop that breaker
breaker breaker
breaker why didn't you call me a name
back oh wait this is am's point of
view
H this is it tell me where to go
I'm
over I'm I'm lost is it Amit I'm jumping
right now no this is
Amy
over do that thing where you like blow
into your elb
[Music]
G I'm
confused did you catch that did you
catch that
over this ised into the
microphone uh I'm lost and stuck on a
cliff
over
is this
Gus yeah where do I go it's am me okay
now it's am me okay okay got
it you know
where wait I'm by the ship I'm by the
ship are you guys
lost just
[Laughter]
me follow the right
um is I the pipes
maybe right these are some
pipes
yes found some
bees
over this is guras this is I passed by a
ladder
you are you at the ship
over
negative where did you
go
over where is this ladder chat you guys
are lying to
me okay yeah this is
good these are some pipes I see you
oh
hello hello hello over hello
hi it's this way it's that way it's
there it's there it's there it's
there I found
something what what wait what a
log did you leave
it
hey guys it's already 2:20 p.m. and you
haven't entered the
building so all they found was soda yeah
they haven't even done anything
see break a
breaker Super Mario Brothers we're the
super san Brothers Oh H know wait wait
wait hit me guys there's a lot of stuff
in there get get it okay oh gift
box you want on it what's in it
uh oh a hair brush I
mean it's just this sucks you can have
it here you
go I tried it didn't let
me wait there's another one here open
this
one gift wait fish wow oh wish wow I
that one's
cooler wait
hello
hello activity detected let's get out of
here I'm going to get out of here too
there's a noise oh bson all right yeah
you want to leave let's go yeah bet bet
Watson let's get out of here um someone
dropped their walkie-talkie oh wait I
left my stuff back there Ander
uh
hello what just happen did I steal my
stuff there she is oh there she is wait
what she's alive I thought you what
about what was that noise I'm leaving
bye I think I can get my title back
right can be oh there's a break a
breaker there's a
lot there's at least
two yeah
you do you guys need help carrying
something no is everyone alive yeah
Calli already went she already went back
to the
ship okay we got to be quiet
wow cuz I should survive that I'm
inow I hear the it's the here doo do go
Doo
here boy here get away from you guys you
guys are going to get me
killed I dropped
it it's a good
boy are yous there many snacks
here oh hold on I'm opening it I haven't
seen any dogs so far oh get in here worm
worm worm worm wor
worm oh that's that's a worm yep I made
it I made
get inside get inside oh everyone made
it worm I don't know see the giant red
do on the screen timing is
[Laughter]
impeccable it's important music is
important when you're lonely on ship in
space pleas some sing us a song You're
the piano
man
yeah uhoh I dropped it
laziest employee wait how can you be
lazy and profitable at the same time
amazing seems like there's something are
you just pushing your tasks to the other
employees yeah what brought me no I I
even I literally saved Amy from Death a
monster was on her head and I killed it
she's
alive hero moment for Kiara big
hero I killed it on my own it was the
strength of my spirit the strength of my
will no my is the FR Thank Me Later chat
tell
her she not
know all right I'm sending us you're a
hero to meet thank you let's go to Ren
okay sounds good like French
it's oh I've never seen this screen
before maybe we should order
50 we're too poor Goomba we can't afford
it get the strong we'll go to offense
because we
are
off what like a high school Friendly
Fire
yeah I st in the someone twerking in the
corner over there what's going on are
you Hing me I was twerking have them I'm
not what I'm not twerk what are you
talking about you were doing some some
movements behind the cabinet I wasn't
sure you know if you were uh right yeah
sure that was me she's doing the oy
spy the
boom yeah I mean someone could stay here
in the and direct us the walkie talkies
can you use that
pre why
is
it's and announcement from the company
please do not kill your other fellow
employees you hear that sare
off I don't need talkie so wait I'm
going to charge mine need more
everyone's Liv matters in this company
okay I'll stay here sounds good let's
going be do that assets though the great
assets they definitely value the great
assets more though what did you say to
me yes you heard me what no she did not
call you an s a great ass scary C I said
you're a great asset to the
company yeah I don't need it I have mine
I have mine hey copy copy break a
breaker
[Music]
over all right crying out to you in
peril you're not going to hear me no no
I will I will be around when you need
me what
she not respond to
that I guess we go side there's a big
bird hat no they hate me Sor wrong
untrue now you're just making up
fibs let's see oh maybe we can go up
here all right you're going to lead us
right to
the
[Music]
theot wonder if we can jum this I see
her there's a different way we can
go we can just go around alarm yeah I'll
Le you yeah yeah yeah yeah jump you got
to jump you made
it Sally gave up though before even
trying no I didn't I'm going to do it
now she like for the job it
coward prank the
rest what you know I just the other day
finished my first ever like um platform
Mario game
wow yeah Mario
Odyssey yeah it was very nice to me it's
a good
game I like it excellent
maneuvering thank you
over all right you never would have been
able to do this it's then you stayed in
the
ship I'm going to leave your ass
behind all right I need I need some uh I
need some comms
here coms clear
coms div there's a spider there's a
spider there's a spider hello this is
morron
speaking
hello what you say hello there's a
spider can't pick up anything C CH can
we kill the
spider there was a treasure over
there the treasure look like there
triangles green Doritos oh I found
something yeah there's one behind you in
a room can you keep a look out for red
dots on uh on
me no it's a
nothing good down here maybe it's below
nothing good down here sadly yeah
there's a green
oh Green Dot there's Lo in that room if
you go to your
right oh did I see two eyes now we have
the generator the generator it's the
generator do not touch until the
end what was that why there no items
there is one in
there oh is this the same room or is
this a different
one oh sounds like a
lightsaber like it now no no no I
wait all right well I'm going to grab
the core and we can go I hear muffled
the scream I'm grabbing the core
um
um oh she's making a run there pretty
quick though not going to lie I'm going
to get her body where did you guys go
the
[Applause]
is I'll carry your body you can carry
the I think there's one more thing hold
on
oh
okay oh good idea gring the items very
nice y
successful wow what a
legend we did it you should wow
that's really admire that I'm a bit of a
coward though not going to lie did I
miss anything who's dead who is
it I can't I don't think we can talk on
the mic with the thing I am afraid to
tell you that oh
Gus someone has passed away can we oh
yeah we have to make the jump okay oh
yeah I think a couple people have passed
away wait Cy did you pick up anything
else did you get an item no sorry
couldn't be good asset this time really
was pretty Barren I'm not going to
lie
hello we're good
at so
slow peace out peace out of existence
huh wait oh
oh just kidding it must have been on the
walkie see I knew they'd be
useful I have uh Kiara's dead body but
what about Kiara's
sign dang it must have lost it the oh I
picked it up I got it oh nice I pck up
her
MVP MVP what a legend all right let's M
on out of
here someone else can choose where we go
next leave it up to you
[Music]
guys
pick
yeah where does chat want to go this
clothes on its own right yeah think yeah
be pretty funny if it didn't though I
will say nice one team um we have about
one day left for the C I think we can we
can fill it how are we doing for the qua
so far hi qu
check I'm alive
again alive oh yeah we're at
216 profitable because I brought back a
body like a noble a noble Spaceman yeah
thank you for carrying me you're welcome
I got laziest but I was Button
Pusher I mean I could I pushed
oh wow Assurance really is the only one
that we can mess around on
huh don't me please no violence
onink oh well in that case all out
Battle Royale
Doo you're radio's going to run out
battery the best
one yeah you got to charge it you got to
turn it off
you know what I should also grab some
flashlight mine's on
to I'm going to grab some flashlights
real quick and then we can
go
flashlight
great
F right now have a report to make to uh
HR yes and being harassed by an
employee harassed by
what Packy ch
listening she's killing
me she's killing me for
Content
wait oh my
God EXC for cont witness you just
committed a crime here yeah I'm
reporting you to the
company report has been made
please
Kiara Kar I will kill myself ban her
from the
server oh [\h__\h] no I okay all right girl
last day of the meet the
qu um I do
Whata answered my
[Music]
prayers what just happened I can't I
can't hear El cuz she's is dead I gained
my title and I my I'm so sorry it's
because I didn't realize you know me
first anyway you got what you deserve
that's okay I got oh yeah it was
supposed to be one for each of us but
plans changed clearly wait wait wait
wait I drop his up yeah me
too how are we going to explain to the
bosses that two of our team well one
committed a crime and the other one
killed himself anyone committed s
um person that was the same person for
now let's not think too much about it
I'm sure that the
company can I please I can't believe
you've done this take on the ra that my
it was for love fellow employee was
going to love you say can I get the
lunch coupon it's kind of different from
the love I know can I get that meal
ticket yeah
that I didn't do
anything potato you started that was in
orbit we already left sounds yummy is
this we were out of
Orit you're trying to blame me that's
what they all say
Kiara I will I didn't mean it I didn't
think I was actually going to kill her
or like she's dared
it run and
jump to the rescue it's like if someone
else is going to kill elit going to be
me kind of thing you know was
too it seems to May me shark has missed
her she left she left I can't die here
wat is going to laugh at me forever if I
die here cuz she literally told me you I
don't think she'll take damage J Jump do
it there we
[Applause]
go I had to fight off the dragon
sorry dragon
but I
lived I was going to make a plan but I
stopped myself I to watch out bir
hostile hostile hostile H HTI hostile in
the area hostile it's just a bird
hostile I'm scared
anyway yeah take jump I did
it oh PR all right now all what's she
going to do with it what she going to do
with it oh oh oh mountain goat strats
take the present hello oh she made it
I'm alive you made it before I found a
present I can't open it for some reason
I pressed y but it didn't work maybe you
can open
it
oh that'll help us
the we got
it we got to survive it look like a
burger
[Music]
nothing in here nothing spotted
people full
nothing oh my
go no way the worst person to find it
can you use
it find something good yeah dude what'
you find not going to believe
it okay all right uh I'm quitting the
game I've had enough of this I've had
enough of
this come here come here come here come
here come here come here come here come
here sit on it come here oh my finger
yeah there for the content G pick it up
pick it up pick it up
up
[Music]
really you know what you've made a
mistake G you're letting me hold this
now which means you'll never get it back
no it's only wore it's not even worth
anything and Y I can use this as
leverage now see how
productive there's a turret be
careful tur it that way where's this you
can use that you know tell her wait
yeah glass
Flash say flash give me my whoopy
cushion back or
El find
her I don't think that I don't think
that I don't think the flashback flashes
the spider does it I'm so proud of you
you flashbang the spider like no
tomorrow
did it did it work did I do it did I
flash it you did you did
y I don't think that kills it though
just letting you know
yeah maybe it just got emotional damage
not
sure where's C his I don't know which
way should she's outside
okay
no oh no is that
Kiara oh that was
that's is
nowhere
jestine disgusting little creature
disgusting me proud of
you I did very
slippery he's not happy is he no the
exit
oh over
Marco she not does she not hear
it get back
battery at least one person's back at
the
ship
yeah the
[\h__\h] she left
me she
left turn your radio on you you she's
leaving she's
leaving she she's leaving she was
leaving oh is G still there oh what the
[\h__\h] a that's what she gets for leaving
her
behind
didn't even check the
cams real sorry about that
one you know on the bright side I got sa
cushion for you I'll have you know I was
fighting for my life in there well
that's fine you wouldn't have made it
back anyway the dogs were
prowling I did it all flavor I help you
now we have maybe
enough are we all getting fired is
we might be getting fired asides from
being fired there has been some
allegations of you
know members there's mine killing
members so that
true abuse body cell for H is definitely
going to hear about this three Warm
Bodies that could increase the qu amount
oh you can actually use
it there's no bathroom in the ship just
to let you know it
[Music]
I figured she'd like
that that makes sense wait so uh if we
want to rotate someone out we can this
is a good time to do it if we want
to I can be the one before before we die
I can I can it's my
turn
okay we're going by the life the r oh I
guess it makes sense how it
works all right I guess we're going to
the company
now you got to sell everything we have
no days left on our
deadline I want some
pickles well you can check if you meet
the quot or not first maybe yeah I know
I kind of did take a look and I think if
even if one of us even if all three of
us gave up our bodies if three people
gave up their bodies it wouldn't matter
matter we can give up our bodies for
points for
money oh like
five oh oh oh that's what you mean oh I
yeah if we beat up each other right
we'll need something to beat each other
with so maybe don't sell anything we
don't sell the soft sign yet I mean you
can just ring the bell a lot of times
this but o I got a sniper o Del Las
pointer where did you get that I I found
it on the floor I think we're going to
for a lot that's good
o yeah if we sell
the we might
need we have to keep spirit I don't
think it gives us any
money no I don't think the boom Box
gives you money does
it that's too bad oh it's gone I
mean oh
301 yeah you
guys you keep feel free to keep your
your whoopy cushion I guess she was
going to keep it anyway she's going to
keep it
any but it okay all
right goodbye whoopy cushion find
another one
baby damn
[Laughter]
it
get moving maybe we can go to some
better moons we're going to go into
orbit and then we'll switch out is
everyone here okay I don't know is every
I mean sorry I also didn't check again
I'm not the best Captain this seems to
be a reoccurring thing Callie all right
now listen here the company hear about
apologies no no no no the company
doesn't need to hear about anything
anything of the sort quote is going to
start getting crazier though from here
on out um we're going to need to go to
further away moons with better
loot you will be the voice that
everybody hears so maybe lead give it no
don't lead us but give us give us give
us useful hints yeah like a talk like a
GM now let's see what we can buy
first see store I can spell store um so
we have quite a bit of money in fact we
could get a transporter which might be
kind ni oh no BL if the ship leaves
before you can teleport I mean good all
Point too but we we actually can't
afford it so I'm going to grab some
shovels
shovel two we need two fighters and then
after that um I think we should us we
should be using the money to go to
Charing everything
mhm number one
employee will going for employee of the
month it's really
expensive um all right what's the
cheapest Moon I wonder is it dine by
chance we won't go there cuz it's
Eclipse but oh
no is
[Music]
R grenades would be
nice um we're changing that's right
correct swapping out boss mmy doodle
okay going to close out the room
now quit bullying
[Music]
girl what is going
on off the ship
oh no
okay oh I guess I got a launch now
huh
[Music]
oh I can un stream now in the
Discord all right hold on one
second such intense
music it is
terrifying oh can you invite me
again I'm excited thank you needs
another invite play Oh Ena needs another
invite you got yes please okay no
problem Captain's got your back all
right youa Jump On
In yeah guys I basically did uh almost
everybody maybe except for one person
cool youa yes guess we can go to a you
see I I sent you a present over did you
see yeah it's probably in your emails or
so Che youram notifications it'll be in
there wa you double now you double can't
go all right oh IED the gift now
mute accept GI I got it don't have it
yet do you have I don't I only have the
first
one please play it I want I want to see
you play it
okay I will I'll Artist Artist yeah I
ended up giving her something else guys
than what I originally said in the
Stream Secret Surprise the other
game oh Secret
Surprise make sure we grab our
stuff
second I'll grab a glad she doesn't have
it okay who's staying in the ship
I can stay in the ship or you can stay
in the ship such an obvious pick guys
I'll stay I'll
atef learn I'm just like pretty right
them's echoing for me oh sorry I okay oh
good there we go
switch display mon wait how do I do it
again is the ship coming you got to look
at the
monitor e
I you type in switch view monitor yeah
that's what it is I got it make sure you
have a walkie-talkie are you staying
inside yes all right get out of here get
out my S my should be
coming chicken chicken chicken chicken
I'm playing Five Night
Freddy's maybe it
reset
watch just press the little plus eyeball
on
Discord
oh my
God thank
you calling in are we not receiving
anything ship I should take is
there this is
HQ calling in break a
breaker don't affirmative Grim shady is
now enter the is waiting to enter the
building but I'm also waiting for my
friends Grim sh over
K's
lost
over I found the main entr
over I think you're going the wrong
way Kar can you hear me over and out
Grim
over she's
lost she didn't take the walkie-talkie
with her like I told
her
she hit a dead
end H looks like she's okay I think she
found a different entrance I don't know
tell her to jump on the bridge jump on
the bridge fun bouncy woo she you tell
her you she can hear you yeah
sorry found another whoopy
cushion
looks like there's two items in there
Grim
Shady bre breaker
whoop Watson can you repeat that please
uh there's uh should be two items in the
room
affirmative there's a
mon I don't see any red dots right now
there a way I can lower this go change
the
floor I guess they're
fine Kiara has found some other
items oh Kiara car there no Ena there's
a monster right behind
you e it's like running away ew e ew
e no Ena needs help Ena needs help oh
ena's being taken away if anybody has a
shovel uh you guys are running right
towards her she's she's to the right to
the right the monster's taking her deep
into the uh it's too
late H don't follow her there's a ton of
enemies down that
hallway I I don't know what we could
have
done do you guys have
shovels
rip all right it looks pretty safe for
now yeah can you hit that whatever the
thing that tooker can you hit it with
shovel oh there's an enemy coming with
right at you guys if you your teammate
needs help no
and someone just snaap their neck what
was that I think it's called
a Breen breaker
breaker is it crunch Watson this is grim
Shady reporting I have two big bottles
that that I don't think that I could
handle by myself if you wouldn't mind
coming to pick one of them up to help me
out I'll try to I'll try to do both but
okay copy that I'm on my way how to get
there wait I got to I got to figure out
how to get there
there yeah which way do I go chat is it
this
way Mine The
Cliff I see
it
sh this
way follow the cliff follow follow hello
oh hi I'm going
back follow follow follow follow follow
the edge of the
cliff wait uh this is it right oh yeah
this should be the okay I see
it that bridge looks way too
sturdy I think I think the bridge will
break if you're too heavy like
someone yeah like someone's big butt
over and out Grim Shady over and
out I love bread
rolls yummy
yummy can you hear
me nah I think she can only hear if I
talk on the
radio oh [\h__\h] it's
getting is going to leave you better
run I'm
lost
there it
is
what what is
that uh Watson do you read me I hear big
steppies
[Applause]
yes stay quiet what is that oh my God
what is all right let's go let's go
let's go let's
go nice one one nice one Watson let's
go yeah
J hey are we lifted we lift off I'm
pretty sure we
did yeah thankfully just got to check
imagine celebrating early
yay anyway nice one Watson that came in
that came in
clut definely
serious
yeah a shame two days left we pull about
the same amount it's all right it's all
right no problem if we pull the same
amount again um a couple more times
then what's wrong
[Music]
yeah oh you got
demoted I can't get demoted
any oh my
Lord for that
[Music]
huh
and stay in the corner of Shame Myers
are haven't been in a
while that's Kiara K she's mocking you
look at
her you're just an intern to go to Mo
there will be no bullying on my
ship it was Kara Kiara did it she
started it
you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] I am
done being your girlf fighting as you
never again oh whatever fine get in the
middle of a couple
squirrel or like gross
grossling nice that was actually pretty
good so we're going to land and we
should look listen look listen for the
delivery I got flashlights for you guys
I owe
you y sure you Char
your why do we have so many whoopy
cushions the best cuz good was playing
with us probably
why true where's the Christmas tree
should be
coming oh
nice
yeah are we looking
the it's
[Music]
there oh main entrance is over
there
it up let's cover it up let's cover it
up all
right moving real
[Music]
fast all right I got a key so hopefully
there's a locked door in here we can use
we got watch and speed running wait I
don't have a flashlight
okay all right shady is there anybody at
over
[Music]
hello this a dead
end dead end just like my career in this
company My
my what coming to get
you there's a noise over there is that a
bomb okay I'll take is
his oh it's a
pipe I fixed it it's still
broken no I fixed it I can't see I
didn't bring my
[Music]
flashlight this is grim Shady are you
detecting any hos I fix it not at the
moment
oh Stu know I always fix the
bo this way in every
game perfect yay key Cera I got a door
over here but I need light yeah yeah
there's I saw elsewhere also another
monster oh oh
let's get
it what I don't know is that several
usages I think
so
H maybe it will stop the
monster maybe I don't remember the
exit okay I think it's this
way what is that
ew
help
what is that sounds familiar why is it
got to follow
the it's Chase there's something chasing
us I thought you were the
ship
o
wait funny I I only have one
[Music]
ey hi it doesn't sound like an airole we
didn't find anything what' you say good
I have this it doesn't sound like an air
horn it sounds like something
else
me elepant almost better as the fart
cushion wait where's C take that back a
squirel there is anyone using these
these things it's Grim shady and I think
I found a continuation but I really need
a flashlight over and out oh if you're
talking about that I think we we are
already explored that
area
over also I found a present be right
there and a
what jiggle jiggle
over what is that ew e r oh my
[Music]
God
oh they're outside I can't open this for
some reason so I open
it yeah
here please be a let's
go thank you appreciate it oh you guys
are coming back in we're all
alive this is easy yeah there was
nothing
mirit chat says oh [\h__\h] fire
exit wait you know went
the is still in
there well I think she's
dead no all right if I don't come
back wait she's moving oh just leave
wait she's
moving you if you need assistance uh do
you have your walkie
talkie
oh my God wait there's actually a lot of
stuff in the fire there's actually a lot
of stuff in the fire exit where is
everyone she's insane Ina's
insane X book Serpentine
maneuver
wow oh she made
it
like how do I see what time it
is you guys
know want to check the
time I go
outside oh everybody made it oh it's 5
p.m. pretty brave of
[Music]
me we have we're going to have a mine
field of
cushions yeah at this point anything
wrong with that hey we know what we're
selling first if we're low on
[Laughter]
quot you should
be we got more stuff than I thought PR
good
[Music]
monsters is worth
52 which one oh a lot way more than I
thought a
lot nice one yes no notes is better than
being called
lazy great a yeah a
nice one day left one day left anything
you guys want me to buy oh
cute I could use a Walky I have one okay
I don't have one either oh really I
thought for sure we had four
definitely
bought yeah all right
two someone to go to the bathroom or
what gu not
Gooding no can out there forever I mean
maybe going to March's a toilet that you
I me Gravity helps
right how would you even get it out
anyway
all right we're on our way where's our
next destination
March all right let's goch time oh team
go March in isn't that right
lady any want staying
behind there's a there's a heart in your
body
[Music]
careful you don't really need a
flashlight technically
no it's not really charged no no you can
just go into the darkness and it's fine
oh there's the
entrance where's going
[Music]
easy oh it's cuz everybody's buying
stuff right now is that why she's going
in by
herself
oh wait no
wait have youer the
building n I'm waiting outside hurry up
over
swag
yippe yippee
yippe I'm here I don't know
are they probably jumped off the C okay
go t go Tu go
t let's
go nothing
here than oh shoot we need a key for
this one don't we oh no this place is
Big wow big room I hear I hear big
footsteps
loot there's a monster above up there
yours no no
no
[Music]
parkour did she know
oh oh hello hi how do I pick this
up
what oh oh my God good
find find bring the mine
[Applause]
[Music]
back oh that's a yeah that's a she's got
the
goddamn how do we de
theor how we going to do this someone's
got to be B we got to meet this qu I
felt something was you sure I don't mind
being we don't have a it running away oh
uh it's
okay
go going
[Music]
in okay
um still all of us
hereit I don't know where it
is ooh bravery see they're confused they
don't know who to go
after I not lose that oh no oh no wait
bring the bees in
oh
no all right well I'll put our body back
into the
ship
oh I feel like there's a lot of stuff in
there but
but Chad didn't we already meet the
quota too I think we
did blur the
bees we should yeah we could have done
some like teamwork I like know about
that you already back in the
ship someone here
yeah oh need help you're going to have
to toss oh you just
I'm going back
oh you're going
back yeah it's still early
hero something weird is happening
huh
feeling I think we could do
it get to the fire exit I don't know
where the fire exit
is
did anybody see the fire exit
anywhere yes
s left of the main entrance past the
bees oh my God oh my
God sorry I'm sorry you got this girl
you go
girl you better you better
hustle right well we
tried I found the fire exit over I'm
coming
all right we still have time it's 5:00
p.m. wait CH do you guys really know is
it actually over here God en's in there
now wait does that mean it's
safe what just
happened I should probably get back to
the
ship um
what is
that he's why is he just
stand oh my
[\h__\h]
for
I get back to the
ship oh my God okay I think this is the
right
way hey
guys are you coming back
yeah wait SOA is dead in the in the
thing h
ah can't help it got to go I guess I
don't think we made enough money I think
it is this our last
day yeah but we made a lot of money
before I think on the previous
days okay it's okay it's okay we have I
I just cleaned we have a lot of stuff I
just cleaned it into the storage oh
don't sell the
whoopies all right sell it all ni work
[Music]
all the whoy cushion playing a song for
you guys cuz you
[Music]
died away with this with all of it maybe
they'll forgive us I don't
know I think we're going to have enough
we're going to make it you think
so kill
somebody I mean okay I mean as long as
one of us is alive company building all
right have something to H each other
with and get the uh I need to buy a sh
the
spirit I think it' be good to have a
shovel yeah you could buy a shovel wait
but if we buy shovel will we have enough
no it won't affect the money that okay
won't affect the money sorry I'm not
really good at M all good well I guess
we can
land Yeah question after this should we
maybe just like chitchat a little bit
and do the like talk about the things
we're supposed to talk about oh yes oh
yeah we're supposed to be
uh supposed something that's true I
forgot about that I think another round
would take uh too long
[Music]
true I want to play
more yeah I mean let's get a let's get a
B
get for yeah I want to I want to
[Music]
play he doesn't like that all right now
the shovel should be
coming there it
is
sh selling our bodies isn't going to
work what the [\h__\h] I didn't know it was
[Music]
coming all the
toys got to sell you
Ena no we could have used that
body I mean oh no ena's dead what the
[\h__\h] what what
sell the walk oh I don't think so I
don't think I can anyway how much money
do we make to sell
itny I was
there oh is this
a he's got to T I can't take it back
it's okay whatever it's okay pretty
aggravated it's F I can't take it back
anyway it's okay please come take the
items there we go
come
on we didn't even make
enough yeah we'll be fine oh wow you
think so okay from just now right did we
hit it yeah we did no we didn't wow no
way we did no we didn't no we didn't oh
no we
didn't okay if we sell
our or
the true enough do it okay oh it is a
good ending although it is a good ending
it is a good ending isn't it when if we
get S to space that's a nice ending I
mean where are you where
okay
what you'll never find me over
here
[Music]
wait this goes really far I didn't think
it went this
far wait what
it's
looping keep going what's what what is
if I if I keep going is there a
shovel say
something hello t
[Music]
t see
light wait I have an idea
chat I got an idea I got an
idea oh what was he doing messing
around
hiia hi where were
you hey hi
yo
you
hey hey I didn't close the door on you
that was I think
I'm I see you guys wanted to be alone I
get it no I'm go I'm go
no man Left
Behind wait something's burning she
bought something you can buy something
here get away from my
stuff it's
mine I think I think you mean
mine I knew it get her I took
your that's my
shovel we survive you will not be the
end of me
this is a
murder go go
go
open don't do
[Music]
this
open
murder oh I could have taken off on the
ship that's
true take
off we should go should we sell our body
first just witnessed a cold blooded
murder I was going to get another shovel
okay I had a
plan oh my God at the end of the day
there's only room for one sheriff in
this now make the quote again
make the I don't think we can make the
quot there's not enough
Point back's only room for one Captain
it's like the ending of a bad space
offer I ran away cuz she was killing you
I was trying to save you by getting a
shovel a yeah just doing what has to be
done to satisfy the
company look at that face the face of a
murder we're still
and she's selling us while we're still
tching she could still help
us any whoopy cushions sure I sell
everything maybe he doesn't want these
things what are you doing
my did they take the
bodies why aren't you hungry yeah he'll
take
them here we go the reaper is
reaping there you go eat up eat
up how much money I she like she's like
the antagonist at the end of the movie
that like actually took over the world
and just like well time for a glass of
wine sits back he didn't want
[Music]
stuff not still in the boom box that's
for sure um with that being
said it's
over there's only one one remains
I think he should jump off the ship
right now be like a
movie the boom box dang
it can I are a little [\h__\h] you are
little
225 look you are I was just doing what
needed to be done he we were so close as
you
have look what you did close
I'm going to
survive I don't want to
[Music]
die
ejected shoot all right girls at least
we had a boom box was nice was nice GG G
yeah believe I got fired again oh
suddenly the double I leave the game
okay I'll do
this you girls okay F ready to talk I'm
ready to
talk unmute Cy
unmute call Un pretty good you know it
was okay Callie yeah Callie call won't
is
she
trans she's still she's still feeling
the end of the
movie why you crying
mate crying you look like you're sad
about your actions like you're
regretting what you done don't you feel
you guilt regret shame I feel remorse I
do great I feel that for sure for sure
for sure what you
me yeah I bit a little bit really IEP
you don't want to show it but you're so
deep in your heart you have
remorse okay well yeah I would say I
mean that's apt that's about right maybe
a little bit I just had to do what
needed to be done you know for the sake
of the company and that we were never
meeting that quota but you know I should
I had the opportunity to take the ship
and leave you guys and kill you taking
it yes In fairness was and I wasn't
going to kill kiar until she killed you
so what were you up my God I saw you hit
her look she doing my job
everybody everybody
[Music]
everybody first of all happy New Year
from myth happy
new May
2024 a year it's a new year it's 2024 oh
my
God
that's
um do we want to say like what what we
should say yeah things to talk about I
don't either okay I have some pictures
prepared I don't have pictures no it's
just like you know the usual uh the
small myth stuff we are here to
advertise the small small myth stuff
that is still on sale
until oh my God no way
cute cute a little while longer um I
don't know when it ends it doesn't say
here you guys can go look at K's channel
for the images cuz I don't have I also
don't have it in the description you're
hugging
them yeah there's a lot of stuff there's
uh the t-shirts where we're where we're
poking out of the the pockets yeah
there's small metal charms there's also
random stickers and the plushies of
course again are also still on sale so
I'm going to put the link in my chat if
you guys I'm waiting on ship interested
Corporation Hey where's my small stuff
the small stuff all of them on my my
backpack but then just keep it in my
house so say you go out with that stuff
no no no no no no I just look at it I
put in like a a glass case and I'm like
yeah cool also can't forget the plushies
I keep my bement the plushies give me
all of these line them up on my bed so
the whole regular restocked item oh
they're regular restocked item oh there
is oh nice so I don't know whenever you
want them gra them nice well well well
so that was just a reminder and then
there's uh I guess a re announcement
that we have yeah kind of a a re oh wait
hold on a sec first did we mention the
figures we've already talked about the
little figures
right the boxes
yeah they're of yes guess they're random
you mean those random ones right yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah they're part of that
yeah okie dokie well then there's
another thing you guys um that other
thing being we announced something a
little while ago which is a brand new
song right can we show the picture yeah
I showed a picture I think we showed it
during the when we announced
it guys fin have a release date
W sorry the wait sorry for the wait you
guys but the song will be released uh a
music video for it will be released on
Janu son of a you would think that I
would Janu no January 11th January 11th
2024 12 a.m. jst so when the clock turns
to January 11th hooray hurrah the song
will release on the official Hol live
English Channel so make sure that you
guys check it out I'm probably going to
do a little unarchived karaoke
beforehand to lead into it
so check out our new
song can you play it am on that
ukulele play
it play it D it whoa the uke showed
up I'm ready wait that can you can we
can do that now yeah we can do it now it
shows up in the groups
cool
let's go ready to
[Music]
party it's a cute song I hope you guys
will enjoy it um yeah silly it's like a
silly one I think you guys like it it's
silly and
cute
changed exciting soon TM soon very
soon flashbacks War flashbacks every
time someone says T he [\h__\h] being
targeted oh anyway
uh that's that's really about it and
then we also just kind of wanted to play
some lethal company today together
because you know only seems fitting
funny that we all join the fry together
that was that was a good time someday we
got to get on those more expensive moons
we'll we'll be able to do it yeah maybe
since this is the first myth collab of
2024 do we want to say something nice I
don't know goals or so together down the
line um give a not a speech just say
something I don't know just short
comment this know I should start I
should start you know what'll put the
pressure on Mor um because I'll be the
example okay because I was today's
captain and I did I did betray my entire
ship go ahead and take the punishment
that is starting off um so let's see
2024 since the number four is included
in the year I've decided that this year
I'm going to go um 5 million per um hard
and so I hope you guys will support me
hard real hard um next month a bunch of
things are happening there's um a
special stream on Valentine's um that's
going to be um about love but not
romantic love it's going to be love
bonic love love of there's going to be a
charity stream on Valentine's
daying for like 12 hours so look forward
to that um I'm not going to announce the
charity or anything like that for a
little bit but that's the plan right now
so look forward to that and then I'm
announcing something big next month um
two big things actually one is
significantly bigger than the
other it's it's the it's the big it's
the big thing um and so I'll be doing a
24-hour stream before that so wow
[Music]
yeah so look forward to that I'm going
to work really really hard this year um
and I love I love Holo and all my
friends and um I'm having a lot of fun
thanks to you guys and I think this year
is going to be amazing um amazing let's
keep having tons of fun together and um
yeah that's all I wanted to say
anyway next up uh yeah let's go by the
line uh well well well we have re that
looks so
stupid you're perfect we have
recently we have recently expanded
gotten a new
generation um who are doing their best
working hard U but I'm I you know I hope
that as myth we can still do a lot of
fun things together it's a new year so
let's let's do some cool stuff myth my
cutest gen mates thank you for a
wonderful year 20123 and on to another
one with more power than ever more
energy than ever let's be
strong go go home
[Music]
baby let's not lose to the new energetic
girls all right we're still young and py
py we have it in our nerves and in our
jeans we we are we are the strongest
let's
go I'm not
wear next to wearing pants to go I I
want to I want to actually get mushy
gushy for a second mush mushy gushy I
apologize um I just want to I want to
say a genuine thank you to not only my
Miss girlies but also to uh everybody
watching right now for your patience
with me as I uh get my personal life and
all of all of its things together and
the time that I've been away I I really
do appreciate it all of your sweet
messages uh that they do make it back to
me and your fan mail makes it back to me
and my myth girls who are patient with
me and they check in on me and they they
say hi and they they invite me to do
things and they wish me happy holidays
and all of that stuff I want to say
thank you I appreciate it very much and
I hope to be strong for my Miss girls in
2024 because I do I do want this to be I
want this to be a happy fun strong year
um with with Miss H live so thank you
everybody happy happy New Year
everybody nice nice nice good well said
Kuba well you guys said a lot of things
you want to say something too you guys
already said a lot of the things want to
say but I hope that this wait am I muted
what no no I hear you you're here what
oh oh I muted her cuz like she was
doubling in the game and here wow she
M you were double at some
point I can't believe you you were
saying things so far damn it I was
please repeat everything for
me well
anyways no I just wanted to say you know
um it's been a wonderful wonderful time
with you guys with chat with everyone um
I hope 2024 is filled with more fun
things and exciting things and let's
let's let's all do our best let's have
fun thank you always everyone to you
guys love you love you
too yeah
right back at
you I guess it's my turn it's your
turn detective yeah it's been really you
know the time has gone by so fast it's
still crazy to me you know approaching
fourth year pretty much oh that crazy oh
dear you know we've been holding strong
and we've been we've been doing so much
everybody's always so busy so um I hope
this year we get to have more fun
together and also get you know some a
little bit of time to relax and and
chill but also do the stuff that we
enjoy cuz you know that's what we're
here for cuz we enjoy it yay y
yay and also I will be having my
birthday stream tomorrow
is Studio 3D special happy
Birthday birth I can't believe we're
only 5 days into the year what the hell
six not crazy yeah I'm excited I'm my
birthday everybody make sure to mark it
on your calendar if you haven't already
yes so p.m PST 8 p.m.
EST
tomorrow I'm my bir I'll be awake I'll
be there yay thank you can't miss out on
that it's going to be exciting I got
some
stuff okay well after this you guys may
have seen But Advent kimono reveals have
been delayed they're after this they
start in 50 minutes right
exciting they'll be matching with us
yeah their first outfit so cool I wonder
how I want to see yeah they're probably
nervous it's
true remember our first reveals we were
just like oh God why more nervous than
the no I realized something recently now
it's my turn to get like a little mushy
gushy I guess y in the beginning we like
we really didn't know we were doing like
at all and it was just five of us you
know like kind of fumbling around in the
dark and trying to figure out like what
what kind of identity is holoen going to
have and now that it's gotten so big
right the group has gotten so big I
don't know it is kind of like a family
to be honest I didn't like saying that
before but I do kind of get that feeling
you know it's it's expanded our our
little Holan family has expanded quite a
bit and I really appreciate all of you
guys being here beside beside me and and
all the fans of myth to kind of like
grow along with us and grow together and
I don't know I'm just I'm really
thankful you know to you guys and the F
and and I hope I hope we can still keep
having a great time together you know
and and just thanks for supporting us
for so long yeah thank
you thank you thank you myth fans myth
fans you guys are the
best we love you thank you for
supporting us for such a long time
yeah been here from the beish star from
the from the
yeah it's okay you're still moving on
our hearts yeah yeah
oh it I can't seem to send everybody to
shiori's stream but I wish I could
just go there
yeah she first I believe she's first
yeah all right guys you know take lots
of screenshots and give them lots of
support I'm sure they're very very
nervous right now need your look so good
I know watch birthday then yeah so
please look forward to it and um yeah
all right thank you for watching today
everybody thank you everyone hope you
guys have a wonderful rest of the
morning afternoon evening I guess we can
sayi okay 3 2 1
Tim thank you bye everybody
byebye bye bye bye bye
bye bye bye-bye
[Music]
bye