[Music]
okay
oh now
now now I think oops now I think they
can hear us k key can you hear us oh
yeah
yeah k
key I'm a witch hello hello what's up
gang it's your boy shiori Nolla oh
actually I'm going to turn this around
because my hands are behind you oh where
are you putting them
I will be putting my hands on some
ghosts today yeah we're going to beat
them up beat them up beat him up we're
GNA scare him out of here cuz I already
I already was uh experiencing some some
staff members uh being like being like
freaked out about us getting ghosts in
here I mean I don't I don't blame them I
have a story but I don't know if I
should share it oh share it share it
okay so my one of my aunts used to work
at some corporate building somewhere one
of your what she worked at a corporate
building yeah one of my aunts not my
aunts I don't have an aunt and uh what
happened was she had to lay off people
so she laid off someone and let's just
say the next day they died um in that
same building so they died in the same
building the person that was laid off
anyway if if someone was laid off here
and might have done that like I guess we
could have accidentally summoned them
and for that I
apologize we could oh my God wait wait
okay this is really interesting topic
but at the same time it's kind of
terrifying uh and scary to talk about
it's what you
wanted well welcome everybody today we
are going to be experiencing some
occultic activities perhaps yeah with
takanashi Kiara and shoi Nolla in fact I
think they're processing me already I
can't even look like one way yeah I'm
also confused where to look um actually
let me fix myself I don't need to fix
anything are you are you are you excited
yeah I'm excited oh wait look straight
yeah cuz I feel like oh it fixes both of
us okay okay okay oh you want to do it
again I'm looking I'm looking straight
to your eyes it's very pretty three two
one wow you're
sparkling did it work wait did it
work I'm making awkward eye contact oh
wait no it doesn't work for you okay
okay maybe can I do it here wait wait
wait I what if I what if I what if I
press this thing yeah I hope this
doesn't mess anything up
no no it's okay it's okay I can fix you
oh you can okay good please fix
me it's kind of working though there you
go see
see I am I am the sacrifice okay
wonderful so in this occultic stream as
you can already tell we have prepared a
Luigi Ouigi Ouija oua Ouija the actual
pronunciation Ouija oua a Ouija board
Ouija board luiga board and as an extra
here we have a a similar board
with a pendulum a beautiful pendulum
yeah yes so we can move that around just
like in Charmed have you watched Charmed
the show the TV show no I don't watch TV
I only watch Let's Plays I don't watch
TV either but I watched it like long
time ago cuz it's a really old TV show
with like free witches they're sisters
wait that's not the that's not the
wisney one right with like that's
something else Hocus Pocus okay okay
that one I don't know okay okay you know
one I barely remember it I just remember
three witches and they were all partying
or something oh okay no they were not
really
partying sometimes maybe maybe they were
Charmed
what okay so uh isn't this nice by the
way yeah real
candles real yeah do you want to like uh
I want to let let me blow on this
yeah yours is I don't know where this
but it reached mine it reached mine oh
yeah okay that works here with my
Phoenix Powers I shall turn them on
again um okay hold on let me try it
again
okay wow with two hands
hand okay popular
Kow okay okay
yeah mine's getting hot your is kind of
dead I know it's just like me there you
go I fixed it we don't want to we don't
want to scare the ghosts away not scare
them scare them who knows if they're
even here yet I think there's one over
here n n who is that
she want me I have one of those as Wawa
cute wait put her here why you get
sacrifice I got punch I want to test
something okay so oh what are you
touching I think I felt
that I will hold your mouth and your
nose let's see if you can breathe I
can't
breathe it sounds it sounds like you're
not really suffering I'm
suffering I I can't bre oh you're let go
[Music]
gently pet the Shi yeah and then wow
that's just like my
childhood how's it feel uh it feels like
a light tab going to bring out the Luna
next the what love chka what you
say okay okay here you get the sh we
back okay protect her so that she does
not get controlled by the ghosts now
she's going to be The
Bodyguard okay she'll protect us yeah
she's real mhm so we have some questions
prepared uh some are from you guys some
are from us and one question is from
Yago oh you missed him but I actually
while I was prepping I saw Yago and I
was like yo yo because he looked into my
room when I was like preparing all of
this it was already dark and I already
had the candles on and everything and
and he very curiously looked inside I
was like
hi yeah today I I'm I'm getting some
ghosts in here do you do you want to ask
something to the ghosts and he looked
delighted he was smiling so much and he
he was really happy to see the setup he
was very interested and he had to think
a while about the question but we I
think we should start off with his
question okay out of respect um but
first do you want to ask the uh ghosts
if they're even there right now all
right yeah of course I'm the uh what is
the there's like a rule here I think
for seanes I don't remember I haven't I
haven't done them but first off you're
supposed to say like hello are you of
the Sun or the moon oh I can't see where
the freaking Sun here
is but otherwise you have to ask are you
are you a good ghost or a bad ghost no
way no well that's what I'm hoping the
way you ask what what's wrong I'm being
I'm being polite or should I ask like
are you there yeah and then and then and
then they're supposed to answer okay but
you're also supposed to have like both
hands on wa you asking was that your
question yeah are you
there wow wow I think I think they're
here W I did not expect that answer at
all that was a
surprise good job you can already talk
to them yeah yeah wa should I be should
it be in Japanese
what already on yes so is that supposed
to are we supposed to reset can can you
can you give us a sign can you give us a
sign
oh did you guys hear that yeah I think
the ghost gave us a sign yeah thank they
gave us a peace
sign okay I'm going to ask a a question
now about yakan he asked
um how to get more muscular uhoh yes I
think the ghosts will know the answer to
this here we go dear ghosts of the H
Life Studio how will how will Yago get
more
muscles okay we go it's
moving oh my God it's oh my god wow this
is crazy wow what word is it going to be
is that the letter s it stopped it
stopped on the S what's that supposed to
mean we'll we'll see is there another
letter goes where where is this leading
us
yeah oh hey I was thinking that answer
to question if this is what I'm
thinking
okay interesting what's this that's that
can't be all right oh it's moving it's
moving it's
moving oh is that what letter is this e
wow is this ghost me
actually you know the answer already
yeah it was the first thing that came up
in my mind the answer was clear all
along and we didn't need to ask the
ghost but we don't need to ask the ghost
let's just buy it oh oh oh an R an R the
ghost was a little bit like shaking
there and wasn't sure where to go for a
moment but it found the r good job ghost
yeah good job what's next oh yeah let
this be a spelling before you
ghost ghost spelling oh that's a oh oh
oh
wow what
that what's that sound okay
okay okay oh oh it's going faster wow
it's excited to finish this beautiful
word I know I
steroid wait did you did you miss a
letter no okay no no I if anything
letter no if anything it ghost ghost is
the ghost is the little B spell uh here
okay yes I see
I wait wait what what word was this
steroids thank you ghost oh wow yeah
we'll let y know we'll let y thank you
okay I thought I thought I thought was
magically going to go into stairs I'm
like okay
oh maybe this ghost is ripped H ghost
are you ripped
yeah oh
they're not only RI but they're ripping
us off yeah S I only see an s e s is an
e yeah okay reset reset so let's we we
have covered the Yago question let's go
to the next one I have a
bunch
um uh Shi I would like you to answer
this question all right all
right I'll put it on the screen
what is iris's last
name anything and come up with
anything I see I see all right all right
wow okay okay ghost there I hope you're
full of Hope and and stuff wow you know
anything about Hol live oh heck yeah you
been they do you've been haunting this
corporate office for oh crap I think I
possessed I've been haunting this place
for who knows how long right wow do you
feel the connection yeah I feel like
it's connected connected the world
connect the world oh crap this is long
awkward wow I wow I wonder I wonder what
her last name is her secret last name
that's of an eye yeah Oh no you're not
hey wow you you know her name oh heck
yeah do you know how to spell it but in
nongo
oh oh man
I wow but what's the last what's the
last letter oh oh I'm feeling something
unexpected
unexpected I
would scar oh but it's not over it's not
over I think there another letter never
death
perhaps Iris yeah she's Iris IR GRE yeah
oh does that have some particular
meaning I wonder I think it means that
she's going to RIS people up m is she
going to raise the ghost up ghost ghost
do you do you want to be do you want to
be he question do you want to be raised
by Iris ghost
yeah I think I think they're
very
confused wait this is not working with
the Ouija
board I need to bring out an extra tool
really quickly yeah okay oh I can feel
the magnet magnetic ISM right yeah no
there's no magnets involved well because
this is real it's real oh yeah the
ticism for real there's really no magnet
yeah do you see do you see the word
there an un no oh heck
yeah so um dear ghosts of the
pendulum uh do you want to raise up Iris
oh heck yeah they said
maybe good it it almost had like a a bad
landing there going somewhere else but
we understand everything you asking us
go it's okay okay okay here bring us
back beautiful pendulum uh let's go to
the next question mhm next one
um okay this is this is for
shii like see
yeah okay you maybe no you can use even
one however you feel like which
whichever you feel is more speaking to
you and speaking to the ghosts um how
long has your yogurt been sitting in
your fridge wow this is like the
equivalent of asking me about my my
credit card
number all right ghost are you aware do
you also haunt my apartment by any
chance all right maybe maybe Shi is the
ghost actually yeah I've been dead all
along
guys H I think it's I think it's
struggling to figure out how long it's
been yes Shi herself doesn't even know
perhaps well I don't keep in track the
the amount of days perhaps like maybe
months at this point yeah for those who
don't know you can still eat it you want
to eat it for me what kind of yogurt is
it I think like some fruit yogurt fruit
y I'm not the biggest yogurt fan but uh
you can have it as a party if there's
two too bad that we probably won't meet
anymore before I leave to B bad I see so
unfortunate
oh I wonder where it is five what is
this month's days
weeks oh three
months you know this ghost is actually
I'm pretty sure the
yogurt what what why why shod why well
okay when I first when I first arrived
in Japan I was like naturally I'm a bit
intimidated cuz I can't make crap like I
don't know what the heck this says I
don't know where to go so I asked my
manager like HMA please get me food I'm
too scared to go out oh so so HMA got me
some groceries okay it was is that much
groceries SP the way you brought a
freaking box and I thought there was
like oh wow you got me like a week's
worth of stuff it's like no it was
something else and then and then you
gave me like I think you gave me
jagaro the the snack and then and then I
I received like yogurt so I ate
everything but you ask your manager to
help you with groceries because you're
new to Japan and himma brings you uh
yogurt and jagaro there might have been
like one other thing but I think that
whatever that was was is definitely not
that memorable that's
so well to be fair they were also having
like mysterious box of merch and they
were carrying that at the train and I
guess like people people were like
really suspicious so but come on had my
yogurt you think yogurt's worthy of me
but but yeah you can have the yogurt
when I'm gone oh for people who don't
know jagaro is kind of like potato chips
but in the form of fried fried french
fries like it's good yeah long long
french fries but they're really hard H
and crunchy yeah yeah yeah there they're
good I like them yeah but they're not
really something I would feed you with
if you're desperate uh about food kaha
gets it kiaha gets it yeah I was get you
some some proper food but okay um let's
ask is is is HMA is HMA like
G yeah there you go see we're all chill
this is all in oh we try our best it's
all Jo done and we don't succeed that's
okay okay so three months was it
yeah probably longer soon enough
honestly maybe eat it tomorrow no it
honestly the the date might be still be
fine no what I was going to do is I was
just going to leave it and it'll be like
a momento like you know like a imagine a
fossil you know or force feed HMA with
it well no I I think I should I think we
should leave the H live office and put
like a like a glass case over it like
this is this is Shor yogurt oh yeah yeah
yeah you can have like a whole life
English Museum yeah yeah yeah yeah I
like the idea okay while I'm turning
away I'm going to get a new question she
Entertain Entertain the audience
okay what's up gang how you holding up
you like
ghost how about I ghost you no oh not
again not again Shi okay next question
is I shall answer this
myself how many bodies does mum hide in
her
basement oh let's reset this dear
ghosts how many go how many ghosts how
many bodies does m hide in her basement
is this like a math question yes
oh oh it's not sure it's too many to
count maybe yeah or maybe it can't
count okay oh we have is that maybe a 23
or a two or three it's it's a it's I
think it's a two for now oh two maybe
two many but then
we wait I should just go to yes
yes there are bodies in how did that not
come to me earlier come to the ghost
earlier yes yes
the E stands for yes yes hi but it's
over 20 apparently because the ghost was
trying to spell out the number with two
and another number oh you could have
still done the ghost could have still
done that come on ghost you feel math G
be more exact please ghost yeah
yeah okay so I have to two again no no
you have to you have to spell it out but
in Roi say it's like what
needu what now come on ghost you're
Japanese aren't you unless you're a
random Foreigner that wandered
in
26 26 26 bodies
dang I think she can like improve that
number though oh yeah I might be one of
them in the
future okay okay okay okay that is uh
scary yeah okay well well well how
about shot what's up I have one question
one question for you for Shori yes what
is the perfect number of cats to own oh
oh okay wow wow ghost what what number
is that they maybe want some ghost cats
go wait dead
cat Callie has one A G what's the
perfect number they're life cats right
all right well assuming this ghost also
owns pets that are ghost cats I think a
decent number would would be you think
the ghost SS I'm getting possessed by a
ghost okay the ghost Is possessing me
right now it's speaking through me it's
going like Yaba Yaba
do two yeah f it two because because
anymore any more might be too expensive
it'll smell probably like piss or hair
and is the ghost telling you all of this
I'm getting possessed by the ghost are
you
[Applause]
okay how do we exer exercise her uh we
got to we got to do
steroids where do get where do you get
steroids I don't Chad do you guys know
where to probably a pharmacist
right need a res uh uh Des prescription
right I I mean I guess so but I'm sure
like the ghosts could
theoretically ghost them from the ghost
Market maybe
oh I don't know what you mean shot
you're speaking in riddles to me oh
blame the
ghost okay so wait two cats I I think
the ghost likes two cats because they
have a buddy and you're not getting like
you're not losing sleep with three cat
M honestly I was kind of looking forward
to it saying at least free because I
have two already and I I maybe need a a
push to get another one oh well you know
but okay I guess yeah if you want a
third I think the Ghost says go for it
really yeah really ghost yeah because
you're taking care of another
cat Well for now for now I I'm not ready
yet so two is fine if the ghost said
nine would you gotten like nine then yes
oh I think in the future that is where
I'm heading anyway oh yeah slowly but
surely you're not you not you're not
heading
there no no but you have cats too right
yeah but one of my cats are like it's
shedding on the floor right
I you're such a bad cat tell me about it
maybe I can help you with that wait you
have you have tips for it like a walkr
like a guide maybe yeah what do you
think is causing it I think it's because
um I'm not I'm not there right now and
oh only now well they did it before but
I think it's when they're not getting
enough attention like cuz you know
naturally when you're busy with this
what but you mean [\h__\h] because I
used to have a family cat who like when
she was not happy she would pee on
something luckily they don't do that for
mine lucky is that I guess so because
like the poop you can just scoop up I
guess but the pee you have to wash
everything it stains the reputation of
the house true too so poop is better I
guess yeah yeah and they only do it in
like the formal dining room in the
formal dining room yeah that sounds so
fancy yeah it's a it's a formal it's a
formal poop I guess they choose the
fanciest place to it's a fancy fancy
poop what's his what's the cat's name
pepper pepper yeah pepper the
pooper pepper the Ripper pepper he's
about to rip it beade let it rip pepper
is he old I don't think so not by cat
standards will he be forgiven for
pooping it depends on how it is it's a
sign of
love poop on your bed all over oh
thankfully they don't do they don't do
that enough for racist cat I'm pretty
sure Lil Man I think I think he did he
poop there or he peed
there I've had a cat what my recent cat
also like my current cats peed on my bed
but not on purpose it was when they were
like kind of under uh an an Anastasia
Anastasia
an Ania I know what you're talking about
from like like uh some surgery and then
they were like dead and they just peed
on the bed cuz I was letting them lay
there a now I have a stain on my bed
well it's it's a stain of love Yeah Yeah
Anastasia who's
Anastasia okay so the perfect number is
two yeah next question according to the
ghost I guess that's probably yeah it's
better than one for sure depends on your
space I think
okay okay I have a personal question
somebody asked this in the hashtag but I
personally really want to know the
answer to this
[Music]
yeah
t you may not know about this but
there's a in the Minecraft Ian server
Ian Minecraft server there is a
mysterious
hole that I have fallen into and other
people have fallen into too yeah and it
was always a question who made that hole
because it was definitely man-made like
human-made or whatever made someone made
it who knows it who it was that's what I
want to find out who made it who made
the hole we still don't know because the
hole is um not in the original map like
if you get our seat and open it aresh
people checked if the hole was there
they investigated and no it wasn't there
this is real ghost activities maybe the
hole was made for you for for me yeah
yeah well for me to fall into yeah for
me to die everyone has their own hole
that's made for
them it seems like several people have
had to share this one hole so that's a
skill
issue well I'll ask the ghost ghosts of
the past of the Minecraft who made the
hole okay it's
thinking it's thinking think
harder oh it's it's going
somewhere
what
oh H what comes after oh H oh oh oh it's
going faster oh man it's pissed it's
angry at the hole it also fell into it
and that's exactly how it dieders
M okay om M that already I feel like
it's telling me
something is it misspelling a Amilia
Watson unless it's like a gender
bent omelia omo wait where's
um hold up the ghost setting wait is it
OMG or om e om Omen oh
oh there it is wow uh wow the ghosts
have decided who to point the finger to
and who to blame yeah Omega isn't that
Greek
Omega shy do you even like you joined
after you don't really know Omega really
but I you've heard the tales yes the
tales of the Minecraft so I want okay
while we're on this topic Omega I want
to ask you are are you still with
us oh my God sorry my
OCD hold up my OCD it's really OCD oh
crap I killed
some no it's a no it's a no Omega omeg
god what happened I think omega's
possessing that one
candle okay okay yeah it's definitely
definitely a no there okay Omega is not
with us anymore oh they're they're
omegon om exactly but Omega what was
your purpose what you were there so
shortly and just not didn't really do
anything what was your
purpose oh is it go for a number it
seems like it but why why would it be a
number what is that number supposed to
mean
oh zero see Zero
purpose is that what it
[Music]
means okay oh God can can I ask you any
any hey where are you going omeg God
what what do
you goodbye wait no I was not finished I
still wanted to ask more it's pissed off
it's oh my God that's the one ghost we
could have like you know had like a good
conversation with because it was a whole
life ghost
man man that's too
bad I was hoping the purpose would be
past the butter past the butter yeah
pass the butter yeah and why are you
missing some butter no it's a it's a
reference to a show I like what show
Rick and Morty Rick and Morty I did
watch that oh you didn't yeah I did I
think I watched all season oh yeah I
think they're making like an anime like
a joke anime episode oh so that'll be
interesting
oh pickle trick yeah pickle
trick okay let's go to the next
question how about okay
[Music]
sh
one question yeah Uno Uno Uno Uno out of
all of of Holo Yen whose desk has
suffered the most a
by I'm trying to it's kind
of I I feel like yeah I feel like my
answer would be
that am I am I am I allowed to say okay
for for like specific context um I
pushed her during a craft game collab so
I'm trying to be I'm trying to be like a
little bit nicer so I not mentioning oh
you pushed your table no you pushed her
no yeah no no I I specifically sought
her out for her table just to push it
while she was playing the no I did push
her into game the crap game game club
right yeah yeah I saw some clips from
that yeah she she was I think I I became
her more
yardy so what do you think the ghost say
oh well well this isn't coming from me
definitely not but but for the for the
ease of spelling things out then I think
the ghost would wow wow I think the
ghost is actually going to say goodbye
no no ghost come on tell us something
wow or maybe what do you think wow it's
it's it's nervously shimmying towards
this wow what letter is this a
oh but it's it's shaking it's shaking in
it it's scared
of scared I don't know about that I
think it's just trying to be nice maybe
the ghost is is 's old desk or so maybe
yeah oh oh oh man that's that's so far T
no that's so far I think the ghost wants
to go over
here oh yeah yeah here I'll help you out
and then we're going back thank you
second ghost the the ghost is continuing
going to go over here
um wow wow after that crab game Cool up
I bet that second desk has been
destroyed did she did she bang her desk
a lot well I don't know but um I killed
her I killed her a lot no my prise in my
defense it was self-defense guys sure
sure that's what they all say it is
selfdefense well all right next question
cute
though next question is for
me uh it's not nor life
related uh but it's very much an
important question this week M cuz i'
I've been recently watching football uh
the European Championship that's going
on right now unfortunately Austria has
been you know yeed out a uh but the
question
is who will win cuz the finale is this
Sunday and it's England versus Spain so
how about we move this way dang a sports
question guys Sports question whatever
the ghost thinks I will believe and then
bet on so how about there's no you know
there's no
like like country names on here but
let's say let's say yes is Spain and no
okay then let's ask if if Spain will win
uhhuh
2024 yeah and yes or no or unknown or
maybe who knows but I would like a clear
answer please ghosts all right I'll be
I'll be a commentator during this part
yeah okay let's go ghost will the Amigos
win the Amigos or will it be the French
Amigos French England England oh
shoot will it be will it be the British
Amigos then yeah will will the will the
Spanish Amigos are you going to win this
Sunday
oh Spanish Amigos yeah will you win
yes
Vos V andos now to see if that comes
true let's go England you can't win the
ghost said so sorry ghosts it is so over
it's she over it's over what will the
score be oo good question
okay man I wonder if be a no a no no no
I need to know tell me what will the
score be so oopsie that was uh an
accident by the ghost what's the what's
the maximum score in sports for this
anyway there's no maximum there's just
like a minimum I guess which is
zero but at least one for one team so
that somebody wins that'll extend
forever okay okay we're circling for for
what number could this be is it a seven
a six wow it's a four it's a four four
for
Spain because it's the win for Spain
yeah For the Win For the
Win okay okay I honestly I personally
don't really like I didn't I know I know
Spain is really good yeah maybe you
don't probably really
know you know who's really good and all
that in Europe but Spain is really good
Spain is very known to be good I don't
really you know you know support them
specifically but I guess now I do
because um this told me so maybe can do
another question with this yeah yeah do
you want to do you want to use the
pendulum I can try for the next one sure
okay next
one
uh wait can I ask one unrelated thing sh
because I don't think this really works
as a question for these things CRA I
dropped it no found I found it um I've
been told I just personally feel a
little bit a little bit offens Ed but
also entertained by this so I've heard
you call Boromir brir and Aragon
airhorn yeah air horn well in my defense
I'm really bad with names and English
airhorn hey he's a lovely air horn okay
he goes like bazon do you read the books
or watch a movie or what no I was watch
a movie that was my first time ever
seeing it okay I I knew nothing about it
I might have seen like clips of it well
you watch just one or all of them uh we
watched I think like all of them yeah
yeah yeah ah yeah right uh so after all
these movies and all these hours with
them you still don't know how can you
can we get maybe the help of for this we
need this one can I get the help of the
ghost could you please attempt to
spell their names for which one feel
free to start with whichever the ghost
wants to start with bro I barely
remember character names oh crap uh
please spell out their names hold up I'm
trying to remember look at the chat I'm
I can't confuse her confuse her with
wrong spellings I'm trying to remember
the main character's
name I'm going to okay it's over guys
it's over I don't remember their names
let's make up some good ones oh yeah
come on ghost if it's wrong it's your
fault I'm
going okay which one are we going for
first
I I'm going to okay we're going to go
for I think it
was the ghost is nervous right here e
that's an e we're going for Aragorn it
was Aragorn right uhhuh yeah AR yeah R
yeah yeah yeah that sounds about right
yeah ah a uhhuh a uhhuh uh okay this uh
it sounds similar yeah g g g for God I
don't know what I'm doing now this is
the confusing part they could do like
have some fantasy spelling with an H
there to trick me but we're going to
skip that screw your hes there's no
there's no h in okay what that era era
Gore go go go where the wow is it or r r
yeah maybe and
then oh Aragorn I can't see is that an N
okay yeah was it Aragorn or was it
Aragon um
um it was not you you messed up in the
first letter but it sounds the same yeah
it's with an a goodbye and I think the r
is uh un uness wait was there an extra r
at the end there hey at least it's not
air horn that's a lot that's like an
improvement yeah thank you ghost for
helping shieldy learn how to spell the
name I don't even remember the main
character's name I was just going to
call him Hobbit at this point his name
is Frodo okay
you have to remember him he worked so
hard he did he did he he like sacrificed
everything well maybe he should have
stayed behind for his legacy because now
that he's gone I'm not going to remember
anything what do you mean stay behind
for his legacy maybe he shouldn't have
went to like uh the elf land you
know yeah but he's retired let him
retire I guess he's been for some [\h__\h]
yeah who who's his best friend again he
was best boy hold on don't don't tell me
I'm going to get it wrong but he's my
baby he gives me the name of Gibby but I
know it's not GI that's they're kind of
going more towards gimly there but
that's not that's the yeah his bestie is
Sam Sam by who's gimy then gimy is the
dwarf oh okay she's so fun yeah they're
different characters I like it I might
do Star Wars in the future oh are you a
fan of it no it's okay I even tried like
doing watch alongs and I had to give up
after like the second we started from
the first like chronological
releases yeah
one it's because like mostly because
that the the dude that pissed me off
dude the the Han Solo pissed me off oh
pisses me off Han Sol you know Han Solo
yeah he's like the girl goes like I love
you and he's like I know yoinks yeah
yeah okay one question U board Did Han
Solo shoot
first yes thank you thank you I knew
that didn't have tell me that okay I
have to watch you remember the stuff all
I know it's like I'm your
father okay okay okay and next
question next question uh I will I will
try to contact the ghosts for this one
um okay who amongst the Holan managers
has suffered the
most
H that's
weird what was that it doesn't seem to
want to go for any letters but that was
a a light flash yeah wasn't it is there
like also a thunderstorm today it are we
outside was there a thunderstorm yeah
it's the perfect night for this you know
yeah but what does this mean can you can
you
maybe um flash twice in uh on the or
flash when flash once when I am right
with my assumption yeah okay Stu
definitely not my
manager is it is it gooda
manager no is it Kia's
manager no some some of the girls are
sharing you know so it could be you know
is it uh ena's
manager
no who's in US manager right now I don't
I figure it out wait who's in haven't
had enough they they soon maybe they'll
have enough enough enough enough okay so
it's not uh blink uh uh blink twice
flash twice if uh if jenma is
okay oh she's not wait was it once or
[Laughter]
twice
okay there was some lag there
ghost is
thinking wow did you guys see that flash
I'm also blinded yeah me
too thank God okay that was in the
lights of his
lightning as long as jenma is okay then
ena's manager can continue to suffer I
don't mind that what about what about
hen mama is hmama okay twice if if hmama
is
okay once that might be it that might be
it you're okay
no I think that's it HMA is not okay
you're okay HMA needs to be safe no no
HMA I will save you
HMA oh no oh ghost ghost has ghost has a
lot of information I think this ghost is
biased I'm watching you she only have a
good one for you it's a topic that we
both are interested in uh but I think uh
you can ask to goost for a good answer
uh no okay I'll just ask uh the second
part of this question for now mhm when
there if there's a new Fire Emblem
game what will be like the title for
example we had Fire Emblem engage or
free houses they didn't even get engaged
in that game started but they wear a lot
of rings I know no engagement I have all
the Rings now oh cool I've been gifted
all of the you get where did he get it I
see no I've been gifted them I don't
know where they're from okay but I no
they had an official logo on it so I
think they're official oh crap I need to
find them then and then put them on
every single thing what if you have an
extra finger though H what oh wait how
many are there I count I don't know cuz
the the main character they definitely
had more than one I think uh at some
point on one finger like they were like
overloaded on rings I think I don't
remember but I guess you can get tow
rings out of them 13 13 V machines in
Japan what oh cool I need to find them
then all right electric Boogle divorce
okay that's some good on now can you
spell us uh can you guys a ghost to
spell out the the name of the next fire
Blom game I see I
see all right what does the ghost think
it will be uh let's see the ghost really
can check the was it K
Teo what who's behind F actually now I
think about it if there's going to be a
new Fire w it be for like the new
console they're making a new one aren't
they you mean switch but fire is also on
other consoles no wait was it well the
new one the new one if you're going to
make a new one I don't think it'll be on
the switch anymore maybe maybe a switch
too yeah switch second switch yeah oh D
was Nintendo and oh Nintendo and int is
exclusive okay it's exclusive okay yeah
okay I
think see well I'm kind of like my
assumption is they might make a remake
of the old ones oh yeah have you played
all of them no uh actually three houses
was my first one yeah wait same yeah
yeah when did you play it like I tried
it years ago but I didn't finish into
like also years ago maybe so you you you
started playing it when it kind of came
out 2019 actually that's I played it uh
yeah yeah we play wa didn't it come out
in 2020 though I I don't remember it's
like one of those wonderful played it
around that time it would be nice if
they had a farming version of Fire
Emblem and you can kill and you can use
your bodies as fertilizer but
anyway I think oh September 2019 ah oh
okay wow it's been years free houses
that can't believe engaged was kind
of yes it was it was
engaging know it
was there were some cute characters yeah
I like the bar Barefoot girl a lot the
Barefoot girl oh uh was that the the
monochrome hands hairs I like her to I
like her to yeah I went for I was going
for um either two characters either the
red boy a diant or the blonde boy
because the blonde boy's been there from
like the beginning so it's like okay
yeah she only likes the boys and I like
the
girls but yeah there were some cute ones
but it's just like there's too many
characters and they don't get enough
screen time yeah free houses was so cool
because of the free houses man yeah
that's so cool and they could kill each
other but that
sad killing okay so the next Fire Emblem
might be might be might be a wow
possibly what a one of the options wow
it's it's going to be a an R
wow wow maybe maybe ooh what a what a
copout is this going to be
huh ooh what if what what if it goes to
oh yeah W I didn't expect that rewind or
so is it
rewind
yes wow yeah I mean that's honestly a
good title yeah what are we rewind like
a YouTube
Rewind oh but you would say that that is
the name for
remake maybe interesting I wouldn't mind
that because I haven't really played any
others besides the most 2 yeah I tried
playing Awakening though uh for the I
think ah the phone game the the the DS
or something yes something like that
yeah I I had just Scout one out oh cuz
when I played engage like I realized
like I I've seen a lot of the um
characters before yeah but a lot of them
look so similar like there's like a
million Mars or
whatever that's really interesting and I
was so confused like if I played some
older ones and maybe I'll understand in
the future I'll be honest there's this
weird section where like you know how
you go to sleep and they show up in your
room right and that's me to be like the
equivalent of I I don't know like the
Romantic scenes like get the heck out of
my room who the heck are at least make
it like a consistent character I have
the highest support with you know yeah I
don't think I cared much for that one
yeah like get out of my room you creeps
I yeah marf buff mu Grill marf red marf
all the marks there was yeah different
colored marks I I did like the gaml
though I did like the the ring mechanic
it's just the characters the the
supports were not that great in my
opinion they only give like maybe four
sentences and support move on to B that
was it but you remember it so well I I
already forgot so much I can't really
Yap about it that's okay that's okay but
I I just remembered I suffered
especially at the end at the last fight
were you doing like hard V or something
no but I I don't know it was still so
difficult I died uh like at least once
and had to redo this the whole thing
over at least maybe twice actually yeah
I think um there was only one part I
circled with and it was like I was in
hard mode why was I why would I do that
oh why did I do that you go there you go
you're a gamer no I did classic normal
no I played on hard what the [\h__\h] you
were nuts I know anymore I don't I don't
like challenges I'm in a breeze uh maybe
because like the first time when I
played free houses I played it like on
like normal and then I was like oh okay
now I figured out like the mechanic and
all that so let's go for hard next but
you can still rewind even when somebody
died you just rewind and usually you're
fine you could do that could you do that
with engage actually you could rewind or
no you could that's that's a weird part
I don't know I re am mixing the games up
like together could we not yeah how the
hell did I get through it then oh I just
that's weird oh yeah okay okay they had
a they had a low reason for the last
game at least but for engage it's like
is it just cuz you're a dragon oh okay
yeah yeah I guess so oh okay well I hope
that whenever if it ever comes out that
it comes out soon so we can Yap about it
when while we play get engaged let's get
engaged okay next
question um oh okay um how
about hold life related question
who I don't think the this has the
existence of this has been announced yet
I don't even know it if it exists so
this is not like an announcement of an
announcement but who will be the winner
of the next Holo Mario Kart tournament
do you know like it's kind of a yearly
thing I I do remember the last one but I
think I was a wait during that time or I
was like selling in I also didn't
participate but usually who's really
good at those is uh OK Senai Senai I
think wasn't Mar Senai also good yeah
Mar Senai G is pretty good from like Yen
M but yeah maybe someone like bio is so
could like you know prac I think she was
like already fine yeah and if she
practices more with her gaming skill
like she could probably get up there am
Senai was also really good yeah crony
Ena Ena is consistently like very stable
but I don't know if she could go for a
win to be honest maybe not like not the
competitive Spirit then yeah and we
don't know yet how good Justice is with
Mario Kart that's a good question none
of them have played yet I feel like if
someone were to be good it would be CCE
or Gigi just based on like the vibe
because herb doesn't play many games
right what I was thinking and I don't I
don't think she ever played Mario Kart
I'm not sure I mean she's playing Elden
Elden ring right now is she good at it
guys if you good at Elden ring then
you're Surly good at Mario Kart those
things are connected for sure yeah don't
you love those Mario Kart bosses
uh uh ah a GG maybe yeah
GG I I think so too cuz CeCe has been
driving she hates racing games and she's
been driving for Europe and um actually
that makes sense cuz if you remember the
debut for CeCe uh I'm pretty sure she
crashed a car yes yes yes exactly gii
was like also maneuvering her way
through the streets uh with the help of
the chat but okay with all of this in
mind do
we want to make a guess is difficult is
difficult cuz there like multiple
branches yeah oh not us by the way the
ghost is making a guiss yeah okay what
you think ghost ghost tell us who will
win the next Mario Kart tournament
[Music]
b b do we have anybody
else was that on
purpose ghost what was that that was
that tell us to be gone was that
beo I'm ready for that
okay um what was that supposed to tell
us managers
what ghosts what did you have to say oh
no one of the managers have died oh
no flashbang B will win with a
flashbang okay okay B wait B could also
be ba let's continue yeah for clarity
yeah oh but it already missed a a i yeah
B okay the ghost does not like like to
call her by her nickname it seems It's
be Joe oh proper spelling coolo we like
it proper thank you ghost for your input
I appreciate
that be who won last time
guys ba B won the
really B good but not race game good we
see like she can she can get there be
who
H to to Senai won the last one she's the
one who hosts it she's really good at it
too yeah she's definitely one of the M
good Flex I would definitely be like the
lower level if I tried it oh oh toy tide
oh that's pretty good
tie okay thi TI save lives all right
next
one I still have I still have a a few
good
ones she only have a question for you
what
up do you do you hear voices in your
head
generally I used to you used to I used
to now I think they become
real okay who or what are the voes in
your
hand is the ghost question oh
Wow Let's get into your
brain it's oh slowly oh but not slow
enough oh wow I I yourself or I I
wow wow it's
shaking What's So Scary why are you so
scared IM
imagine I will make you spell it out
until because it's
funny W ghost where are you going is it
I again IMI
IM what could that
mean w pleas spell it out for me so fast
wow wow imagary is I'm confused I can't
keep up anymore are you guys keeping up
Mario Kart wow wow W stop zooming ghost
stop zooming stop ghost
stop goodbye okay okay what was all that
that was that was Imaginary Friends
imaginary friends oh really that yeah a
I used to have like U I had like my my
OC's and we go in like imaginary
adventures together really yeah a now
you don't need the anymore cuz you have
real friends not just imaginary ones
yeah but I still have a voice that keeps
him protected so that's nice they're
like don't eat that
shi the yogurt y don't eat it ah I would
trust them then if that's if it's a
voice telling you that no I think you
should trust it okay
imaginary friends I think um I don't
know how accurate this is but uh someone
told me like not everyone has they're
not able to talk inside her head yeah
yeah yeah yeah that's true I can I
cannot really yeah that it's like yeah
internal monologue yeah that would be
crazy if you can't like think to
yourself I know I guess they just plan
it plan it out like it just comes to
them physically or they say it out loud
I guess maybe they this is one thing
that really bothers me in like animes
and movies or whatever like when mostly
animes I think they just have so many
conversations with themselves alone and
I'm like this is not realistic like
normally you would just think these
things to yourself like you can just
like like have them like give a little
bit of a Reverb on the dialogue so that
it sounds like he's thinking or so
character yeah and they just always talk
out loud but maybe those are the people
who can't think in their head exactly so
all anime characters they just don't
have internal dialogue yeah I could
believe it maybe anime characters they
just don't have that kind of brain I
both of them should have internal
dialogue if there's so many anime
characters that don't have it I think
that's a skill issue
yeah no offense if you don't have
it why did you like yeah they also have
a lot of like external monologue there
yeah I that that it's mostly like a like
a dialogue made with some Supernatural
stuff isn't it yeah that's that's whole
thing you're making a new one right yeah
yeah yeah a trailer of it have you I've
not seen it you're informed I I'm aware
of it I've seen the clips I've seen the
toothbrush oh yeah okay cuz that's my
favorite anime and I've been watching it
for years and they finally after many
years finally now are releasing a new
anime it's been years and people like
everybody was like oh I don't think
anything is like going to be released
ever again and I was like there will be
believe in it and here we are there's a
new season yay yay yeah we rewatched the
we've been rewatching the anime and so
we watched the toothbrush scene together
yay oh for me like one of the things I'm
excited for uh there's this there's this
series called mon no it's not the the
not the movie yeah yeah it's uh it's
like a supernatural thing they're making
a movie out of it oh so I'm excited for
subtitles mon no mon no yeah is it made
by a Japanese uh like yeah yeah yeah um
the the main character is like a like a
medicine seller and he's like demon
exorcist so that's cool I'm excited for
that interesting oh when is that coming
out I'm not sure but they're still going
to have to translate it unless my
josu Janai brain sh did you know because
of the toothbrush scene that's in my
head now did you know that Rea and Ollie
brushed like Ollie brushed rea's teeth
on stream before to like test out the
effects of
it how did how did I go it it was um
it's a good clip I see it's a really
good clip guys look it up it's it's for
dental hyd of
course m m okay uh I have do I have by
the way do I have any like question
yourself that besides the one that I've
written down anything person not that I
can think of where the ghost no my brain
is silent there's a voice in there right
now maybe something like 3D related wow
oh man ghost for those who don't know
yeah yeah do you do you know when the
debut dates are would you mind like
maybe telling us over here oh maybe I
don't know is is this more useful cuz it
has like days oh I don't even remember
the day I just remember the numbers okay
okay give us the numbers wow where is it
going
oh zero yeah if you could see that oh
and then oh where's where's that yeah W
what is this is this wait what month Aug
August yeah okay good okay wow zero
zero so so so smooth like butter wow
yeah 2nd August is yours or for mine
yours okay PD which which in the order
sorry I didn't see the announcement I
guess that's what you guys were
announcing it's just like this morning
what was it which order is it tell me
about it for me advertisement time
oh oh according to the ghost for me it's
uh August 2 and then and then for be
she's the day after so a three and then
you're going to have to like a a week
waiting time and I believe a Reese is I
think is the the 9th or the 10th 9th or
the 10th yeah probably so like a
Saturday probably right yeah yeah and
then the dogs are right after so you're
the first
yeah unexpectedly actually expectedly
you're the first probably because you're
your life life to the debut was the
first your normal debut was the first
right was the sacrificial W you're going
to be sacrificed
y i i um I I may or may not or possibly
I may have seen she will win pretty
already yeah and she looks
beautiful look so
good I'm so excited for it it's so soon
yeah are you
excited I'm not doing my
best it's I I'm sure it'll be
fine can we can we what could we ask
guys do you have any any questions uh
that we can like finish it off off on
like any any spontaneous questions I
still have like a few ones in here but
U most of them I've already used so here
spontaneous when is my food order
coming uh
will she already do a dab in
3D will she I
wonder do you got to tell us oh man tell
ask the ghost of
she will
she hold up you looking for a maybe
maybe's only over
here
maybe okay oh wow it landed on the movie
yeah wow or it should go to the unknown
yeah I know you got to unkn know it so
go what's
the my OCD can only fix this
side the ghost jumped all the way over
excitedly will will HMA get a 3D
model um I was thinking of getting like
a puppet oh just because it'd be funny
how demented is hen Mama right now I
don't think they're demented
will Kiana dance the booty shots I
already did did you see it oh yeah I did
see it I did see and everybody was
saying like oh she only is like her her
f is
spreading that's cute I thought you
talking about my butt was spreading
no I understand I understand I attempt
to spread your your butt no this just
right there and fre is this a Frey W I'm
a good girl is this Frey sh will we it's
40 cute
oh she's so warm over here cuzz you were
holding her this whole time her butt is
wow don't tell them
that cute she W me okay can I ask a
spicy question what's
up I if it's if it's too spicy I've I I
stream you my spice level gets spicy
right to some degree she already lay
down here wow um okay I don't know
what's going on
uh okay I have several questions in my
head
uh so scary sounds did you hear like
that surgery game where you're about to
like put something in and you're
supposed to get it out and not hit the
walls I don't no no no that's not what
it is okay okay um
Shi off the
table where where
where where does uh what
where yeah I need to phrase my question
correctly where what
uh in in uh in regards to
narissa what where I'm coming up with
this on the spot Uh Oh you mean the
ghost right yeah the ghost uh the the
ghost has seen things uhhuh uh I mean I
guess who has
okay the uh go okay the ghost has seen
it and narissa must have seen it perhaps
at some point who knows um where does
shi have a secret
mole I have a mole or you don't even
know about it perhaps I have a mole
secret
mole that well you would only see if a
ghost like I I technically have multiple
secret moles because I have spy
connection
wow okay that's where I'm masking ghost
you know exactly what I'm asking seen
anything I'm a good all right all right
okay I think I think I'm I'm feeling a
traction attraction I don't know the
ghost is being the ghost is going
somewhere where is it going the secret
mole oh oh there's a lot of energy over
here around the feet man I think that's
my are you seeing this no it's going
it's going oh oh oh oh oh on her her
right from there there's a secret mole
on the right foot you have a secret mole
on your right foot I don't think so it
it seems so next time today if you take
a shower or so uh or tomorrow then take
a close look at your right foot no maybe
if I like stick my finger in it it's
like a dark hole to another
dimension like herbs blue flame I do
want to know why that leads to I just
think she's a it reminds me of bleach M
you watch Bleach I I watched a bit of it
yeah I didn't finish it naturally I
didn't I watch it I like the music
though I think I just played a a bleach
game on the phone I mean I Ed bleach for
laundry you do I've never used it before
actually I used Tide Pods bleach Mansion
bleach Mansion yeah I was sponsored long
time
ago okay um I have maybe two or three
more questions yeah do you
know uh this I might have to explain
this do you know of the muffin man
no do you know Casper does that say
something to yeah yeah the the ghost
right yeah my my my my rat or my mouse
I'm not sure what it is but I haven't
seen haven't seen Casper in a while oh I
want to ask the ghosts if they have
Casper among them or
not to see if Casper is dead by now
either the ghost or the Fire Emblem
character there's a fireemblem Casper
yeah I think that was uh the blueh
haired dude who from which fraction was
it free houses yeah yeah I think it was
uh prob not the one I was really or was
it was it the the golden no it had to be
edelgards yeah oh I didn't I generally
kept mostly only girls yeah
F okay so Casper are you with the ghost
or are you still alive kill
you oh oh oh it's it's Wednesday it's
unknown it's
[Music]
Wednesday it's Wednesday my dudes yeah
no it's unknown what's that mean unkn
know they don't want to know that's
confusing a Casper do you love me I'm
sure it's going to be a big fat yes
yeah it's
oh Lov me I love C too there's this
weird emotional connection that I have
to this rat
a okay um okay a yeah okay okay sorry I
haven't been writing this question on
the screen no you're fine you're fine
next one I'll put up there
yeah maybe next one might be the last
one unless you guys have one more good
one in the chat Co yeah the last one uh
I think I'll leave this to sh
mhm could you ask the
ghosts and no pressure to the ghosts
really like really I just want to I'm
just curious
okay who is the ghost ooshi
oh right first before is the ghost
single can you ask you want me to ask if
it's single
yeah wait this is a different ghost
right no it's all the same ghost it's a
it's a it's confusing then all right
ghost oh no not Casper not because for
Casper also I was asking the ghost not
Casper directly wait were we asking
where the ghost ay ghost okay ghost are
you are you are you single and ready to
mingle on e-harmony
or or christianmingle.com let me know oh
yeah what's tinder for
ghosts ghost Ginder with
GH ghaster cuz they're about to ghost
you
no oh this ghost this ghost is oh oh oh
oh what was that I think it said yes I
am what I sound out was I thought that
ghost is excited to make
oh I'm kind of interested yeah ghost
mingling are you are you interested in
ghost dating or
something okay ghost can you tell us
your
name oh I wonder who have we been
talking to all this time for this one
question
oh m m do we get more do we get more or
you want to stay mysterious sound like a
ha
person oh we don't get more just an m m
the fudge is M singular letter what the
[\h__\h] wrong with you I think I know
what it means
oh then I don't I don't even know if
it's necessary to ask the O oi question
oh oh they I feel like they turned off
and turned on again I looked at the OBS
screen oh that means that there r a
ghost here were they oh yeah wow okay
wow so
haunted
um okay
okay let's
ask Yago yeah everybody's Oshi is Yago
for
sure in a way
yeah okay
oi
what ghost M who's your oi
oh is that a w w m w it's a w no this W
is like no it's not the name that's the
OSI oh oh this is a new new person it's
w for
womo it's
womo oh no no oh we going back it's the
n
w to the
s a wa is at me what no
way stop girl stop wow this might mean
this whole stream was biased all along
no no it's not biased they I bet they
fell in love with you during it yeah
yeah love love love no I I have a
feeling that this ghost May or not may
or may not be possibly related to a
certain certain ghost made out there
oh maybe who knows that's the only ghost
no I think so okay rigged no no it's not
rigged it's a real ghost it's a real
ghost that has been haunting this office
woo
yeah okay I think that's it on my on my
question except the I one more question
not good okay yeah okay one last one M
can you tell me Shi because I honestly
don't
know is Ana to real Ani
Ani well you
know I'm going to throw this over here
huh oh
for oh
wow where you going here I wonder yeah I
wonder I wonder where it landed wow that
ghost that ghost is really angry I know
no the ghost is excited it's excited it
landed on the floor so maybe Ana to is
on the floor like that's how bad it's
doing right now that's a cabon on the
floor it's a yukadon oh oh that's even
spicier than a cabon I think is it I
just think it's a floor but if you think
about a walls are technically floors but
they're on your
side that is some beautiful wisdom that
you have imbued on me thank you I feel
philosophically
pleased that's a Point okay so that was
our little occult occultic
stream with these beautiful candles that
are totally real wow Phoenix Powers
W yeah sh collab with W our first
oneon-one collab I think yeah yeah and
it's a special off collab thank you for
for having me here thank you for being
here you suit this kind of vibe very
well so you should do like more occultic
you like handcam streams too yeah yeah
they're a little hard to set up usually
on your own yeah yeah this is really
nice set up yeah I know it's it's really
nice thank you so much Studio can you
please do a voodoo doll stream not
necessarily with this one I think I
would need a lot of Doon if I want to
hurt people yeah oh you should just go
to daa's place yeah cuz I was there and
she has like every single like existing
whole life friends with you doll yeah
she took us to um like a bunch of like
merch stops so I was like
o neat merch stops yeah like merch
stores for oh
cool actually I had to buy my own debut
acrylic you had to I mean if you would
have asked maybe they would have given
it to you
here
no how much was it oh was I mean it
wasn't too like I don't know what it is
in USD like $15 if you have the receipt
maybe you can
re wait that okay wait while we have a
handcam scen can I just show one thing
to say thanks to kfp I received this
today watch I I received this I don't
know when you guys sent this to
me but it's
special oh
what is this it is
a what do you think it is well obviously
had your face on it yeah but what what
do you think is an
Al kind of it's a vinyl yeah so it it's
not my like like it has all my songs so
far in here so technically I guess it's
an album in a in a vinyl veny form woo
it's a beautiful form Des AR is so cute
and it has all my songs with like Lo
custom logos can you see yeah
yeah I finally got it I don't know when
this was sent to me but I got it wait so
so they can actually send you like a
merch here
to not like usually just letters but
there's Sometimes some small exceptions
like at events or
so if the staff is
nice and if it's not too big or so you
know
what you want a viny vinyl Vin vinyl
Vine maybe I don't know I think could be
vinyl V then we need an album first she
won't we h a album we need an album then
oh if you want something on a ven I mean
I feel like it should be like I would
need to sing first yeah let's go to sing
okay sunm perhaps maybe maybe at a later
date yay thank you guys for watching
this a Cold Stream I hope you had fun it
was crazy for me here we have to say
goodbye to the ghost how do you say you
kind of know it right technically it's
like uh go thank you for having us here
uh we're going now and then you say
goodbye goodbye Ah that's why it says
goodbye down there like twice yeah you
always had to say goodbye oh thank you
guys we had to do this
because there was a terrified staff
member and and she's a newbie and she
was like
you make sure to say goodbye because
otherwise this place will be haunted I'm
like come on okay just for you safe yeah
yeah just for you well thankfully we're
not doing this at our house yeah just
here you do it at home nothing weird
will happen here because we said goodbye
properly but even if something happened
it's a staff's problem exactly
exactly thank you guys for watching and
in German we say Al Zen this was she
to Salt bird oh high in cholesterol Yum
Yum Yum how do you say goodbye
and byebye I like
it byebye bye-bye don't she W
bye goodbye she w we blow out the
candles oh it's it's out she did it
bye-bye present see you soon on Sunday
for the football finale oo
Spain Spain Amigos
[Music]
a