[Music]
thank you
foreign
questions
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
wait one second can we go back to
loading one more second
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
is dead what
yes she said yes she's dead oh I changed
I changed
cut
I miss her so much
you're not crying you're celebrating
[Laughter]
all right
do you want to come in now I guess so
I don't I'm so fake I don't fit through
the door oh
God you got this you got this I got it I
got it
I ate too many it's many fireflies oh no
foreign
[Music]
oh I'm stuck on that world oh
okay yeah and it'll keep it there okay I
think no it's still following me but
that's okay
oh there's like oh
oh is it I don't know sorry sorry sorry
guys
you were you were crying about a certain
takanasikiara until
yeah um I'm really sad about you know
her being turned into a frog and
everything
well the thing is I ate her she's in my
in my belly right now she's right there
wow wow she tastes like like gravy and
chicken
yay I'll be crazy
so now Mommy I took over her channel so
sorry you can't collab with takanasikara
you can collab with me though
is that okay
I think you're so cute I think it's okay
Maybe
you're so close yes but I'm also slimy I
hope you don't mind that
oh I already felt the slime
yeah you like oh you like the Slime the
Frog slime
yeah can I is it okay to like a like a
yes
all right all right I guess that was it
wait wait
oh I'm transforming oh I I gotta create
a a kiss from a from from a lovely
friend that was the kiss
what did they say
uh
was it a kiss it was definitely
something like a kiss
I'm trying to maybe find my
transformation
ah I am totally changing right now she's
a magical
girl magical translation
[Music]
this is
the Sparkles
oh there it is
[Music]
so frog
almost although hold on everybody hold
on technical maybe maybe magical
difficulties the kiss was not good
enough yet
oh here come here I'll lay one on ya
oh
I was delayed it was the thing
[Music]
she lived she lived Beach yeah thank you
what are you doing
what are you doing I'm just brushing
your hair I'm getting the I'm getting
the slime out of your hair
yeah yeah there should be no slime only
sorry I'm still trying to figure out
this camera guys
confuses me it's different oh there we
go that's beautiful well so maybe we
should since this is the first first
time special collaboration maybe we
should introduce ourselves to each
other's okay okay
yeah okay
okay
I am fun
something's wrong there's something's
off
where did you hear this before sounds
familiariki it's yeah it might be a
secret secret code word oh but no please
please more please more introduction
more and more and more oh
okay
um boomerang
from
me and I'm really nervous I feel like
I'm gonna throw off oh God
[Music]
did you say that make it clear
yeah first generation
[Music]
we're both we're both first Generations
yeah we're like like kickstarters of of
a very special chunks
I pledged revolutionizers you
okay okay
[Music]
a Phoenix from her life English whole
life myth and I'm thank you very much
for Reviving me because this stupid
Trump [\h__\h] took over my channel and she
was screaming on my channel
yeah but she thought she could really
just eat a phoenix and nothing would
happen no no no no no no I mean did she
have the guns and everything yeah but
did you know that that eating a phoenix
is the only way to really like like
make them go away forever if you end up
you know going to an idol meeting and
then like getting rid of her but as long
as she's still the Phoenix Sun your
tummy then there's still a chance to
revive and I was still in her tummy she
has a really slow like digestion system
so thankfully you came just right on
time
I don't think you should tell people
your secret like that
I'm writing a lot of ideas no I I don't
think anyone else would would attempt
such a thing ever again
oh yeah surely I think maybe your fans
are different than my fans
you get rid of you
yeah I think so we can have like a
love-hate relationship
yeah you got you have like you know
everybody working at you know kfp I have
my Arch nemesis's all of them but you
wrong if you think that KSP chickens are
all really loyal and supportive some of
them they want me gone too they always
ask for like raises and stuff even
though they should be grateful to get
the races tonight
oh my God
the audacity right now I'm hearing I I
can't believe this that I'm hearing this
oh
you're a special bomb wow
oh celebration over all
first collab let's go whoa yeah
nice do you have another one of those no
only one yeah we have to share no I have
one oh we have it
I'm like stuck on the ground oh gosh
shoot
sure
um
all right so uh one thing I wanted to
say that this VR chat VR stream and we
are going to show each other each
other's worlds right now we are in the
league of Sanji Indian world and then
later we'll go to the hollow in many
many various worlds and will you know
shall we yeah sightseeing and and yeah
get to know each other because actually
it's the first time that we're talking
like this right yeah I know I was so
nervous to join the Discord
oh God
I was like
I was like um you know setting up
together with Ahmed and then right
before you came in I was like oh God
this is the first time I'm talking to
her I'm so nervous
it's okay it's okay we just choose girls
nothing nothing to be nervous about we
all know this wolf fairy or Phoenix
right
yeah I don't think we're we're not human
we're like yeah
that saying doesn't really work
unfortunately we're just Phoenix fairy
after all doesn't sound like the same
the same way but
oh wow so they both kind of start with a
f sound ah oh true Phoenix and fairy but
mine is pH
yeah yeah yeah just uh you know ignore
that part
all right so you're not gonna show me
around you just Sanji world first and I
already I saw this before in in some of
your guys's streams a little bit I saw
it and I really like the design of the
train because this is guys maybe you
didn't see it before but uh let me pick
you up what's up
door you see this guys whoa there's a
train do you like trains guys yeah
is there like I really like the okay
shooting stars outside they're so pretty
yeah yeah hold on guys I gotta get my
camera let's see let's do this all
righty shooting star
where are we yeah located in right now
but where is this train right now
um we're in Diamond lights City almost
we're you know we're going to Diamond
light City we're going there right now
yeah yeah yeah yeah that would imply
that later the whole livian world is
Diamond light City
oh
I mean it could be so pretty so there's
like there's pillows of of your like gen
maids and not gen mates and so on around
here huh oh what is that ducky makura
yeah
I know her
ah they want a hug they want to hug it
that's the first time I've ever saw
whoa it has like physics
damn do you think she doesn't mind if I
like punch it
well she might enjoy it even I mean I
know I would really oh yeah
[Music]
Pomeranian what do you think about that
nickname
I love it I'll bark for you
this looks like dogs are my favorite
animal but I feel like Pomeranian is a
nice nickname for you
yeah I feel I feel we
um we both share a great love of cats
together
show me around what do I need to see
what do I need to look at
okay um first if you would like to have
a sip of tea oh yes there's some tea
right there oh it's Tuesday feel free to
on Tuesday
pick it up drink all of it no milk
that's that's good oh there's like um
your bosses in here oh I'm drinking it
did you meet your boss when you were in
Japan recently
oh no I have a chance to this time
not the red carpets for you and be like
princess bubble it's so such an honor to
talk to you can I have an audience with
you and talk with you please we need to
have a moment
you should you should um go there again
and then talk to him again not again
first time I'll bust down his door yes
this way if we go this way I will show
you
hold on camera okay camera camera this
okay this is this stuff actually also
flashing for you this like there's like
this is flashing like crazy it is oh I'm
not sure why let's just yeah if you come
this way it'll I think it'll stop okay
yes it's uh somewhere else now let's go
okay
oh this is dangerous this is dangerous
we could fall out there
holy [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
you're going to Diamond City Lights
I think we were dead this is a dream or
something oh God where is that no it's
like you know
don't worry about it don't worry about
it it's not a trap or anything at all
that's exactly what somebody would say
who's kidnapping me to then
you know we all you know we can even
like jump off later if you want actually
Romeo and Juliet this yeah oh we can
jump up oh sounds exciting yeah all
right so what do we have here the food
area
yeah welcome to the cafe
but the chairs are so high
they're so hot just uh yeah I'm just
like uh I'll click on it this will
become oh this is not made for people
like us
oh my god oh um my chest being
voyeuristic right now what are they
saying what does that mean voyeuristic
do you want to do they want to go on a
voyage
same thing
really so they're being nice yeah yeah
they're looking out the window for me
well let me fix myself my my body moves
really weird today
oh what um so can I order something
yeah what would you like
um something sweet
please sweet okay I got you I got you
she got me um what some sweet you guys
hold on I know what to get her I know
exactly
[Music]
this makes my dream come true of going
on like a train trip you know just for
the sake of riding that train because
the train is special and I guess what
you see outside the windows so it's not
about to go it's about the
wait how do I say this philosophically
it's not about the destination it's
about how to get to the destination
how do you guys say this
it's a journey yes the journey the
journey it's not about the destination
it's the journey yeah
oh gosh you have a magazine here I need
you Sanji oh
grand opening need your time to express
exclusive interview project leader seren
tatsuki
she the project leader
well can I open I'm gonna open this this
is a fake magazine
I can't open it what we
publish we don't publish fake news
it's not a magazine where's the real
thing
there's a cake right here wait it's not
even wait it's not even it's not even
need to Sanji it says Nissan
meet me
I don't know what some seems pretty
suspicious sounds like it's not enough
oh
oh am I in the maid Cafe yeah
um okay
um
magic please magic okay
okay
where's the magic okay um
me
[Music]
oh there we go oh uh can I change my
camera
oh yes
how how many
how many made outfits do you or did you
own until
laughs
um
you know that's a bit of a loaded
question don't you think I mean who
knows
[Music]
I don't think why I'm asking
because I um I I used to um like um
about
um eight different made outfits at a
time
I liked um mates as well and and I
wanted to be one too and I was smaller
oh my God
yeah
I had like
um you know normally they're like
um normally the really classic ones are
black with a white apron right yeah yeah
yeah yeah my favorite one was the
opposite because it looked really
offensive by having the the main dress
be white and then the apron Why Oh
I like that oh fancy sounds kind of sexy
oh fancy yeah sorry
[Music]
I had I have a couple I had also one
that was like light blue with white and
I had one that was like oh yes huh yes I
had a light blue one too
oh
you had one good taste one or how many
I've had I had like the traditional one
black and white I've had oh
um the blue light blue one I've had like
ones that multi-colored
oh like pastel colors yeah yeah
your head is so big
it takes one no one
that's model but seeing it in VR right
in front of me I was like holy [\h__\h] this
head is big
this is
where's my body I don't even know don't
worry don't worry
it's it's a it's a Disney it's a disease
that's called Chibi Chibi body we have
tiny hands at least tiny legs fingers
you have fingers
my frog model has fingers this one
doesn't some of us have fingers some of
us don't you're one of the lucky ones
you release some fingers
also you have ears
also your poop yeah right oh my God Papa
we're Powerpuff Girls were chibis
yeah basically right if you think about
it the Powerpuff Girls are like Chibis
who was your favorite Powerpuff Girl
I really like Buttercup
yeah yeah yeah she suits you I think so
yeah too yeah yeah
wait who did you like
um
it's hard to remember I think
probably was her name Blossom the orange
one
oh yeah what's your pink
her hair was Orange right but her outfit
was pink yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah as
it's mixing up in my head yeah yeah
another surprise is that like the orange
girl
[Laughter]
she's just you know you were a young
Chihuahua you just saw yourself in her
right yes it's like you could you could
be there maybe
do you still have I was watching you
stream uh yesterday as you may know
stream
wait I'm mixing up things but but you
had like a you both got like a tea right
and then you and then the maid was like
oh yeah wearing it and she was like say
stop when you don't want any more tea
and selling just did not say stop and
then it almost overflowed but you you
respect the maids and you probably said
stop
they even said they were like they were
like we won't stop if you don't say stop
stop and I told her that and probably I
understand
wanting to test it out like how far do
they go I get that
she called their Bluff she did call
their Bluff oh by the way Paul oh my God
you're supposed to show me around and
we're just sitting here okay show me
around please oh yeah okay
of course
how do you say you're welcome uh
petition petition thank you
so cute
oh let me look at the counter what are
you selling here oh
pomerang is the classic for 800 Yen I
suppose that's like eight bucks around
here and bear Bento Milly's Buffet
finatos what's finatos
I know it's for free Nana but what is it
supposed to be
they're Doritos ah
but not Doritos makes sense you know
they're a copyright free Doritos oh here
they are bananas
oh yeah I can't reach them
tiny tiny people
oh they exist oh my God does every
product on that on that menu exist in
here
I think so oh just about everything whoa
here's my Palmer rice
[Music]
at the table oh
oh my God my eyes oh is that what you
were laying underneath to uh show your
your new outfit
is this the one this is the real thing
oh yeah yeah that's the real thing
that's what was used to reveal your
outfit wow
she's stuck in the wall or stuck in the
table oh dear
I didn't realize
give me your head long long live the
king
man
[Music]
I'm gonna have to clean that mess up
later
this is really exhausting okay holy [\h__\h]
oh God sorry guys
I am alive I lived
yeah you're a phoenix after all right
yes yes nothing can stop me no no no no
all right what's next Pomeranian
okay I'll take you to everybody's rooms
oh they have everybody has rooms
everybody
yeah almost everybody oh my God okay
that should be good
okay
let's go this way that way yes
[Music]
it gets really laggy here for some
reason
oh oh
this is where we started
yes this is where we started there's
some darts there
there's a
yeah there's a game thing there Sky
dragons please yeah it's like the most
popular game in niji Sanji right now oh
you know I thought it was really cool
when I saw
um you know wheniji Sanji and second gen
was announced and they saw that you guys
have like uh sister designs in there I
was like yo
[Music]
yeah our sisters
wait are they half sisters or full
sisters
they're half sisters because they you
know they don't have the same last name
different different Papa right because
Say Mama say Mama
uh yeah oh gosh I can't reach the door
oh this is so small
oh does Elena have a room
I don't think so actually hold on oh
this is my room here we go
oh welcome to my oh my God I'm taking
Kiara to my room
oh that's right
comfy futon on the ground and then like
a comfy daisu and comfy table where's my
camera on it what I lost my camera
oh
yeah
kfp just like where are we
it comfy ah can I stream on your channel
from here
there's no keyboard yeah yeah let's go
keyboard I'll give you my stream key
wait there's no keyboard
it's like a really high tech like you
know it's everything I don't need to get
the keys I'm a gamer
understand I understand it's like a like
an iPad do you do you see me sitting
right here do you see me sitting right
here yes yes you're you're in under the
covers
why no it's a ghost of me
what I'm staring at myself
well now you moved yes what
are you seeing a ghost
yeah I think I said I think my room is I
think my room is haunted I don't see you
there I only see you there
what's going on
are you I don't know are you are you
okay
I don't think I took my meds today yeah
I'm worried about it it's probably
hallucinations I'm starting to
hallucinate you because like the headset
is really freaking heavy and like
strangling my hands
it was like the first time we collab and
I hallucinate it how embarrassing
I'm sorry everybody
Nation this is all just a hallucination
oh what's that button there's a button
here
[Music]
wait actually you know what when you're
saying um you see yourself that was
probably me because I'm Pomo too aren't
I aren't we oh true true
is that the thing
I'm totally quiet though I'm palmer but
I hear it
I'm mama
and Paul I'm Paul
so you have this spot is it good in
reality too
actually I saw someone make it for real
button
scientist
oh
okay okay
I'm trying to fix my headset but it's
it's just designed decided to strangle
me today that's okay oh
I haven't worn VR in so long oh gosh
it's it's a pain in the butt but we're
doing it for this realistic experience I
really like it though like it really
feels like more real than a normal
collab mom yeah like I can touch you
yeah
the Dutch
touch
you know what's missing in your room
was that a box
a box there's box in this thing you need
a box
a box what I'm
Justin why do I need a box we need just
a box
[Laughter]
I'm disappointed
[Music]
[Applause]
I was thinking it but I was just like
surely surely she's she's not talking
about you know because you know I
won't shut up I want to shut up
oh God we all know Paulo won't be going
to Metal Gear Solid convention because
she's not a real fan
are you a stalker Kiara I'm sorry I
found that's a little direct but no I'm
up to date I'm just up to date okay I'm
real informed
okay
go next
room hold on Everybody follow me yeah
or maybe I don't have perms no I don't
have banana room perms uh how to open oh
wait hold on hold on
what am I
a fish there we go
oh hello everybody
go in going I can't I'm too I'm too
thick
I can't remember
[Music]
oh
hold on camera
where are you guys
and up there there's fish
they're real real fish
she has such a nice room she does
well
oh bubbles bubbles and fish oh she's
putting two
laughs
to say what does it say
it says girl and mother trucker
everybody has a button oh maybe I need a
button too
oh can we have like oh can we jump on
her bed
oh
yeah
you're stepping on your clothes
I didn't take off my shoes
yeah
wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah acting yeah
a nice room this is finana's room yeah
very afraid very cute I like the scale
pattern on the wall and then at the
ceiling there's like there's Ray wave
reflection
look chat yeah wow
whoa
did I remember like pretty sign like I
mean obviously you didn't design
everything probably but did they like
give like a concept of how they wanted
it to look like
yeah I think uh for mine at least I kind
of just said what stuff I wanted in
there and uh they decided what to put in
and what yeah what not
nice okay I think there's one more room
actually one more
one more
please
is it okay
you left all the doors open yeah yeah
it's pretty safe
I guess there's no one else here who
comes into a [\h__\h] outer space to this
train
your sails must be terrible here
it's a pretty hot destination I don't
know
hello
[Music]
cool
she has like a fancy round bin oh wow I
know
that's like I don't know if that's
comfortable to lay on or sleep on I mean
I don't think the shape really like
makes it
uncomfortable I'm sure it's comfy what
if you would it be a long legs
she's probably about the same size as we
are oh she also well is this what the
real Gamers nowadays have they have all
these
um laptops that have no keyboard at all
yeah it's not that we got a sponsorship
um
it's like a lemonade sentence
[\h__\h] kick ass oh is this with manga
that looks like mango
no yummy do I wear mango there's a mango
on the drink
in German it's called mango
mango and anime
oh my God
people you also have this when like
people who don't know really what
they're talking about
um or what what you do they ask you oh
are you like a manga
are you like are you like Naruto
that's my Naruto run
oh yeah
oh yeah yeah oh yeah yes fast I like how
she kind of kept her room like more like
chill and down to earth like it's not
like finana who had freaking fish
everywhere
this is very cozy
I can't see it I don't oh this is
dragons
yeah someone made a fan game is that a
reference
I mean I mean it's not like Battleship
oh
actually actually I don't know Chad do
you know cute
she'll never know we were here I'll put
it back
it's okay I I come in here periodically
and [\h__\h] up her [\h__\h] you know
I think that that's all the best
what about like what was the maze room
for example
that's right that's right oh my gosh you
know you know better than I do
oh there you go how did you forget this
where are you going it's here it's here
whoa okay
I'm trying to find my camera oh there we
go why so it's okay
it's so pink uh I'm once again too thick
these doors are now made for wealthy
models like mine wow
oh there we go
cute
[Music]
that is so cute
yeah Rosemary's room is really cute very
pink with a with a rose a carpet very
pink and girly oh she has like a like a
dressing table cute
oh so girly oh does she like hamsters
yeah she has a hamster yeah she has one
so oh okay yeah
cute
I like it honestly like when I was um a
couple years younger this would have
been my dream room I would have I I
tried to know my room looked like
something like this everything's super
like princess like and girly and pink
yeah yeah but but pink too not not
because I love pink so much but just
because all girly things are always pink
for some reason even though I liked like
purple pastel purple violet and so on
the most oh
I think pastel purple is like underrated
with yes this kind of aesthetic yes yes
yeah yeah yeah
I look I like the wallpaper in here
though with the Roses oh yeah they're
like not too strong they're just really
faint and makes it look really yeah ah
you guys see this let's see I guess that
it's so bright
there it is there it is
okay beautiful beautiful 10 out of 10.
would would stay here if it was an
Airbnb and then we have Petra is this is
this real no this one doesn't work
that's why you're not sure like
yeah not everyone has one so
it gets a little confusing what's did
she not have the funds to buy um a room
here for permanent usage I can imagine
it must be really expensive a room a
permanent oh yeah in the train space
yeah it's you know the rent is like
breaking my back but it's okay you know
you have to make sacrifices for some
luxuries yes yes
exactly I'm a bougie I'm a bougie
girlie girl
wait dude what does that mean
it means
um Emma
boogie boogie boogie boogie boogie
woogie
Woogie
Boogie Woogie it's like um
it's like you're really into a like
fancy things like oh
like me
yeah I like you exactly
okay Kiara is a boozy [\h__\h] nice I like
the rooms really they're so nice and I
like the whole terrain idea I didn't
show but up here at the top it has like
a really fancy you need to Sanji logo
pattern
yeah everybody has such a nice
atmosphere
there's one last thing I have to show
you and then we can move on
a maid Cafe this is a shrine is it a box
oh um
I wish would you get in the love box
with me Kiara
no
[Music]
you wouldn't get in the love box with me
to be true I don't know what the lovebox
is
the left box that's exactly what it
sounds like
definitive denied rejected
I can't make it too easy for you eat it
oh you're playing hard to get I get your
girl I get you
all right where are we going now okay
not least all right this this way
back to like oh gosh sorry everybody
hold on let me fix my camera
everybody's going through walls [\h__\h]
are you
my head hurts okay head towards please
cut off it please
I want to be like Anne Boleyn have my
head cut off please
I love envelope okay you guys stay here
oh can we go up oh
yeah
go up go up go up well how how to use
whoa whoa that was fast holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh this is [\h__\h] dangerous oh is it
oh
I thought it would say something like I
love you Kiana but this is happy
I mean honestly it's already uh middle
of October end of October almost so so
we're getting there we're getting there
oh
[Music]
wow wow planets oh I knew this was outer
space
how many stars are there Puma
right now in the night sky
um
[Music]
give or take a little bit maybe seven
five six seven
laughs
ridiculous this this child cannot count
[Laughter]
this is the job that you get guys if you
don't get to school if you don't go to
school and you don't learn how to count
you become like us a YouTuber
I'm a modern day mathematician
how how
much is
uh three times nine
.
the question or the the real answer is
what does three times nine mean
that in a in a cosmic sense
I will tell you in a German sense is
that okay
yeah yeah three times nine means
she really
or he really are you really we really
don't [\h__\h] wanna deal with your [\h__\h]
what
three times nine nine nine nine is this
a German lesson yes nine
nine means now
I learned I learned think about it
that's actually really deep
laughs
well thank you for visiting my German
class today
um so at the end of my German lessons
I say
alvida's in so am I supposed to jump now
oh my God
I was not even ready for Dad oh my God
you jump too
yeah
it's really good that there's some
safety precautions like that that bring
you back here thank God oh God oh God oh
God it's flashing okay so nice world you
got there I like it I wouldn't mind
going on this train a few times to
travel around the world
ah thank you yeah and space anywhere you
want to go to no space all right but
next we're not going to space we're
gonna go to no hello
life Ian world
and you guys you guys should stay until
the very end because we have something
special planned in Hawaii and world so
come with us we're gonna go in loading a
screen for like a moment until we get
into the world so we'll see you guys
stay tuned stick around stick around
stick around
all right I'm going to my loading screen
[Music]
oh oh Chad just let me ask you is
everything like audio wise okay so far
tell me it's probably a little bit late
to ask but
okay the timing is actually good it's
been one hour so we took one hour for
your world audio okay okay okay
oh
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
oh oh wait
oh yeah me too
me too
[Music]
thank you
sorry guys the
um the camera systems is like failing a
little bit so I'll have to restart VR
chat so we'll be there in five minutes
[Music]
foreign
thank you
don't leave yet we're almost there guys
don't leave
[Music]
foreign
business
ah hi yay I'm good I'm back
oh hello where's the camera hello
[Music]
kick it again Welcome to our famous
elevator uh yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh camera crew
so all the people who get dizzy from VR
are not suffering anymore sorry yeah
yeah all right I'll be showing you
around pool
[Music]
I'm excited there we go all right so
first I show you the first world we have
many words but I'll show you the first
one first uh so we opened um
[Applause]
come here
cause we keep on like adding on to this
so it's starting to get really confusing
like a like a maze but uh oh yeah I
guess this is right there we can go to
the auditorium first
is infesting this area were too powerful
and broke the local Quantum metrics
please exercise caution to this hallway
be careful okay take my hands that's
like hold my breath okay okay I can't
oh
okay
[Music]
so then here there's an area with some
props yeah you can like bring into the
stage
yeah two
2022 why is there is there someone shoot
for that oh no it's because it's for you
too oh
okay and then you've got the breadstick
and you go over here and we have
the auditorium like in the school you
know like for chaos yeah
oh it even has a basketball court yeah
and then we would go up here and this is
where we had that that like special
moment where we were hugging each other
up here and we were like oh we want to
meet him
[Music]
self I remember that
you do review don't remember don't cry
don't cry right now I don't remember I
do I do but since then we have got a
breadstick breadstick
garlic I need some garlic on this please
oh you're a garlic girl me too
garlic is best yeah yeah yeah yeah nice
if you don't look close enough it could
like a yellow light stick
closer oh yeah you just gotta want some
bread guys it's a little dirty Maybe
dirty yellow
dirty yellow bread is superior
so this is the auditorium but let's go
next next we have so much to show up
follow me
[Music]
I'm running I'm like a I kind of like a
really really stressed out overworked uh
tourist uh guide
got no free time follow me come on don't
get lost follow me straight right behind
me
run run run run run
yeah run as if they're following you
I'm Naruto running I'm Naruto running
oh oh yeah I didn't realize this was uh
there ah we can like turn on different
decorations here like off season all the
myth anniversary Halloween happy
holidays Halloween is close so I wonder
if we can turn on Halloween yeah
oh
yeah
there's pumpkins everywhere this is
about the size of your head you could
fit in that one
yeah yeah
[Music]
guys take a screenshot cheese cheese
and here we have a bar you can get some
nice drinks we have for example
oh
wait I can't pick it up I'm on the table
oh there you go
here I am I am going to serve you
some doctor oopsies
would you like some oopsie take it tick
whoops well like make me have a whoopsie
Pepsi or you know Dr oopsie do you see
it
yeah I do it it makes you uh be able to
hack through the gate
oh I'm chugging I'm chugging
[Laughter]
that's um be delicious that's 20 please
oh no this is one of those this is one
of those host clubs that doesn't give
you the name of the or the price of the
boys
depends on how much you look like you're
able to spend until twenty dollars
please
[Laughter]
[Music]
you look like a million dollars
oh
all right and next we go to the lobby
there is
um from there we can go to all of our
different uh rooms which are not really
rooms they're more like worlds yeah we
have the the crying golden juggle
okay
are his tears drinkable
yes
yes that's what we thrive on that's how
we are able to stream every day by
drinking his tears
[Music]
do you feel energized I feel like I'm
ready too
stream for 24 hours
oh time for a 24-hour stream look
there's a there's a crucial detention
coffee over here I don't think you can
pick it up but you can look at it from
the other side it says
potential coffee
oh my gosh it's because you're the boss
yes and the next one is Toki no soda
okay
oh I get it I get that reference
all right which which um which myth
members world would you like to see
first
can we go in order and just go around
okay okay then we go to Ina World Series
[Music]
it's kind of Japanese style
yeah traditional
it has tatami mats yeah big big plushies
lots of books
science oh there's so there's a pumpkin
Taco I just noticed now
it's so cute
so cute cookies it's cookies Tuesday
wait
do you think he'll be mad if I take it
no no you did
eat it
unfortunately we don't have the actual
eating mechanism that you guys had over
there that's something we have to look
into
delicious
[Music]
give me a nose it made me grow a nose
and I want to I want the cookies
anyway I'll make myself a cookie nose
too
yeah
cookie nose
oh
here
all right we look like Muppets if the
cookie knows
oh God
I love chocolate chip cookies yummy yum
yum yum
so you know Ina is the artist of the
group shows there's a lot of art here
and it's her her at atal here I think
wasn't there like even
a function to draw no no no no no that
was not here but I guess we have that in
a different world
very much artists is your passion
artists are fashion artist
okay next
yay
so then we have a smaller gouda timeline
because she's already smaller
wow I really like this one because it
has like this Atlantic theme it's really
cool
do you like fish themes don't you
I actually it's not like you have a fan
of fish but uh I like these Aesthetics
you're so powerful
stop stop stop stop stop
no don't do it to them actually maybe
they deserve it yeah yeah do it it's so
fast it looks like it's made out of like
diamonds
yeah hold it
touch
you've got the power you've got the
power I feel like I'm in Minecraft
play Minecraft now oh yeah did you know
that in Minecraft sorry I have to flex
now that you say it
Once Upon a Time kilawa was chilling in
Minecraft minding her own business just
going through the water and then
suddenly she gets attacked by this this
thing in her face whoosh and I'm like
hey yo so I kill him and you know they
really Drive rarely these figs but it
dropped it yeah I ever killed one yeah
[Music]
oh my God
she's cracked
it wasn't thin it was so insane she's a
gamer I'm a gamer
she's like oh she's okay I bow about you
oh yes
there's an archive of that if you guys
are curious look look for
um wait what is this thing called again
I'm having a brain freeze moment
underwater themed
and speaking of under something there's
also an under underworld under Cali
world
yeah wanna go there next okay under
there yeah over there over there she was
about to underwear me actually no next
is AMA I guess
is it no oh wait uh
how how did we get uh there's oh
oh exit oh this is oh I'm confused this
was the accent what's gonna go there
last wait and the world is the exit was
it always called exit
all right let's uh this is the other
world
I'm a World's exit no we're not exiting
yes
but
wow
[Music]
almost stripped
oh God don't trip be careful how can I
trip it's only sand
do you like sand I don't
no actually I have a I have a really bad
relationship with sand
me too me too it's the worst like when
you're when you're like booze and when
you you know on vacation don't you like
walk a lot like I walk a lot on vacation
not not even that much but still enough
to get like blisters on defeated and
then yeah yeah you want to go to the
water because that's what you're here
for and then you go there and and then
you get out of the water and all the
sand will be in your blisters and then
you try to wash it out again but you
always have to go through this freaking
sand again
so I was gonna say it's in your
underwear
[Laughter]
and I don't know I like this this like
wide
loneliness somehow because there's this
bus stop with the with a small armor
here waiting for
for something who is she waiting for
hmm
what she looks so peaceful look her dog
Bubba has a little candy thing in her
hands in his mouth
and then we have here I can look at you
closely with this oh you can look at me
closely just kidding it doesn't actually
have like a
I think it works pretty well yeah let's
just act as if it has a magnifying
effect
oh you have nice nice skin very smooth
really yeah yeah I feel like my skin has
been I don't know kind of like wow not
so good you need to take care of it no
no no maybe it's the stress because I
was eaten oh gravy
gravy but the frog the frog
Mr should like yeah yeah
you capitalize on that actually that
sounds like a new business venture for
you I honestly don't know where she is
right now I don't know what happened
with her after I transformed
also just hold on generation let's look
at you guys
what are you saying we're trying to find
something
I'm trying to find where I give a [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh I see I see a lot of them
oh
I'm glad hi guys
[Laughter]
before the sand infiltrates our
um systems let's go to Cali
[Music]
I'm running so much faster or I'll leave
you behind
no
okay next would be Kiana but we'll go to
Cali first yeah yeah it's very pink yeah
yeah yeah because she's a girly girl
it's just kidding oh my God although she
does have a lot of like surprisingly
girly parts around about her oh oh by
the way I want to say thank you Kelly I
don't know if you're watching this but
thank you Kelly for helping us with
something you know you know what it is
yes thank you thank you so much and
while we're at it thank you I'm never
also helping yeah and also thank you
thank you thank you the rifle for fixing
some things and helping and also ask
thank you also for helping thank you
in all right thank you all right so she
has this little moon stage here
yeah wait wait wow
I feel so hip
oh I'm getting the I'm getting the
Boogie oh yeah
I'm getting the Boogie yeah
oh yeah
oh my God I throw a bag holy
show me your twerking oh
does this show up
that's some intense twerking oh my God
oh my God
[Laughter]
I'll do it the other way yeah yeah oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
sorry sorry my son sorry my son we're
stupid I'm not don't decide no don't be
sorry
so here we have some Unapologetic some
cool shades
[Music]
here take them will they put my face
yeah they're made for big faces
oh stylish yeah oh and then I have
profile uh if you want to be a little
bit more like Cali you can have her save
yeah here you put on the glasses
um hold on
there we go hey
hey
what's up
[Music]
MTV my cribs or criminals
MTV Cruise yeah so this is our free
million dollar home yeah we share a joke
I thought you said free at first it's
like what was free no no no no no no
cost costy huh and I can give you an
injection how much does the real estate
go about here oh okay where would you
like the injection
I think you need it here oh okay
I don't think you need a butt injection
okay
oh
it will take up to five days for it to
have effect
okay for now I'm already feeling a
little funny but
and now
now the best room Kiana
[Music]
although I might be I might be a little
bit biased but uh
you know oh there's
oh there's my my vampire
umbrella
oh
wait then I should I want to change you
look around and I I change into my
vampire outfit okay
I won't watch
[Music]
did I change
oh no I didn't
something about this I'm not
understanding
now
now not yet
you can look around look at snacks or
something okay
you have so many candies I don't wow
I like I think I I'm a fan of this one
what's your favorite type of candy
God damn it okay
[Laughter]
what's your favorite
[Music]
um
um I like Kinder chocolate they have so
many different kinds
yes oh I love under chocolate
Kinder chocolate have you have you eaten
Kinder country before
I don't think so in the country it's
very very yummy
what's it like it is
yeah yeah kinder eggs but there's way
more the Kindle country has like the
cereal cereal inside the chocolate bar
what what wait maybe I have had it I
just don't know chocolate bar kind of
tastes like the Kinder Egg but like
bigger
oh oh my gosh that's so good I love
Kinder chocolate yes
well I'm trying out some Expressions
don't mind me okay so here this is
basically this is supposed to be like
Austria you know because we have many
mountains and we have beautiful yeah
beautiful nature and yeah so it's kind
of like specific a little bit like
Austria
and we have the Kotori monument in the
middle it's my
my bird Kotori
over there oh hell yes yes Lord Lord
Kotori glory and back here is is a is a
closed kfb branch
I don't know what they they probably
closed down because they they saw froggy
Wawa working instead of me or like not
working but streaming so they were like
is gone all right let's let's leave kfv
let's go
I see what you're doing I'm lazy I will
not forget lazy you better come back
right here in this instant I don't want
to see you work open this shop and serve
me some burgers or else
yeah you better be ready in uniform
right now we have a guest after all
maybe once we eat some burgers and we
thought about that I do the burgers what
burgers
all right guys
perhaps we have um a phoenix Burger
Phoenix burger and the Jaco burger
burger and many other different I've
always
I've always wondered about the you know
the um the ethics of the Phoenix Burger
effects
FX the ethics yeah
no no no it's just called Phoenix Burger
but it uses chicken meat
okay which doesn't mean that I have
chicken okay it's just I called it that
night obviously
but you're not a chicken no no
no okay follow me follow me we need to
make a speed run into a window world
I will show you our beautiful beautiful
winter world let's go
if I can
yeah do you like do you like snow
yes well kind of I don't know I'm not
really good with cold places but I like
snow I think it's pretty
oh well uh snow happens to be very cold
so
if you don't like cold then the next one
it's really suffering for you
I'm kind of really hot because of the VR
so maybe it'll be oh yeah
let's go oh
oh hi
I'm Glad You Came where uh what
oh is she able to follow she um
yeah uh oh maybe not maybe not
wait let me let me go back oh
are you uh
uh shake your head if you can't if you
can't come to Window World
oh I take I take okay okay can I help
yes okay okay
let's go
oh
there's a camera right here
oh I got it got it ah I see I understand
oh yeah
so this is um a world that we got when
uh I think last winter last Christmas
last Christmas last Christmas oh my God
you guys know the song
last Christmas
Christmas
and give it away
special
[Music]
follow me oh you can push these these
balls and they become bigger I think
there's one over there this one this one
this one is so small
ah push push and push push and push push
push I think it's getting push it push
your finger's getting bigger
[Music]
can we get much bigger
how big does it get I'm not sure I never
tried to make it maximum size
Max we can do it
hmm
nice oh you can like dance on top of it
trying to get on top of it
oh
there we go
[Music]
let me drink some water and if you look
to the middle you see our Christmas tree
we had decorations up there but it's not
Christmas so we took them down
understandable sorry I'm drinking water
too come on
oh yeah
over here is right in front of the tree
is where I did like a Christmas karaoke
in my Christmas outfit right here
I remember
that was fine it's the pilgrimage spot
do you already feel chill down chilled
down
actually a little bit what is good you
can come come here to warm up again
oh okay
we have like a sauna
what
come here in here
only girls allowed
only girls here oh everybody get out
it hasn't been used in a while now yeah
real toasty
I think yeah okay I'll just brush away
the dust a little bit okay guys
just kidding just kidding ah you were
trying to figure
when I went outside she was she was
trying to she was trying to peek for the
window
naughty naughty
naughty naughty yeah and in there it's
even hotter there's uh what you're doing
there quite hot in there and then here
here you can go ice skating and ice
fishing oh
swing wait are you are you okay in there
Swing Swing
swing I'm drowning
I can't swim oh my head is too big my
head is too big for my body
[Music]
we have another one of those moments
here take my hand
yeah okay all right we're just too short
and I know
something's working yeah it's probably
working
okay guys
[Music]
there's Christmas hats oh and spooky
witch hat
oh my God so cute
I have spooky witch hat
oh
I'm a spooky witch
spell on you
um
[Music]
and now you're in love with us oh
oh lava lava
oh my gosh she's a real like a real man
real Idol
why are you so cute
right in the Coconut no you oh no you no
you
okay one more come come over here
we have a cozy
cozy place
oh this is so cute yeah you can Grill
some marshmallows or grill some sausages
you want the marshmallow Okay good what
do you like you have a marshmallow
though you don't like marshmallows
you want to switch do you like what you
do like more
um sausage
I don't really like mine I was gonna say
that much
I was gonna say if you liked
marshmallows and I like sausage you know
I feed you and you feed me we can share
oh yeah oh it's like it's like lady lady
in the [\h__\h] but with the sausage
oh sorry sorry guys no no free show
tonight no no no
no secret secret
it comes in the endings also this hot
dog
there's hot chocolate you want a hot dog
here here here uh
oh
thank you thank you
I love her chocolate
[Music]
I'm melting it's so hot
I have nicochita syndrome
[Music]
all right bamboo the sports I think I
wasn't there like a where where is the
drawing area there was a drawing area
I'm not sure if it's like working right
now though
is it here well where was it
oh oh I think
ah it's here oh
okay
you can you can take the entirely pan
and then when you when you press the
button you can draw
when you when you press like the the
equip button
and you can draw on your snowman okay
you make snowmen I make snowmen
okay okay
oh gosh I'm I'm struggling that's okay
you'll figure it out I'm an artist me
too I'm artiste
who can make the best snowman
what do you what kind of snowman are you
drawing from uh
I'm drawing a really punchable one right
now that's a bunk
yeah what kind of snowman and
you know just one that you know I just
look at it and I wanna I wanna punch it
in the face I wanna
bring it what problems do you have with
with uh snowmen what did they ever do to
you
wait where's yours
what is yours you say wait I'm not done
so that's that okay I won't look I won't
look it's not recognize
do you guys chat do you recognize
well from the side it's like really kind
of you have to look
um up front up front
oh okay okay okay okay it's ready oh
wait no no it's not ready yet where did
that ah some of the lines disappear when
when time passes oh no oh no oh no oh no
no no oh no okay look look look
ah
okay it's okay
it's you it's Watashi oh it's so cute
oh my oh my oh my wow
okay Palmer you know what
uh yeah VR is starting to make me feel
like absolute [\h__\h] so we'll go to the
studio next week we'll skip the
Halloween world but we'll go
let's go let's go let's go okay I'm
gonna sit down
oh I don't blame you yeah it's starting
to make my head hurt a lot
we are we are so exhausting
she's zooming
Look at Her Go
what do I look like
oh
um sometimes her legs like come out of
the ground
okay
super special Amit dubbers do I have to
take the the camera I think so okay okay
yeah yeah
can I returned to Lobby can I press this
oh I still have the pen oh yes okay
I got it oh
okay there it is I think you'll have to
hold it again though right that's a
golden up oh yeah well yeah true
probably do we
if we go to the studio do we have to no
I will I will take it just in case
because I'm confused no okay okay okay
okay
no okay I think maybe fine maybe digital
let's go to that I made the birds the
studio
[Music]
what's up
hello
surprise
[Music]
oh my gosh we're so tiny in here oh yeah
but but it's actually supposed to be
like
um
made for us tiny people because there's
also like instruments and stuff and
they're all made for us
perfect size for your perfect little
hands I drink some more water
oh me too me too everybody hydrate
hydrate everybody hmm
oh I think this is the same for the
Ninja sandsian World probably if I if I
remember correctly but both of these
worlds if I'm not wrong you guys can
visit right
I don't know if you can visit at the
moment oh was it like wasn't it like
visible before
yeah it was it was it was ah okay I
think our world is always visitable but
not the not the studio I think of maybe
the studio might be different
so actually uh I wanted to show you
um a a little game that I um prepared
like before yeah I changed it I changed
it up so that it says pomo's name I just
find you know it's it's fun to have a
little game and before we do something
else let me go yeah I'll turn on
game game
use tonight
oh
welcome to the Maldives Maldives
[Music]
yeah yeah I know I know I remember your
streams about it yes I went on a
vacation here with kindness so I before
we went I made this uh I have to I had
this area made with a little game a
gimmick uh oh yeah how do we start the
game it's not here now is it oh God
oh I think it will be prepared yeah
yeah so we're gonna play this
um just just once just one round so the
rules are uh by the way this is this is
um today packing game so you see all
these items here various items and you
see two suitcases mine is orange one
yours is the blue one and basically I
will start by taking for example this
brush and I say I pack in my suitcase
the brush and then it says
[Music]
your turn you have to remember the brush
that I packed and add something onto it
but you have to put both both in your
suitcase
yes
okay
brush okay
and we'll do stinky sock
stinky sock which one
um the right one okay
um
the brass and this one suck stinky yeah
and a new item I will bring item my
bikini tops yeah
sexy
all right your turn and we got a brush a
brush yeah for the beautiful bubble hair
a stinky sock for the beautiful
oh yeah
yes yes
a bikini top oh it's a little big on me
I think it's more for you it's a little
don't worry don't worry it has pads it
has pads inside it makes it look bigger
than it actually yes yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay good good okay all right round one
more thing let's do the Chucky camera
do you have one of those I have one in
pink actually
oh man I love mint color nice pretty
yeah okay brush stinky sock brush I
don't know what this game
yeah cute you know actually I I also
have um like this is really cool you
know for checking camera you were like
uh when you make a mistake then the
photos messed up and you can't save it
but I have uh like a checky printer that
can print out any photo from your phone
yeah and then it looks like a real
cheeky so that way you can take a photo
with your phone first make sure that
it's actually looks like something you
want to you know save spend lots of
money on checkies for because they are
like really expensive right they are
really expensive yeah so yeah
um yeah and I have that
yeah
I don't even remember what did I do and
then oh yeah oh yeah sandal yeah
flip-flops we call them flip-flops
oh the flip-flops yeah
item promo
yeah um
um before that I just um
yeah yeah yeah yeah
I just you know if you if you wanted to
like you know maybe talk more like you
know about you know how
um you know just just anything you want
to honestly just anything you know how
was it how was yeah how was
[Music]
these I only like um terrible timing
because we went when there was like
constantly uh uh typhoon uh would you
call that again
typhoon is all right Monsoon wait
Monsoon is different yeah yeah as soon
as I guess the season
[Laughter]
actually we're doing a really good job
at like confusing ourselves because I am
confused right now
um bikini Tom
and chicken
and then the flip-flops I think yeah and
and then and then a ticket ticket
[Music]
reminds me we're packing our bags right
now remember remember that guys remember
the big bamboozle when I showed you guys
[Music]
yeah
you made fun of my fanny pack yes and I
I still stand by my statements
actually Kiara I have a I have a bone to
pick with you a bone um okay yeah I also
you know
you know okay I'm gonna fight you right
now this is this is about my gingerbread
house
oh if it isn't the consequences of your
own actions of picking a fight with me
oh my God
[Music]
wait what was after the stinky sock was
it the sandals oh you're messing up
there you're messing up there already oh
[Music]
and then
flip-flops
and then beat the ticket
and then what and then what
declare your loss
give up give up
give up give up it's my win
okay yeah surely it was the shock take
it put it in there yes
it was this
yeah it was the passport
[Applause]
[Music]
wait was it actually the sock no I I
just um took the this here the
90s ones oh the ears earphones earphones
oh
I was I was just like why you were
talking it was like oh this is the
moment quick quick while she's talking
about it was good because you can't see
it so well it's like you know just it's
so small
so you couldn't have caught I got
Bamboozled yeah
this is exactly all according to keikaku
[Music]
and next time I'll get you next time
okay so the game is over we can change
to the the like other background now I
think
yeah yeah
let me change I'm gonna try to change
oh Studio I think oh oh
blue orange purple red white
this one
can you play any instruments
I used to be able to play the violin oh
what
what that's so cool
[Music]
that's so cool I can't play Anything Is
there a violin here no I feel like a
guitar should be somewhere here oh oh
actually yeah Mama come here
get yourself a microphone
or or you can even get a banjo there's
like all kinds of cool stuff back here
uh
wait the microphones were not here
yes I take microphone
I'll take this one okay
sorry we have no no Pomo colored
microphone but we also have light sticks
oh yeah let me get a promo colored light
stick
yeah
what for what for what could it be for
no
foreign
light stick too
I have
um
now you have some in your in your model
thingy
yeah yeah
how do I do it again
uh gestures
I don't think I have those
ah
there we go and then I can change the
color wow it's so long too
I can make it shorter um
[Music]
next let me change it to
orange wait do I have orange
Orange
the first one does not have orange first
one look like orange not that one did
the one that it started out the first
one of Orange
that was red
so there was a different color before
oh it was oh but when you first opened
it was right on my screen oh well anyway
pick whatever color red is fine too I
think
um okay so guys you may wonder why did
we bring out some microphones well well
well I thought uh it's a special
occasion so we might as well make the
most out of it so I am
to join me and sing some songs but first
before we sing together
I make the stage
[Music]
yes
Paul was saying fine
um
it's
it's too real
okay all right
tell us when you're ready
all right give me one second oh yeah I
also have to switch them make the volume
louder maybe you have to do that too
just saying
yeah okay
okay guys
okay are you guys ready do you want to
hear some cute Pomo fairy singing
[Music]
it's your stage now I'll turn on the
music from are you ready
yes
okay free
[Music]
uh I just saw I just saw the message yes
one moment please one moment please
um
okay I'm ready I'm ready okay stop two
three two
one
[Music]
memories
[Applause]
[Music]
fingers
foreign
[Music]
but they keep pushing and pulling me
if I go wrong what awaits me in the dark
could you tell me please where I need to
go
[Music]
tell me I can hear it clearly
[Applause]
[Music]
shut up
I'm so embarrassed oh my God
foreign
[Music]
so maybe it's time for me
what what will koala sing hmm
what will she sing
what could she possibly sing when you
guys think I'll be singing
so you know
where you stand right now by the way is
perfect because I had to cut it cuts off
exactly with your cute ribbon I like
that
it I can see that I have an audience I
like having an audience
I mean
[Music]
thank you all right I'll sing a song oh
please listen while I sing uh
okay uh I'm ready I'm ready anytime hmm
one two three
that day I opened up memories door
I found something that I could live for
Curt and shook as you open my eyes
and Light Came rushing inside
behind my hearts and grips
[Music]
your fire Spike the passion that keeps
burning
magic that helps me to believe
[Music]
these emotions
don't cry look in my eyes
[Music]
yes
yeah
when gray skies take the colors away
far away and the rainbow lasting for
days and days
[Music]
we'll never have to be alone Diamond
City
news
Skies
[Music]
behind don't cry look in my eyes and
kill my
firing light don't let me guide you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
somebody
aren't don't cry look at my eyes
[Music]
Rainbow Skies
we finally arrived for Mom finally
arrived in the diamond City Light City
you're right right we finally the train
departed or dropped us off here the song
is so hard
I tried so hard with the deeper lines
it's so difficult
them
you know I was like I was like I wonder
I was like I wonder if I have time to
learn the dance that you have for
hinotori I was like trying to do like
the leg
um
even if you were to do it oh where am I
oh
um
sorry even if you were to do it with
these small bodies then you you can't
show it properly
ah I'm trying
oh God I'm exhausted from Dad Palmer I'm
exhausted
don't be exhausted yeah we still have
more songs
what is missing guys what is missing
what is missing I think a song with both
of us right
yeah yeah okay oh boy I'm nervous let's
Stand Together on the yellow one here
okay okay
oh there's Spotlight cool
I have to stand in the middle oh gosh
wow okay so
um both of us each chose one song that
we want to sing with each other
yeah right we're gonna stop I haven't
gotten the song yeah the one that you
picked it's been stuck in my head like
ever since you sent it to me it's so
good it's so good yeah I took the chance
to see something that I I was like
hoping to sing with someone one day but
first at first we sing the song that you
chose which I okay actually I didn't
know before ever but I I really like it
too
I really like it it's a really chill
song I like it a lot yeah it has a nice
vibe to it oh but I also want to say oh
my God I love Diamond City Lights it's
stuck in my head forever and when I was
practicing
the first couple times uh after like the
second chorus
the moment the third chorus starts at
the latest I would like I would start
crying because
it made me cry man it's not fair I
always
I know I remember when I first heard it
the like the first time we got the demo
I was thinking that way too I was like
oh my God am I gonna cry every time I
sing this just has that like kind of art
yeah cool there's nobody
okay uh are you are you ready for our
song Together wait let me get in
position again yeah where's my I lost my
well then I'm gonna get rid of this oops
let me
um I think my my microphone went over
here for some reason okay wait
okay
okay okay okay
I'm nervous I hope all goes well
alrighty
I think I'm already maybe if we raise
our hands then the music upsell holy
[\h__\h] the music can be cute when when we
both raise our hands
okay
[Music]
all right hold on
um
let's sing together
foreign
[Music]
anymore
oh God
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
but it's back it's bad
oh no no you can watch promo's archive
later to uh watch the uh almost a rapid
version I don't know if my archive will
be on interacted
oh but her hers definitely will not be
interrupted yeah yeah we're back with
back we're back welcome back chat
welcome back welcome back
it was just a tiny bit at the end you
didn't miss much guys don't worry and
yeah it didn't miss much because we
missed the whole fireworks oh yeah that
was a big firework yes yes yes
okay oh there's one more
I'm so excited about this one
yeah the next one actually has like
harmonies and it's supposed to be a song
that sang with two people so when I was
saying changing songs
[Music]
it is a hello project song it's so good
yeah and I commissioned an instrumental
just for this occasion so if you guys
really like and singing this maybe who
knows since I commissioned an
instrumental maybe we can put out an
official song cover at some point
you know it's really good yes
so cool yes the instrumental is made
made by raining marbles the credit will
be in the description afterwards too so
thank you for making it sounds awesome
okay so actually so you know you don't
have a project right
yeah yes of course you do so
um this song
the song is made up of um uh two members
from two different Idol groups one is
from Vegas my favorite Idol groom that
doesn't exist anymore sad
and the other one is cute cute dog you
know cute though
they also they also don't exist anymore
also sad yeah
the Golden Era yeah but but so these two
members they were put into a unit and
they released literally only one song
but it's really cool so please listen to
many more minutes are you ready
[Music]
where's my mouse where's my mouse
I hear this okay we raise our hands I'm
ready when you are okay when we're ready
to raise hand okay
okay
lady mermaid
version go
[Music]
one other one
for the one
one
[Music]
time
that anymore
[Music]
foreign
Keep Me Down
[Music]
here
foreign
[Music]
oh my gosh oh gosh there we go
guys I think I think if there's anyone
in the chat yours or mine who knows who
knew this song from before I honestly
want to have a talk with you have a cafe
a coffee
with you because it's even in the inside
of the hair project where it's like you
have to really dig really deeply to get
to that song because you know like how
sap units
[Music]
so this unit wasn't even just a normal
unit you know hello project had like
this weird thing where it's called like
satoyama something something where the
idols they would like um do like some
some stuff on the countryside like
agriculture kind of stuff and for that
campaign you know that oh my God yeah oh
my God
they made like several units with songs
about stuff like that like this lady
mermaid song not not quite so much about
agriculture but some other songs they
made for this purpose but kind of
weirdly about agriculture
tell me something about about your
favorite your favorite idols
tell me because I'm too excited I need
to calm down I need to calm down
I like that you know it's hard to find
sometimes girl fans of Idols I know
we're like basically different sections
you know because you're like really
hello Pro yeah hello
I really like um
[Music]
morning musume songs oh um
there's hard they're hard to find
sometimes karaoke for them like I really
like the um
[Music]
during the time
I don't think I knew enough to have an
Oshie I really like the sayumi but you
know because she's like an idol Legend
she was such
[Music]
and she would go like uh
beyond your Headliners
she has some solo songs
yeah yeah I listen a little bit to it
yeah I've heard you I've heard you
yurushiyan
[Music]
maybe maybe with our powers together we
can drag people into the rabbit hole
that is it could be and a hello project
let's go
you know
oh you really became like it's like it's
like this kind of reminds me of sherbert
it feels like you're like in sherbet ice
cream yeah yeah yeah yeah like a gelato
ice cream I want to be orange floor
there we go
[Laughter]
[Music]
um yes beautiful
um so I wanted this one to be special
and I think it was special don't you
think
I think so yeah
so Chad please look forward to lots of
fun collapse from now on yeah
yeah
I'm like oh I need a shower
me too
how do you sink into the floor like that
I literally lie down on my actual floor
how did you do it oh gosh I'm tangled in
poor you're not you're not quite ready
to become one with the floor yet
get down on my level
I can't physically cannot
we need to chill you have so much
experience yes floor experience
she's also one of the floor
yeah floor gang what's up floor gang
what's up if I if I if I lay down okay
here we go I'm testing I'm testing my
limits
whoa you're getting there
enamel you're becoming one of the floor
again you just have to you're there
you're there you've reached the floor
you became one with the floor
you sure you should become one with the
yellow floor right next to me
[Laughter]
how are you doing
I'm turning on the floor I'm getting
dizzy
[Laughter]
oh my God
[Music]
we're spinning this is next level floor
again
next level [\h__\h] yeah oh I feel like I'm
going into a new dimension I'm traveling
or no one has traveled before
[Music]
can we go faster
I can't go fast oh God I don't know
how are you how are you spinning so
smoothly I can only go with free FPS
you're oh you were spinning smoothly
before really
it's okay I'm happy with this
so I really want to take this headset
off as soon as I can guys
I hope you enjoyed this oh God yeah uh
yeah thank you very much for watching
this was uh takanasikara from Whole Life
English and
yeah
you can see our channels in each other's
descriptions well thank you for being so
kind I know that my audience
um they are all very very welcoming of
Pomo in there or they all love promo
because I talk about you a lot and also
I think they just kind of like because
both of our personalities I don't know
about your your daddy's but I thank you
for
um yeah letting me uh get closer to
Palmer yeah
[Music]
I'm really glad that we could finally
have this yeah actually happen yeah like
after so long yeah yeah I was bound to
be we we wanted to do this for a long
time
and finally the time and now now the
gates To Hell have been opened yeah I
was gonna
we should play Monopoly
oh God we just became
so thank you guys for watching and uh
yeah please support us and let's have
more fun in the future and be nice to
each other and yeah yeah yeah
and in Germany what do you say in in
German or in English
the German I say uh
three times nine
three times three times nine
[Music]
wow I love you
too
oh God time to get up now
[Music]
foreign
this is nice
things
foreign
[Music]