[Music]
guys we have a problem now
we have a problem
i think uh what is it
you know there's good news right i think
i'm dead hold on
i think i'm dead but that's not the
problem that's not the problem
it's not a problem i'm dead i'm gonna
restart myself for a little bit
but
okay the problem is
you know i got my ac replaced right
sorry i died
but
you know
i got my ac replaced so i gotta i gotta
tell you guys a little bit of a
backstory
so
the day before my birthday
my ac died my air conditioning died like
of all days i just decided to
die
on that night
so how happened was
nothing i was just doing my business as
usual right
i was just doing my business as usual
and then
i don't know there was like a tiny bit
of a sound of you know
the weird sound when
your lights kind of like
die but like it doesn't
it's weird i don't know how to explain
it to you at no english
and then suddenly the hc just shut off
like you know when the ac turned on it
stays uh you know like the mouth is open
right when it's turned turned on
and if you turn it off like the mouth
will close or something
that's just how it is in general right
well how it happened was you know
suddenly the ac turned off and it was
just
dead
and then
i was like oh no how am i gonna do this
it was it was actually during the right
before the right before the birthday
countdown stream and i was like oh i'm
okay am i gonna do this so i actually
signed the countdown in extreme heat and
in this extreme humidity i think but but
yeah
it wouldn't turn on and then
you know there really wasn't
apparently we tried contacting like this
you know the oh ac service people but
there was no person that couldn't come
like the latest was tomorrow and
tomorrow it was like almost what it was
almost impossible to but kind of like
they clutched
yeah so
for one night i slept without any
cooling and
you know
it's awful
but the good thing is the good thing is
now now now now the ac is back
you know
the ac is come on
the ac is back but
i now have a new problem
the problem is
you know it broke okay the ac broke
that apparently we had to change it
you know but i was like i'm not going to
live without ac for the rest of my life
i mean i'm not going to not live without
ac for the rest of my life so i had to
change it right so that's a good change
and finally yay we got it changed but
my current problem is the ac is too new
so it's too cold
[Music]
yeah
i mean i could make it softer but i
could make the ac softer but i don't
know
what a rainy problem i know it's like
but i don't want to turn it down because
matt and ac these this naturally cool
you know like usually like even when you
when the ac is low and then you set to
the lowest settings the coldest settings
like it's not even like that cold
but now it feels super cold and i you
know i'm gonna lose this privilege when
the ac starts you know breaking down of
old age so i want to make use of this as
much as possible you know imagine having
a room this cold
well
wayne is sensitive to the cold i'm
sensitive to the heat and the cold
everything
yes
yes yes might want to keep it yeah it's
like it's better if i'm cool it's better
to wear a jacket like this is
you know it's still doing full capacity
so i'd rather use it to its fullest
potential
yes yes yes yes oh no the room became a
freezer
how about blocking some airflow okay a
good thing is i have my new chair now
and it's pretty good at blocking ac so
you know i'm only getting ac from from
the sides
from the sides the ac is behind me but
i'm only getting it from the sides
yes yes yes or maybe i did adapt to the
state of no ac so now it feels cold but
i don't know
i just want to tell you the random ac
story uh but today's stream is a calling
stream you know normally people do
normally people do maybe uh you know
like speaking for 10 minutes and then at
the 10 minutes mark they immediately
start to call in but i want to talk to
you for like 20 minutes
accept your artic lifestyle my goodness
but um yes today is a calling stream and
as usual people are going to be calling
in
and you know we have a setting today so
it's not really just a regular calling
like we did last year but i prepared
also like a very very very short game
for them
yes yes yes yes
30 minutes times how many people oh oh
no no no no i mean like i mean like
before the calling starts we have like
yeah so we're starting calling in like
probably like possibly 17 minutes from
now
spicy game yes
so if you guys you know you guys might
not be able to tell because
this is very realistic like i'm working
from home so it just looks like my house
but this is actually a maracating a
maracating academy a marketing academy
so
the concept of today's call-in is that
you will you know people will have to
call in
and then there i will show
a wheel a certain wheel a certain wheel
let me
i can show it to you guys
whoa whoa whoa
no the wheel is showing chat
he's so annoying wait i change
now stupid wheel
ah okay give me give me like five
minutes no one minute actually
uh basically okay i'm gonna explain i
will be showing a wheel and then there
you guys will
not you guys the callers will spin the
wheel and then they will do the prompts
you know the prompts are related to
marketing they are trying they're gonna
try to sell me something
yeah chat is everywhere my goodness
why are you guys everywhere don't infest
don't infest the wheel
come on
um is it properly
is that yet
yes
hello uh and now as punishment it's
gonna cover you
[Laughter]
it's not gambling
it's not gambling actually i'm gonna i'm
gonna try to move you elsewhere that's
more visible
because you guys are funny
yes
okay
i don't know maybe here
yeah spin the wheel so um this also has
japanese and there's some english but
maybe you know some messages don't fit
so i will explain it to you guys one by
one
in a rainy marathon academy work from
home edition we have
this wheel and then you can spin it
we can spin it we can try spitting it
[Music]
yay
there's actually like a very uh there's
a very tascadu
noise but
let's see if i can let's see if i can
get it on stream
all done
okay
i'll try to spin again
ah for example this landed in arada
right
yes yes yes yes yes yes
what's raining dude i don't even know
why it's raining there
we can uh
uh we can
what the heck is this
um
free let's make rainy free
let's make rainy free
i don't even know
i don't even know what that is
free so they can choose
[Music]
love msg yeah basically uh oh sorry it
made uh with x oh it turned to expired
food not ara sorry sorry guys that
wasn't on purpose so
if you land on expired food that means
see i call you see you're calling in
hello and we're gonna play a little game
and because this is a sales academy
you're gonna be trying to
sell me
sell me some expired food for example
you can pick
maybe
oh my god this expired this expired milk
you know it has a very distinguished
flavor it's freshness and sourness is
guaranteed to wake you up and you know
the line that you're lying you know the
very very unique texture is um different
from any other milk you know only one
way you know only one chance to try and
this is very special because mostly
people leave milk for like three days
and gone bad but this one has been
fermented just like your finest wines
for one month isn't that special
something like that
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yeah this is the milk you can chew
what is the difference for bonus one and
bonus two okay bonus one is bonus two is
actually not against you but more like
quote unquote against me
so
bonus one if you're lucky to get bonus
one you can make me say uh if you get
bonus one you can tell me to say
anything so it's kind of like me telling
you to say ah
but you can tell me say anything but and
then number two is a free tweet ticket
you know
you can claim if you don't claim it's
your loss but you can claim a free
tweety ticket to me
yes
is that so exactly it is what it is
and i know message love messages
basically just um
it basically said and give me a love
message you know gives me a love message
and
four is a food it says a food dude but
this one is a food you want to recommend
to me so it's no it doesn't really feel
like a punishment but
it's really i want you guys to
tell me a food you like that you think i
would like so just recommend it and try
it
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
okay
leave it to better recite the entirety
of love me love me
and then number three is furniture
really uh it really can be anything if
you guys are out of ideas oh yeah well
sell me
sell me this this gaming chair sell me a
gaming chair
or sell me sell me a mic you know you
guys can find inspiration from my own
layout anyways
yeah it's not supposed to be that hard
because i mean this is just to like
spice up the game you know to just to
spice up the collins you know i think
after after
after one year you know it would be nice
to feel i could do something else so
this is what i came up with randomly
would you get a food that doesn't sell
in indonesia what do you mean doesn't
sell like it's not sold or like in
general like they don't sell
[Music]
get a bamboo map for your bed
bamboo mats are they say it's like good
for the back you know like compared to
soft beds uh harder beds are actually
better for for your bag they say but you
know what i don't care i just want my
soft bed
and
yeah and for rainy there's also a act
like me like basically rainey no
monomoney like
act like me but if somebody uh i don't
want to put anyone in like an awkward
position so you can they can choose if
they get number one they can choose
either a act like me or
just me in three words
yeah
so this is it this is what the wheel is
i hope you guys like your faces in the
middle
yes
oh my gosh if you guys if you guys if
you guys were in here and then you get
the bonus too i bet you guys are gonna
make something like oh my god i love
socks so much or something like that
thank goodness it's now for holo mims
and there's actually there's actually uh
uh mostly today's holobands and then
there's also not holoman one person can
you guess who it is but yes
she knows that's well of course
of course of course of course of course
but um well we have uh
10 minutes until the first call and that
explanation went um faster than i
thought it would be um there has been a
little bit of change of schedule um i
have five minutes
no wait i think the first 15 minutes was
supposed to be um
was supposed to be uh filled uh with um
with with with some people but
there has been a change of schedule and
they will be moved to the back so
i will be opening uh gifts first some
members sent me a video
some members sent me a video and so i
was about to open them maybe after all
the collins but i'm gonna open it once
first
okay i'm gonna open them i'm surprised
there's no join there
they all joined in their hearts
yes yes
okay we saw ollie's present oh yes the
cake
which one she also made a different
present
[Music]
and yes yes yes yes yes
yeah the cake was um something i guess i
was like
imagine
yes
imagine being
um
yeah sorry
what was i gonna say it was very bloody
honest yeah i was like imagine being the
person who had to write that but i think
you know because that person is so used
to writing a lot of messages maybe
they're used to it you know how many
people like are like ollie you know
there might be like a lot of people like
that
yes yes yes yes
yeah the ac
that's the ac's fault so sad
okay actually we have several videos to
show so actually very very
we have three videos i think i am going
to um
import them
i'm going to import them here
just
to be
just so that i can show them soon
[Music]
oh my god i almost exactly played the
message without showing it
okay
remember kiara's valentine's day card
what did it say i remember the card and
then i remember making a remark to it
like ooh aggressive or something but i
really don't remember what it said sorry
it's not like i just have like the brain
the brain of like a goldfish
bless you
thank you okay so you know what i might
turn off the ac wait okay which one
breaks the ac faster if you keep turning
it on and off or if you keep if you keep
like changing the temperature which one
breaks the ac faster this is like legit
new ac so i'm like scared
[Music]
it's not a rainy stream without me
adjusting the ac
i'll gobble you up
on off and breaks as fast okay
guys it's like 23 degrees but it's so
cold
oh my god this is real 23 degrees
you know this is what 23 degrees feel
like you know like when people usually
like flex with with ac's you know they
do it all the time like i remember when
i was little they would be like well
what what ac what what degree is your ac
and i would be like okay just like 18
because you know like in fact it's not
18 right and then they're like oh i'm 16
you know because apparently 60 is the
lowest setting for them but it doesn't
even come close to real 16 degrees you
know because either the ac quality has
deteriorated or is just like the
combination of the heat of the room but
this one this feels like real 23 degrees
actually it might be colder than 20 ohm
okay this is 23 degrees but i'm wearing
like very minimal like
clothing so it's like
cold hold on
okay
yo they do increments of decimals this
new ac they have they can do 23.5 that's
so good
[Music]
okay i think it's um i think it's the
fan two that's causing it to be coldish
okay i'm gonna
i'm gonna oh where's the message
okay okay
nice nice nice nice
nice
oh
i want to put on an accessory first i
want to put on an accessory because
uh one person
one person one person who uh sent me a
message also gave the same uh
same props as her
hey
of course celsius indonesia are normal
human beings yes celsius because we're
normal people
oh
minimal clothing
yes yes
yeah okay let's make let's make this one
reflect this as well minimal clothing
let's
go yeah we got props actually
let me let me just try
let me just try
okay never mind i don't know
maybe later
23c is hot
i don't know why yeah i guess this is
not 23.
it's it seems colder than 23 also i
don't know why i'm dying
omg undressing live how could you so sad
not so sad but okay and also i don't
know why i'm starting to die but it's
okay
but yes all these meatballs
it's okay i think it's like i'd like to
think that i'm very very nervous that
i'm starting to lag out but you know
guys when i move to my new studio this
will not happen anymore i'm so happy
i think they're um they're gonna do it
next week so i'm gonna i'm gonna be able
to actually move uh
next week i don't know what day yet so i
do i think schedules are gonna be a
little bit weird
because i have to move all of my pc set
up
technically i would be able to stream
from laptop
so it shouldn't really be that big of a
deal
even if i end up taking time to move the
pc i can play some like lighter games
over there
i was going to like play the new hollow
cure like oh i could play the new hole
here the laptop but my data is on my pc
so i don't know if i almost how i'm
supposed to do that i can move it and
then move it back when i can use my
laptop again
new studio soon i know right okay i'm
gonna
i'm gonna be putting a new video
um
[Music]
put it
okay
restart playback when source becomes
active i don't know what this means
okay
i think it's okay
and then
[Music]
i can
show you guys
oh the video is not here so i think i'll
have to pause it first
and then play it
oh means autoplay it means a new hide or
show it okay okay okay i got you i got
you i got you
well it's gonna be 10 30
soon so i'm going to be
i'll be right back because i'm so
nervous i want to wash my hands in the
bathroom and i'll be back real quick
i'll be right back
[Music]
okay
we are back
nobody's so good let's go
please say it from earlier it's still
pinned what oh okay i can see yeah
please wait okay this one means please
wait for the call call-in okay we're
gonna play the
video
oh no
[Laughter]
restart playback i needed to take that
okay
so cute
[Laughter]
[Music]
i can't hear it you guys probably can't
hear it but i can't so i need to
i need
to you go
news output i think
should i mute output yes i think
okay let's play the video guys
watching duck video
okay i'm gonna turn off the
thingy
turn off the music for a little bit
okay let's play it
[Music]
bye
today
i had that today
is rainey's party and i can have fun
talking and playing a game with you
so
i'm sorry i'm so sorry
bad
next time this friend
ah and let's
go on a trip sometimes
uh i want to
travel with you and horatoli
i cannot forget the beautiful thing lady
showed me before
i would like to
hear
if you have any friends you would like
to visit in japan or abroad
and
if we want to travel
please show me lenny's cute neck pillow
[Music]
i cannot forget that
cute snake pillow
happy
[Music]
so cute
[Laughter]
so cute oh my god guys uh yeah that was
like the max audio audio volume i could
put in in the yeah i hope it wasn't too
soft but yes do you guys remember the
neck pillow the next pillow that i
showed
the next pillow that i showed her uh in
the did i submit it in the mid corner do
you record on the uh show
yes
it's a segment about like if uh you know
uh they have to guess like which items
whose or something like that and which
ones but no one yeah the yakuet the
yeah the
the 100 yen
shop thing
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
yes and then uh actually uh it's the
same pie i also like talked about like
trips and everything so yeah next time
next time next time we should definitely
have a trip together
yes
[Laughter]
to most that was a normal neck pillow
tushy but it was the most important
thing of her life it's really cute right
cute neck pillow i actually have several
i have several so you know
neck pillow party let's go you know
usually people when they do sleepovers
they have
you know pillow pillow fight but for me
it's the neck pillow fight
okay uh i will uh show you guys another
video
[Music]
i will show you guys another video and
um
there are three videos i think yes yes
yes yes who's next i wonder
[Music]
i'm gonna turn off the audio again i'm
sorry audio you came back so soon and i
have to mute you again
is this an animal video too
uh yes
yes it's
animal video
okay are you guys ready
oh my god
okay
[Music]
hello rayne
happy birthday
happy birthday hello reign
of hololive indonesia it's me
i'm here to wish you the happiest
birthday
[Music]
come here wish you a happy birthday how
many times can i say that once
do you want to twix i came on prepare
but i have a twix
and i don't really want it anymore but
i'm here to offer it to you i've already
eaten a piece of it would you like the
other half
i just i want a bite
twix
okay so happy birthday i made you
something that's not a twix here it is
wow
that was delicious um anyway happy
birthday bye
oh my god
[Laughter]
thank you for
for the twix
yeah good god told me she was gonna send
me a video
[Laughter]
yeah very cool twix i know when was the
last time i ate twix
i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna
get it i'm gonna get it today just
because i mean like totally eat the the
twix from from gura yeah of course
that's a weird animal video
i think it's marvelous thank you so much
google for the funny message
for the whole the wholesome message
yeah
totally regular group of videos
let's go
yeah
sure yeah so many animals in whole life
i feel like
interesting interesting wait bear with
me i'm gonna um
i'm gonna steal uh i'm gonna steal
profile pictures
i'm gonna steal profile pictures for the
collins
who do you think will be the first to
call
in uh there's there's actually no really
no order but
uh there was an order i mean but it's
not like really based on anything
so
yeah who do you think is gonna call in
first there's gonna be one more video
after this and then the actual calling
is going to start at like a minute 45
so yes
so yes yes i'm gonna create call in
folder
oh my god i forgot i think wait
save
okay i forgot i made a folder and i
forgot to put the actual person in the
folder
what did i make a folder for
okay
[Music]
i need to stand by i need to stand by in
the call-in so i think i might play the
last video after this
will we expect em chance evanston's hard
at work
behind the scenes
she's not gonna call in story guys i
know she's your favorite but yeah
i'm gonna show you guys the last video
this one is this an animal i don't think
this is an animal
but
but but you'll see
but you'll see yeah hello fans of the
managers okay okay
like actually none of this none of these
videos i i never watched i haven't
watched them this is this is this is the
first time i'm watching them because i
want to be surprised and i don't really
want to talk over them because um i just
want to like listen to them for the
first time so
yeah let's have the third one
are you guys excited
okay let's go
i think
okay let's do this fauna was restless
all day she had been anticipating her
senpai's birthday for what felt like a
year but she still wasn't sure what gift
she could give
chocolate
no that's for valentine's day
maybe a video game
but which game
fauna turned over the ideas in her head
until it was too late to make chocolate
or go shopping
there had to be some way to show her
appreciation to her senpai
she sat at her desk gathered some loose
papers and began to write
there was something that rainie would
surely appreciate
a fanfic so spicy her fingers would burn
holding the pages
after riding late into the night finally
the fanfic was done
all that was left was to give it to
rainey fauna rushed to school the next
day gripping the worn pages between her
fingers
if she could just catch rainy before
class you would be able to give her the
gift
8 10 a.m i'm late
vana began to panic as she realized
rainy's class was already starting she
sprinted down the hall as fast as she
could but
she crashed into rainy as she ran in the
corner fauna fell to the ground as the
fanfic pages scattered floating through
the air around them
rainey reached out a hand to fauna
[Music]
are you okay she asked looking very cool
i'm fine
it's just
fauna stammered
rain i noticed the pages floating around
what's this she asked
fauna wasn't prepared for rainy to read
the fanfic right in front of her but
rainey had already picked a page from
the floor
she began to read
their lips met as the setting sun turned
at the sky the vibrant shades of pink
grapefruit whoa fauna did you write this
this is spicy who's it about
rainy picked up another page
rainey is such a cool senpai she's an
amazing singer and talented artist with
the best taste in analog horror in video
games not to mention her sense of humor
and kindness
huh
this is about me
but when reynae looked up from the pages
fauna had disappeared
did she die of embarrassment right on
the spot or simply run and hide from
around the corner
no one can say
the only certainty is that she hopes
rainey has an amazing birthday
happy birthday raining
[Music]
[Laughter]
the end
oh my god
thank you
there's so many creative people in
hololens
reconcile
well it seems like fun and needs to um
of that embarrassment
for
the greetings i i just randomly chose
the order of the greetings and they just
like get more and more chaotic but
more and more chaotic
part to doco oh my gosh maybe we can
make it like a collaborative
effort
creative people are spicy people oh
wait i'm gonna uh i'm gonna go in the
or maybe maybe maybe maybe i need to
make sure
that okay this is
okay okay okay
i have two minutes i have two minutes i
have two minutes
to put image
image for the people
imagine for the people wait i don't uh
i'm scared uh i'm scared i will
accidentally spoil
so i'll have to be sure
okay this one is
okay
yes
yeah guys okay
i will show the picture over here
[Applause]
i'm so nervous it's my first time doing
something like this
because
i don't know
i'm just very nervous because normally i
do normal callings and this will be the
first time i'm doing this work from home
oh let me let me spin the wheel a few
times let's spin the wheel a few times
[Music]
yeah okay see okay this one i don't know
what so i'm gonna spin again
yeah sometimes like it it arrives like
right in the middle or something
but yeah so cute right
[Music]
why why
spin yeah in the event of uh you know if
it arrives in a very like vague place
then
um i'm gonna have to
ah okay love message yeah okay okay this
is just for practice okay
okay okay okay okay rigged wheel
nice and then three is basically you can
choose
to choose one two six
[Music]
it's message no msg yeah love message
not love msg i you know i wanted to
write it with all caps but i know that's
what you guys are gonna say
anyways the first guest is gonna be a jp
member
gonna be a jp member so yes uh please
come in if you if you if you want if you
guys are if you if you are hearing this
please come in
oh my gosh they're still actually
submitting png's
oh my oh my
i guess we can we can put this png
yes yes yes yes
[Music]
it's time
then um
how do i ping how do i ping this person
uh i can't write
um um
i don't know how to ping
[Laughter]
there we are
okay okay
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
okay
[Music]
yes
okay
let's go spin
come on
[Applause]
[Music]
you
okay
yes
[Music]
thank
[Laughter]
okay thank you for coming today
thank you
[Music]
oh my god
so she was selling me a stew that was uh
that has mold on it
she was telling me uh yeah
still with mold
okay
who is here
uh maybe we could move on uh is she
okay next person
just to save time maybe
uh
okay okay okay okay
maybe maybe
oh oh oops
oh she's there
yeah we're on a bit of a time schedule
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
let's enjoy
[Applause]
so
three
[Music]
is
okay thank you so much
[Music]
okay
okay okay okay uh i think
so cute
so cute i think the next person
can come in
[Music]
the next person can come
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
me
yes
m
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
she got the love message and she told me
that you know oh it's a very very cute
love message but she told me that you
know basically whenever like uh let's
have a let's play i want to play
together a lot and then if i if i go to
japan and then let's have like a you
know like a real like let's go out
together and have some fun have a real
date so nice
and then uh kyla's message because she
got a bonus uh it's like kyla is 100 not
a penguin
yeah but rules are rules okay rules are
rules
okay
thank you for the translation yes yes we
have a lot of different languages here
so i think once in a while after a few
calls i'll try to like translate what's
going on
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes yes yes yes
not a penguin just for today but anyways
our next person you can come in
[Music]
wait okay next person can come in
just for today hello
hello hello
hello
thank you for coming today
thank
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
so anya i preferred a little game today
do you wanna
try it out uh if you have if you have
the do you know the rules because uh
yeah um i i did it already okay nice
before that before that uh let me send
you something oh of course of course of
course it's like a little something but
it has all my emotions
in one picture so spicy
it has all my emotions in one picture
omg
wait let me let me show it to everyone
[Music]
oh
the most important
yeah
okay
so cool guys anya's picture oh my god
omg it has all my emotion in one picture
do you like twin tails
um yes nice i mean
okay are you ready to spin
oh my god oh my god okay okay um any
so i tell you to start oral i tell ya
you tell me to start and i'll spin it
for you okay um
okay um three two one go
okay it stops by itself go go
[Music]
it's okay i'm a professional you know
expired okay
no show me let's fight food yeah yo you
can sell me try to sell me expired food
okay
expired food okay
so rainy
you know what's the most delicious food
in drust
what what is it
it's anya's meat
oh my goodness
even if it gets like even if it's
expired you can still like sever it to
its fullest because it's that good oh
wow but doesn't it doesn't doesn't human
meat make you thirsty make you
dehydrated how do you counter that
nah it's okay it's like a first-class
meat even if you feel dehydrated that
just means you're halu it actually
doesn't make you dehydrated because it's
the first class meet in the whole server
the last whole server
oh my god
yeah if you come upon a melvisa meat a
meat fisa you say
it's called meat fisa by the way you
should definitely eat it without
thinking
yes of course of course of course the
next time i see melfissa i will try to
kill her and harvest her meat
yes
exactly
happy birthday
thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god oh oh
wow
[Laughter]
so amazing guys
there was anya with her
not addiction
that's what she sold me
very cool
[Laughter]
okay i think
yes you can come in please
okay who do we have
who do we have here
[Music]
hello
hi
um
[Music]
thank you
okay
three two
two one
speed
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
oh
is
[Music]
okay
so scary
she's making she's making use of her
bonus very well
she's making use of her bonus very well
um i kind of told her to maybe like
write it but she wants me to uh post
like a picture of like
um oh i like this style
or something like that
wow
the pressure is real
uh i think
happy birthday back to you but i stopped
myself before i could
i'm gonna get your picture oh
soon okay okay
yeah
yeah i wanted to play i want to play uh
rest with you but i haven't had a chance
yet maybe next week i can play more
yeah
let's go on a raid together yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah we can go to i don't know
whatever is there in the new island
oh yeah i want to see
okay so ahmed do you have any confidence
in your marketing skills
uh i guess yeah they could be pretty
good i think okay do you want to try to
spin the wheel and see what you get yeah
spin the oil spin away okay let's go
[Applause]
that's so rigged oh my god okay
well you get a free tweet ticket i guess
free tweet ticket yeah you can uh if you
dm me whatever you want me to say
whatever you want me to tweet i will um
tweet it
yeah
oh no am i the third person to get it so
far no uh bonus tweet is you and
soda senpai right before you
yeah so
yeah it's up to you if you can come up
with it now i can like tweet literally
right now but if you want to like keep
it and then
you know just tell me later on discord
um it would be uh okay too so it's up to
you okay okay i'll think about it i want
to sit on this one all right all right
all right
oh no
i'm gonna make you tweet stuff
i think i think there's something wrong
with this wheel because like you know
when i was like trying it out sometimes
it would work well and sometimes it
would like land on things so i'm like
what are the chances that two people get
the same bonus in a row
yeah it's probably it's just it's just
uh rng i got lucky
yeah i guess you got lucky i guess you
got lucky
oh sure you can you can spin
yeah yeah one more one more one more
[Music]
yeah everybody gets five minutes but
actually you get sued ah
okay okay okay okay
this one is um you have to try to sell
to me uh a food
a food that you want to recommend to me
basically oh okay
i got one do you want to do that one
yeah yeah
okay okay there's this uh cake that i
saw and like you cut into it and you
know how there's those videos where it
looks like a real item but it's actually
cake oh yes yes yes yeah but it's the
opposite it looks like cake but it's
actually like turkey inside what wait
i've never seen that before
what is that did they sell it over there
no i made it
[Laughter]
no
no i was so i was i was like half
excited you got me you gotta be half
excited oh okay
but you could be you could be the first
person to make it real you know yeah
yeah if i really want to eat that it
sounds turkey with frosting
i mean it doesn't have to be real
frosting it could be like gravy but like
maybe you know like whipped gravy yeah
something like that
yeah it kind of feels like you know how
those uh dogs have birthday cakes or
something oh yeah yeah but they're not
actually like sweet and stuff right yeah
right i have a feeling that it's you
know it's a little bit like that but
it's for humans i guess
savory cake yeah
yeah i would try it yeah we got we got
one new idea yeah you can use it like
make a new business you know
is it
is it cake
is it cake cake or meat exactly
wow okay thank you so much for coming
thank you yeah i hope you have a
wonderful birthday yeah thank you so
much
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice
i'm in with the re-roll i'm glad she
re-rolled and offered me food but i mean
she can keep the free tweet ticket if
she wants to it's okay the more the
merrier
okay um i guess
who is next hi
hello
[Music]
[Applause]
oh sorry i forgot to send you oh no it's
okay i'm just i ended up using uh
twitter pictures
are good yeah yeah
okay
your purple picture looks really cool i
never really see you let me put my
profile picture behind you that it'll
look like
you wait
let's see
do it do it really do it
okay
hold on hold on
where is it oh no
here oh no where oh where here okay
[Music]
do you have a confidence in your
marketing skills
um
no
well i don't i'm not gonna take it down
for an answer it's time to spin ina it's
time
oh free
actually i think i should come and cure
you why didn't why didn't i think of
that
i should have gotten kyoyu for everyone
so dumb i think it still works it's
still worth watching your stream anyways
oh okay okay contribute okay okay this
one is free so you can choose between
one two six
one two six yeah not the bonus okay you
can't choose
oh i wanna make a joke and say what
about three four five
one two six what about three four five
huh
okay i don't know if anyone has given
you this yet but
um
wait wait can you do it again i want to
turn it on the music off
oh
are you sure about that yeah retake
retake come on
take retake all right
thank you so much ina for being the
first the first ara
yes you're welcome you're welcome wow
a very nice treat for everyone today
did we get an artada from ufo
oh um if you get bonus one you're free
to tell me to say
like um
we also have a person who also claimed
bonus one earlier just one person though
oh sad okay maybe next time
i did have one question for you though
oh yes
you know i
i've been
i've been kind of looking into keyboards
lately and i heard i heard you like the
clicky clock of these oh yeah yeah i
like keyboard let me let me if you are
free sometime we can you can help me
pick out some quickly clackadies oh i
would love to do that i would love to do
that yes
of course of course of course i would
definitely love to do that for you
let me know let me know whenever you're
free okay you know it's your birthday
but i feel like i'm getting a gift oh no
no no it's fun also a gift of me
maybe maybe in the stream where you can
you can pick us i don't know oh we could
we could we could we could yeah we can
talk about that
behind the scenes
okay
happy happy happy happy birthday i hope
you have a wonderful and eventful year
too
thank you
you too
yeah let's go again sometime
okay
so cute
hold on i think i forgot to like uh plug
in my charger
[Laughter]
i think i forgot to plug in my charger
so uh give me a second i'm gonna do it
real quick
technical
technical fixing stuff in the rainy
stream
more likely than you think
oh oh no
oh no guys
wait give me a sec yeah i don't know why
but um
i have no idea why but
there is a problem i think there's i
think i accidentally like messed it up
somewhere but like my charger
doesn't work
so i'm gonna oh no
oh shoot no way
hello hello hello
sorry i have my headphones off
you gotta fix it
hi
happy birthday
happy
[Music]
thanks for coming today i'm going to
fetch your profile picture real quick
of course
how are you doing i'm doing great
i'm doing great how are you doing great
too i like your i like your cheese
earrings your profile pictures
oh thank you thank you very much yeah
like today i have the chance to like
look at people's profile pictures really
closely and i'm like there's so many
details that i'm like
i don't normally yeah you tend to you
tend to miss like if you ask me what
your profile picture was i don't think i
could tell you
so often but it's like the difference
between seeing something and just like
glancing at something i see it every
single day yeah yeah i don't know what
it is
yes yes yes yes yes well bae
do you have confidence in your marketing
skills
yo i am a queen of marketing you know i
can just if you want me to sell
something i will sell it to you i've
even got the announcer microphone ready
i am ready to sell you some reliable
goods that can change your life rating
i'm serious wow i'm so excited okay well
what are you waiting for let us spin the
wheel let's spin
[Applause]
i like the sound
yeah it's very very satisfying oh
okay
this one's a little bit different
uh you you basically can choose between
two like there's like an easy mode and a
hard mode uh the more difficult mode is
uh
like basically act like me
and then
the easy the easy one if you feel like a
coward you can do like three words
like what else
like me in three words
which path you're gonna take
which path you're going to take
which which path you're going to i'm
reading i can't how do i sound like you
uh
what can you say something real quick
um
[Laughter]
is my catchphrase when i tell everybody
to join my membership
it means everybody it's so easy
you know well that's the college i can't
do it i can't i can't i can't
um
recreate your voice i don't know how to
do it it's it's your very unique voice
rainy ah thank you
i think no i can't do it yeah i can't do
it i can't do it nah it's okay it's okay
but you're really good at voice acting
right i sometimes see your uh your
content the uh what's it called
oh no oh no i saw it
i saw it yeah
oh no oh no
yes anyway anyways yeah you learned what
indonesian phrase thank you so much for
coming today bae
yeah hey guys everybody who's watching
guys
you know the rainy's membership is just
it is filled with exclusive content that
you can't find anywhere else and if
we're very very cheap how much is your
membership i don't know it's like i
don't know how much is it in dollars but
it's very it's a good price
get you get content that will absolutely
blow your expectations out of the water
what a deal um if you want to know the
exact details please head over to
rainey's membership content and you know
we promised the best here thank you very
much i'll see you there happy birthday
reading
thank you friends girls
what a deal let's go
so i think um
it's kind of like what a deal basically
right it means it's something different
but it has like a similar sentiment
right
okay okay oh it's time it's time time
time
[Music]
juggling between
okay
[Music]
hello
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
um
yes
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
maybe
[Laughter]
is
bye oh my god
[Laughter]
oh my god
ah
so nice you know some some words i kind
of forgot what they meant but she really
made sure that i uh i understood
everything like you know hey yeah do you
know what uh would you want to mention
this do you know what uh you know you
know what uh
methodical methodical you know so
basically what she was saying oh by the
way there's uh it's break time now so i
have like a lot of time to uh talk to
you guys
it's break time so basically uh money's
call is about uh you know
she spun three times and she didn't get
the bonus
uh love message
and expired food and i'm glad
[Laughter]
sadly no
yeah i can't be helped guys it's okay
she chose ice fire food so too bad bonus
is not in her favor yet
yes but um basically
she says because she lives in such a
methodical way uh
she doesn't have any expired food in her
house but you know what's expired
it's hers it's marine it's herself and
she she was basically trying to you know
sell her spiciness to me you know
yes
the goals do not smile on her ambition
but you know she's always she's always
really great and i'm really really happy
that she still remembered like the
indonesian phrases i told her last time
so
even better
yeah guys we're gonna we're gonna live
in a luxury mansion together and i'm
gonna prepare her a room in the basement
uh and then we can read uh manga etsy
together okay
what a deal
[Laughter]
yeah bacha manga eti read uh read etsy
manga
yes
so basalanga etsy together stream went
oh i don't know if it can do that can we
can we wink wonk em chan
uh yes yes free tweet ticket actually
soda senpai uh soda senpai sent me
her
her her free tweet
and
cinnamon
oh okay okay okay okay
so she sent a tweet but i can't tweet it
now because uh there's a there's a point
there's a there's a section that i have
to fill by myself
yes
[Music]
you know that that was very very
unexpected
has that
that that prankster side of her
looking forward to the tweet yeah the
tweet isn't japanese but it's about
swimsuits and everything
yeah okay
and of course uh so let's look over at
the cause
yeah so
the first one was nenechi nene she was
the first person she also got uh expired
food she sold me
she sold me a stew in her fridge that
has mold on it
and
we have kyla kyla got the
bonus one and she made me say kyla is a
hundred percent not a penguin
and the next person is chuco sensei
choco sensei uh got love message and she
told me that
uh well she sent me a love message and
said that uh you know let's let's play
together more and then when we go to
when i go to the japan let's play let's
play a lot together let's go out let's
and then she's gonna you know yeah
arrange like a nice thing
so i'm very very excited for that you
know
i think it's really good at cooking too
so i think i'm i'm super super excited
to you know be able to uh hang out with
her
gutsy yes and anya
anya
gave such a beautiful
drawing
where where's the drawing where's it
hidden
it's because it's when i was it's when i
was doing the
where is it i think it's this one yes
look at any drawing
rain it's intel
[Music]
very cool
on your drawing masterpiece of course
and next one is soda senpai soda senpai
one soda senpai won the the the free
tweet thing and she wants to
she wants to she wants me to tweet
something about um
my favorite theme so you guys will see
[Laughter]
you guys will see after the stream out
tweeted
yeah what kind of swimsuit do you guys
think is good
um what kind of i wanna i wanna i wanna
ask you guys what kind of swimsuit do
you think is good
spicy swimsuits
yes yes
two-piece
dupe one-piece competitive swimsuit
watermelon swimsuit
band-aid
oh
i like wearing ven aids swimsuit what
the hell is band-aid swimsuit they're
just band-aids aren't they
no peace no peace swimsuit
no peace not one piece not two peas but
no peace swimsuit
so spicy
oh my god okay
okay okay
um
yes yes you will need super glue for
band-aid let's have the waterproof
band-aid then i think we wouldn't need
super glue for that
oh okay okay yeah kowkini oh my gosh
what's kaokini in japanese
what's kaokini in japanese i i need to
um
i need to i need to look that up i i
might i might tweet it like that i might
tweet kaokini because because it's like
it's really cute
body painting swimsuit
we got some nice ideas
nice
migi
migyugi
nice nice nice nice so cool and then we
have
uh after soda senpai we have amelia
which did her reroll first she yeah she
she she
threw away her bonus
for uh to advertise a food she would
recommend to me which is apparently i
was so excited but it turns out it was a
food she made up
it was a food she made i was so sad
but yes
oh
so sad
but it's okay thank you for you know
404 for making me dream you know amelia
can do her own like
shop because nobody has done it before i
don't think you know
[Laughter]
make the turkey cake real of course like
you know the frosting they could be like
gravy that's like you know frozen so the
consistency is like
just like frosting or just like
you know whipped cream yes
it was a good pitch i think it could be
a legit idea
could be a legit idea or i could make it
like an ad you know like in my um do you
know in my streams or in special streams
i usually have like an ad segment i just
like chuck in i just chuck in the old
royalty ad well that can be a new ad i
think you know i think it's nice
mashed potato or sour cream is frosting
mmm i'm actually kind of hungry i don't
know like the imagery is really weird
but i am getting hungry
[Laughter]
turkey flavored cake
[Music]
so cool yeah i want to make more ads
i want to make more ads like that and
then we have inna ina
ina was a champ she got free she could
have chosen anything but she chose the
ara
blessed us not with one but two aradas
oh thank you so much ina
so blessed
[Laughter]
and then she wants to talk about
keyboards with me so that makes me
really happy
and then we have bae
bae what did they do
oh she tried to she tried to act like me
and say mr kali
yeah
muy that's the kali it has the it has
the same thing it has the same vibe it's
like what a deal right
the words mean different the words uh
they mean different things but seriously
it has the same vibes
yes yes yes yes and then uh the last
person for the first segment uh there's
two there's two groups is money senpai
money senpai is uh
she's she rerolled like three times she
really wanted to get that free ticket
bonus
but
yeah
she was yeah she was like kind of close
to bonus two but then again everybody
could be close to it
yeah first she got love message and then
ada and then finally she has expired i
think
i think the expired food is like the
funniest
each one worse than the last
turn they expect to selling herself that
was so amazing
yeah
yeah the iron jesus didn't let her but
yeah it was um it was it was certainly
entertaining yes
[Laughter]
didn't expect didn't expect that to
happen you know actually uh when i was
trying to make this um
when i was trying to make this i was
thinking maybe i should try to make them
sell themselves but i didn't know how to
like make it
uh sound not awkward so i've actually
put love message you know
so i wanted love message to be like
pretty much the same as you know try to
appeal to yourself you know
and i think my battery is oh my goodness
i wonder what she would do if you got
her bonus i don't know i'm glad we
didn't get to find out
i had to sell herself as well i know
true true true true true
that is very true actually let me try to
like um i don't know i think like my
charger
[Music]
because we have time guys it's okay i'm
gonna play electrician and i'm gonna
yeah well nothing happened i'm gonna
play electrician uh before uh while you
well i well i'm playing electrician you
guys can look at this ad
you guys can look at this ad hold dawn
hold on hold on
[Music]
hi what it is
while i'm playing electrician you guys
can
look at this ad
it's it's sold out yeah i i actually i
actually realized
that it might be
[Music]
where is it
i wonder where is this
[Music]
sorry guys i'm not done playing
electrician i'm gonna be done soon
okay
limited set got sold out in minutes for
real
i'm gonna i'm gonna ask amtran if you
know something could be done because
uh because because obviously we would
want as many people as possible to have
a chance to get the merch right
yes yes
okay guys
ads are here
i think i just i think there's still
some stock in the id store
um
there is still stock so if you guys are
you know if you guys want to get it then
what are you waiting for get it now
before it sells out
yes yes yes yeah
yes yes yes
yeah are you guys excited for the goods
yeah i feel like yeah i i hear a lot of
messages from people who are like oh no
i couldn't get it sold out
i'm gonna i'm gonna ask i'm gonna ask
but um the the glass is actually one
liter
so it's a big it's a it's a big big big
mug it might look little but it's not
and if you guys uh see it
if you guys see it
uh
did you guys see the tweet where there's
like the sample goods
the sample goods in the um
where is it
the sample goods like the picture
from cover the desk
and
the desk and the thingy with the goods
is it glass or bowl it's a mug but it's
really big so you i mean you can use it
as soup
soup bowl
i think i think it's okay too
i think it's okay too i can show it to
you my my my room will be messy
makes doors visible
okay there we go
here
here's what it looks like pretty much
yeah your setup could be like this but
maybe like with a more ergonomic chair
and
yeah
i love what mandy you can can can also
use for showering you know people in
indonesia sometimes they use like that
kind of container to shower
instead of a shower head
yes yes the rubber mat must be big too
yeah it's like 60 cm by 90 cm very cool
right
very cool side somebody pointed out like
rainy you're using a
full-size keyboard and i gotta tell you
it's for the it's a it's an artistic
choice
it's an artistic choice
can you zoom in on mug
sure
there
there we go
zoom on mug
it's really big
yeah
i'm gonna put this here maybe
yeah it's really really big so but i
guess it's also very
good for people who for example uh maybe
they don't have a fridge they don't have
a fridge in their room or something you
know something like gamers have fridges
in their room i personally don't it's a
personal choice if not i will never ever
ever get out of my room
but yeah you can bring like a large
large large glass of water and like
little up drink it and then yeah you
don't need as much
yeah you don't have to refill as much
yes yes yes really love the outfit you
have in the mat thank you so much
actually um
actually uh we can talk about the goods
later because um somebody is coming
after this
the next calling session starts uh
in 10 minutes in around 10 minutes and
it will go on for another one hour
so yes i hope you guys are excited for
it
no the size raining oh yes yes yes yes
uh the details of the size is there on
the page
uh i didn't really put it in this
slideshow because like the image
specifications are different
so yeah
illusionite is a banger thank you please
listen to it lots illusion night is my
very very first english
english original song
so
hopefully you guys enjoy it i tried
something different
um
yes yes yes yes
birthday celebration yes one liter
it's one liter no i'm thirsty i want a
drink
lyrics are spicy don't you guys like
spicy
yummy
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum mug is
10 cm high and 3 13.2 on diameter
and now i've got at least one language
for uh
you know one one one song for each
language yes
[Music]
you can cook rice with it you know if
you want to put rice in the rice cooker
you can also use that so see my mug is
very very there's a lot of function in
it you know
yes the music and lyrics is by aida from
dream monster and
the lyrics uh and the trans lyrics were
done but was done by akanesa
yeah they really did a great job
and i'm very very very happy with the
song
yeah
reyna's mug is very versatile
so yeah
look look forward to that when the merch
arrive i arise i look forward to seeing
you guys uh use the mug for you know
your daily activities like measuring
rice or like just drinking or eating or
something i was thinking like making
maybe like because the mug is so big
then you can put like cake in it and
like make it into like
uh like some kind of like bowl cake or
like a
can cake just like remember when uh
they posted the whole live
cake the can cake
i can think of that make it make
something that's homemade like that so
nice
but yeah if you have access to the whole
cake uh you can try and get the wayne
cake i think it tastes uh
it has blueberry taste and i'm not
mistaken
yes yes yes a mug cake you can make a
microwavable mug cake or something
a literal cupcake exactly exactly or a
cereal bowl true and because it has a
handle you can eat the cereal and then
when you're done you can use the handle
to like just drink the milk normally
right you don't have to be like drinking
off a bowl
so versatile we love it right
yes yes yes mug brownies this vanilla
ice cream is amazing yeah
i'm looking forward to seeing you guys
like post your picture of how you're
gonna use the mug because it's not
really like the standard type of mug you
know it's it's shaped like a little bit
round so
multifunctional
you can't make royalty with it you know
um i refrained from saying it before
but i was so close to saying oh yeah
guys if you want to drink hollow eye
drink
you can use that for maximum dose and
effect nice
mug and cutlery what's a deal
and use as flower pot
yes use this flower pot if you want it's
fine up to you
rainy trying to kill us hoy no no no no
one liter of full andre i mean i think
if you if you don't
get the spice or too much spice you will
be able to survive drinking whole eye
drink like that apani
what is this
oh
oh my god
[Music]
hold on
yes there was a
manager message but nothing nothing is
yabby i'm fine guys
just got here what does the cup look
like i will show you again
i will show you again we have a lot of
time until the uh the next the next
collins the next call-in is starting at
t
not 40. 0 5 0 0
14 0 0 jst
this is what the mug looks like
yes yes yes yes the art is by yomo saka
sensei
and this one is by pucci mama
[Music]
mama mama
so cute right
yes you can use it for anything it's up
to you
spicy need to remind all people
i need to remind those people
okay let me recheck the schedule
for those of you who missed it as well
uh
before the collins we had three messages
from subaru
um
[Laughter]
we had three callings from another
collins three messages in video form
from subaru
uh gura as well as fauna
they made very very very cute videos
so yes
hello happy birthday thank you
yeah
they made i should you know i feel like
the production value of the videos are
so high i feel like when they have a
birthday
i should have
put something
you know
yeah
rewatching the videos on another monitor
oh my god you guys are so good
i guess i can i can uh hold on hold on
yes uh
let me okay
let me watch the videos i can't really
make a slideshow as of now
but
i can
i can't make it i can make it so you
guys can see
oh but this one's uh
oh this one if you don't have the voice
it's um
you can
give me this one
[Laughter]
oh my goodness
but the narration well we can have the
narration hold on
[Music]
i'm here
let's let's have it like in low volume
oh sorry sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow
[Music]
let's watch it again
happy birthday
[Music]
does it still have double audio
twix
okay
i made you something that's not a twix
here it is
[Music]
you guys can listen to guru uh while i
prepare for the next call in
hello rain hello rain
happy birthday
happy birthday hello reign
of hollow live indonesia it's
me i'm here to wish you the happiest
birthday
i'm here to wish you a happy birthday
how many times can i say that once one
day
do you want a twix i came on prepare but
i have a twix and it made my stomach
hurt and i don't really want it anymore
but i'm here to offer it to you i've
already eaten a piece of it would you
like the other half
i just i want a bite do you want my bite
okay so
okay i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna turn
off the audio after this
because it's time for a call-in
mom wow
that was delicious
okay okay okay i'm gonna turn it off
okay guys i'm gonna turn it off sorry
bye girl
[Laughter]
i love it
we can we can change videos
or maybe we can keep her here we can
keep her here
it's okay
okay
wait wait please
[Music]
[Laughter]
hold on let me see
okay okay okay okay
i'm gonna be calling
calling calling calling calling calling
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
so good
so good so good
do you want to talk
[Music]
i watched the kilo chance stream and
stream of the contents of your bag
so i was so amazed i found out you have
the same cosmetics as me yes
yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
let me try
[Music]
okay
thank you
[Music]
wow we got the best
for we are in the best timeline guys oh
my gosh
from porchy mama
so spicy
oh my god
[Laughter]
okay okay okay
[Music]
is the next person here oh i'm the one
who's not here
[Laughter]
i've i made them weight
made them wait
yeah
i was like hello
hello hello
hello so sorry i'm late i i just
realized that the time is in gst and not
in wib
oh no no no that is okay that is okay
hello
thank you for wearing the uh
thank you for wearing the the what you
call it the icon frame
oh for sure i wouldn't miss it for the
whole world nah
i love it it's so cute did you design it
yourself oh no no no no i didn't
i love the maraca stamp over there it's
so cute i got you a present by the way
oh really
yeah i sent it to you oh my god oh my
god look i'm gonna i'm gonna save it
i'm gonna save
do you like
the right one you know the little bird
that's what that's what the maracas look
like
it's so cute
it has like those what 50s cartoonish
vibe
yeah yeah i love the 1930 thingies so
cool right
so cute wait let me let me put this
image by the way ollie how much are you
confident in your maracating skills my
acting skills
um
not i'm not as con and well i wouldn't
say that i'm the best
oh would you want to try it's free
try okay why not
[Music]
oh my god
guys this is not rigged
this is not rigged uh what happened you
got you got you you got ara
hold on
i need to share my screen again
yeah so you know it's free but
apparently now you have to give us your
arata but you know you have some uh
free villages uh if you wanna re-roll
it's also okay
but are you gonna be a coward
[Music]
i'm not a coward i'm i'm a brave zombie
let's go
okay are you gonna do it
yes all right
okay
[Music]
thank you so much for coming well this
stream has been a blessing
and thank you for having me i hope you
liked the ponjok yeah i do i replaced it
on the wheel
also thank you thank you thank you for
for the drawing and much more and your
help yesterday
my
cake by the way i posted it on twitter
oh she's so great what a great
jedi thank you ollie
also
[Music]
okay
i'm kind of hungry
maybe i will eat after this
i ate food oh hello
hello
hi hi
saturday happy birthday
hello
i have something for you
oh yeah yeah yeah
one second i made it really quickly i'm
sorry it's messy
oh no problem no problem no problem
that's so cute i'm gonna put it on the
stream
yeah
oh no and no one already exists one one
one one
i always save my files in a certain way
yeah so i never
so that i'm never able to find it ever
again
exactly a key smash but then sometimes
it'll be a super long key smash and i'll
say this already exists yeah i know
it happened to me this is this is so
cute thank you so much
i really like your your signature it's
like a heart so cute
thank you
happy birthday so cute i'm going to put
it
there
oh no that's okay
so cute
how confident are you in your marketing
skills
um i have no confidence i think i'm
going to freeze on the spot i do really
bad uh with presentations but i'll try
my best okay that's what we would like
to hear it's free you know it doesn't
cost anything to spin so would you like
to spin
i would i would like to spin yes please
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
oh it's bonus one it's like uh you can't
tell me to say anything so it's like me
telling you to say arara but you can't
tell me to say anything
um
somebody claimed it once
oh what what did they say oh oh it was
kayla she said kayla is 100 not a
penguin you can't tell me to say
anything oh okay can you say
my name is lenny i'm a really cool nice
person i'm really beautiful
and um
uh yeah i'm just really awesome can you
say that
uh are you sure uh sure i can
well okay
uh
i guess i'll say it
what was it again
my name is rainey
and i'm
could you guide me through it
i don't remember i'll try a really kind
awesome person i'm really kind awesome
person
um i
oh gosh
i didn't i didn't ask for that oh thank
you it's a bonus for spinning the wheel
you get an additional line
i win yay
yeah we gotta treat the bonus customers
really well so sometimes we do give out
bonuses you know i hope you guys hope
you enjoyed that
i did amazing service i'm going to leave
a very good review thank you that's what
um we're gonna be happy about yeah
please leave a good review rate and
review
and i hope you have a very very great
day
happy birthday have a good rest of your
stream
thank
[Music]
i'll be coming back but i won't be but i
meant as in you know such good service
i'll be back oh okay yes please come
again soon
[Music]
so cute
[Laughter]
she's so cute
hold on
my my
i hate it i hate it whenever like
whenever i hide whenever i hide like
girl i just showed up
[Laughter]
okay who's the next color do you have a
next color
uh
okay
hello
hi
happy birthday
thank you
thank you for coming today
i'm going of course i love your new hair
ah thank you thank you
it also has some blue
it's like you oh
nice profile picture
oh thank you it's so cool but not as
cool as you oh really
okay well i mean
really
you can't be more perfect than me but
you can be cooler than me okay okay okay
that's what i thought that's what i
thought just making sure
just making sure all right i hope you
are doing great today you know because
welcome to rename rocketing academy
you're here to demonstrate your skills
are you ready
yeah i was born ready let's go
well uh i don't think you
need an explanation anymore or i can
walk it through you like as we spin the
wheel uh do you want to spin the wheel
uh
sure
yeah let's do it okay
okay it doesn't cost anything you know
so let's spin it
all right
yes
oh this is actually the first time
somebody got furniture so basically uh
this means you have to sell me a
furniture it could be anything
it could be any furniture
also i think i just died but i think
it's all right um you died yeah i died
but i came back to life it's okay you
know just just vtuber things uh oh yeah
i mean but you can't die on your
birthday it's a very special occasion i
know it's okay i'm reborn every few
minutes it's all right but yes sell me
any furniture uh it can be like your
gaming chair your mic your i don't know
whatever's right in front of you
i would like to see you
i'd like to see you try and convince me
to buy your products
okay
well you see
um
the chair that i use is ergonomic so
it's very good for your posture and even
if you sit on it for a prolonged period
you're still gonna be fine your back is
gonna thank you your butt's gonna thank
you and
uh what else
and also i stat on it so that's a big
plus i think
um
yeah it would be
pretty difficult to get that anywhere
i
guess you have a point well you know
what
because yeah you said it that way so i
guess i have no choice but to buy it wow
only one of the crony chairs
very very limited and ergonomic too
is your backpack
my back
yes
yes it's perfectly bad
it's perfectly bagged like it does not
get any worse than this let's go
let's go how's your ball my back is not
as perfectly
bad as you but pretty bad as well i
think if i buy this it will you know i
will be closer to perfection never
perfect but close to perfection
yes yes with your perfect keyboard
thank you thank you thank you
thank you
and
uh my gift
to you is that
you can call me anytime
one thing
for anything i know i know you
you have the opportunity
to be in the collab with me
very soon even now i don't i don't care
hit me up okay
wow what a gift so amazing the most
perfect gift thank you so much cronie
for coming today
of course by the way yep
good good concert
oh thanks
thank you thank you thank you thank you
love love forever love omg love forever
thank you for
of watching
my
my favorite
oh wait
my
man one of my man many favorite birds
there we go
oh okay yeah okay
yeah
all right yeah
have a good day cronie thanks for coming
bye-bye
[Laughter]
wow
almost almost almost oh dodge the bullet
there
okay
uh
okay we're in the we're in the middle i
think
uh
yeah wow cronie actually watched watched
the concert very happy
crow yasumi
hopefully not forever
[Laughter]
very nice
hello
hey na happy birthday reina
hi yes thanks for coming today
yes of course i would
oh so nice
birthday it's my second time calling
into your birthday
really second year birthday wow you're
ready you must be such an important
friend
yes of course why are you talking like
that to me and karaoke
[Laughter]
of course of course yeah i saw your you
know i saw your your tweets about going
on like workation i was like oh my god i
want to do that as well
yeah it was really fun hokkaido
yeah the food was great ah yeah they
came they kept talking about the food so
i was like
mainly food mainly food did you eat like
crabs or something because i feel like i
always
you know i ate a lot of sushi sort of
things like raw fish but actually now
they think about i don't think i had
crab oh okay
and melons yeah i love i love raw fish i
like sashimi and sushi i'll go someday
yes yes come to japan yeah i will treat
you oh i will treat you through
delicious meal yes oh let's go i'm gonna
take notes i'm gonna remind you every
single
week
every single
week it's monday remember when you go to
when i go to japan you gotta
treat me insane
some delicious food by the way iris do
you have a car yeah you have confidence
in your marketing skills um um if it's
something that i'm that i i'm knowledge
about a bull about maybe
okay
well the i mean the wheel will determine
your fate it's a free spin you wanna you
wanna spin yes please okay
let's spin
please give me don't give me furniture
please i don't know much about furniture
anything but furniture anything but okay
well do you want to be a coward and spin
again because a few other members also
spend uh spending uh you know spin sure
sure sure anything but furniture was
basically okay
[Music]
oh expired food
expired food
uh it can be any food yeah any food or
if you have expired food at your home
you can also have yes okay
so you know that how i went to um
hokkaido right yes and hokkaido is also
famous for their cheese because their
farms and their milk so i bought a
cheesecake oh frozen cheesecake at the
airport
that uh i could carry for six hours with
a with ice on it but so i was able to
get that back home safely but i went to
hokkaido like
like two and a half days ago
and the cake was
and the cake has an expiration date of
eat it
before the second day like just you can
only have it like one day after
you come back with it basically and i
still have half left
so basically it is one day expired
what
but
the cheesecake itself
i actually had a stomachache the day
before but it couldn't possibly be the
cheesecake no i'm sure it's not the
cheesecake it's probably some some maybe
spam music or something i ate besides
that but you know um it is very
delicious it is made out of caramel
cheese i don't know if i'm pronouncing
that right in english
and it's it's an omiyage from hokkaido
where you know usually you don't you
can't go there and you can't buy it
unless you're in hokkaido so it'd be a
waste not to eat it right oh my god i
guess so i guess i have no choice but
yeah but try it right yeah
i'll try i'll take it
you know it's half a cheesecake it might
be one day old i could sell it for maybe
like half the price i bought it you know
since it's half a cheesecake right
[Music]
what do you think oh sure i i think yeah
i have i think i have no choice uh yeah
i'll buy it from you
thank you very much for your business
yes yes you can't say no to hokkaido
i really gotta finish eating that though
but yeah yeah do it
tell me
yeah okay yeah i i don't know i've been
having a loose stomach the past two days
i don't know why maybe it's from the
trip i don't know but
i'm good besides that though
good good do you have a strong stomach
uh no i feel like out of like everything
in my body this my stomach is the
weakest oh yeah same i was just like
because your one of your um choices was
expired foods i was like is eating
expired food or thing that you do often
no
i just wanted to punish people a little
like oh well how would they market as
far as food but i guess there's a lot of
creativity to you guys so yeah
yeah i was thinking maybe it was a
common occurrence in the reyna household
no
we're we're not in the iris household
okay
what do you mean i don't need expired
food all the time no
no one day maybe but i i don't go well
maybe ice cream i did eat expired ice
cream once i was in the freezer for like
a long time and i it was like three
months past this expiration date
it tasted okay but it was like not
creamy anymore
i could have lived my whole life without
knowing that but thank you it was like
frozen like ice like it was ice cream
but it just became like the cream kind
of disappeared it became ice
well thank you so much for your uh
wisdom oh wow you shared uh such
precious stories to me today on my
special day i guess that's my gift
oh yeah
sorry sorry it might be long but as your
gift i want you to build a mode mode
sonnet for me
would you want me to build your modes on
it yes for your birthday for my birthday
yeah i'll i'll order the mozart i'll set
it to your house and then i'll have you
build it for me so you get to build a
keyboard for free
[Laughter]
yes thank you i'll still treat you to
that meal of course all right
thank you bye
crazy
[Laughter]
oh my god
okay
let's see hello
hello
[Music]
thank you so much for coming today
thank you
[Music]
very very kawaii drawing
[Laughter]
okay
it
god
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
[Music]
so cute
[Laughter]
next person is oh okay okay okay okay we
can do the next person
we are waiting
waiting for the next person yes
i have to juggle and ping people thank
you rigged wheel yeah i'm so excited oh
hello
hello hi hi
hi
[Music]
oh
okay wait
how's this hello hello hello is this
better oh oh i still here myself
i know
okay i think you're in this
[Music]
yeah
thank you for coming today do you have a
do you have confidence in your marketing
skills oh
i do i do wait before that can i send
you something oh of course of course of
course all right i made a little present
[Music]
okay
okay should be in dms i think
where oh yes
oh my god okay okay okay i saved this
wait i saved this and i'm gonna show it
okay okay
okay i'm gonna name it with like one one
one one one
my obs is so messy
that's okay it's okay
where's the one one one hold on let me
save it again let me save it again
there we go
oh
spicy spicy
bon joke
to make it more realistic human
realistic it's just wearing a bra
yeah it's your bruh oh the outside the
outdoor bra the outside yeah the
ipx on rainy
[Laughter]
so nice i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna
put this here is this okay uh yeah yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's time to uh give me a love message
oh
message
yes yes love msg
here
okay that was close though okay love
message um are you ready
yeah i'm ready okay zetta love message
in three
two
one go
you are the cutest the most beautiful
the most amazing
turkey ever
i bet you would taste good with gravy
i love you
wow
such a
lovely message from zetta oh you're kind
of making me hungry
this is my special day you don't want to
find me on my special day right
fine not on your special day
how should we do it tomorrow i'll mark
it on my calendar
planned meeting when yeah plan meeting
of course we're like all busy women
right so we gotta play all right google
calendar
i'll actually do it
oh man yeah thank you that's all for
coming
thank you
[Music]
so cute
so cute so cute
she says she wouldn't find me on my
birthday but any other day is fine
[Laughter]
okay really really cute picture too
hehehe
hello
hi hello
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Laughter]
so cute
guys look at the umbrella
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
okay nice guys
that was
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh
[Music]
thank you for watching
[Laughter]
yeah okay spin one
okay three two one spin
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
um
thank
[Music]
bye-bye
so cute she recommended me i think like
a home theater that's like um
that's like
oh hello hello hello
howdy
hi
happy birthday
thank you kelly i'm gonna i'm gonna put
your profile picture on my stream
yeah
oh i see
i see is that
is that girl there
yeah she sent me a birthday message and
it was funny so i was like i'll just put
it on the screen
it's good i like that
cute i hope you have the happiest
birthday i'm uh
i am like
i'm talking to you while snuggle deep
into my bed but that's the best way to
talk to your friends i think true true
true true
thank you so much for inviting me i hope
you've been having fun did you just wake
up
yeah so i had a i had a stream in the
morning right and then i was like well
time for a nap because it was early and
then i i passed out and it's like the
afternoon now um and i'm planning to go
back to sleep but um then i'm probably
gonna stream again i get busy again
later in the evening but i wanted to
make sure that i definitely woke up
so that i could wish you the happiest
birthday ever
um and tell you
that i'm gonna get your merch i'm
excited thank you
yeah the mug looks so
looks so cute i can't wait to use it to
drink my tea it's one liter you won't
get thirsty
whoa that's like hold on i should i
should be drinking soup from there yeah
you can eat cereal if you're a cereal
person you can't eat it from there
yeah i'm gonna eat my fruity loops from
there
my my frosted fruity pebbles thank you
so much
is that your favorite cereal
yeah it's my fave i like the really
sugary ones it's probably not for the
better yeah true but i guess like
it's not it's not always about health
it's about taste sometimes
yeah exactly which is why americans have
pop-tarts for breakfast which is just
you guys
yeah it's just it's just straight up a
cookie with like
jam filling or like sugar filling and
people are like yeah this is america's
favorite breakfast pop it into the
toaster before school and enjoy and just
you eat it but it's literally just a
cookie like it's straight up dessert but
that's what kids eat for breakfast
sometimes okay
it's messed up it's messed up america's
messed up just uh just don't worry about
it eat a real breakfast you guys you
gotta eat that
well eggs and bacon
okay well cali
um do you have uh do you have us uh your
confidence in your marketing skills
perhaps it's time to you know promote
good frank breakfast
yes
yes i do okay let's try spinning the
wheel it's free spin do you want to spin
sure here we go
okay spin
let's go give me something nice
what do we got here
oh
oh sorry not not marketing but you can
you can re-spin actually uh if you want
uh this one's uh
[Music]
or
the easy the easy one is uh
it's uh act like me are like three words
to describe me
oh that's so cute i love that i'll spin
it one more time though okay
one more i'm going to use my free spin
get free skin it's okay somebody spawned
like three times
oh my gosh she still didn't get what she
wanted oh man you got the bonus do you
want to use it or do you want to spin
again you got a free tweet ticket
a free tweet tickets yeah
oh to be honest dorene i don't i don't
want to make you say anything that you
wouldn't say on twitter i'm fine with
other people doing that for me but she's
so i'm really bad at that for other
people so i'll spend just one okay just
one more time
exhaust those free spin limits
right people are gonna be like
[Music]
this wheel is kind of broken i think
oh that's okay it clearly has its
favorites it knows that it wants to hear
from me kelly wong
moment
uh
maybe we can cheat a little bit and
because it stopped living at number four
it's the food you would recommend to me
okay pop-tarts pop-tarts definitely not
definitely not um
the food i would recommend to you
um let me see
let me think
you know
you kind of remind me of this food
there's a certain kind of do you know um
hold on a second it's uh
it's called
there are these like
these white sort of candy things and i
think it's called like meringue or
something oh yes
yeah yeah i found them at like the
international store and i ate them and i
was like this is a classy dessert that
you would like to eat with tea uh-huh
um i recommend them to you because
they're like very like they're crunchy
at first but then they're soft and
fluffy and they melt in your mouth
that sounds good
what's it called yeah
i think they're meringues oh just oh
meringue oh yeah yeah yeah okay i
thought i thought it was called like
something else
i think it might be called something
else i think i might be a dumbass oh
i'll message you later once i go to the
store and look at the label and see what
it says on there it's like a it looks
like um
a whipped cream like a small whipped
cream uh thing but it's not whipped
cream it's like hard like a cookie and
then you eat it and it's crunchy yeah
and it melts in your mouth
also this was a bonus i'm i am going to
give three words that remind me of you
you are you are classy
and you are relaxing
and you are elegant it's right
but you're new your new outfit the
rapper outfit is so cool
i like it so much
oh i'm so glad that you like it that
makes me really happy i i um i worked i
worked really hard for that live show so
i could get a brand new yeah
yeah that was so cool
yeah thank you i hope i get to use it
more often because wrapping on stage
with the like the dress and like i
spread my legs like like they get really
wide
like when i'm like on the stage like
sometimes you get low and then the dress
is just it's moving like a balloon
this sounds like a really a bi thing but
i'm glad i have pants now oh yeah shut
up and stop talking immediately but
i wanted to say happy birthday to you
renee i hope that it's a wonderful
birthday and that you get all the things
you wanted and that you spend it well
and it looks like you had a lot of fun
friends calling today so that makes me
happy yeah thank you so much for coming
today too cali
are you gonna sleep again
i'm about to go pass out all right have
a good rest of the time
okay happy birthday raymay take care
okay
thank you
yeah kelly's new outfit is really cool
when i first saw it in the in the live
thing it was like wow that's so cool
yeah it's uh
yeah people calling from their video
watching you i've done that before
definitely
but sadly sometimes like a lot of times
i have to like crawl into the computer
and then go back to bed
but um
okay
um
let me see
[Music]
okay
something
okay i think we have the next person
[Music]
do we have the next person
hello
[Music]
um
okay okay okay
okay guys skillet stick man
stick my dad for my beloved gin one
senpai okay how are you guys
[Music]
me
uh
um
okay
[Music]
my
yes yes yes yes yes
three okay two one
go
our arrow
five
foreign
[Music]
bye
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
yeah i think we have um
i think we have do we have our next do
we have our next caller i don't know uh
let's do the music yes
[Laughter]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
guys
[Music]
you have to advertise any furniture you
want
okay yeah are you ready ready okay three
two one go
ahead
and
[Laughter]
foreign
me
[Laughter]
foreign
is
okay
[Laughter]
yeah guitar guys uh so she sold me a
chair a chair that apparently can
vibrate she wanted to sell me a desk
that can like go up and down and vibrate
like uh
like what you got i didn't want to say
electric chair because it sounds weird
like you know the standing desk but i'm
actually buying myself a standing desk
yeah she sold me the electric chair but
not the kind of electric chair you guys
are thinking about
okay okay i'm waiting for the next
caller um hello
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
by iranian 15
in three
two
one
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you for calling have
[Music]
love you love you mmm
[Laughter]
so cute
cute cute cute cute
so my senpai is so good at marketing
so good so good
do we have our next caller hello
oh my god you sound so dead hi are you
okay hello
[Music]
hi
thank you for coming
today i love you i love you
hello
hi hi
thank you for coming even though it's
probably
sleeping dead hours for you
no problem i wanted to call instead of
doing a video for you because you're
special
well
i'm sorry for making your
making you use your brain in sleepy
times but
um i'm gonna make you spin a wheel i can
read it out to you if you if your eyes
are you can you can close your eyes i
can read it out to you
so the wheel has six things actually the
first one is
or three or mitsu
and second one you have to advertise to
me an expired food
third one you have to sell me a
furniture
fourth one you have to sell me a food
you you you'd want me to try
fifth one is i no message
six you have to say arada
and there's two bonuses
uh bonus one is you can tell me to say
anything on stream and bonus 2 is a free
tweet ticket
oh just kidding
okay
do you wanna
do you wanna spin
[Music]
no i don't want her to sell me furniture
can we spin again
i tell you furniture oh you're gonna
sell me furniture okay what's furniture
we can do several things well you know
there's one thing that you'll need in
your apartment
no there's several things
one thing you need is
a mirror because then you can look into
it and you see how beautiful you are
[Laughter]
okay
and then you need a big big big bed
so that there's space for meat for sleep
over
and then what i also recommend
is
a shower
for no specific reasons
okay wait that sounds that could have
any implications but
um
i don't know
we shower right
a shower is good because you know
there's a say an ancient saying from
that it goes back like 6 000 years ago
um
it's really old
i have a hard time translating it from
ancient language to
actual english but
um
it says
shower together safe water peace oh okay
yeah i guess we can save water what a
good cause yeah i'm all for saving water
all right let me spin again go okay okay
spin spin spin
you're actually the last caller so i
guess you can spin
like when you were the last one
oh and this one's
a food you'd recommend to me
well
you know
recently
you sent me
some snacks from indonesia
and they were yummy
my mom also enjoyed them by the way
no nice nice nice
but maybe i should send you some snacks
from austria yes please i will be happy
to receive next from austria
so i can put in that um iron beats
rainer
[Laughter]
oh no
oh no it would be difficult because it
looks so cute yeah but i will try to
feel like
they're like sweet things more or savory
things
i like an equal amount um so you can
like do half and half i think well
that's perfect so there's an there's an
austrian dish called schnitzel ah yes
and um the thing itself is savory but
you eat it with
lingenberry
jam
which is actually swing but the
combination
is perfect
and there's also potatoes and they're
really yummy too the way we make them
but schnitzel itself it's kind of like
tonkatsu similar but it's
uh it's just
there and it's usually
different kind of meat like it it can't
be it can be um
and they're made with different like
remove all kinds of meat but the classic
one is
um
oh
yeah
yeah yeah or
well there's several ones you can also
have a chicken schnitzel brush
anyway so you should eat that schnitzel
for you i i know how to make schnitzel
oh you should cook for me i can i can
tell you a story so when i was um
traveling uh back then uh in a country i
would rather not say so their airport
had uh different things so i think like
i was like in the mood for like uh
chicken so i had like so and then they
had like chicken still on the menu so i
ordered it but
and then you know and then my other
family members ordered like maybe like
chicken burger or something and then
when i looked at it like why does it
look so flat and then
apparently it's just the airport food it
says chicken schnitzel and in the
picture it looks good but the real thing
is that there it's just a really big
chicken nugget and then
i looked to my family member and then um
she uh they were eating a
hamburger but the meat is the exact same
chicken nugget meat just a different
form so that was like very sad
wait so you know how in chicken nuggets
the chicken is like kind of
like like
mashed and like put together again yeah
it was like that yeah
like the frozen chicken nugget
yeah it was weird it was so disgusting i
was like i wanted to eat legit meal but
no
i mean i love chicken nuggets but that's
you got you get bamboozled yeah i got
bamboo so i was so excited too i was
really hungry but oh well
just thought i would mention it because
you said chicken
yeah forget that crap i'll make you a
proper schnitzel from austria yeah
yes please i would love to taste it
taste quinoa cooking let's go i know
oh my god i never showed you i never
showed i never showed you a picture oh
my god
it's okay it's okay no problem yeah i
think right now
your viewers know
um
my face and they know
that um reyna is my
mind she belongs to me yeah sorry i was
too distracted by your beautiful voice i
forgot to actually unhide the layer
sorry story story
i know
yeah i love you
and then i wanna say
thank you
for making me feel
like wanted and like i have a friend
here because
um you're like
thank you always you always like hear
from me
and we've been on a really special trip
together and it meant so much to me that
you came there with me
and then even after that you didn't
decide to suddenly hate me no you're
still nice to me
and also you're super talented and
you're a great singer and you know that
and you're a great entertainer honestly
you have really good entertainment value
you should become
an idol or a comedian or an entertainer
right now i don't know we're always just
you should become a streamer we're just
talking on the phone right now right you
should become a streamer ever thought
about that
i think you would be really good for
that yeah
and i hope we can meet again
i'll visit you
in indonesia visit me and then
let's go to bali
and then you come you come to australia
so you you promised me to go you that
you come to australia i'm promised
you're waiting oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah
i already put
on you know all the special
rainer bedding
on the bed
and i put like everything there i have a
toothbrush ready for you
i have slippers and a bathrobe of
everything for you
yay
i'm excited
and i'm so happy to have you you know
i'm really glad you you came into
whole life as
who you are because that gave
us a reason to connect in the beginning
i mean we may have connected later on in
other ways anyway but i think that gave
us a good reason and it was a a good
start
and i think it's destiny
yeah and even though i like um teasing
people
because i love you so much and i never
say you're a turkey because you're a
beautiful peafowl i don't want anyone to
say anything bad about you because you
don't deserve that i don't want people
to be mean to you you only deserve the
best you should sweeten and you're the
kindest most beautiful
sweetest
loveliest most charming bird in the
world
and i
i love you i love it just did i say i
love you i love you beautifully and
admiring
how am i supposed to react to that one
thank you so much i love you thank you
so much for calling
oh no you're cutting
out okay i love you
oh don't can you tell me good night
story
a good night's free
and
once upon a time
there was a peafowl and
phoenix and they decided to go
on a vacation
and even though it was cloudy they had a
lot of
wholesome fun and
after the trip
they
got married and
uh moved in a luxury castle
uh
happily ever after
the end
the ending yet the first half seemed
familiar though yeah
you know it's like stories you have to
like mix it with your personal is to
make it more real you know something
like that i heard oh yeah to make your
whoever you're telling the good night
started to make it more believable yes
yes
you're going back to sleep
yeah yes i have to um but i think it
will take me a while to fall asleep so
because now i have to think about rain
all day every day every night all the
time
yeah you can watch you can watch more
animal videos and then you'll think of
me
also i have an ear worm now from
firebird
oh
firefighter it's a really really good
song
yeah you rocked it right now thank you
and thank you for it thank you for
helping me out with firebird
of course you were so cool singing that
song you had so much passion thank you
um album
album
maybe hopefully
i'll be waiting for that and then i'll
buy
hundred copies a hundred copies
if it's a visual physical a physical
release yeah it'll have it'll have one
of those like free tickets for like a
handshake or like an event but then if
it's you i'll give it to you as much as
you want
you know about the handshake event
tickets yeah
yeah that's why they buy like a million
cds from the same cd
yeah and concert tickets too
yeah yeah raffle for concerts
howdy
how do you know
oh um because i used to buy them too
like my favorite bands like my favorite
like bang dream bands and stuff in japan
when i went to idol concerts like that i
always i always wore like the full on
merchandise with a t-shirt and then a
scarf oh and like everything
yeah i would wear the
yeah the wristband that they would
sometimes sell like the huppy or
something
and then the t-shirt yeah it's concert
gear concert gear
yeah oh i want to see you in concert
here i wonder if we can go to a concert
together i wonder which one we would go
to because like what are is there any
any like music artists that we both
like really much from japan hmm i'm not
really sure we're gonna talk about it
but yeah usually like if we buy a ticket
like we can choose like oh for two
people right usually yeah yeah so maybe
if like one of us gets a hit then then
we can watch together
okay
i can introduce you to
to my
you
my favorite idol company but they don't
have the
idol groups anymore that i that i loved
so much back in the day
sound
but you know what i never went to i
never went to like an anisson concert
before oh
okay
it does seem like so much fun because
they bring out all the classics like
the best anime songs ever and like
everyone is like so into it so
passionate
i wanna go i also miss concerts so much
i haven't i've never been so long
i want to go like
that
but like sometimes because like we're
girls like it's so hard to like chant
in like the same pitch as them and be
loud and stuff like that do you feel
that
after chanting the same pitch yeah
it's nice to have a good harmony yeah i
love
my voices
yes
don't worry about it
[Music]
although you could bring you could bring
a megaphone and the voice changer
true
is there like a you know like a you know
like a detective condom kind of thing
where it's like
it's in the ribbon and then you can like
speak through it and then it'll change
your voice
oh
oh oh yeah probably that's that that
definitely exists
well you don't need to change your voice
i think
we need the beautiful reiner voice in
the audience or on stage
yeah
okay i i started tension thing i should
sleep okay
yeah go to sleep thank you
for calling
we're cutting out
love you
sleep well
you too
me too
okay
wow
wait oops i died i think yeah
wow i hope she sleeps well i think it's
like pretty early over there and
yeah um
yeah it's nice that she
actually called it last
so cute sleepy voice kiwawa
[Laughter]
it's 8 a.m
8 30 oh my gosh wow
show show so early
so early around six i don't know i can't
count guys so maybe around i would
assume it's like around the time where
she should be sleeping but she's still
called in
she's still called in thank you so much
kiwawa that is um the last call-in uh
for the day basically we talked so long
but
yeah
yeah she's she's such a loving and
wholesome
person
yeah please support her too
[Laughter]
so nice yeah she's fun she spun twice
and then she still did two of them
anyways
very wholesome very wholesome 8 30 is
the time where most people are like well
i'm not most people i guess
is it midday for you yeah
it's like midday for me i woke up a
little bit early for like the call-in
because i normally start my day like a
little bit later
but i wanted to make sure that you know
it's a good time normally i do i do call
ins at night but
i just want to try a different time slot
today
[Music]
yeah hold on let me let me change the
video
let me change the video
the gura video is so funny
gonna take a nap after the stream uh
nope
but uh okay we can summarize group two
calls
um for group two we had first person we
had potsi mama calling in
uh she was the one who drew the she's my
mama of course but she's also the one
who drew me uh who drew the death mat
for me that's illustrations from her
and she told me she told everybody a
story about uh when she was drawing this
you know when she was drawing she used
she just used you know for example she
put in stuff that she would normally
wear like one of them was a brand of
lipstick she usually wears and then uh
last time she saw kiara stream remember
that what's in your bag stream and then
she saw that i have the exact same
lipstick that she's wearing so
apparently uh
we wear the same thing we use the same
thing and she wears the exact same brand
for
everything and i also i also use that
brand a lot
so it's a really really amazing surprise
uh
it's it's for it's for uh makeup by the
way so yeah
it's uh it's destiny i know right it's
such a nice coincidence like we never
really talk about things like that
makeup or something and then i guess now
i know
like mother like daughter moment and
then for the wheel we actually got mama
to say ara so cute so if you guys have
missed it be sure to check the vod
because it's amazing
right happy birthday thank you yeah you
have more in common than you know yeah
it was a really pleasant surprise
and next up we have ali ali's present is
this don joke the punch
it's so cute and
she's always so sweet she sent me a cake
what did ollie do i forgot
she's did she sell me anything
or did she get
i don't know what she's totally not
rigged yo it's not rigged it's out of my
control
she also added yes oh yeah the very
mature ara ara yeah actually there's a
lot of ara araaaras in this so you guys
please if you missed it you guys can
re-watch and
ollie did the super mommy like
so cool she gave me cake and she also
helped out yesterday it was so so so mad
i love her so much
[Laughter]
yeah to the right wheel carried hard
nice and we have mummy
mummy drew me something very beautiful
look at that so cute
[Laughter]
mummy what did mummy do i feel like
after having like such a long talk i'm
starting to forget
oh
uh got the bonus right moment a bonus uh
she made me say
anything
basically rome made you spit facts yeah
very very kind and beautiful just like
moomae right
yeah she had me compliment myself and
then i added a special bonus for her see
you know we gotta be nice to our bonus
customers right i mean all customers but
bonus customers also
and then next we have crony
cronie well
cronie sold me furniture
she sold me a crony chair which is very
very ergonomic um and which is good and
it's a one-off because you know there's
a lot of ergonomic chairs out there but
it's the one this is the one that cronie
sat on so it's a one-off man what a deal
right so there was no choice for me but
to take it
[Laughter]
crony ergo chair which can bring my back
close to perfection
oh
ergonomic chair for the perfectly bad
back she told me i was one of her
favorite birds
i think she almost dodged the bullet
there but you know we could let's just
not talk about that
very easy deal what about marine oh
marin was from the previous group marine
uh she still remembers the indonesian
and
which is super happy maybe maybe super
happy she spun a lot of times because
she really really wanted the free tweet
ticket
and
she really wanted the free tweet tikka
but she
ended up getting
expired food and then she ends up
selling herself
so actually the only person who got the
free tweet ticket was
ami i don't know if ami wants to claim
it
and sora senpai really
yeah
and who else i forgot
marine sold out some expired money
[Laughter]
yeah
yeah kelly did a re-roll
yeah you got a real yeah soda senpai hmm
i i need to tweet that i need to tweet
that
sayabad
and then we have iris iris uh there's so
many expired food
there's so many expired food
i don't know why this wheel likes
expired food so much she tried to sell
me a two day expired hokkaido or like
one day expired hokkaido cheesecake or
something
oh yeah might also tell me to let's read
batamagaichi together read itsy manga
together i am going to prepare a room
for her in the basement
like a dungeon
yes yes yes for half the price yeah wow
so generous right
yeah and then the keyboard for the
present she wants me to build her both
sonnet i'm so mad and send it to her
is it's gonna be like super costly like
does so much shipping
yeah but i'm glad she's getting her a
new keyboard i also got a new keyboard i
forgot to tell her but there's always
another opportunity
yes
we next up we have roboco senpai
robaco senpai um was
selling me what what did she say
also
she did
i think she's like i don't easy
it's like
easy oh
so yeah like a champ wow
everybody's like
you know like the that meme with like
the the small dog and the chat dogs like
i don't know when you do it or something
i was already told she was going to ask
him wow holy crap she's serious
i mean sure
sure i mean if she's serious about it
i was just concerned oh ah
but there are ways there are ways there
are definitely ways
yes there are definitely ways even if
she's serious about it um i would be
glad
to uh yeah
she won i'll be glad to do if she's
serious if she's joking it's fine too
the scene roboco stands for chad
robochad
yeah i know right and then zetta
zeta sent me a love message even though
i'm not really sure if that felt like a
love message or not
we need to mark our google calendar to
uh you know the next time we need to
fight
yes
we have poble
we have kobo next time
um
not next time this time we have kobo
kobo
what did she do
the gravy turkey yummy
does it tell a message she's done the
same way a cat would do it exactly
she was semi serious okay if she said my
serious um you know i might do it
just you know she just needs to message
me
and like hey
kobo sand gate open start oh yes she
wants to she needed to act like me so
she sang gay open start
so say so and she also gave me an
umbrella
so cute right and oh zetta also gave me
this
this realistic
this realistic marac
with the hand and the and the booba
so cute
rtx reigning
yeah
very cute qq and toast senpai tried to
sell me home theater
so it's really really really really nice
yeah
and then she mentioned something about
yogi woo what's it
oh
bean bag
it's bean bag or something like that
i think oh yes so like the home theater
and then maybe we have the bean bag
okay okay okay okay okay okay
oh i don't have a bean bag actually i
don't own any but maybe in my studio i
might
just
get one like put one in the corner or
something my studio is not really
spacious but
yes
but yes
that's why i have to be careful about
like filling in like my furnitures and
everything
okay and then next up is
uh kelly kelly kelly kelly also spun
three times i think made use for
made use of her spinning privileges
five times and she cheated
what did she choose
i think um i think she said um
the she chose number one i think
oh food oh yeah food and then she also
said number one is a bonus
yeah
pop tarts and meringue i thought no i
thought like uh it was like a different
dish like made out of meringue but
apparently i guess it's meringue yeah
technically i cheated for her yeah i
guess so
pop tart let's go
and then
he also gave me three me in three words
food recommendation yes yes yes yes and
what she initially rolled on yeah
her i really like her rapper outfit so
yeah i forgot if i have ever like said
that to her
because i mentioned it like quite a lot
but yeah i thought i should like say it
to her while she's there
yes yes yes yes she's glad that she has
pants oh my god i do feel it like you
saw um i don't know if you guys have
seen uh yesterday
my concert
but it's like you know i'm glad that
like i'm glad that my uh
my dj outfit my uh the id outfit is
wearing pants because they're just like
a lot of songs that look
weird for me like for me personally if i
move a certain way but i'm wearing like
such an elegant skirt or something
yes yes yes yes
yay pants
but yeah
it just makes me feel more free i guess
to move like a certain way yeah
it's good that i have options that is
true that is true which is also why um
you know
i revealed something else that happened
uh
happened there
uh like i said having choices is good so
that's why
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah i really like to like do like those
kind of movements so i'm so i'm so glad
for pants
van pants but actually not
and then we have kiwawa how long did
that call last
[Laughter]
oh not yet uh before before that we had
gen one
gen one first we have risu
risu got free because but because she's
a chad she chose the arara
oh my goodness
and then muna tried to sell me a chair
she wanted to sell me a vibrating desk
the stand electric electric standing
desk but because uh that's actually that
the kind of desk that i'm ordering for
my studio so she said okay then you can
get the chair the you know the elect not
like not electric chair
the you know the chair that's also i
don't know it vibrates maybe like the
massage chair or something
and then the last one was
our vibrating that's the thing i have no
idea what she is referring to but i
think it's like um
i think she meant like the standing desk
that's like
that has electricity that you can like
push buttons and like
you know
and she gave me a date ticket yes yes
yes date voucher
um
yes yes yes yes
we have
eofy
eofy's fun
and what did eofy get
yeah my tantrum my aunt
she did
it
the husky arara eufy edition
so many ara guys so in total how many
how many araara did we get
uh
um
yeah there was only one arara and it was
like a free choice too in group one but
in group 2 we got so many so ina ali
ali
roboco senpai
um
mama
i like five from risu i know so six
people got out of well i would say we're
winning guys
yeah i'm so glad i did this wheel you
know gives me like
a nice you know thing to talk about you
know because usually it's uh you know
collins like chatting is fine but
calling in is fine but you know having a
game to like spice things up is always a
really nice too
which
do you think is the most spicy everyone
is spicy i will burn them into my brain
ingrain them like permanently
figuratively um you know engrave them in
my brain
[Laughter]
yes and then the last one was kiwawa no
arada from kimawa but we did talk about
a lots of stuff very cute it feels like
she's like really really sleepy
and she's such a chad because it's not
like she got ara she got free
and then she
had my goodness
so
see the cute was so cute and
she wanted uh to sell me furniture
sold me a mirror
a bed and a shower
and then we talked about a bunch of
stuff and it was a pretty long call i'm
kind of glad she's a last caller um she
didn't really she did uh want me to like
hey put me last because you know of
course uh the calling time is like very
early probably a bad time for her
but yeah we talked about a lot of stuff
we talked about
idols we talked about tickets we talked
about
trips
we talked about
a lot of things i think yay
i wonder if they sell they sell the
furniture shower in ikea ikea i don't
know
yeah it's so early guys but i'm so happy
about uh this year's calling i think um
it was really really
interesting
interesting especially with the
introduction of
the games yeah i'm so so so so happy
and thank you to my friends um
who you know who called in
but yes yes yes uh before we end the
stream
before we end the stream uh i want you i
want i want to advertise a little bit
about rainey's birthday goods
wait
okay
we have
two special merch items spicy rainy man
and giveaways plus drinking mug if you
want the details you can check out the
post
um i think it's in the description as
well
if you want um i think the last time i
checked i'm sorry it's a little um
it was sold out but i think in tokopedia
currently there's still more i don't
know i'm gonna like ask if you know yo
it's sold out can we like do something
about it i might i'm i'm gonna try
asking
i'm gonna try asking
um but in tokyo video you can still get
it and um
this is japanese version
and this
my original song has come out it's
called illusion night
vocal by pavolio rainey music and lyrics
by ira of dream monster and english
translators by akhane sora
yeah it's already available since
september 10th 2022
and it's available to listen to on
itunes apple music spotify etc various
platforms mood as a kali right
yeah i hope you guys listen to it lost
it was premiered uh yesterday the first
time
uh and then i hope you guys like the
studio version
yes yes yes yes yes yes
very nice and yeah the mv actually isn't
out yet the envy will be out at a later
date so uh while you guys waiting for
the mv please listen to it lots so that
when the mv premieres you guys will
already remember all the lyrics and you
guys will be able to sing along okay
[Music]
spicy spicy spicy og song
hallow night yes
[Laughter]
yes the mp is not there but please wait
for it please wait for it it's coming um
it's probably gonna take like a little
bit
uh like a little while but
yeah please
please be patient
and
listen to it lots while you guys wait
lyric breakdown stream maybe
[Music]
i guess we could do it maybe in a ran in
a free talk like maybe in a segment
yes yes yes hallow night what a fright
yes yes yes
um we're kind of like working on the mv
right now it's probably gonna like take
a while until release like but we're
aiming definitely like within this year
so um
yeah please do look forward to it not
that long just a little bit a little bit
of a while but not that long
and it's tomorrow your rest day
uh tomorrow i will be having an event uh
called comic kalimantan
kamikalimantan
it's a local event in id so for those of
you id bros who can
who can attend i guess i'll see you guys
there
um
[Music]
um i really didn't want to get too
ambitious uh with stream schedule
because a lot of things were happening
like birthday stuff
but if it turns out that i have extra
energy to stream i will try to stream i
have several games in mind because you
know there are new games releasing
a game that has started its new season
and stuff like that
um
and then
[Music]
but i will be having another
i will be i might show up somewhere
i might show up somewhere though
even though even though i might not be
doing like a solo stream or something i
might be showing up somewhere but we'll
see
we will see hey
okay um i guess um i hope you enjoyed uh
today's call in stream
and don't forget stream fever night also
stream other rainy stuff
stream stream stream stream the already
on your schedule oh no no spoiler
spoilers already okay then i guess
that's okay
okay okay okay okay okay
did you see the rain rain adapted mem
zone i skimmed it i didn't want to like
read it all because like i want to save
it for like my public reaction but i
stopped that there was like an ad that
made me laugh out loud and i was like
okay listen i'm gonna i'm not gonna
continue
like i don't wanna waste like my first
reactions if i read it alone
[Laughter]
spoiled
okay guys um birthday's been fun thanks
for you know there was countdown there
was the concert and now we have the
collins thank you so much for joining us
birthday is
i mean not really over we still want to
like uh open some stuff read the map
zine and stuff like that but that's for
next week as for this week uh this is
all for the
birthday festivities thank you so much
um i had a great birthday i hope you
guys had fun too watching me
and yeah let's let's let's let's keep
doing our best now that i'm
i'm i had my birthday
let's let's do even better until the
next birthday okay
yeah
uh yeah have a great day
thank you very much for your attention
everybody
bye-bye
[Music]
you