TS of Symphonia had a collab with Mar
Kip during my last trip in Japan it's
one of the biggest crap chains in Japan
I think and H life had a collab with
them before too remember and I really
love crap so much especially in Japan
because they add so much stuff telum
Symphonia is actually kind of the game
that got me into Japanese culture and
gaming oh look they gave us the crab
wrapping papers for free we got the
Lloyd one and the zealous one sorry
Colette uh this one has strawberries and
the chocolate brownie and lots of
whipped cream and some Marshmallow with
chocolate filling and a Lloyd print and
then I got the delas one even though I
hated him always but can't say no to an
ice cream topping besides that it's
mostly the same I just didn't have a
brownie we sat down on a bench close by
this was in akih Haba by the way and we
just ate it happily I never saw a print
on a marshmallow before that's kind of
cute so yeah anyway in case you haven't
noticed I really love