[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n PA
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
K welcome to my
farm every
everybody Welcome well
to my
farm
[Music]
hey I'm wearing
overalls it's so cute it actually moves
pretty well with my body so today I'm
going to show you a bit more than usual
but first maybe you want to see the
whole
thing
blue these are so cute oh my if I don't
move then it's really like on point they
look like my normal
pants but I can you know see you see the
normal pants in the back a they look
like them so cute it's like an extended
version It's a DLC for my
pants
cute come on
Wow
Wow thank you thank you and then I
thought my straw hat is absolutely
perfect for this
right oh chunky wonky
is in the
distance very
loudly what do you think she
wants why is Mommy streaming
again ah So today we're going to play a
game that is a first for me a first on
this
channel start you
Valley is your little chicken on the
logo so that is a good old
man and it's apparently kind of a chill
game I mean I've seen like kind of what
it's about and I've seen my mom play
it uh and Okay so
the bad story is of why I'm playing this
cuz you guys were surprisingly surprised
but I don't even know why you're so
surprised because why is this so
surprising why just because I didn't
like tell you cuz like normally I tell
you oh in the in the next few months I
want to play this game and that game and
that and I didn't mention this one right
yeah
but how is this not like I mean chill
long game kind of minecrafty maybe I
don't know why not it's not not it's
it's not unlike me it's like you guys
were acting as if I suddenly bring out
the Outlast on my
own
so I don't
know but it's probably because I didn't
uh mention my my pixel game I've played
several pixel games until now okay Dave
the div was also a pixel game okay it's
not like I have a problem generally with
pixel games
okay it also really depends on their
overall Vibe yeah in terms of farming
games I've played farming games
sakuna okay so my mom she has 600 hours
in this game so she was very excited and
very motivated to backseat me
today
um yeah it's like every time every like
she always has a phase where she's
addicted to one
game once it was Minecraft and the start
the valley and then something else uh
where did I save the
picture what I told her to send me a
screenshot but she has apparently the
600 hours are like split between
several uh
saves I think this is her strongest one
I can't really judge anything by this if
it's long if it's if it's wow I I don't
know I watched her was it the same game
do you go like into dungeons or
something in this game or is that a
different game cuz I watched your
play like running into a dungeon and
resetting it every time I think I don't
know what is this
game yeah yeah yeah yeah it's it's a
most recent one so yeah she played way
too much of this game already oh there
is a dungeon okay oh yeah has like
several levels right hundreds of levels
and yeah I saw her like teleporting for
that mhm she has the best sword it looks
like a never rde
sword and then some gold
Minecraft thingies hly it just looks
like also the the the the
the the the freaking fish uh uhi uh
unle also look this this looks like
Minecraft some of these
things so much Ginger where's a ginger
you mean me my
hair I'm Ginger Spice now that's a very
end game really I think that the dungeon
is kind of end game right I don't know
but yeah so that's my mom she's uh in
the in the starting
tracks uh to backseat me today
help
me she's welcome to do so but okay so I
thought I have to play this game at some
point because I told you I bought this
game for my mom like when she was taking
care of my cats one time uh and she was
going to spend like a bunch of time at
my place she asked me if I can install
stardew Valley for her to pass the time
and she didn't
say any like you know any detail about
it so I just thought okay I guess I'll
install it on my Steam account so I
bought it on my Steam account installed
it and then when she arrived I was like
here there you go she's like Ah that's
not what I
meant that's not what I meant I'm like
now I have the game I wasn't planning on
playing but okay I guess now I have to
play
it I guess now I have to play it
eventually and I mean the good thing is
it's not really uh as I said it's not
like it's Outlast or something so it's
not so so unlike me not so
unbelievable knows how to make you play
a game no no no no no no no that n
necessarily um um so yeah guess I'm
going to um give it a try let's uh open
it
up open it up probably the sound going
to have to be
rerouted oh how have you guys been two
days without me suffering suffering
sufficiently I would hope so Hey where's
the why is the game not hello oh it took
a
while
oh it's not going to the side window
mode
please
uh oh music
wait oh but wait I want to put it
there I know it's loud
[Music]
I love how the icon is also
chicken were you
crying wait wait wa you missed me okay
okay I need to oh cute wait I need to I
need to how do I is there no settings in
the beginning
[Music]
I want it to go on my middle
screen [\h__\h]
wheel
where
uh do I just have to start a game and
then I get the
settings no Cog wheel yet bottom right
[Music]
nice cute I like the font it's so
cute well I guess we start on my right
screen and I can't see the chat God damn
it why must it be like
that oh wait I moved it okay I got I was
able to move it now I moved it okay okay
okay okay first it didn't work now it
worked
and that's uh not me that's
me I'm a cats yes oh wait there's only
cats oh no only cats I'm going to start
in only
cats a cute why is there several
[Music]
cats H then you li what seems to a bit
off with the scaling I didn't do
anything um I I don't know orange cat
maybe because I'm
orange seems
appropriate oh oh
oh what's this cres shaped hairstyle
very
edgy M oh the buns are
cute oh
a it's audio is probably still too loud
but I'm going to change it once I'm in
game
again um oh cute they're all cute oh my
God there's so 41 there's so many
hairstyles wao oh I think this is the
boy
hairstyles oh oh wait we're back to girl
hairstyles oh my
God wa there's so
many I mean when you don't have to draw
that many pixels
then I guess all of this is
possible ah why you give me so much
[Music]
choice I can't
decide move the character what I I I
know I can do that oops
no
uh wait this looks a little bit like my
hair but very very 60s 7s I don't know
very
poofy
uh
what I don't
[Music]
know this is
okay this okay let's go with this one oh
different shirts oh this is the C shirt
M okay oh overalls is there overalls
with the orange shirt
no well that's kind of lame then let's
just take the orange
[Music]
shirt oh
oh so there's only jeans
okay accessory is a beard your beards
are accessories
guys understand was there no like oh
glasses there you go it still looks like
I have sideburns now to me
what the [\h__\h] cute that's kind of cute
like nerd glasses oh necklace oh oh sick
wow they're detachable no it isn't
you're so accessorized oh my God I love
it you're rocking those accessories
where did you buy
them my whole face becomes a smiley face
what the [\h__\h] what is
this oh a happy mouth
actually that's cute you normally just
not have a mouth at
all I'd like to have a
mouth maybe I'll maybe I'll keep the
[Music]
mouth oh my God girl where did you get
that beard wow just wow ooh the eyes
Okay per
[Music]
purplish uh yeah purple pinkish
something in between
ooh uh orange had to check for a
moment uh
[Music]
orange probably around
here like this oh that looks like
me W wa and H oh man I already came up
with something but it doesn't work like
that like on on my my tweet it was the
kfp farm K's Farm
process because we'll have a lot of farm
process
probably kfp Farm then well maybe I
should
capitalize capitalize favorite
thing cats why are you asking me that
anyway okay my mom said I should take
the Meadowlands
Farm my mom's said I should take the
metaland farm because there's two
chickens there and they're really
important cuz otherwise they would be
very
expensive good pig good
P yeah you start with two chickens I
guess the others have no chickens and
you have to buy them yourself and
they're really
expensive yeah she gave me some some
starting tips
so
[Music]
okay it is already back seeding oh is
that Santa
Claus why does Santa Claus have a like
fancy sword and for my very special
granddaughter I want you to have this
Shield
envelope oh ye
[Music]
is the early game meta oh no no don't
open it yet now listen close stay a
while and
listen there will come a day when you
feel crushed by the burden of Modern
Life sometimes it's too fast sometimes
it's too slow and your bright spirit
will fade before a growing
[Music]
emptiness is she okay he feels crushed
when that happens my dear you'll be
ready for this
gift when when is that
how isn't this an endless game now let
Grandpa rest XX years later so
20 EG
computers wait this looks like kind of
looks like a kfp
farm terminated oh [\h__\h] the computers
look different from this
angle oh that's me oh I'm like [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h] I is this like
Amazon is this an Amazon reference the
logo reminds me of
it I'm like I want to go farm [\h__\h]
this oh ah I got to read it immediately
because now I'm feeling crushed by The
Emptiness Dam
W if you reading this you must be in
dire Le of a change the same thing
happened to me long ago I lost sight of
What mattered most in life real
connections with other people in nature
so I dropped everything and moved to the
place I truly
belong I feel like my mom wrote this and
I'm going to read
this in one
day uh I've enclosed the DAT to that
place my pride enjoy the
kadas what was it Farm not food process
could fit to K's F process
F it's don't read it all out because
then it will stop making sense just say
kfp okay it's located in stard De Valley
for stars Like You on the southern coast
it's the perfect place to start your new
life this was my most precious
gift
[Music]
precious gift of all and now it's yours
I know you'll honor I didn't know my
grandpa was gum
I know you will honor the family name my
dear good luck love
Grandpa far K's Farm of
power P if Louis is still alive say hi
to the old guy for me will
you a that was nice quite sweet
oh I love love the
scenery oh I'm in the
bus the wheels on the bus go around and
round round and round round and round
the wheels on the bus go round and round
early in the
morning I'm bsing oh little bird you are
not the chicken
oh oh it's so colorful and so bright oh
my God that's me that's like literally
me
Robin you're
me hello you must be Wawa I'm robbing
the local carp oh she makes the carpet
okay okay okay good to know good to know
[Music]
let's go mayor mayor
Lew sent me here to fetch you that's
self fetch she believes in the fetch I
love that that's self
[Music]
fetch H fet you and show you the way to
your new home he's there right now
tidying things up for your
rival enough
the Farm's right over here if you'll
follow me man it's so colorful
wow I think I like playing this in in
full screen actually normally play
everything in oh my God it's Animal
Crossing in like probably a way better
Animal Crossing ah
okay this is K be fine sheesh nobody
cleaned up here in a million years
man what's the matter sure it's a bit
overgrown but there's some good soil
underneath that
mess yeah uh yeah uh let's hope
so lots of work to do here my mom must
have felt like this is real life to
her girl you live like this no no I just
I'm I'm starting to live like this I
just came here I'm going to undo all of
this don't worry
with a little dedication you'll have it
clean up in no time okay my mom said to
not get rid of the Blue Grass because
the animals like
it and then I'll become popular with
them
okay
uh and only only oh YouTube chat memory
is
[Music]
overload nice advice it's hard to come
by m and she said only to clean up uh or
clear up a little part a relatively
little part of the farm because in the
beginning I have no Sprinklers and big
fields will uh take up all my time to do
it without sprinklers
oh oh
chat we should just give up on
chat I'm just going to stream about you
guys
uh and also remind me of this because I
I feel like I'm going to forget it uh
buy uh from every vegetable in the shop
a few seats and then don't sell it all I
don't know what this means really uh
don't sell all of the products
or you you will need uh a lot of this
later she
says yeah I fix you I fix you not
Neil I'm the only one who can fix you
specifically wait can I have a little
cookie I I need some chocolate just it's
it's small bites of the big cookies I've
been eating recently there's a small
bite version too that I told you about
before it's the the Mini version of Li
nits chocolate
cookies
nice m so
good but they have like a like a way
thinner layer of uh coat of
chocolate bite size
yeah okay and here we are your new
home I like it it's cozy and smaller
smaller t
house did you
feel wait her why is her hair more
orange than me why did I not manage to
get that kind of bright orange is she
wearing a
wig where did you buy that wig I want it
it looks so unrealistic I want
it I didn't know you could could get
that orange I I
tried skill issue God damn
it well look I'm a blueish May of Bing
town you know everyone's been asking
about you it's not every day that
someone new moves in it's quite a big
deal you like my voice guys it's my new
voice I'm going to stream like this from
now on so you moving into your
grandfather's old colleage it's a good
house just a million spiders inside
because he's been dead for years
now no problem yeah no
problem I I'm not scared of spiders no
no especially not if they're in the
millions no rasic that's one way to put
it crusty might be a little more apt
though
rude I am jealous of her
hair don't listen to her waa she's just
trying to make you dissatisfied so that
you buy one of her house oh my God
Animal
Crossing
exposed
exposed anyway you must be tired from
the long journey you should get some
rest tomorrow well you ought to explore
the town a bit and introduce yourself
the town's people or the town's people
would appreciate that
[Music]
people oh I almost forgot if you have
anything to sell you just a place it in
this box here I'll come by during the
night to collect it well good
luck oh I go bye thank you now I'm all
alone and I don't know how the hell to
take care of a
house
[Music]
k
w
woohoo that's a good one that's a good
one mum has to learn from that one holy
[\h__\h] oh it's a real
deal wakey wakey snaky snaky oh my God
you go in
like oh my
God what what game does that remind me
of the way you go in there poke like old
Pokmons or m n maybe something else
this makes me so happy why the why why
why does this why ises this Mak me so
happy I love how you just like stand in
there ah
Pokemon M after all also this looks like
it's missing a face it looks like
Coronet dog version the
chair you know what I mean Al how do I
there's still no settings is there what
the
hell okay then I'm going to turn it down
a little bit on my
[Music]
own I'm noticing a lot of
things okay just a little bit oh my God
these cookies it
does escape this is escape button
[Music]
oh nothing looks like ah
here yeah I already turned it down
anyway
though okay
present open with a hammer I don't think
that's how I should open it but I don't
see any other way maybe maybe with the
Scythe oh
sheesh oh oh I can move it oh I can't
open it I can move it though okay okay
anything here that I can use uh move oh
oh now the fire is off how do I turn it
on again God damn it I ruined
it oh this I cannot take with me the
rake oh man right click oh right click
oh wait red click for the fire oh fire
fire like the
fire but I can't righted click
this so this is just what what what I
can't oh oh
no nothing
nothing ah I have to stand right next to
it to
open I got a lot of hay
hey hey to you too hey girl
okay I don't know what to do with that
uh okay so she said a small field
who can anywhere be a field have to
don't I have to pick this up or do I
chop it oh I chop it and I received the
wood okay ooh
amazing okay okay pick it up and then
the I mean the wood I can get rid of all
of it I would assume
but uh
maybe the grass I should not take uh
brown dirt area okay okay yeah so we'll
clear up some of that this is like a
maze now getting through all of this
Butterfly fly like a
butterfly it's nice that we have all the
tools right
away inherited
maybe there's some upgraded versions oh
yeah totally right but actually nothing
automatic right because I saw my mommy
had like golden versions but that's not
quite it either chicken chickens already
uh normally I wouldn't even know about
the existence of the chickens are they
in here
oh that's a problem right that that's a
problem I think that's a problem because
then if I let them out they can walk out
here right
click well now it's too
late
no no what do I do how do I fix it no
not Freedom
no free range
no y I'm so scared to push anything
because I want to I want to be
empty-handed please I don't want to
break everything
I got I have to build a new I do I know
the recipe for that
chin
cute how do I
a CA looks really happy today one month
old
baby a it really looks like a proper
chicken but you you just look like a
chick Goldie Goldie looks really happy
and what do you mean with feeding do
they eat the hay or
what do I mean now they seem
fine
but ah I let them out probably with this
door
right close no no not happening now not
happening now I need to fix the
fence uh put hay on the upper part right
click the little door no no no no no
no put hey top right oh okay
uh over
here how do I how do I put it
down
how E Eh no e for crafting okay right
click right click not
working oh in the middle Oh I thought
you meant in that one space over
there okay
nice
so uh
crafting there is a gate I guess we can
just make another gate or now wait the
wood fence as well okay okay uh I make
one and
then that fixed
yay I figured it I figured that out
almost on my own so
now we can let them out out and breathe
some fresh air and be eaten by some
bigger birds or so I look at them oh oh
it eats the grass oh and they will eat
the blue grass and mommy said they like
the blue
grass
cute well they're eating it so they
don't need any more food
[Music]
right not the bigger Birds well you got
to become the bigger bird yourself then
the circle of
life I'm the big bird who's going to eat
you okay let's try
this looking good what
[Applause]
up and you guys were all saying good
that I'm bringing froggy waa because
it's frog
season it's frogging
time I guess what can you maybe
normally catch the
Frog maybe I'm already doing too much
maybe this is already too much what do
you think cuz my mom said don't do too
much maybe I stop like around here
after I get rid of
this it's probably already too much
stream chat oh
we should just I I can't like I can't
constantly fix the stupid chat
there God damn
it oh you don't that's not your style
oh what's this
anyway Hammer right this oh there we go
okay it takes a few tries
okay then I'm just going to use like
this first half
approximately of the farm for
now okay so what now uh well no didn't
he say like tomorrow I should go to the
city and then there I guess I can buy
some
stuff like the
seeds what I do now
what's there to do maybe I can go over
there check out the go
now
okay is this tomorrow oh oh yeah right
that was a big Ki the key true true
true uh do I go with the bus I guess so
oh I remember this from my mom's uh game
sorry no I don't want to for the bus
don't worry I just don't know how to get
into it shop may be closed by now ah
really it's already
5 is that why I can't get into here it's
out of service oh the Calico desert
ah no bus driver just go right
oh bus I BS I broke the
bus oh
hello Harvey
it's a pleasure to meet you I'm having
the loc
doctor
sick that's sick what do you mean what's
sick I just said I just mean that sick
what what do you mean like where how why
you how what are you feeling exactly
tell me more I I'm feeling like that's
totally
sick imagine this interaction between
some some
Zumer some cool dude and a doctor who
just wants to know what's sick and they
just say like that's sick wow I'm so
funny check the question mark yeah okay
what is this the
birthdays what do I care about all of
your birthdays flower dance book
seller question
[Music]
mark comedian oh
forgot you guys have to remind me dog
where is the
dog why is it so dirty
here it's really
pretty why do I buy those seeds
guys maybe in
there that doesn't look like a shop
oh never mind it's a shop
who
uh
here oh
no come back when ah okay no one's
attending the
shop oh okay
goodbye oh um yeah maybe at almost 8:00
p.m. no one's there to sell
anything the present head seats
the present in the
shop time is important in a game maybe
now it won't even open
anymore oh it opens what present the
present I opened gave me
hay I got one guide God damn it I knew
there was something wrong with that
yeah I got hay m
you're so wrong okay my mom says I have
to make a field I don't know
how here gravel path okay paths okay
animals
map uh
ooh we have a skill tree it's like an
RPG game use to hold the hammer
ah
this
oh ah [\h__\h] ah
[\h__\h] N I want it to be lines can I undo
it can I make it
nicer how do I undo
it
[\h__\h] I I don't I don't have good control
over
this with the pickaxe why does the
pickaxe undo
it why why what's the logic behind
that okay I kind of want to see what I
do so I'm going to I mean I guess I
could get rid of the tree but maybe I'll
still need the
tree no this
way just going to make some
lines have a ah proper system
now it's really hard to see
though now maybe I should
sleep get rid of the tree
okay goodbye tree it's so
over I don't want to see you
anymore
diminish and then I get rid of this too
okay W oh I got some seeds I think saps
but is it just for more
free I don't think I
really want
[Music]
more at least don't now I'm starting to
feel
exhausted well well my first day as a
farmer I can't slack
off we got to do some ground
work will I just
faint or do it like like like this
doesn't that look good okay M okay mommy
says I should buy build
a
a a uh uh what how do I make my hands
empty get in how do I get in how do I
get in no
I can't press the
the my right click didn't work sometimes
okay sleep come
on she said I need to build a
chest okay I can do that should I put it
inside or outside maybe
outside wait there was no K Kitty key
are my chickens
dead oh no they're they're there they're
having breakfast but I guess they
weren't the ones who said Kik Kei in the
first place I don't think they have the
power to say
Kiki just yet they don't have the voice
yet hello they just got back from a
fishing trip you should come down to the
beach uh sometime I've got something for
you m I have a feeling I know what it is
wait a second what happened here did I
make it on even I don't think I did this
happened overnight or but
I didn't do
that I don't think I
did no water well don't don't just tell
me stuff like this tell me how to fix
it h
oh ah okay unwed field mhm mhm well then
how do I water
it wait we need to I make a I need to
make a chest I'm missing one piece of
wood and my YouTube chat died
again
okay okay I have the one piece of wood
for the
chest and then we'll put
it
h here
and then I'll put the hay and the fiber
and the stones and the saps and some
coal oh wait I do have a water can I
didn't even see it what the
freak okay then I shall
water one by one
okay okay no problem o went too far oh
it kind of connects though wait a
second how how does the meta
work uh
no never mind it doesn't really connect
I now it kind of connected feel like
that was two
[Laughter]
patches okay
okay okay okay okay okay well well well
well you said it will go away if I don't
water it so I wanted to water it
first nothing wrong with that nothing
wrong with that
we're making mud I love mud we're making
mud for hey it's too early almost oopsie
sorry for spilling water there we're
making mud for beauty
procedures
oh really couldn't have opened the shop
10 seconds
earlier m
M mommy said
everything
okay I don't have that much
money maybe maybe this is okay for
now potato
potato m M wait how many four different
I fought I bought four different things
right that's perfect then but then I
only have two seats of each so I can't
fill up the whole field can I or is
there more seats than one in
there
goodbye
okay let's see how this
works this is pars what the [\h__\h] is
parsnips what's parsnips kot or what how
do I put this
down Ah that's
it what the [\h__\h] is that beans or what
did I just put there this is
cauliflower and then the
potato okay oh Mommy says pick up
everything what in
the in the city there was something in
the city oh I guess all these like
wheels and and those things were also
something I could pick up can I pick up
this these
flowers maybe
not uh what water water water water
water do I water them
again you think they like that even the
ones were already watered beforehand I
mean the soil is already watered so you
would think they would get the water
already from the
soil only the ones are didn't
okay
H my Mommy wants me
to put the wild seeds in there too but
isn't that just going to turn into grass
again I don't say they're wild
seeds can you overw water them that's
also something I
wonder can I run no can go slower
hello chins how you doing I'm here
because I think I can get more water
from here yeah oh it looks so
pretty Wow have a good time chickens go
get the blue grass apparently you're
going to love you more if you go get the
blue
grass okay uh uh I need to sell is there
anything I can sell anything I don't
need because I feel like I need more
money or maybe if I pick up the things
in the I can sell those
things doing
great I have to pet them every day oh
guys you are so
needy okay okay okay when I get back
I'll give you a nice little pet pet
pet okay so stuff like this
right no not don't water them how do I
pick it
up can I you really pick up these
things it doesn't quite seem like
it oh Mommy says go
down down in the
[Music]
city right the trash when no one's
looking looking look into the trash
trash
trash okay man I'm kind of like lost
without you I would be even more
lost how how do you play this game
without back seeding I don't think I got
anything
uh there's a
girl cute
girl now you have to read the
wiki it's like you have to read a whole
book to understand this
game I don't I don't know but maybe
these flowers oh these flowers I can
pick I
think
oh I got the
[Music]
daffodils daffodils were some of the
like the first flower in English that I
learned about in English
class has a funny name
daffodil okay I got the flowers I don't
see anything else that I can take oh
except these birds
maybe can I have no
stay I will turn you into a chicken it's
a better life a better life on my
farm no wait there's more
flowers oh oh oh it's up there how do I
get up
there a I can't I can't hey yo nice
playground I want to use it oh can I
take these
things excuse me can I raid your
farm that's not okay is that
okay uh I feel like I'm going to get in
trouble for doing this
I got mixed seeds yo
y talk to her apparently you got to be
really social in this game
huh where where did she go wasn't there
a girl just here or did I imagine
her wait what is uh can I do something
with
this
h h
she she right there was a girl right
there was a girl I'm sure there was a
girl
totally oh oh what there a person here
are you just the same person I talked to
before no
M oh aren't you the one who just moved
in I'm M I've been looking forward to
meeting
you really that's where you end the
conversation you don't look so excited
to
me I don't know where I'm going
h Hello She's Got a Hold telescope
yo can I can I have your
telescope greetings I'm Demetrius local
scientist and father oh you must be
really proud father to mention that as
one of your jobs thanks for introducing
yourself
I whoa it
whoa why does it feel like it turned
something around on me oh this is
cute W the lily pads are
cute but then I don't know what to do
[Music]
here he's a family guy he's a Family
Guy B I will take this thank you so much
it's a leak oh I can eat this right away
apparently uh don't look how I'm taking
your things please is that your son
oaba guyaba guy
wait [\h__\h] okay I need to go back I'm
exhausted
edgy
Sebastian Sebastian oh you just moved in
right cool yeah I don't really want to
talk with you
either can I make it back do you think
I'll fall asleep
wild horse
[Music]
radish okay okay there's some stuff here
and there a hi Robin sorry I don't have
time to talk to you I need to go back
and
sleep but she seems like she wanted me
to do that
anyway I have until 2: a.m. oh okay okay
okay so you always like fall asleep at
2: a.m. oh what this no no pick up okay
wait where's uh oh wait I'm not there
yet
oh damn it there's some quests
here okay what if we do them like one by
one so this will do
tomorrow the beach south of town before
5:00
p.m. oh random cop yeah but like uh can
I I I can probably like replan things
right if oh wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait flower
daod cuz if I plant it with my potatoes
or so and it doesn't turn into a potato
then I'm kind of
mad here uh I think it's watered so
that's okay and then can I plant the
lake no can I plant the horse riders
no does it go
bad can't plant this either huh
does it go
bad ah I can sell them keep one of it
one of
these
sell and then the fiber I don't know if
we need the FI probably for
crafting that doesn't go bad okay okay
so I
sell these
apparently save flowers for gifts
oh uh it's going to be fine I'm going to
get
more sleeping early I guess
no feel like I need to do some
more I mean I don't even I made these
fields and I'm not using all of it
[Music]
yet so I don't know let's uh what what
to do is there something to pick up here
no well maybe I should
sleep a bit of cleaning before
bedtime yeah it's so dark I can't see
though I forgot about the
chickens I need to pet them good
night they won't even know maybe cuz
they're already sleeping oh no oh Sor
sorry you're trying to sleep I can't pet
them I'm too late no no they're going to
hate
me
a they're going to hate me
forever come
on don't worry don't worry you're not
you're not you're not I didn't I didn't
I aimed really badly I didn't get you
with the pickaxe
oh man what did I do I need to restart
the game cuz I didn't pet you for one
day
okay oh is this what I
sold
mhm
okay woo
[Music]
money go good
morning oh it's raining I don't have to
what I don't have to water in my plant
then don't ruin my perfect
pattern do you think they're awake yet
they must be awake
early
W that's some fat ass chickens and they
gave me some eggs
let's
go oh my God you're already so grown
up sorry I love you I love you too a b
a cute so that's why they're not out
because it's raining they don't like it
understandable ah I was just wondering
like why the hey if they eat outside
anyway but makes sense for rainy days we
want the hay inside my mom just said and
it's so
true um okay uh okay uh we got this new
thing oh if you want to become a farmer
you have to start with the basics feed
your chickens each day by letting them
eat grass outside or by placing hay into
to their
troughs once they're mature you have
snegg oh we got 100 gold for
that
y
okay uh south of town before 5:00 p.m. I
guess I'll go there
now I hope it works on a rainy day
[Music]
too that's a tough word thank
you thank
you maybe we need bgm
for
this game like my own bgm by the way
what do I do with the eggs do I cook
something or do I sell
them and with Beach of south of the town
do they mean here oh wait yeah I'm
supposed to meet
him good good good good hatch them oh I
can sell them sell them for now
[Music]
a heard there was a newcomer in town
good to finally meet you that's
it cook s I'd sell them for now but you
can C cook them turn them into
ingredients and hatch
them I feel like the kfb fic are to
hatch you
guys we don't sell eggs at kfp we
sell
well you know
we sell actual chickens so I have to I
have to hatch you but no I will sell you
in the game I will sell you I'm still
trying to unwind from a month out on the
salty Seas it was a big haul I sold a
lot of good fish finally saved enough to
buy a new
Ro so give me your old one thank
you thank
you with your nice family yeah that will
hatch you yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah or that will boil you for 3 minutes
and then eat you but don't worry you you
I guess oh wait yeah I don't have a
rooster so these eggs are not um
fertilized right so don't worry about it
guys there's no life in these eggs I
think it's important to me that the art
of fishing stays alive and that hey
maybe you'll buy something from from the
shop once in a
while your shop t
yeah yeah yeah yeah so you are made to
be boiled in this state you received a
bamboo pole a pole
okay there's good water here in the
valley all kinds of
fish oh yeah my Shop's back open now so
come buy if you need supplies I'll also
buy anything you catch if it smells it
sells that's what my old papy used to
say anyway
okay I
try how how
how do I don't I need a
bait oh
hit how what do I
do uh keep the bar behind fish behind
well how ra click to raise by release to
lower bar ah what what what what keep
the bar behind a be ah the green has to
be behind the fish okay ah oh oh I get
it I get it
yeah like Flappy Bird okay that's a good
explanation actually I got a
herring I got a herring
dude but wait let me fish some more oh
[\h__\h] so oh too close I
guess still
works oh
nothing am I too
close let me try
again oh that
barely that barely went any further
what see we wait that might not be so
bad we can sell it I guess
oopsie
impatient
Max now I want a big one I want a big
one come
on
no just seaweed
is this is this exciting guys for
you are you enjoying this hit oh I got a
fish I got a fish oh oh [\h__\h] oh
treasure it was so
difficult yeah
really I know a lot of you guys were
already telling me when I said I'm going
to play this that you play this for
hours and as you're relaxing chill
game it seems it seems like a game that
you can put way too many hours of your
life
in got it come with me little fishy fish
oh oh
[\h__\h] this is so
difficult this is so difficult but at
least I don't need bait right now so I
can do it
endlessly I need more
feeling oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh I'm
feeling this one I'm feel I'm oh I'm oh
yeah I'm with you I'm with you fishy oh
[\h__\h] wait
wait how the
[\h__\h] controller better for this one I
hated the fishing mini game also it's
just a mini game you don't really do
this much fish it U mommy also says it's
really difficult in the beginning
holy [\h__\h] why was it so difficult I
guess I can oh
[\h__\h] I guess I can sell the
fish
uh M PR
gold I'll take
it try ta it okay I I I'll I try one
more time oh [\h__\h]
a [\h__\h]
ah yeah probably can get better rods and
maybe
bait I don't
know come on come
on come
on go fishy fishy fishy oh I kind of
want to eat uh like a
fish oh oh T yeah tapping is good
tapping is good thank
you oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] the balance
when it falls down it oh
it oh
what
oh oh I was so close to getting it but
now it really doesn't want to be caught
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah I want some fried fish oh [\h__\h]
I didn't expect it that
early I need to cook something
today but it's not
fish okay okay okay oh oh oh oh this
time this time you're going to be mine
that yummy
salmon yeah I'm not going to let you go
I'm not going to let you go not
[Music]
let no no come on come on I'm so hungry
please please stop wasting my time
I swear to God please don't this
me [\h__\h]
you oh look at that little emo
kid deep in his thoughts oh I think this
will be good money what the [\h__\h] man
that fish I almost had it I piss me off
I kind of want to fish
again man
wait wait
what
what I heard about did you hear about
edging content like on Tik Tok or no
YouTube or like live streams some kind
of live streams
where they like there's like these these
people they say they're going to do
something like they're going to they're
going to eat this like something with a
[\h__\h] ton of hot sauce on it and they're
like oh I'm going to I'm about to eat it
I'm I'm I'm I'm totally gonna eat it
like I I'm gonna eat it like yeah oh my
God I'm so excited I'm also so nervous
oh this is gonna be so bad oh and they
do that for like an
hour just because they want to [\h__\h]
piss you off I don't
know apparently that's a
thing
yeah uh I heard that from Cody Co excuse
me what is this what is this
oh wait what is this oh I guess I can
fix this wait did I do the thing yeah I
did the thing right build a
silo okay I don't think I can do that
now no what H talk no no no no no no h
talk soon
[Music]
TM we only have 400 p.m. so maybe we
can pick up some more
things yeah okay my Super Chat readings
might be
that oh my YouTube chat
died okay okay well let's talk to this
person Pam you look like a from a
different
Century I get the name is Pam that's it
okay she was insulted don't be a jerk
and we'll get okay I guess we won't get
along
fine W what's
these cute car Jo jart I'm guessing this
is a
ripoff wow
corporations hi orange
hairir oh there's a seats here too
actually speaking of seeds can I still
buy some in the other
shop I'm guessing they're more cheap
over
there
Piers no what you guys probably knew
that
already that's why you didn't tell me to
go or so close on freaking Wednesdays
are you kidding me
[Music]
ridiculous anything else to pick
up smaller smaller business hours that's
why you might want to I don't know go to
the other big place where's this
pot oh flower daffodil
daffodil I got a
[Music]
daffodil daffodils are nice daffodils
are
pretty Stone
no oh that's it oh wait no we can go to
the other
side look at your other Quest
okay wow
scarecrow I need to greet a lot of
people okay
maybe I'll think about it I'm not that
social I want to be the emo kid why does
that dude get to be the emo kid I want
to be the emo kid oh I can't pick this
this stuff up
a then I should probably not be running
around here if I can't pick up the
things
anyway uh okay there's no one out and
about in the rain wait the second these
flowers I can't pick them up either
no maybe I go inside and talk to them
is this an owl on your
door whoa what's this w m
shaft hi
Alex hey you're know New Girl in Town
you think we're going to get along I'm
Alex
okay why hello and welcome to our little
Community my dear you can call me Granny
if you like
sweet it's irritating to have to beat
all these new people exactly my name is
George by the way now Buzz
up he gets
it oh okay I think there's no one in
there so greeted a few more
people nice oh hello sorry
sorry hi uh you almost killed me but
okay I'm
Clint sorry
wait new
dude no
no no no what what what's interesting oh
no a [\h__\h]
no
I person by
[Music]
accident I didn't even know him
yet at least I didn't give him the
egg am Sam good to meet you now he
thinks I like him just because I gave
him a
present I don't like
him man my run is
ruined okay I think it's time to go
home can't go into their
[Music]
houses yeah H
awkwardly giving them random
shells I should give him something
worse oh is there things that they don't
like
receiving oh wait wait a second okay
so
uh we give these and these and can I
give the clam too even though I only
have one
see which should be
okay the guys said keep for presents the
the
flowers yeah
okay I'm just going to sell
it and then I oy oh wait the world is my
oyster let's sell one
oyster one
oyster okay
ah I pet them in the morning right so we
good we
good we good we're
good you know I've only seen like a
small part of my land I
wonder what else there is down
there one day I'll find
[Music]
out ooh 100 gold for one egg didn't I oh
well 50 gold okay okay okay forun
fishing okay okay I want to buy some new
seeds go go go go go I got some money
now let me sell K where is that rooster
coming from must be from my
neighbor must be my neighbor I see the
male but let me take care of the chicken
petting first so that I don't forget and
that they're not asleep oop sorry almost
almost took your part again too
early okay they love
me
okay how my crops
doing I wanted to check how you
doing I don't know I first tried red
click and nothing happens so it's
righted left click and of course this
happens keep finding cool stuff but my
backpack is full do sound like you Wills
got you
coverage check out our affordable size
24 backpack oh I can buy a bigger
backpack reset I can
uh uh how
[Music]
how should I exit to
title oh for
real did it auto save cuz I don't
remember saving I guess it saves after
each
day okay wow you guys support this
lifestyle huh
right chickens
first let's just for safety always go on
the watering cans and I don't I don't
hurt
anybody [\h__\h] where's the other
one oh there you are a they're so
cute they're so fake and fluffy oh I
love I love the
chicken this was our SCH to together
second petting
a yeah that works
okay okay oh [\h__\h]
no that's
right here we
go just going to read
it read it again
the backpack I want to buy the backpack
and talk to more people and buy uh
actually I want to buy more seeds but if
I buy the backpack it's probably going
to cost a lot of money I have received
the
leak a egg
collection I
forgot oh my God they really make them
every
day I want your eggs I I totally want
him you're my money
Farm where where
oh I take I
take beautiful very nice big eggs
today lots and lots of eggs please more
[Music]
more goodbye
I'm taking your kids no don't worry
they're not
fertilized don't think so deeply about
it I need more eggs yeah 100 gold a day
amazing oh it's oh I'm too again I'm 10
seconds
early just like last time anyone around
like you
you a the the ball in your
hand wait Alex didn't I talk to you
before I overheard someone saying that
you got your first chicken the other day
I have two chickens already excuse me
don't forget about the other one
everybody always forgets about the other
one man I wish Grandma had chickens I'd
eat a dozen raw eggs for breakfast each
morning holy
[\h__\h]
ew cook him cook them into
something please eggs have so much
potential look cute
girl
hi
Penny I I I I've seen this girl before
oh hello I'm
penny Wait yeah my mom isn't my
mom no where did I see Penny
before is that all you're going to say
to me
daffodil what if I give her the
daffodil thankss this looks
[Music]
nice okay
hi sell me
something should we just take the same
ones again so that we can fill
up
uh each of my
Fields yes we
should the potatoes that's okay the
potatoes
uh um they have an extra seed there the
random one anyway
I can talk to them two to three times a
day well I I I have to talk to so many
people I have to have to be
organized do they all just like keep
their doors closed for so long oh my God
wait that's in your
trailer how's this
possible how is this possible how how is
it how is this possible or did I just go
underground
what where even is
the
uh where where where is the
wheel I guess no it's a trailer where
that you uh attach to a car I guess oh
it's you
Pam never mind then I already talked to
you I need new people or does it not
matter if it's not new
people not sure
oh hello grandpa Louis again
ah your grandpa used to complain about
the rickety old bad but I think deep
down he actually loved that house I'm
sure he did can I take your plant
no hello new
person wow Elliot got that nice hair
she ah the new farmer we've all been
expecting and whose arrival has sparked
many a conversation strange
spikes I'm Elliot I live in the little
cabin by the beach it's a pleasure to
meet you little oh little cabin by the
beach this
one shees
[Music]
nice I mean bird hello oh this is like a
romance me and the other birds that's my
Affair that's my Affair I meet this
other
bird on the other side of the River
every day talk to
them and we wish we could be closer to
each
other and you guys don't know anything
about
it you don't
know and you will never find
out oops oh wait this
[Music]
bubly no go to the
bubbly does it come to
me I'm going to try again oh [\h__\h] bad
[Music]
start oh you're going down oh you
yelling timber are we going up are we
going up yeah yeah
wooo I just got a [\h__\h] Herring for
it that was such a hard work for
freaking
hering pay me good
money freaking 40 bucks get out of here
get out of here wait where do I buy the
backpack
again it's not in here is it it is it in
the store where I bought the seats
more characters and a shop under my
under my own
place is that what you
saying oh nice
place it was in the store where I bought
the seats old gay cute Grandma you're
the one from that house that I talk to
oh
Evelyn I'll be Bing cookies
today I like to make flower shapes in
the spring a a wait Girls Girls Girls
Girls green hair
girl Carolyn or Caroline hello you must
be waa the new farmer I'm Caroline or
Caroline Jody oh you ear exactly how I
imagine excuse me that's okay I'm Jody
yeah you probably thought my hair would
be more orange and now it's just this
shitty Brown
[\h__\h] I have VC little boy oh a stranger
my name is Vincent mama says not to talk
to strangers but you seem okay yeah
totally uh I am okay but
still don't trust your judgment little
boy it's not always something you can
judge as a young child you don't have
that proper feeling for it yet I
think I don't get anything from these
trash
people hello why are you looking at that
because your birthday is upcoming I just
saw that you're so excited
huh oh
yeah no it's not about of money I'm I'm
I'm just not interested I I I don't
really care about the
backpack that was so unrealistic as if I
could afford
that okay I need to save up for that
then cuz this tiny inventory is not
doing it for
me
inventory wow look at that radiant
shining Barbie girl can I call you
Barbie
haey oh she's like wow so Gorge oh
you're the new farmer girl whatever oh
whatever
a she looks like she likes the word
fetch uh hi I'm
Haley um if it weren't for those
horrendous clothes you might actually be
pretty actually mind oh my God shut the
[\h__\h] up shut the [\h__\h]
up damn girl
you are pretty on the outside and a
little dumb on the
inside I like it
no self fetch me a
shovel
oh oh uh yeah talk to him is there
something
here o a little something to pick up
free things
actually that was wild horse radish but
these healing items don't I need it is
it okay to sell them
[Music]
actually I didn't oh you think I didn't
oh did ah he walked in right when um
when I was coming up to him he was
scared I get lots of them
okay selling okay
okay sell selling better now okay okay
okay okay
okay wait there's another one of those
statues over there I wonder what that is
lenus why why did I go like oh isn't
that like a it's not like Windows or
lenus no what am I thinking of a
stranger helloa
don't mind me I just live out here alone
L tchs
Ah that's lenu God damn it I am not a
computer system
obviously the [\h__\h] was that
sound oh it's
him Bonk Bonk Bonk
Bonk oh so noisy are you are you okay
with living here like it's so
noisy you liveing
right next to the
minecrafter and we
know these OAB boa stard you Valley
people don't get along with the
Minecrafters Let's help him from the
other side maybe I
can and then we can meet oh it doesn't
seem like it's
working it's not working it's totally
not
working oh wait did I talk to the girl
here yeah I
did I I know I talked to
you I'm missing eight more
people
o need
Dynamite well it's not is is isn't my
body enough
I stuck into the caves last night and
got a nasty cut from a rock crab don't
tell anyone okay why would you tell me
why why would you tell
me thanks guys
thanks uh where's everybody I feel like
I uh what wait I didn't go in here yet I
think oh people a [\h__\h] I didn't see
where I was oh wait that [\h__\h] where am
I here
okay oh no
talk ah freaking Pam again freaking Pam
all over again I want to talk to you it
looks like
Mario
Mario oh not anymore not anymore well
hello there I'm G chef and owner of the
stardrop saloon a
saloon nice em cute oh I can read it on
your face you're going to love it here
in Pelican town if you're ever looking
for something to do in the evening stop
by the saloon that's where I work oh
Emily you're such a lovely blue-haired
girl think I like
her oh Shane yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
you look like you would enjoy your time
in this Saloon when you want leave me
alone okay I just wanted the greeting oh
Clint again anyone over here no can I
play these
games
no this one though there's a
skull-shaped keyhole I need a key oh
this one I can
play
uhoh all right oh oh wait how
ah oh
okay I thought it was with mouse I
didn't see the
controls okay here are my
skills
sheesh wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wa already already
going so hard hardcore oh okay and now I
used up my free lives oh I have one left
okay don't go so hardcore right away
chill or is this from the beginning
again
B
yep oh they dropped some
stuff oh oh
oh
what what the [\h__\h]
look what what there's no enemies for me
to shoot because I'm just spawn spawn
killing
them
what oh once you get this like triple
bullet
thing everything oh my God no
no oh man I want to do it
again again again again this is
fun bring it
on I want to get strong again give me
strong
Wawa oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] give me the triple bullet how the
[\h__\h] do I get the triple
bullet uh
[Music]
help I'm just a simple farmer I'm not a
gamer
oh okay okay okay I cleared it up I
cleared it
up chilling
now when are you guys going to drop the
o oh is that it is that it is that
it no I don't know what that
is
no F finish again oh one more
try oh okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay go go go go go oh go go
go
go what how did I get so powerful so
early on last time
H I guess I give up I can't be playing
all day does time pass when you in
here I'mma I'mma take my leave now
thanks for letting me play that was a
lot of
fun zero luck with drops yeah what the
hell
okay we got some new
seeds let's plant them passes no time on
single player
okay yeah yeah yeah
yeah now I don't really remember I I no
I think I
do this goes
here this goes here oh wait I have
more yeah and then the this potato right
no wait here
potato potato was here and
here and the cauliflower I hate this
this is like one of my least favorite
vegetables goes here okay then water
them of course otherwise you guys are
going to lose your
minds don't
worry how long is this going to take
like this you guys going to tell me when
it's finished growing right cuz I don't
think I can
tell
okay two to three days you'll know or
maybe we'll have like have a little
spark or
something all right have some much stuff
to
[Music]
sell
yeah I feel like my nose is so itchy I
must have like really tiny cat hairs on
my nose from cuddling them so much
because I was gone for one
night you guys want to know where I went
I was so happy to come back because it
was really exhausting
[Music]
and oh I really missed my cats too oh
level one 14 o plus one ax proficiency
Tre sometimes drop seeds new crafting
recipe Wild seeds ooh new crafting
recipe field snack okay nice
look I went to colon colon and it was
funny because just the day before like
in girl talk we talked so much about
colon so I really wanted to make this
joke
that all the colon and now I'm in
Colon oh was
that I don't know I don't know I I don't
know how to make a joke out of this but
was just uh kind of funny yeah in German
we say k
that did sound like a BP but I just said
like a and then it turns into
that yo nice
income not
a why don't we get a Kik the key every
day there it
is that's what I want to hear otherwise
how the [\h__\h] should I know when it's
time to wake up huh
H colon in Germany
yeah I heard a little B look so cute
happily sleeping on the
[Music]
ground a bed oh water the chicken yes I
must water the Chicken Little shower for
you you stinky little
chick but you prefer that watering over
over me sihing you right how's the hay
doing in there no let me get in there ah
okay you're still fine oh with the eggs
I forgot the eggs
again
H oh no see I still don't really
understand the uh controls
sometimes remember to water your
chickens so they will grow big and fat
and juicy they need the high ation I'm
come
on come
on I think this one almost has reached
the final stage except for the new ones
oops
MH and tasty well I feel like you're
tasty by default it's just about about
the seasoning
[Music]
really but the night or so or two nights
before I left for
cologne I was supposed to cook that
chicken after my stream or so I think it
was after
stream and I didn't like the hello beep
recipe because this time I forgot again
to choose my uh recipes on my own and
they just sent me something random and I
didn't like it
so I I had a [\h__\h] ton of vegetables
still and a fillet of chicken you know
what I made I made chicken soup with
veggies and
noodles like carrots and leak and
potatoes and and chicken and noodles but
normally you make that with soup chicken
I made it with a chicken
filet a breast
filet but it was fine it was good and I
I kind of freestyled it
I made a big serving and then I ended up
only eating
one so that went a little bit to waste
but
okay oh the Jo
jumart is so good yeah I was happy with
what I made what I put together it
tasted very much like a
soup CH Val joam Mar customers our team
members have removed the landslide
caused by our drilling operation near
the mountain lake did I see that I'd
like to remind you that our drilling
operation is entirely legal responsible
stewardship of the local environment is
our top
priority uhhuh that sounds a little bit
sus we apologize for any inconvenience
this accident may have caused as always
r value your Contin support and
patronage you wasted my time with this
and even made me flip the page
when there was nothing interesting on
that other page just one more sentence
could you not have shortened it a little
bit
please but yeah cologne actually my
first time in Cologne I think I've been
to other uh cities in Germany a lot but
not
cologne but I went to see the cathedral
you know the famous cathedral in in
Cologne I saw
it I saw it it is very big and then
somebody just randomly started playing
the Doodles suck right next to it you
know like Street Music but I never heard
someone like in terms of Street Music
just play the Doodles
suck the Doodles
suck what's it again in uh
English the
suck uh the back pipes yeah yeah yeah
somebody just randomly started playing
the back pipe there I was so happy
actually hyped me up really really badly
let's go B
pipes oh yeah I have a I have a tangent
about the hotel let me tell you in a
moment oh hi
there why why are we having this cut
scene no I didn't go I didn't go inside
I didn't even know if that was
possible that seems so Random I thought
it was random too like normally for
Street Music you hear like
guitars and maybe violin maybe a piano
or so but like a freaking Doodles sack
back pipes sheesh I like it though a
nice for a
change what an
iur yeah this building is
nice this is Pelican town community
center what's left of it
anyway oh yeah I heard something about
the community center like building that
is like one big
it used to be the pride and joy of the
Town always bustling with
activity come back chat there you
go their monk Coes there inside what
what's
that didn't jree saw one too when they
went over was you mean back
pipes this is where you need the item
saved up okay now just look at it it's
shameful these days the young folk would
RAV it in front of the TV then engage
with the community
M that is tool I guess oh not the TV
though I mean yeah maybe the TV but like
not the antenna satellite TV
know not what you think Louis well
listen to me I sound like an old
fool Georgia Corporation has been
housing me to sell them the land so they
can turn it into a warehouse Pelican
town could use the money but there's
something stopping me from selling it I
guess old- like me get attached to
relics of the past oh well if anyone
else buys JoJo Cod membership I'm just
going to go ahead and sell
it
eh no I will fix it up don't worry let's
go inside
okay show me show me what's up inside is
it worse
inside yeah yeah yeah o
the wind is going
through oh dear there's
ghosts what's this I guess Vincent and
Jazz must have been playing in
here this place is even more
dilapidated did I say it right then I
remember I thought it was a egg plopping
what's this an apple move legs and
arms the [\h__\h]
I said it right
yooo what's the matter are you will no I
just saw an apple with arms and legs
what the
[\h__\h] you saw something I wouldn't be
surprised if this place was full of rats
oh there it is again [\h__\h]
Apple
oh you're worrying me
W me you
look I think I'm going to head home I
need some
lunch okay but but what was the purpose
of this if you're just going to leave me
alone
here hey I'll keep this place unlocked
from now on maybe you can help me catch
a rat if you have some extra time the oh
the apple right the
Apple it did not look like a rat to me
strange I'll have to come back and
explore this building
further what if I wanted to do it now
don't kick me out
what's
this cannot see what's this cannot
see but I'm I'm sure I can pick up some
things and bring them with me
right oh it's
scary what the [\h__\h] a big ass
safe broken
up oh this is spooky
so spooky oh there's nothing no apples
oh there is the
Apple no don't run
[Music]
away no
no I guess I need to learn a new
language in order to understand
this I saw a golden apple wasn't even
the green one one from before
fascinating
H okay it's another day maybe do you
think we should buy more seeds or should
I save up for the backpack
now oh my mom says I can go into the
mine do I want to go into the
mine oh jod the food at joj might not be
the healthiest for my family but with
such low prices you'd be crazy oh so the
seats actually cheaper
there I'm missing five
people into the mines you can eh is your
choice about the oh hey I'm trying to do
a kickflip well do it let me talk to you
Sam Sam kickflip
guys if you look at the word don't
doesn't it read like kfp to you
cows they look like
dogs but no this cute wow
bunny I want to catch a
bunny come out little bunny don't be
scared yeah kickflip kfp maybe kfp
stands for K kickflip I don't know
fish maybe I can reach this
one still a little bit too
far okay okay okay okay okay oh oh we're
going down we're yelling timber and I
got it that one was easy
Sunfish yay first time
why was that one so easy I appreciate it
though
oops oh the [\h__\h] soggy newspaper
great now I'm out of inventory space
though what if I catch a
fish
oh oh [\h__\h] yeah yeah not happening I
think yeah okay
that's all right one fish per
day
keeps
my H what do fishes give you this looks
nice can I get
this H oh yeah I can but inventory for
maybe the trash can go away then uh how
do I trash the trash can I not just
throw it on the ground go back into the
water
a here I trash the trash but this looks
nice a
Dandan dandelion
dandelion where am I anyway any people
here
rapon I can hear someone
inside does this person ever come
out Dandy lion oh [\h__\h]
hey why is it not
dandelion dandelion sounds
stupid I'll
see
when oh that's a broken down house I
doubt there's anyone
here I need to find more
people hello Mossy
Mossy the Audi books say like I don't
what
really which audio
books English language audio
books that's because I spoke
them oh another D Dean
dandelion oh there's so much stuff down
there but I don't think I can even go
there can
I and I don't have space anyway but can
I go down oh I can no I can't never mind
o so much
trash okay okay let me tell you let me
tell you while we're on the way
back oh wait this oh what what about
this is this wait I want
that
damn can I is it
but it doesn't add it to what I already
have should I eat the fish do you think
it not not going to sell for
much well yeah okay let's sell the items
and then come
back uh if I find my way back that is uh
is it that way I going to a Comm and
catch well but it was the first time for
me it's special to me
B oh hello have I talked to
you a you're the cow
person Marney a May Le told me you just
arrived at Marney
Marney I sell livestock and animal care
products at my ran you could say uh you
should swing by some time Tom
time all right we talk to
her wait another with Dand liion you
guys just making fun of me by saying
dandelion and dandelion is the right way
to say it
maybe whatever I'm probably not going to
come back too much time will pass
anyway oh hello oh cute girl small girl
Jaz is it short for jasman H hi and you
want talk to right yeah panty if you
take in the dirt you can find some
interesting things well I need a shovel
right wait do you want a Dany
Lion Wait wait wait wait here is this a
gift oh you don't like it wait she
didn't take it did
she oh she
did
okay
nice nice let's look at my
social
M Penny oh this is such a dating
game telling me who's
single even for the kids the [\h__\h] who's
this wizard I didn't see this wizard
yet
oh who just went in there did I see that
person
before what about you Alex are you
again H I think we have some new people
you new are you maybe not handling Salty
Fish a yeah you're the the Fisher guy
all day makes me real first step
okay understandable hey it's Mr Mrs Wawa
the new farmer and PR owner of the local
General Store if you're looking for seat
my shop is the place to go I'll also buy
products from you for a good price will
you any new people Shane don't you have
work to do
wow
chill look at all these orange haired
people mocking me
Leah Leah is new I think hell nice to
meet you yay she's cute she's orange
haired is this the other best girl you
picked a good time to move here the
spring is lovely the spring is lovely
the spring is lovely the spring is
lovely okay okay Leah is wife Emily best
girl what about Pam guys no [\h__\h] love
for Pam you guys for
real I thought I thought hgs were in
demand ah spring the SE of pastels I
actually prefer jewel tones myself oh
excuse me I was mumbling about fashion
again wasn't I
fashion
fashion look at him dancing
shees okay I spoke
to 20 oh I missed one more
person one more one more van more van
more van more van
more feel like I could get that mushroom
can I if I Chuck down the
tree a Rapunzel yeah what the [\h__\h]
Rapunzel how do I talk to
Rapunzel if her name is not Rapunzel I'm
going to be so
mad oh the fish I should sell with the
fisherman huh can I sell it here too
I'mma sell it here it's probably going
to sell for less but it's
[Music]
okay yes yes for what wait what did I
ask oh wait the
here the Box sells for the same PR ah
okay nice
nice oh frog come back you froggy wow
friend all froggy W friends are my
friends because I need to intricate oh
[\h__\h] intri in no in
infiltrate her friend
Circle oh
[\h__\h] cute damn look at look at this
whole big ass plot of land she
[Music]
she exploring a little bit oh what whoa
what's
this what's this okay I should go
back I should
sleep might want to yeah I was thinking
about the
hay but I'm not getting any hay what is
this mixed seeds oh I got some mix seeds
woohoo
and I don't even I can't even tell the
grass apart
anymore it's okay we can one way or
another if we need hay we'll find it one
way or
another ah let me
out
okay
uh I think I'll plant the seed really
quickly
let's
go oh I was going to tell you the
tangent
about something that
happened oh wait we got a little bit
more than usual because one egg was
special wasn't
it yeah big and good job chickens good
job the special one
okay okay nice nice nice 30 bucks good
money how much was the backpack like
5,000 or so I try my best try
harder
K to you too
sir cherry
blossoms wow the flower petals are all
over isn't it a beautiful day M Mr
Chicken Mrs Chicken B in
indeed let me say hi to you too why are
you inside still it's so nice outside
you got to check out the the beautiful
flower petals come on come
on a fine Kik key to you too
sir all
right all right wait I need some
water so
okay so I stayed in Cologne for one
night in a hotel
and you guys know I worked in the hotel
before right for a few years so I
know what happens in hotels I know how
you try
[Music]
a it's over r back let's
go oh how beautiful look at the flower
petals yeah I know I know how um you try
to uh
act let's just put away the destructive
tools
shall
we oh my
God oh my God so what was I
saying anyway so I worked in the hotels
before so now how stuff works
yeah
and uh
so I I went uh with a friend too okay
and I paid for both both rooms we had
two rooms same type both are supposed to
be a uh what was it like a double
room so I mean single use but
still double beds are the parip is ready
which one's the parip
ah wait this also a
parsnip Tada oh wait it was ready
anyway that's why I plucked it ah
[Music]
and okay do I sell those
now need new
seeds got to get new seeds yeah okay
okay okay I'm on it keep one sell other
okay
so okay so I'm doing all the check-in
procedure
everything's already paid we got those
uh double rooms and we're checking in
and
then we go up we are in different floors
okay
and after like I get into my room I'm
like hm this is weird my room is only a
single bed first of all I'm like kind of
surprised because I haven't seen a
single bed in a hotel room in like a
million years
except for Japan in Japan that's still
somewhat common but I haven't seen that
in Europe or anywhere else like I don't
ever see even though I travel as one
person a lot I don't ever see the choice
of a one
bedroom one single small bed rather than
like one big double bed I don't yeah
it's rare these days because like I
think it's just a logistic kind of thing
it doesn't make sense uh financially for
a hotel
to build single rooms anymore they
realized ah this doesn't make sense
let's just build double beds and we can
use it for single Travelers and for
double Travelers a couples or
whatever
[Music]
yeah my solders tell me you've been
poking around inside the old Community
Center why don't you pay me a visit oh
my chamers are west of the forest lake
in the sto Stone Tower I may have
information concerning a rat problem
problem is that the Rapunzel
okay
bunny
no you had a single bed hotel in Spain I
think it's really really rare I mean
maybe in like
a like a motel kind of setting not Motel
like hostel kind of setting maybe
there's single beds
there hi Harvey
usually see two twin beds in one exactly
that's like the most
common
uh I don't want to buy too many I need
to
save ah now already my inventory is full
I forgot to sell the eggs okay let me go
back and plant these immediately so I
see the single bed I'm like well I'm I'm
traveling I mean I'm not I'm traveling
not alone but I'm sleeping alone so like
I guess this is fine but still kind of
weird I I'm pretty sure I booked uh
double bed
rooms like so I should be getting either
two twin beds or one big bed I mean I I
don't don't really care that much but
still it's I feel like I should
get you know what I what I booked even
if I don't need it
necessarily I just felt something was
off so um
I met again right away with uh the other
person and I asked oh so how's your room
you have the double bed or single bed
like me and then it turns out yeah it
was a double bed and I only got the
single bed what the [\h__\h] I'm like what
what what I I even paid for this and I
think it was pretty obvious why do they
give me the lower floor single bedroom
when like it was so obvious I'm the one
paying for all of
this like hello
hello what's going on so I decide
to get Justice normally I will accept a
lot of things I'm not really a Karen
okay I will accept a lot of uh
circumstances and I worked in the hotel
before too so I I I
actually that's that's why I might feel
like I know I want one how do I take one
ah here here we go
okay I might accept things at least if
you maybe give me a good explanation
like you could tell
me uh that you need to give me this room
because you don't have any other
availables you could ask me if I'm okay
with it because I I understand
circumstances like over booking and
stuff you know but whatever so I go back
to the check-in counter and I speak to
the same person and I'm like and so the
room that you gave me is it actually the
room that I was supposed to get and like
not he said nothing at the check-in but
now he's like oh uh yeah it's a it's a
you got an upgrade I'm like an upgrade
how is it an upgrade I'm pretty sure I
booked like a double room I mean I'm I'm
I'm alone so
it's okay I guess but like I don't think
this is what I booked how is this an
upgrade and then he said oh yeah you
know I we gave you an upgrade because
it's a it's a room to the oh it's a room
that looks to
the in inside uh so it's not not to the
street so that it's uh less
noisy and at that moment I was like oh I
see what you're doing I see what you're
doing you have the problem problem that
you have more couples
arriving uh and you have some single
Travelers arriving who book double rooms
but you need those for the couples that
are arriving that are traveling in pairs
so you secretly hope that I don't notice
you secretly give me the uh the tiny the
one person room because I'm alone even
though that's not what I booked and then
you will just tell me that it's an
upgrade just because it's not to the
street side
I know exactly what you're doing I know
this is how we do that kind of stuff but
the fact like if it was an upgrade that
actually feels like an upgrade and that
you're actually proud of to give me an
upgrade then you would tell me in the
checkin because that makes the customer
the visitor happy but this is not the
kind of upgrade that makes anyone happy
it's not an upgrad to boast about right
yeah you can't fool me I have experience
with
this so I told him like oh well it
doesn't really feel like an upgrade and
I I don't know I feel like i' prefer to
not be upgraded then you know and then
and then the moment I said that I
noticed his attitude and his facial
expression kind of
change uh so he looked like more annoyed
and like like he gave off a sigh and he
was less talkative and all that so it
was very clear to me what was happening
like I was right with my assumption that
you're just you're trying to you know
give me the smaller room without me
noticing but like I'm not traveling
alone so I can com I mean I I'm sleeping
alone but I'm not traveling alone so I
can compare with my friend who you gave
the proper room think about it you have
to think about that I'm going to talk
about it with my travel partner
dude think
think if the local fishing SC got a a
bit more lively I might expend the shop
stock ooh all right all right all right
you're telling me to fish more I'll
try no one pulls a FAS on me no no no
the thing is really I I I I know this
wasn't like the upgrade that you you try
to sell it uh as it's just circum like
you're trying to
um what's the
word you're just trying
to organize
the you know you try to minmax your
hotel booking and oh yeah I asked him
actually like if the hotel is fully
booked uh and he said like oh we are on
the path to it and I'm like well that
that says you're
not yet and I would like to have my room
cut category
[Music]
please
yeah and then he said okay but it might
be on a lower floor than now is that
okay and I'm like yeah whatever it
turned out to be on the higher floor so
so much for
that I don't know
I as I said if you would have not tried
to hide it because it obviously felt
like he was hiding it because he knows
it's not a good upgrade it's not an
upgrade at all
also it wasn't noisy on the street side
either but if you would have told me
like oh so we're like a little bit oh
sheesh a little bit over booked right
now do you mind
like and then but then you should have
given me like the breakfast for free or
something like that because maybe in
your system it's an upgrade but no no I
don't I don't even buy that I mean yeah
it could be like in your system it's
kind of like an upgrade
[Music]
but [\h__\h] where is the the tower I
thought it was in this
area yeah if if they'd give me a little
discount on the breakfast or
something yeah if they'd
the comp the breakfast then I'll take
the smaller room for sure keep going
left and down
okay okay to the left to the
left
H and then I got the proper room
and then everything was good but I
noticed I noticed the attitude changed I
was like aha I gotcha I got
you I mean moving rooms is always like
after you check someone in moving rooms
is always so annoying I get that I hated
doing
that but yeah I didn't touch anything in
the room I went in I put my uh suitcase
down and then I was like
okay I don't like this yeah so so at
least it doesn't have to be cleaned
again you know you just have to change
me in the system but that's not a big
issue
either he just knew that H now I have to
do like I have to try to give this small
room to someone
else hope hoping they won't know this
hopefully it won't fail again ah damn it
I wish that stupid dump naive little
girl would have taken it I'm not a
stupid dump little naive
girl I even I don't know they even knew
that I was working hotels before because
at the check in like they were
apologizing for uh like the the system
being slow because they have a new
operating system like oh oh which one is
it I worked in hotels before and they
said Opera and I'm like oh yeah I worked
with that one before too that is a
shitty one um so they knew they even
knew they knew they know I'm I'm paying
for this they know I booked all of this
they know I worked in hotels why you
should have oh yeah I talked with my
friend about how they should have just
given it to my friend because my friend
would not have noticed honestly and
would have not complained would have not
thought about it would have Pro probably
been properly happy with it because I
mean I didn't even I don't I don't think
I even shared what I
booked so
H they were testing me unfol that's yes
I am un folable I am
unable give it to my friend don't give
it to me is what I'm saying
or just tell me straight up anyway
anyway you could have just swapped with
your friend maybe but in the end I mean
things have to be done properly oh maybe
I am turning into a
Karen maybe I am well it's a I spent a
lot of money you know so I have the
right to sound like a
k oh well whatever whatever
but you guys are always telling me to
not get scammed and then I'm always
getting scammed and blah blah blah now
this once I'm standing up for myself and
now you're calling me a Karen
wow
wow the two faces of
[Music]
kfp thank you thank you I I did I did
try to get what I paid for
[Music]
uhuh I got to yeah I got to assert
myself to not be rolled over
exactly yeah my win yeah yeah yeah Karen
fried Phoenix excuse
me doesn't make you Karen just makes you
strong yeah I need to I need to get
better at this kind of stuff yeah cuz I
do get rolled over a
lot I need to become more confident and
stuff yeah this stress thank you
maybe you're also a Karen maybe we're
both carens
anyway oh come
in
[Music]
uhhuh fancy place you got there are you
hiding a Rapunzel at the top of your
Tower no I'm rodia seeker of the Arcane
truth a mediary between physical and a
pheral master of the seven Elementals
keep her wait this sounds like a Game of
Thrones title
Seven Seas and blah blah blah chains
breaker blah you got the point I love
game of fron and you w are the one whose
arrival I've long
foreseen call Caren
rot here I'd like to show you
something is it the is it the Dragon
Balls
Behold a [\h__\h] Apple
guy it's
you I must eat you to keep the doctor
away you've seen one before haven't
you it scares me the vitamins are
terrifying to
me they call themselves The jyos they
only just look like apples don't they
these ones for some reason they refuse
to speak with me oh my jet died
hello the
vam yeah that's not a wizard hat is it
you're right the [\h__\h] is that hat you're
Faker
hi I'm not sure why they've moved into
the community center but you have no
reason to fear them
you found a golden scr wring in an
unknown language most
interesting stay here I'm going to see
for myself I shall return
shortly
[Music]
bye okay
okay then he comes back from the
door I found a note
okay can you read it for
me the language is obscure but I was
able to decipher
it we the junimo are happy to Aid you in
return we ask for gifts of the valley if
you are one with the forest and you will
see the true nature of the
scroll gift as in every single item one
piece of it and that's why I'm keeping
one of
each one with the force what do they
mean h h h
ah sort of maybe multiples of some one
piece new season wi come
here my cauldron is bubbling with
ingredients from the forest mayy f m
scrab caramel top toad stool can you
smell it
uh no no no no I'm not no no no no no I
don't want to drink it
you no no please no have mercy on me ew
why is she actually drinking
it
e i don't look I don't feel so good and
I don't look so good I think I got
poisoned oh maybe I can talk to them now
and I can read it now
oh
dear it's the toad stool it's the
[\h__\h] toad
stool I'm turning into
toad stand back I'm
toing need
cookie
okay can I skip this oh I
can I've gained the power of the forest
magic I can decide for the true meaning
of the J Scrolls let's go
oh oh did
I it didn't
count maybe
now I predicted you arrive a long time
ago it doesn't
count weren't we at 27 already before
no is said actually 28 people and have
to find every single one of them oh my
God the girl in the
shop purple hair
girl in which
shop Abigail didn't I talk to
her okay
you have to open the village M if you me
to help no I'm okay okay okay I'm going
to be fine is it not her she's also
purple-haired
girl but I talked to her
before well I can't talk to her anymore
anyway hey you're in the
way dad's coming back soon I hope he
bring me some toys wait you're blocking
the way
where in the shop I hope o time's
ticking can I go through I can this
feels like I'm thiefing right
now Caroline but where's the purple hair
girl there's no one else in here maybe
she comes back later oh what the [\h__\h] is
this
some kind of Temple Shrine in here
hi you can pass
now tiny tiny
hallway where's this girl maybe outside
check Saloon or north of here
purple
[Music]
no
no may maybe North
[Music]
then but this
late at 8 10 isn't she a child maybe now
she's back in the
house no she's a young
adult girl where are you
ah found her cute picture oh that's
right I heard someone new was moving on
to the Old
Farm don't tell anyone but I stuck into
the old Community Center last night I
think it's haunted oh yeah it
is oh I found her I found her I did them
all I talked to them
all well I didn't hear you I'm pretty
thinking about
something
mhm what is it meaning of life doing
some deep thinking I
see
okay
then oh I already gave someone a
gift now I don't have anything with me
it doesn't count what I did before also
don't I get like a
reward did I get a reward for talking to
so many people that was a lot of work
okay a lot of socializing it's not that
easy talking to 28 strangers when you
move into a new place like that
damn respect to my self for doing
that I'm going to Chuck that tree down
now cuz it's an iur go
away seeds more
smos seeds yeah
vamos vamos
smos o
[Music]
oh yeah I I was shook at by how empty
the cologne airport is by the way it was
so
spooky no people so tiny even though I
feel like cologne is a big city but and
and then it's not even an airport that's
just for cologne it's like sharing it
with uh another city and I was at that
airport before many many years ago but I
went to the other city that it was
sharing it with h
no both when I arrived and when I left
it was just really really
empty yeah cologne is a big city so I
was
surprised I went to Cologne Bond
airport I guess maybe you can get there
from dorf uh airport as
well H naming your city after
perfume yeah I I was thinking about that
the whole time as as well I still had
all the cologne in my
brain the DOI Place yeah the DOI place
is kind of
close you sure you're sure
sure just trying to get some work done
here before I
sleep Chuck Chuck Chuck how many wood
Chucks can a wood chuck ch ch ch
ch ch yep yep
yep fiber
Stones I don't need to sell these oh
wait I still have some hey
hey
stops Maple Maple seed this is for the
maple tree okay okay
okay H how many
how much wood would a woodchuck chuck if
a woodchuck could chuck wood
hey would you like to be a guest for
games SC and cologne if tails is
presenting a new gamees [\h__\h] yeah [\h__\h]
yeah you think you think they would
present their game
there I mean I've never been to Gamescom
which is in Cologne and is like really
famous for being [\h__\h]
huge never been there before wa level up
I can make the Scarecrow now it looks
like me what the
[\h__\h] are you saying I'm a scarecrow
excuse me just because of my
hat my hay hat makes amazing sick hat
watering whole proficiency new basic
fertilizer awesome though
nice okay we barely sold but wait 195
noce that was a good egg in
there I do frighten Birds I frighten you
Kik so much
kiky you love to see it you love to hear
it wake up chicken are you always up so
early
cutie chicken did you like me some good
eggs to thank
you you got you still got some hay
nice okay eggs for the day thank you for
the breakfast I'm totally eating it I'm
totally yeah yeah no I'm not selling it
why would I sell
it I love your eggs give me
more okay watering
time nice
[Music]
eh what else was there to talk about H
oh yeah getting home yes today was kind
of rough everything was taking so much
time and there were
delays I found some American
dude who was like confused about the
trains being delayed and how do I get to
where I need to go now was trying to
help him but he seemed a little bit
drunk seemed a little bit drunk but
tried my best he was so like what the
[\h__\h] I mean it was pretty late
already I felt bad for him there weren't
many train options left anymore for
him but we looked up a route for
him that he could take and he took us I
I told him to take a photo of it so he
doesn't forget cuz he seemed he just
seemed very overwhelmed with
everything uh told him to take a picture
and then he's like I mean I guess I
should
and then later I
realized that that train that we told
him to take ended up also being delayed
and then he would miss his
connection then we didn't see him again
though I hope he figured it out I hope
he got to where he had to go did I water
everything yeah I think I
did oof it's so oof I feel I felt so bad
for him because I mean he doesn't speak
German and you know being in a country
so far from your home not speaking their
language I mean we speak you know
English you can talk to people and then
they will answer you in
English you know no issue there right
let's make a
scarecrow
um oh I have to have this in my
inventory 50 W I think I have that stuff
no no he needed to go to another city
not just like within the city he needed
to go to another city so that's not that
easy that late in the evening and then
trains are delayed and all
that what was it what was the other
thing Stones right I have stone I think
I have it
now 50 wood wait I took the wrong thing
where's the wood
ooh okay I need to check more trees
let's go let's be productive let's get
the Scarecrow though I haven't seen any
birds uh making a mess of my Fields
yet hope they made it hope he made it
really I like picking up these
things Chuck Chuck Chuck Chuck Chuck
Chuck oh oh already got enough I think
H what are we missing now one coal oh
wait I have the coal in the inventory oh
[\h__\h]
sorry can you break
it I think it didn't need the fiber at
all oh no it
did it
did
yay a how nice oh I got pine cones too
let's put it down wait my my my keyboard
is is going crazy there you
go eh how do I put it down it looks
exactly like why does it look so much
like me why does it look more like me
than
the character I
built where do I put it how do I where
do I how do I why can I not place
it how to place
Scarrow it's
me I got ah oh it's just okay it just
has to be near to me oh my God I will
never understand
this let's put
it how much does it
cover like how how big is the area it
covers like if I put it down here will
it cover the future Fields you know or
should I just put it down
here eight tiles one two three four five
7 okay the width should be
okay uh although over on here this side
might be
too but it's okay then I'll put it
like one two three four yeah it should
be fine if I just put it here
whatever and then I'm going to make
these fields a little bit longer
I know like
this so that the Scarecrow is in the
middle and then I'm going to make this a
little bit shorter so that the length
looks is actually is it right side
longer like this yay this should
be the proper way
oopsie right looks looks about right
looks perfect
[Music]
H oh you know in the airplane I
downloaded a YouTube video from dendle
German YouTuber that I watch a lot um
like I downloaded like some streams he
was doing recently where he
played the breath of the wild
randomizer I'm not going to explain too
much what it is but it's so [\h__\h]
funny cuz
wish I could play something like that
because it was ridiculously
funny look look it up look it up maybe
you can find it and it just like it just
randomizes everything it randomly
teleports you and it randomizes the
items you get it randomizes like
everything it's so so [\h__\h] funny he
was like he was molding so
much yeah it's so funny it randomly
takes away your hearts it randomly takes
away your but then it adds money and
then it gives you oh yeah like you get
you you you get a [\h__\h]
uh what do you call those little things
again in English but then instead of the
the sapling or whatever that it gives
you the the little uh poop instead of
that a COK yeah is of the poop or like
additionally to the poop it just may
randomly give you one of the the like
for example mea's mea's power you know
so
random and then then where you should
actually obtain mea's power you just get
something
else it's so
funny oh my God it was so funny to watch
I I haven't laughed out loud uh watching
like videos and
streams much except for like okay every
once in a while I laugh at a codo video
and every once in a while I laugh at a
dendo video but like generally it's
really rare so that was so funny was so
funny
yeah yeah and Pokemon ones M
mhm so is there oh got a little
sapling okay it's already so late yeah H
should i h inventory full what's this
again this is a mixed seed
okay
here and the Tre the trees I just keep
for now I
guess pine cones coal put back this
stuff
okay I'm done with my classes for the
semester let's go
congratulations that's big big
otu okay looks nice now doesn't it why
why I I you look more like me than
me I
can't I
can't I oops I just
[Music]
can't uh what do I do
uh
here oh ah I did eat
Yahoo ah let's try to build the silo if
I have the re and give someone a gift
let's do the gift first wait I don't
have let me get a
flower
sorry H Van van I'll find another one
don't
worry why am I no I'm moving I'm the one
that's moving not the one that's just
standing around hey this one this one
that's
me I can check the community center oh
okay yeah true
okay let's find a cute girl to give the
flower
to cute
girl cute girl times two hello Maru a
yeah that was you do you have fun
working at the farm of course well
that's good isn't it was that a quiz
question I feel quizzed Penny hello the
weather's interesting today don't you
think
[Music]
give me give me give me
thanks okay a
[Music]
silo H was it up here the community
center oh wa no
here wow
I don't have that much time left
though Apple
guy I can speak your language
now don't run
no
oh
aha reward Bridge
repair
oh wait that is actually I could already
finish this one if I didn't give away
the death the or whatever what it was oo
that's going to take a
while that is going to take a while I
haven't seen any of these before I
haven't seen these
before I think I've seen this one this
one before but I haven't picked it
up oh wow okay big construction bundle
well it's
manageable okay not a h so I I bring
those things and I put them here so the
first thing to aim for is this one then
we need wild horse radish daffodil leak
and a dandelion you guys remember that
please different seasons ah oh summer
season specific oh [\h__\h] then maybe I
shouldn't have given away the daffodil I
hope the season doesn't change
soon oh
no what do you think about
Falon uh I mean I wouldn't I wouldn't
call myself a fan
uh well he's got some cool
[Music]
songs I never get anything from here do
you guys ever get
anything I got J Earth crystal what the
[\h__\h] is that looks fan
see yeah the problem is with German
songs I can't really sing them in Koka
streams to be
honest I can't really because of oh
field snack because of um German
dmca very particular for German songs I
mean I'm not going to I haven't been
getting any dmca and so on but
um it's you know
the gamer yeah the [\h__\h]
gamer um makes it so that you know Jaz
wck says
no hello Abigail you again I've been
pushing off my home work all week and
looks like I'll be pulling an old ner no
that's not good for your
skin you shouldn't be doing that take
care of your skin girl
[Music]
you like the Alice
noi thanks hey what the [\h__\h] is
this hello what the [\h__\h] is this
pig
hello oh belongs to the wizard
huh cute I should go back a traveling
Merchant well now he's not in I suppose
well the floor looks like it's live
okay I'm on my way back everything looks
way more taunting when it's dark
scary Yeah well yeah those are really
exceptions the ones I did saying like
for example for the EUR trucker
stream don't get used to
it don't get used to it
I'm sorry unfortunately it is what it is
you
know
strict strict
stuff I guess I just got to make my own
German oh Mommy says do not sell the
crystal I need it for the Mayo
machine oh oh I could have gone up I was
thinking if I if that path leads up to
me I wasn't
sure that looks like candy canes
yeah German original song when
H I don't know I wouldn't want to put
out a single like I put singles out
maybe once or twice per year
so like making that one single
[Music]
German maybe a part of a song can be
German you
know or like I did a Korean version for
do you I could make a German version for
a song
didn't I make a German H
[Music]
before What a fine kiyy day I'm going to
kiy kick some ass is this really trash I
think I can sell it I should have I
should have sold
it maybe I'll keep the
snack for when I'm going out
let's sell the
trash
okay okay get the first ground work of
the day
done keeping you safe from Silence I'm
here for you good morning
B cute baby oh the other one where where
was the other one they still have all
the hay we're good we're good we're
going to be okay oh there you are S I
love you I love
[Music]
you B B B B B yeah maybe I'll rename
them at some
point how many chickens can I have is it
reasonable to have like 100
chickens is that is that you think I can
do
[Music]
that oopsie
they're both special eggs let's go if I
build enough cops eight per CPE oh
that's
uh it's going to be difficult
then yo yo yo yo
yo oh I think maybe these are finished
no still not oh they take a lot of time
they better sell for good
money
CH is that
something is something right you need
water we good we
good they keep growing off the Harvest
oh those ones ah so I don't need to buy
new ones for those ah
okay then that's nice that's
[Music]
nice oh okay okay I'm a sell
no hey what the [\h__\h] I guess that's okay
potato potato goodbye potato let's go
out look for uh death fil I think is the
one I'm missing
now the beans will keep producing that's
[Music]
awesome the strawberries that I'm
growing are getting bigger and bigger
too they're still green but they're
growing bigger I wonder how many I can
get out of those my Mommy gave me like
the the base plant that she grew to like
teenager
size and I'm going to make it into an
adult hello Benny wow what's wrong do
you want something no want know what's
wrong with
you like now I see maybe like four or
five green small
strawberries but are there going to be
more oh mommy's
typing mommy is
typing what am I doing anyway I'm
looking for
flowers flowers I want to get the one
flower daod
it takes time this is training for your
iral
garden perhaps you may see it like
that oh oh oh although I'm not going to
go that hard uh like my mom goes for
example like she makes everything right
like a million different types of
vegetables I I I don't have the green
fum for
that endeavor
I'm not ready for that slowly
slowly I will I at least want to grow
like some yummy fruit like strawberries
and then I want to be able to grow uh
cherry
tomatoes I did get some cherry tomato
like plant that already had some cherry
tomatoes on
it but I think it's already
dying I think I over for watered it
maybe the cherry tomatoes are looking
nice but the leaves are like [\h__\h]
up
yeah Mommy do you mean buy strawberry
plants IRL or in the
game where's the festival egg she's
talking about some egg
Festival is it yellowing no
[Music]
not light or insect
problem both Ah that's my place let's
clean this
[Music]
up if i' have known the Dills are so
rare I found oh what is this geode why
is she so excited the local blacksmith
can break it open for you who who knows
what might be hidden what gotcha
got
got oh my God the game got me excited
for that
one
yellowing thank you for the yellow Super
[Music]
Chat Rock gotcha I want to go right now
can you guys tell me where the
blacksmith is do I have access to him
already
[Music]
y
y bottom right of the town
okay I'm on my way Mr
[Music]
blacksmith so guys uh tell me in Celsius
how hot it is over there where you guys
live right
now tell me tell me
what a lovely D 18 20 25 what Celsius oh
M Mia maintaining household is difficult
work but somebody has to do it 18 8 18
29 oh wow 29 27 25 28 38
sheesh yeah I wish Abby wouldn't spend
so much time in a
room oh Mommy says I should go into the
mine and check my TV and the fort tell
okay okay one after another first the
blacksmith or is is this the black
that's not the blacksmith house
right more bottom
right that's not a blacksmith
house right across the bridge this
one no the other one huh
yeah so um it's not that hot in Austria
yet either it's quite nice
though can go
outside uh perhaps without a jacket
already I sensed you would be
here now let me tell
you
got what is it Sandstone ooh
thanks I
guess I am
going somewhere that that's what okay so
there's no schedule this week because I
was gone yesterday and I'll be gone
quite a bit of the
week and I'm
traveling to a very very hot
place and I think I'm going to die
M oh
train you can donate that to the other
building I should donate
it you want me to donate
it to the
library is that building the library do
they need it do I get something from
donating
[Music]
it oh Mommy also says donate
it hello
howdy G abysal not a single piece in the
entire collection ah I
see you want a stone
Museum H what's this you found something
let me see
it m i I got rewards okay remarkable
it's very old i' have to study this in
Greater detail but is yours yeah
yours H I've got a few a favor to ask
you would you consider donating a any
new artifacts or minerals that you find
we could make a groundbreaking discovery
together and who knows if you keep
donating I might come cross some
interesting items to sent you
away think about it will you if you
decide to donate just bring the objects
to the front
desk okay so this is the museum and the
library yeah I know high humidity I hate
places with high humidity but Japan
counts to one of those it's really
really rough is so rough
man ta oh I can even place it myself
nice you're welcome
yeah like high humidity will make the
Celsius whatever it is like like 10
hotter like for example if it's 30 it
will feel like 40 in a dry place but
you're in a humid place so you know and
I'm going should I say it I mean I want
to talk about it afterwards I
think I don't think I cannot talk about
it so I'm just going to say
it uh I'm going to
Thailand yay really short trip but wait
let's buy some seeds just a
few drum roll T Brazil no why the [\h__\h]
how much is this again there's no one
here right now 2,000 okay never mind I'm
going I'm going to save up for that
2,000 I'm close I'm
close exciting
W I've never been I always hear about
Thailand
being cheap wait the mine where's the
mine guys where's the
mine mommy says I should go to the
mine uh a cheap destination for nice
vacations like Beach
vacations I think my sister went there
before also for a
vacation the top of the town oh okay
North
nor from the bus
stop and not from here
North TI lesson stream of
people do you think she would do
that do you think she would do
it you have to take a be
boo yeah but the problem is it's like
40 C right now there and you know the
humidity will make it feel like [\h__\h]
50 C kill
me but probably going to not be outside
that much due to
that is this the
mine
railroad let me
in I don't know where's the
mine how much is that a fire night look
it up Google is your friend somebody
tell him how much is it in Fahrenheit
far
height I to the right
oopsie right of the 10 okay okay okay
120 yeah yeah my poor soul yeah yeah
yeah I will be I will
be ashes Phoenix return to
ashes oh this place over there I thought
I couldn't get there oh no I can
the message from the the Amazon
Place am I okay to go in it's so late
too
hello
H yeah they have to sweep me up and put
me in a
bag in a zip looc bag and send me back
to
[Music]
Austria I was just pairing down into
this old M shaft it's been a bner for
decades
still there's probably good ore down
there but a dark place undisturbed for
so long I'm afraid ore isn't the only
thing you'll
find hold now here D this you might need
it what Sal
y let's go cheaper you think they'll
make it they'll make it cheaper just
because I'm ashes I I doubt
it still have to pay same price for one
seat you receive a rusty sword yay it
doesn't look so right to you name's
Marlin by the way I run the adventurous
Guild right outside I'll keep my eye on
you prove yourself and I might think
about making you a member a member a
member to
remember okay but I feel like I
shouldn't go in so late I need to go
home I'll be exhausted
soon oh my chat
died your pickax isn't strong enough
well done
[\h__\h] can I go down here
oh this
sound
nice oh it's just normal
Stones
a Copp
ore yay will I need
this I mean Stones I think I need for
one of
the things one of the packages like I
need like 99 or so
probably might as well just only go out
at night I feel like I think I saw that
even at night it's 40 I think I saw it
in
the in the uh weather
report so
rip
takik I'm still looking forward to it uh
it's going to be a short trip so I'll be
back
before a
week but yeah so you'll have a few more
streams with me
and then I'm going to be dipping I'm
going to go back cuz I'm
scared I'll I'll come back eventually
soon soon
TM try got to try Thai food hell yeah I
hope I find some nons spicy
one I um actually in Cologne I went to a
a Thai Vietnamese restaurant that was
really good and I don't know if the food
I ate was Thai or Vietnamese but I had
oh yeah yeah it seems to be all over sea
I had
the
spooky he's also raging for the trash
just like me just like me for real for
real I had the the chicken saai sa Sati
again with the peanut sauce so good
sorry it's so [\h__\h]
good so good and then I had like a mango
salad that had this one um herb or spice
or so in it that makes it the tastes
like very
different mango with like other salad
stuff what was what is the
herb
coriander is that different in English
coriander chicken sa is so [\h__\h]
good
mhm no not cilantro cilantro wasn't that
something else what the hell
oh no yeah wait that's that is what it
is
oh wait I think coranda was a German
word for and a word in Austria that we
say
differently and I thought it was
different herbs
completely now I'm confused
now I will say I think the salad would
have been better without it but it was
an interesting
taste anyway sounds like those raccoons
are back again filthy
varment you turned up at the right
moment Miss could you do an old man of
favor could you go around the corner and
scare off those raccoons for me they've
been causing a
realness thanks make sure you give him a
good scare well
I I do be an IRL
scarecrow literally made one built after
me
boo it was me I'm
sorry oh it's okay I why do I not get
called a raccoon when I romage for the
trash in the middle of the day I've r a
lot of hot fresh food and newed cans
stuff that will go to waste if I don't
take it
that's good but I feel like that's so
nasty cuz my trash you don't want to
rage through my trash
man I'm so much
like
e ew I recommend you to not rumage from
my trash like the things are mixed like
there's like from cooking you know like
and then and like old food oh God I have
something in my fridge that I keep on
forgetting cuz it's covered in like
aluminum foil
and I keep on forgetting about it and I
really need to a it's probably molding
underneath the boil can someone else get
rid of it
please oh man
help this is something I cooked before
quite a while go
now I'm gonna I'm going to close my eyes
and then
just throw it away off the
stream I will do
it help me science fair project
yeah it's it's it to be creating some
interesting special effects in my
fridge I wear a mask to migr the smell
really
well that also means you have let it go
too
far that's
terrible help me most like
Ira
yeah oh okay so do you think there's
something wrong with what I'm
doing is it illegal I guess it's illegal
because it's like also like people's
private [\h__\h] I don't know but you're
you're throwing it away so are you
giving up your rights of Ownage to the
things in your trash once you throw it
out I guess you're you are right but
then still the act of dumpster diving is
illegal
still so well yeah that's a point of
trash does do you give the rights of
your trash to the city when you this wow
such a legal question when it's in the
trash when once you give it into the big
trash dumpster thing
is depends on the
country good question right I want to
know the
legalities where's my legal
eagle tell me also
congratulations what the [\h__\h] you got
married you snuck in pineapple no
way w p hey really did that fit
well oh my God e congrats what the [\h__\h]
you got
married she the city takes your waist
why not your
trash yeah they take it so I would think
then it belongs to them or is it a like
a gray Zone H
anyway I would
say like I mean
it is disgusting but if you're okay with
that and you are you have no other means
then it's
okay but be careful because like
ah like even if you find some okay food
what like an apple or so like uh you
don't know what that touched inside of
the trash
like so don't ramage from my own trash
don't do it
thank you thanks wa I know you were an
open-minded person I feel good about
what I'm doing I'm not harming
anyone yeah that is
true you can go on home I promise I
won't rumage in George's scan
anymore yeah maybe not his I'll do that
it's my my my territory territory you
can tell him you scared off the raccoons
for good which kind of sounds like I
killed them scary
scary why am I hiding there
now oh [\h__\h] no he got caught wait he's
going to give him actual food though
right it's going to be a wholesome
moment
right I know what you were doing
lenus whome moment if you need food just
ask a I don't want anyone in Pelican
town to go hungry
a hm M sweet here I've got a basket of
zucchini
for with sour cream maybe no spicy
marinara
no now do uh like the um the taiki sauce
I think I would like it with ttii
sauce go and take it oh that oh that's
amazing sheesh maybe I should give all
my hellofresh second servings to someone
else too
cuz sometimes they end up molding in my
fridge okay I really need to go home
it's so
late I haven't been out this late in a
long
[Music]
time
taiki but then you're mixing uh cucumber
with
zucchini the brothers the long lost
Brothers back together in your stomach
isn't that awesome I like the thought of
that
H
titty
titty guys do you think I will get those
flowers again I feel like they're
gone I have to do a proper Furrow
search I guess I'm keeping these things
for now I have to research the G the G
geod and this one I'm keeping too as a
resource I guess I really need that
bigger inventory now I even got a sword
sheesh now respawn
okay sleep good
[Music]
night
whoa oh ah okay I thought it was just
the eggs no it counted the other things
too nice good
money oh the trash actually did not
bring in any money damn
sad understandable I
guess where was the Kik key I need to go
back to bed uh hi there good morning I
noticed that you've been breaking some
rocks open and finding or that's good
are you are you are you going to be
angry at
me if you want to get the most out of
the ores you find you'll need a furnace
okay okay just so happens I had an extra
set of blueprints lying around here I
want you to have them why does everybody
know what I'm doing I
feel
observed learned how to craft a furnace
okay fur fur fur
fur fluffy
fur they're watching me they're watching
the
stream they live in my walls oh just
like
Casper
furnace f f f f
f are you guys part of the town are you
guys in stard you
Valley the furnace allows you to smelt
metal bars the bars can be used for
crafting construction and Tool
upgrades okay when you've smelted a few
copper bars consider having me upgrade
one of your tools
it can make your work a lot easier well
okay I'm heading home take it
easy
relax take it
[Music]
easy relax take
it
relax take itow
[Music]
relax say hi to the
chicken a a hi a
a my
babies nice okay here and here Fresh
Hair there you go enjoy your day inside
sometimes you just want to stay inside
on on a rainy day very understandable we
don't want to get your fluffy fluffy
feathers too
wet yeah although I do think they're
kind of protecting you from getting too
wet all right actually I guess I can
leave my some of my tools like for
example the like the hole when I'm going
somewhere and maybe even the side what
do you think oopsie not this I just want
to put it in different oh yeah and then
the watering can as well right and if I
don't have plans on fishing I can leave
the fishing pole at Rod yeah fishing rod
that's the word what was that
sound someone's burping or uh
farting so much money oh I can almost
afford the bag let's
go feeding animals okay I need to still
do that reach level five in the mines C
craft the furnace what about the silo
furnace where's a
silo I don't see I don't see Silo
guys do I still need
the I need to visit Robin who's Robin
again
guys close on Tuesday
[\h__\h] ah is that is that what I need
oo D
deal wait I think I have what I
need the very first red head okay a red
head I'll be looking out for a red head
oopsie the carpenter in the mountains ah
I think we need this and this
and
[\h__\h] I didn't keep the other flower
either
okay
yeah yeah I'm missing that other flower
the the flower uh that has more flowers
to
it a damn it maybe maybe something's up
there also in my own field that like
this looks like a flower but not the one
that I
need and there's stones and stuff
nah a
frog M I don't know too lazy for that
it's not even the red flower I think you
can drop them off individually oh okay
then I wouldn't forget about it okay
let's do that then I don't accidentally
get rid of
[Music]
them
okay then let's bring
the
parsnip H they need the parsnip too
thought those four things the the wild
horseradish the the leak the daffodil
and another
flower par it for a future oh okay
okay
mhmm yeah hopefully we'll find something
on the way just one more of those
flowers I think it was the the flower
that had like several
colors whatever that was uh not a
daffodil it was
[Music]
a uh the funny name right the funny
one there's a little button on the top
right menu you think you can check the
buttons from there ah a dandelion yeah
yeah yeah yeah dandelion dandelion it
probably is dandelion and you guys are
just like trying to confuse
me sassy
buckers okay Apple guy I'm back you
don't need to run away I'm not that
scary please wait
no God damn it
it
oh
yay
woohoo
parsnip
parsnip bar snip Stone oh but the not
enough mm Oh you mean future as in like
after oh this is not even all of them
okay well well well well well well well
well so we're looking for a flower and
we're going to go to the mine as
well but H flower
flower where is the flower of the hour
oh wait let me
ask I need to write a message really
quickly
okay I sent the message we're good we're
good we're good
um also by the way I was originally
wanting to play the ollie game again
today again I I was planning on it but
uh the patch apparently is still not
done the English patch so OE told me to
wait a bit more so I'm like waiting
waiting waiting and then this was like
my backup
idea maybe maybe the day after
tomorrow hopefully because I you know I
just finished a big long RPG game so I
kind of just want
to you
know play some smaller oneoff games
right now and that would be a perfect
one
yo but
I can't play it yet I mean I could but
Ollie says I should wait so I
wait I'm back at my place didn't find
the
flower maybe down
[Music]
here is there a place where it spawns
more what this
H take
it why can I not take
it
uh spooky
sounds the bunny Garden no I'm not
really interested in the bunny Garden
one um I don't know it's funny and all
but like I don't see what's the
point like I don't know just looking at
girls um panties
and sorry guys I'm not
really interested in that at the moment
the panties and the big
bubble I I I really don't see the
point I I
mean like I don't
know I'm I'm sure it's funny but at the
moment I don't feel
very
uh interested
yeah it's just horny
game I mean maybe an fotm game then I I
should play more fotm games oh another
geod let's just go to the geod guy
wait now can I sell them now cuz I
already put them in the
thing oh oh maybe not the maybe not the
par snip the other thing you agree it's
fine no hor you just want to be happy
yeah not the part okay yeah I feel like
the other uh popular game right now is
surprisingly Buckshot
roulette I see a couple of people
playing that
one I'm not exactly sure what it is what
kind of game it
is it looks
coolish it's kind of dark
looking rational roulette with a shotgun
it reminds me of the like other like
little shotgun chest game that we played
but not really just because of the
shotgun
the raindrops are really loud on the
metal roof of our trailer oh I can
imagine oh
man a tricky game but I'm not a fan if
you played it once it's
done Stella yeah I want to okay okay
okay so Cellar Blade's also kind of
horny game but it's more than just that
I want to play Cellar
blade it's like near
automata kind of all over again
oh wait yeah wait wait wait wait wait
wait
wait Sony game rip is that a reason to
rip it R it really ah [\h__\h] no I'm a
little bit too late ah man why you do
this to me give me some flowers at least
come
on oopsie oh ramage for your
trash yeah I watched a little bit bit of
gamep
play and it looked pretty good looked
pretty
smooth and uh shiny butts and with this
I'm
okay in this kind of scenario I'm okay
with it oh another flower but the wrong
one it looks a a little bit difficult
though I I've
seen someone
struggle a little bit with it so maybe
the difficulty is a little bit High have
you guys tried
it I've heard it hard yeah yeah that's
what I've
seen you can play on E yeah I think I
would probably like
seeing how it is pretty difficult
apparently PS5 exclusive so is that your
answer to me asking have you guys played
it and your answer is just uh it's a PS5
exclusive
cuz you don't have
one that's too bad so I'm just running
around because I want that one flower
but okay let's uh it's not too late then
maybe I'll
go uh check out the
mines if I find them
again one more time time going to go
mining are there perms R yeah I don't
really
know I need to check that out I'm
curious too wait have I passed the mines
it's not here huh or is it oh it is it
is it
is let's go is there a flower here by
the
way what's this place ah you're the the
weapon guy
okay on the bridge is broken here
okay who whoa whoa what's this weird
sound freaks me
[Music]
out okay I'll give it a try with the
perms you never should give up right
away just because you think it might be
impossible we never
know so under one of these Stones is
always the ladder to go down huh looks
like this one no in the the first run I
I got it like almost first
try there it is though found
it AOE I would totally play AOE more if
it wasn't like if I could play it
spontaneously I hate planting ahead and
it's like you know 3 days ahead but like
weekday
so full full working day
is it's so
annoying like even if I ask on on Friday
to play it on Tuesday it's not enough
wait how do I go
down oh there we
go undertale undertale is one of those
games that I told myself I'm going to
play it one day
probably and today is not the day
tomorrow is also not the day but one of
those
days I'm not opposed to
it Super Mario Galaxy didn't I already
play that or what was it the other one
what's the other
one oo
fancy quartz let's
go yeah I know I've heard about the
community I know it comes with a lot of
uh yeah oh Earth crystal don't I already
have this
one I've heard it comes with a lot of
back seating and stuff I mean well it is
what it
is my brain has managed to be very very
selective oh yeah Odyssey oh so I played
Odyssey and gal galaxy is the other
one yeah I know it's a good
one I
know uh okay I guess we have to fight
the first time in this game oh he
doesn't care for me
I don't want to get too close but okay
it was a one hit oh oh and it reveals
the E it revealed the
[Music]
ladder I did
it I just mashed my
uh my my my
thing uh oopsie
it's kind of dark in here that's a
problem oh I'm falling asleep no no wait
no I have to get earlier to the
mines God damn it okay I'm going back y
can we make it I think we can make it
time passes so
fast Paper Mario in a few weeks oh is
the new one coming out in a few weeks
now E I feel like a already came out I
guess it didn't wait what didn't it
already come
out
order the Remake
yeah the
Remake and was there another release of
a new one or am I mixing up
things I think I'm mixing
up that's just this one right
yeah yeah the remake of a Thousand-Year
Door H should I play
it I don't think I've played a paper
Mario game ever
before 1:30
a.m.
Cinderella faster
y okay I made it today we stayed up
really late
wow super myy was paper Mark zero kind
of a pretty close a yeah it's just the
the visuals are kind of different though
right can we afford it
yet come
on day 10 of
spring C to you too so close I'm just
going to go uh fish a fish cat it's the
cat that I like so
much according to the game hi M can I
have this
cat you see this cat here yeah can I are
you giving it to
me I found it sitting outside the
entrance to your farm I think it's a
stray poor little
thing my little Garfield yeah I think it
likes this place h H don't you think
it's this Farm could use a a good cat of
course I will adopt it but then I need
to give it food too right
Misa uh no I mean I could name it one of
my cats or we're just going to do
Garfield
oopsie orange cat behavior let's
go chunky
wonky well Garfield you be a good kitty
now okay
they gave me the one I chose what a
coincidence
nice mommy is back seating me telling me
there's a shorter path to go
home okay good morning uh egg production
Farm oops sorry almost hit you don't
worry don't worry where what one
go I he you are are you playing hide and
seek with
me y he's so cute baby
boy okay here we
go uh ah wait I need to water my crops
need to get
my need to get my thing out here
watering can
ah oh I F again I fought I accidentally
picked
them well no they're ready again what
what what I don't even remember putting
anything there oh the cauliflower
flowers is getting
there and these look ready too ooh let's
go M I need more seeds but I'm I'm so
close I'm so close to great
and so should I keep all my parsnips do
I need like several of them to make a
golden one or something like
that yeah we can totally get the
[Music]
backpack tell me tell
me isn't it close ah come
on that sucks goldens are
picked oh okay so I don't need the
normal
ones one part of any quality and five
okay okay so these ones I think I can
sell cuz I think I have one in
here mhm and is there no cooking don't I
need these for cooking eventually I
guess don't I can grow new ones anyway
okay
then if the shop is
closed then I will just go to the mine
right
away are you with me guys let's go maybe
on the way we can keep an eye out
for
um
flowers keep one potato [\h__\h]
I
didn't level five I'm on my
way but it looked we were like I think
at at level uh three or so it already
looked
pretty
[Music]
spoopy not going to yeah no I I'll break
the geod when whenever I can just bring
them all in a stack I
thought do I always want to like mine
every single one of these or should I
just move on once I have
the the
stairs there they
are I can find food when I'm down there
like what
worms and bugs and
spiders just move on
mind the fancy look oh Gio was that a
fancy looking one which ones are
fancy so I think it you guys want me to
play The Paper Mario
RPG I'll think about
it
wooho f
Yoo oh okay this one again was hiding
the
path what is there he there's another
one which one should I take do they lead
to
different variations of the next
level
[Music]
H same outcome oh okay
oh always this one do I need several of
them why is my e meter so low do I need
to
eat or
exhausted what already can I eat this
and then feel
better I think so
how do I
ah uh it went up only a tiny
bit I'm not going to get really far with
this
huh slime we got some slime let's go oh
wait what the [\h__\h]
I was poisoned he hit
[Music]
me fighting feels kind of weird cuz it's
hard to move while you're
fighting uh
open oh just some wood I thought there
would be treasure in
there y I'm going to die give me
this h
moving on seems kind of difficult I I
kind of need to bring more food
then yeah I'm so oh God I think I got to
go depends on the luck for that day
oh I got to go so much for moving on to
the next level
maybe if I don't do like gardening in
the morning then I'll have more energy
at that point but uh I got to do the
gardening in the
[Music]
morning thank you for the membership
pool appreciate
it spring onions M I like spring onions
e this looks different from
oh it was just leak okay okay okay I may
have no energy but can I please find the
freaking flower that I
want I'm I'm going
the the uh far path because I want to
find the flowers
somewhere n NY
[Music]
yeah I can craft some foods H try the
lake
area is it in specific areas that
flower go south left in the
forest which Forest the witch
Forest do you mean the witch
Forest which
Forest so yeah the wizard Forest so it's
kind of the witch Forest
[Music]
okay uh what did you say
South there it
is is it always
here wait no space um might as well eat
this
uh
yum that helped me a little bit I got it
okay that means that means I can go to
that place again
come with me
kfp first bundle complete
yay
exciting what do I get do I get
something wait I don't want to throw it
away I just want to um can I like touch
there we go
snack give me
snack that would have helped in the in
the mine I guess I'll keep it I'll put
it in my storage and then when I'm
really serious about the mine again I
can take both of those
sck love your overalls thank you aren't
they so
cute
oh
[\h__\h] wait what did I oh thank God I at
least didn't give you the what did I
give her the no at least I didn't give
her the flower I just wanted to talk to
her I didn't give her the snack and I
didn't give her the flour the copper
okay
H oh
well we'll find more of it right
right
goodbye it was even a special one that
could have sold quite
well oh yay W reward spring seeds
assortment of wild spring seeds thank
you 30 of them let's go but if I do all
of them it repairs one bridge I feel
like I've seen several Broken Bridges or
do all of them get
fixed
now besides that I don't think I can do
any of these besides
the this one in Fury I can probably work
on this hard
hardwood hard wait he's going
somewhere oh
oh I can do them according to
Seasons what's
this aha this is where it continues oh
this is I'm growing all of
this oh and here's a speci speci ones
the five golden ah corn corn
corn
M
mhm shees
eggs okay if I have like some non-star
eggs then I'll bring
him
oh there he
goes where where is he taking them why
is he taking my things and what is this
another new
thing the fish tank ah I already gave my
son fish that's whoops that's going to
be a lot of
work
ah ooh oh maybe with a better fishing
rod corn I love corn I want to eat some
corn corn every day please okay but
we're done with the flowers so and we
have some seeds so we can improve our
farm and then tomorrow will buy the the
the bigger backpack
and maybe maybe we'll give the mine
another try another
attempt sounds like a
plan oh but we're already getting to 4
hours holy [\h__\h] the time goes by
fast I know you can like stream this as
a like really long streaming game I was
like how long should I stream this today
and I checked the other girl streams on
this and like some streamed it for two
for three hours some streamed it for
seven or eight hours wow
well I don't want to go too long cuz I
need to read super chats that's my
problem uh
um so I'll probably just uh do one more
day or so hi oh sorry I love you do you
not need food
he's so cute my Garfield
cat it's one of those
games pickaxe proficiency and Cherry
Bomb oo so I can blow up something
big okay so we definitely have the money
now yeah narissa I know she loves the
game too she played it a lot Cali too
know like a lot of them oh wait the TV
by the way ah Fortune Del
welcome back to wildes Oracle if you
seek kind the knowledge of the future
well you've come to the right place the
spirits feel neutral today the day is in
your hands oh okay on Lucky days I might
get something out of the treasure
chest welcome to living off the land
we're back again with another tip for
you all now listen up woes from crows
sounds like you need a scarecrow already
have
one need a bigger backpack to hold and
don't worry about
it welcome to close of five you're
number one source for Revenue
entertainment and now the weather
forecast for tomorrow it's going to be a
beautiful sunny day tomorrow not hold
hold for tomorrow let me plant all my
beautiful beautiful seeds that I have
now I wonder what they are they're
random
right they look like little beans should
I make more Fields
now I think I should
I'm farming
[Music]
Yeehaw
oh okay
skill
issue mom mommy tells me to get
oh mommy's like really stressed telling
me that there's a spring festival in 2
days and I need to get strawberries well
maybe one of these is a
strawberry who knows ah oh no it no this
one I really didn't pluck I think I
destroyed that one [\h__\h] it it was just a
bar snip
right whatever you're missing one tile
oh
[\h__\h] I think it just disappeared that
was not
me and now I'm missing yeah one freaking
space whatever I'm putting it away
[Music]
I hear C where is
Kato mommy says don't are you saying
don't buy the the inventory upgrade
don't buy the backpack is that what
you're saying mommy are you crazy I
saved up for
it wait free
eggs wait oh oh are they from yesterday
did I forget to pick up the
eggs what's going
on why
ah build a
silo oh oh yeah she says don't buy the
backpack now I'm going to make a lot of
money with the
strawberries hey are they going to even
be ready in time cuz if it's only 2 days
left
[Music]
then I will water them in a
moment she's right
huh I didn't I patted you I patted you I
feel like I did
anyway let's sell this and no I want I
want to I want to keep one of each
because they're not
so yeah these ones are not so special so
I can bring them to the uh thing
whatever that
is there's a cat there it is pooping in
the woods oh
flower freaking dandelion oh it's an
expensive one
thank you JC wolf thank you so
much
oh
flower yeah yeah yeah okay uh what are
we doing oh
[Music]
yeah the month has 28 days yeah but you
said the 13th and now it says it's the
11th I fought in two days
HH okay so I need strawberry plant
seeds do you have
some no why do I get them oh wait wait
uh no just as apricot orange Peach
pomegranate pom
Apple do I get them somewhere else oh oh
they're sold at the Fest
Festival on the egg Festival it's where
I get the
strawberries okay with noal money or
with eggs why is it called egg
Festival okay now I understand I thought
I was selling strawberries in two
days wait then let's do the geod let's
go get my geodes and uh gotcha
a oh it's just
Easter well my leg is
so numb I've become so numb I can't feel
my leg cuz I'm sitting on it it's all my
fault uh geot I already have four
geot anything else
no that's he's sleeping why you staying
over
there oh ah wasn't this filled with
water
before did was that is that your place
and you drank the water
already oh the water water the C okay
okay
okay oh a
book I heard a little book
why are you so close to the gate are you
thinking about
escaping there's no
use forget about
it to
tomorrow will either be a member stream
or something else maybe this game again
or I don't even know it's good that I
don't have a schedule this week because
I don't know what the hell to
do I don't know I'm so lost kind of
deciding when I wake up I hope that's
okay
guys
yeah thank you oh my God already out out
of water holy [\h__\h] I need
sprinklers I mean I misclicked maybe
once but that's
it chat died again holy moly YouTube fix
your chat problem it's been going on
for two fre weeks
now what you doing what you working on
stop changing the layout of YouTube that
we're happy with and used to that needs
no changing and fix the issues instead
of creating new ones and it's not that
difficult preach it w
uhhuh thank
you I am saying what you guys are
thinking because I am the voice of the
[Applause]
people I do it for you I'm one of
you we share one heart one
Soul got to do some
socializing you want to you want Pierre
to cook for dinner tonight what are you
sick of cooking for him all the time I
been Bing cookies F you said that before
ah Grandpa Grandma is so forgettable for
forget for forget the eh forgettable
sounds like an insult forgetful
forgetful sorry
Grandma I mean you forget about things
then maybe someone will forget about you
too so so I don't know maybe no never
mind I'll never forget you wait it's
closed I'm I'm on the I'm
they closed the doors right in front of
me and they were laughing in my face
when they were closing it did you
see I certainly
saw man
[Music]
okay I I I'm I'm I'm [\h__\h] I'm gonna go
fish
maybe I don't
know
man
[Music]
man man so lazy not even one minute
longer where's my cat where' my cat go
maybe inside
oh wait I have a little cave over here
hey
yo
he what else just exploring now so much
for
fishing aha mommy says to fish in My
Little
Pond
interesting mommy's a back better
backseater than you
guys what are you guys doing H what are
you guys adding to this stream
huh let get
this
yeah I'm going to fish some fish fishes
Fritz fish fish Fisher no not quite
fishes Fritz F no fishes Fritz fish F
Fisher there we go German tongue twister
it's about uh a Fisher called Fritz
who's fishing fresh fish I mean you
could probably make the same one in
English do you guys have the same one in
English fishes FRS fishes fresh fish
that's a a little bit
[Music]
different
cin
cin give me some
cin it that is a DA col is it empty
probably
[Music]
oops it's a
seashell sea seashell German
equivalent fish of fruits fishes fres
fish
yeah o o o I'm not getting any money for
that it's already getting dark why are
the days so short h
does it oh I wonder if it gets like
darker later in summer in this game did
they think about
that ah where are the
carps free smart fellow they felt smart
free free smart fellows they smell
what I see I see where you're going with
this
one first I thought oh that's not even
that difficult but damn it gets more
difficult the more often I say
it I didn't say the whole thing broken
glasses am I getting skill uh
improvements even
when I'm fishing
trash I don't think there's any carp in
here oh different
one oh this is the wrong
one in the South where the dude was the
dude damn I sometimes think this is a
person that is the trash
Lake what about that one this one the
river by the chickens let me test it out
[Music]
yeah I don't think you can fish
here okay I guess can you not fish in a
river I guess because of the the
current oh I went too far
ah Rin here I know there's a lot of
stones scattered around your farm if you
have a surplus you might consider having
me build a well for you oh Wells can be
replaced can be placed all over your
farm and serve as convenient places to
refill your watering can to ring by my
shop with 75 stones and 1,000
gr 1,000 G of what oh
gold
gold well I think I first need to use
all my money for the strawberries
dude wait is there another
one missing I lost my favorite axe if
you find it please return ASAP also
Ramen by the way I'm having a tough time
finding it there's 250 gold in it for
whoever finds the thing m
m is it a better axe maybe we can
switch small boy cat curled up in the
[Music]
bowl oh wait I didn't sell everything
[\h__\h] I forgot I forgot to sell my
trash mommy says I don't need the the
well because I'll get a sprinkler
eventually and then I don't need the
well
anymore oh you can drink this oh it also
gives you
speed oh maybe I'll keep
it this one this stuff I'll
[Music]
sell I think I'll keep that okay let's
go to the geode
place and bring the
eggs just so that I have this done
before everything's
closed
right the trash is useful when I get a
recycling machine
a too
late K needs water ah I'm so
sorry
[Music]
no no don't starve or
dehydrate there you go
oh it has to be a large
one oh they gave me tiny ass
eggs [\h__\h] then I'm selling
them oh wait I need to greet my my
[Music]
chickens hello good morning
chicklets where where are you here you
cannot hide from me no no
no you want me to catch you don't you oh
that's that one's a big
one I saw this the sparkly ones are the
big
ones uh I think
so cute aren't you cute aren't you so
cute so I'll keep this one I
guess you need to cab a on this
game I'll keep it
um well
B okay oh wait look
woohoo this time I didn't destroy it
let's
[Music]
go wait I can I oh I got some
beans I was just say uh I made a a
discovery I can water both rows when I'm
in between
them
efficient minmaxed
gardening
oops running out the
water a papa
I don't know when to
stop I said I wouldn't do much longer
and since then 15 minutes have
passed so is the life of a
Takashi ah
okay uh looks watered looks watered wait
I have space for the last
seed and going to
keep wait a minute I have to give one to
the museum one of these or five of these
oh five golden ones or five normal ones
middle row not watered are you sure I
did I remember maybe the right side no I
think I did
both you cat me out when I me
out I love I love the
cat I did both yeah I did both one
normal and five golden ones okay so I
can sell wait didn't I already give the
normal one there
anyway ah Mommy gave me good advice if
it's for the community center this thing
will be like blink blink blink
blinkink blink this is where I need to
look uh oh can
I oh HH
oh I cannot it looks like I could place
it from here from home but I guess I
have to go there
actually
[Music]
okay so I still uh
need one of these so I can sell these no
no sell these plant this get to the jeld
guy def I don't need any more I'm
keeping it for
presents no oh [\h__\h] uh
here okay ah
water
okay wow I'm so organized we have mail
you've got mail tomorrow we're holding
the egg Festival in the Town Square you
should arrive between 9:00 a.m. 2: p.m.
if you'd like to attend you wouldn't
want to miss an anal Eon x x x so I
think I'll do that and then I'll
uh end it for today and read super
chats wait do I have all my geod
yeah hi Square wall we we go Zoom oh we
go up the
tree W let me visit your treeh
house let me check it out I want to have
a treeh house too can I live with
you I I don't think I've ever been
inside a treeh house is are tree houses
actually that common in America as like
how I see in movies and
stuff tell
me please don't K again not planning on
it no not really I had when as a kid but
I'm European
oh they used to
be probably for the middle class
families
[Music]
copper and the Earth
thing
copper oh something
new thank you that's
special can we bring one of these is to
the
museum
donate oh yeah donate
the donate
the
okay hi
kids how's it
going Miss Penny says I have to read
this book before I can go
play if you're taking the dirt you can
find some interesting
things but I need a shovel I don't know
you uh
well you always don't know someone at
first the people you know there were
times where you didn't know
them
flower I want my own Treehouse too
yeserday is an adult you can totally
like make something really cool as an
adult out of a treehouse especially if
you're like talented with like handyman
skills make like a like build build like
a a cool dude get together kind of place
with a Billard table and and like beer
and I don't
know uh what else should I do oh
hi you care be Farm is going very well
thank
you good luck getting a build well you
got to build it inside you don't bring
it up there you don't build it outside
and bring it up you build it in there
from scratch from you know like in a
cave from scratch
scraps a man cave but in the trees
exactly doesn't that sound
amazing but I'd like a girl cave
what's a girl cave consist of you
ask depends on the
age I
[Music]
suppose May what what could
it
[Music]
uh depends on your hobbies if I was a
reader I guess like
books but I'm not a reader
actually I don't know what I would put
there nothing specifically girly just
uh I won't destroy your
tent just yeah cats and a
TV a cozy phon
I don't know what would I put there
snacks obviously girly
snacks yeah for girl
dinner I don't know what to do right now
cuz I'm just waiting for the thing uh
maybe I can build something
interesting I the furnace I think uh 20
copper ore
[Music]
ooh ah not quite there yet I have 12
I make a sign basic
[Music]
fertilizer torch will be nice eventually
to light up everything
maybe oh I can make my own wild
seeds and then what will come out just
anything I don't know could go mining
but it's already so late my energy is
like man I'm not going to get really
[Music]
far not going to get really
far unless I bring some
snackles
yeah I guess I'll do
that level fishing skill yeah I want to
do that
too yeah but now now already decided I'm
going to to go to the mins of
[Music]
morio we're taking to hbit to Eisen
guard taking The Hobbit to Eisen guard
taking the Hobbits to Eisen guard guard
guard guard Guard we're taking The
Hobbit to ien guard taking The Hobbit to
aard taking The Hobbit to are you guard
guard guard guard
guard oh
lucky oh I didn't maybe I wonder is
today my neutral day or did I check
that the other day was I neutral
yesterday and I don't know what I am
today guess we'll never
know open up I got wood so I don't think
I'm particularly lucky
today so I guess every time I mine a
stone I lose energy right so I might not
want to really mine every single one of
these got to make the smart choices if I
don't mine everything then I might get a
lot
further use a sword on the crates ah
okay the sword
copper copper is welcome right
now music is chill down
here no
enemies oh one up there little blob
little slime it reminds me of
Riser out here
Risa green alga and some
slime this is fancy and now we break
oh I'm already full inventory then I
guess let's eat one of the snacks or two
of
them um then oh did that raise my
energy yeah a little bit
okay K SE I didn't have K before you
played 200 hours in this game you all of
you guys are crazy with this game
huh okay moving on oh I've never been
this this far down before let's
go n n n
n speed buff gone oh what's
this I
mean I'm not full energy so might as
well
eat yum yum
yum and another another
[Music]
one okay and what is this small glow
ring emits a small constant light can I
wear it though like why oh yes I
can let's go that's cool I get an
elevator point at every fifth level cool
cool
[Music]
um is this something I can open
can't touch
this it did and touch
me e don't fart at me so green your
farts are so green what the [\h__\h] where
are the
stairs do I have to mine to find them
cuz I don't see
them all
right [\h__\h] it's going to take up all my
energy but they're random right they're
like is it like a randomized thing or is
there a guy that tells you where it
is feel like they're random every time
you never know ah
yes level five
woohoo uh
wait oh now you're telling me to reach
40 well did I get a reward for reaching
level five though
dude okay it's 910 p.m. getting late oh
it's a little crap yeah y y y y y y I
don't know how to fight you okay is this
a hermit crab but it has a stone are you
really a hermit crab you call this
something else it's losing so many legs
e
oh nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice nice nice nice kill the Slime kill
the booger out of my nose no no no no
yeah
oh is that a tree
St I guess I could eat the leak or leave
something behind like the wood I can get
endless
wood elsewhere and the geod I want to
take the geode with
me maybe leave the coal behind although
I don't need the sap do
I eat the
algae wait wait [\h__\h] uh how do can I eat
it like from
here uh yeah let's trash the the sap
okay and let's eat the
algae okay oh I'm that that's crunchy
ooh didn't look so
crunchy where are the stairs let's go
further down although I don't think
we'll get to level 40 need to bring a
lot of food for that
oh throw it on the floor again if you
want and then pick it up how do I I
tried to click outside of the
inventory I couldn't get
there
ooh no Enemy No
stare you have to do everything
yourself
GE get all
it's okay I still have some leak if I
run out of energy but it's getting late
it's almost 12:00
p.m. I got to go Cinderella
time e this is so difficult like what
happens at 2: a.m. do I just uh get
teleported back or do I fall asleep here
and then get
some um
no oh
finally hey should I go
back that should have dropped it I'll
try again
sometime you die in real life go back
hurry
back okay you have to uninstall the
game oh but now I can go directly to
level five right with the elevator I
love the Ring The Ring was a nice
find cuz now I can see where I'm
going and see what's around
me very good find must have been pretty
rare right the ring is huge woohoo no
the ring is Tiny though what are you
talking
about does that look huge to you it says
small not huge glow ring Mr Donald Trump
small
no matter how many times you call that
thing huge it's still small small small
smaller smaller
peee sick
burn sick
burn uh 185 Stones how many stones do I
need got him real good he's going to cry
like a little baby
it's it Festival
[Music]
time what was that I think is it
Festival time oh Mommy says you just
fall asleep and wake up and pay some
money K get
[Music]
key is he Festival
time I see you've been exploring the old
man you've got the adventure spirit that
much I can tell if you can slay 10
slimes have earned your place in the
adventur skill oh okay that's not so
difficult
mhm Festival day okay we'll get the
festival behind us and
[Music]
then we'll call it a day or
night uh
ah wait
see I'm doing both rows so don't one guy
me you got to look closely at what the
WWA is
doing
okay water for the cattle
w got one guide again a few times
today but it's okay I figured it
out hello
chicken good morning come here well look
where's the other
one I can hear you but I can't see see
you are you
inside no where are you
Jimmy stop
hiding wait this egg looks small oh it's
just normal egg oh so there is small egg
egg and large
egg free stages or H did
I Goldie ah dare you are
me why are they so cute [\h__\h] they have
have like such a perfect
friendship but it's like kind of like a
half of a heart shape so if you put two
chickens
together you know what I mean they they
become one heart you know what I mean
their shape look at that it looks like
one half of a heart you know like those
friendship or couple uh
necklaces with a broken heart they they
have that shape kind of and you put them
together with another one
m a large egg egg no wait this one these
ones I
sell new merch
idea I don't know how that's going to
work the chicken necklace you guys can
share with another kfp member wait I was
going to finish
watering as actually thinking when I was
traveling because I saw it in the shops
we already did a luggage tag but you
know what I didn't do and I really
regretted that I didn't do it together
with the luggage
tag a passport
case cuz I actually never I travel so
much but I never in my whole
lifetime uh got myself a a passport
case we could have put a cute design on
this that but together with the luggage
tag so mommy is stressing me is it like
ending soon or
what hey
wow where are the strawberries you have
the strawberries
yes I'll just
buy all of them or do I oh there there
goes my
money okay I'm done Festival is over for
me all the okay go broke okay go broke
or go
home easy cute wait can I
go
almost
[Music]
ah
perfect I became the easa bunny
screenshot he also wearing an overall
cute
okay I'll just talk to everybody AB
always Lov the egg hunt ever since she
was a tiny
girl spring is a busy time of the year
so it's nice to have a day off to catch
up with friends egg what a strange thing
to eat excuse me you're strange I put
something nice into the punch she spiked
the
punch [\h__\h] there's kids here I hope
everyone's enjoying the food I've been
cooking for days to get everything ready
fried eggs boiled eggs poached eggs
deved eggs scrambled eggs chocolate eggs
you name it I don't think I've ever had
deviled eggs
before get buzzed on Easter these events
are good time to get conversation yeah
right I was thinking so too cuz
everybody's in one place vincon loves
this Festival it's a joy to see him so
happy I've an ups and St coloring eggs
it's always my favorite part of the
Season yeah I did that too on stream
before Easter egg painting stream
IRL this fruit punch is unusually good
um don't give it to the kids
taking breaks from work can make you
more productive in the long
run welcome to the egg Festival
compliments of my wonderful brood of
hands uh uh I would say my hands are
more wonderful than yours do you think
everyone's ready for the egg hunt uh am
I
[Music]
yes
uh is it easy yby or I'm joining with
the kids I feel bad or are they all
joining it's time for the highlight of
today's festivities the annual spring
egg
hunt bounce calm down now kidos you're
going to need all of your energy if you
hope to find the most eggs and take home
their elus your
prise oh Mommy says I will lose she
doesn't believe in me do you guys
believe in
me now is everyone
ready woohoo and now you're jumping let
the eggo begin oh uh uh well uh I'm a
professional egg hunter then they're
really slow you I guess you could take
one of those like speed up
thingies how
how how do I know will it like will my
mouse
change and how far is the region
anywhere I guess oh wait I see
one did she just pick it up
automatically I see another one and
another
one I think I picked it up myself with
the
mouse or no not sure another one another
one another
one another one maybe I'm not so bad see
one in the
truck over there I don't think so you
probably can't go there right ah sh yeah
oh wait there's another one there I
think it was pretty good I passed by too
what I want to go
again egg egg W look at all these eggs
now if only I could get you kids to pick
up lit suff would have cleanest town
this side of the green gem
what and now the window of this second
is
me [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
Abigail stupid sussy
kid she's cute
though how did she doing she was
cheating she probably had some helpers
she probably had some eggs like already
in her dress hidden
somewhere from
home
cheetah he's surprised to have a g en
Joy also I'm new to this town she knows
all the places better than me we're
that's it for this no not already over
no that's fun though I want to try
again we have egg hunt at home egg hunt
at home in VR chat
O Okay so I have like one month
apparently my mom said I don't know how
that correlates I don't
know okay mommy says plant them
now I
will uh uh uh
here then I need more Fields though
more fields to hoe more fields for more
dough the dough being the
money
she thank you guys thank you so much
stupid tree Susy tree maybe I don't need
all that space anyway we'll
see
mhm
well okay a little bit unsatisfying but
okay we still have to put the water
I can chop the tree yeah I will
eventually
but the beans man I can't go past the
beans they got some beef with me those
beans oh [\h__\h] my
energy what if I can't water them
all is my energy just right
see it's like look when it does
this oh okay it's so
over wait I can still water but now I'm
going run out of
water
yeah I'm going to get water but I'm so
slow I'll eat something yeah but it's
almost 2: a.m. what's going to happen to
the
strawberries I guess
but is it I'm not
[Music]
uh okay I can make it I can make it I
can make it play some Europe beat
[Music]
music oh God 20 oh I don't want to lose
money I don't want to lose money I don't
want to lose money I don't have I
actually I don't have money so it would
be okay to lose the money that I don't
have I made
it no no
no mommy says I lose
money
really I
died
oh did I lose money
that is a right of passage what's that
mean I start with less energy what the
[\h__\h] well good day to end it I can just
end it here right cuz it saves every
[Music]
day no energy reg what the [\h__\h] well it
sounds like a rainy day
so I think rainy day is a good day to
stay
inside
GG no no need to water anything
perfectly
calculated
totally what a way to end it by
dying who would have
F who would have fought
guys
nice let's go to my
office it's been a
while it's been a while I guess I can
stop advertising the froggy waa merch
merchandise because it's gone have you
guys all
gotten your froggy W merchandise thank
you so
much thank you really thank you
indeed
okay not quite my usual office attire
but so cute oh my God the overalls work
so good I need more overalls I need more
overalls I need more different kind of
overalls they actually like move so
well looks cute I want more please and
maybe an apron maybe a cute mate apron I
got the full frog said thank
[Music]
you yeah super groupies is also still on
sale I know it's very expensive but I
have to advertise it
so um if you want something from the
super groupies collab and go get it oh
the EUR truck simulator uhhuh didn't I
stop like Midway
through as I
recall so thank you guys for watching so
far we're probably going to play it
again sometime feel free to come by
again and now we're going to Super
Chat or read the super
chats hold
lier you don't want to talk about
it why does make you feel bad that you
spent so much money I'm sorry oh I
skipped that one okay so you want me to
read that one first before I finish the
other
one I mean feel like I want to finish
the other one first where which one was
that it was I think the like a dragon
infinite weal part
eight and I
stopped oh no maybe it wasn't
this
no no maybe not ah
[\h__\h] you're going to go into a little
depth no please don't do something like
that that would be not
smart bgm please keep on on goinging so
I don't have to put on my own
bgm hello damn it I have to put on my
own
bgm
or we play it oh there a NOP NOP no it
looks so cool though okay as long as you
really want it then
okay then I think if you really want it
then you should get it but yeah I know I
know I I I'm aware that yeah lot of
opportunities to spend your money at the
moment it do be like that see let
me find a good
track this is nice I like
this I barely Dr water like I always
prepare like a huge jug these days I I
barely make use of
[Music]
it saving up for school that is a smart
choice to
make oh yeah if you do want to get this
kind of merch from the super groupy
collab go to the Japan shop convert rate
is so low what the
[Music]
H tomorrow should be kimar 1 million do
we get that a capella version yes you
will yeah yeah yeah okay wait that's
actually perfect then I can upload on
one of the day those days where I'm
gone that actually is
exactly perfectly timed oh yeah good
night mommy sleep
well mommy is done back seating for the
day and now sh
sleep maybe it was this one part
whatever no maybe not okay well I'm just
going to read the EUR truck ones then
H all
[Music]
right your truck
simulator there we
go good stream
you guys liked it so much even got a lot
of va views
so I might play it again sometime
soon it's like $200 cheaper than the
full set for the full set wow 200
sheesh don't say that too loud cuz some
people probably spent those extra 200
and that's really [\h__\h] painful oh man
H it was a great idea oh but this is the
one without the singing
no this is the no singing one that also
got a lot of va views I mean the other
couldn't get VA views because it was uh
gone I'm the one who saying it out loud
well yeah I'm just say you know I'm
trying to give the people who didn't buy
it yet the advice so they don't you know
spend too much but then I feel bad for
the ones who did buy it
no singing Only Trucking M eight D for
the pinky hey T yesterday I got one of
the vice shs and B boxes ooh I got maa's
signed card but then I realized the
special pack actually has two cards in
it your stained glass foil card was
behind MAA just like an
eclipse
oh
sheesh also if they send you a box it
would make for fun short of you opening
one up yeah you know those kind of
things I don't think I can really do it
because they always like ask us if we
want to have this and um I'm like yeah
but when they send it first of all it's
going to take longer for me to get it
than for anybody who lives in Japan like
Cali for
example uh to do pack opening
streams but then for me it takes even
longer because it's definitely going to
get CAU
in the
customs and that's going to be so
[\h__\h] annoying who knows how much
they'll charge me for it so generally um
because of that I don't do them anymore
I could do it through JMA
yeah but I don't have this like urgent
desire to do it anyway so it's like
whatever yeah I think cie got them I
always always see Cali like when when
when whenever there's like something
some card boxes to get she's always like
oh can I please got them thank
you she's like the first one
always the JMA way it was fun but I also
just want to be able to like move them
myself and uh have control over it oh
well anyway that's nice that you got my
stained glass foil card that one's
really nice thank you for supporting me
by getting those boxes those cards I
appreciate it py Dan Jacob 47 Dan B Ruby
com Dan for the red super chat hi K I'm
a new kfp chicken could I get a kfp name
and job here yes you're not that you new
you already have a
kot uh uh uh member emo
thingy are you here
now bza
Ruby I hope if you're not here now I
hope it will still reach you he says I'm
good at car racing I can deliver a kfp
buckets quickly to any dangerous place
and then some Korean text that says I
love you and glad to watch your driving
well who knows if that that's really
what it
says
uh likes driving
H we already I think we already have
quite a few drivers but I mean we always
need more right maybe we can have this
one be a special one like a specific
type of
driver
like
truck
kfp truck load
Deliverance because it was a truck
stream I don't know he only delivers
truck Lo so whenever whenever there's
like a a big big
big
mukbang mukbang because
Korea whenever there's a big mukbang
order Baza
Ruby uses the TRU the Carefree truck to
make a truckload delivery and you're
always waiting you always on call for
the truckload deliveries can't be
trucker I guess you could call yourself
just kfp trucker if you wanted to be
shorter or or
kfp truck deliver or
delivery one of those yeah or truck
cloth I think that's the best you know K
TR clo
delivery it's long but it's going to be
worth
it I hope this reaches
you Korean friend
I hope
so hope you're going to watch the Super
Chat reading of this
V
come thank
[Music]
you frog Lulu D you are D Andrew SW D
Pyro
sagio or sagio thank you for the pinky
nice to finally see K playing ETS 2
greetings from Austria to Austria by the
way
Samia D and thank you for the support
back I've sent the greetings back from
Austria to Austria we go
like you know that little game the with
the ping pong ball I'm I mean okay I'm
for some reason I'm thinking of the
digital one but I guess it also just
exists in real life we're just playing a
a ball a game of
pingpong yeah we go ping pong ping pong
ping pong E pingpong I think it's called
pingpong is it not called ping pong in
Austria then you guys just call it pong
that's so short want to play ping pong
want to play Pong I think we say want to
play ping pong
pingpong in Dutch okay okay okay okay so
I'm not going crazy ping pong but pong
is the game what what are you
saying you call it ping pong or table t
Okay so we're playing a ping pong game
of greetings from Austria to Austria
greetings back to
you thank you rice of out of o Fortuna
than for the pinky tring and clocking
yeah
yeah D star also for the pinky I'm
watching a try drive a truck while
driving a
truck thought I saw a cat it was just my
shadow don't ask how I sent the Super
Chat while driving why you you were
Trucking as well were you also clucking
once you get to my level you'll
understand it's not easy delivering
supplies to every kfp store ah also
thanks for playing this it means a lot
hearing you excited and having fun is
awesome been Trucking for 5 years
what do you rent your truck or do you
have your own
[Music]
truck got to ask for the EUR truck
meta fun out it gets lonely but since
you joined you always accomp me on my
Journeys have fun and drive oh that's
awesome so I'm your radio in the truck
trucking
through wherever you're Trucking through
H drivers don't own the trucks they work
for a company yeah but in your truck you
can buy your own right so I thought
maybe maybe it's not like that IRL okay
well then uh if you're renting it then
be careful with you know not damaging it
too much like
me I mean even if your even if your
company pays for the repairs
you don't want to charge them too
much unless you want to get fired then
maybe charge a lot like make a lot of
incidents
[Music]
accidents hope you have safe Trucking
ahead of you thank you so much M to
dstar ninja Tim D M D boohoo 7 to3 D and
10 talk thanks for Pinky request for
official kfp cap merge and a Truck a kfp
cap that says I'm excellent thank you
for your attention a cap um maybe in the
future yeah I always thought like cuz
omocat merch is even available now that
like shirts and caps and hoodies and all
that I don't necessarily want to do it's
not urgent you guys have the really sick
omo cap merch
um but uh now I did a hoodie because
specifically for frogy Wawa I wanted to
have one so you know at some point I
think I might want to do a
[Music]
cap theat hat isn't really a kfp hat
though it's a waa hat
oh you want something that's more kfp
but what's more kfp than a waa hat
HH
huh you you buy several C raring your
shirts
really thank
you I maybe I should make more clothing
merch um on on my side
because I think I'm getting a bigger cut
so maybe I
should I I actually
should you have five finger shirts wow
thank you
those are so worth it those are so
soft oh yeah the thing is though ocat
can make several sizes I can only make
one
size but caps at least are more one
sizable than
cloves yeah maybe I'll make a cat a cap
for real No
Cap t l d dingo Ringo D thank you for
coming by I do like the point and click
games
yeah lunchbox than maple Le thanks for
the r Super Chat this stream reminds me
of a story of my truck or grandfather he
was driving his rig at night and at one
point he would wound up getting his
German this German tourist with his
motorcycle stuck on his
front stuck what you mean stuck for a
solid kilometer or so the tourist was
fine by the way sent him xmus cards for
years Christmas cards stuck as in
like actually stuck like you collided
like he collided and
then and maybe the trucker didn't even
notice because you know you sit up so
high and I guess the motorcycle is
really
low like scooping them up yeah
like that's kind of crazy
easy well thank God the tourist is
fine what a story that is uh that could
have gone really
wrong how the [\h__\h] does that happen I
mean at night you still have your lights
on and the Motorcycle also has their
lights on you would
assume what the [\h__\h] they have huge
blind spots oof oof oof and I guess
maybe the motorcycle guy was like trying
to honk honk honk but maybe motorcycle
honks are really really small and maybe
the truck uh grandpa had a had a loud
radio
on or so or just didn't know where it's
coming from cuz you can't [\h__\h]
see sheesh okay to all trackers out
there if you hear small honks
continuously and you don't see where
they're coming from but but they're
still sounding close by then stop on the
side and check the front of your
truck holy
[\h__\h] honk
honk I saw a video of a bike sandwich
between two big trucks they survived oh
my
god well thank you mayap for that
interesting story
she supreme leader Beetle Dan Toro Dan n
by Dan donle Dan vex raffle WAFF
Supremacy D thank
youi thank you for the pinky I'm glad I
woke up at midnight to watch the stream
F SP thank you ooh so late for me you
woke up for me thank
you my my poor poor sea friends watching
at the shittiest times always I feel
your determination and love thank you
I she right in D out run the wind D
thank you oh you were you were on your
way home from seeing the eclipse
cool man yeah I can imagine pictures
will never do it
justice so you can outrun the wind but
can you outrun the eclipse huh
huh R 4 for one d b d m d Shy Boy D oo
yeah I want to
go to one of those Spain or Iceland in
2026 is this Spain or Iceland both in
H you guys got to remind me when it gets
closer ch ch D Co D Ty
d d oh SMY SMY poy smoy toy
she loves me so much guys what do I
do
no I have her tail between my my um big
toe and the one next to it I grabbed it
with my feet oh so
soft hello did you go to the toilet is
that what you here H you want to make my
arm wet again I picked her up up
carefully okay you want to go you don't
want to be
here okay goodbye goodbye goodbye what
was i d Jim Tracy D V faction F on a
pinky hey that's pretty cool oh me
singing o to Joy I think because
somebody else commented about that right
after you could hear the purring I don't
think she was
purring that was just me
that was just
me thank you V faction
[Music]
no
thank you could hear her purring are you
sure are you
sure
midnight Midnight Rider mik Maple
Leaf I was actually surprised so many of
you were like oh that was so beautiful
So Divine in Clips also I'm like eh I
was like just messing around I think I
can sing it
nicer especially at some point I was
just kind of not mocking but trying to
imitate like this kind of like opera
singing But in a stupid
way Lou moonight than on Pinky just got
home and I was received by an absolute
treat Kaba singing the song of her
people and then almost dying because she
was looking at her phone I feel like
it's a true Tru experience hope
everyone's having an amazing day thank
you you too
hopefully watching my streams shall make
it an amazing day I hope I hope I
hope wait I WR that for the pinky I
share your pain of trying to put stuff
in your eyes T you I've never been able
to handle eye drops glasses for Life
yay well I don't wear glasses but um I
understand you
yeah ey drops so scary oh God just
thinking about
it no anything that's eye drops or nose
drops no
please take it away I don't want
[Music]
itan Carter
vanim thanks for pinking I'm planning to
go to the doomi this year it would be my
first time so I'm really excited oo
first time doomi or also first time like
convention
I also registered myself as a helper for
it and I also saw that some K members
are preparing a booth there so I would
be excited to meet them yet they've been
preparing booths at dokomi ever since it
was my first appearance there and then
even when I didn't appear there they
still made a ky Booth what you guys are
crazy German kfp have so much passion
even though I don't get called to
European
conventions one first time DOI oh it's
so nice it's so worth it DOI is best is
best o
wow this year toi will be my first anime
convention wow she oh that's crazy
that's crazy that's a big one to go to
for your first
one what I'm suffering
can you just please break my neck please
please please do it Release
Me From My suffering
please all why are you all going to do
me you guys so many of you even from
overseas and I'm not even
there something about doomi just gets
all the K of people there it's like a
holy Place holy place of uh um what's it
called what my brother did when you walk
pilgrimage it's a pilgrim it's part of
the cave of pilgrimage
kadas something pilgrimage Kat faithful
pilgrimage
[Music]
oh
faithful only for the most fa full of
them
[Music]
all sheesh I do it again and again and
again new Discord name
incoming I love the kfp word plays too
me too me
too well have fun
everybody and uh yeah be friendly to
each other
okay be friendly take down sword yeah
that little chicken knife you have there
take it
down
and rice of free d d for the pinky
employer couldn't do be living the true
K fre experience with all that covering
they have to
[Music]
do I made them spend so much money but
some I really think sometimes it was
bugged because there were some crashes
registered that there was really no one
around me or it was one of those cases
with motorcycles but I don't think the
game has motorcycles driving around on
the highway actually I didn't see a
single
one
so I don't think
so now not my blind sides like cuz I
even checked the angles the different
angles once and there was nothing around
me is it the thing in this
game or is it just me because I F like
there were several times where I was
yeah really not crashing into anything
and I was being charged or not even that
like some some other things they charged
me for too just didn't
happen some offenses I don't know but
mostly the crash CRA
crashes he a bit janky right some cars
were too close to you too well yeah but
they can do whatever the [\h__\h] they want
apparently most you're drifting into a
never line and hitting someone behind
you no oh I don't think so there was no
one behind
me unless they just poofed Into Thin Air
once I box them and then when I turn
around there's no one
there you don't know about invisible
walls everywhere I didn't think they
would be in herot truck simulator what
the [\h__\h] oh
man [\h__\h] hokan thanks for the pink for
the red chat woohoo thank you for
streaming this this game is beloved and
dear to me I still remember I stayed for
the first first time for your Super Chat
reading because I was in middle of
delivery oh truck delivery and never
trucker so many truckers ever since I
fell in love of you and that's how we
are here love you Teno you played my
beloved game so I think it's only fair
for me to try something you love so any
recommendations with game or sure to try
oh I didn't watch any shows beside Top
Gear and Grand Tour
what what you're saying in your whole
life the only shows you watched is are
top gear and Grand Tour
what there's no
way a big mistake
hokan
what
[Music]
what oh only a in-game trucker Oh I
thought you were Trucking
IRL how like how what how
have you never watched anything
else did you never have a TV or
what
like
H not your way to spend
time H okay um H okay I'm even going to
recommend
you wait are you saying you never
watched Game of Thrones
[Music]
either God there's so many
recommendations I could make I could
recommend scrubs I could recommend if I
want to tease you Gilma girls I could
recommend handmaid tail or The Marvelous
Mrs
masil Game of Thrones
this m sauce all over again for
real M sauce was more about food
[Music]
though I just W eggless
person I those sh I mean I would like to
recommend something that you might
actually like and not be like man I
watched this [\h__\h] now I'm done I'm never
going to take your recommendations ever
again smoovie is hunting a fly by the
way eat
it baby oh she's so cute oh she's so
[Music]
pretty tutor now oh the [\h__\h] fli is
on my monitor here here smovie kill it
here here look
look there yeah yeah right there in
front of my
face yeah yeah I'm behind the monitor
now I
[Laughter]
guess what are you doing where is it
now where is it oh you're so
soft it's a fat [\h__\h] fly that's one
thing I've noticed now that I have a
house and a garden now that I'm so close
to the ground ah [\h__\h] fly right in
front of me fat smoothie come back it's
right here I don't know why it's trying
to say to stay so close to me are you
calling me Stinky oh there there it
goes uh yeah I've noticed uh there's way
more flies and [\h__\h] flying in whenever I
open a window they're like Zoom zo zo zo
Zoom
constantly and they're so fat they're so
fat I did not have this problem when I
was living over the ground
level wait till we get ants yeah I I um
I I feel
like I feel like that is definitely a a
ground level apartment uh or house kind
of
problem but I I think I also had it in
the past when I was living in an
apartment with my family like a little
bit above ground even then I I think
it's like more of an isolation kind of
problem in that
case because
I think when like the building is really
modern and wellb
built
then they don't get through as easily as
in older buildings right cuz I think
back then it was like an older more
random
building yeah and the Ants were coming
through hold on we also probably had the
window open back then all the time like
in the kitchen I think it was like
constantly open m H but I swear I
haven't had ants I haven't seen ants
inside in the previous
years ever ever and I had food lying
around for
sure but I think it's just like that
well H closed off
everywhere but now it might very well
become an issue yeah I don't think my
rats no no no no no no no no no that's
not going to happen I don't think
so I don't think
so we'll see though we'll
see we did have a Casper well that was
in Japan and that was not an ant that
was way bigger than a [\h__\h]
ant no [\h__\h] cockroaches don't really
appear
here cockes I've only seen in Japan
before m
which freaked me the [\h__\h]
out yeah we don't have those pets cuz of
the cold coldish climate it gets hot in
the summer but not hot enough for like
cockroaches it's not the right climate
for them thank
God at least we don't have some of those
issues I mean there's surely some
roaches somewhere in Austria
but like no I've never I've never seen a
single
one yeah mice mice are a thing but I've
also never seen I mean sometimes on the
streets maybe I see a mouse or a rat
like zooming around at night really
rarely uh in Austria like in the
cities sometimes really
rarely but I've never heard of it
becoming an issue
inside yeah again the cats might help
with
that how are
you when I lived by a park M often in
the summer but just clean up good and
yeah I don't think I'll have issues with
that I one in my in my room as a kid but
I live on the Austrian country yeah
Countryside again might be a kind of
different
experience
centipedes I want to have
caterpillars anyway I got to read super
chats let's get done before Cinderella
time but like I mean obviously I'm not
going to read all of them then probably
I don't know how much I have
left um thank you
hokan you got me into aen wait I didn't
give you a recom I Almost Got Away by
the
recommendation
um not letting you get
[Music]
away oh I
must a funny show you want to see a
funny show okay the marel masil I'm I'm
just going to go for it I I think even
if you're like a metal kind of guy you
will appreciate the comedy of The
Marvelous Mrs
masel there's some seriousness to it too
somewhere but it's very well buried by a
lot of
comedy please watch it yeah you watch
the first episode of that and oh my it
what happened in the first episode I
don't remember but damn watch more what
the [\h__\h] yeah if you like there's also a
lot of uh like standup comedy in it
really well
written um you can watch it on
Amazon Prime I don't
know yeah written by the game girls
right there yeah yeah yeah yeah
but I think you will notice if you
watched gimo girls before there's like
some similarities in style of like scene
writing and there's some reoccurring
character actors
so I got only to fourth season only
there plenty well how many seasons were
there wasn't there how many were there
five [\h__\h] fly the lights of my
monitors are probably interesting
because everything else is Pitch Black
right now
I just got here welcome I'll watch it
and report to you okay okay okay
okay is this deal for like you watch at
least one season or
what what's the
deal what deal do we
have one season deal please give it at
least one season otherwise come
on at least one let's go let's go let's
go let's go W woohoo I'm excited about
that
woohoo go with it go into it with an
open mind okay don't be like I'm going
to watch this girly W show no no no it's
really
[Music]
good let's go thank you hokan enjoy
marvelous Mrs
masil she's so marvelous She's So Divine
she's so
[Music]
Exquisite I am a beep PE thank you for
the pinky I really love today's stream
thank you was thank you I'm glad you
guys enjoyed my simple Trucking Stream
So Much although I was quite on the
tangent binge
I went a little bit crazy there you got
mik thanks for the pinky as well this
got to be up there for my favorite
streams this year it's so fun seeing you
spot so many things and I love your
German even though I don't understand
the thing I love the tangent to your
story makes me admire and respect you
even more thank
you yeah I was uh I was really playing
up the
accent the Austrian
accent uh my German
it's so difficult for me to make I'm so
embarrassing well thank you though thank
you I'm glad you enjoyed it there surely
will be more of this game on my
channel black FR D ja monkey dun Flappy
boy thank you for the red super chat dun
for serving us as
trilingual FEA TR of a stream F K the
most dramatic thing in kfp history and
it's not even on the my channel since
that channel is clinically dead by
now I should use this opportunity to pay
my oh do I have to pay some too by the
way oh got to check all my bills man
tomorrow
is 1 of 1st of
May
this that means maybe it's time for some
bills again
[Music]
I to go for mine
too
labor where in
Austria oh yeah but as wait first of May
is a special day usually
oh
oh they off this car
oh oh indeed
well I guess I got to go find a tree to
climb
upon but like not a normal tree I'm got
to find a like a big M
tree time to climb up a Big M
tree a yeah
y get that Grill on waa oh you you you
mean it's grilling time when there's a
holiday I should climb fall us world
tree
huh H got to find something to climb
something out there must be
climbable thank you Flappy boy I'm glad
you enjoyed it so
[Music]
much oh translators why you were you
translating in the Discord I already
asked you why why go in the chat Lord
Oblivion than space waterfall than for
the pinky than you for the stream that's
had selfish
bask I love you so
much stop it's embarrassing to read so
much
German I feel very hazukashi
thank you though I'm glad you had a good
time German Wawa made an appearance but
don't get used to it guys no no no no no
no no no no no no don't don't don't
flatter
meia happy birthday
I was a fax machine just
now was that was that a fax machine
sound uh what am I thinking
of the the the not connecting sound I'm
thinking of that like um yeah the modem
the modem the modem sound and modem yeah
dialog dialog
sound yo ah the kettle edits were so
Good by the way Kettle edits were so
[\h__\h]
yeah happy
birthday happy birthday happy belated
birthday chocolate sonn chicken and the
pinky I'm an iral truck driver see there
you go this is a real trucker the other
one may have just been your truck
trucker but this one seems to be a real
one oh why was YouTube telling you that
what did I
say um I give you the stamp of approval
really don't don't you shouldn't really
just going to cause accidents on your
behalf I'm excited to see more tracking
laa best tracker in I ID Tru
collab if only I know a lot of them like
tracking on Euro Truck Simulator but if
only they had an online mode why the
[\h__\h] do they not make an online mode
there's online mode for flight simulator
right
why I mean all I guess not the same
people made the game but
still still what the [\h__\h] and they
do is
there for flights or maybe I mean a
different one I saw like
uh like an airport online
thingy the one I T you about where the
pilot was like role playing with the
other with the
others there's an official
[Music]
online yeah micro Microsoft Flash
simulator has
online play on your own have a call at
the same
time I don't know I don't know if
there's no proper online mode then I
don't want to do it nah I'm not feeling
it I'm
sorry ER is Year my job let me drive an
American semi truck in Sweden for winter
testing which was really cool oh
American American truck into Sweden
why
why cor is still playing that ball
rolling game cuz she was doing uh
endurance I saw she's still playing it
that looks like another one of those
shitty
games she is
man I watched a little bit uh a little
bit just a little
bit she fell quite
far I mean it's not really her falling
is more like the ball going somewhere
and you have to run back to get the
ball but
yeah winter test
tracks what people bring their freaking
Tru TRS to Sweden for that what why
can't you go to
Canada why can't you go to Canada
H why get it anyway I'm glad you had fun
with that sounds like you are a proud
truck driver as you should be safe
Trucking for you and safe clucking
chicken OAB
be Eric Baron happy belated birthday
congratulations
I was wondering when your next song will
be well I just released one Kima so next
one will take a little while but I'm
thinking of starting to work on it soon
soon soon soon I want to get it done
early um but yeah probably going to time
it
for uh like around
birthday
probably Templar sword thank thank you
ooh found you from
Kima you K be here found you from Kima
and listening to it then sparksman we
pick up a 10year lyric to try to
complete it before writing something new
oh thanks for inspiration to pick it up
again algorithm
Chan um thank you the [\h__\h] algorithm
Chun algorithm
Chun Alor RM Chan bringing me new
viewers for my music are you okay are
you drunk
algorithm there must be something wrong
with algori joh we have to bring them to
the hospital or
so what the
[\h__\h]
welcome uh stay a while and
listen if you're still watching the
stream sometimes hope it wasn't a one
time only thing yeah you're so close to
1 million and I I didn't even try so
hard with promotion I could have tried
harder I could have tried
harder went pretty
smoothly he's here right now right
really I didn't see I'm looking at the
chat and I cannot
[Music]
see
a ah there you are
ah hey nice that you're still around oh
bi answered
me oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
ah oh
[\h__\h]
yeah no doesn't seem like she can
circumstances don't allow
it I don't know if she you
know spraying in front of a child who
who oh she said something okay okay no
no bi no bio
perms she's not streaming this week yeah
[\h__\h] bad timing ah
[\h__\h] damn
it damn it damn it would have been a
good reason to do a one-on-one collab oh
man I mean could still do it afterwards
but before makes way more sense but I do
I do want to go to Thailand again
sometime just for vacation because like
okay so I'm going pretty short right and
I thought that the rest of May I might
be going to Bali that's why I kept the
Thailand trip short otherwise I would
have extended it and then gone to
somewhere like a nice vacation
destination in
Thailand um but then now that I knew
that oh Bali isn't happening I thought
okay then maybe I can change my flight
back to later but the cost is a little
bit high so I was like maybe that's not
worth it I'll just go come again at
another
[Music]
time too bad cuz I I know there's some
really really nice resorts in Thailand
that are really beautiful and still so
cheap M some really nice nature really
nice beaches and good food and yeah good
service I'm excited for massages man the
moment I arrive I'd like to have a
massage
[Music]
please okay I have one embarrassing
question though cuz I already noticed
this [\h__\h] fly go away in uh Japan
last
time when I was looking for massages I
found some that looked very Sessy I was
like what the [\h__\h] it's
real now I wonder uh do I have to
be careful with what massage place I'm
choosing is it easy to mistakingly go
into a weird
one does anybody know any Tai kfp in
here right now cuz I would like to have
a massage
with an ending that's just me yes indeed
I would like to go out happy but like
like not that
happy I feel like advertising would make
it yeah I F so too like the masses that
I fought were Susy in Japan they had
like the the pictures were like really
pretty girls dressed up really nicely
you know like what the hell this is not
professional really is it easy to tell
okay [\h__\h] off F so fat fren shaped
fly h
okay well I'll have someone find good
places for me perhaps now it's in the
middle of the [\h__\h] screen go away do
I need to bring froggy waa out with her
fly SWAT thing
thingy is it time for frogy waa to come
back I don't see her mening those at
least keep an eye out you'll be good
okay [\h__\h] off [\h__\h]
off Super Fly
feed her she shall feed herself
please feed yourself girl okay let me
read the super chats I want to get out
of this room with the
fly uh Templar sword so thank you really
cool that you here black F dang te thank
you for the red
chat thanks for the o to Joy I have
ascended behold my idol K taka n she
aggressively doesn't like so I guess
that's okay
don't write my name like that I
immediately have to sing that
song there are others like her but she's
my idol her songs and dances illuminate
the world her Flames warm and Enlighten
her subjects oh who are definitely not a
cult love you Ki I love you
too if I smack it now I'll have fly
blood all over my
screen it's taunting me
like rubbing its hands [\h__\h]
off should just turn the light on in
another room maybe then it will
go oh man that'll be
metal a [\h__\h] off
man oh fly blood is good for cleaning
monitors where the [\h__\h] did you hear
that get the
Chun h
it's scheming something it's trying to
taunt froggy Wawa probably to get her to
come
out oh you little
[\h__\h] no no come back come back
yeah I I have my elbow rest right here
that looks like a
baguette I would maybe use
that anyway thank you so much DCH sorry
for changing topic a [\h__\h] fly
stalking me thank you so much you're so
sweet a you're so supportive so kind I
appreciate it thank you for all the love
I hope I can give it back to you Saka so
Avenged me H
H hope you had fun in Korea unknown
twins chat not enough lesbian more
lesbian please Kiana more lesbian okay
careful and so for all the newbies this
is a
meme
uh this is a little bit of a meme that
we have going on thank you
unknown speaking of Australia I asked
the staff to give me a code because
apparently you were able to watch the
Australia thing in
spawn so now I have a code but I don't
have the time yet to watch watch it I
might forget about it I hope I don't
forget you guys have to remind
me the fake red one what do you mean the
fake red
one ah oh yeah the meme yeah yeah
yeah it's only an hour yeah so I saw the
YouTube part
already I saw the YouTube part it was
really funny when Callie's microphone
wasn't
working not only an hour so I guess I
already saw like what 20 minutes or so
of the
hour yeah holy [\h__\h] the venue is huge
like it's I saw in one scene I saw like
in the
back like the rest of the
convention so it's not like completely
closed off but damn they wa it's huge
what the
[\h__\h] that was so sick that they they
prepare such a
huge venue for just at a convention a
little
concert and then you know I mean you
know how much goes into oh thanks for
the membership you know how much goes
into doing a concert like this at a
convention in
3D um a lot of work that's like a lot of
money too so that's why it's not normal
that's why we don't we're not always
able to do that but hopefully it will
become more and more
common they use two Arenas so crazy so
big
[Music]
yeah damn I would have loved to be there
man I'm so jelly I'm so jelly I want to
go to
Australia when will I get to go to
Australia my home country my
homeland
[\h__\h] should have kept up the Australia
wink bit H maybe that would have helped
for them to choose
me
[Music]
yeah how many seats they're selling for
the super Koka party in
taipe super Koka party I'm not part of
that am am I
but no I haven't
seen I got to make the pilgrim wed
that's my
pilgrimage was sold out sheesh
sheesh yeah I saw chimo was
playing oh and it was kind of cool to
see um some non myth members AKA uh it
was TOA and and cie well Callie is myth
but yeah the other ones sing our myth
song toas English was really good there
wow that was so
cool TOA English was really good she
sounded really really smooth with her
English journey of a thousand years made
me quite happy to see her sing it and
dance it because I don't think like she
would have sang or danced it otherwise
guys
ever so that's pretty
sick cuz normally like we from Ian we
sing the Japanese General songs like K
mck Ryder and all that we sing that a
lot but it's never the other way around
I mean it's also difficult because of
language and all that and you know
Japanese branch is the main branch so it
do be like that but so that's why it
made it so special to see the other way
around yeah
she did such a good
[Music]
job yeah
so thank you so
[Music]
much this Super Chat looks so familiar
to me or sounds so familiar I feel like
you wrote this before anyway thank you
Sky H
brand space waterfall D
and right
yeah thank
you
yeah kop waa what a cute little
nickname
k cute
okay what do I read
next this one I skipped so now I can go
back maybe to part seven of uh [\h__\h]
off go away go
[Music]
away I guess yeah part seven I probably
didn't read yet
[Music]
go away go away go
away [\h__\h]
[Music]
you I sound like I have random anger
issues
okay no don't go guys
stay oh sheesh oh sheesh green Wilder
went wild in these super chats okay okay
okay okay okay part seven
here superat swatter I need you where
are you when I need
you
man M sauce thank you for the r Super
Jad after one year of being a member I'm
finally delicious
I really want to say thank you wa and L
kfp for welcoming me into this community
with so much kind immediate kind
kindness you all wonderful person and I
love you I've never been happier to be a
bucket of fried
food yeah uh I don't know if you have
the right to be a bucket of fried food
if you probably I don't know have you
ever eaten fried food
HH M sauce how is it with fried food
have you had fried chicken
before yeah huh don't be like yes
question mark like it's not a given with
you it's not a given with you I don't
know about
you okay if you have it before then I
guess you maybe come
one OMG yeah that's the kind of
reputation you have here
now that's how it
is what was it besides eggs what else
did you not eat before I feel like there
were like a million things that you
didn't eat before and you were also not
even like open to
trying have you had an egg by
now a soup oh my
God [\h__\h] soup how can you ever talk
to
narissa with that
attitude LOL no
LOL no no egg that is some really
eggless Behavior
there there's no surprise that we're
going to continue bully you about
it LOL no is that funny to
you is this [\h__\h] joke to
you you know where you are right
[Music]
we're all really serious about
this [\h__\h]
Insanity I can't kiss your mouth like
that or your cheek if you've never had
egg before M soce I don't know if I can
give you a choo choo for red Super Chat
where where's the egg where's the
egg the beak
yeah shut
up your heart is broken well egg is
too as the game is
called egg is too egg is more
heartbroken than you are
yeah because you refus to eat it so I
refuse to give a chew until you eat an
egg and I want to see proof of an empty
eggshell or
whatever waiting for it take 47 D take D
green Wilder going wild with a rainbow
thank you so much M MW mwah mah My Egg
not eggless person egg fulfilled green
welder gets the kisses yeah yeah how
does it
feel the other day on the Arisa stream
you were asking about what makes you
cool and I want to share my
take oh the way you are strong enough to
persevere and do what you want even
sorry that was my
hip and do what you want even when it's
hard or stressful or scary stories like
going to Japan at 15 the time you stood
up to the angry guide the post of is
[\h__\h] yeah you remember that or just your
general will to keep entertaining us
chickens no matter how much you're
dealing with behind the scenes it's
something extremely cool and inspir yeah
what you didn't even know the story of
all the moving yet now you know so this
makes even more sense of how much I'm
dealing with behind the scenes
mhm it's something extremely cool and
inspiring about you I personally have
natural I have a naturally high
threshold for stress so usually things
don't get to me but when
things did I eat a clown
ew things um do actually get hard for me
I tend to give up really easily so
seeing how hard you try for what's
important to you is genuinely
inspiring thank you you call yourself
lazy sometimes but to me you're
absolutely amazing like they say see
being brave isn't about not being afraid
it's about pushing on even if you're
scared I love you wow and I'm definitely
not the only one here who
does so cute thank
you thank you so much for the sweet
words I don't know I mean I have my lazy
moments for sure but I feel like I'm
just trying to regain
energy you know being always highly
energetic in my job for free and a half
years it drains you a little bit so when
you're not streaming you know you have
to be able
to I mean you know especially if you
feel like generally you're a low energy
person I don't know I can be very high
energy but then I need to charge it
back so that's why maybe I feel like I'm
lazy off stream but I'm just regaining
energy by trying to use as little as
possible
maybe I should take a month off without
like doing a lot of exhausting stuff
during it I agree but no it's okay I'm
fine have you tried wireless
charging I think I'm always wirelessly
charging but yeah thank you for your
generosity and your huge sweet kind
words I really really appreciate them
thank you so much Queen Wilder Wilder we
thank you m
m I'm glad I can inspire
you you inspire me too
guys I wasn't Twitter for half the break
well the
Twitter doesn't take energy
not
[Music]
really space wonderful than and Omega
gaming
CH 145 thanks for the red chat here's my
tax money for the best Phoenix Idol and
Super Chat backseater what we all can
wish for G at stream Kima oh another
Germans speaking person and indeed shm
Kimera we're so close to 1 million thank
you for this necessary
reminder and for your tax money I
appreciate it I actually just got my tax
payment reminder from my tax
[Music]
lady less than 14k oh my God we can do
it maybe by the time I wake up even who
knows woo let's go we're getting there
let's go thank you Kizashi M feeling
dunk
you guys kind of ruined that word for me
man that phrase space wonderful danin
spanheim danin thank you for the rested
of chat okay the cats finally let me get
out of bed oh I know how it is nice to
get a little morning K Yakuza yo I also
woke up early today cuz I slept so early
I was really tired but the cats the cats
make me stay in bed longer because
they're so sweet and I want I cuddle
them and just chill man B is just so
hard to get out
of I stream like five times at the gym
oh nice thank
you
I I love my
cats I love them I love them so much I
love
them and I noticed I was the one to wake
myself
up after like 7 or 8 hours of 7 and 1
half hours or seven s or 7 and 1 half
hours of
sleep smoovie didn't say a thing smoovie
did not try to wake me
up which really makes me
think maybe I do have to get up earlier
and then she'll leave me
alone yeah maybe she is a morning cat
and as long as I don't sleep until noon
or okay it's not usually not noon it's
usually like 10 or
11 as long as I don't sleep until then
maybe she leaves me alone I don't know
but I feel like I tested that before and
it it didn't necessarily work so maybe
it was just a lucky lucky
morning the Smoothie alarm clock
spankenheimer so lucky to not have that
anyway
[Music]
thank you spankenheimer
dog who loves bread and Hungry Jacks
face little pinky Joe Ammon is the
secret super boss in every game with his
occasional Ammon Clan students testing
Gamers patience and skills to see if
they deserve the title of dragon of
dojima easy is not in his name fun fact
you face two Ammon super bosses in
Yakuza
zero I played Yakuza
zero who was that
then not sure but nice lore nice
information thank
you oh it was a side quest thing
[Music]
just
another
I oh yeah I would agree with that yeah
it has to be German
Gothic
Thomas for the pinky I just realized I
am free now fun fact when I originally
remembered I meant to do it in January
but mobile didn't have an option to
remember to w
yeah so I forgot until I managed to do
it on my
Xbox for Microsoft
Edge that that's like like you know
taking a picture with your [\h__\h]
Nintendo
DS it's like such a weird way around it
it seems like you're doing it as a
joke thank you for going the extra mile
to m to
me man very much appreciate it if it
works it works
yeah yeah I've been seeing more and more
people take pictures with their [\h__\h]
Frey ass camera like what are you guys
doing are you just adding to the meme or
are you
serious you can't be
serious own aesthetic
yeah but they are they're just meimi
it's the meme
aesthetic Michael
H Michael H Michael H where youf D for
the pinky was a busy week for me and I
couldn't watch your streams in the time
I got reborn as a hybrid and left the
bucket behind I fried but I lived I hope
I was a tasty chicken yes you
were two J and 3 D now without
interruption 2 J uh two years two uh
German years is with Jay
excit for ex
excited for my armor for many years to
come
yay you have to clean and oil your armor
properly make sure to take good care of
it
okay you're looking so handsome in it
thank you for the long long long
support I appreciate it one day you get
that RGB armor as
well Anthony web thanks for the red
super
chat oh wait no I think UF mod
doesn't yeah do doesn't have the armor
yet I think uh yeah yeah yeah yeah next
rank is the armor I think I
misunderstood
still Anthony thanks for the red of 10 I
always enjoy watching your stream and
play games I love you love thank you
my mom said something like that to me
the other day too and I was like like
she was pointing out one laugh of mine
and she was like oh this laugh this
laugh I really like this laugh of you
because this laugh I know that you
really find it
funny and I'm
like and then I felt really awkward
about laughing and I
just I don't know that made it so
awkward I'm like what do you mean like
every everyone on my laughs
is I'm I'm laughing like I
mean I've had more serious
laughs I don't know it felt really
awkward embarrassed
weird which laugh she meant the the one
that goes like
uh I don't I don't know that that's not
even a belly laugh not at all it's not
even
close it was just like such a random one
I'm like what are you saying
now I feel so
weird so [\h__\h] weird
now like she never said something like
this to me before I'm like what what
caught me off
guard
[Music]
really I have laugh number five it's
like a
menu we oh is is golden week starting in
Japan golden week is always special for
Japanese people finally some time off of
work
man I'm tired I'm going to get time off
of work now too in a moment thank you
Anthony from you hearing it from you I'm
not that embarrassed also because you
didn't specify which love so that's
that's that's I feel less embarrassed
now
Michael H D DC D Michael H Dan Michael h
d s
Hy Tracy Michael H
motion oh I once needed to pick up a
paper at the hospital for my sister and
stood around for over an hour because
everyone looked busy then another
patient saw me and got someone for me
instantly that's your embarrassing story
motion
that's
[Music]
it that's
it I'm not impressed come back I guess
you went to sleep but you better come
back right now wake the [\h__\h] up come
here tell me a bad embarrassing
story someone's had a nice life you
little [\h__\h] motion you're just flexing
your nice not embarrassing life to us
huh mocking
us you little [\h__\h] motion you may be
sleeping but I'm giving
you Eternal usual room sentence until
you tell me an actually embarrassing
story oh [\h__\h] that's crazy you better
come up with something
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's for
you I want to I want to see motion
reaction when he finds out about
this if he reacts to it on Discord or
something make sure to screen shout it
to
me
please yeah I know like people's um
feeling about embarrassing things is
different and I I can understand that
like some things might be more
embarrassing to you but this is small
smaller smaller
thing very very small smaller thing
it's actually more
funny like haha oops I mean I kind of
get this kind of situation I've had like
something like this surely before like
the feeling feels
familiar okay you let me know
good oh God I shouldn't be eating
cookies oh my God I'm Cinderella
time it's midnight it's midnight guys
I'm I'm feeling I'm
disappearing wait where am I where the
[\h__\h] am I
[Music]
it's
happening um where was I I here lunchbox
D oh you also have a story I made an
experimental film about my ex-girlfriend
and put it in the school Film Festival I
realized later how cringe she must have
felt and still feel awful
so she was in the same school and she
also saw it in the film
festival you were already not together
anymore what kind of film was it like
more like uh I miss you kind of film or
like
um in any way that is
um not not something you should have
done good good that you uh realize it
and wouldn't do it again
Michael Ed d reer d for the red super
chat uh why is why transparent because
I'm I'm I'm going into Cinderella time
no thank you for the daily stream stanel
please say good care of your health
because we want you to be healthy as
much as you do next time take all the
time you need to rest and recover
knowing that we patiently wait your
return with open arms and much and
hearts much
love why why are you saying all of this
did I say something that sparked
this at that
stream but thank you for your worries
and your concern that is very kind of
you did I spark this did you did I
stream
Sparks thank you though I'm okay and I I
I do uh Pace myself quite well I think
so don't worry I mean currently it's a
bit stressful because like those days
off that you guys are seeing like
yesterday and the day for yesterday and
then the coming days I'm I'm I don't
have like much time to relax on those
days um yesterday and the day before
yesterday was very
stressful and then uh the day before a
couple days before that was it a
Thursday or something or no Friday I
think it was a Friday I took it off
right and that was also really
exhausting and but still fun fun though
definitely fun but stressful so every
time something looks like a day off it's
often not even a day off at
all so the the thing that I do then is
on the days where I do stream I at least
try to before the stream relax as much
as I can just
chilling and that's why I also love
taking my naps because they're the most
relaxing thing ever to me falling asleep
with my
cats he so good I feels so good so
fluffy yeah I'm good I'm good I'm good
very good right now a bit
uh nervous but I'm good I'm I'm glad
that the previous days are now
over so I have a little bit of a braver
right
now thank you rain
air we're doing Moonlight F pinky I'll
confess something now I don't remember
if I mentioned it before before but
anyways I have a crippling phobia of
heights to the point where even in games
I get chills oh and a little bit of
shaky hands if I'm too high and look
down
o that
yeah I mean fear of heights I I think is
very understandable I don't really have
that I mean there's some incidents where
some positions or like
heights in a certain setting where I
would also be like oh [\h__\h] like if
there's no like proper fence and
security and all
that that's very
understandable yeah it's nothing that I
would even say you have to get over it
at
all oh no oh no I'm
fing don't worry about it zly D and py
D okay it's so over I am I'm fading guys
Just Dance perms I think it would also
have to be
unarchived if anything cuz doesn't it
have copyrighted songs but anyway I will
go now and think about what to
eat I kind of honestly just want to eat
frozen pizza today but I got to check
the date on my
meat I think I have a pork filet or
something like that I feel like it still
has some time
I'm see this is me being
lazy this when it comes to food oh man
there's times where I cook properly all
my recipes but I didn't even get the
recipes that I wanted this time so
yeah get rid of The Moldy stuff no can
you
please I don't want
to I'm scared I don't want to see what's
underneath I don't want to look like it
scares me
girl dinner it's not a girl dinner it
sounds so weird you guys said frozen
pizza is not a girl dinner take a
picture oh hell no hell
no but I'll throw it away I'm my ready
to fight the mold oh my God so
appreciate it you're the
best no I'm not going to Tweet it that's
disgusting no no no no no e ew e e I'm
not into that kind of
thing I'm immune to everything
more like a boy dinner I
agree she already did it
before she
already shot is the breaker of
boundaries
everybody shiy is kind of crazy in a
great
way oh my cucumber yeah wait her
cucumber I I mean I feel like everybody
had something like that happened to to a
cucumber before cucumbers that it just
happens what did I miss ghost while is
real it's because it's past midnight and
I'm Cinderella so I have to go now the
magic will wear off and I'm going to
show my
webcam just
kidding the magic of life to De will
wear off and
reveal nothing because this is
me this is a real this is a me I'm
exactly where I'm supposed to be now
I'mma let the light shine on
me yeah high school music well okay guys
you have one thing to do one job stream
Cima I mean honestly I'm so chill about
it because it's going there anyway
algorithm is very nice D algorithm
we'll get there maybe we'll get there
before I wake up that would be cool
otherwise it's fine
too one way or another way we're
reaching it tomorrow or today actually
today few hours let's go I'm so happy
people like Kimo man makes me feel
excited
for actually also scared cuz I don't
know how H now it's like okay I want to
make a new song I don't want to
like disappointed people who really like
Kima like so many of you guys even
though you don't like the K-pop genre
you really like
Kima so now it's like it you're probably
not going to like the next one I don't I
don't know what I'm making
but what do I
do how H but I don't want to think too
much about that I just want to make the
kind of music that I want to
make so yeah
yeah Pi pop that's right we've liked all
your different genes thank
[Music]
you now have a nice evening my old
favorite Fe night a thank
you favorite favorite night fite night
is like I I really think it's a bob too
h
also it's like so so different it stands
out a lot within my
songs yeah thank you guys we'll see
we'll see what we can make um I've been
talking about it a little bit with my
team telling them kind of what direction
I'm thinking of but it's not finalized
yet oh I'm glad you guys like fever
night
yeah okay okay okay you love the dance
in Frey yeah I dance in Fry I I really
like it it's
fun I love the baby
part always got to got to make that uh
spine go like a roller coaster
curve as much as I
can the chair is
talking I look like so cute with my
outfit oh my God I'm such a farmer I'm
going to upload a picture on Twitter I'm
going to go now bye-bye enj we
say that's right
I'll see you tomorrow I'm gonna stream
something something something
something bye-bye
[Music]