[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
I remember in my brain turning them off
[Music]
you guys
however
[Music]
I can't believe it you guys
did not send any
[Music]
oh my God how
how how well behaved and Cooperative are
you like okay I understand you guys most
of you know the rules but maybe there
should be like some words to know the
rule and would be like well or even if
you know the rule maybe maybe you're
like well [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it like purple right
she turns it off I'm gonna get her in
trouble
everyone foreign
[Music]
before the stream starts and it was kind
of okay
so I guess I would have been maybe five
following rules is cool you guys
what the what
yeah Elven ring
um
[Music]
maybe the title helped maybe the title
helped when I said well I'm rich anyway
so you guys thought okay then we don't
need to send our money Batman rich in
game by the way
laughs
[Music]
it's actually incredible
yeah this sounds incredible like oh my
God teamwork
are you sure I turn them off check again
they should be up
[Music]
I can't believe it
can't believe it
I'm I'm genuinely
I'm genuinely shocked
[Music]
it's done
what
[Music]
you saved my bus I mean it would have
been fine one way or another
for the main a new stream but that would
have been really annoying
wow
[Music]
here's the beautiful rooms
Lisa is listening to do you on my on her
Spotify
[Applause]
[Music]
Twitter
ask when it collapsed them
wait what's it sweet
get Anna has Tomatoes
only tweet on their sub accounts one day
I'll be good enough for somebody to
tweet it on their main account
one day oh
taking a place to do you oh my god
what
[Music]
was on her main really
I don't remember anymore
Christina
[Music]
I wrote back
foreign
[Music]
about the coming up cream
that I feel very passionate about okay
anyway
[Music]
we are practicing
oh
[Music]
hello
[Laughter]
how you guys doing
the stream is GTA stream in case you
haven't noticed uh but the hands should
have been a giveaway the head the hand
should have been a go giveaway
where did I put you
where do you want to be
okay
still work but I'm hanging on
your workship just started thanks for
watching anyway
upper middle okay
uh
it must be a Tetris trainer I never
played that the only the puya puya one
ah it's a cute stream too it can be both
GTA and kiwawa stream
hello
it's oh I just got up uh and
one and a half hours ago
uh
I
I am mentally still waking up
[Music]
yeah good morning
will we ever get a froggy about one frog
bread collab of course
someday
sometime
no it's currently I'm doing this on
purpose I I thought you know I'm gonna
get my sleep schedule messed up anyway
so I might as well do it like one or two
days beforehand
uh so that I can adjust to it
and be ready for the tournament because
I know I know I know I can't do it the
other way around I know I can't wake up
uh sleep early and wake up early that's
I've tried many times before and it just
doesn't work for me like not that early
I can sleep maybe two one or two maximum
three hours earlier than usual but I I
can't I I'm incapable of falling asleep
at like
10 p.m or so
or earlier that's impossible so I'm
doing it the other way around um
uh yeah and the good thing is though
that now I'll be available
and we're gonna do me and the girls are
gonna do some practice
uh
before like between my GTA stream and
before the actual tournament
yeah
um yeah we're doing that
yes
at least once
whereas nap time ah I don't know I don't
have Red Bull prepared
um
yeah yeah
practice against fans to give you guys a
real challenge
yeah cause like I gotta say that even
the Bots were
pretty strong
um I I I'm not gonna let anyone
you know
say something that makes my practice go
to waste
the Bots are strong too and they were
like
doing things the way I would do it
I'm a bot
um and I definitely like I I hammered
some
like a system into my brain of like what
I'll be doing and what the order is and
all that so I got in my own practice
time really familiar with
um
with like what happens
and you know
yeah
but what happens throughout the game
um yeah and it's not like I have a
choice every freaking game I joined was
fully Bots apparently
I'm shook head because I thought some of
them some of them you know there was one
match where one of one of the Bots was
like side by side with me helping me and
I felt like wow this person's really
nice and and helps me and this is a good
person and now I find out that was a bot
that's like
traumatizing
[Laughter]
then it's so sad
like what how can they all be Bots
they're real to me they're real to me
to me Lance
[Music]
um
yeah but I I've been ranking up uh once
I realized that you know I I just got
myself a another license so I could do
ranked matches because apparently you
can do rent you can't do ranked matches
until you have a certain amount of
licenses so I uh got another one and
then I started doing ranked matches and
even those had uh fully full amount of
bots
um
yeah yeah anyway
here we go
here we go here we are here we go why is
it not showing up
Mamma Mia
capture this [\h__\h]
do it
what
Mamma Mia
wait a second
time
[Music]
usually when I tab in after a few
seconds is that yeah
why not from the beginning Mamma Mia
okay will it have sound
how do I play this game again I don't
think it has sound right now
does it
and no I don't hear anything
[Music]
um
I should hear some things
there we go baby
a little bit quieter
hmm
um
[Music]
if only you can replace these learning
stories of yours they're really short
anyway so whatever
ah
yeah apparently we're
I would say in the second half of the
game by now
what the [\h__\h] Percy
check emails there's some work that's
paying heavy heavy doing 250k heavy
otherwise I don't know man what to tell
you
you hear the uh the game wait I should
probably
um
[Music]
yeah
um I want to start without music I'm
like I need I need to ease into it
okay
what
I've been there it's not nice it's not
love you want Love Don't You Love
[Music]
you recruiting for a cult
or is he
advertising for Jesus
Chopper
he's riding shotgun Jacob the roster
don't ask unnecessary questions
no civilian casualties we're taking out
a chopper
sting dude interesting but
maybe go to a more crowded place like
here you're not gonna what the [\h__\h] go
to the closest car
you're not gonna get much feedback
Getting To The Choppa
okay
everybody everybody
about
about like I don't know a million years
ago or maybe more like one year ago or
something like that long time ago I I
reported to like the the building owners
that there's something
you know that needs to be fixed
maintenance
uh
and first of all they didn't reply for a
long time
it kind of pissed me off
um because it was bothering me
I reported like two things
and then yeah eventually I I reported it
again and I don't know they were like
just it didn't really seem like they
don't give much
many shits
about it so eventually eventually the
problem kind of resolved itself because
it's a it's a problem that was like it
only happens
at certain times
and kind of like a
a weather condition thing
and yeah it didn't it didn't really
bother me anymore for a while
recently it's been
kind of happening again but
yeah I didn't message them again because
they just
didn't really seem to care and also they
were I think they were like a little bit
in in the beginning implying that it's
my fault but it was something I could
have literally not have caused
yeah so I don't know it was just just
it's just annoying but then suddenly
today
a guy shows up
suddenly a guy shows up
and and I I was like already awake just
chilling in bed about to get up
and
I hear the doorbell ring and I I quickly
put on a dress
like quickly really really quickly brush
my hair a little bit so I don't look too
much like I just woke up at 3 P.M
and I run over to the door and it's a
fixing guy
a maintenance guy and I'm like did I
miss some kind of appointment because I
reported this like a year ago
uh and nobody ever cared or said they
would send someone did I miss something
and
no I didn't miss an appointment they
just randomly come whenever they want I
guess and and those fixing people they
just didn't get the memo until recently
it seems like
and and he was like I opened the door
and he's like well good morning and I'm
like
don't do this to me now don't don't be
judgmental
first of all I tried my best to not look
like I just woke up and I don't think I
look like I just woke up but what do you
know about my working times you know you
always have to assume some people maybe
work night shifts and stuff and I am if
you think about it currently I'm gonna
be working a night shift so
I hate it when people are like you know
like well good morning
well good thank you thank you sir
who shows up one year after I reported
the issue even though it's not his fault
but it's more than the owner's fault
well excuse me
yeah but so the issue was fixed really
quickly at the spot
right there really easily
um
one of the issues the other issue was
like that's just what it is that's just
how it is I'm like okay
foreign
[Music]
like affect
anything but it was just like it made
annoying sounds
rocket launchers
how do I fly this again
like this right okay
I remember I remember
no f
do not F me
shut up
just like riding a bike to me now
follow the Target shop or don't let him
get away easy
wait a second wait a second ah wait a
second wait a second
wait a second
I couldn't make it like a quick turn
[Laughter]
[Music]
I was pressing and D too though
oh well okay
I was running right in front of me but
then he turned right and I I couldn't
make such a
sudden turn
okay why are we here
normally when I restart a mission I
restart from really far away
this time
this time I'm right there
Young
[Music]
good for me very convenient could be
like this more often please
don't report me okay dude there's a dude
standing there watching
[Music]
hey Jacob
yeah of course it won't be common
okay here we go
[Music]
rocket launcher boom let's find him and
get this over with so he's gonna shoot
it right I'm just I'm just focusing on
flying right
I don't have time or the hands to shoot
a rocket launcher
all right now I know he will turn right
I think
unless he changes his route but I don't
I don't believe so where is he
oh there
another little shortcut this time
okay
following
a moving Target is a bit more difficult
for a man
this guy is safety conscious what we had
to do previously oh God
between all those buildings of course
wow wow wow
ah no no no no no what I'm not losing it
I'm trying to move forward
where is it
out there
this is really difficult
oh God
oh God [\h__\h] Jacob you really want to
smoke something now
coordination
why he got the flame with me like that
I don't see him but I see the I see him
on the map so okay did he wait for me
how close do I have to get or is this
like like a thing where we have to reach
a goal before
where where did he one
one
[Music]
get close move to the right of the tiger
Chopper okay I'm not even gaining height
right now
line up your helicopter to the same
height yep yeah
okay
don't hit the airplane though
I'm
here
hang on come on Jacob you need new
lenses in those glasses hit the thing
live we need some
there we go whoa whoa how do you does
that have like some kind of like
controlling in the in the
whatever that is
I can't speak English right now
but does it like nowhere to go that's
what I'm trying to be at homing I think
that's what I'm trying to say
but if we would do this in the middle of
all these buildings for example would it
maybe heat seek something else
to do more than this
entire turn
probably
should be him let's do it
ah
I'm going to land this
Beast very smoothly just look at me just
look look
oh yeah
whoa whoa
is here okay oh apparently something
broke
I would say here here is okay what the
hell
can I just get out and walk over
ow get back into the helicopter oh come
on these five meters
at least it's calm now
drop Jacob at the helipad
drop in can I drop him from really up
high or is that the no no
I don't know he's already high
foreign
look how he's walking it's so chill as
if nothing just happened we didn't just
shoot another helicopter out of the sky
nah no big deal
where are we going next I could use the
helicopter but
I don't know
but let's go to Ray botino
should we
oh
shut down that chopper for you you think
I don't know that sitting around
scratching
scratching up my ass I'd be impressed if
you had been [\h__\h] rude
why is everybody so rude
[Music]
wait did I get paid for this
hmm
use heli no
give I a call if you need some cash I in
Batman usually got some jobs easy
leave me alone is this like
side quests
what he is suggesting to me
potential information
side quest okay okay then I won't be
doing it
uh
yo
watch me don't do it
watch me watch me watch me no thank you
okay
uh
what ah on the side
you know
how you doing how are you doing listen
dick not my fault you got robbed not my
fault I had nothing to do it nothing
really
I'm on a cell phone you jerk
oh you want a me killed oh yeah screw
you
you understand finish no no you know
what I ain't even started yet you demon
[\h__\h] sounds like I have to kill
whoever's on the phone
open your mouth [\h__\h]
push your [\h__\h] luck what the [\h__\h] man
what the [\h__\h] do you want you told me to
come well sorry having a bad [\h__\h] day
oh I'm sorry
calm the [\h__\h] down
[\h__\h] it
curly head we just gotta talk
he reminds me
um
blaming me for everything everything I
forgot her name but from
um The Marvelous Mrs Maison the manager
no diamonds
so much
really the way of talking too right
get a coffee please
I finished watching that by the way
go to The Majestic Hotel
okay I finished watching
um The Marvelous Mrs maisel recently I
I had some time to catch up on the last
couple episodes
yeah it was really good but I'm just so
sad
that it ended oh
please leave it's my taxi now
hey buddy where your head two nickels
three
and and I I I think I understand why
they were doing all these weird
flashbacks that I told you about is
because
[Music]
I wanted to show us
cute car they just wanted to show us how
you know everything ends up
without making another season
they were just trying to help us imagine
it was flashbacks and Future
slashes whatever flash fronts
[Music]
I was like okay not as bad as
um like you know like the typical
compilation episode in series where they
only show old footage
and it's just such a filler episode no
it wasn't like that it still felt like
it had a lot of value because it was all
new footage too
hmm
compilation not I didn't say copulation
it's a compilation
what the [\h__\h]
should I have pulled my gun already
but I have to
security breach
that was [\h__\h] I I didn't have any
ah
I didn't have any armor [\h__\h]
my health
there's still someone there right
someone was just shooting also you
should be dead
nice Okay
can somebody give me some armor please
[Music]
I got it
I'm gonna switch to this one
[Music]
faster
I need the HP potion
please
hey come out of here
come out of here
is he gone
when is he gone
I don't know if I'll survive this though
to be honest with you guys
oh
my aim today is a little bit off
[Laughter]
I hate I hate when it's like this you
have to turn around
I hate these staircase chases
are in there
down
I knew he was coming out of there but I
still panicked
wow what a nice
what a nice room are these are these
normal
um people nobody's normal here right
um that was just
[Music]
am I supposed to shoot these people
I'm not sure
[Music]
why is he getting up you're supposed to
be dead
can't hurt
okay yeah they're shooting back yeah but
you never know in America
they could be you know normal
pedestrians and still be shooting back
come on that's that's not an argument
[Laughter]
can't get his head
still alive
am I supposed to go into this room
because it sets up on the map but maybe
there's a stair inside this room
a scare
maybe there's Ace there
is he dead now
there's at least one more person alive
on this floor yeah okay there is a stair
s okay
that's quite some I've never seen a
hotel room
with a stare before
[Music]
crazy I'm hurt real bad just let me go
anyway sorry about that
oh they got some but really long
baguette holy [\h__\h] that's a really long
ass baguette
wee baguette
[Music]
I quickly
changed my aim see how fast I reacted
moving Target is always
dangerous
she was lucky that I have really quick
reaction speed
what
um
sorry
you're not the one
what is pretty
I got a little bit distracted
oh this is Freddy
[Music]
they were so ready for me I expected one
person only but they were like free the
whole time it was always more people
than the map showed what the [\h__\h]
oh it's pretty
um
okay
let's take a cab again
if I find one
that was fun though I don't mind doing
it again armor oh
am I close oh yeah I'm pretty close to
one of them
foreign
a police officer
so it may be better that I didn't steal
that car
healing kid in the kitchen yeah I think
I saw it
I think I saw it I saw something green I
think here we go it was not broccoli
what
New York taxi drivers be like look
so freaking bad
at their job
apparently
uh where's this place again out there
why did I not pick it up because I know
you're doing it I need to because I need
to get back into the groove okay
and I need a little bit I we've just
played for like
actively playing for 20 minutes okay
are you good to go dude
still waiting for me so nice of you
hmm
hey buddy where you headed to Nichols
three mm-hmm
here we are let me tell you a little bit
about the Nina Vincent how about that
while I'm doing this because now I
already know what to do and what to
expect
late checkout yeah yeah
let me okay
so you know Nina she like first year
clumsy yes
oh yeah first she only told me that she
would be
like coming sometime so I was like okay
oh sometimes she'll she'll she'll we'll
figure it out but then suddenly like she
tells me a date and I'm like [\h__\h] most
of the time I'm not there because I'll
be in London
so like we only really had two days
uh uh and I got sick that made it even
worse oh [\h__\h] I should have
wait I still have time to get out my gun
[Music]
okay
uh yeah so I felt really sorry but she
was really understanding that I couldn't
like spend so much time with her
um you know very very understanding
only within me being in London I already
was like starting to feel better around
the end but problem is
I also felt really bad about not being
able to stream you know
because I was gone for a while and I
felt like when I come back I will stream
a lot so that I can make up for me not
being around for the days before
but now now I was I I had to be with
Nina because she came all the way
to see me
so I had to make some time for her so
thank you guys for being so
understanding now
so
on the first day like I I wanted to
spend like at least half a day with her
but I I ended up just being only being
able to do some like dinner with her
because I needed to rest a bit more how
many times I'm gonna kill that guy
um but
I planned to make up for it the whole
following day
so for dinner
um we went to a place that Nina asked if
we could go to she like looked up some
restaurants
that was like
oh yes a little bit fancy
I mean the website was fancier than the
restaurant so I I was a bit deceived
but I dressed really cutesy for her
she actually first came over to my place
so I introduced her to the cattles and
she really freaking loved my cuddles and
and I did my makeup while she was
cuddling and telling me stories many
many muchos muchos grada stories
okay
mm-hmm
and then we took ah we actually went to
have a little drink before because we
still had some time uh
I only drank
water I think no or yeah because I was
still also I didn't I couldn't even
drink Coca-Cola because I was trying to
take care of my throat and like sparkly
stuff is not good for your throat when
you're recovering from something like
that right yeah
yeah yeah one thing I noticed throughout
the whole time is like you know I tip
too and we we do in Austria tip I don't
think we tip as much generally as in
America because people are not so
reliant on tipping here
um
but yeah Nina was tipping so much to
everybody that I feel like people must
have loved her maybe in general American
tourists when they come here
they might generally be going a little
bit overboard with the Tipping which
honestly nobody can be
upset about right
people must love American tourists
they just I mean they probably go on
Google and they look up
hipping in Austria and they see yeah
it's a thing
it's a thing but
you don't have to
him so much
[Music]
but they see yes you have to tip and
then they probably assume you have to
tip as much as in in their own country
yeah no okay not hundred bucks but like
she was
normally I just round up but even when
there was a like a close round a
roundable amount she would just still go
over it
yeah and pay way more
she definitely tipped like 20 percent
I never tipped that much I'm so sorry
well that's
unfortunate
this timeline is
the worst timeline
is she dead
oh yeah oh yeah uh
well
can't be helped
she should have stayed inside
and not moved okay okay
so we went to this place that kind of
has like a lot of courses but you can
choose to like skip courses of course
and and of course
and just go with whatever you wanted and
and the waiter very very strongly
recommended us to not go for a full
course thingy because all the single
courses are actually quite filling and
and big
surprisingly which is a good thing right
get some you get some value for your
money
um
and
oh
so we ordered we started by ordering
some starters but then later on we
realized that yes
even the starters they could they're
like main course square feet especially
if you have a soup before and then one
of the starters yeah but the food the
food was really good
I ate some steak Tatar even though
normally normally I wouldn't choose it
honestly I wouldn't order it for myself
what where is that last person I can't
see also [\h__\h] police
[\h__\h]
um ah
should I get out of here
but probably not probably not for the
hotel frock door right
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
I can use the lift to the roof what I am
on the roof
um mate I don't know how to escape
Hunter it's too late to take the front
door now don't you think I don't know
there was a vest here
elevator there the elevator
elevator elevator elevator elevator
huh
what
at this thing
[Music]
uh
are they gonna be there I can't look
down
I can't look down
let's see it
okay ah
you think we might be fine
um
quick quick run run
for these guys now
um wait no more car normal car
when somebody's just calling me
okay
[Music]
I was just pressing F endlessly
a bit
I may have canceled the call but they
will call me again right
[Music]
anyway we had really yummy food we had
like oh my God we talked about so many
things and I feel like we
we talked about very deep things to a
lot of very deep things I think I told
you guys I told her things that
I've never told
to anyone four honestly
so it was actually really nice too
talk about some things let some things
off of my heart [\h__\h] I wanted to go left
yeah
not even Cali no not even calling no one
in Myan knows and
maybe only my best friends you know
but like Nina she's so sweet like she's
good at creating an atmosphere that
makes the other feel
very understood and loved and
accepted
you know whoa
so I really appreciated that
it felt good
felt good to let some stuff out
it really made me thank them damn
I I really needed this
[Music]
yeah she's very very sweet
she was like how the [\h__\h] how the [\h__\h]
are you even functioning how I don't
know I'm I'm she was like
stunned
and I'm like I don't know man I just
I just forced myself through life yeah
um but that was a nice evening and then
we walked around a little bit she didn't
wanna
she didn't want to go home right away
she wanted to see
just just walk around because she was
like fascinated by people being outside
on a weekday at that time I think it was
like who knows
it was 10 11 P.M
oh
finally official she just wanted to
watch people
walk around
apart from those other ones you screw
right
they were just distractions from My One
True Love yeah okay
[Applause]
I'm working on it cousin there's this
girl I like she's called Kate McCreery
we like her wedding
try not to embarrass me congratulations
on the engagement
congratulations
sweet that was a cute call he's so
excited thank you cousin
I'll fight her
um
what was I saying
okay uh yeah yeah so I walked around a
bit and
and yeah she was gonna stay over at my
place and I already had everything but
per pad I I cleaned so much I cleaned
for hours you know
the whole apartment
and I made her bed
and
the bed is
um you know
it's where the the cat robot's toilet is
so I wasn't sure if she was gonna be
fine with it but I told her it doesn't
smell and so on and if she didn't like
it we could move the toilet away but she
said it's fine
it's fine the past couple days I also
slept somewhere uh where there's a cat
toilet in the same room
oh okay
because it immediately gets rid of the
the poop and it brings it into a
compartment you know
it's really really convenient
[Music]
hell no
collect you within the hour no not with
Brucey with Roman okay
but not with you
oh my good English
sorry Brucey I can't actually go bowling
with you right now
[Music]
yeah sorry
um
so we got home and we talked a little
bit more and we removed our makeup you
know we had curly time
and finally we went to sleep on to
another day
right
then Bernie opened the door
what's going on let me in come in
are trying to kill me
can't stand it I won't stand it it's not
fair I'm just being me Bernie what are
you talking about I came to this country
to
to get away from small
angry Macho Pricks oh like me yes
well no picture she's pointing
it was pointing Progressive Place how
does my hair look fine I put the rinse
in wow it's Audrey night it didn't move
a single bit when he just shook your
head
oh no
no forget about your hair Florian Bernie
I mean Bernie
what's the problem
someone is threatening to kill me
every time I go out jogging and doing
aerobics or playing ultimate disc some
guy comes up [\h__\h] is Ultimate this
because
I think just because I'm fabulous
what I keep thinking I'm being followed
and I don't know why I'm a prisoner in
my own home okay Bernie exaggerated
I'm so glad you've come back into my
life it's cool but listen a lot and I
don't know each other how can you
can use guy to attack
come on
I love him
I think he's my favorite
[Laughter]
I love the headband you added to your
outfit it really makes your beautiful
eyes stand out even more
okay
not really
I keep active you know is there a name
for that fitness plan I take a class if
I could be guaranteed funds like yours
the mob yeah
it's been very stressful you know
um
okay
so I hope they're not starting to talk
again
oh wait wait we're just going to such a
close place
let me let me move the chit chat about
the second day
too little
Buns of Steel
I've got Buns of Steel
no no I take it back my buns are soft
like a castle I'm not going for a jog
Nico trying to keep up and stay back too
we don't want to be rumbled
keep up and stay back
stay back but keep up
oh man
oh my God look at him
oh my God
run faster
am I doing this right
follow me
[Laughter]
My Sunshine
oh
oh no
I'm about done with you homo
what's your problem [\h__\h] lover whatever
you say buddy unfortunately for hitting
my friend I'm going to kick the [\h__\h] out
of you
should I shoot him or should I punch him
I feel like shooting is kind of brutal
when all he has is a bat you know
there you go oh wow
okay
no a weapon yeah we can just take the
pistol Maybe
[Music]
yo the pistol is really slow too oh
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] no
[Music]
God damn it okay
foreign
once I think
I feel like I got him again but still
not enough
because I saw some blood
sorry I know that was the wrong person
but
you gotta do what you gotta do dude
there we go pick up Bernie but I got a
[\h__\h] star let me get rid of that
first
holy [\h__\h] these bikes are so unrealistic
The Landing
doesn't always lands so smoothly
okay just chilling here until the star
goes away
there we go no Bernie
Bernie my man
where exactly are you this is still the
same park Ryan
what do we do about his balls
what are we gonna do
and does Central Park have a lot of
squirrels
is that so
yes
too many tree rats
that hurt
why am I always so stuck to the bike on
my you know like Landings but this this
is what gets me
this is where I fall off
oh yeah it was right down here
look look how is this possible
over there
done
hi I want to get on the back of my bike
all right
as if you knew that we were gonna ride a
bike back
Perseus
okay
is he always bringing his pink helmet
cute
absolutely fabulous
it's like we're going to the Barbie
movie
and he's the girl that's bringing me to
the Barbie movie but I'm I'm just a
boyfriend who gets dragged along and
really did not want to dress pink
hahaha
scenery
sorry Bernie
it's just this bike has double standard
it's okay
when I crash into other things I fall
off immediately and when I crash against
the ground or so it doesn't matter
what's up with that ah
wait my house holy [\h__\h] wait I almost
died
um can I make a quick stop here oh wait
maybe the uh
when I bunk against that really lightly
he he gets angry but when we just had an
accident that almost killed us that's he
said nothing
he actually said nothing
thank you
you want one too Bernie hmm you want
that sausage
excuse me
[Laughter]
it was just too obvious okay
[Music]
he looked very hungry
but I guess I'm the only one eating
[Music]
meow meow meow I want that track suit
give it to me
you know yesterday was my day off but I
was recording and practicing all day
recording two songs including the
harmonies
and practicing
Pokemon Unite
for like three hours
he's not going to attack you again
[Music]
I was productive
is that his helmet on the ground
are you just leave it on the ground like
that take it take it
just
okay
what what
it's just gonna be left here
maybe I should wear it huh
I should be wearing it
anyway
um
let's drive to
is that Brucie Oh Mamma Mia Brucie I'm
coming for you
okay so
[Music]
um
for the actual full day that we had
together unfortunately it was raining
but I took her to a museum where I
booked us a tour a guided tour not just
like an audio tour I booked us a tour
with an actual Talking human guide
which was really interesting and she
really enjoyed it she was like quite
fascinated by it so that was good
um
and then I brought her to one of my
favorite places and I always show off to
anyone who comes visits a nice cafe with
a great View
but going up there was a little bit of a
hike because it was
um
not on the same level as anything
everything else was quite up high
and we had a lot of desserts there
desserts and and this and that and wait
do you see it
what the [\h__\h] is this
I have to admit that was not my first
thought when I heard I'm happy for him
he's not going anywhere him and Mallory
you're only getting married we all have
to settle down sometime
sure sure enjoy all that extra [\h__\h]
then mercy I'll see you around
okay I actually forgot before we went to
the museum and everything else
um thankfully we got to sleep in I asked
I begged Nina to let me sleep in because
I I need some sleep and I won't be able
to sleep early and and I want I want at
least eight hours of sleep and she let
me sleep in and she also was able to
ignore my cat meowing at 5am in the
morning for [\h__\h] sake
oh yeah
um and then I took uh actually we
started the day uh you know and doing
our makeup together like uh side by side
and then yeah I brought her to a really
really popular
well-reviewed breakfast place that I've
never been to before but you know
and at the breakfast place
um I just ordered something pretty
simple
um but Nina she ordered something that
was quite Austrian I must say it's never
left over food it was like that's why I
mentioned
um I think for
a different thing where she also got
some I added the three types of soup
which was also kind of a leftover food
and she said yeah she likes this kind of
stuff and it was actually pretty yummy I
enjoyed what she ordered more than what
I ordered so uh when she was like done I
ended up eating all her leftovers hmm
Yum Yum Yum Yum very good baby yum good
breakfast place 10 out of 10 I want to
go again
um and then yeah then we went to the
museum and then we went to the fancy
cafe uh but we were both
mostly me but I think she too we were
both pretty tired afterwards after all
of that because the museum thing it took
like two hours I think and it kind of
made us really tired uh because like you
know
you know in a museum when somebody's
like constantly talking
and you're focusing and listening and I
don't know the whole atmosphere was just
very very tiring
yeah you get it right
I didn't lose my mind if a motorbike
driving like this I'm just having fun
okay let me do my stunts
yeah and and then you know up to the
cafe it was quite exhausting going up
there
uh
yeah and Nina Nina does more work out
than me so
it was pretty tiring so after the all
the food we decided to just go back to
my place
so she could pick up her fangs and she
would have dinner with her other friend
yeah so it actually worked out fine
it worked out nicely and honestly we
talked so so much she talks way more
than me even
to be cute
so I think even though it was a short
amount of time we got to exchange
a lot and bondage it was really nice she
can help
and I hope she enjoyed her little
private tour
your wife honey
this is for Real made by me I wanted to
show her more but she was um she wasn't
there only for those two days and she
already explored a lot on her own so
strong
oh man I am cool enjoying your new life
in the land of opportunity this is no
time for jokes buddy oh sorry
trouble Nico real trouble man is giving
blackmailed about what about
me okay
that's not good
did they find out any information about
Darko brevich yet no
but he's working on it
you've got to help me
how we're going to warn these bastards
off kind of dead on myself come on
you just woke up good morning welcome
that's a car sweetie look at him
standing
Army dating oh this is big but not
intimidating is it I don't know
and Let me refresh it's it's just uh
hyper chat I think oh wait it's back
it's back yay
this this looks kind of intimidating
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
please let me in
is this good enough for you bruisine no
way I'm not getting dirty
perfect
to the random room and meet with the
blackmail us okay I think I've ever been
north of middle part this is exciting so
yeah they don't even know what they're
in for no their mind they're talking
endlessly again strong enough to rip
down mountains and throw trucks and all
that stuff am I right
are going to show them
[Music]
we don't know they won't even meet us
themselves it's just some flunky they're
sending you have to tell them to tell
the boss we won't be pushed around no
way
okay
no problem easy easy I'll do it for you
anything for you
my love
yeah and unfortunately like pretty much
all of the things we talked about are
things I can't talk about
on stream so I can't really share
anything about that but let me just you
know have you know that we had a great
time and and Nina was great to see you
again I was so happy to see her again
honestly
she told me that she had a souvenir for
me but somebody ate it
somebody just took it and ate it
apparently
[Music]
so no souvenir for me but it's okay
I I just imagine having received a
souvenir
uh
I don't know I don't want to tell like
too many things but
because I don't know I don't know what's
okay to tell
I hope you see her again in another in
overtime she said she really wants to
bring her parents here
she said like
they would love it and she really loved
it I don't know how you can love it so
much I'm honestly I'm honestly shocked
because I feel like there's cities that
are so much nicer in Europe like so much
more impressive at least
like Rome many Italian cities are more
impressive and prettier I would say but
okay she she she seemed really really
happy with
Austria
um
she really liked Austria
Austria sounds very very peaceful
peaceful I don't know I mean I guess
overall yeah
peaceful to live in yeah
I mean every place got its like
dangerous areas I guess but
even the most dangerous areas that I
that I know are
[Music]
um
I maybe don't feel like super
comfortable being there but it's not
like anything ever happened to me when I
went to such areas
so yeah I already already meeting the
parents no I didn't meet her parents but
she wants to bring her parents next time
whenever that is yeah
I'm looking forward to that
oh oh
that just reminds me of something but
let me that share that information yet
[Music]
oh wait he wanted something intimidating
so we would intimidate them maybe we
wanted to speak to him that is red boys
listen
you're going to speak to your boss and
tell him to back off I've touched the
way you want to play it fine Bryce will
be all over reviews on news tomorrow
morning
maybe the best way to get a message to
your boss is for me to send him your
heart
how'd you like that
if you don't talk
your lovers career is over
[\h__\h] the meat
are we gonna follow and shoot
eliminate the black man okay okay
well one light is off and another light
is off
wait I can blow it up right I can I can
also just blow it up like last time plus
I didn't want it so this time I think
they would let me blow it up
the police
I've escaped from them a million times
now they really oh I already lost them
I can switch to the other side right
together
I'm going to handle this
[Music]
all right the guys are dead I'm taking
back to your place wonderful and once
again
seems like police oh
[\h__\h]
I am at the crime scene but I have
nothing to do with it
my car being really [\h__\h] up is no
proof of anything
that didn't work out so good at least
they can't tell Dimitri about the
meeting or go to the papers Dmitry is
too much of a red to go to the medium
self the information he has on Price is
too valuable you think
about that when he started dating you
not that there's anything wrong with
dating oh choice is your choice we
should have thought about who it was
before getting elected on the family
values ticket it preaches homosexuality
as evil it's Insanity he's a hypocrite
and there was only a matter of time
before someone like Dmitry tried to
capitalize [\h__\h] I'll shut up now you
don't need me telling you about your
life I don't normally talk this much
oh wow that's like
he's really getting Nico to show his
sweet and soft boiled egg side
cute
really cute oh nice car
yeah
look after yourself yeah I hope the man
can we even drop him off at home
it's like we just went on a date soon
he loves me it's so cute
[Music]
me out of the car
I will take it now I just wanted to see
how it feels about me taking it soon
was pretty
it's probably gonna go wee wall I don't
care
no
[Music]
if you have a car like this you should
[\h__\h] alarm system into it
this one has no alarms I remember what
what hey I actually have nothing left on
This Island right now only over here
are we done
are we done oh yeah
Phil Bell or Derek both of them are new
people
are we ready to move on
hmm
oscon
go to D
erek first
okay
New Missions but I met them before
really I don't remember the names
[Music]
okay yeah so
told you about
London told you about ninar
I wonder if there's still stories from
Japan that I wouldn't tell but
is there something you guys can think of
that I should have told you but I didn't
New Jersey
Hollow Birds
foreign
I told you about everybody bringing
snacks right
and besides that I I told you about
updating urui about new jeans
[Music]
um
what else
the purple video now showed me some
it was really cute I told Pomo she was a
little bit angry at Mina
[Music]
yeah I don't know I I can tell you
what can what can I tell you I can tell
you that there will be a hului
collaboration next week
and I am actually I'm I wanted to ask
you guys uh for ideas because like so
far
we did garlic phone before right and
then we've only tear that can we did
um
a [\h__\h] yell
we did worms before and I kind of want
to play worms again but at the same time
I was thinking I wanted to be a game
that
um will be
like has several point of views and
would be on everybody's Channel I don't
want it to be just um
or like one POV you know
or Pico Park would be cute too actually
but that's also a one POV game
worms is great yeah I was I was really
thinking of worms but
um
but we did it before already I don't
know I want to do something else
[Music]
stop blackmailing my friends
anger me more
give up the contract
to work together I will cut you in Nico
let's be friends no I made the mistake
of working with you before it's not one
I'll repeat
goodbye bye bye Dimitri
yeah
we've been waited
I told them to turn on their rating
thing for me so I can rate them back
sometime
we're in the middle of GTA
GTA
g-a
and we just arrived in New Jersey what's
New Jersey called in this game
what is this island called let's say no
good morning what did they apologize for
today
what did they
clear up today
take care of family hey
Beyond being taken care of now hey hey
hey bloops
your brother said you needed the hand
looks like you need more than that yeah
yeah cool the same blue because it
sounded like boob
okay
is it a reference to 7-Eleven
oh
that's pretty good gear
okay
good for you
don't get sanctimonious on me
okay
why'd they do this to you it was here
because it feels nice
it feels better to be high than not
does it stop you thinking don't stop you
Karen
which is even better like Nico is
getting nicer and nicer every day
hack his brother what do you care about
I care about
claimed I was a grass people use that to
steal [\h__\h] off me
huh
maybe that's what your brother was
talking about and when they said you
needed help taking care of all the
business
sure
I mean
a saint
I ain't a man of principle
all right I messed up
but I tried
I made a mistake thank you but I admit
it we all make mistakes exactly what do
we do and this guy is still threatening
to kill me and my family
what's his name we'll kill him
Bucky Sligo Bucky Sligo he was living in
Albany kind of name is that
can you get more memberships thank you
sure
find the [\h__\h]
um shut him what is that name this piles
up
violence
is always the option and the the
solution in this game only only violence
nothing else
nothing else matters
find the cop car okay we're looking for
cop car again ah
well that was easy there's not even
anyone inside
oh my God I got in trouble when there's
no one inside
he locked it at least
oh
nothing I've ever done
nice okay e
uh search police records by name what
was it Bucky slico
I think
right
Bucky's Lego
is that his real name whoa this is so
weird the keyboard is really weird
um what what oh my God
I just pressed the keys once and it just
skips over free
eh I could just type oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm mad Burger Shot Elder knee hit and
run uh-huh
he looks
kind of like a nice guy but apparently
he's not a nice guy
wow wow we'll teach him a lesson
hi police friend hey Derek apparently
your guy hangs out at the Burger Shop in
the Alderly go check it out let's make
sure it's pour into that I want them all
to paint
[\h__\h] you'll do is run back to his crew
come on Howard the product everyone go
down then him take a ball alone
I guess he did man convenient when it's
done
okay all right we're gonna take him down
all of them probably he'll be alone
because they're already like hinted at
him being alone and then running to his
friends
very good
I I like a little way
a little Murder Party
uh how do I turn on Sirens again
G
[Music]
armor no I have pop armor I think I'd
love I'll be fine
[Music]
hey it's on the highway they all moved
away
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
no okay
I saw about the game
[Music]
huh I wanted the worms too but I don't
know don't feel I feel like
ah I feel bad like I don't want it to be
only on my channel and we could do it on
like Subaru's Channel or so but
um I think best is to have a something
on everybody's Channel
I can't think of a good game I I was
reminded of
um Don't Starve Together
but I don't know if it's so interesting
it what about rafts
although Raph is also it feels like a
game that is supposed to be played
with uh over the course of several
streams I want something that's like for
one stream only
[Music]
left for that that's for four people
right we're five we need a game that
works for five people
[Music]
are you really suggesting valorent to me
wait what
foreign
[Music]
did he run through here
don't lose Bucky stick with him
uh I am trying to I don't know where he
is though oh I think down there okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
[\h__\h]
is he on foot
I feel like he's
pretty slow but yeah he runs through all
these like alleys he must be on foot
[Music]
Chase
why ah no he's in the car [\h__\h] [\h__\h] no
this is bad this is bad this is bad this
is bad this is bad I'm gonna lose I'm
gonna lose him I'm gonna lose him I'm
gonna lose him I'm gonna lose him
did he go through here no but we're
going through oh nice
I got a shortcut
s okay okay okay ah [\h__\h] no not here you
found back his crew oh really oh I
thought the chase wasn't over yet okay
uh take down the whole gang all right
are they just chilling there
they are um
[Music]
wonderful hello everybody
we're about to meet you
I am takanashikiara and I'm here for
justice
I will serve you justice
which weapon will we go for maybe this
one again
[Music]
hey police on my side hold on what side
is that one
what is it
well now they're against me
at least the door is closed
so the police can
[Music]
[\h__\h] my HP is [\h__\h] is this script that
does police always join this oh God oh
God oh free stuff no
no
[Music]
was it the last one
no
that was
mean I I'm I I am a police guy okay
honey
I'm a policeman they they have to help
me
go fit
um
[Music]
I don't know that seems a little bit
maybe we'll go for garlic phone after
all kind of like feels just so good and
if we were four we had so much more
options but we're just we're fine
foreign
is surprisingly fun
I'll look into it
uh what am I where are we
what ah police car first right
might as well
[Music]
all right
and I probably need new armor now
is there one there is no oh no wait
there is there is there is this thing
nice nice let me just take this
what the [\h__\h]
now a jackbox came I would do jackbox
but I don't think if even I struggle
with Jack box
games then I think Subaru and Louis
would also struggle
also struggle yeah
you need to be pretty damn fluent to be
able to keep up with jackbox games yeah
it's not even about the n a focus topics
because I found out that in the newer
games there's some way you can turn that
off
yeah uh Gang Beast
oh I know ultimate chicken horse is four
people right
right
pretty sure
God damn it why is everything for people
damn it hey Derek apparently your guy
hangs out that the burger shop in the
elderly go check it out DVD is fine
I want us to play something more bright
and and happier I don't know not
something scary alone
[Music]
you know
it's Pummel party for ah there it was
it's Pomo party for five
seconds
was just like one of those
uh games where you have like a little
little uh
man that's like wobbling and you is that
is it like I played before right
yeah it's like isn't it like Gang Beasts
Duck game has five
[Music]
okay I'm prepared that game Duck game I
heard about that one I don't remember
what that one was like
I think you can buy the RPG now
[Music]
it's Mario party for PC what duck games
if that is true
then
Hummer party
is Mario party but for him for PC
really
doesn't have like mini games and stuff
it's good with the right people okay
okay play it up but I don't remember it
being like Mario Party
good I was gonna pee on my bed
with them
I don't connect that with the game
memory
yeah it must have been a long long long
time ago
[Music]
okay I'll think about it so Pummel party
or Karthik phone again or why can't
people drive in this country
warm worms but I don't want it to be on
only one channel
[Music]
because
there'll be some info shared that
I hope reaches as many people as
possible you know
Smashbox but Smash Bros is also just for
all these games are just for people but
we're five keep that in mind
[Music]
eh what Nanny
okay we're chasing again guys Focus
what if I kill him now
is that even possible
ah he's in the car
did I skip the sing last song
well I don't know if shooting or trying
to shoot him much here is really
meaningful
he drove through here
how about the fence is not broken
what do they just respawn immediately
[Music]
oh there he is
those are some strong shrubs right I
mean I've never tried driving with a car
through shrubs
but
can you
oh he lost the tire
we've done good damage I think that
might be slowing him down a little bit
but we're also better at keeping up this
time because now I know
where he's going all the time
I'm more aware of it
[Music]
I could try to kill him already but we
want to kill all of them anyway right so
hey
so true don't you hear the police siren
we're doing a wild wild goose chase
why can I not shoot
[Music]
ah wait I'm trying to shoot what is he
doing
oh okay
out of Emma no I'm not it was weird I
could have totally killed him there but
not the police
again is this bound to happen
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
it
why
down
there it's around it I'm not gonna kill
the cops this time but what am I gonna
do
[\h__\h]
no please oh okay
[Music]
oh
can I avoid this
situation
what did I do
[Music]
sorry
hey
should I leave I'm trying to get rid of
the cops and then come back but am I not
gonna lose the mission if I
hey
I was thinking of around the grenade at
the end but it wouldn't let me
was taking too much time and I was dying
anyway
[Music]
um
I saw I saw the cops eventually uh at
the end they're aiming for
a Dem for a moment but I think they were
also still aiming at me
at first anyway they're definitely
aiming only for me they don't care about
the
I don't care about those people
will try the melee them yeah yeah that
was a problem
they were he was trying to melee them
try going in by the back to have less
Witnesses
need to hide from the cops so they kill
the criminal
can I really do that
Mario Kart line of fun all of you have
different yeah maybe I don't know maybe
Mario Kart
maybe oh I have an idea
maybe a challenge where
um we play against viewers as five
and we have to get number one we have to
get first place otherwise we were not
allowed to share the information
the information
but what the freak what if we actually
because five is quite a big number
uh
it might be easier
than
yeah
um
[Music]
you guys gotta bring out the big guns
to race against us
what was was it Bucky's Lego
it's gonna be a long stream I think so
you think so
um
wait for uh Mario Kart how many
how many people is it in one Mario Kart
race was it 12
so seven people racing against us
apparently you're
I think it's a good idea though
I like the idea
that the Burger Shot in the elderly go
check it out let's make sure it's pour
into there I went there
he'll see you I think you're taking him
down
[Music]
like everyone go down let him take a
ball alone why do you not think MK is a
good idea give me give me a good reason
my car no I don't think we can play
Pokemon unite anymore
after the tournament
I think it's only
time limited right now
I don't really see it I don't think it's
a bad idea
because we can banter
[Music]
while playing a two
and we can strengthen our bond by trying
our best to do teamwork against all the
odds there that are up against us
like there's always lag in Mario Kart
but in the end Lego I played it with
International people all the time and
it never really was
an issue during the race maybe there's
some disconnects even every now and then
but mostly it's fine and you get a
chance to race against Polo Tony I mean
how can you even turn this down I want
to do more viewer participation things
anyway I haven't been doing so many
recently
um
take a few of these options to hold a
Tony and I'm gonna let them decide what
they want to do okay
democracy is a democracy
my chance stopped moving again but I see
it in OBS hello hello
[Music]
[\h__\h] this I was looking at the chats
ah it's coming back
[Music]
ah
no no no I already said are you guys not
listening sometimes I wonder I already
said jackbox we can't play that because
of um
their English is
like nice but I don't think it's good
enough for jackbox I mean some games
maybe
but you're gonna be fast and witty
even I struggle with Jack books
so
like we could only play like maybe some
drawing games for example but still
I'll think about it but yeah
[Music]
pasmo also four people
I'm talking about
anyway this discussion is over I have my
a couple of suggestions thank you very
much
why is the game lagging so hard right
now
it crashed
just crashed
cool we have to redo it again
at least it didn't crash in the middle
of the the shooty part
they don't want me to finish this
Mission I've I'm getting the same vibe
[Laughter]
uh even my voice almost crashed really
yeah sometimes when something like this
happens
apparently my voice becomes a little bit
robotic sometimes
the game really doesn't want you to
complete this Mission this mission is
really
it's really a little bit massive messing
with my confidence because like last
stream I was like
just zooming through all the missions
quickly everything was a walk in the
park
oh no sound though
and suddenly this little mission
is trying to mess with me
why why is this one so difficult it
feels like inevitable
to have the
police on my butt
but I'll try to enter from behind but
don't they already know that I'm coming
so
hmm
is there even a back entrance
hello
sound
how many times do I have to fix you
hello
moshimoshi
game sound
the problem is I also only hear it when
I tap in so it's a bit difficult how
about now no
the [\h__\h]
you are angering me
game scuffed
yeah
a little bit
here come on come on unbelievable have
you tried turning it off and on you mean
the game or the sound for yes both
because it just restarted the game
um
[Music]
interesting
how it's messing with me
should be on
dub over the game with your own effect
like that
sounds like I'll never catch a freaking
break though
don't worry guys I'll fix it
come on I'll restart it again
because it's acting funny
um
Rockstar Games
are sounding pretty quiet right now not
much of a rock star are you
everything else is working properly it's
just because the game crashed and
restarted now it's messing up everything
does Minecraft work now no I don't know
not yet I'm focused on the freaking
Pokemon tournament
one by one I can't I can't I can't I
can't
I'm supposed to hear something right now
too right
no I don't hear it either
you and me we both don't hear it
I cannot hear the game
no if I want to restart the Galaxy I
have to restart the whole computer which
might fix everything
I don't want to do that
yeah oh yeah it's yeah
it's one of those moments though
it'll be really fast
it will be really fast don't worry guys
see you in a moment
[\h__\h] sake
hey
say something
hello
am I back
yeah
hurt her tightness
her tightness
okay good let's hope it works now her
tightness that reminds me of uh
I saw atelier's new game
um
no no what did I do
yeah I I can't even I don't I know it's
too long it's so high the name is so
difficult to say
how do you say The Game's name is
and yeah apparently it's gonna be a
mobile game
even though it's supposed to be a main
release right
I saw this this part I don't understand
because I I guess I don't know all these
Atelier terms but people were saying
things like it's an it's a numbered
title
and
that means something I guess
but it looked really good the trailer
was really pretty and and honestly it
looked like a normal Atelier game like
quality wise
yeah it's it's a main title so there
should be proper story and the trailer
did look like it had proper story the
graphics were beautiful as always and
the character designs were beautiful as
always it's like like a normal Atelier
game but they they made it so that it
plays on the phone
when you can't judge it yet guys you
can't
I know I know I saw like Atelier fans
were kind of upset
um and I personally prefer PC games over
over
um there we go
over uh phone games too but
it so far it looks pretty normal
um
okay sounds
you will bow to me
uh why I heard myself I heard YouTube
for example
I will not accept this
hi
please
this should make sounds too right this
no the game is not muted in Windows
I keep on Switching the sound output
and honestly it should be working but
like this is my usually what makes
things work
um
why why does it not want to work
about Wawa
it's getting on my nerves it's actually
annoying me
I want to stream
feeling
please let me let me play GTA
please
[Laughter]
I'm sorry
um
staying true to the
somewhat German
uh stereotypes I'm Austrian though
foreign
I'm gonna not stream so long today but
not this I only stream for two hours
verify the game cash what how's that
like
you can hear it on your side no no I
can't
I could hear YouTube but not this I can
hear myself too
um
foreign
Ty
um
this is just a game yeah let me try a
different game really quickly but I
won't show you
I won't show it on stream
[Music]
um
oh I hear I see it
that there is sound output like you know
I see the the the
I see the visuals of it
on Windows
but
it doesn't
wanna talk to me
it's just
routed wrong
but I can't seem to fix it maybe now
maybe now
sound settings is literally where I am
at the whole time thank you
do you have a controller no not right
now I know that's a that's a common
issue so I don't have it plugged in
foreign
let me try again
no give me the Bell bam give me that I
want to hear that
please
it's like I cursed Myself by saying this
will be a shorter
[Music]
no I keep on Switching the sound device
of GTA 4.
let me go for every single one of them
I always have to keep going back in
and back out
I'm I just feel like recently I've been
very unlucky
um
I feel like there is is a ghost thing
because you know how about uh after my
debut I had many technical problems and
now Advent debuted and it's like
some ghosts are haunting me and they're
like hey debut that's a nice word I
remember you debut time it's when you
had all the technical problems let me
bring that back to you that memory it's
a such a nice memory for us ghosts
[Music]
um
I don't know how to fix this
output in in-game settings I never saw
that before wait
oh and then it's just like the stereo
headphone stereo
but
um I don't think that does anything
unfortunately
[Music]
um
what what do you mean unplug oh PS are
you kidding me
yeah the other game didn't make a sound
either
oh man I feel like it's ruined at this
point
um why did it have to crash
[Music]
foreign
I'm going to lose it
I am going to lose my mind
I was already not in a good mood these
past couple days
I could
I I would appreciate it if
things like this
just don't go wrong for no reason but
I'm just doing everything that I can
to make things work
the the things I just like tried to like
move some cables and it immediately
makes the go XLR so angry that even
though I see on it that the visuals like
my sound it's still picking up my
microphone but it will just not work
anymore on on the PC
so then it doesn't fix itself until I I
restart my PC but that's also partially
to do with you know
um goalk2r not having [\h__\h] support
anymore
because I don't know the team was like
[\h__\h] it
foreign
[Music]
ah
what
are you guys hearing me for my usual
microphone because I just attached a
different microphone but OBS isn't
finding it
uh
what
the [\h__\h]
I'm
I'm so angry
I feel like can I hear myself I don't
know anymore maybe I don't know
I even I brought over my my cooking
microphone
I brought over my cooking microphone
uh
I'm so [\h__\h] angry
because my microphone stopped working
just now and what is going on
does this sound normal to you
oh okay
you are going to comply
you are going to comply I said
or I'm going to cry
I'm I'm going to cry
but wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
hello oh my God what what is that sound
holy wow
terrible oh the game
again
well I only hear myself in one ear
[Music]
why do I only hear myself in one ear
well do you guys also only hear me in
one ear
um
Xbox microphone
[Applause]
it's a Yeti it's a Blue Yeti
um
both channels what
what do you hear Do you hear it
in one or two
it doesn't sound like one okay
um so I disconnected the go XLR but my
microphone is only works it needs
something like the girl XR in order to
work my blue yeti however is an
independent [\h__\h] microphone and can
live and work on its own
maybe the Shure sm7b should learn from
that
and cut itself off
a slice of that loaf of bread
yeah it's a strong independent mic
now because I think you know all these
things are intervening with each other
and that's why the sound is [\h__\h] up
um
now the game doesn't show up in my
oh yeah
the game doesn't even show up in my
games in my in my sound
thing I think I've I'm
I'm
losing it
I will restart this game I feel like my
mouse is also not working properly
anymore
[Laughter]
things are just not going well for me
I think so just now going well
why am I still here trying
why am I still trying
oh oh now it's working properly because
I didn't plug it properly and the the
headphones
okay I hear myself in both ears at least
um
but this is not really the quality I
would like to deliver to you guys
you know that right
anyway
GTA
that was [\h__\h] loud
um
Mamma Mia
wait wait how wait uh
wait wait wait wait I got it to I got
the sound to work in my ears
but do we really want to play like this
though
I don't think so
oh
wait I don't understand this
oh there's sounds but what caused
I'm going to lose it I'm going to lose
it
oh my God
hmm
cooking everything
I don't know I don't know if it's smart
to continue yeah it fixed it's somehow I
made it work but do we really want to
continue like this I don't know
[Music]
I don't think so
but this mic picks up everything it's
not good
it picks up
oh my God
well I still have to adjust volume sorry
um
[Music]
ah
well oh fancy apartment
uh Mamma Mia why why
ah
we can't stream like this
I'm gonna give you guys heart attacks
constantly
whenever I scream and I scream a lot in
this game
I'm too low on my volume
lower
the game
everything
but the thing is the problem is it
doesn't have an equalizer this thing
doesn't have an equalizer that's the
problem
that's why I love my sure and my ghost
and I'll be loud when I'm loud but this
is like it sucks
or a compressor whatever it's called um
can I add a compressor an OBS I don't
know does it have that let me see
there's an up yeah wait there's a
compressor I don't know if it works well
though uh
uh
I don't know what to do with these
settings uh
I
I don't know what it does
ratio
ratio ratio ratio ratio
ratio ratio ratio ratio it's always the
same
huh
I don't think this is the compressor
that I wanted maybe the upward
compressor
L plus ratio ratio
ratio ratio ratio ratio oh
uh uh uh uh I think that's it this one's
it maybe ratio
ratio no maybe not
I don't know what the [\h__\h] is me with
output threshold fresh oh
uh uh
oh this is it
ratio ratio
Horatio
this is so not for the effort but none
of this is worth the effort
before I lose my [\h__\h] mind I think I
should end the Stream
just none of this is worth it this is
not [\h__\h] life
I'm so sorry
I'm gonna lose my mind so I better leave
um
thank you for suffering with me
laughs
we should have played Pokemon ultimate
uh unite unite we should have played
Pokemon United
this was a mistake
maybe I'll put up another stream where I
play Pokemon unite if I can fix my
problems
yep
okay
I'm so traumatized
biotechnical issues
and in German we say
Alfred us in
I'm sorry I couldn't really fix it
nobody is more sorry than I am
about this
see you in at the in the worst case in
like
nine hours no 10 hours I could sleep
that's so much time
wow the stream was funny regardless
thank you
um the the short amount of time we had
together was definitely enjoyable
until the game crashed
hmm
thank you guys
I'm sorry
I'm currently cursed
bye bye
what's guys
I know
Pokemons
yeah mind break entertainment let's go
it's been a while since my mind has been
broken so
maybe it was necessary to bring me back
down to earth so I'm not so cocky
anymore
thinking that everything will work
everything is always going well no no no
no no no no no no
I I'm out of here bye bye
yay yay and this misery
foreign
[Music]
why Skype you can Skype with a good
quality microphone
[Music]
puppet make oh yeah I only make puppets
when I'm mind broken
I should make some puppets
[Music]
I it was already thinking about me
having to make Advent puppies
this Christmas
yeah
I'll make a Advent skit
this year puppets not puppies did I say
puppies I said puppets
[Music]
no I said puppets
tormented Patrol
[Music]
maybe it's better this way
so I can practice
[Music]