[Music]
do
we're just listening to some music
yeah it's like opera or something i
don't know
what the hell is that opera
i gotta are you hearing something else i
get it uh no not really i don't think so
it's like a bum bum but i got like a kfp
chicken nugget in my hand
[Music]
chicken nuggets in your hand
yeah
oh wait is a bit too loud well that's
that's
like
[Music]
did you hear that what did that discord
muted
i heard it it was good
it's just random
okay
well we're back wait did you just sing
as well i didn't hear it oh no i didn't
let you try to recreate that spell go
beautiful
beautiful oh yeah
i think he was like
you know i've lost my job i'm just too
good at opera i'm out of here
uh i found some uh
crack rocks here
rocks yeah
uh today guys we're doing it a bit
differently we're uh just gonna do like
we're gonna talk to one another the
whole time
uh because i think you guys kind of
requested it so instead of doing the
walkie-talkie thing we're just gonna be
talking constantly uh hopefully
so
uh please enjoy i hope you
uh like it that way no one has an issue
with that
and you're supposedly finishing the game
today
yeah
supposedly
wait how many chapters are there chat
well then uh sorry if you guys in my
stream hold on one second uh how many
chapters are there
[Music]
i think i started you know it's okay
though because uh
at this point it doesn't matter last
time it kind of mattered but this time
it doesn't matter um i think we switched
rose again
oh
okay
it doesn't matter right
yeah that doesn't matter but i i started
out uh somewhere else than where i left
off last time like last time
yeah
that's where i am
i don't remember so
[Music]
okay how about now is i'm not so loud
anymore now
[Music]
what hello
wow
in obs she
still wait let me let me lower all of
this
is that
a lower and obs
[Music]
well
okay can you just say something normally
not
not screaming
oh uh testing hello
wait can we switch because now i have
all the potions and these are like
you're the potion lady
you're the watson concoction manager
okay
you'll be fine we'll figure it out
together amen
so i'm in a
church
looking
place
oh
[Music]
okay and i remember
i see
i see weird
drawings with
weird names i see uh mushrooms mushrooms
it's like mushrooms i don't like
mushrooms either but i think they're
cute
cute yes has to look so dumb or indeed
cute i have to agree with that
uh
uh wait i have to turn myself a little
bit up and obvious okay
uh tell me guys is it better now i don't
know it's only a little bit
you'll have to deal with it
i should be fine
and i see a blackboard that has
um
[Music]
sorry i was just i ran into something i
thought i got electrocuted
i have a blackboard that shows me
letters and their connections but the
letters are like always like two letter
combinations
what like what
like
uh
o h o l p f o t p a
like for example o h is like
a creator or or whatever about okay okay
hello otp and then out of ot is facebook
and pajamas
okay yeah i see it i see it stuff like
that maybe you've seen it last time when
you when you left off when you before
you ended the game maybe you
saw this oh anyway i don't think so but
i i do have um like this little
uh potion turner where i can go through
different potions and their different
colors and have different pictures on
them i also have a book um
that sounds like the letters you're
describing but instead it uh it just has
the letters and then like the full name
next to it so like uh
eric savor babe
yeah i didn't say that right uh and then
i got another book it's got some rocks
in it
and there's a blue rock a blue rock uh
and then plus the kfp chicken nugget
rock and then if you put all those rocks
together it makes a red rock but then i
put my rocks inside the oven that i saw
and i can't take them out and it says
that i need a third rock but i only have
two of them
ah okay i found the one you just said
paraxia braids uh i have that written on
some of my posters uh-huh one of my
posters
um
yeah so i
what does it look like
uh looks like an animal like a cute cute
animal um like a crab with a shell
it was a purple or yellow
oh i don't have colors on them oh is it
like a drawing and a name is it like a
pointy shell or like a round shell with
a flower
a rounded pill with a flower
okay i have that potion but i don't know
what to do with it so
it's called hermit crab
oh
yeah is that h silent in that word no no
not all day
english inconsistent language
maybe somewhere because like you have
those thingies connected
maybe somewhere there's like a
guide on what to do with the potions
maybe i have to make the rock oh
you said you need yeah you need a third
rank yeah this like
on my blackboard it all leads up to
one red rock oh okay i suppose we're
making a red rock
okay
but on my on my recipe book it says
blue a blue a dark blue rock plus a
light lighter blue rock plus the kfp
nugget rock equals the red rock so i
don't know if maybe like one of your
combinations makes the blue rock because
i already have the other two
uh yeah yeah i have like three three uh
combinations make the red rocks but uh
the three like each of the three um
combinations is made out of
other combinations and that combination
is made out of landfill and so on and so
on so i think we have to start from the
bottom
which
says
p e and f r what or is it d e d e no
that's a d
or is it is
[Music]
oryx
i have that in my book
and it's uh it's a it's it's like a it's
like a flower that's like bells like a
but but ah the others also look like
bells this one has
a leaf on the right side
no
a leaf at the top
two two leaves
uh two small leaves on each flower
and there's like
uh
on each bell i guess
they're kind of like
how they
where's the difference between they look
so similar um on the very bottom of the
flower there's like two round balls
they're like
hanging down like grapes
oh
yeah
you made me do you think you got it
yeah yeah i see it i got it yeah i see
it whoa
that's the pristoxy forex
okay and then the other one you said was
what do you what
ah the other one was fr like proud
[Music]
hungry brahmos
um
it has one big body that's made up out
of three umbrellas
and then at the bottom it has like
a handle
a mushroom
yeah it's a mushroom
okay purple triple backer yeah
it might feel so big
i got it so good
i think do i like mix them
yeah you should make some and that turns
into
tv peanut butter
okay
i got it yeah
peanut butter
if we can make a ammo in the am
oh
but for that we need
ox okay that is
oxymericosaurus
oxymeocsaurus
wonderful i see it
it's um
what do you call those screaming plants
dreaming plants
what are they called again but they look
like they look like um
they look like a carrots
ah mandrakora
mandra
[Applause]
okay i mixed that with the peanut butter
this is like there's several ones
there's one the one that i mean is like
a fin solo one oh okay and it has like
uh one leaf on the left that's higher
than the one on the right
no no it has three leaves coming out of
the head uh
three leaves yeah
and they're like the first the one one p
pokes up to the top the other one
is like in the middle and the other one
i don't have that one i think we'll have
to make something like that is there
like
i don't know this one is
uh
this one's only used to make other
things but it just doesn't show
like it's a basic basal component i
think
[Music]
pb was made out of p e and f r but o x
is like a base component
unless we can do it the other way around
like
going both directions
like like making out of pb making p e
and uh
yeah i think there's like an extractor
yeah there's an extractor
oh
yeah you can split it into two in that
case
if you have because we are trying to
make
am right now i guess i don't know if you
even have am or po that we would be able
to extract ox i don't know what those
are i'll just read the names we need ox
but no we need we need pb and ox in
order to make a.m
so rx is part of am and ox is part of a
different one people what makes ox again
uh
i am and p-o
okay wait what makes the ones
uh
what is them
wait when you say what makes ox um like
there's nothing here that says ox is
made by this and this but you can split
um
two other ones
okay so what what are the two other ones
that you could split it
um
uh
am and po
so basically there's a tree here okay
from the very bottom that it was p e and
f r we did that and we got pb and then
if we would move upwards
um if we combine pb with a certain ox we
would get am uh but yeah but i don't i
don't know what like
i don't know what the image is so i
don't know what to grab to try to split
so what are the letters again so i can
read you the full
uh oh
i don't know
the ones that that splits from
a m
and p o
okay prime mix
prima
primexio felixo
primaxil that sounds like a harry potter
spell max
oh yeah yeah i have that premaxio filexo
it's uh it's a cute one it's
uh it's like two daisies um it doesn't
have a color so it could also be not not
a daisy but
um
if we're ignoring the color it looks
like a daisy and it has two legs
and two leaves one on each flower
uh
there's two flowers
yeah it's two that connect to one
body
and it has really hairy legs it didn't
shave for quite some time
okay um
like the latin name of these flowers
probably not i think they made it up
[Music]
okay so you're looking for the mandrake
one
uh
probably yeah yeah yeah yeah because
like all of the all of the mandrake ones
no no not all of them almost all of them
start with
we have ox
osteomoraxirate and oxymoronta roxas and
oxymoraxorus which we
already
oh
we already made that one which one is
the one that where we need to make the
next one
now that we have the the one to mix with
pb or something
oh wait we have it
what
oh we have it we have the
the you mean wait oh x was uh
oxymoroxiris i don't know if that's the
one if that's the one that you described
as a mandrake then yes
well yeah there's several but this is
the one that we first
tried yeah yeah that's that's the one
that one together with pb is am
if
you still have the pbe right
uh yeah
okay
if you combine those i
[Music]
all in all it has a very thin body
and
like i see one that you probably mean
when you say old
where like the eyes are really big
no that's not the one the one that i'm
talking about it has like
um two arrows facing inwards as the eyes
and it has kind of a mustache
but a very thin body
free leaves
and
mean they're all kind of not not all of
them two of them have three leaves
yeah there's two
two under my drag case that have
three leaves
and it's the thinner one out of those
two
okay
as i can
[Music]
all right can we start again from the
one that you said looks like a dandelion
oh yeah
uh
that was
[Music]
what what was that which one what which
two letters without supposed to be p oh
i don't know because the the potion
bottles don't have like any of the names
on them i just have the translation for
the
um what is it called like when you
shorten a word
apparently yeah
abbreviation yeah i just have the
abbreviation key
but not like what potion it corresponds
to
uh
wait so i think we're yeah that was p.o
primoco philexo
and it's a daisies when one has a
leaf on the left and then a leaf on the
right
exactly the splitting stems
exactly and long hairy legs and from
that i'm supposed to get
yeah if you split that one you should be
able to get ox and one that is like
sensing okay
but i don't know
that's the only one that's censored
which is uh
correct annoying press x you brystaxio
luarborite
chrystextio
chris
[Music]
no
i do not have that anymore
i guess it's like the secret ingredient
that's intense i guess yeah okay so
from the daisy uh besides the pl one so
the other one that we got oh can you
describe how that one looks
uh wait what wait which one do you want
me to describe uh i split the daisy ones
and then there should be other than the
censored one there's the other one
they're all right yeah
[Music]
with three leaves
yeah it has uh it has three leaves it
has a face so the thin carrot yeah and i
mix it with what i mix ox with what
uh well uh you mix ox with pb and then
you get am
uh can you confirm the uh
identification of peepee
pb
was uh
peepee
be was
wasn't that for stock studio forex
um the one with the three
bell flowers and the cherries at the
bottom
okay
uh
that's the triple one
crack plus
that one plus ox is a um
okay i think i need to make the kfp
juice again which is uh
because i used it and i i got the wrong
thing apparently
because uh when i mix the things
i think you told me all i got was the uh
blue
well you can't tell the color but
it's a old looking mandrake with two
leaves
oh
that's not the one right
nah it doesn't look old no i mean i mean
if you only see that one maybe you do
think that one looks great but
out of all the ones i have
it looks like more of the younger one
oh
um well well the one that you got do all
of the leaves
like stand up straight
oh it only has two leaves
and they're flopping down
ah you have to do that one you have oh
wait you have the olio or mignole
oh that's the right one
i don't know does it anywhere say what
ally will make now what the abbreviation
for that is
what are you saying with an o or an a
[Music]
i only have o through
um
i only have things that start with o p d
f
that's it
i don't know
i can't tell you
wait but you said two leaves that are
flopping down
yeah
and that's this one
oh
well that would probably be a.m
that's right wait so
right now
you
well
and you can you can make like that's a
wait sorry i need i need one thing for
clarification the things that you carry
like for example the the flower is that
an actual flower that you're holding no
it's a potion
okay so a potion that's made out up out
of that flower i guess
something like that okay
so but it has like what like
how do you recognize the
the plants and stuff on it ah because
the potion has it just has a picture on
it and so i'm just going off a base of
like like based off what you described
okay
and there's a name on it as well right
no there's no names on them i only have
a book that has the abbreviation and
then the full name next to it but not
connected in any way to identifying the
potions oh okay
uh and in that book
does it say anywhere what am stands for
no
oh
okay well let me tell you that one is
allio mignon
and that's the one we need at like we
are pretty up high in that uh
um
yeah in the chain we need we need to mix
am with p.o
but
wait we have p.o or not i'm i'm confused
i probably gotta start from the bottom
if it's one of the top ones
or uh sorry yeah oh let me check the
name
po would be made out of like one of the
the censored one and ox oh okay
i don't think i can create the lick so
oh but i have the censored one
oh you have it oh yeah which one is ox
again
oh x's
[Music]
the thin carrot
okay have one of those i can't wait
you have one of those oh yeah
okay then combine the censored one with
alex and we should get p.o
uh p.o is just it's the dandelion one
i think
sorry daisy one
okay so you have that one too then we
have am and po okay so i just mix them
yeah then we get pf which is one of the
three components the main three
components for the stones
finished and we only need to do two more
okay i have pf
yes
[Music]
nice nice i thought you were saying no
at first no no no
no nice
yeah okay then put that one on the side
and we start with the second one
okay
okay let's do um
let's do i guess i'll start with the one
that's right next to p-o we need p-o and
f-a let's start with p-o
oh wait we already have p-o
piano oh the flower the two flowers ah
but i used it so i have to make another
one another one yeah
[Music]
which means we need the censored one
oh uh i have another one of those
okay then p o with f a f a do you have
the name for that
uh funky barracks
funky
down fungi barracks
yeah this one oh okay i see it this is
already going much better than last time
i think we talked much more yeah it's
good stuff sangha is like funky down
with those funky you're gonna get really
funky a man
chad are you following are we smarter
than you this time
so
the funky fungi it looks like um
it has one two
three four big ones big um
heads
of
umbrellas separately
and a lot of small ones sticking out on
the side as well
uh uh and one relatively big one in the
back but it's like shaded out like
it's in the back it's dark so four big
main ones although one of them is
rather small it's a rather small one on
the left
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
i think you found it okay so that one
combined with po gives us
the l no it doesn't give me anything i
think i have the wrong one so we'll
probably have to make whatever that will
because i mixed it together but nothing
popped out of the thingy
what
yeah
what p p o and f a didn't give me
anything
p f and yeah okay okay so is there like
a chain for fa
uh no
both of the ones that i told you oh i
thought you said psf it's uh no p.o
oh which one is that again
p oh is the one that has the censored
one in it um
the double flower
double flower yeah we need to make that
one again we used it before but i
thought you had another one of that no i
think i used it
or something else
okay so if we need to remake it then um
uh do you have
the censored one from before yeah the
the the the the fourier er ali
the olds the old carrot that you said
that had two floppy
uh
leaves one to the one side one to the
other side that's the censored one
you don't have that one anymore
uh
how did we get that before
uh i remember
oh wait no that's damn i didn't which
one was the censored one
e-l
yeah
e-l was the centered one i didn't i
thought i thought it was pl
p l p l
p l
p l was p l
first taxi for no wait for 64 works
yeah that's the one that i
don't have written anyway right right
right uh
but wait you have access to the censored
one
l oh yeah i mixed it with the with the
one you told me i think and it didn't
give me anything
maybe i don't really have the
or umbrella thing that you were
describing
okay we have we have pf right now right
that is one of the three main components
okay
but in order to make that
we used
am npo and for po we need an ox and
spencer that the po one we need again
for the next one
wait do you have dl
anywhere
wait no wait i need to first ask what's
the variation i think i already asked
that what was the abbreviation for the l
alpha legislate
[Music]
but yes
do you have anything wait wait what is
here nothing
else
no extra recipes
no
[Music]
okay okay thinking time
thinking thinking time
thinking time
something is missing maybe we can start
with the one on the very left first
maybe that helps us
okay
okay dad would need
fb and pg like facebook and pajamas
thunky
[Music]
that one
looks
uh like it has only one big umbrella and
only one
big hand
it's a very simple
nice nice
nice mushroom nice mushroom
it's very simple okay and then uh you
said p a
[Music]
oh um
paraceo philip sorry
all right that one is a cute crab it's
super cute there's a flower on his head
it has no flower but
it looks like a [\h__\h] pile the shell okay
i see it
it's like okay
all right
and it looks like it has a
whole eyes
but that that's that's ot that's ot what
does ot stand for does that say it
anywhere in your thingy
uh
[Music]
mirror
now it's okay we got a new one
okay uh
so
we need that one later for the middle
one no we don't need it okay so that we
so with ot and
pa that's the next one you need to make
uh we can get oh which is the next
opponent of the main three ones pa
what's the what's the full writing for
pa please
christexia oh philip sorry
for stacks you feel like sorry okay
that one looks like
five pieces of garlic
on one stick that has two big leaves
going on to the right side
all right i got it
nice then combine those two and we get
the third the third the third component
what i'm combining the garlic one and
then uh
mandrake yeah the old one yeah yeah
butthole
yeah
i feel like that didn't help us for the
next one the the one that we were first
working on but okay we got we got two
main components out of the three ones
okay then let's just reset let's reset
our brains
and start all over uh for the middle uh
uh component we're trying to get
a cute
cute ol a girl worker
okay um
p-o and f-a is the one that we're
starting off with remaxio felixio
[Music]
yes those are the two flowers we have
that currently right the two
flowers with one leaf each on one side
one to the left one to the right
no i don't have that one
that's the daisy one
the daisy one yeah no i didn't have it i
got a minute okay yeah that was our
problem before um
okay in order to make that one
we need ox and the censored one
[Music]
we made we made peel before
um
we had we had ox before as well what
does ox stand for
um
oxymercs source
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
so we need that and we need a censored
one which was
something i didn't have written on here
so i don't know what it looks like
how did we do that before
wait
[Music]
and you have
you oops do you have
the censored one you don't know which
one i mean
i haven't i have it oh you have it okay
and ox
[Music]
more umbrellas
waxes uh oxymoroxories that's that's the
fin
manderake oh yeah
we have to remake it
okay
we we made that one by splitting
a.m
i think no there it was a different one
that we split
wait it's super weird
[Music]
we split oh wait no no i don't know
do you just have p.o lying around sorry
if i keep on um
asking the same thing
then i'm gonna get it
p.o was
one of the flowers
[Music]
dude like
um
we had p.o before
and we split it and we got the centered
one and oh x out of that
but like can you get the same one wait i
have the uh i have the daisies now
the
daisies where primoxio philexo
which was was that p.o that was pew
right
then
that was
that was peel before right premaxio for
electro is peeled correct
uh
yeah
okay okay
okay uh
split that one no wait no way don't
split it
you have p.o uh-huh
oh
okay keep that one thing we need f a
then
f a stood for
uh
one of these
what does what does fa stand for
uh
hungary barracks
oh okay okay okay
we
[Music]
that one is the the one the mushroom
that has
um four big
umbrellas all separated and the small
one looks to the left side
[Music]
uh
yes but
it gave me okay yeah i got it
okay that one combined with p.o
uh ppo was
the one you just got before that
combine that to get dl what po is what
is that what
pl was the one that uh
should
be
the
two flowers
the double flower one with the
one with the leaf to the left and one
was the leaf to the right uh-huh
[Music]
oh you did it already
that says you already did it
you got the you got the dl already
you know where you combine them we got
the thing we need
okay
okay then we need the for the last third
big component we need to combine dl the
one that you already got with pl but pl
is something that's
it has
no
no daughter and no um
sun
it's it's just a crystal it's existing
on its own so i suppose oh i got it i
got a big uh mush ball with like
eyes and symbols and arms sticking out
what
eyes and symbols and mushrooms sticking
out
yeah
that's that's pl
or oh i combined the pl with the one you
told me too
the l
oh and you got the the next thing oh
that should be what does a whale stand
for can you check for me
uh
you're working fast mrs watson
oh l
uh oxymerotoxis
no wait uh sorry oxy lure breaks
yes okay yes let's combine that
with the other main big ones that we've
got do you need me to help you recall
which ones they were uh no but i only
have like
okay
we have
we have oel we have o-h and we have pf
those three make the stone
okay
[Music]
i thought you barely slept how are you
able to use your brain so much i don't
know maybe maybe it helps my brain
function
yeah maybe
you work better on
lack of sleep it's a detective life you
know
tell me more about detective life
oh so i can't get out of this room
though
well then i just gotta put the stone in
i think okay
all right well that's so cool
and you were down
you were doubting yourself
uh why wouldn't you do that i mean
the perfect local potion
i couldn't have done it any better
another bigger rock
oh what
i got a cutscene me too behold
you seeing the same i is a sword coming
together in your scene
[Applause]
[Music]
oh i try to laugh no
i already have that i don't need it
ah
the soul stone
restored
you've done it
not but flesh may hold the stone
until presented
before the throne
you
plead your path brilliantly mortal
now
it's time for you to exit the stage
in the kids
all
i require
no
unfortunately for that my gun
well
i am in need of your soul
i think it is almost at her highest
position
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay well i'm in a cage now so
[Music]
ah
thank you ghost is that
is that you
angry ghost
i don't know what the hell she's talking
about that man
huh
where are you
i'm i'm still following a ghost
okay is he helping you
oh it's still the cutscene
waiting faster
okay i'm out of the cutscene uh weird
ghost this is getting spoopy
uh uh uh
i'm gonna go left cause i'm left handed
are you left under the right hand and
now man i'm right-handed
okay
i expected nothing else
um okay
uh what is this
i see i'm in a room i uh with uh
like armors puppets
and levees
and arrows
[Music]
oh i'm quite crazy in here i need to
break out of my cage
oh
thank you oh you're welcome was that me
i just turned around the leather and
then it made ding dong
you let me out you freed me
okay what was in the other direction
you're still
i was i was easy yeah
okay then you got out what do you see
now oh i'm in a throne room uh there's
these mannequins
uh four of them which are standing in a
default position uh one is turned to the
right and then there's a king sitting on
a throne
uh and a big red button um i pressed it
oh and it's turning the okay it's like a
puzzle
oh
i have four mannequins as well
um they look into different directions
uh-huh
um
and yeah they also in people pose poses
uh
they have like
i don't know
one of them has an arrow to the right
side but he's looking frontal to me and
one of them has also an oh this lever is
broken i hope eleven is broken but he
looks to the it looks uh backwards to me
arrows
over to the right this doesn't make any
sense to me
not yet but we will figure it out amir
okay figure it out
uh and the others okay one looks frontal
to me
uh everything right
to the right arrow to the right
okay
[Music]
oh is that the problem
okay wait well i'll just i'll just try
something i'll pull over
okay did something move
again
uh
pulling again
[Music]
oh
what if i pull
this one did something move
some mannequin
uh no i think the cage moved i heard
something move but
[Music]
oh one of them is moving i think we do
it again oh
again i did it again and again
and again
is he moving again
uh
i don't know i hear something moving but
i don't see anything
um
i do hear like something constantly
moving like
um
[Music]
every four seconds in between like every
five seconds i guess
oh there's a stump some clock or
like it sounds like a
chain
um
like being pulled oh something moved
something moved pressing
buttons wait wait wait wait keep on
moving that keep on moving
nothing happens in that one because i
have two different rooms and they're
pretty set pretty far apart from one
another people moving people moving
okay no nothing
i hear something moving
comes from that
direction it's moving
from here
maybe you're above me i maybe you're in
the room above me or something like that
yeah i think so because i'm hearing
whatever you're doing
you hear what i'm doing i'm not doing
anything right now
[Music]
did you hear that
uh i i heard when you were like
triggering stuff before but nothing was
moving because yeah i hear the clock so
it was a different sound
oh
what happens if i oh i can't move this
one anymore okay cuz i already moved it
okay
[Music]
tell me about the knights again because
the only thing i have to interact with
is that button
uh it rotates the knights
in a
uh clockwise
uh rotation
um yeah my knights i have four of them
one looks straight at me and i have like
a lever in front of every knife but when
i pull it
the only thing that changes is an arrow
uh that is like sticking onto the
pedestal where the knight is standing on
so it moves from right to left right to
left every time i move the lever but the
mannequin himself doesn't move and
something just ding-dong
yeah i think we're running out of time
what there's a time
i think so
no way no way i don't understand this
puzzle last one the one before was
easier yeah
um is there anything else that sticks
out to you in your room
uh there's a king sitting in the throne
who's a mannequin and he has a big it's
a big red rock that we made in his chest
oh
and he's stealing other than that uh
there's another round room before the
throne room that has the two cages in it
and then like a little chair for
somebody to sit in to watch over the
room but uh that's it there's nothing
movable the only interactable things
with the big button which just wait a
second
and uh i found symbols hidden behind
flags behind each night
oh wait what the hell
there was
did you just in the moment i said what
the hell did you just like one second
before i do something uh probably
i mean again
i'm moving uh different
flags that are showing different
symbols
i just turned on here like oh i guess
i'm letting light into your room
oh
[Music]
yes like you like um
in front of
in front of every statue in front of
every mannequin i have a window okay
only in front of one mannequin
only that window
um now has light shining through okay so
try turning it uh with that lever uh on
the left that's the only one that has a
broken lever okay well let's move to a
different one then okay uh and this one
okay yeah yeah yeah okay oh
interesting
um i moved that one but i don't know did
that do anything i'm moving the level no
it doesn't do anything but
one thing that just stood out to me is
when the light was off they all have
like some kind of flag behind them or
curtain or whatever and they look black
to me when the lights are off but now
that the lights are on this one looks
yellow to me and the other one looked
blue to me
the one that i couldn't move but this
one
um i guess like
maybe the colors have some significance
as well yeah because um
so like the
flags that i'm moving out of the way
each have like a different color to
represent like each night and so the one
i just moved out of the way to shine the
second light
was a green checkerboard and then i also
have the first one that i moved was a
yellow one and then there's another one
across which is a
red and white checker and then there's
another one that's just blue
the one that you
the one where you um turned the light on
for me like most recently
what's the color there
oh uh green
okay for me that's yellow
um
by the way what i want to ask chad one
thing that's been bothering me is do is
are my fbl slow my my own body's fps is
that really so
am i fba slow
yes why
why
but the game is fine
a little choppy okay but it's not a big
deal okay
okay okay
anyway back to the game thank you chad
um
the one let's go to the one where you
turned the light on for me
um
which
i guess which direction does the
mannequin look
to
uh
well i can move the button when i press
the button they all rotate clockwise but
none of them are
or sorry two of them are synced up but
uh the other two are looking in
different directions
they could look in any direction because
i can spin them
okay i cannot spin them but the one
okay maybe you need to have them look in
the same direction as they look from me
but but this one's yellow and it's green
on your side maybe so maybe it's like
maybe
maybe i need to find those
press the lever for that one
the lever of the lever i have the lever
for that one
move like i can move it okay do it
okay
okay okay okay
all right i see
uh so when you trigger the lever what it
does is it does correspond to like the
yellow one like you said
corresponds to it but what happens is
that um
it switches the rotation so
now instead of turning uh clockwise it's
turning counterclockwise
now i have three of them facing the same
direction and i suppose maybe i'm
supposed to copy
like uh
you think they should all be facing the
same direction
okay
um
so
all right wait i have i have three of
them facing the same direction if we
want to go to the other room or the
other side
okay okay okay other room
let's see what the colors are over there
red blue and yellow and i guess maybe
here is red and green
okay one light is on right now oh i see
yeah i see the level for that one
okay wait wait wait by the way
did you on the on the other one did you
um
just check oh
oh i guess it's fine okay it's good all
right uh yeah for the
blue one this one
the the arrow right now looks to the
right side i don't know if that's like
does that move does that mean that yours
will move to the right side whenever you
do that
um maybe yeah
let's see i'm pulling the lever and i
was looking to the left side
okay uh can you do it again
okay now let's look into the right gun
[Music]
you do it again wait
i don't know
uh
it's
difficult
[Music]
when it moves right now which direction
moves does this one move
uh
clockwise
clockwise okay then i think mine is
currently set to clockwise as well
oh oh does it if i okay now does it
still move clockwise uh no
okay okay okay so i control that okay
which
is i guess
i think so
what
[Music]
what what
of course we both knew oh
well then it goes
yeah i see the ghost too
talking to a jester yeah
oh you see this thing cutscene oh you
must find the way
[Music]
oh he's there pointing at you
this game is more
like magical and
fantasy like i fought with me okay so i
don't know about your room but in my
room now behind the king there are four
different knights and one is holding a
hammer one is holding like a
staff sword one is holding an axe oh i
see you
[Music]
okay okay
yeah yeah me too
oh pretty seal
how should we do it then
there's a text in the middle so maybe
that gives us a hint
the knight closest to the king's left
hand side wields the sword closest to
the left the king's left
and where's the sword okay i put that
there
wait i see more text the dragon can be
found somewhere to the king's left-hand
side
dragon
i guess that's a shield
oh yes i have a shield with a dragon uh
so this one over
you see where i'm jumping
oh wait uh
where are you wait wait
i feel like the kings left oh yeah this
one
yeah the last one
okay
um i have a shield that has a uh bear
and
uh
i suppose uh
big bird slash phoenix
oh
and one is uh what do you call that
again a deer deer with corn you put the
you put the dragon one on the last guy
yeah i put it i put it this one here the
drive again okay
it says the deer cannot be found at
either end the ax wielding knight is
somewhere to his right hand side
the axe willing what
well then i'm putting
it there oh it says for the shields it
says the deer cannot be found at either
end
absolutely
[Music]
my text says the boar has the mates
wielding knights somewhere to his left
hand side
boar the board the board on the
left-hand side wait i have a boar
oh there's a bora bear is this a
boar this doesn't make sense it's the
dragons
the border has the mace willing knight
somewhere to the to his left side and
then it says the hammer railed in
phoenix stand somewhere to the deer's
right hand side
okay wait can you put the dragon one on
the first one
the dragon one and there's another guy
next to him yeah
on the guy next to him okay
or bear whatever uh on the last one
and okay
the four has the mace one laying
somewhere through his left hand
also navatek says the knights at both
ends do not wield the hammer
okay so this guy
okay so we have all the weapons in now
it's the rest what do you have left
i put the dragon in the board so i guess
the deer and the phoenix
wait wait wait wait wait uh
look
[Music]
the hammer whaling phoenix stands
somewhere to the deer's right the hammer
yeah the hammer is here uh the one
closest to on the other side
i'll be off
the other one on the other
wait
wait wait wait
[Music]
yeah uh the knight closes the king's
left hand
builds a sword maybe it's reverse
because i did it i'm like uh
oh yeah i can't yeah i know kiara has an
echo i think it's just
i said maybe we should change everything
all right so i'm gonna put it
i'm just gonna swap it around just in
case you do the same thing like take it
from the first guy on either side and
then swap it
oh okay okay
[Music]
now um
wherever i'm jumping the one with the
mace that one should have either the
board the dragon
right these here
um
[Music]
why is
i'm not using the in-game audience i
think i'm
[Music]
somewhere i don't know which order
wait let me read this again the hammer
wielding
phoenix
oh then somewhere into the deer's right
hand side oh
the hammer should be where the phoenix
is right yeah
okay
the hammer is to the phoenix right side
so the phoenix would be on the axe
penis will be
uh right side from your side you need a
rest uh yeah okay okay
uh this okay well that might have been
what was
messed up on the last time because we
switched sides so
oh
oh we'll try it like this
wait the
boar has the mace wheeling knight
somewhere to his
left-hand side
all right the maze
the main board goes on the sword
the boar
what the board goes on the sword
that's what how i would maybe understand
it too
wait wait wait what what what
[Music]
the boy the boar has the maze smelling
night somewhere
but when they say
they mean from his perspective
wait who's whose perspective are we
talking about tonight's perspective so
it'd be the same it'd be your
perspective too since the nicest the
night is facing outwards so
oh
the boy has to make sure
[Music]
so the board the boy should be
the brush
so
the boy should be to the left side of of
the so somewhere on this
uh side i guess i can swap them
and then
the banner
what else is on the left side that's
what i want to know i think i think
we're messed up
i think we're gonna have to start again
okay no problem
[Music]
the hammer is currently uh
nowhere okay
chill princess too
and um
let's start with like figuring out your
first text
i
oh okay can we skip dad
shut up
enter no escape escape longer longer
pushing okay okay okay release me from
my cage
i will do
wait
i need to release you from the cage
again
probably hold on wait another cutscene
i'm skipping
skip okay
[Music]
wait what
but we we did this one
no
it's okay we'll figure it out
i don't know
[Music]
yeah but we'll figure it out because
it's like a pretty good probability of
us getting it again
[Music]
cause it was only the one night so
no why do they make us do the skin
make you suffer
what the hell game
what okay which one are we starting with
let's open some curtains i guess
yellow
yellow i don't know which forever yellow
was one second let me see was it here
yes okay i don't know where i left that
one off last time
no
let's do the olympia
okay i moved it
all right now i'll go to the other side
of the room the other room
there's no way we can do this
the probability is so it's so easy there
are all the other three already lined up
it's just like the other one
right
um yeah red red okay i think it at the
end position was this though
no maybe not okay i moved it i moved the
left
[Music]
because there's only so many
possibilities it would be easy to
replicate it
skipping skipping
what
you know
[Music]
okay so going from the left
king's left
okay yes
i'm taking all the shields
yes okay well it can't one thing for
sure it can't be this uh order can't be
dragon
and okay okay
um
so
uh on the very left side the board
the boar has the mace wielding knight
somewhere to somewhere to his left hand
side
so one even one of those
somewhere too left hand side
yeah where you put is that the mix no
that was the hammer the mace maybe put
it here
yeah and i'll put the board
wait where's the bullet right
[Music]
and
what's your first text
uh the knight closest to the king's left
hand all uh side wields the sword which
i have there and then it says the deer
cannot be found at either end the axe
wielding knight is somewhere to his
right hand side
which means the axe is at the end
right yeah just right so then the deer
would be this one
yeah
and it says something about the deer
here too the hammer wheel being phoenix
they have a really grilling phoenix
stand somewhere to the deer's right hand
side so the hammer should be
here
on the very right no but it says
the knight closest to the king's left
hand side with the
lord
wait what where are you wait wait what
what what does it say to say again
nikolas king's left hand side wheels of
the sword
the knight closest to the king's left
hand yeah that's that's the sword yeah
that's correct
but uh
uh the hammer wielding phoenix stands
somewhere through the deer's right-hand
side we have the
yeah i would say the hammer would go
here yeah you put it there that's okay
okay okay okay yeah we
did it right i think
but the knights at both ends do not
wield the hammer
even though it should be standing
somewhere to the tears right hand and
the hammer will move
anyway
oh wait you put the
and
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
um the dragon can be found somewhere to
the king's left hand you put the dragon
there right on the left side
uh
right right
yes i know chad there's double i know i
have ears uh the dragon can be found
somewhere to the king's left-hand side
[Music]
what does it say about the deer
can you read the beer again
uh it said the deer
it says the deer cannot be found at
either end the axe wielding knight is
somewhere to his right hand side
the phoenix stands somewhere but now the
phoenix is next to the deer as well so
no this side must be correct
i mean it could still be on the
i don't know
where's ryden
hammer wielding phoenix
stands somewhere
the hammer wait what that said that's an
axe though the phoenix must be on the
hammer
what is this what is that the hammer you
already have a wheeling phoenix
strike stand somewhere on the fingers
right hand side
but the hammer is also not that if the
deer is on the sword then that still
makes sense
because it's to the right of the sword
regardless of the space between it
wait the deer's on the sword why did i
switch it out again
let's say it's next to the axe
uh
what what's next to the axe wasn't there
one i don't know
well then
the boar has wait what about the board i
haven't switched out the board anymore
the boar has the may swelling knife
somewhere to his left hand side i mean
that works if you put the deer on the
sword it sounds like
wow
that's yours wait wait wait the deer and
the sword
the deer is on the sword right now okay
yeah
i wore it as the main swirling night
somewhere just left penis yeah but then
no then the boar since the since the
maze is on the very left now well it
could be any of the nights then because
it doesn't mean it has to be directly
next to it
[Music]
okay bye we're running out of time okay
so the board is not on the very left
eh no wait no wait
the boar has the mace moving knight
so okay okay okay so the board should be
on the right side
okay
yeah cause the the mace should be on the
left side to the board okay okay
somewhere on the right side so which one
of these two is incorrect um
need a rest
nice
[Applause]
no can we just get out of here
we have to choose who dies
why
what a good question i don't know
okay i'm just sacrificing myself well
you're phoenix i guess you'll get
revived in here
even if i don't worry about that what
are you doing
oh
we'll meet again
but wait why i lied
i don't understand why what what
why did we get into this [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
i'm fine chad i'll revive don't worry
[Music]
what is this story i don't understand
dude
it's not about the story okay it's about
the journey that we talked about the
riddles
yeah
i think the uh and and the ending is
also part of the riddle cause i don't
know what the [\h__\h] of it
what what
what's to read earlier i think i think
somebody had to sacrifice themselves to
i don't know they like said that line so
fast i don't remember what she said
so that the world doesn't
you know
crumble and
maybe just yeah
at least
did we do all of that for that one gun
uh yeah for the flare gun so now i can
escape and your soul will remain forever
interesting i got a flare gun from dad
that's
that's all we got
yeah i don't know i don't think it's
supposed to like really make sense you
know it's just
wait but this was much shorter than i
thought it would be we were the last
riddles were kind of easy or like easy
to at least like randomly yeah and we
only had we only had those two chapters
left so i guess
wow
yes wow
okay hey uh
okay uh that wow we did it yeah that's
fast
we're like pretty smart so
i
i didn't even bring up my talking topics
oh today
i had talking topics
okay let me bring them up now
okay okay i'm it
what did you eat today um
i ordered some white honey
what have you done now
girl i remain
cursed
as is
[Music]
my dear friend
you never
cease to entertain
you've played the part of stewart long
enough
it is hard time for royal commands to
resound in these holes once again
oh yes my liege what you're the king who
would you command
the last remaining inferior
is punished
you are kings
i need to look up the meaning of this
game
redemption
the gesture sounded a little bit like
you but you'll sound much cuter oh thank
you wow thank you thank you steam for
doing that you stupid [\h__\h]
stupid steam
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
whatever i have i have many steam
accounts okay
[Laughter]
now i'm gonna get a million friend
requests there as well great okay
it's okay
uh so okay what did you eat today
oh uh i had um
like one fourth of a chocolate chip
pancake
you and then
yourself no i i ordered it
okay and then um
i had some
eggs with spinach and ham
i don't like spinach
it tastes good eggs i like it
and then uh i had some fruit
oh wait that only really sounds like
breakfast yeah i had breakfast
oh yummy
i'm gonna make pizza now oh i was really
excited for my pizza shoot you just find
me i have to
order pizza i'm gonna i'm ordering pizza
for my family
yeah they're like
well they're like
i was gonna send them breakfast today
but um
but they were like oh we're not gonna be
there so can you just send us we want
this pizza at this pizza this time so
what
do you just send food to them every day
uh it's because it's someone's birthday
so oh yeah oh
only today
food delivery like
yeah
well when it's like when there's like a
holiday or something i'll send them food
or like somebody's
birthday oh that's so sweet
oh
how kind of you you haven't eaten
anything today you're just gonna have
pizza later
uh i had i had i had breakfast cereal
and then i had before before dji kami
which was before the stream i had i made
soup i made noodle soup with sausages
cut up sausages oh noodle interesting
yeah
was that so interesting it was pretty
i've never heard that a soup with
sausage and i don't think i've ever
maybe like an italian soup i've seen
like a sausage in it
it's like super super basic soup that
you made for children here yeah super
basic kind of like egg noodles oh that
sounds good
no more noodles
uh
fin really really not not like the ones
that you use for like a pasta spaghetti
or whatever yeah like thin chicken
noodles noodles
and then and then cut up sausages yeah i
made that because i had cut up i had
sausages left over now i'm gonna make
pizza that was my motivation for playing
the game today pizza nice like uh it's
not ordered pizza it's frozen pizza oh
that's so tasty sometimes it tastes
better yes
i i love this one frozen pizza i'd say
with tuna
interesting i've never heard that before
in australia i've i've said that before
too that i'm like eating tuna pizza and
a lot of my viewers i think mostly from
america they were like blue but do not
be wet but it's so common here it's so
good is it like the kind of tuna like
from a can
like that shredded up tuna
yeah kind of yeah oh and then with like
onions and stuff it's so good like i'm
usually not the type that eats fish a
lot but
tuna pizza is so yummy it's really super
common okay you should a fish is really
good for you it's you know it's got a
lot of things that help your brain so
it's good if you i think if you go to an
italian like a really authentic italian
restaurant where they serve pizza i
think they would maybe have tuna pizza
as a choice on the penny normally we'll
see but i was so surprised to hear that
it's not very common outside of uh
europe yeah although i think i think in
japan
i think of yeah yeah definitely because
but they make it like they japanize it
by like adding mayonnaise to it which i
don't agree with i mean it's like tuna
salad that's like tuna salad pizza
i guess so but they just put mayonnaise
on everything over there i like how you
say it i like you say that word
mayonnaise
i love mayonnaise but i don't think you
should put it on everything no i don't
agree with that
that doesn't sound too bad to me male
pizza
it's it's edible that's for sure but not
my my first choice of yeah no
no i like like olive says topping
i don't like
but that's good because i'll give you my
leftovers
i'm going down my list i wanted to say
because i never thought of it today did
you call me
you said amitori like
like
rain bird or candy bird and i would like
to say if anything i would prefer it to
be called candy bird because
you are
you're sweet and enjoyable and desirable
like candy
while rain is melancholic and you're not
enjoyable and desirable so candy food
that's so sweet
okay thank you
yeah did you read that off a script you
wrote that down in your notes too
i wrote that down and it was like i'm
gonna tell that later to amen because i
thought of it and i wanted to say it
smoothly but
that one was like a script
that's cute i like it
don't call us candy bird that's kind of
weird it sounds like it sounds like a
like a
70 or no like a 60s rock band or
something
oh
candy bars
rainbird could be like the melancholic
edgy emo
yeah
they sing like songs about
how how
they're all alone and no one trusts
no they don't they trust no one and this
is sad sad world
well candy bird is more like
yeah i am
packing candy
candy candy that's my candy bird yeah
yeah yeah
that's cute
let's make it
candy bird okay okay one day one day
candy bird releasing soon tm
did you guys enjoy uh did you call me by
the way was it chat here were you there
were you there yeah did you guys have
one spamming in the chat i actually
didn't have the twitch chat open i
forgot i had it open yeah i wish i had
seen it
i just i don't know why i didn't think
of it
it was it was very sweet very supportive
thank you guys for being so supportive
yeah thank you i
i believe you yeah
a lot of people apparently don't have a
twitch account though until they didn't
didn't like rat at all but thank you for
still showing up thank
you it was fun it was um
i i think from all of the panels we did
this year
i think this was the one i had the most
fun at
um was just a good day and good good
questions yeah
interaction thank you i miss good
questions
of course you're so sweet
you're so sweet
and you you again
i don't know what's it
why are you so kind but you did not only
advertise
sparks randomly during the past but you
also put it uh put it in in the
description oh yeah of the stream of
your uh was it of the waiting room or of
of this stream well i think it was from
this stream this because i had it in the
last stream and so like i just went i
just scrolled back and used the same uh
i didn't even know you put it in there
last time i just noticed it today
because it's because i went to your
channel originally to like copy the
like your channel link but then i i went
into your description oh that's
otherwise i copied the permission text
from your channel and then i also
highlighted the sparks from your channel
and i
like by accident i was like i'll just
put that in there too
but you kept it on purpose yeah
i'm it
i
i i feel like
you're so amazing because
you always
think of like
others like me
and the others in myth like rather than
being selfish
and putting yourself first and only
advertising yourself you were you
retweet so much on twitter and as always
wanted to say i really appreciate that
because you you're so supportive of
everyone in the whole life you you think
of like instead of like uh having to
succeed or wanting to succeed all alone
you think of like the bigger picture you
want to succeed with all of us together
yeah i like to ramble
i like seeing like you guys i mean not
to say i don't like seeing myself
succeed either but uh you know
i like that i like seeing you guys
succeed more
i guess
[Music]
yeah but it also shows like in in the
way you try really hard to make stuff
like the one year anniversary great like
you that's what you do your best to uh
[Music]
yeah but you could have done it alone
and made it fun but you involved us in
this and following things that
are in the works now it's going to be
more fun with you guys
[Music]
sweet um
you're so sweet
you make me want to better myself
you're already a really good person
shut up
you know i'm i'm always very nervous
when i'm around you but
your heart it looks stucky and goes doki
doki but because i
i want
i think i think uh well it's only when
i'm on a one-on-one collab with you
when we're surrounded by more people
then it's like whatever but when it's
just us i feel like i i uh this
confession time today this is being
honest today but
i
this is like in a little it feels a
little bit like in school where
um
i kind of want to impress the cool kids
and you feel like the cool kid to me
[Laughter]
so whenever we're one-on-one i am like
nervous because like
i would i'm i'm
[Music]
i love you too
stop
i mean you're going on vacation soon
right oh yeah for a few days
oh i'm happy for you because i also just
came back from my vacation oh
yeah it looks really nice yeah did you
see yeah you looked at some of the
pictures that i sent today
but i
i showed even more like on my i'm back
stream but ah and it's like it was
really really nice it was like in the
mountains yeah i want to see that
it was in the countryside yeah
yeah it looks really pretty
i originally wanted to go like to some
beach but in europe
uh
it i would have i would have probably
had to go to like spain or greece like
italy would have already been cold i
think but italy would have been the
closest
but yeah
and all the flying around would have
taken up too much time so i ended up
just stressful staying in my country yes
it is a little bit stressful for such a
short vacation
um because it was only like
three nights four days
um yeah yeah anyway
um i don't know you probably
can't uh
say where are you going on your vacation
until maybe afterwards
okay looking forward to it or you can
tell me in private
yeah i will i'll tell you after win the
stream
i'm excited i'm happy that you're taking
a vacation when was your last vacation i
know it wasn't that long ago
it was like a week i think it was during
the council debuts so it wasn't that
long ago oh you're right you weren't
there yeah yeah
oh
well it's good that you're taking them
like every once in a while
yeah i wasn't i'm planning my next
good
i want to go skiing
it's fun because you know like part of a
lot of our content has to do with uh
telling stories or you know like our
experiences and talking and stuff yeah
yeah you can't really gain like anything
new from
uh just like sitting and playing the
game and talking to chat like you don't
get any new experiences to talk about
exactly like
i ran out of things to say
oh yeah guys in chat there was somebody
in the chat like a few days ago and they
said blah blah blah blah blah like
that's the only thing you get which you
know sometimes it's fun but
your brain needs more
nourishment
yeah
yeah yeah yeah i agree after i came back
from the vacation
i i still have some things to talk about
i hope i will
have some for a while but i'll run out
soon again and then i'll need to go
outside again
yeah yeah
um good for your brain
girl i'm immaterial
did you sing that before in your karaoke
uh no maybe i will oh what i did i had
oh
[Music]
i always thought those lyrics were a
freaking joke but i realized they are
real why is she being like mikasa
that's like the easiest spanish that
people pick up well because it's catchy
like probably yeah
your house is catchy
yeah
just thinking about like my house is is
your house i don't know actually i've
never really listened to the lyrics i
don't know if they're like coherent like
that
oh
oh i need to look deeper into it i don't
think it's that clear
yeah but if you ever sing material girl
and you need some some backup okay uh
vocals i already sang it in my most
recent catalogue unarchived
along with that because you do that yeah
i have a lot of uh karaokes to catch up
on because i haven't i haven't i don't
think i've done any duets from your
newest one and then there's also like a
i don't think i've done any council ones
yet and there's a lot of people
cali did a a really edgy karaoke
recently
oh
yeah yeah yeah
there's so much material for you
material
to sing along with
i want to listen next time you do it i
want to listen again the bee kyoku just
it got me good it got me good ame i
would say for the next karaoke it won't
be because it's going to be this coming
week uh it's not be
a
but it is a regular small ami but oh not
in the b
not as a b
okay just regular okay
i i like any kind of almond i was
thinking because you did b
i was thinking i kind of want to
um make like a frog yeah froggy i know
yeah
because that's kind of been like uh
a thing at kfp and i don't know i kind
of look good as a frog yeah i don't know
why but i think it looks good in
contrast of like your hair like orange
and green because they're
uh
they're not exact opposites but
by the way i'm just saying it's not my
it's not going to be any like halloween
costume guys i'm not going to be a frog
i don't want to do that i want to do
like a frog costume some sometime in the
future i want to commission it
there's some very specific things if
well i'll tell you afterwards earlier
yes
i'm curious but i also
want you to sleep because you barely
slept oh yeah
i see you
tired well you know how like when you
get really tired and you don't really
feel so tired anymore it's kind of like
that
oh
yeah i i know that feeling oh but you
should make sure to get enough sleep
anyway when you get next stream
uh tomorrow
i oh well it's not confirmed yet but
it's a collab in minecraft so i don't
want to say
ah
oh i see it on the schedule i'm not
gonna say it
oh you have enough time to sleep for
like oh yeah yeah
did you already put out your schedule no
so are you gonna make it now
probably not
i think i will make my schedule now and
let's see it out there yeah it's like
monday for you already huh
it's uh
no it's still sun sunday yeah uh sunday
oh but we're getting closer to monday
um oh oh we'll have a ttrpg on tuesday
yeah
i think this time uh wait who it was on
whose channel was it was on inna's
channel so i think it'll be on gooda's
channel
this time
well yeah i don't think we have really
like decided on it yet but it might be a
good chance oh yeah oh we were doing it
in order of uh
the tutorial
oh is she next okay i think so yeah
maybe i'm not gonna hold on i don't
remember maybe right
but i next
like we did gouda's channel fairly
recently maybe i'm confusing things
oh
it's my turn
it's your turn yeah
why why why why you don't have to do
anything you just
callie is doing all of it i know i know
i have to press i hate to press a button
damn it
those damn buttons fm
it will be fine you just have to lay
back and give a total
yeah and collect
we're going on a new mission this time
oh yeah yeah
exciting
she's gonna put us through for hell
again
yeah
i feel like we got out really easily we
got out really easy because ina had like
some really good roles
last time both both ina and gooda and
then us both of us were like like
getting there
and we both like even if one group would
have failed the other group would have
kind of found a way to
uh
get the solution last time oh yeah yeah
i'm doing at the same time
but my rules were so
so
to
last time
yeah we got screwed over
for real it was so unlucky like we were
trying so hard and i was like doing the
same things over and over and over again
like uh trying to try to look into a
freaking drawer i was rolling for dad
yeah well at the same time fighting a
vampire so whenever i fought off the
vampire i was like okay i want my next
role to be looking into the drawer and
then i failed and then the vampire had
enough time to get back up and attack me
again so i had to take care of him again
and i had to look into the drawer again
and i failed again and
i think he got off pretty easy because
there were like a few turns where callie
was like he's preparing to pull his
knife out he's he's approaching you with
his knife he's holding his knife above
you
but his
he can't do anything against me when i
shoot his eye out
that's a good point maybe what happened
with our rolls we didn't like uh which
was like blowing the dice or like kiss
the dice or something
we should blow blow into the dices and
kiss them yeah
okay i'll remember for next time i did
indeed not do that last time yeah that's
probably why
by the way our rolls are [\h__\h] oh it's
rake it's all right it's all right dummy
it's a wig
yeah cali rinsed it
she had yeah on the contrary she had
really really good uh rolls perhaps
yeah
suspicious i'm suspicious
you have to investigate
yeah invest speaking of investigating i
i am
baby maybe it's because i'm looking up
to you but i'm just recently
recently um really into
investigations oh like a true crime
stuff
yet
yeah
i'm constantly watching that right now
but it's like my new netflix it's insane
i'm like watching that before this
stream and before did you call me and
yesterday yeah
earlier
wait which specifically
i don't know any of them did you watch
them too um i haven't really been
watching them too much but i've been
reading some like true crime stories
like i read a book
about this lady serial killer yeah right
when did you read a book
uh it was like last week i'm reading a
different one this week
she reads books ahmed ahmed we have
something in common i recently read a
book
oh
do you have a kindle
no they're really good um don't get me
wrong the book that i read this week was
the first book that i read in like um
six seven years oh
what kind of what kind of book was it
was it like uh
oh no it was a tolkien book
oh okay nice those are pretty big huh
those are meaty chunks
it's not like a lord of the rings book
because
you know the story i wanted to pick up
something new to read like during my
vacation so i went to the bookstore and
i looked for any book but i didn't know
any of the recent authors and what books
are good right now and it was kind of at
a time pressure so i just went to like
offer a section that i knew that i was
talking and then i chose like one of his
like um one book only um
like books like not not a series so
yeah which one was it the one that i got
the
you probably don't know it have you ever
read tolkien uh no i i haven't i think
because uh my aunt like collects books
and stuff i think i've tried at some
point but i was like this book's too
damn thick
but you're not like the genre or you're
also like i don't like the genre i just
have never like gotten into it but i
probably would like it i think
it's still fitting though that that you
read a true uh crime book
yeah a fitting useful main character i
should do more information it's a little
surprising because usually i like like
fantasy sort of books or
like whatever like uh young adult novels
they used to read those a ton but i
tried reading and i was just like i
can't do this and now i'm for some
reason my brain is like yeah i want to
read like either you know non-fiction or
like uh
like recently i've been reading a book
about simulations
and like
simulations world building is pretty
intense yeah it's about building a
simulation that
is complicated but essentially they're
like creating these virtual building
blocks of life where they go through
explaining like how they make a from an
atomic level create atoms virtually and
how they kind of
uh evolve into you know like more
advanced things from there and yeah i
guess
i mean i get it but it's like
yeah it's
it's a bit much sometimes
that's
that's probably not something that i
would pick out of the shelf
i'm just trying to get through it but
it's kind of interesting because i i
like reading it because it talks about
like some time relativity stuff and like
going through experiments because when
you're uploaded to that virtual world
like uh you experience time differently
so
that's pretty interesting
you know
right now when you're talking to me
all i
all
all that goes through my head is like
cryptic signs
i didn't understand english it was just
like cryptic
cryptic signs and stuff
i didn't understand we used to get a
kindle they're really good for reading
oh but i don't i mean i don't read that
often um
one time
while you're on vacation got it
yeah
but maybe maybe i'll pick up a
another book after that one and then
another who knows who else maybe maybe
i'll
get caught in the web of books
it's maybe because i'm running out of
netflix
you can't run out i mean if you run out
of netflix you just go to another
subscription service yeah i'm running
out of walls no but
i do have i don't have a bunch of time i
have a i have a disney plus subscription
that i
have since like three months and i
haven't used it once oh yeah i usually
i'll do that i sign up for subscription
and then i i don't end up using it but
then my family is like oh do you have a
subscription for this i'm like oh yeah
yeah i just use it because i'm paying
for it and i'm not using it
yeah i mean why not share because you
can usually usually share those so why
the hell yeah share with friends
yeah why not why not i'm
gonna watch some crime stories after
this
yeah
i'm gonna make a little one right now
i'm not gonna mention any any cases
because
it may be problematic yeah
it's very interesting yeah i think i
think the algorithm got me there was
this i think this one this one i can
maybe talk about but there was this
video that got a lot of people in the
algorithm the one that explains like how
you can tell uh like a real
uh
fake one like one that's faking it oh
yeah yeah i know what you're talking
about that channel that like
psychoanalyzes like why criminals yeah
those are really interesting
jcs
yeah
it was very interesting to see uh
how how um how ridiculous people act oh
yeah trying to get out of it and try to
act like this
yeah very interesting
yeah
i've been watching a ton of those
they're good oh
and now i'm in there too are you
sneezing no okay you look like you're
about to sneeze me
yeah oh no
i was just looking down at something
i'm playing with this little screw thing
squirrel
yeah screw it this little adapter for a
microphone uh mount
i'm i'm
yeah
you know i remember remember when uh
we set up uh
on the
the small 3d
oh yeah yeah
i asked you like we talked a little bit
about cable management oh yeah and how
my rooms freaking mess and i was like yo
is yours also freaking out yes
you said yeah right yeah it's really
really bad i have so much [\h__\h] like so
many cables for everything
so bad
but i actually while i was gone i had
someone um
take care of my cats and that person
also did cable management
oh i know so nice it's so clean i'm not
tripping over cables anymore yeah
i told you you could hire somebody to do
it they'll do it for you
i didn't even have to hire anybody
it was done voluntarily yeah it's cool
i'm glad it's all cleaned up now it
looks really good now yeah
i'll send you a picture of mine
oh yes
maybe you should hire someone it's like
i don't know how people do it it's like
magic like how can you not end up with a
big big knot of cables
but then more and more you buy more and
more things and you add more and more
like equipment and then more and more
cables are there and it's just not all
there from the start so even though you
planned from the beginning to have it
all clean the more and more new stuff
you get the more the more chaos you get
especially now with the with the new vr
sub i have an ex extra amount of a [\h__\h]
ton of cables thank you amit uh you're
um
it's kind of bad because there's like a
there's like trash on the phone oh my
god
i'm not even gonna judge you because
that's how it looked uh here as well
until a moment ago it's just a napkin
and uh
it's like a
collectible twitch card that i i cut oh
for my ukulele on the floor it's not
that bad oh there's a floor
because i have a ton of packs in them
you have a ton of what
packs of those cards oh yeah i couldn't
find a pick that's why
i see the cutout of the card it's the
shape of a ukulele pink
well when you don't have what you need
you gotta create out of other means yeah
yeah
oh i'm i feel
a bit more um relieved that i'm not the
only one with such a freaking mess i
didn't quite expect it from you i felt
like you were you would be more the
argument organized type of person
because you know your stuff you know
your everything else
everything else aside from like my my
desk and my office is organized
this is like the only place because
sometimes i'll just like sit here and
like work on stuff or stream and i'll
just eat and then put but i'll just put
it to the side for later
future i may will deal with it later
and then and then my dogs end up trying
to climb on the desk and knocking stuff
over my cat knocks stuff over oh no
yes my cats are a bit more well behaved
because they don't really knock things
over
they're not little shits
no the only thing that is like
a little bit like
um
triggering but still i forgive because
cute as hell is that like when i am
laying in bed i often have a like uh
my laptop open in bed
and then chunkers will deliberately
um
in order to reach one point when like
the corner of my bed like right next to
me she would run
over the keyboard of the laptop even
though she has more than enough space to
go around it
even when i stop her she will jump on
the keyboard and just run over it while
smoothie
always makes a huge curve around the
laptop i don't know my trunk is just
deliberately walks over
yeah sometimes they're just attracted to
it maybe it's the heat they like the
heat
but she just wants to like quickly run
over it she doesn't even want to lay on
the laptop although she did that today
but generally she just really wants to
trigger me by walking all over it maybe
it's an attention thing because my cat
like i'm looking at my phone and he's he
headbutts my phone out of my hands and
he's like no look at me
oh maybe maybe or she likes the sound
when she walks over to the keyboard yeah
or she's trying to tell me a message
oh
typey something
she's trying to tell me give me snacks
give me chicken oh yeah usually that's
that's when cats are like really kind of
annoying sometimes in your face they're
like my football is empty it's been
empty for two hours i'm gonna die
you you got that a lot uh yeah my cats
yeah
at any time or only like in the morning
uh
any time well i feed them like two
two times a day like a little bit uh in
the morning when i wake up and then like
at night but then there's definitely
times in between where they're like
hey hey hey
i think it's because maybe they're
i don't know they play and run around
and stuff but i think they just get
bored sometimes you know
oh i need i need to give them some more
enrichment i gotta get them some more
toys
yeah i want to do that too in richmond
but but actually like chonkras doesn't
ever annoy me about food ever
she's she just
she just like always just chills she
doesn't ever ask for snacks or whatever
and then smoovie only asks for food
really annoyingly in the morning because
she knows in the morning she'll get wet
food but besides
they're both always really really chill
and quiet they don't annoy me with it
that's cute yeah okay
your cats aren't very young right
because i have a i have like a kitten i
think he's like five months older six
months old and
whenever i like be eating an avocado and
he tried to steal the seed the avocado
he eats melon i have like a video of him
like licking the inside of a melon
because he just eats anything he's crazy
he tried to bite a pear he took some of
my pizza he was eating rice yesterday
that's so cute
i mean he's trying to be healthy he
wants a healthy diet i don't know what's
up with him i feed him like quite a bit
i feel like i feed him too much and he
still just wants more he's crazy think
he doesn't see it as eating though maybe
he sees it as a attacking
cry
yeah maybe yeah
just wants to attack whatever maybe
maybe he thinks that the melon or the
whatever the peach or pear is attacking
you when you're eating it so he wants to
add fruit because he wants to protect
you sure
we'll say that
attack
it's so cute he's just playful okay i'm
sure he'll stop eating fruit when he
grows a bit older
yeah he wants those nutrients
yeah he'll sit under my monitor and then
like put his paw underneath and press
keys on my keyboard and i have a picture
i have like a picture of him doing that
and it was when i was playing uh
oblivion that's like a skyrim type of
game so it has reloads and
you [\h__\h] me up
oh no oh no that's so cute though i
would forgive
beat for gibb
don't don't don't be mad don't be angry
no i don't get angry with him now
good good uh cat mama maybe i should
have watched cats with you
ah
oh oh god actually it's funny that you
say that because i think it was i think
it was yesterday i was trying i was like
looking for something to watch and like
oh they added cats
to the hbo app and uh i was like i tried
watching it and i i just i couldn't like
after
yeah after like a minute i was like yeah
i'm not watching this why not it was
really good
because i don't like the way that they
make the cats look like humans and then
like the perspective is all messed up
like they look really tiny like i just
imagine somebody walking out on the
street and seeing them and they're like
the size of like not ants but like
really small and it i mean that was
funny to me but that didn't bother me at
all i didn't even notice that oh
you know maybe i'll give it another try
if you vouch for it yes yes i don't know
why people don't like it it's a good
movie 10 out of 10. i say that i grew up
like listening to the musical because my
my aunt really liked it and so
i've seen like the stage play of it
before
oh
you should want you should give the
whole movie a try it's it's it's worth
it trust me trust me i i liked it too i
watched it together with ina
and she liked it she gave it a test
being polite
no she said best movie she has ever seen
in her control line
okay
i see
i i did a quiz today
uh which cat's character am i
well i did a buzzfeed quiz
and i came out as the the character that
taylor swift played oh
yeah that's a weird kitten that they
threw and looked like
he's not a kitten
um
i'll read it
you are bombarina you're flirty and full
of mystery you like to have fun
and we'll risk everything for good time
you're confident and won't take no for
an answer
okay that sounds i mean that sounds like
a pretty accurate yeah
do you want to do it too i'll do it for
you wait um
i should ask you questions and you'll
give me the answer one second all right
here
this character
okay let's do this uh
okay choose
a disney villain you can pick between
scar
from uh
the lion movie
lion king lion king
or uh
hates from uh
hades
yeah and or sir you're sure
from ariel i think
[Music]
oh
choose a fictional dog clifford snoopy
goofy or brian griffin
clifford
cliff clifford who's clifford it's a big
red
dog it's from like a cartoon i think
it's originally from like a children's
book that got turned into
yeah and then uh
the soup i used to like to eat it always
had like clifford branding on it and i'd
be like i wanted
i don't even know that dog this big red
dog
it looks it up but it doesn't look
familiar to me at all
okay okay which member of the mystery
gang are you
shaggy
scooby
daphne or velma
uh
i don't know chat what do you guys think
kiara what do you think
what
maybe you're shaggy
i just talk like this all the time
that's good i like that
okay pick an art form dancing acting
writing or painting
um
i guess acting sure
okay pick an andrew lloyd webber musical
uh from the following jesus christ
superstar
evita every time
uh phantom of the opera or cats
uh
i guess i'll pick a phantom of the opera
okay okay
i picked cats by the way oh gee i i
wonder why
uh choose a type of milk whole
almond
two percent or soy
uh
two percent
two percent okay
pick a vacation spot
new york city
hawaii
paris or rome
all right
okay
i think i picked that too yeah uh pick a
female star
lady gaga
rihanna beyonce
or ariana grande
brianna
a nice good choice good job i would have
chosen her too by that she was ariana so
i couldn't almost couldn't choose
between between those two
how this one i was struggling with i
wish i had an input with that one i
didn't know which one to choose i'm
sorry just choose randomly but how would
your friends describe you
loyal mischievous
fabulous or funny now what would you say
uh
i'm pretty loyal i'm kind of like a dog
you know
really you would you think that your
friends would describe it you couldn't
know me right now i would probably just
yeah
what do you think
funny or mischievous mischievous
it's funny or mystery
okay
chad also says miss chivas
at least on my side
uh they're mixed
uh like
you guys have to pick between funny or
mischievous they're your friends as well
so teammates get to choose other they're
they're choosing mischievous
okay good okay
okay i'll send this to you as a picture
okay
oh my god i'm so excited what cat am i
what cat are you
[Music]
the full uh description yeah i was
watching like the first five minutes of
the movie and they had like a really
cool
uh part where they showed up you know
like a
very important plot device where
obviously this is like the evil guy
because they had him parallel with
moriarty
would you like to read the text
you live a secret double life nobody can
figure you out because you choose to
hide who you really are once people get
close to you they love your personality
but it's not easy to get past those
walls you put up
i feel like this is kind of hard
wow you guys should all take the cat's
quiz it's so accurate
both mine aren't yours
[Laughter]
why am i going crazy here come on i
guess yeah yeah i guess
i because like the secret double life is
kind of because you know you're like a
you're a detective
detectives often live double lives
that's true
and yeah it was also for me like i feel
like i experienced those walls with you
before but now now that i got closer to
you i love your personality so it's
exactly as it's written here
i have an idea
shall we do in the future
uh
a chit chat stream where we do buzzfeed
quizzes
okay i guess it's fine as long as we're
not showing it
yeah
i mean maybe we can get uh permission
for one website but anyway we can just
read out the questions and then yeah the
answers and then explain what we got and
we can do it alone
[Music]
i don't think we can call it buzzfeed
though i don't know
yeah there's just genuinely
cool personality quiz
yeah personality quiz stream taking
thingy like stuff like
uh
this these even quests even seven
questions will reveal which disney
character you most similar to oh
what which character from the aristocats
are you based on
[Music]
well i got one for everything huh
these five questions and we'll tell you
which lindsay lohan character you are
that's very specific okay
or take this quiz to find out which
underrated disney villain you are most
like i kind of want to know this one
right now
okay
okay this is the last one and then we
end the stream let's do it together oh
oh okay send it to me i'll send you the
website and we'll do it together at the
same time okay this is a test run
this thread okay so pick an animal
goldfish
rat
of course cat cat cat cat which one are
you picking uh i think a goldfish
i like the ones with the puffy cheeks
so much for being loyal oh my god
okay read the next question please
oh um pick a sandwich um there's no name
yeah one looks like a grilled cheese one
looks like a grilled cheese with more
stuff in it one looks like a very
healthy whole grain
yeah with sprouts and stuff and then one
looks like a sub yeah i'm going for the
last one because it has salami and ham
and potatoes and everything here these
potatoes
and i put the ad mental cheese what the
hell is wrong with my brain right now
i'm gonna go for the green one because i
like sandwiches that have like avocado
lettuce or sprouts is stacy help me
wow
okay next is pick a sport baseball
soccer football or tennis to watch or to
do
probably
right
maybe yeah i'll pick friends too
i'm not good at it but i i kind of like
um tennis like being bad at it i enjoy
that oh well i think a singer again
would i read the options adele camila
i don't
[Music]
and taylor swift rihanna i pick it
though
you're not picking rihanna even though
you picked rihanna last time in this in
this selection you would choose adele
yeah
i like adele but i will choose rihanna
here
understandable
okay
the last one is pick a subject math
science english or history
science
i don't know i always like english or
science best i guess i'll go science
i'll go learn english because i was the
best in class at english oh back in the
day
who are you
i got randall boggs for monsters inc you
are cunning and intelligent
i will not be from monster inc too
i got someone who i don't know
tell me what i'm edgar balthazar from
the original cats
there's a lot what the hell you're
organized and well-spoken but you're not
fond of cats what
that's a lie
as the
animal yeah it's what it's broken it's
right
i chose cat it's my favorite animal
if you misclicked
no i didn't i looked back up it's on the
cat right now oh
what
what yeah that's that doesn't make sense
that kind of destroys the
um
authenticity yeah and i believe in on
this
on these quizzes but we're still gonna
do the collab the hell buzzfeed i
expected accurate quiz results
i like that uh you hit the table for
your in order to let out your aggression
all right let's do that like after your
vacation
what oh yeah okay sure
i'm excited more and more quizzes yeah
i used to take those a lot it's pretty
fun
thank you guys for watching today thank
you for hanging out
yeah and also thank you for joining us
at did you call me and supporting us
both there thank you
thank you
and we'll see you guys soon and in
german we say i'll take you soon
goodbye
[Music]
uh
foreign
[Music]
you