[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
so
hi miss
oh god my voice is loud wait
um okay
hi rice
it's
iris
good evening good evening
how's everyone doing
again
genki that's
cool okay wait
let me raise my rust volume a bit more
i think last time my rust volume was a
little weird when i was streaming
and you know hanging out with
some peeps last time totally not off
stream of course um
wait why is it so dark
did they replace iris's va do i sound
that different
do i sound that different wait um
it's dark
i'm in the comfort of my own home okay
wait
wait a sec
where did kiara say she was good
okay okay p8 where's p8
okay so today
we are playing rust for the first time i
love first time logging in today yup
you sound tired no i slept a lot i'm
good i'm good i'm good
where's p8 oh
pure weight is all the way across the
map okay
see if you have any mail oh do i have
mail
alright first
is there already morning or not yet
oh yeah i'm gonna wait until this
morning and then i'll go hop on my horse
uh in the meantime let me just get some
ammo because i don't have much i have to
make more
and then where's my gun powder maybe i
should put some wood in here
and empty my pockets because my pockets
are full of
scrap and
unnecessary stuff
you know went to sleep guys
literally didn't sleep for 24 hours
i wouldn't be surprised this girl is
asleep too though though she's pretty
much like an npc in this game
i didn't notice that girl was around ina
too and i
when i showed up at the gambling place
and then your girl was like wait wait
karo's here too
yeah
uh
okay wait let me put some guns away
i don't need all these guns
i kind of want to put this away too it's
kind of
it's one of those guns i don't want to
lose right away
i'm 39
and yeah
i'll bring this along and put this away
so kiara invited me to go on a hop air
balloon right i wonder if i should bring
some fuel
this which is very fun
i have good memories with hot air
balloons
a very good memory with
memories with hot air balloons they're
great stuff
let me just get some food
i don't have anything to
chop these up
great way to testing gravity in it yep
you're like oh yeah so that means that
where the place we are right now the
setting of rust is earth is how i found
out you know i wanted to double check if
we were not on earth or not
that's the whole reason why
you know who knows maybe we're on the
moon or something you know like a moon
of a different planet or something
i wasn't so sure i had to double check
and no don't worry about the teams it
seems everyone we change really often so
okay wait let me just cook this pork so
i have something to eat on my way there
i actually don't have much food because
at one point i found four horses and i
had four horses at the same time and
they were eating my food like
like a machine like a machine gun
which is a weird way to say it but
yeah that's why i don't really have much
food in the house anymore
ah
okay
i don't need this
i don't need this jacket either
but i don't have enough space so i'm
gonna
put them oh wait
i am going to
bring
i can put this away
how did girl get inside here
how did she get on the roof
i have to double check my
my security sometime
oh yeah i need to bring i need to make
more bullets i almost forgot about that
you know what i'll just i'll recycle
them later it's okay
should i bring some scrap
i'll bring it okay
[Music]
since when did i get an audio oh yeah
ina gave it to me oh yeah
so as you guys noticed my house has
gotten bigger nothing's on the second
floor though um the reason why it's such
a weird shaped and humongous house is
because i wanted to make just the second
floor like just this block over here and
i wanted to connect it to a staircase
over here but the staircase kept this
despawning and never connected to the
building for some reason
oh did was kiara in chat here wait wait
uh why is my chat always off
oh yeah
wait wait
i was i'm coming
do you need fuel
oops i'm saying i'm saying this in team
wait wait uh uh uh
repeat
[Music]
i'm just gonna bring some water
okay now plenty gotcha
oops
nope let me just make some
um
ammo
i guess i can make ammo on the way
ah wait wait wait
okay
okay off we go
i'm not trying to make them wait no i'm
going right now i'm leaving right now
on my horsey
so yeah i wasn't able to expand um
vertically so i expanded
uh horizontally instead
and that's why i had two trowels here
because i found i had three horses in
here
oi
okay where's p6
p
[Music]
was it p8 actually i think she said p8
wait do you guys remember i'm just gonna
put on p8 for now okay
p
p-8 okay
where's p-8 oh oh it's this way okay
my sense of direction
oh seven it was where the balloon
currently is okay 0707.07
remember last time i tried using the
balloon um
it just kind of went round and round and
didn't really do anything
so i wonder how she's doing it
[Music]
oh seven oh is that
you also jumped out yeah i did
yeah you don't have to remind me you
don't need not need to remind me of my
blunder speaking of blunders you know
that right with
with eno and girl just a couple hours
ago you know how i exploded and died
as soon as i said i'm walking in like a
terminator and i just kind of terminated
myself yeah um
i saw a grenade
and
yeah i blasted myself yeah that was that
was my own grin
i tried to throw it at the enemy and i
didn't notice it just kind of it didn't
it didn't reach there
and then it just kind of exploded in my
face
yeah
literally committed
involuntary um sudoku yeah
hmm
i saw a clip and girl's like laughing
laughing your butt off yeah it was
pretty funny
that was growing chat
agora what did you say
i saw a clip of that man
so i tried to act like nothing happened
when i came back
i hear everyone saying
um
safe zone okay uh wait wait um oh
there's a cage there
wait
okay
i see it oh yeah i almost okay wait
i forgot that i was passing through
safe area okay let me just go around the
safe area
thank god i have a horse
oh god i'm a target now
no no
okay
[Music]
i didn't have a horse this
this would be a very long trip
stop it i'm not in the
not in the
where how far how big is the safe zone
we do have to go around
i have to go around
wait did i yeah i switched to oh seven
okay
stop holding the pickaxe oh yeah
oh god that's how safe zones worked oh
let me just pick up those mushrooms real
quick i might get hungry soon
that was fun
yeah i hear them saying we did it so i
was just like yeah we did it though i
did almost nothing in that
i really want us did you bring your
binoculars
[Music]
i totally forgot about the binoculars
oh yeah it's sightseeing
okay oh there's a supermarket
are there only two supermarkets on the
map
oh okay
p8
i really want a sniper rifle i've been
like
got getting so many air drops and stuff
like this off stream
but i never oh is this the balloon
kiara's using um
but i never seem to get a sniper rifle
or do regular rifles become sniper
rifles no right
[Music]
do you really get enough sleep somehow
do i sound that tired
do i sound that turned
joint what does this say
joy
joined uh
join us
oh join the the the the t ah yeah
okay
it was arena's horse
steal reina's horse
why is there a compost over here
where's our poop container over here
no no chiara and reina live close but
[Music]
did you hear my new song you little [\h__\h]
you were the only one named by the name
mentioned my name oh what
sorry i couldn't hear what i i put out a
new song it goes you little [\h__\h] you
little [\h__\h]
i always see a little [\h__\h]
oh
really that sounds like an amazing song
it will hit the top charts
it is oh wow really i bought it
i'm honored i am very honored
you know
what the [\h__\h] oh no nothing nothing i
should be shooting you for that comment
on my hat i know it's a beautiful house
it's bigger than my house it's
beautiful
don't you think horsey yeah i wanted to
take a look at it too
where on your where on the map is your
house my house is on like in between f4
and f5 like right around the line
of f45
oh that's perfect you know we can slide
with the hot balloon to your house sure
do you know how to like move this lady i
think you brought a [\h__\h] yeah it's a
fireplace we have a horse sitting
service
horse sitting service
is that not like a i will yes
it's not a i will steal your horse no
service
no no no no no i've already had one
customer aka my inaudible i've protected
her horse successfully um
charge however i see your horse is
already eating so you're automatically
signing the contract by having your
horse eat it
how much is how much is the feed
um so uh per rl day real life day
it's um
30 scraps
actually for jen mates it's fruity
scraps for non-gen mates it's some 45
scraps and 50 pieces of meat per hour
all day because your horse
looks very hungry
it already is eating a lot though so um
you're gonna replace that meat for me
we'll see we'll see what it comes out
too
i'm considered kind of a i'm considered
kind of a gen mate right
right
i get a discount you're at least the
same branch right no no no that's all
your discount non-branch members are 55
scraps per day oh you're 45 scraps per
day oh so it's still a discount
i see
i see this cut
so let me show you my house okay as you
said it's not very
it's not very lip balm
it's beautiful but i worked hard on it
this is beautiful looking for a short
amount of time yes two days and this
much and this so much progress
sasuka
i am not a little sheeta no i am i am a
little uh
i am a little angel yes that's what i am
wait
i forgot that uh
well
but yeah so i'm really proud of this
actually oh
i've accumulated a few things all on my
own oh
that did you did you get a mixer i can
imagine you've been playing a bit more
yeah i i have the the recipe for it you
should oh yeah you should make one it's
good to get scrap
you can make scrap tea mixing table you
can get scraps out of it like you can no
no you can grow berries and then you can
mix the berries to make scrap tea and
then if you drink scrap tea you can get
more scrap when you
when you like hit barrels and stuff
yeah
you iris is so cool for that information
yes that's sick
will you forgive me for the house
comment well
[Laughter]
oh
only
only if i get something in exchange
here um
also you're using my house at my horse
sitting in that case in that case as a
proof of friendship um
here's some corn
you just see that i have a corn field
here right yeah but i thought maybe you
wanted more corn
it seems like that's your favorite corn
and it's not even buttered or salted
i mean i could cook it for you if you
want it cooked but actually no i don't
think you can cook corn oh but but you
know i thought corn is your favorite
food because you have a whole field of
it
i am very disappointed in you but follow
me
we're still going on our lovely balloon
date though right
yes
i am i hope that we make it safely to
our destination
of course wouldn't it be such a
such a
such a waste if we wouldn't make it
safely
what would make you assume that we
wouldn't make it there safely
well it's my first time controlling an
air balloon there could be some
accidents ah that's true i fell off an
air balloon once
oh a real one in real life or
oh yeah in real life as well i came
unscratched
yeah just but a scratch though it was
totally fine
that's good
okay so here's the air balloon i already
fixed it for you yeah simon thank you
thank you i just have to turn it on but
honestly no idea how to
it
yeah i don't know how to control it too
last time i tried
doing this like it just spin around it's
just span round around and i didn't know
how to move it
oh
well
i mean i've seen it in like i don't know
children's shows or so that if you drop
something
some wait oh yeah and then you can go
back down but i think you can just turn
off the button to just turn it off to go
back down but
i guess so
at the same time it's currently going
yeah it's going north
nor
wait i think i think this is yeah
right now i hope they don't follow them
wait let me let me put them into the
actually before they fall down oh
there's a sack
into the storage
yeah
holy [\h__\h] it's going so fast actually
it is
but i think it's spinning round and
round
in circles oh yep it's going in circles
it's beautiful
did you run out of fuel no no we have
fuel
why didn't why why did it go down oh
they're still in there oh
did i did i accidentally press down turn
off i don't know you turn it off and on
to maintain the right height the wind
goes in a different direction depending
on height
oh is that what it is you keep on
turning it off and on
definitely oh
need um i want to go
west
never eat spoiled watermelons watermelon
and now it's going
not going east
[Music]
okay okay now
i get this and then
okay so okay now it's going
west sort
[Music]
this is making me sick to my stomach
please enjoy the ride
[Applause]
gravity direction kind of reminds me of
how like when you go on roller coasters
and when you go down that that feeling
in your stomach
yeah i hate that so much you like roller
coaster and i can only handle disneyland
ones anything further than anything
harder than that i can't i can't enjoy
[Music]
yeah actually i was i was just saying
like
if you were
um like i don't know either if you
joined earlier like you were part of
myth or so
then we would have been in japan at the
same time
and
i
i feel like you know me and callie we
would have gone to disneyland in all
kinds of places oh my god we should
totally go when you guys come to japan
oh wait
wait wait wait wait wait oh
okay okay okay we almost crashed on
someone's house
oh we're slowly getting there though
landings
it's hard and that's going to run away
again
it's okay we're going to try getting go
higher again
we should totally go when you guys come
to japan
eventually
yeah
although disneyland is so freaking
crowded man yeah
it is
but we can stand in line together and
eat churros
you good
yes
i've had like churros once in my
lifetime
that is a sin
and chocolate flavored popcorn
[Music]
i can already try like different kinds
of
popcorn but what is that sound i think
someone's trying to snipe us
for a second i thought that was just the
sound of you turning off the hot air
balloon that's why i was trying to
ignore it but
i think it is someone trying to shoot us
well good luck with that i wouldn't be
surprised if it's growing the wrong way
again
yes ma'am could very much be
she has a sniper in her face i don't
know where it is um her base is
somewhere like around like f f 11 or f
12. it's it's much lower i think or
maybe even lower wow
um
i heard it again i heard it too
is it really just not the hot balloon
hot air balloon turning off is there
really someone shooting at us because
that's pretty accurate
i think i think it's
it might be someone shooting yeah having
a little bit of a giggle a chocolate
they're dead meat
that's probably what she's saying right
now
oh
she's a good sniper though
the fuel
we have 77.
oh okay yeah last time i checked it was
like around 119 yes i think we still
have some more
[Music]
yeah
but i think all right now it's going
pretty well we're getting closer yeah i
see i see our destination oh yeah
wait it's oh there we go oh there was a
way there was a lag look
it's again you go back up we'll go back
up
okay
i should become like a taxi a flying
taxi
you're my first customer i'm a customer
i thought i thought this was free
that's a practice run free practice run
i'll forgive
i'll forgive i want to see dad's
oh so luxurious house
it is impress me it's it's a it's a very
um
quirky you know it's full of originality
um it's it's a full originality house um
yeah it's
it's got
it doesn't have a horse anymore because
the horse is at your place but
but it has everything yeah
uh
yeah it's big
what could you say ff6 or what it's f45
around f4 f5 so we can do i think that
f5 might be a little bit more accurate
oh okay
yeah
we've made progress at least
so i've heard your goal for today is
getting a what was a bazooka a grenade
launcher well yeah pretty much a bazooka
ooh there's a horse
when it's too hot here
with the fire of the
air you gotta take off some clothes
senpai
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
ah
okay i took up some clothes maybe take
off that jacket don't need to take up
some clothes too
i'm
i'm pretty cool
let me take off that jacket i was so
cool
[Music]
no i'm good now the game game is not
telling me to take off any more clubs oh
really maybe okay i don't know you look
like you're sweating a bit
how do you know
i can see the sweat droplets
oh
oh no
not
the game graphics looks realistic the
ear looks really
fresh
[Music]
we're so close keep getting there just
go up there we're getting much closer
now you just gotta wait for it to go
north yeah
oh yeah that's the right way that's the
right one yeah ice oh
oh no that's not my house i see my house
sorta is that my house i think that's my
house i see it
[Music]
there's a lot of people living around
here
yeah who lives here i don't know these
houses popped out in nowhere apparently
bailiff's pretty close
uh she told me that
this might be close
i don't know whose house
on your roof but
you want to land on our my roof
you can try yeah but i don't even know
which one
it will hopefully stand out to me
because of its luxuriousness and it's
right
um it's it's the biggest one in the area
do you see it it's right next to the the
red tower
in the woods
[Music]
oh
right now i'm not sure what i'm supposed
to be seeing
around just like right right right north
right north
right above us right north
and then you see there's red tower and
right below the red tower there's the
luxurious
iris mansion
that um is our destination today the
lighthouse right no not the lighthouse
no no no no no um we're going a little
bit to the too much very luxurious yeah
you could call the the lighthouse my
second home so it's like my
um
yeah it's it's like my uh what you may
call it my vacation house so yeah
we're just gonna land here okay
[Music]
it's close enough it's really close
yeah
see i see it right it is oh wait it is
yeah see
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh
nice
soft landing
[Music]
let me mark where it is it's um
here f4
okay right here
your walls are disgusting
[Music]
girl you live like no i don't know
construction it's still in construction
where it's going to be look better
i use those walls anymore
no no
it's it's still it's still in progress
there's nothing up here the my real
house is the there's the rock and the
wood part see
okay so so first there's
my my main my main room uh-huh the main
room is all made out of it's actually
stone in here
[Laughter]
oh
i'm sorry
i forgot wait
i almost died by my own trap
[Laughter]
too my god
[Music]
ah
friendly
return service special offer do i have
oh yeah cure's dead body
[Laughter]
she doesn't have anything valuable on
her
100 scrap
was this a setup no i swear i didn't
like the moment she died i was like oh
wait
oh yeah i forgot about the traps
wait why'd the trap disappear do they
disappear once they go off oh no never
mind there's one over here
i'll turn them off now yeah
let me just empty them if i empty them
they'll be fine right
in that sense i'm surprised in on them
were okay because i'm pretty sure there
are more straps traps somewhere else too
obviously we expect all my belongings to
be included in the payment
would you
oh wait wrong wrong chat
let me make sure that the other traps
are also optionally
um there's not one over here i'm pretty
sure
okay
leave just one bullet
okay this one's empty
um
oh this one okay let's leave one bullet
just just just one bullet oh wait no no
that's not how it works
okay one bullet shouldn't be able to
kill her right
unless she's naked
now my tc i'm scared of upgrading this
more than it
it's already upgraded because my tc
won't be able to hold everything
and i'll have to like log in every 10
hours to
refill it which is kind of scary
if she's going to be naked most likely
okay
i won't
i won't play the same trick twice now
actually i seriously didn't do that on
purpose but
yeah i don't wanna
i don't wanna accidentally
cause more wrath than
there is on the table right now
i do not want to upset the president
any further
but there's her body right here
she has a spa
and the corn that i gave her
okay
i got what i wanted
wait let me just cook this first
i won't take anything else
just take a leg
she won't need it anymore anyways
yes mmm chicken
fresh chicken cooking in my barbecue
the helicopter close by oh no it's fine
ah the smell
it smells so good
too bad it doesn't have her name on it
which reminds me
um
base
i love how the skull has her name on it
says skull of chapstick so i'll never
have to
should i get the skull too
wait would her body disappear if i get
the skull
alright let's let's
let's hope that her skull comes off
i want to collect skull oh you don't
have to move body
do i have to kill the whole do i have to
take the whole body i don't wanna
ah damn it
no skull
it becomes a backpack she's gonna
oh yeah maybe it
huh
what
no skull
[Music]
i'm gonna
i'll give this as a present
when she comes
i'll be like
would you like to eat some hope
and she'll be like sure
and i'll feed her
without her knowing that it's herself
that she's eating herself
oh wait why is one meat still raw
oh it's cause i had three okay
the trap blew her skull
you know actually sounds kind of
accurate it is a very
i'm glad that these traps seem to work
though
the first time i actually saw it in
action
yeah i can't i can't i can't feed a
robbie no no that's that's that's that's
not that's not nice
hope she's not lost
it is a pretty far off road
even we have standards exactly
she did buy a barrel
could invite her to the team yeah wait
would the would the traps be okay if i
invite her to the team
[Music]
ah wait let me just go store it store
some stuff
and
uh oh
okay
let me just store some stuff real quick
and i hope kiara's okay
she's fine
let me just i'll just save her stuff for
her
i'll put in a box or something
[Music]
so what a nice cool high should do right
mm-hmm
so
oh did we change your name
i knew i saw someone
you saw someone on my roof
oh yeah i have to have to store her
stuff wait
whomever will grub be my bodyguard
is she gonna be my bodyguard
kiara might be very mad because i killed
her with my straps
and nowhere is me and bae we have
we have um
wait was that actually my gun
we have
said that
we will be peaceful
oh
i here
yes
horse deliveries
thank you
it was um wait i'm i'm totally uh not
troublesome
everything went super smooth and fine
there was no danger whatsoever of losing
your horse
okay wait a sec
i'm almost ready wait
i see hydra can i drink your water go
ahead
help yourself no no no
i think this is pretty much everything i
don't know and the traffic these days
unbelievable come on in you'll be you'll
be fine this time
thank you
okay do you want to bring your horse to
a food source i think it might be hungry
i don't know
oh no it's fine it's fine right now
come on in your stuff is right in here
yeah
oh wonder wonderful wonderful
thank you
wonderful i hope there is nothing
missing i will check your vod um it
should be it should be pretty much
why did you cook human meat in there did
you cook a part of my body oh no no no
it's it's me i thought you wanted some
hope
so
i thought maybe you would like to
like to have a bite of hope
all right where where are the uh here
scraps huh
what's up
thank you for the 100 scraps thank you
you you said it was a hundred
yeah
thank you
thank you so much
was that that was the price i'm leaving
oh yeah you know um
you should you shouldn't be afraid of
just me though because um
you know
people here huh
it's not me who's hiding them
there's you know some npcs in this
server that tend to
be around
um
to haunt us us regular players every
once in a while
um
and they are watching
from
many different angles
that you do not expect
um
[Music]
i'm gonna i have another delivery to
make thank you thank you so much um
so it was a fun time
i'm i have no weapon in my hand so um
really you don't i'm sure you you have a
you had a spa
so i think you do have a weapon in your
hand
that is just to protect myself from any
dangers on delivery um i am off shift
now and i'm on my way to report
no no no no no that's not fair that's
not fair that's not fair i don't care
i
[Laughter]
touch
i'm sorry
[Laughter]
girl's saying something on the syrian
chat no no no no no
my aim is usually horrible it's usually
very bad
um
i expect an immediate return
or extra charge for pickup
i'll guard your body for you
i just want to hang out with her more
you know
oh look at her she's making a split
oh yeah i could take her skull this time
can't wait
but i don't know maybe did i blast your
skull again take the skull yeah the
skull oh no i'm starving i'm starving
what should i do oh thank god i had
regular meat okay
i have an axe axe is better
yeah
[Music]
i got the sky i got the treasure i got
the treasure
[Music]
let's go let's go
this is just the beginning of my skull
collection
i wanna write where bae is
her name changed which is a shame
but i'll guard her body yeah i was gonna
put
i wouldn't be surprised if she comes
with a gun to kill me though
it's time to
oh okay bang brewer together
[Music]
am i going to die yes
ah
my goal is to get everyone in the end
uh but then the server wipes happening
really soon
it's happening like
really soon i heard
which sucks because that means i'm gonna
lose all my skulls
store her stuff
okay i'm gonna go grab her her box real
quick
and put it outside
research stuff for next wipe yeah i
gotta do that
how do i pick this up again oh do i need
a hammer
oh she has a horse i hope kiara has a
horse
you already have a hammer oh
blind
excuse me i'm
a bad eyesight
she doesn't
is she walking over here that means does
that mean she's walking here
huh
okay
um oh there we go
has
wait
how'd she get
did i drop her most of the scrap
wait
why did she have 600
did i
[\h__\h] seriously i gave her 600
wait
i didn't mean to
i gave her 600 no wonder she was
surprised wait wait
no wonder she was like yeah i thought
she was saying 100 500 was a lot
no no 500 not 100 was a lot okay okay
that makes so much more sense now no
wonder she was shocked
okay i thought i dropped 101.
i paid her too much well you know thank
god i accidentally killed her then i can
fix that
i'll give her a bit more though you know
just just as an apology fee
as an apology fee
and i'll give her
two fried chicken
instead of one i'm also giving her more
cloth so she's got a deal
116 scrap
i'm sure she'd be happy with 126
but if you insist
did i give her this gun
i think i accidentally gave her this gun
it's okay
she can't have it
i just have so many clothes
yeah i feel bad for her to be honest i'm
sorry
i'm so sorry
seriously didn't mean to kill her
both times
[Music]
make a maze for
i wonder if i'd have enough time
[Music]
put a bear trap in your heart i'm not
gonna be that mean okay
no no no i'm not gonna i'm not gonna be
i'm not gonna be a cruel devil no
i don't have a plan mine either but i
won't still twitching it's fresh you
know
oh what's up
what happened
behind dome
i'm guarding kiara's body wait wait um
i could put a i can put a code on it
you're right
goomba's calling for aid what happened
i'll come in a bit wait a second
i'm just going to put a
coat
on the box is degrading
here i'll put a code on it
[Music]
okay
stash the skull first
repair the box
how do i repair the box again
i hope she makes it in time
okay there we go
and yeah i need food i need food and
then i have to go
help banger actually they don't seem
like they need help
but i'm curious i'll go anyways what
happened to my goal
getting hungry
oh wow that really made me dehydrated
mmm but chicken
um
give me the meat
man the barbecue is so convenient
i can't believe i didn't have it for
quite a long time
okay
i'm wasn't hitting my horse excuse me
okay oh god why do i have so much
unnecessary stuff on me
oh wait kiara's here skull
you're a skull
okay
i should put the skulls together
okay but first let me just uh i'm gonna
make a
some extensions for my
thingamajig
oh i hear her
i hear
i hear her
let me
hmm
[Music]
did you find the box
yeah she found it okay
i heard her say irish
[Music]
okay
whoa
whoa whoa wait wait wait wait wait
horse is in danger
or c is in danger and i had deactivated
the traps no no
oh no
i didn't see where the where did the fl
where the fire come from
i mean i mean she's mad for good reason
yes
but
wait wait wait
hmm i think it was an npc npcs don't
walk around here
uh npcs definitely do not walk around
here
um
i want to make this oh i need tech trash
shots came from behind the horse
hmm
[Music]
what's happening with
with van gora
i'm honestly very curious but i'm scared
because someone's after my life right
now
kiara has a gun yeah her spa was on her
body
wait did i cook some meat
oh i burnt it oh thank god
yeah i'll load the traps
i feel like 10 per trap is probably
enough
and i'm i should probably add more traps
to be honest
considering how it's almost gonna be
raid season
you know i i put this in such a
pain in the butt place and i don't know
how to remove it
not on purpose
and i can put the rest
in this one
okay
yeah i tried the hammer
it didn't work
okay oh
horse
i got a second horse
okay
i'm gonna go see what gorin them are up
to
[Music]
sounds like they're having some fun
do they say dom
[Music]
did
inna's horse
is kiara's horse
no inna logged up since she left her
horse somewhere
around the area
it's my horse now i guess she she left
it at the safe zone i remember
food
i'm at the bottom of the dome
bottom of the dome
i've died three times trying to figure
out how to get to the salute
what
loot i think i think somebody's up there
huh yeah
but is that the very top here anymore
not a clue how to even get up there wait
leave it to par chorus
i will save you
i will save your stuff or whatever
i hear still here i'm i'm right here i'm
right i'm getting there
i'm getting very close
oh wait how do i jump sir okay
oh do i just okay i can just go up from
there
okay
um
it's okay
we gotcha hope is here
am i going backwards
the pipes
that's backwards oops
[Music]
oh wait
ah it's scary
do you have a hazmat suit on no
no i
don't huh wait uh
why is it that is it that toxic
you're supposed to keep going straight
and jump to the pipes
you need it
is the radiation
is the radiation bad
huh
big pipes behind me
this
oh my god that's scary okay
i fell inside the dome oh
okay okay wait but i don't have to go
inside the dome right
oh my god i'm scared
okay
let's go
this looks like a trap and i'm scared
wait
let's go
okay
what's going on you really you people
are like girl
one of them streaming
oh
i'm here
down
oh yeah i should bring some grenades
i have bad experience with grenades um
[Laughter]
i don't think
hmm that's what they all say
man this this hits like this sits real
hard like karma where's my armor
hmm
okay wait do i have a hazmat i do okay
yeah she wants to talk
yeah once we heard the bottom let's talk
then
don't believe her lies oh wait i should
make a light too since it's dark
okay
oh yeah ammo i almost forgot emma and my
email uh god
[Music]
i wait okay
let me just
uh
gun powder
are you gonna collect your skull
how do you find stuff in this house
don't worry about it
okay and then um
i guess i should make
this then right metal fragments
woof
it's this bullet that the lr uses right
you can't study this i'm pretty sure
yeah you can't okay
friendly talk yeah
um
[Music]
i wonder if i can make another house
that it
[Music]
yeah
sure
how do i make a hazmat again
[Music]
uh
suits
is that you
hi
i'll go grab your stuff
and i'll also go kill the person who
killed me
how long has it lost
30 minutes
has 30 minutes passed
yep i originally went there where was
your stuff is that the very top
that's very important like it's inside
the dome oh i thought you thought it was
at the top
okay
[Music]
inside the dome and then i just fell ah
okay okay i see i see oh no no chad i
didn't mean i didn't sorry i might have
miss worded it i don't mean to kill her
no i i meant to i'm gonna go talk to her
yeah
so
it's just gonna be a friendly talk
yep
hmm
your knight in shining armor is here
okay oh yeah
i
guess
i'll go grab your stuff first it'll
happen oh no nothing
i mean i can worry i can just give you
the suit that's true grab it and then
come back out yeah it works too yeah
i'll give it back to y'all
that works yeah
there you go
here we go
okay
i just remembered i don't have any food
on me
oh can i have some food
yes
please
why am i getting deja vu
i've just been in this place before oh
thank you
there's an airdrop wait where where's
where's the cute little kohlhai
there's an airdrop
oh yeah bandages
[Music]
what is this cute voice out here
foreign
how dare she do that today
who's that
was that girl i think that's girl okay
her body's just going wild
is
i just want my freaking diaper
you had a tambourine
that's rare
is
foreign
hey
what are you doing to her body
my god
it just happened to do this i don't know
i i don't know the game is
what are you doing
no it's not your corpse it's correct but
it's corny kohi's corpse
you can borrow her husband
i was just trying to get my temper
huh i didn't kill you i thought cory i
don't know coryou said that you fell you
killed me
did coyote kill you
wait she killed you okay then that means
okay i'm taking your stuff
no no no no no no good
[Music]
wait a minute
oh
[Music]
yeah you guys look alike with the hazmat
suit and everything
yeah they were standing right next to
each other
yeah i ran into her how do i get my
stuff now that my body is
what hell
your body should have been normally
wait wait where where is it
no it's no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no that's
that's corey's body your body's right
here
i don't see it it's right here oh wait
can you is it not on your screen it's
like right in front of me wait
wait i'll just grab here here here
here's your i'm bugging you out here
i didn't really i didn't have anything i
just needed
a suit so i can go in and thank you
i think please plugging
yeah of course cory's corpse is bugging
the hell out of the system
okay
oh it's normal now
how'd you even fall inside there
oh yeah
wait do you want to come see
oh god i don't have a yeah i want to
come see how you play do you have a do
you have a pickaxe on you can i borrow
pickaxe
okay can you give give me a pickaxe when
you come back
or if you have an axe that works better
i'm i'm still i'm
i'm at
normally just around here i'm i'm at the
usual spot
okay
can you rockers call off i could try
my stuff
my stuff is still at the top
wait wait but skull
let's go ah damn it
oh
[Music]
you're very welcome
oh
thank you
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
oh
thank you
you need an ad
behind
friends
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
yeah i'm gonna
i'm gonna go grab my body if it's
all
around hey
[Music]
no i can't see it
maybe it's because my dead my death mark
is over there too
i wouldn't be surprised if corey took it
yeah
i fell
hi hi
can you see
thank you
i fell
what
thank you girl okay oh wait what
happened to ben
yeah
what happened
did i drop my gun oh dang it
she fell too
oh no
yeah i gotta remember where my
how did i do it the first time
it's pretty dangerous
how do i think about what time is it
okay
okay be careful
oh no i'm dehydrated
i don't got water on me
gotta go make bullets get cake
i keep
i keep saying i'm global chat
it's almost 12 a.m
magical
it shows on when nino is on too so
okay
oh
this is my stuff
oh yeah it is my stuff
okay
um
god i have so much unnecessary stuff
chiara's meat takes high priority
she is one with rust
that is pretty true
i guess everything else i can just kinda
[Music]
okay
ah
see how she took stuff
she took the good stuff it's okay
i'll grab this
um
oh is that clarity's water
wait
that's a lot of water
noise
i think we should empty this then
why did i not see that that loot box on
the map
buggy much
okay
how do i get down now
going on floor yeah yeah
it was around here right
okay
next to horse yep
got to get ready for that oil rig so
that hopefully i can grab a
since i have clarity at our side i think
it'll be good i took your gun
okay
that's fine too wait
she kind of needed
one uh how do i
oh
okay
you can use it for the raid
i'll go grab another gun for myself then
[Music]
oh
that was close
where's my horse
oh there it is
um but i have a night
okay
5.56
[Music]
yokai
is base house that close
see our on the map really close by
that's really close
[Music]
hey
why so much radiation hello hello
where's your house is that oh that's
your house oh my god you are a neighbor
i was wondering whose house that was
okay
what should i bring
what do you guys recommend i bring
i can bring an mp5 for i'm gonna put
some stuff that i don't need
lots of healing oh yeah
sounds about right
[Music]
rifle and scope oh i can bring a scope i
don't have a rifle
i mean i have a regular rifle
that counts
mom
[Music]
ask bae to visit for monopoly i don't
have a monopoly board on me
okay wait
um
food oh yeah and i have some health i
have some heels in here i can make more
i should probably make more
[Music]
metal fragments and look refuel okay
okay
and then
sculpt
should i make more than one scope
yeah maybe i should make a scope for bay
or something um
how do i make a scope again
oh did i not make
damn it i thought i i thought i made a
recipe
hey
oh wait my tripod
i forgot about the trap
i didn't know i could die from it too i
thought if we were on the same team it'd
be okay
okay let me close the door wait
okay okay
okay
let me get her skull
it was an accident but i'll i'll get the
skull
sorry i died too
yeah my trap
i forgot about the trap
i closed the door so you should your
your body should be fine can i just grab
your skull real quick
oh what happened
did you drop the gun i dropped it yeah
well let me grab another one then maybe
here wait
i have yo on but i don't have my pistol
anymore oh you can just use the one i i
dropped in
do you have heels
nope i have nothing here
um
okay wait
did i not have another scope somewhere
oh yes i did okay good good good
i mean let me just
maybe i should put one on the research
table though
do i have this i should have the
125.
what to do into the door
here
oh you're trying to get your body here
wait wait baby
pick this up
put it on your pistol your
your gun if you can
[Music]
i don't have food i have water i don't
have clothes
you don't have clothes wait i don't
really have that many clothes either
wait um
oh wait let me see what i have
pants shirt helmet
i have a helmet oh okay can you give
that back to me then
a coffee can helmet
perfect for you right
how do you tell oh yeah we need a boat
for that okay
uh no but do i wonder if we need a
paddle i think it's probably gonna be a
motor boat
i don't know
not 100 sure either
should i bring this along too
wait i should just make more scopes now
scope
oh wow it costs a lot okay can you eat
ammo yeah you should bring some ammo but
uh cory says that if we needed any 5.56
you can bring some
uh
you're gonna need a lot of
here wait ammo here wait
oh
uh what wait what what pistols does your
gun use again
i don't know this is yoga i'll try to
unload try to unload the ammo unload
them and see
okay gotcha i'll make some um
where where did i put it
i'm bringing
soda
i'll bring a decent amount of heels
okay wait um
[Music]
okay
damn it i hate how we have to be in
range for the thing to work okay
and
looks then an ammo
oh
i don't know if we need that
much stash away the skull oh yeah
do we need a hazmat suit
hope not
oh yeah you're still outside
wait uh
okay wait how much ammo do you want
come on i don't have any okay wait
oh wait a kiara's meat
i don't know what kiara's up to
she's still streaming
okay wait i'm waiting for my ammo to be
made
meanwhile i'm making a lot of syringes
c14 fishing village should go there okay
see 14 that's where this fishing 14 yeah
wasn't far away
[Music]
i don't think we can we can both ride a
horse i'll just walk then huh
no
you can't ride the horse do you have a
horse
i don't have anything
look
i haven't
i can't wait a sec
how much more do i have
okay 25 more okay
oh i'm out of water
is there such a machine gun
might be a machine gun
you can also ask coyote for some i think
i made some but it might not be enough
for both of us
do we need key cards
okay thanks
sleeping bag oh yeah we should bring our
sleeping bags
i'll make more heals then
i might need more
do you guys think i need anybody anymore
no great feel
body bag
you mean sleeping bag
repair your gun
oh yeah
make a bit more
okay i'll make another
body bag then
and then i can just leave the rest of
the low-grade fuel
one two four six eight ten twelve
fourteen
sixteen
eighteen
the key cards
i have a blue key card from fishing
and a green one
don't have anything else though but
i wonder if i should make regular pistol
ammo too
maybe
uh but that should be fine
prepare the gun oh yeah
uh what do i need to repair this
actually i don't really like this guy
you don't know this item's blueprint
never mind
ah so dark uh how do i how do i turn
this off again oh there we go
i'm switching guns
okay
what should i bring
you bring a shotgun
mp54 okay wait let me just
grab this
two mp5s
i don't have that many
wait
why do i know do i not i only have two
mp5s though
sniper do i have a sniper
i don't have a sniper
you have a sniper in chest do i
what is the sniper
i don't think you i don't think i do
i have three mp5s
bolt action rifle
m39 is a sniper is it
should i make another light then
wait what about the laser where'd i put
the laser
my inventory yes i know my interest
horrible
um
and it reflects
in the way i play things um
food
someone's saying i don't need to bring
the sniper
is it because he's gonna be the sniper
yeah
yeah i know wait
i know i'm taking forever a week
uh wait where did i put that thing i'm
just gonna make another one fudge it um
texture jazz
[Music]
what
okay
we can go let's go
sorry for making weight
yeah you got everything yeah
oh we were going the wrong way
[Music]
oh yeah
oh yeah i have two horses babe
take the horse
[Music]
take the horse over
yeah i'm always like this what you
talking about you're right uh you can
take the horse that's waiting outside
oh yeah
oh yeah sorry sorry the trap
okay let's
go let it go
uh
yeah
i see you see both of them on the map
c14 c14 so we're just gonna
go
[Laughter]
get on your
figure horses good
[Music]
horse riding in this game is hard
i don't know what's wrong oh i'm making
them late
what's with horse riding in this game
these horses don't know how to jump
yeah i'm i'm feeling confident in this
raid because we have gura and coyote
and then there's two of us dead weights
here
they'll balance up the team well
maybe not two dead weights
one half dead weight and
one maybe almost
pretty much a dead weight
oh
be careful [\h__\h]
and that base is also scary as hell
i remember getting shot by that bass off
stream once
his base stuck
there's no coming back if you die okay
i'll lose three guns
it's okay season's almost over anyways
i'm stuck
fudging horse
here here
horsty
is that gross base really
wow she plays a lot oh there's another
horse over there
[Music]
okay
face falling behind
[Music]
yep
no you might you know i can't hear but
we're good i don't have a phone
i don't think bae has a phone either
oh
[Music]
she
thank you
very much
[Music]
do you have um
bullets
present for you
well it's my first time playing what do
you expect
[Music]
i'm a present
oh thank you thank you
yeah
cool
um
[Music]
oh
uh
yeah i forgot the futon futon
oh
right we put it there hey do you have a
futon i brought two just in case but do
you have one two okay i do i have one i
have one okay
yeah because we're probably gonna die
yeah
okay
hmm
is anya around
uh
okay
thank you
nice
wow
[Music]
you guys have to mount otherwise you're
gonna be left behind
oh
yeah
girl can you okay hi nothing
okay
yeah the large rig i don't know where it
is
[Music]
i have a little bit of pumpkin
oh pumpkin it's good
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
um
a little bit closer she's going a little
bit closer
the great point on this thing
you have a scope right okay yeah okay
[Music]
overboard
let's go
oh i have to reload many of them
yeah it's a lot
wow
oh
oh my god the recoil
okay
the top floor guys it's probably better
to aim for the top floor from this
distance first
[Music]
okay from here
foreign
[Music]
oh no you don't have to i thought she
gave you or you already used it all
nice she gave me the
she gave me the 5.5 isn't that what you
used in the on the piste on this on this
gun
wait oh i used the other sniper
oh yeah
aim higher oh okay
nope that did not work
[Music]
around
okay
oh
[Music]
okay yeah one one
foreign
hello
right
but it's not
is it the same it should be the same
right it's not
does it use the regular oh it's the same
oh i'm sorry i think it's the same
ah there we go
that feels good
[Music]
magical
where is he
[Music]
for a while
there's so many what the heck i know
where'd he go
25 minutes to respawn okay
um
can i board
uh do you want to get on the on the ship
is
[Music]
hey
okay
how do we get on here
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
nice
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh i have a little bit more right
here we are absolutely so nice
oh great you have food can i have some
can i have a bit just a bit
thank you
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh from above too
might be
you you must protect that
okay
i don't know when you did
[Music]
oh never mind
i hear another one
[Music]
how
what
you guys good
okay no
okay
why i don't know
what's all that effects
be careful
okay let's go third floor
be careful careful though third floor
probably has enemies
nice
who did that even
oh wow my stuff going on
down all the time okay you guys good
hi
[Music]
i hear their radio
oh
is
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
thank you
nice
[Music]
where'd that come from
i have no idea where they are from
coming from
what
oh my god
i don't know
someone see me
[Music]
i don't know
where'd my gun go did i drop my gun
there's a full heal over here
you can take it
on
anyone got any more
5.56 i have i have a here here's here's
one stack
do i have this light on
yes you can put a light on your gun
if it's dark
no wait
it's an attachment
wait help yo you need you need to you
need to make an attachment yeah i forgot
about that wait i wonder if
i might have two wait
oh wait baby
oh wait no actually nevermind sorry
nice gross carrying
[Music]
ah they're inside here
huh
[Music]
oh i'm using the wrong ammo fudge
okay
no no wait
oh did i use
pistol bullets first
i brought the wrong gun it's okay
is
[Music]
um
yeah apparently there's green enemies
that are going to show up after
after we open a box
so did they eat the kuru
[Music]
does anyone have regular pistol bullets
um but they had some of the bodies had
them oh really here's something scary
[Music]
okay one of the crowns that cranes are
supposed to be a safe zone yeah
[Music]
um
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
okay
one more time like
at the top of your jumping so that you
can start climbing the thing
like you press the jump button twice so
first jump push button once to just jump
and then another jump button and then
you hold on to it so that you can
actually climb the thing
second jump you hold on to it
try to try the pipe try going the pipe
right next to you and then maybe jump
from there
there you go
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
gonna bring the enemies to us
and then we snipe from here i guess so
yeah
we're all gonna shoot
them from afar
if it gets dangerous we we hide behind
the crane
i heard there was an enemy inside there
too hope she doesn't die
actually should be good
that's like trembling in the back you
see that
trembling sounds like really boss music
[Music]
oh i see it
i see
don't shoot the helicopter
[Music]
music
is it distracting i'm sorry i'll turn it
off no it's actually great i love it
[Music]
what
i need some heavy
how do i help how do i help
okay
[Music]
crazy
god i have bad guns
oh god he's coming oh god oh it should
be a safe zone though according to
clarity
[Music]
do i have grenades
oh damn it i didn't bring any grenades
might be a good idea
are they already dead over
there's one at the there
oh my god they're fully armed
honey there are more good
grenade yourself i know
you wanna
oh god
okay
everybody
somehow
how many do we kill so far somehow
is somebody in the white box building
can i shoot through the glass
maybe no you can't i don't think so
where are they
okay
[Music]
how many more
m
they might be right under us i'm scared
to go out of this safe spot they're like
really strong
yeah
he's right there do you see him where
look they're here
okay you want it you want to go down
but if i go down it's going to go down
yeah
i don't know if i can go back up oh
but i guess it's only one dude right i
think
holy sh there's a lot of that word
that's a lot of them what i thought
of them
yeah
do any of you guys have grenades i think
it might be good to throw them right now
i have two
are we gonna put it
they're all together
oh my god
[Music]
is this really just 11.
oh my god it's still all there it's like
four of them right here are they just
all together they decided to group up
yeah they're all together all five of
them are together somebody had to teach
these boys a lesson about spacing
nice i heard a nice sound
how many more
where is he where is he
the bodies are piling up
look at the bodies
um um door stuck
nice job oh
nice job guys
i'm running like low on ammo i only have
10 left do you have uh what ammo i have
a lot of bodies yeah we i think we can
loot the bodies if it's safe
i'm just scared oh okay you know what
i'm going down
oh wow
nothing
oh
no they have some ammo
and heels
and some grenades
okay
that safe spot was a lifesaver
that was
do any i yeah i find a grenade launcher
is there a grenade launcher anywhere
grenade launcher i twist
but
i have another gift for you
oh
thank you
you're amazing i'll make a recipe and
give you one um
[Music]
ah
where is it oh
nice
wow
should wait for corey for the big crate
though she helped a lot
oh there's a targeting computer i don't
know how to use it
where could she
you guys are like wait pick up korey but
um how do we pick her up
oh yeah wait her body
i don't have that much space to get her
stuff
she's getting a boat yeah she said she
was getting a boat wait
uh wait where was her body again
is it over there
i know i don't i don't know if it was
this was it this
was it this cream
i feel like it's the wrong crane
was it that crate everything you're
getting all this grenade launcher ammo
huh there's grenade launcher ammo
yeah the weird looking ones these ones
like the dome looking one yeah
oh these are grenade one oh
they yeah i got 12. um
yeah thank you
oops
okay okay and i'm gonna go grab coyote's
body
okay that is that is where she is um
what should i save
oh yeah probably this
[Music]
you could try
what should i say for her
leave the body go get her where is she
there's a storage of the boat you can
use bull has stash
okay uh wait wait wait wait yeah i'll
put it in the loot boxes up here up here
they have a lot of the boxes or the
crates they have like crates up here oh
we can put her stuff in there
okay wait
i'm crazy i don't have much i can't get
rid of that
she's venting
it's safe on body i don't know if she
takes more than 30 minutes
use the boat you came in
the bench
you guys good
good
oh yeah you can see her on the map where
is she our way down okay
i'm gonna jump
hello
[Music]
you can vent in this game
you can
oh there's a barbie you just gotta find
the open button so you crawl through it
sauce
it's
okay
oh
i don't
i the adrenaline has left me
that was fun
the boss fight was epic
that felt more than 11 people though
oh wait iris
yeah
wait let me just uh
you can get those anywhere so it's not
that hard
i just dropped it because
you can put stuff in simple
let me just
yeah i'm not gonna touch box
yeah she's coming back but she should i
i told her that if she needs a boat
i can go back we can go back for her but
or i can i can drive her back
she's almost there okay
oh yeah she's almost twice
this food is poopy
is it
we worked so hard for that
oh it is kind of poopy
for all that work it is crap
literally just like a box okay
[Music]
hey
we had fun though right yeah it's about
the experiences
we made along the way you know how to do
it
and besides you got your grenade
launcher yeah i can make a recipe with
this
thank you where'd you pick that up from
is it from one of the soldiers
thank you
look at her those moves
she needs food
corey
where is she right now
should we just go back i'm just gonna
i'm gonna go down to greet her wait um
i don't even know if i'm going the right
way wait
[Music]
hmm
us
foreign
[Music]
thank you
is
[Music]
um
let's go
big fish where is it
scan blue card room
voodoo castle here
where is it wait follow the music
music music
where is she
[Music]
i hear girl's voice
i hear i heard her voice dead in here
yeah there's a dead end here
[Music]
wait
oh
[Music]
what oh
there we go
[Music]
is there more
oh i dropped my green card
oh it's just scrub it's mainly just
scratched
it's kind of bad yeah
it's kind of bad
no
is this
this house
this is what we risked our lives for
yeah
really yeah
i don't know how i feel about this bro
mixed feelings should we get
on the boat
bows right there
there's a boat
it's got three oh
[Music]
what
is
[Music]
yes
is
[Music]
my
oh
did you just use a heel
do you have food
oh
where are they did they go down oh wait
i see i see a gorilla down there we can
go down
we take are we are we commandeering the
ships though
crowd is pretty down for it but then
chad is telling me that
we're probably gonna zen loss
[Music]
oh
chad is telling me that it's hard what
do we do
we can try
um
i think i actually have to go so i might
might not be able to help okay it's okay
then oh that's okay
we got we got a lot of stuff going we
don't stand a chance
yeah
if grass is gone
[Music]
okay
yeah
i just need a ride back to the shore
okay
[Music]
thank you
what time is it over there
oh
[Music]
okay
yeah i almost did nothing
i feel like
like half at least half of the enemies
if not more
good hungry
it's like a christmas tree
oh it doesn't
hurt
oh
[Music]
okay
time time-wise
oh my god maybe not actually yeah
house first
[Music]
thank you
okay
[Music]
oh that was fun
in the military tunnel where's the
military
tunnel is it the same tunnel that me and
girl already wanted one time
not so sure
[Music]
i think
are they still talking
it's the same ooh
i want a revenge on that
i do want to revenge on that
it's different that one is subway
ah
oh my god i had a deathbed
thank god i had a deathbed
[Music]
deathbed right here
oh yeah i have to wait five minutes
i didn't notice i was in a safe zone
to hit
it's okay i'm not done lost yet
now be able to do that at least not the
bay today i think
i just gotta wait a bit
only chapstick would yes chapstick the
bay imposter
hmm
[Music]
they died
how'd she die
oh she died
oh no
i'm glad i wasn't the only one
we can still get our stuff right as long
as 30 minutes
i just gotta wait for my
timer to
complete
it should be fine
yeah as long as someone else doesn't
loot it yeah npcs don't loot right
yep two two minutes left two minutes
left
i mean i think bae is coming
i think bae has a timer on her too i got
a letter now
boy
did you die too
[Laughter]
how'd you die
what did you die wait
you have a you have a red mark on the
top uh right right side of your screen
right probably
no you don't
how'd you die then
[Music]
okay
she did not die the same way i did
but she was fully armored how'd she die
from wolves
okay a minute left
bro that's worse
get your own skull later
but then i can't no i can't i don't
think my body's there anymore plus if i
get a weapon out i'll be
they'll be alarming me again
i don't i feel like bae is better than
me at apex though
that's where clarity lives
okay
15 more seconds
oh
[Applause]
wait you gotta be kidding me
wait was i already in the safe zone
wait
how did i die
how
it was 15 seconds left you got to be
kidding me
you got to be kidding me
where's this chicken
die
i need to eat you
how do i wait
why won't i
huh
ah there we go
seriously
the chicken doesn't exist or something
there we go
i'm not gonna waste
five minutes doing nothing
i'm gonna make a fireplace
and use my time to make food
okay
fire
no bae is going to sleep i think she's
already
she's going to sleep in a
it's bit late over there too probably
is there another chicken anywhere nearby
no
be nice if it could find some food
somewhere
i'm scared to go close by again but i'm
gonna go across the road
i still have another raid waiting for me
raids are so fun
i can't refute
an invitation
i just gotta be careful not to get too
close
okay
[Music]
oh mushroom
very much necessary right now
[Music]
it's nice how these mushrooms are all
edible
okay
maybe make weapons while you're at it
i don't know if weapons will be
necessary
could make it bow and arrow
but what can you do with the bow and
arrow at this
point in the game zen lost said hi chef
i'm not gonna zen last no
i still got
20 minutes right
i don't want to lose that grenade
launcher please
no or a spear i've never used a spear in
this game before
[Music]
wow that uses a lot
i didn't think i would be seeing these
days of me
stabbing with the rock
before
the wipe
okay
don't die don't die if i die again and
then it's actually zen lost time
okay
okay okay i'm good now
as long as i don't see an npc
and i don't have any guns on me so i
should be fine
if i have a weapon on me i'm going to
get shot to death again no
[Music]
sniper
toys
where's my body oh there it is
huh
where'd my other body go
wait that's my most recent body but
there's oh thank god
for a second i thought
i thought
[Music]
okay let's just wear
nice nice nice
and i just had to find my horse where'd
my horse go
no weapon in toolbar
ah
okay
where's my horse though
there it is
combine the scrap
yes
okay
[Music]
kiki butts
that was dangerous
now i just have to get ready for next
raid
she said i needed to bring a hazmat suit
and
and a lot of
the
rifles the rifle
so much backtracking
i know it's all my fault but so much
backtracking wait
where was it again
ah there it is
rifle
where could it be
this is the first body
i don't see the gun anywhere oh
okay
i need to study this
as in research it
if you get what i mean
and this game is so
it's terrifying the npcs are actually
pretty good
like they know what to do
they know where to hide
they move and they have aimbots on them
it's kind of like cheating at this point
they're much smarter than the npcs i'm
used to in games like this
especially those green suited guys
how much life did they have on them
it's pretty epic though with gurus music
and stuff
infinite ammo
sounds like it
can i get down from here
somehow
yes
yeah i don't know how guru's music
worked this time i thought it was
something about the dlc but never mind i
guess i gotta buy that dlc that i need
to learn how to dance
it's so useful
who'd thought that
being killed by coyote would start this
oh base still online
i don't have much food i thought i just
remembered
i'm gonna do a food
was that default bgm really
i don't think so
is that a plane
is that a cargo drop
[Music]
thank god i have a horse this is far
away
focus iris i know
i am focusing
on the task at hand
toy
run faster
and faster you dumb horse
you have a lot of hp left
why is your stamina so low
run faster
ah
okay
oh
hey hello
you're still here
oh thank you
bye bye
okay okay let me
let me put this precious stuff
in here
i should put a lock on this oh wait
okay uh i guess put it here
um
[Music]
fishing is fun in this game i have two
sharks you've noticed in my
storage but it's hard to
actually
use them
okay um
two worms did i say guerra
sorry
yeah oh yeah no yeah two sharks yeah
right here see
[Music]
then you guys do another hazmat she said
hazmat
hi
what
[Laughter]
here wait
a sec
when it's cooked you can take
why do you not always not have food
did i not have my husband i didn't
do i leave it somewhere
you're welcome
oh there it is
ok
[Music]
i love how jew is you
let's make
let's make a flashlight then
[Music]
um
i wonder if this if these
guns should be enough i don't know
does this use
let me try unload
i'm not so sure what bullets these use
okay okay okay thank god
[Music]
i can do that later
um
what else do i need i guess i can bring
one of these
what's going on over there um okay wait
pistols
bullets oh yeah metal fragments
[Music]
okay
don't take too many guns
is this too many guns
is this perhaps too many guns
what should i leave behind i guess i
don't need
two thompsons
okay and then heels heels heels
where'd my
claws
i thought i had more
[Music]
should i kill something
i dumped both the smgs
what is an smg again
so really just bring the bolt rifle
is that what you guys mean
you only need the rifle and sniper
which is the sniper again this one
sub machine gun
it doesn't say if it's a machine gun or
not
bolt action is sniper
mp5 and thompson's
okay okay
[Music]
i don't know this this gun doesn't have
that much lifespan though left
what are these guns all looks the same
should i switch over to this one maybe
actually no
i'll bring a new one
no i can't repair guns i just don't
want to do it like right now
just cause
just because i don't know oh there's
more floss thank god
two four six eight i can
leave this behind
got lights
okay
check if you have the right ammo
i'm bringing both types of ammo just in
case
i don't have a holo by the way you guys
are like use a hole but i don't have one
i don't have a recipe for it either i
don't know where you get those
nine
hey
i guess i'll make more heels then
it should be in tech tree too really
should i bring grenades
i feel like they were useful last
time kind of far down
ah
yeah that's pretty far down
that is pretty far down guys
really do i not need the pistol ammo
should i make more of this then
5.56 rifle
uh charcoal
where's the charcoal when i need it
should i be wearing hazmat all the time
and food oh yeah food
are
i would have to go hunting if i need if
i want food right now
just kind of a pain at the moment
so i guess i'll wear the hazmat suit
then
oops
and sleeping bag
wait first
okay bullets bullets bullets
favorite this too
um
drop the thompson
where can i drop the thompson
okay
both my guns have lights on them
yep they do
okay
and then
what else do i need i have a lot of
heels
got i'm gonna get food from coyote
i mean i'm gonna use a lot of these
heels anyways so
i think it's good
so yeah
okay
where else
oh there we go
okay
i'm good now
[Music]
my
okay
okay let me put one of my horses back
i'm glad i got my grenade launcher
though
i succeeded in my
in what i aimed for this stream
okay
let's go
you can live off of that
i double do i just go to l5
i don't know
grenade launcher is different from a
rocket launcher oh is it
is it different
well that's okay
is it
was there a rocket launcher on that
clickbait oh shut up i thought it was
i thought it was
oh
one shoots grenades the other shoots
rockets thanks for the explanation
totally needed
and those kisses are cheap then
it still goes boom boom that's true
i wonder if there was a rocket launcher
there
[Music]
but i'm scared about the
that thing
okay
we already ran out of 5.56 ammo really
[Music]
where is koya she's um i think she's
waiting for me at l5
not so sure but i'll just go there
anyways
oh that's where her house is
huh
really
highly secured
houses
people have turrets in this game no
wonder she didn't need scrap anymore
karma from qr season 2.
[Music]
uti
[Laughter]
uh why is my caps lock on
bookie
you
jarrett will shoot anybody nearby
man that's high security
your horse death i don't know might be
dead
it's okay
there's plenty of horses in this world
they all just kind of spawn out of
nowhere
they get reborn into this cruel cruel
world
okay i'm halfway there sorta
and the four more blocks more
and turrets are op
do you need like an electric source for
torrents you probably do right
i want to make a turret base next season
but i'm i'm kind of
i'm kind of not the sharpest
tool in the shed so
i don't know how to
how you
build something like that
i'm assuming you need to help make a
whole process
you don't say
you're like sawdust in the shed shut up
rust electricity is super easy it's kind
of like how i don't get the red dust
thing in minecraft either
redstone yeah that's what it's called i
keep forgetting what's called redstone
i literally have to keep going back and
back and back to the video to watch like
how to make the um the melon farm even
after making it like one twice already
i still don't know how to make melon
farm properly
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
see
okay
[Music]
where can i put
my
[Music]
so niko
elite box i still don't get what it is
though apparently it will save us
in our time of need
okay
hi
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
okay
i'm getting pretty close to them
[Music]
oh my god the recoil
picky
uh
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
oh nice
okay
foreign
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
uh
[Music]
oh
hip fire what's hip fire
is hip fire like aiming like this
no aim equals hipfire
[Music]
is
you
[Music]
is
volume is fine okay
that says the music is amazing thank you
okay
[Music]
foreign
okay
shoot in small bursts gotcha
[Applause]
[Music]
i didn't notice there was another one
oh nice
[Music]
me
where
[Music]
okay
ah
[Music]
oh nice memory
oh
[Music]
foreign
um
only one dude
okay that was close
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
look at the left one look at the right
but we should probably
[Music]
someone
no i'm not using her as a meat shield no
that's not what i'm doing
of course not
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
foreign
okay
um
foreign
[Music]
it
is
[Music]
it's
okay
[Music]
foreign
thank you
okay
[Music]
is
peekaboo
[Music]
it
okay
yes i went through almost all
[Music]
hey
okay
where oh
[Music]
thank you you're welcome thank you
foreign
[Music]
oh
is
hey
i don't have bullets
come on
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
m
foreign
[Music]
is
it
[Music]
so
foreign
um
there
[Music]
oh
okay
is
[Music]
okay i'm gonna get my rocket launcher
guys
thank you
yeah i need to make sure
you need me car iris i don't know how to
make a car
if you succeed no longer clickbait
exactly
except i didn't say i wouldn't i
wouldn't end until i got my rocket
launcher
okay now get this
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
um
[Laughter]
sometimes the voice chat seems to bugs
[Music]
does anyone know whose house that is not
so sure
is
[Music]
foreign
thank you very much
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
hey
okay
[Music]
foreign
huh
[Music]
please
foreign
[Music]
how do you make a friend in this game
does anyone know
apparently it has something to do with
the tc
no no that's promoting to leader try
talking to people being nice to them not
that
you're going
to talk today
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
season
okay
that was fun
sometimes depending on the word some
words it sounds it's it starts sounding
very elite
she starts sounding very elite so cute
ah thomas got that
oh yeah
trap ammo disappeared but it's okay i'll
make more
okay wait let me just
research oh my god that's expensive yeah
okay i'll research next time
yeah you have it i streamed until two
okay that's a four hour stream let's go
um
and i have
i have the members only tomorrow
tomorrow afternoon
time to go gambling not right now
we can just go to super chat rating
okay
uh
oh god
low fps
okay there we go
the moment i close the rest i'm good
okay
ah
i'm drinking grape juice by the way
that was fun
very um
it was a very eventful
eventful stream
so many things i've never done before
okay
let's read buzz
for those who are sleepy go to sleep
it was a very productive stream yeah a
lot of people
help
grow is like odd all day
[Music]
girl was on all day
the friends we made along the way and
the enemies too
and i actually got my rocket launcher in
the end in a way that i did not expect
that i would get but
i feel like i played rust all day
henry thank you rocket launcher fund if
only were that easy it was that easy you
just have to get someone to
give you
to craft it at your crafting desk
happy hunting thank you
joshua thank you orphan of cousin thank
you as part of graveyard shift i highly
appreciate these early morning streams
thank you no thank you for coming and
also for you know working hard as well
someone to be the meat shield i was not
using her as a meat shield okay
[Music]
yeah i do feel a bit bad for kiara i
didn't i didn't mean to kill her both
times
and i think she was shooting me a farm
from afar though either that was babe
i'm assuming it's her
she was shooting randomly at your house
oh that's what it was
i'll get her i'll get her i'll get her a
gift
i'll leave her a gift sometime
a gift of apology
you foreign the meat no no not the meat
no no no
[Music]
okay
james henry thank you uh
i think yeah another rest stream another
horse to replace unless the stream will
finally break the curse
uh no i had to replace that horse off
stream though gonna be partial vlog yang
here since i've been sick the entire day
oh no i hope you feel better soon drink
lots of water it gets lots of sleep
graham can i think yeah
ricks and lenti thank you but there's a
rocket launcher and split
oh yeah splatoon 3.
it's happening tomorrow morning
i have a members only stream
i might the members only stream might
not be too long
if it's not too long i might have some
energy to do splatoon stream afterwards
i don't know
or maybe i'll stream i don't know
i want to do splatfest but at the same
time i don't know if we have perms to
stream splatfest
i asked but i'm not so i didn't i don't
think i got an answer yet
i'm assuming since it's it's a nintendo
summer it should be fine but
i'm not
so sure since it's still like new
like it just came out
oh okay
if that's the case maybe it should be
fine
yep okay in that case i should be fine
then
yeah i want to play splatoon 3.
i've been waiting for this like forever
in that case
in that case it should be fun
probably
why have i not got an answer yet i asked
like
i asked two days ago
i was saying are we allowed to stream
split too i guess they just didn't
notice okay um
okay where was i
but i don't know i'm not so sure yet
and that's not sure yet
i might not have the energy to do it
especially after this long stream i
didn't mean to stream this along it's
just it had so there was so much going
on and i wanted to have fun so
i'm also kind of a slower player in
certain areas so
i honestly don't take it to her too much
um
thank you
alan thank you hi loan shark rose did
you eat any anus and takoyaki before the
stream i didn't kill ina
i did not kill ina
nina's like the least harmless the most
harmless person in the whole server i
did not kill lina
i might have you know scared her but i
didn't kill her
excellent thank you backgrounds looking
suspicious my imagination really
was it
looks was this suspicious it was just my
room
rick's uh rigsum thank you again toleshi
thank you fi or door frame in the horse
stable where the garage doors place
isn't upgraded someone can break it with
simple tools that's how they got out
last time
thank you for the heads up i gotta fix
that
what if i haven't fixed that yet i feel
like i fixed that last
last time after that but i'm not so sure
after i made my house so much bigger
um
saison ichi thank you it's been a while
since i was able to catch your live
stream hope you've been well i'll
continue to pay for your health
especially your throat that it will heal
completely remain strong thank you
just start thank you
thank you for the multiple um mike lynn
thank you jm henry thank you ricks and
monty thank you again
excellent home security install yours
today
the the traps worked wonders though
that i do agree
it worked wonders
orphan thank you for the gift um say
something gift
um my glenn thank you
you anime girls are the best thank you
senpai
x thank you so uh i think the traps work
yeah they work wonders
they were so efficient i think it took a
lot of lives today
why is that so many people say that my
new home is
it
my
what's so yellow about me
[Music]
hmm
foreign
tamani
i usually just kind of stay at home so
and welcome to the family thank you for
the big amount of gifts maybe end
not left hand man thank you you should
name your home shattu de poners
what does that mean
i know what chateau means it means house
but
curious what motor means our shade and
think yeah so now we know you're great
at setting traps may i suggest setting
them outside someone else's house maybe
a certain ex-wife instead of yourself
but it has like the only thing is the
trap has to be like i think on a
foundation or like a floor
and
that stuff has to be connected to the
building so that
i'm assuming
they despawn after a while so
unless they're connected to a house it
means castle in that house oh
really
chateau
i thought it was like it meant like a
cottage or something like a like a
homely house okay that was weird
wife status updated after the grenade
launcher
we called tris
a stream
until they're because like apparently
she got pretty hooked at the game so she
was playing right just now
so like we were like hey i want to read
somewhere
okay
where was
i bailing baker thank you
check it up under self-defense gruesome
murder and dismemberment done on
privately owned property doesn't count
as a crime i think just fresh chicken
meat perfectly tenderized with this
shotgun
yes it's just fried chicken you know no
harm and some chicken everyone eats
chicken um shugo hastagawa thing yeah
iris i'm so blessed today to see you
kiara i dream for the day you two can do
karaoke i love it sweet and funny or i
wish i could watch more street lives but
time zones can't wait for more music i
listen daily
thank you very much yeah i hope i you
know i hope everyone come everyone we
can all like do karaoke when everyone
comes to japan one day
and of course kiara too kiara is amazing
at singing so
it would sound fun to do karaoke with
her and i can see i want to see her
dance moves in real life
i want to see her dance moves live
um
jim let me thank you
thank you for yet another fun stream
it's been funny fun to see things get
spicy on the inside of rust embracing
the chaos and conflicts is probably the
way to go i'm sure you're used to
embracing chaos by now what is that
supposed to mean
um
embracing
black and white thank you if they
switched your name you know what that
means you need to get her skull again
yeah somehow
somehow
i almost got it last time too
low simply thank you errol konrada thank
you
general butterscotch thank you i started
to think what you do to people you
actually intend to harm
i never intend to harm
never never ever murky thank you today
on rust iris finds out guns aren't toys
i was i was
i thought that you needed more shots
landed
for people to die
that's all it was
that's all i thought because the npcs
you have to shoot them like a gazillion
times for them to die
meanwhile when you get shot
the npcs are like they're like
[Music]
they're like bullet sponges yeah exactly
sway me thank you for the gift um hell
thank you karma delivered by the coyote
yeah karma hit hard uh har shayden thank
you
god rest has been some of the best
content i've ever watched from whole
life rust is fun
i'd love this rest arc
chroma thank you
blood for the blood god skulls for the
sculpture
i'm not making a skull throne okay it's
just my little um coined
collection just to satisfy myself
um
miko 101 thank you no bully please thank
you
green tea thank you don't use traps
you're always the one who gets traps
before anyone else does uh no grenades
either it's super duper dangerous
because you might miss throwing it and
blow yourself again but i i like using i
like using grenades
hmm
[Music]
as long as i don't you know accidentally
blow myself off
chappie loveless thank you for the
gifting um potato thank you for the
gifts uh itsuki thank you
thank you very much for the red super
chat link it's a lot of fun playing
games with friends thank you iris and
ganbare gambarimas
um itzuki thank you again
um
be okay thank you mr babe thank you
when coyote said i don't have confidence
i literally thought she said i don't
have coffee this as i said take a sip of
my morning coffee
i don't have coffee this it does sound
like it
if you
if you um say confidence in the
in the japanese um accent it would be
like confidence which is this kind of
sound the coffee this is
thank you for the gifting um thank you
for the gifting hdh thank you very much
for the pink super chat you're cool up
play on oil league with the coyori uh en
members was pretty fresh and fun i want
to see someday another like collab like
this thanks iris and it's pretty late
but congrats here you know to cover
1 million views oh is it
nice
that would be my third 1 million view
cover let's go
let's go
thank you very much for the pink super
chat
ken aaron thank you for the gifting mav
notora thank you grumble dog thank you
maybe the real aura rig treasure was the
npc friends you made along the way what
do you mean by npc friends
mike glenn thank you for the gifting uh
gret and kim cannon thank you angeline
thank you again thank you very much for
the pink super chat
good morning iris seeing the state of
your storage would certainly cause some
aneurysm in some people i know just will
come from resting poster rating 16 hours
for destiny two day one raid we placed
5400 for globally not a bad placing for
the team i've never played that game but
congratulations five four zero four
it kind of sounds like an error code
that you would get when your computer
suddenly starts going blue and
and shuts down on you and it's like
error code five four zero four and you
have to google it and even after
googling you will never know what it
actually means
um raven but congratulations thank you
it's fun to have fun and get a decent
score at the same time
raven thank you
can earn thank you and my limits are
going to sleep now good luck on the oil
rig i'll vod your run with coyote when i
wake up later thank you
angeline thank you second more thank you
today's flares and grenades are proof
that iris is good for being heated not
eating anything herself also nice
headshot that was cool i wonder which
headshot you're talking about there was
plenty of them on the stream
pride thank you magpie thank you very
much for the red super chat that was a
great stream iris don't forget the
number one role with guns is to have fun
lots of victims of traps and misfires in
this game it's always exciting any plans
for some action before the server resets
next week i don't know if i can squeeze
it in but hopefully
hopefully maybe
rickson lenti thank you thank you very
much for the red super chat a link and
my thank you for the hefty red zipper
tattling
um
thank you thank you very much for the
red super chat i got promoted and my
boss said we should give the bonus to
our waifu for appreciation but i don't
have one so i can only put it in here it
doesn't mean anything else just to
coincide
wow your boss actually said that
give give the bonus to your wife for
appreciation or you could just
buy yourself something fun too
sure yeah it's just a coincidence just a
coincidence
thank you and congratulations on your
promotion
and at e7 thank you very much today's
raids were so successful you conquered
the oil rig and almost won the military
tunnel and also you collected a lot of
skulls
kawaii
[Music]
it's never been a clickbait even if i
didn't get it it wouldn't mean it would
be clickbait because my title just says
i want a grenade a no a rocket launcher
it doesn't mean it doesn't say
i will get a
rocket launcher no it doesn't say that
it does not say will not end stream
until i get a rocket launcher it does
not say that it just says i want one
so it's never been clickbait
[Music]
haruko thank you very much for the red
super chat oh ink again um thank you for
trying your best to have healthier time
management recent streams to save
yourself although it's quite hard for
fun games like rust yep as you can see
but i can see the future that you'll add
you're you'll be addicted to another
literary literary game which has ink
yep
you could change the title now so it
looked like a successful stream true
uh james how do you think yeah i help
people tell the stories about the great
oil rig heist you might need to
exaggerate a bit when describing the
loot in there the the luna there was
really was really bad
is it usually like that i heard i hear
that large oil rig has pretty good loot
usually
or are we just really unlucky
it was pretty poopy huh
[Music]
not even worth the effort yeah exactly
i got a rocket launcher not clickbait
yep
sounds like a title that get they'll get
a lot of clicks and views
or more like will she get a rocket
launcher
may get a question instead so they get
curious i don't know
new stream title showing off my grenade
launcher to my way
they got me that grenade launcher what
you talking about
adam you won't believe in they're in big
end caps
grenade launcher dowry
you know i haven't i bet they also
thought that what i really wanted was a
grenade launcher too because i totally
didn't notice until chad told me it was
different
oh my god my oh she's a cliff baiter
finished work not too long ago super
excited to watch your raid today pulling
bristol is on point thanks for the great
stream i really appreciate being able to
catch it live so i hope you don't screw
up a rear sleep yes i'll try to get the
adrenaline out of my system real quick
so i can get ready for stream tomorrow
as well
uh i haven't been able to learn any much
new songs i've been listening to like
old songs to see like if there's
anything i could learn from it
but at the same time like i don't want
to practice too much because then i'll
use my throat and it's just like i
haven't i haven't sung much besides my
recordings besides recordings i just
don't sing
[Music]
so yeah we'll probably just i mean you
know it'll be it'll be a chill
uh on archived karaoke and since it's
unarchived and members only you know
it'll be
you'll be a quirky singing stream
honestly i could i could also just do
practice on stream too because kara fun
has like these guide vocals that can
help you
thank you
and something
really fun stream thank you iris
outservice thank you very much and maybe
once again thank you so much for the big
membership gifting um and robbie thank
you bloody emperor thank you very much
for the pink super chat it's okay not to
be good at building it because we know
iris is more like a tank or gps class
than a support class you know i kind of
wish i was a support class
whenever i played rp like mmorpg's i
tried to either be an archer or
a healer
maybe next rush stream fire more turrets
traps and spread your base with them
you should also have a turret facing the
hole in your stable how do you even get
turrets
archer is dps though i guess
shells have a turret facing the hole in
your steam
wouldn't that turret i mean i just don't
have a turret though i need to get a
turret
i wonder how
much scrap that's going to cost really
thank you very much
may i know how many inches are your
heels are you perhaps maybe half shorter
than b without it
no no no bass really uh
wait how short is bae according to the
website wait um
bill's height
she's
149 centimeters
yeah
yeah i'm not i'm not like that
i'm not i'm not 149.
that was that was uh
i was
maybe like
a little
a little while ago
still a little bit taller than that
without heels
a little a little bit taller than that
um but sometimes i wonder if i grew i
don't know i haven't checked my height
in a while
166 is not a little bit tall
that's like i said that's the height
with me on heels and those are very very
high heels let's say
let's say those are very high heels
it's very high heels
like humongous heels let's say
116 without heels that's too short
um
you know who's short guru is short
isn't girl like 140
small enough for cali to eat oh i think
i saw that cliff
i wish i could swing her around kelly
and her eating him
okay where was i
almost done
uh kaisan thank you very much
blue emperor thank you again rest has
bullet drop different weapons shoot with
different velocities meaning bullet
travels different speeds so there are
there are sites to show you the
calculation stats but best way is to
practice a lot and get a feel on the
range and velocity needed man that's
going to take a lot of practice
but
i'll learn along the way thank you
or maybe i should look it up it's just
that some guns look so similar to each
other
and literally like mix them up
nissan 10 thank you
thank you very much for the red super
channel link harris your voice is so
clean and listened to on stream i can
understand everything what do you think
of doing an unhinged anime talk stream
where you talk about anime without
spoiler shackles you mentioned something
before without spoiler shackles
sounds dope
be like i will spoil all the animes that
i've watched to you
if you do not want to be spoiled don't
watch
but i don't know i kind of spoil a lot
usually i just tell everyone to cover
their ears for like five minutes
isn't that just normal spoiler is
we need more pure zotz's pure 100
percent pure organic
be
maybe and thank you very much for the
big gift again
and flacco more thank you so rowan thank
you i just woke up so i missed
everything before when i heard it was a
very successful day today so good job
proud of you i can't wait to watch the
vlog heard the war between you and bay
is over so yay from now for now
for now
yeah she lives really close and you want
to keep your
you know your friends close but your
enemies closer
um
uh caitlyn happy new year thank you
and auntie seven thank you again by the
speaking of watching three have you
decided which team to join i joined i
joined um scissors
i already joined scissors
and joining the japan region though
because they tell you to choose where
where you actually are so
yep
jp server for me
scissors it's either rock paper scissors
of course i choose scissors
and dougie thank you
fun stream and lots of schnagen's ps 166
centimeters including the horns yeah i
think it also includes the orange to be
honest it's still a little cheat um
never mind what do you mean cheating
horns are part of my body they're
irremovable
they're irremovable
so
yeah
that should be part of my height you
know i wouldn't be surprised if halo is
also part of my height to be honest at
this point but i don't know
actually i feel like the halo would
be a big jump in height if that was true
maybe not
eh
okay i think i read everything correct
i will see you guys again soon
i will see you in the family again
pretty soon
tomorrow in the afternoon
[Music]
i'm going to rest my voice
and see you guys and hang out tomorrow
yeah
alrighty then thank you very much for
coming and i'll see you guys again soon
i don't know if if my throat feels
upward i do want to also stream splatoon
fast but
i'll try anyways i'll see you guys again
soon thank you very much virus
the
virus
oh if you like this [\h__\h] please press
the like button and subscribe to the
channel like a button is good for
algorithm thank you very much
i noticed a lot of my senpai is saying
that
so i thought i would
learn from them
[Music]
my
um
[Music]
[Applause]
wake up
[Music]
m
you
[Music]
foreign
huh that was
that was fun but
man i wish i
had better aim
i wish i was better at games
but it was fun
i do wonder
if i spent
like
10 hours a day on fps games for a whole
year will i actually get better
i don't know
[Music]
yeah if i had better images it looks
cooler
you probably would would i
i don't know
but it was fun nonetheless thank you so
much for coming guys
virus
papyrus
man
it's so hard to
pretend that i'm not good at games
ah
but you know that's what
that's what people like
they fall for it too
oh [\h__\h] it's a stream of stone