[Music]
la
a
[Music]
la
oh
[Music]
a
la
[Music]
a
la
[Music]
n
la
[Music]
n
la
[Music]
I'll open too I'll open now she car
Kitty
Oh
[Music]
yay
oh everybody
[Music]
hello welcome to B
w
y wow wow thank you for the
green and as you can see I think all of
us have already uh see the inside of the
borod door and this is the outside right
now oo it's it's massive
[Music]
very
massive you want to know what else is
mive your
nuts my
[Music]
tail so yeah I would like to say thank
you guys for joining and uh we're still
kind of in the beginning so first thing
first please group with your
[Music]
[Applause]
te
[Music]
don't we
have
[Music]
hello
hello y please say
something are you ready for
[Music]
today sound
much you guys are practicing so I bet I
bet you guys are
ready okay yeah are you guys ready are
you guys positive that you can yeah we
feel
[Music]
good
good we're going to do it what is what
is your team name what is your team
name well we have
one prob
[Music]
and next team the Dead Pan
team dead P
team come
herei
[Music]
SMI loud okay I want to listen quietly
all right so how how are you uh how is
your preparation for this for today
event we are preparing so much right oh
so
much
poon are you guys are you guys positive
that you guys can uh win today so
positive no idea oh yeah we're so
positive yeah
yeah and uh what is your team name do
you guys have team name KY what do you
think no hope team no hope so good I
tried to call her you say we need to do
the reaper psychology I tried
to I wish you good luck
[Music]
every
us over here please a little bit away
from everyone it's really loud yeah h
hello hello
K attention please attention
K attention key attention key attention
key a very nice Synergy between the two
so what is your team name
p p we didn't even have to think of one
because we were P nii all along we were
a team for years now
oh no sticky keys I hope you enjoy today
yeah p n will even if we don't win we
will be the winners anyway because we
are the ones who love each other the
most a that's so
sweet wa one request can you can you
during Simon Says can you please speak
slowly okay's job I can do that okay
slowly
okay okay thank
you thank you
ma wait no I mean I'm much better now so
I can do the
coughing
360 C Cole please you were dying last
night I was so worried for you I will
see the doctor again today so no worries
okay where is your teammate cing ASMR I
so call
her her manager should try to call
her G manager
go what what is she
doing hello what are you
doing will you be burying me in this
that's not my te that's what you want
what is your teammate doing there are
you having a fight
she's narrating she's narrating to make
her louder Just trying toer voice yeah
she does this often she's skiing the
toilet crony oh yeah you can adjust my
volume name sticky keys how to turn off
sticky keys on this
computer no idea go to settings H
keyboard shortcut for sticky keys off
stupid I'm laughing because I feel bad
okay okay off now I can do this as much
as I want
can I do it too oh yeah it's said it's
it's oh this PC not even my own
[Music]
PC that's a little too much guys that's
a little too much if you're if you're at
home it should be
off when you when you go to V and then
to settings and then to select
microphone do you really have the mic
that you should be using there yes
really maybe we'll fig out from people
what m is it I already got used to that
her that that this is her voice I forgot
to tweet I'm going to go write a tweet
under the tree going to write a tweet
under the
tree I
[Music]
sneeze thank you thank you who is it me
oh bless you don't you recognize my
sneezes
yet no because you never sneeze in front
of my
[Laughter]
[Music]
face
Minecraft
ID okay yeah I was going to write a
tweet and then I forgot about it too
busy hunting hi hello you guys you guys
like the thumnail it's nice right see
something really nice that me and we
still kind of waiting for kind
nice I don't
know they should they should ask her
manager so I don't know
man I don't know okay my tweet is
written hey what the
[\h__\h] I was tweeting
wait how are you going to how you going
to compete without your teammate
huh I will
res thank
you look at this such a modern home wow
I would prefer to live in the temple of
there that is
called I think I remember
[Music]
okay ATT pleas ATT pleas ATT pleas
attention please
[Music]
okay
guys treasure hunt so the first uh game
will be treasure hunts they uh there
will be around 10 spots of treasure it
can be in a chest it can be in a shelter
it can be in a dble it can be in
anywhere um so your
uh your mission is to find it yeah chest
have around three emeralds o that you
can use for The Maze
later uh there is hint around the area
that you can
check so
[Music]
y okay so before we started let's sleep
first
again oh okay is there enough
beds survival for the fittest next to me
is it
enough don't know everyone just sleep
it's okay I can I can
[Music]
oh good
morning thing one more thing
everybody the time the time for uh
hunting the treasure will
be uh 10 minutes so after 10 minutes We
Gather here again we will uh we will ask
you to gather here uh by
chat wait where's the
treasure around it it's on the it's on
the first floor okay it's on the very
first floor with the mini mini
grass
so it's not inside
okay it's part with the many trees and
grass
okay no we don't need anything RPG spaza
my RPG senses are
tingling I know where the treasures
are I can see them no it's everybody
ready
no yeah but what about Canada I'm I'm I
guess they'll have less to count the
timer so are you guys
ready yeah so if we don't we don't have
okay everyone stand
by yes okay
go find treasure okay I'll try like
around here there's probably a hint here
is this the vines that twist and Twine I
justest hden a secret sign okay I can't
read the whole thing I don't have time
behind the vines but is it like is that
does that mean it's like right close
by is it can it be up here too
how hidden is
it oh okay wait so among the flowers
vibrant and bright a great chest hides
from S search the blooms with gentle
care the chest is tucked away somewhere
and do I have to
dig oh what if I like do like this is
that okay is that like could it be
underneath that I have no
idea he there's already the next ah so
it's got to be be in this area
right what I have no
idea no I'm looking here Lis L Lis is it
like could it be that's like underneath
a block like this like a carpet no no so
I I don't have to dig any nope there
might be there might be Contraption like
buttons anything huh there's a button
here but it doesn't work you can you can
check the book for more hints I I ran it
is search the blooms care gray chest
gray chest gray why is it gray why is it
gray we need to
find I'm panicking now they came over
here what what what what what what what
what what what Ma help me
why should I help is there like a a
pressure
plate I don't know I don't
know but what's what's with the
buttons doesn't do anything what's with
the buttons ah I I I see it do I have to
dig do I have to
dig no that's me wait that's me that's
fine no mind that's just
me cuz I'm making these like did they
give up the others or did they find it
where is it MAA did they find it and and
I don't have to look here
anymore I don't know you have to search
everywhere what what n n n NY n what the
what the
what can they C go to another place if
you feel like they're already searching
it no they they would have reacted they
would have reacted if they found it I
have no idea all I'm looking here for
like five minutes now and I have you
already checked the book
yeah it says like among the flowers 500
Bri a great chest hides from side
so maybe they did find it I don't know
among the flowers among the flowers
among the flowers I'm trying I'm also
trying like try harder try harder did
you find something no I see buttons
though do we have to press them at the
same time what is this have
toak how far would it be from the
chest from the from the sign no I don't
think we're supposed to break it right
not it I don't know I'm going to the
next
one hello
hello is this one gone
yet in the forest deep an old there's a
chest with treasures on to open it you
need a clue a special key that's right R
in here
you
okay okay I'll go to the
next are we allowed to break re are we
allowed to break blocks are we supposed
to break blocks no we're not supposed to
break block okay okay
good well
then what what are these
buttons on Stones you stand both near
and far to find the chest where
Treasures are press the stones to make
the way only teamwork ah wait
wait I guess you have to press buttons
at the same
time uh ah ah Goble go
away you don't have a teammate
anyway uh
um back back go come on wait we're too
far she can't hear me in the voice so I
I see this one button where is the other
one
oh wait wait the book the book read the
book I need you for that on Stones you
stand both far near and far to find the
chest where Treasures are place the
stones to make the way only teamwork
will save the day ah I guess it's okay
there's this button right oh this button
here so I guess this is the near button
and there's another far button that if
we press it at the same time I guess uh
it will activate something but like
oh she's also she's also thinking about
that one need to find but could it be
this
one ah nobody's finding any treasure I
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait I'm
going to I'm going to do that now
actually wait keep on pressing it keep
on pressing it wait no no no I'm going
to make a group chat for us and can we
do that
oh
okay ah the team work okay that way you
can hear me even when far away yeah okay
so can you keep on pressing the button
I'll just press buttons that I find
close by far away then but like I guess
I don't know if they're related but cuz
we have to press them at the same time
right oh there's so many buttons here
are also pressing the
yeah what's this one among the leaves of
brush wai touch the gray and look around
the chest is where the branches bound
okay I'm going to go to the next one
where kuo is
coughing this one this one a chest is
waiting tucked inside search the grain
look around the chest is where the
branches
bound branches bound bushes
hide
branches branches bushes branches
Branch tree
branches how can uh how can choco chest
camouflage I don't think I've ever seen
that before is that a mod maybe maybe
hidden in
like up here is nothing right probably I
have no
idea the forest deep and old are the but
this one's like you need a key for it
and I'm like key we can't even find
something that's not
keyed has anyone found
anything what's this
to yeah see this is like something but
the dispenser doesn't do
anything that's sus that's that's sus I
see
people what another another another
weird button that's doing something but
no book
here yo have you found anything just out
of curiosity
no oh wait so I guess the people outside
our voice chat can't hear me okay what
was this one H the book is gone for one
the book is gone are they allowed to
just take it maybe it's because the
treasure is taken
oops should books be taken away there's
one
missing there one's
missing should books
be here they're laughing at
me what what
the no that's I found a shul book that's
uh empty just so I already found it and
I guess that's why maybe the they took
the book but they weren't necessarily
supposed to take
it okay the shers don't look hard to
find I want to find one maybe it's in
the tree somewhere in the trees got to
look at the trees why is there like a
destroyed
Moss uh I destroyed one Moss I think
before ouch
jees nothing like there there's like
weird wool Bo WS too and like I don't
know which one's like part of the thing
and not this could be a gray shulker
right but I feel like why is it why is
it not standing out to
me why don't I see it if it's a gray
Sher it shouldn't have the pattern of
the
blocks yeah I'm just like so confused
cuz like there's like Wes
yeah we don't have
time I didn't find anything finish okay
let's
[Music]
leave up up did you find anything
guys I found it really did you find
anything
Kyla yeah what let's get what
did I did crony did
it God damn it what the
hell okay where were the beds again
somewhere around over there maybe or am
I on the wrong side
now too much Panic the texture is mess a
maybe no but the other Sher chest I it
was like pretty obvious to me feel like
I recognized that one oh there was one
here too a book I didn't see this
book man I wonder if this one was
found wait where is everybody ah
okay
hello
hello wa wait who found who found what
Kobo coobo found four and I just don't
know how what I want to check her POV
after this yeah I don't even know so you
guys did you guys find any no no I don't
know what to search for no no did you
guys know that there's actually one
really close by well probably right here
ah what the
hell no Al so that's what it's supposed
to look
like said shers and test and Hoppers see
I would I would recognize that but yeah
me blind go down because I I only
checked like
this by I'll make you another
stage who got the emerald who's got the
emerald we did how many how many Emerald
you have um in total
nine what nine emeralds
that's maybe free Treasures if there's
free yeah free
[Music]
Treasures that's awesome two
Treasures are we the only ones
wa the only ones who didn't find
anything did you guys get
[Music]
any oh I guess I guess it's fine cuz
everyone
yeah we're going to be
honest fell in a hole like right after
the and then she found
Emeral that's okay
what what after the time
finished time
finished but the time finished I got the
one but she found them after the time
fished oh you're just salty cuz you
didn't have any emeralds huh
but that's not [\h__\h]
Fair did you get that all right then
I'll cheat in the other
games no no no did you take that one
there is it already empty I'm not taking
anything
now okay
[Music]
everyone everyone
hello hi attention
please hi okay thank you thank you for
the attention since we already done the
treasure hun so we have to go back and
the baburu to continue the Simon sa the
next game so shall we go in we sleep
first okay let's
[Music]
go what if we sh a bit together in
Minecraft the game we are
that'll be
crazy be
crazy okay everyone please go in let's
go
hi oh oh I'm catching up I'm catching up
no you're not no you're not catching up
I'm catching I'm catching the other MERS
but don't tell anyone I'm only salty now
because you guys are calling me
salty it's okay you'll
get it's okay you do pretty well with
Simon Says
yeah that's true you're going to make it
up here are you talking to me I have I
have a feeling that I'm the one who's
going to mess up Simon says not because
I don't understand but because I just
have bad
memory I'm so it's okay we'll probably
mess up before we get to five or
so
Wow Let's Go p is ready
Simon are we ready Simon am I
ever what Oh I thought it was a one of
those
dragons
find what they say why the we listen to
what Simon
says why does it matter to us what Simon
says hello
[Music]
everybody I I hope attention please
please I'm
attening I wish I could
like who's
ready no I'll let someone go first okay
okay okay let somebody go first you guys
you guys look like you're ready
no I don't want to go
first I think it's based on
no no whoever found the emerald first uh
whoever found the most Emerald should go
first right
true we have like demonstration we have
an example
ahead because s is at the top so s goes
[Music]
first
guys you will always go first in
[Music]
school how fast it goes
like I was like oh we should stand
[Music]
here okay
yeah what
else
P one Emerald per level
[Music]
what you
guys
there's okay
[Music]
okay we don't want to
practice what what's going on oh wait
hold on hold
like I was like
[Music]
okay you're
givy
right
[Music]
not when is it going to be
gu I think they're just
explaining oh okay y y wait that means
we go last right if they go by order of
emeralds do do you want do you want to
be we should be in gr could be a good
thing let's go to group p as well then
wait hold on okay
oh oh
oh
Pabi
VC where is she there they all they all
staring in silence they all went into
group
reces oh okay we so we can't even hear
the
dialogue are we not supposed to I don't
know I think it's so nobody so I if
everybody's in a group we don't need to
be in a group I think they hear us
though when we're not uh in a group they
still hear us I think they hear us but
we don't hear them no hope right CR turn
around if you hear us
yeah blink yeah yeah yeah yeah she hears
us they hear
us what toil ski
toilet okay wait should we go into a
group okay okay yeah I'm I'm going to
name it p p
no I'm going to name it mass destruction
oh what's wrong with you I don't know I
just we we needed a catching name
because they were all like no hope Pap
she's
catching it is like they do any of them
have like a I can't I can't check
no I think are we the only ones maybe
iOS sorta is like a
common uh couple name also that they've
been
using they're like time Smith or
something I don't know yeah yeah yeah
time Smith but they're not using it
they're calling it no
hope and Kobo and Canada is canibu you
know what canibu is is it a word in
Indonesian yeah it's kind of like um
like
a like rubbery
um like a handkerchief not handkerchief
it's kind of like to wipe um surfaces of
cars after you wash a car or like clean
the bathroom like a rag wiping cloth oh
that's like the Famous
Brand wow like a sponge rag exactly
uh-huh yeah that's it wait wait test me
test me and give me like give me like uh
five in a row okay ow
had
K wait are you allowed to do that or you
you start after everything is done uh oh
yeah okay okay right okay
okay
mhm um
you said back once I think then look
left and then okay I already forgot but
I think like in in the actual thing like
we start with one and then it builds up
so I feel like it's easier to remember I
guess cuz I I'll have it okay let's do
it one by one and then add up like one
and then two and then three and then
four and you
know Mund sat yeah Mund sat and back
okay K Mund had
K Mund
L how many times
L look to the left uh Kitty and jump
twice and then what you say uh throw
once and go back nice nice nice nice I
don't even I don't even remember what I
just told
you jump
twice
once is free
Okay jump twice throw once but I don't
want to lose my potatoes so I'm not
going to throw now and then
said something three times um oh yeah
what did she say what did she say three
times p p po three times right I think
so Wow Let's Go five
Emerald oh okay five rounds they did
okay I think the way we just did it now
is how they'll do it so I think I can do
it cuz I I remember the words and yeah
okay we're done okay no need practice
nice now one more one more give me the
fifth one give me the
jum what oh
she why did you leave me oh I don't know
I thought we were not anymore oh yeah we
are and everybody's in their own groups
anyway I don't want to make my brain
tired you have to make my brain
tired mass destruction
V2 oops sorry
sorry okay can you continue the previous
one [\h__\h]
um jump
twice slowly slowly what was
that sorry I just picked up my
potato okay okay okay wait okay let me
do it uh uh uh okay start one step back
look to the left uh I jump twice uh uh
throw once and uh punch three times
and did you say
jonok
j i I don't remember how many times it
was damn it let's do
once whatever yeah I think you're good
my's so tired I can't remember all this
at least four the emeralds should be
manageable
yeah Jun Jun yeah cuz if we practice too
much now my brain will be so tired come
on for you it's easier you already know
Indonesian no yeah yeah I know but my
memory is so bad well I have to think
twice because I have to translate in my
brain oh good
luck okay are they what are they
doing are they all out the what
now I think it's just e soda
[Music]
she was closing her
eyes good sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry
sorry oh this is Meta Meta red I didn't
think I would go
past flexing her wings
I I can't I can't stay quiet I can't
stand still not in Minecraft not in real
[Music]
life I'm not teaching her K or whatever
because like honestly you don't need to
I already know K yeah it's like
Li yeah it's just like times you know
even if you if I say and without K it's
the same
thing it's just saying it's just having
to remember warna Mera even though the
only thing you have to remember is Mera
yeah and Mera somehow I think of Cali
because meaa call song right and then I
think of red I don't know yeah it's easy
[Music]
why is my chat not showing on the
screen I want to
watch why should we be
last what the well okay I don't mind
fine whatever uh okay we go to their VC
I
think hello hello
welcome everything now please speak
slowly
ma
okay everyone stand by in the red
ARA
lamp uh
okay stand on the red stand on the red
ARA please am I on the red all right
yeah yeah stand on the red oh stand not
on the red area stand in the red area
in thank you are you ready are you ready
yes okay it will be super easy speak
slowly in Minecraft not in real life
again Ry ready K ready yeah okay I will
give you the first one guys pray for
us
lampar three two one
go okay can I pick it
up I so scared you're starting off of a
difficult one because Lampa sounds like
so that's like so that's like lampar
three stuff or is it just lampar and
then you're like this one stuff one okay
okay okay okay what okay okay I thought
they were telling me to throw okay so
next is lampar
J three two one wait wait I have a
question I have a question okay not
question do it wait but okay Lampa if if
I don't say it maybe it's only one time
I don't know okay okay yeah yeah yeah
okay one time okay okay and if you want
to stay that's also fine if I want to
you got it you got it ah okay but you
know uh yeah you next next is getting
harder mhm lampat mhm J M
lumat Lampa J oh I already did it okay
Lampa J
L let's go let's go let's go okay next
next next
L okay okay three two
[Music]
one that was four times already right
yeah next next next four emeralds okay
okay okay next Lampard mhm
J
L
[Music]
ma oh God oh God two one
uh hi W I see your name
okay next
okay
next uh
lamp
J three two
one
L
J was it J
uh uh wait uh L Pot and then right and
then here and then here and then did I
forget one did I forget one I forgot and
then if I turn and then if I turn right
do I turn like 45 right so to the front
oh well I mean yeah as long as you turn
right right that's what I'm confused
about no as long as you turn right I
think so I guess that's correct yeah can
we hear it ding ding ding no what was
wrong I me right oh what did I do wrong
no what did you do you should you should
end it with fing means that what fing
the other
way KY yeah first you're faing to R and
then facing to me huh he but I what I
faced right that you don't say how many
degrees right yeah no no that's 90 but
you didn't say how many
degrees Yeah I think it's just like okay
well it's a understanding oh well it's
had
up had up means only it's kind of like
we we're facing here and then because
this is Kitty and then had Kanan is like
to the right of this position so you
have to face here
yeah so that means four emeralds five
was it five right five five five five
emeralds five
emeralds yay
oh you go okay thank you thank
you
what
what it's so over what do you mean it's
so
[Music]
it's the same as me
they have the same
situation I thought as is this right
right yeah I mean that is still right
yeah still right that's still right
[Music]
high
five we going to VC
[Music]
or never said that
what do I say can you know
cupcake no but Chad there isn't even we
weren't even taught like a turn behind
or so so like if if there was a turn
behind then I would get it cuz then I
turned around but there's just right and
left and I turned right but okay seems
like like we're not the only ones I even
said it out loud and I even discussed it
with wait so you know my intent right I
even said it
[Laughter]
like yeah
man I even said it out loud I said left
right and then wa asks me like
oh oh like oh and I'm like yeah as long
as you turned right
right great
[Music]
let's see how far you make
it oh are they doing the
same wait I think everybody's doing the
same
routine wait if they're if they're all
doing the same routine you can tell by
watching you don't even have to be in a
[Music]
VC yeah but that kind of question
doesn't come up until like when it
happens cuz it didn't happen during
practice or
[Music]
so do you want to do VC
okay okay I want to also explain
something to the chat so we can do it in
VC as okay I
made hi so it is very unfortunate but I
guess after some thought I guess we were
wrong because technically had up is um
the real meaning is to basically turn
turn as in so like if you turn you turn
45 but at I guess um but there we
weren't told that there's like for
example a back if if there was a word
turned back then you know no no there
there wasn't right wasn't a so then
facing right to me is just any right as
long as I turn right yeah yeah I think
it's kind of like they were strict
because um because iOS soda had the same
issue yeah they can't say it's okay for
us when they say it's not okay for them
yeah but I don't know honestly to be
honest if they let iora move forward
they could go 10 easily because I feel
like like still easy you know yeah it's
like a little bit no honestly I don't
know I don't think it's that easy cuz
the nervosity really made me forget
everything I just
heard yeah me too even if I heard it
five times yeah as long as I repeat it
in my head it's like better but I feel
like I I hope I hope they do the the
exact same thing to them though
otherwise it's not fair yeah like had up
Kanan after had up kitty and see how
what they do if they do it right then
it's fine but I hope they do it because
we all receed the same treatment yeah
yeah if they got the same so I I get
that we would get the same too yeah yeah
they get the same gestures everybody so
if you stand here watching them you can
remember it oh okay
okay well okay well let's just um view
then I feel like if everybody makes the
same mistake then it's it's whatever and
if they don't then they're lucky it's
fine
that's why it's I don't even know
degrees I don't even know deg I don't I
can't count I mean 360 is is a 360 like
a full turn right a full circle and 180
is a half circle of
it I'm not really
sure is doing
it she's she seems to slow be in it
yeah how far are
they let's see when they start moving
again or are they discussing something
maybe probably same thing
maybe
D N
oh uh they just went yeah they're pass
they're like they're oh I feel like
they're at eight or nine or
something cuz they're past the look left
right oh they did the yeah they did the
jumping now we didn't even see
this did crony K
already get their
turn no right why is she dying
Kyla panicking
really
why no Panic calm with k
Kyla is gamer she doesn't need to
worry it's all
right but even you know no matter how
much we get we are still tied with I so
it's okay oh tied in this game but not
overall right yeah cuz they got
Treasures they got Treasures well it's
fine we can probably we can probably it
doesn't matter cuz like I said in the
beginning even if we don't win the game
I'm winning because we love each other
the most I'm winning you yeah we win
each other at the end of the day we're
the only ones who went to the
males nine they got nine
nine that's so
good
[Music]
BR you should you should show off your
Indonesian my Indonesian
you should say in the Minecraft chat an
an yeah a n j a y you you always say
that when we an Oh I thought I was
saying
an what does an
mean we don't need to what happened
right do we the title is It's so over
maybe not I think it's
fine I don't get it we're not
communicating ah there VC is called
that now they can hear us too it's so
over Bluetooth
restrict is crony Kyla the last ones I
wonder Oh Canada Canada KOB didn't go
yet is Canada having issues
accid press shift instead I did the same
thing yeah yeah I did the same thing
that's a Minecraft
issue there's Vines maybe you can climb
up the
vines yeah yeah
yeah nice okay they're going that was
one I think oh two got two steps okay
yeah yeah that's what I mean okay so in
total we have we got
14 yeah we have 14 wonder how two steps
two steps I love that they included
Vines um so I have it if you free
steps three steps we have two no no no
no is there the F stage
[Music]
they're throwing the same thing two
three
and oh they're still
there oh they're still there I guess
they don't need
to I wonder aord and
[Music]
aord probably has more reach but there's
only a wooden
sword a breaks Shield
one two
three four that's that's four I guess I
think five okay she looked left now
there now the question how is she going
to now the big the big
moment I mean they may have already
heard it because we were in public VC
when we talked about that in the back
[Music]
H yeah maybe they maybe uh I know I
don't really care it's fine N I think
it's okay yeah it's fine come on come on
do it do it
come
one
two three 4 five and a she did my
mistake she did my mistake
oh no I really feel they I think they
should say that's okay that's my
personal opinion but
whatever I know I wanted to go further
like I I I knew what I was supposed to
do feel like I could go further if I oh
definitely everybody definitely could
even could for sure they got the EOS
connection yes
like everybody's making the same mistake
almost
everybody
damn well I wouldn't I wouldn't call it
a mistake
though maybe my way of thinking is wrong
but it seems like several people's way
of thinking is
wrong we're we're having a different
brain moment the brains are built
differently it's just like I think um
the schedule of Holo ID cup is so tough
you know and a lot of things happening
so I feel like even during practice we
were still like um testing stuff so I
think when when I was practicing and
they were like kitty Kanan I was also
turning like quite drastically but
nothing nothing was said then uh nobody
and then we didn't do any like right
turn right right after turning left you
know so it was less noticeable yeah
possibly you're right K Kyla also did
the same I wasn't just crony I I just
watched uh crony but
I did it correctly because oh wait oh
okay yeah you made it you made
it okay I'll do my best let me tell them
crony
Kyla oh yeah you're not the only ones
who did that how many rounds do we have
yeah because I was like pretty confused
right because after the that one and
then I was like stopping here and then I
was like should I yeah right which
because the reset position right you
like yeah because it's like a reset
position so this front or is this right
okay maybe the default is here and then
so I turn turn right one I just thought
it doesn't matter as long as I turn
right no matter how right cring there a
bit also did the same mistake too should
I do wait wait what was it so like
they after turning left right to turn
right so you have to so the correct
answer is apparently to turn 45 but you
turned 180 0 90 90 but a lot of people
turned 90 which is technically it should
fine but apparently it wasn't yeah we
turned the same and iOS too my group and
you we did the all we we the three of us
did the same but it's fine okay cuz like
we we think we're turning right so we
were doing in our head we were doing the
same the right thing but we went too far
and that's the problem I'm just I'm just
relieved that you know like I I didn't
mess us up I was like I thought I
did no you did good good job it's okay
it's it's it's not it's not partly you
good
job ah what 90 is correct we did one 180
okay 90 I don't know I'm confused to
getting
confused okay how's it going over there
with KOB is last right okay let's let's
watch them let's go yeah yeah yeah let's
go watch them let's see if they
but they hear us when we're in outside
here so
maybe I will not say anything yeah we
Hush Hush okay
so quiet it's allk p let's go into
VC let's go
V okay hi hi hi and now we can talk okay
we can talk yeah she probably needed
something to throw
mhm what's going on in this
one they're whispering
H ku ku was training Canada really hard
like they're in the military
[Music]
so what why Ena why Ena of the mountain
why what's Ena doing she pushed me
down or was it Ana because she hates me
you never know if you don't have eyes in
your back hate each other no we love
each other but we hate each other love
hate all the same if you know play the
game oh Kitty oh she looked left and she
oh it looks
90 180 instead of 90 degre oh people
[Music]
people I saw it I saw it so another
group who made the same mistake another
another group another victim 0
yeah at least we're not the only ones
that makes me feel better yeah yeah that
makes me feel better much better okay
maybe leave uh VC again I guess
okay uh Bob Bo it's so
over it's so over it's so
[Music]
over we hate angles we only love angels
I hate
angles angles who needs angles angle or
your devil yeah no can you be my angel
not my angle no I would need to die
man skiy skiy
man it wasn't for
that five so many so we have n 5 five
three
[Music]
[Applause]
is building gu oh noing oh my God I will
I will try to
[Music]
smart should we just build
build don't confuse me with your mask
what the hell oh sorry oh
[\h__\h] I like wa is talking to me but I
see Ana's face what what does this mean
pleas come on come on
[Music]
come on let's go downstairs let's go
downstairs wait if you said that with
Ana voice then I would have really
fallen for
it Anya Bo is really good
yeah
still no
[Music]
pushing pushing pushing
is pushing yeah it's kind kind of like
you're dizzy pussing pussing yeah
pussing you know you know in in German
in German busy is like a little a little
yeah a little a little CH a little
little um like kiss on your cheek oh
okay I
lovey pussing from too much booy yeah
pussing from too much
[Music]
booy oh my God
oh they made uh areas to build oh wow
are we building at the same
time where
she are we doing this at the same time
all we are how do we know R SCA
here
okay oh we have to write it down
to prevent people from cheating oh nice
so people don't scream and they're like
but like well you will probably explain
this anyway but like does that mean that
everybody gets the same amount of time
how do you write this yeah everybody
gets 1 minute each oh so as long as we
get it the same time it doesn't matter
if we get it after 10 seconds or after 1
minute have right yeah because we'll
wait for 1 minute anyways okay cool guys
how do you write this
hey you just open it right click
yeah now I think we have to decide on
one guess we can't write
several oh
damn but then you can't oh that's that's
quite different from yesterday though
because like yesterday I knew that if
you if there was no ding ding ding ding
that my answer was wrong and I could
continue answering answering answering
now I have to think of one answer and
decide on it a minute and it could be
wrong though I can't ask you right
so in the practice I mean obviously you
can't ask
me please go to all VC go to is there an
old
oh
is we'll be explaining the rules now
okay
okay so everybody
has uh 1 minute each and we will be
starting at the same
time
uh how do you say it
[Music]
in okay
so for the builders you guys will go to
the corner over
here and you guys will see the theme for
yourselves so we made a room over here
and then you guys will come in and see
it at the very Corner don't don't come
in yet don't come in yet oh okay so this
is like secret room I forgot yeah secret
room so these are all to prevent anyone
from cheating mhm okay
cheating so when you know the answer do
not scream it
out in the books okay now for the
builders please um
come to the uh
[Music]
corner do not turn the page
okay uh
turn oh and chat please don't spoil the
like what you see in the
Builder side in the guesser
side only only only press like they're
right okay there you go go ahead can I
can I try and I guess when we're
building it's best to mute
right okay when you're
building round one the one yeah okay
maybe maybe the guessers shouldn't look
at
chat yeah
that's um um also I think a better
idea okay remember this right
I got the okay wait did you guys both
already
saw answering
[Music]
right in the book
question guys I think we'll have to
change the theme because and K they both
look I accidentally signed it was
[Music]
acci okay attention
please I cannot okay Builder
[Music]
is this all of the builders for the
non-b builders please stay in your lane
yeah please stay in your spaces so that
we can um monitor you guys yeah yeah I'm
on the
V and monkey
[Music]
how do we write the
answer iite it okayy soror I got it yeah
monkey has good view
B right wait do I have to sign the book
and it's obviously just one
[Music]
guess please look at the chat okay okay
Builders go to
bookroom okay um wa hold on
guys you guys the Builder yes
okay build hold on please wait okay
please wait okay
okay
okay run
one it's it's the time girls again
fighting in a timely manner
intense this is just like done looking
at it this is just
like we need to see it
now okay okay
[Music]
okay the pr not
yet the pr is here round one
okay already
see okay okay
okay
okay okay yeah okay thank you
[Music]
4 p.m.
okay I couldn't hear your
voice um I'll I'll I'll face this way
then yeah I
guess this
way over
there is that I don't
know they're doing it they they have
scaving inside
appreciate it
rainy okay is everybody ready
yeah group chat I'm going to have a
voice group chat so we cannot watch so
from the PC group chat okay
okay
okay proximity only or should we have a
group but we're not supposed to okay
let's just create a
group oh okay that works too from on the
floor because it's like more surface are
okay leave it to you okay wait I'll make
a group I'll make a group P
nii why do I call her papanasi
now it's supposed to be mass destruction
but okay sorry yeah okay I I'll build
from here so there's like more
surf so you should look from
it's okay I'm uh I'm looking from up
here from The Vines I have a good
view okay I can also see what the others
are building so I guess everybody has
the same prompt so I'm going
to I'm guessing cuz I mean I'll probably
oh well I guess I can do it like this be
able to
tell count
it okay well I I think text is better
definitely take take your time with
building by the way I think you should
should build like uh as much as you can
in that one minute don't don't just like
try to build fast because it's not about
time anyway anymore okay okay you goody
you
goody
[Music]
go oh they're all very these ones are
all similar
[Music]
oh well I mean that could be anything so
[Laughter]
far um I me could be
anything any kind of
animal
yeah how much time what
already it's
over that was one minute everybody did
the same thing that's so [\h__\h] funny
what
what wait she there's still building
wait there wait somebody still building
yeah so Z still changing
things and Ena is still changing
things then I'll change stuff too if
people are changing stuff yeah it's it's
fair that
way that also changing more what or are
they getting rid of it oh they're
getting rid of it never mind well I
don't know some animal put it on here
awesome so animal WR down answer and put
it
[Music]
here
wait I don't
know that could be animal first I
thought it was a alligator
but
okay okay okay okay okay but there's
like no way there would make an
alligator it's got to be simple
words
theer oh my God I mean it could be
anything
[Laughter]
why are you
laughing no it's okay I like
[Music]
it well all answer checked anyway so
it's not changing anything did you
happen to see the other the other people
build yeah they're drawing the exact
same thing right I kind of saw yeah the
ones next to you pretty much built the
same
thing well since they check the answer I
think it's I it's fine to tell you it's
a car
car not all vo yet I thought that was a
tail and eyes the the holes look like
eyes and there was a tail animal brain
then it's fine that brain and also some
parts looked like ears but then some
like from the others too and then they
got rid of it and you also I feel like
you also got rid of it but I think there
were ears
first it's like the you know some like
SUV
car damn it but I now that I know it I
feel like I get it yeah okay wait so do
I get rid of the book that's
what
wow wow oopsy what how do I get a take
book
okay
wow
damn
genius maybe should I change my strategy
maybe I should no no it's okay it's okay
don't worry I think you're doing well
okay okay but think of what I what else
I could think of and how you could
prevent me of thinking of those
things that's
so especially is you know
yeah H like like if you give it Windows
you know it looks like ice to me but
it's probably not going to be a car
again so we'll see we'll see yeah
because there's not enough blocks to
differentiate I I'll read again ah now I
see they were building like upwards
maybe because they wanted to do
threedimensional like an actual car but
that would that one minute one minute as
we now know is way too little not as
long as we thought
so she shears I
will I might try build yeah but but but
you know how how short the one minute
just was I don't know if you can build
three dimensional like at least you can
build flat threedimensional but not like
three three
3D you know what I mean oh what the
[\h__\h] cuz like I don't know you know what
you can you can you can never I'm sorry
3D 3D is tough sorry here's your shears
do you mean do you mean you want to
build
upwards yeah I think I want to build
upwards yeah upwards should be fine but
like 3D like having it be you know
friend shaped that's difficult I'm gonna
give it a try I don't know G but just be
you know wary of the
time it's not as long as I thought I I
don't know how I'm even going to build
this on the ground that's the problem
okay don't worry you can do it it's all
about my brain I'm getting a migraine
ping
ping sorry sorry
sorry okay don't fall down
okay all right oh no
well they all
started mm mhm
mhm MH mhhm that looks like the thing
from
before not what you're doing waya the
other ones oh every oh oh they all want
to
oh there is no way there is no
way they wouldn't do that
right I don't know okay let's
see I can't no there's no way I can't
this is the only thing I can
do I I I'm I I'm thinking of something
but I can't believe they would build
something this looks like a
Bora yeah that's what I was thinkle it
seems what
wow it looks like B to
me or I can't say anything what the
[\h__\h] but wouldn't they go for easy
awards that looks I don't know did it
have I feel like it have one
top or it's um a
plug could be a n that doesn't look like
a plug over there e wait wait wait wait
wait
wait let's see the way I know if I'm
doing IM
I'm good or not it's like I'm seeing
everybody they're building something
pretty I don't know how to write it
but cuz there's no other way
honestly I feel like it had only one
thing sticking up I don't know I don't
[\h__\h] know what is wait wait maybe
it's a wait no no I want to change I
want to change
no what what if it's a cake no nah it
doesn't look like a cake with all
[Music]
them okay she didn't laugh this time Rea
didn't laugh laugh at my answer Rea
didn't laugh at my answer okay
but I can't believe that it would be
such a difficult word but that's all I
can think
of and maybe they do it because ID you
know oh oh only K
there but there looks very different
too I did F cake at the end but your
candles look like you know they make no
sense to me why wouldn't they be more
aligned like but that one over there
looked like a cake after you know I
thought about didn't I say it out loud
for a moment when I wanted to change it
oh my God yeah the cake makes so much
more
sense cuz it's a simple word but I
thought simple words
like but why was it separated
over damn damn it obviously it's not but
you know I thought maybe you know ID
respect you know think about the temple
that we're inside of oh my God you're
you're thinking so much over thinking
because you love I love yeah we're in
here you know we're celebrating ID you
know can you clean up for me um please
thank cuz they're making me no and then
damn a cake in the shape of a
temple believe in
yourself okay something difficult
sounding maybe a simple word but
difficult to build
obviously Aura awesome believe in me oh
yeah M I feel like there's like a lot of
bias with the color even though they
said like the color but it helps people
think if it's like the same color you
have colors nope I can't I'm we're stuck
with blue this thing is definitely not
going to
help
okay
hi hey what's
up she can't hear you oh yeah I think
she just wants to know if you saw the
theme yes I sh oh sh
you have Sher in your
hand that was Lampa lamp shears oh okay
oh
oh there you
go start
in I'm probably going to fudge it up
it's okay I'm going to I'm building
um oh freak I don't
[Music]
know um how I should do this
oh I mean that looks like a bell to me
no no
[Music]
this looks like an egg what the hell is
that this also looks like an
egg this what is a 3D
[Music]
attempted
may please um I know I know I think I
know but when I look at the others it
makes me doubt myself like what are they
making what the
please this is the best I can do no I
can't no don't say over what the hell
what are they building I can do trust me
trust me what what are they what this is
the best I can do
really um this is the best I can do what
is that what that confuses
me because there's no other way to build
this one minute I
mean I'm sorry Raina that looks like a
Christmas tree to me more like an egg
though look at the Symmetry
though suppos to say this but
[Music]
it's stop dissing our it's a Christmas
tree that one too that's the decorations
here same as there and it's like tree
shap and there's the the Bas mine isn't
there's a symmetrical yours isn't what I
mean trees are not always super
symmetrical I'm going I'm I'm going to
look at oh is it I mean but like we we
are struggling but like what's everybody
is
struggling cheese wait is it cheese I
don't know but then why they
look [\h__\h] Christmas tree I think is
pretty simple cheese is fair cheese is a
fair guess cheese is fair yeah cheese is
a fair guess
because I get and pizza what about pizza
pizza is a fair guess also but I can't
change it anymore right well I'm just
I'm not saying it's right I'm saying
it's a fair oh yeah they already checked
it I was fing pizza too yeah I want
melon oh my God that's
why but
like that is difficult we could choose
our colors I wish we could choose our
colors onestly well yeah but then even
doesn't make sense it kind of gives you
the bias yeah melon
watermelon and iOS probably did a good
job too but their blocks were red
ah so I think like it's just a brain
thing you know yeah
that's but it's a brain thing even
though they
say yeah yeah yeah cuz if someone's
building with yellow I would 100% think
of cheese like Swiss cheese know they
say color doesn't matter
yeah everyone should build with
gray just gray
wool yeah that's okay I'm I'm sorry way
I'm so useless right now no no it's it's
okay I'll think I'll think of but
watermelon watermelon isn't simple isn't
that simple it's not even a simple
word h
it's okay it's not your fault it's it's
really hard I was guessing I'm so sorry
like every like you know everybody's
building the same thing and not
everybody able to guess either
yeah oh no I don't know how to do this
I'll try my best though I'm going to
build
horizontally and did you already see it
yeah I did okay
[Music]
it's fun though I like building yeah
come back way Builder switch no after
this is there oh [\h__\h] sh sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry I AC pressed
don't don't stress let's go okay
[Music]
what why is theirs
roundish and yours is like flat on the
[Music]
bottom like that's red so it makes me
think of a cherry over there but
this doesn't look like a
cherry that looks like a perfume there's
probably a reason for that if one tree
it looks like a cherry and the other
Stone yeah that because it's not a
cherry that looks
like that looks like an Alchemy bottle
sorry sorry sorry actually that looks
also
ah is this like a potion but is it but
that could be a lot of things it could
be potion it could be bottle maybe the
more but po if it's a potion even if you
get it wrong maybe bottle because like
that is square and that's if it was if
it was a
potion um um um uh wait
um I
will go with the more generic thing that
could be more more
[Music]
simple I don't know I don't know I don't
know no I don't know I don't know I
don't know I don't know I don't know I
mean the potions are in a bottle
so it could be both po there's Potion
bottles there's bottles where there's
potions in yeah yeah yeah yeah there's
bottles where there's potion in and
there's potions that are in bottles but
there's
no B there's not always a potion in a
bottle I don't
know she's still
laughing what I've been I've been muted
by the way so it's fair I am I'm talking
to
[Music]
chat no
no is it is that wrong that wrong waya
you can tell me now I won't change it
anymore so you
[Laughter]
could hi what is
up oh no
[Laughter]
was it po no no you know but it's the
same thing it's the same thing Los our
[\h__\h] it's okay because we love each
other L what we
switch oh oh no I thought I was I
thought that was by
choice here here I'm give you the oh
no oh no I'm going to do worse than you
oh shoot
I'm going to do so bad because
especially cuz from this angle I can't
really see how the others are building
it that well one can see kind of over
there I I didn't see at all I was just
trusting my gut it was just that
apparently they're building the same
thing as me I fin one minute is too
short oh wait I have the book no I don't
have
it oh shoot um well wait can I just use
this book yeah yeah you can just delete
what what I wrote oh no oh there's a way
book also
sorry can you take it can you can you
take this please me wow wow so I can put
my book ah
okay I can't write how do I write take
book oh and then the lect wait I didn't
see that wait I didn't see the
wait I didn't see the
prompt I didn't see I didn't [\h__\h] see
the prompt what the [\h__\h]
that was too fast I was dealing with
your
book uh you know what it's okay we can
do the same
prompt just give me one minute can I
start I don't
know um go on okay but then how
much okay um did she even see I don't
you know what it's
fine I can wait
okay this one isly kind of how do I get
up there
impossible I
guess did I say it out loud by accident
I didn't right no you didn't
okay
maybe I think it's like switching you
know on it's
M maybe a little
bit can't reach
it I'm going to mute
myself I mean that
looks pretty
[Music]
decent maybe
let's let's do like
this how does that look
guys cuz I think think you
know it
it okay I mean I mean wait consider what
the others are building too right oh Oh
that's oh that's
good not a h but that looks like I have
no idea what that thing is over there on
the left side the right side is
good what is that
what is that what is that I think that's
I okay this is that part no hold on this
is that part mm
hold oh did you ride it already wa I did
I don't know though let's
see I I think since you already wrote it
and they already saw it I can already
talk about it I guess so yeah yeah so as
long as alligator and crocodile is the
same then should be fine okay okay okay
nice
baby I forgot the zigzag that's a good
idea from Orange side the zigzag is good
I was going to troll you and say oh
that's a really nice shopping bag
honestly while I was building it I was
thinking of a dolphin because like the
the uh the blue makes me think of
dolphins yeah but I just try really hard
not to let it affect me you know yeah
yeah uh it's like when you I thought it
was like some sort of car and then you
added the four legs yeah yeah the legs
were cute right yeah they stuck out to
the side because they have like side out
sticking legs kind of the blue made me
think like a think of a dolphin at first
yeah yeah but it's probably not a
dolphin yeah don't think the CU you
didn't draw the fins or something yeah
yeah it's never the first thing you
think of maybe I don't know no actually
thought of a lizard first oh wait can I
should I look again do they have a new
one they didn't announced it yet okay
okay oh
okay we should we should just destroy
everything before Ru passes by so she
doesn't diss our builds
yeah M how did you know by that
damn that thing that was funny but it's
the it's the head it was the head you
just have to look at it that way but I
feel like this this one if you look look
at that then and after uh and after the
answer is announced just go straight to
see the so you don't forget got you got
you thank
[Music]
you could have also been a dinosaur
skull yeah but I just thought I don't
know I I wanted to write house gecko or
gecko but I think remember the house
gecko saw like when we had dinner we saw
many geckos I love geckos gecko but
that's also too simple H too difficult I
mean gecko yeah Geck is like more Niche
I
guess still
no still no no score no score yet
apparently they haven't announced it no
more wait there's green here what are we
supposed to build with green
h what do you mean there's green wool in
our hello maybe we're supposed to build
with
green was there someone else building
green I'll do green
now I'm
hungry zaa looks like me I'm not going
to lie a little bit it's the it's the
gray hair and you wearing the same
clothes
yeah y finally sorry Raina that we
didn't get anything until
now I'm sorry it's fine take book and
then I'm going to erase oh [\h__\h] take
also I wasn't laughing at their answer
like but like for what they had I think
bug would have maybe been my answer too
is that the last round I don't know I
only Built once one more okay one more
round what I I don't know I don't know
where
my where's my box oh there we go gang
gang yeah see the promp see
the okay I think I know how to do it
okay okay
[Music]
think I know how to do it
wa what you're okay I'm I'm building
right no I'm building huh I only Built
once you you built four times or so oh
sorry I for oh my God I forgot go never
okay never mind oh my god oh yeah
yeah my head that's why I didn't have
any wool you didn't you didn't look at
the prompt right no no no I didn't okay
I was just like yeah never mind never
mind never mind
okay I I know how to build this it's so
confusing has anybody seen the book not
me has everybody seen the book not W you
see the prom
right uh W you should see the promp
right wait did I
take that's what you meant
Chad I took it like
automatically I thought you meant you
have the book as an I have Way's book
Oh I thought you meant to have Way's
book bro
oh
[Music]
ca okay okay okay are you guys ready I
hope you guys are ready we are ready
fief CH I am thiefing once again oh my
God I am hungry
[Music]
let's go let's
go oh I have a good idea I have a good
idea wa wait wait stop focus focus
oh oh free five not
sing so
hry
that middle finger
in my brain it's like what the [\h__\h] in
my [\h__\h] [\h__\h] um wait wait
uh wait wait wait it looks like snail
yeah look
like wait
um
[\h__\h] um I forgot to put
it ignore the thing on the side
obviously I
I I can actually kind of see it maybe
here maybe like that
[Music]
I
mean I mean you know and you
know and you
know you
know you know you know you
know you know you know
[Music]
what this last round we can leave it
like that anyway I
guess that looks like a poodle to
me looks like a cute
[Music]
poodle oh oh all he said oh
oh wa what are you
thinking what are you thinking
[Music]
wa camel why are there so many camels
[Laughter]
I mean you always see it like
differently when you're not the one who
built it
right
so I'm just not
seeing
it is that is that like is it
like is it
like did they spell it out
they spelled it
out was that the
r Wait you already put it in
right
wa wa oh sorry sorry
hello I put it in I put the answer in
okay already what is that thumbs up yeah
I know that's not it but um I know
that's not it but I I just
yeah yeah and if you see coobo and if
you see coobo Team well there's no rules
against it but they just tra that's why
they got points in every round I don't
know I don't know I didn't see but uh
it's just for this round I looked over
there I was wondering like what they
were doing over there it always looked
so
weird
H I was wondering in between though if
we were if we would be allowed to do
that and then I thought ah no way we
should not do that I don't think I don't
think we should cuz like it doesn't make
it fun you know cuz like cat you can
just ride c a pretty easily on the small
field yeah whatever it's fine let's
[Music]
go co I think I need
to uh punish her you need to I to punish
my child for that kind of
play please get your emeralds in the
chest so we got what
one why
five yeah why there five so I just take
five I think it's the total so far from
also the the game um from before maybe H
I got mine oh I don't have
mine do we both get
I don't know then I'll just take mine
now I took it I have
okay I don't know that's probably fine
I'll join yeah it's whatever if they put
five join muted okay
I
M okay everyone oh you think it was
Canada oh wasn't it like every round
mute okay yeah yeah mute who knows mute
everyone mute
uh one round five emerals one salmon uh
one draw
round that makes sense CU I think we
only got one round thank you so much uh
for playing this game we move to the
next game yay it's a wrong wo so we have
three minutes to play with the team
minutes every each round got five
Emerald there will be like three rounds
so let's go to the to the wrong W
together shall we come on come here come
here follow us wrong rules literally
wrong
rules let's
go I wonder guys for this game if I
should ask if crouching is allowed
because what if some people do it uh to
not fall down you guys need to uh and
then I don't do it because I think it's
not allowed you know but then some
people do it and then it's like oh
because nobody asked about it so it's
okay like should I ask at least cuz if
you crouch you can't fall down the hole
but generally I feel like you want to be
faster anyway so if you crouch you're
not fast enough to fill
holes we're not going to do this I'll
ask
not ah we put
our do we keep oural come up
here come on up
here
[Music]
everyone come on
Jun Jun I wouldn't want to be crouching
yeah cuz it's too slow H
okay just wanted to clear it up
[Music]
so this is some everybody at the same
time too right
I
czy it's going to be
crazy that's going to be crazy that's
going to be fast can explain okay okay
okay there will be three rounds in total
it three
round and there will be no switching
switch switch switching M
[Music]
soay it's a battle royale
basically we're not going by groups
we're not going uh solo everybody's
going at the same time
mhm and for for the wool Cutters you are
um you are to press F1 when you want to
play the
game okay and for the
foreman you cannot Crouch
[Music]
okay wait wait wait wait well if if if
hitting is allowed then is eating also
allowed or like what if you die and not
fall I guess you're also hitting is only
for like you know make people fall don't
don't kill people you're not allowed to
kill you can hit but you don't
kill but what if like you've been hit so
many times you're about to die from uh
just not eating can I there is food
there there is foot outside uh in the
upper there in the middle so you can oh
foot in here too there's
here going to distribute the
color do you get
[Music]
please can join I have another uh
but what if you end up dying from the
punches even if they don't do much I
will take can we come back thank
probably
not lot of hits to die from puning
okay
byebye
here and the purple box what Co
left here what
happened why is co going
what
[Music]
what but soada also
out yeah I wasn't supposed to take so
long this event and me and Ena have
something too
[Music]
actually let me check if I have any oh
Discord DMS hi hi hi okay okay's looking
at me I think we're thinking the same
[Music]
thing um still all the foran can I can I
see what your color is okay crony is
yellow green wait are we a sign color is
pink
yeah where's your is no one
[Music]
okay
wait what color there is no orange do
you take two or three shears no orange
there's no orange okay only Brown pink
green yellow blue and red because that
is the obvious color uh yeah it's you
guys requested you guys didn't want like
uh colors that are to close to each
other we won't even like use one fully I
think so hey what color should I
take for the foreman for the foran
already has their color should we have
green if it's not
taken for the foreman who has taken
their colors please go upstairs because
it'll be easier for us to monitor
Brown yeah I'm Brown cuz Okay Okay Okay
is not there's no close by I
think you guys can go inside
the right here so green pink and yellow
is out green pink yellow and red okay
let's go with orange again I have brown
there's no orange there is no orange
has
brown has yellow red green and pink is
already out so the left one is brown
brown okay Ena Brown I'm in
blue okay now go up please wait how many
stacks can we take sorry two please two
oh oh only two two should be enough two
or three is okay who's Canada working
with now I'll bring some down
okay but I think that's everyone no we
don't use shears
upstairs only the bottom ones I'm going
to say it again
okay uh is everyone here one two three
four wait where are we just going to use
all VC or putting my stacks of Ka VCC
[Music]
Ka we're going to stop using the all VC
so proximity proximity
[Music]
okay okay I made
P did she also make bab nii at the same
time yeah don't forget to F1 for the
lower
level oh proximity oh okay okay okay
okay okay what if I die
immediately please let me know that
you fall already so I
can you please let
[Music]
me I think like even if I fall down uh
you can still keep
[Music]
using focus on not falling down
cut Gladiator
match can we play peacefully guys up
here up
peace like no no pushing
please oh God
[Music]
God full Focus
H where are the
holes ah what the
[Music]
who
fell who fell if you
[Music]
fell our best we try
my heart is my heart more
minutes my heart my heart my heart my
heart my heart is
that my heart
[Music]
who's still who's still up there I don't
know are we
still time Smith still continuing
[Applause]
still oh no I'm so close I so close my
heart one more one more one more okay
one
more
it if if everybody dies then the last
one standing way does it matter if you
place
block but if everybody survives
[Music]
then and then I can just stop placing
wool when there's only two people
left I believe in you
[Music]
should I do
that that's rough unless it goes on
there's a there's a time limit right is
there a time minutes 3 minutes okay okay
so if you stop placing wool then the
risk is that cuz you were just not like
being careful but two people are left
and then you
know you didn't build enough cuz you're
just extra careful as not good
either God I'm
shaking where do I put the blocks I
got Al to their perspective colors
please
okay okay damn
it you know are we
Dau we are not Dau right but it's it's
it's probably that sh because only this
and then one more game right we have two
more rounds of this and then there's
multiple rounds of the maze so multiple
rounds really yeah I thought it was just
once because the last person standing
wins and then d e f and then the final
round ah okay okay okay like two rounds
then right to
take to
nice
okay how many
stacks pressure disc can we
try can try a bit faster yeah cuz
otherwise we might have to leave during
the maze match or so okay uh wa wa
please check uh DMS please thank DMS DMS
is everyone already in
yes
[Music]
uh okay okay one and a half minute
okay okay I checked DMs I have replied
okay 2
[Music]
1 oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God oh my God oh my God oh my
God who is so aggressive
one more
[Music]
minute I can't see I can't
see I think cuz I was
like I
a
[Music]
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] you weren the only one I'm shaking
what do you mean
[Music]
okay W that's a lot of
brown everyone stop in their place right
now
stop no win but I
survive 1 2 3 four 5
I destroy a lot of their
colors brown I feel like
mostly mostly it was
peaceful okay mostly that's a lot oop 24
pink
26 and then brown
right yeah two three I'm counting Brown
four five six
seveny
[Music]
sorry yeah me and Ena will have to leave
early
guys 4 42 4 44 44 45 46 so many
yellows
wowow
[Music]
wow I think there's one more round of
this then we could probably still be in
that a lot of blocks so Brown
WIS okay let me Jo put the is there
another round of this put them back one
more round one more
okay
okay is that
take
anaa uh uh uh and I have to leave for
the final game so we'll finish the whole
game off here okay okay okay all right
got so my night timing is very tight
today yeah I could I could probably
maybe stay for one maze round for me
because I'm have a bit more time only
one
round yeah I thought so too I thought so
too no no but then there's three teams
going at a time there's six teams so
there's one round and then two round and
then the finals so
[Music]
yeah if they put LA and my team in the
first round then we can the first
no explanation
[Music]
necessary okay no it's something that we
can't really too much which is
why yeah bet but Ena is a good sniper I
think I don't want to be next to her
friend why don't you stay in that corner
okay the other side stay in the corner
okay we
start I got to the
corner oh F1 oops oh yeah F1
please yeah I hope she's like obstructed
for me I'm sorry but if we f one and you
only say 3 2 one go in the chat we can't
see it oh I'll count
down five four four three two
[Music]
one someone went down
there so scary no need to be so
violent for real nice 1
[Music]
minute no idea where wa is that's always
oh
sorry just go down
[Music]
and somebody's out to get
[Applause]
me what the [\h__\h]
fell down because of me I'm no it's okay
it's
okay
[Music]
myle I kind of I kind
of sorry nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice nice
nice nice nice nice
nice I hate my
life green wait no you can't
anymore I'm good at it but not good
enough
guys good but not good enough but pretty
good
though pretty
good pretty good I'm proud of myself for
that performance in all three
rounds definitely
I'm proud of
myself good try
Tak good
[Music]
try
come we got one win it's
[Music]
okay was there two people left at the
top at that point
[Music]
[Applause]
who is
[Music]
pinkow let's go
here wait so we only have 10 it's okay
it's okay oh no I'm just saying we
should uh strategically shop sorry what
were you about to say I was just going
to say sorry I didn't win I really tried
and I think I I stood I was yeah I think
I stayed pretty long in each match but
it was always at the end know it's it's
just like a different rules you did very
well
[Music]
I'll put this here for
now wait you can take my emeralds right
to buy
stuff here I'll put it in this first
chest take it
[Music]
at shooting
because one bow and 10 arrows is already
nine what I thought that was free I
thought that was free of charge to the m
you have a free time since everyone is
shopping right
[Music]
now what yeah I'm just like what should
I
do we can only really
afford weapons for one of
us how much is
I could I fought the arrow and B was
free he then my role is actually kind of
meaningless because I'm not going to let
waya go out there without a
weapon okay you buy your weapons and I
only navigate and I try to not get hit
by the others
either I only navigate and try to tell
you who where is who
wasn't I can still guide you we can ra
[Music]
do
no I thought forever was free
no I thought so too be honest because
the Navigator's job is like to shoot
people and we can't even pass they can't
even see past like I don't know but to
be honest me shooting people could go
wrong like I shot all in the practice
when she was with me in a team so I
could accidentally shoot you too and
then you know you should be at least
able to protect
yourself I guess yeah you should have
something to like fight because even if
the Navigator dies I think the fighter
if if the fighter is still alive the
battle continues so it's more important
that you stay
alive okay well you're just going to
watch
microtransactions you need the weapons
you need the weapons more get whatever
you want baby your sugar mama all
[Laughter]
right
damn how much money do the others have
man
[\h__\h] they're like shopping like they're
in in an airport in the taxfree section
baby and we're like sorry we're
economy sorry no cash no tax free I I
can't not even afford that I'm like the
lowbudget
airline economy and I don't even have a
seat I'm on stand
by no let honestly I can't even afford
that I I walk I walk from Europe to
Japan that's how it
is okay how's the time looking they have
to buy
faster I don't know how long it's going
to take for everyone
um um [\h__\h] I don't know well the thing
is Ena I could already drop out because
I'm useless right now we can't even
afford bow and arrow for me
[Laughter]
so I could just
call players um hopefully this
I could just go but I have a bit more
time than Ena I think cuz we're you know
different locations but we go to the
same
place and I'm kind of closer I
think God damn it PC please oh to ah she
does she mean our
groups I think so
[Music]
hopefully although I could be cheering
her on with those it's kind of way
colors cheer
lader should we join
would she
noce hello
here hello wait what go to
the
okay l o
e r e i n e lovely wait actually works r
e y n e L way I'm too shy to chat I keep
on deleting my
[Music]
messages damn she's got a
shield I think me and way are so not GNA
she will have to hide honestly better if
she hides in the
beginning as much as she can don't just
don't get
found oh she does have an axe
okay have Mone toy
okay okay okay we don't need it
yeah so hard to get those
shot are they going to give us she's
like way they don't even have money to
buy she knows we're poor piss
poor she
knows maybe they go aim for
us the biggest on the darkg story I wish
it would be so cool but there's no way
unless like they if they destroy Dy each
other you
know hello ah wait wait wait our
strategy should be you hide I tell you
where you can go to hide and then you
let them destroy each
other because you're to be coward yeah
you hide until there's maybe just one
person left on the field I tell you
where they are and I'll tell you if
they're coming for you or
so are you aware of the colors and the
arrangement of the colors of the field
like um can you tell me I know [\h__\h] fell
uh Pink yeah pink is next to Red and
besides that I don't know uh ah next to
Pink is purple I need to sorry so next
to is like right or left I can well uh
try to get on the tower and like look at
the hold on give me give me a second I I
need to
eat they said they're going to give us
food but so Oh you mean real food H not
real food Minecraft food Minecraft food
but um oopsie
is this our can we be in this Tower
we're just going to claim it so red and
then next to you is clockwise Okay pink
purple I don't know what there is but
then there's gray next to Red on the
right side yeah I know I know and
then should we look over there let me
check what's next to
gray I hope nobody has optify or else
they have like yeah oh that's like red
that's like kylo red after Gray
ked the order is the order is um Ali and
then like 15 on the left and then Holo
is like in the middle is oh yeah but I
don't know those blue there's like a
nice blue next to Kyla red like Kobo
blue yeah that's that's uh that's Kobo
blue I know coobo blue is probably on
the right I'm just guessing and then
besides coobo blue I think it's
definitely mine yeah there's another
blue yeah KOB and then way I know I know
the order okay okay and then there's
lime green right is that green yeah lime
green that's E's color so it's basically
uh on the left it's ARA 15 on the middle
is Holo but the thing is if you go over
there I I won't even be able to see you
so I shouldn't go to green right yeah
depending on where our Tower is though
but yeah where they put us okay but I
know I know
yeah damn okay i i i i m
I can probably only really navigate you
in the colors that are closest to the
tower yeah it's fine
yeah but if I see someone in in pink and
you're in pink I say run run to purple
if purple is empty but yeah what's
what's what's next to purple winner do
you
know um I I know I know by heart but
it's it's um it's confusing if I if you
if I tell you like what's next to
something next to something so it's like
a three by three and like left center
right from left from left top to bottom
is Li green and then we should yeah when
whenever I say left or right we should
decide at least that it's like left when
you look at the center of the field
right if I say left I mean left to the
like when you that's confusing because I
don't turn around just say um go closer
to purple or something and then if I go
the wrong way you can just say no the
other way okay okay it's going to be
chaotic but um uh it's otherwise it
doesn't
[Music]
work the blue Tower because there's blue
Towers I don't know if the field is blue
in front of
it I think so yeah where's the blue
Tower you you mean blue
flags not blue
floor right yes I assume that's what I
think so too
yeah all right let's
go okay
okay okay so we start at Area 15 area
okay we start at Ma green to the left
pink to the right I think red red is
next to Pink right I know I know uh I
remember it I'm just asking for myself
also okay
cool food in everyone touch bed is there
a bed here I I think I touched it like
when I was over
there doesn't matter if we die once it's
over anyway I mean if we die once we
will get somewhere yeah it's round one
team ready for round one team we we we
cuz I have to run afterwards I have to
go wait so do I wait wait wait so do I
just go down yeah just go to the door
yeah
yeah bab we really don't have much time
was there a timer for this no right it's
just like last person standing right
last person
standing okay okay let's
go ah yeah I hope you guys make it you
have to but yeah I think we can be a
little bit late but not too much yeah
hopefully I mean it's just not nice if
you're late ah we see all first for
every okay oh
no hello hello hello thank you everyone
for coming I want to check it first oh
okay okay perfect
perfect so the first one will be Yi Sora
in red flag Ana Ina in yellow flag and
Rain Kara in blue flag wait everyone is
already on the temples hi yeah good so
um I'm just going to say the
rules all right hold on wait a minute
okay
so uh as you guys can see there will be
three round but this time you guys in
the round one team mhm mhm uh there will
be a fighter and Navigator if the
fighter
de oh
okay if the fighter it's GG right so can
can I
talk okay thank
you he so um if fighter dead that mean
game over for your team if navigator
that that mean the game still must go on
but Navigator cannot help at all yeah
cannot shoot cannot navigate okay so all
you can um all you can do is depends on
your Fighters
team okay um and
wait if navigator navigator cannot be
outside of the of the
temples but can uh fight with bow and
arrow so if you have a bow and arrow you
can you can use it if you kill the the
enemy and the items fall you can take it
ah
okay okay the bed is outside as you guys
as you guys can see the outsides um if
you guys date then you're dead that mean
game over should I translate really
quickly the the items thing I think it
might be yeah thank you
[Music]
okay giving me the weapon yeah come here
okay okay okay wait is there supposed to
be a bed near the temple
uh you're not even if you die once you
can't do anything either as a navigator
or as a fighter really so the bed
doesn't have to be close right yeah it's
just it's
okay are we are we good to go sorry I'm
nervous I'm nervous because of the time
yeah do we go back into our own
VCS yeah okay
byebye I'm more nervous about Eno's time
than my own
time okay
group y y y y y y y okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
wait I was supposed to I was supposed to
do something with with uh with Ina
manager oh so oh my God I have so many I
forgot to pay you
money a so I think I'll have to like
send did through Ina manager uhhuh but
yeah that would take some time I guess
but maybe I'll rush through Ina man oh
it's okay we can talk about that later
later can we start can
we yes
ready no B waha let's go panachi only
existing by Wayne and let's go should I
go left right who I don't I don't know
who's on which side right
no you should oh wait wait I think uh
they haven't begun
yet is that on the right side is that
soda Senpai Andy oh know it doesn't
matter I'll just tell you when somebody
comes 3 2 1
go yeah go out then walk out then
can you see me in the green uh yeah oh
my god oh they're shooting
me I see you in the green there's no one
around you as far as I can
tell there's no one in purple yet NE
which is next to us next to Green yeah
there
uh there's someone over at the red Tower
but you're you're pretty safe over
there I'm stuck I don't know where I am
I see a name if there was one there I
don't know where I should go you see
names too right I do so you can kind of
tell if somebody comes closer to you oh
there's someone in the
middle but not going not going to you
yet I don't know where to stay stay in
purple for now maybe although maybe
they're all stal
mating yeah pink is staying in
pink so far they're just like walk I
think they're all ah they're they're
relying on The Navigators right now uh
who's on the walls are only somebody
shooting yeah they're trying to shoot
you red is trying to shoot you which is
I think
Sol yeah I I think uh they're they're
aiming somewhere else now I can
tell oh it's it's pretty slow
everybody's so careful this
time
ni yeah she's aiming she's
aiming stay close to the walls because
that's really hard to get
you I know from
experience they're just Yi is just
staying in her territory I want this to
open what oh my
[Music]
God I think everybody's playing super
defensive huh I'm lost I'm I'm just lost
honestly let just stay stay there
there's no one there no one there we got
to wait for them to kill each other come
on come on guys wa where are you going
wa don't go
there I see Y is going to the middle uh
but I think she's looking for the door H
[Music]
oh I'm at Blue right now why
why because okay I'm bored honestly it's
okay it's okay have fun don't take it so
seriously anyway I think you know we
don't have much
chances Yi is in the middle in the free
middle I'm at cobal Blue so far away
from you I'm so bored I cannot see you
oh my God it's so crowded it's so
crowded oh
[\h__\h] like I I can't see anyone
everybody's gone oh oh okay one down Ana
was a fighter so their team is out Ana
Ena Ana team is out
nice okay wa there's two other teams
left right who is the other
team there's s e who's the other
team uh entities is not
oh there's someone in the middle Y is in
the middle Y is in the middle but I
would not bait her she she has a shield
and who knows what weapon and the and
the working naig oh you why are you
walking to Pink careful soda is soda
simpa is aiming for you I see
her she's she's she's oh oh she took a
shot she's totally going for you only
three teams oh okay now it's vers you
versus Yi so actually we probably should
not um
yeah you will have to fight her I guess
but it's but try to fight her where at
least s Senpai can't like shoot you that
easily you're both in the middle have
fun have
fun so if I could accidentally shoot
y'll be that would be
fun oh yeah oh yeah I don't know oh yeah
okay you're surviving
wow damn how are your heart
doing oh what wait
what how the [\h__\h] did you take her
weapons take her weapons you can take
them I did I did who Underdog
Underdog wait I I ruined something sorry
with one weapon and no functioning
Navigator five more minutes what do you
mean oh yeah we win yay five more
minutes I don't know how where to I
think I got to go too now so if you move
on to the next round you got to get
someone else to navigate you pick me up
no pick me
up pick me up me someone else navigate
way thanks I'm lost good luck way good
job so far damn girl you did it you did
it you were underpowered in terms of
armor but you did it so let's go fun in
the next round I got to go so thanks wa
for working with me I had fun thank you
see you again
sometime okay
bye-bye byebye
come okay yeah I got to run Ena is
already gone I need to I need to go uh
y thanks for watching in German s it's
ending so abruptly really tried to drag
it out this was not supposed to be this
long uh they told us I think like 1 hour
or one and a half hours now it's fre
hours sorry about that now we're ending
it like this that's kind of lame I'm
sorry I'm sorry let me know what happens
with the results on Twitter like tell me
update
me byee
[Music]
byee
byee support wait I I'm going to raid
waya okay support her support her
bye-bye
[Music]
can't rid waya sorry oopsie I can't rid
waya she she has raiding off for God's
sake man God damn it okay please go to
her on your own okay let's support waya
she's my team still manual raid okay go
go to waya stream bye-bye