[Music]
ah ah
ah m
[Music]
hi M elf M
Zelda oh oh
dear I need Coca-Cola I suppose
like there's still something so [\h__\h]
up in my like neck but like in the front
part of it like I don't understand why
my the front of my neck is so broken
right now these past days it
[Music]
hurts all right before the stream I used
my neck shoulder massage thing
yeah it goes like
pretty uh far to the side of the neck
too so it helps a little bit for the
issue now I guess but not
completely no no no vanilla
caola what I'm talking about my neck not
something in
OBS my real life neck
I need the
energy yippee I need energy from this
Coca-Cola even though you
know in the end it's not as strong as
Red Bull or coffee but actually I don't
even need that maybe this is good enough
for me I even when I drink a Red Bull I
only take like two sips and I'm done and
this tastes better anyway
H you like my sips ah where was I last
time like where was I positioned did I
play full window I don't think I did did
I
[Music]
me waiting for my game capture card to
start up and then realizing oh it's not
plugged in because I plugged in all my
stupid motion capture
[\h__\h] and you know the one good thing
about
me like okay so the other
night wait you can't see me uh the other
night um I told you guys I was going to
do motion capture
right and I was
charging the gloves for like two days
before that just to make sure they're
really charged
and these are on purpose these sounds
are on purpose because I'm unplugging
and plugging things don't worry okay I
don't know if that was on purpose
but um yeah was doing
things um well that should show up now
honestly
ah what's wrong what's wrong with you
oh yeah you don't hear it oh okay good
good good good even
[Music]
better there it is finally okay let me
finish my
tangent
so basically hello hello
guys
um yes basically
ah my neck hurts oh I'm trying to
massage
mine neck without choking
myself what was I saying
basically H what is this cable what does
this cable do I don't even know
basically so the other
day Kana uu told me hey
for your music
video you the motion capture that you
took in the cover
Studio the hands are [\h__\h] up can you
please retake the hand
motion like with your setup at home I'm
like huh why is it it was supposed to be
like it looked fine and in the preview
that I saw and like why is it [\h__\h] up
it's not supposed to be [\h__\h] up
that's anyway
um so I was like one of these days soon
I'll try my
best and
then when was it last night or last last
night I wanted
to do it and I was putting on my
gloves
and I'm opening Photoshop right now
because I want to separate these ears
into two different files but Photoshop
is not not responding cool then let's
just continue to tangent um
I uh yes so I was setting up my gloves
my 6,000 plus dollar man's
gloves and I put them on and kind of
said that in order to record only the
hand motion so basically I have two
programs I have the the pr that is for
xense the whole suit uh where I would
record full body motion uh including the
hands but there's also the software for
the gloves which is a separate company
um which you just um put it up to like
calibrate the hands and so on separately
but he said yeah I should uh record it
there separately only the hands I was
like okay I'll try and then I try to do
it and it says your license you don't
have the right license and I'm like what
the [\h__\h] do you mean like I need another
license I'm already I already have two
licenses for the exent
stuff uh one for like just using the
program in general and one for live
streaming for using the live stream
function and that already adds up to
several thousands so are you kidding me
I'm not going to pay and even when I
looked it up I couldn't even find uh a
way to buy one there was like one sold
out somewhere like on some reseller
website where you could buy licenses in
the past apparently that was
2500 for one stupid ass
license 2,500 are you kidding me to
press a record button because the basic
program like you can use it you can
record the thing is I could totally
record all of this uh in the xense
program if I did full body map and we
could then isolate and separate the hand
motion only but I have to still put on
the whole setup otherwise like on
Accents in their program it won't let me
record anything unless I have all the
trackers on um yeah but so basically I
could just record it there and then
isolate the hand motion with my existing
licenses and yet this other program is
asking me for another [\h__\h] license
just to record the hands only in their
program bro it's so stupid and it's so
stup stupid it's so stupid so it's likeu
I'm not going to buy another license
it's stupid and we were like discussing
what other options I had and
um um I didn't I just said okay whatever
like it's now like 2:00 a.m. or so but
let me
um let me just record the full body
motion again at home uh since the full
body doesn't have to be high quality as
long as I get the hands it's okay right
and so I was going to do that but first
I slept and the next day kind of told
me never
mind the motion is fine actually there
was just something weird going on but
the hand motion that we got from the
cover studio is fine so you don't need
to do anything I'm like well thank God
cuz I was I was actually worried um like
why is it why is it not
usable why I bought like just this once
I wanted cuz like in the past for
Kima uh I recorded at home with my
accents and it was so scuffy like I had
no idea why it was so
scuffy like there was so many issues
with the motion I recorded at home home
so I was hoping that this once I can
just record something that's not scoffy
and it doesn't need a million fixings
and we can actually use the whole dance
recording and not have to try to
pinpoint the good parts and only use the
good parts which maybe adds up to like
30 seconds of usable
footage yeah but apparently it was fine
it was just something like the fingers
were assigned to the wrong
hand or something like that and that's
why it was weird or so I don't know
Photoshop didn't open properly let me
open it
again well that's the good news so I
would I thought okay even in cover
Studio when I record something it's
going to be messy but no turns out it's
not it's
fine yeah so it's good that I didn't I
waited one more day to record it and and
didn't buy any licenses whatsoever
okay it has opened itself so I will
quickly
uh fix cuz if I have them as separate
files I think it will not always end up
in my face as much as
[Music]
now and then I'll also add a little bit
more of a gr
ration
gradation
oopsie we have a lot of time guys today
don't
worry uh we're going to play this game
again for a long amount of time
[Music]
yippee okay call this ear right ear call
this ear left
ear I want to save as PNG
please yeah I'm also glad we're back on
it so soon because I'm really hyped up
about the game right
now okay right here
have you guys called
up please play the game guys so that I
don't spoil you and that you don't have
to feel like you can't watch My Stream
because you don't want to be spoilers we
don't want that to be you know the
issue okay I think I did it
you like it when I spoiler
you Uno one
[Music]
ear second year
okay yeah I was frozen cuz when I load
in it makes me
freeze whoa Big
Ear it's still
wobbling oh damn it I did it on the blue
oh well that's fine
[Music]
blue no wait
probably that's
good yeah
well it will still go into my
face
but it's okay it's okay
wow should I just have one really big
ear or one really small
one
no no then and I would look so funny and
you guys would not take me
seriously
okay right they're so wobbly damn it
okay let's fix it on a different layer
how about
[Music]
this that's all right I think that's all
right I fixed it on my braids
Wiggly
ears well okay they still end up in my
face I don't care just I just got to try
to look straight as much as I
[Music]
can nose ear and nose
hair Yum Yum
Yum also Ro toar thank you for the big
red
wow all right I'll try to stay
straight
let's
play Legend of
wait got to go here
[Music]
sorry rearranging things from
yesterday there we go there we
go Legend of Link
yeah we're so
back
[Music]
Yi oh no wait
okay sound fixed Legend of
blink Legend of kisses Echoes of all
life what is that about he she wants to
talk to me already I'm I was going to go
off to get my heart container
immediately you there
hen Captain Dona left a message for you
on her way out she mentioned that she's
heading to the Oasis and she'd like you
to join her there you to get to the
oases head to East when you leave town
you can't miss it that's all she shared
for you uh does she want us to
immediately fight that
worm the worm I wasn't going to go there
I was going to go right
there her name is link
yes apparently so
um honestly like it's not worth
making yourself
something for just jumping up a little
bit higher well you can just quickly
switch
to you know um
link all right so did you guys know
there's a freaking heart container
here
unbelievable yeah
what do you want HH what do you want now
you disappear
cowards was there something else here I
forgot I I I missed some stamp rally
dudes but I don't know if I really want
to
seriously try to collect those ah okay
there's one that's not the one that I
thought I missed
though but here let's get a
stamp stample rally
get that stamp I really like these trees
they look funny to
me how do you know they there what the
stamp I wasn't sure I was just thinking
something was up there but the heart
container H
well you don't need to know why I know
things
[Laughter]
right it's it's cool to see after I
played to a certain point it's cool to
see how others go about it you
know for
example not knowing that you can pick up
these tiny ones also for example oh not
knowing that you can just heal up your
HP just by sleeping in a bed like
forgetting about the most basic things
just sleep in the bed that you can
summon I guess it's just not on your
mind when normally in normal Zeda games
you can't just bring your bed
everywhere but the big ones
here can I cut them
no how does this
uh no but I also kind of learned
some or gain some New
Perspective I think like here in the
beginning it was another stamp I gained
some New Perspective myself
too
like how to do things a little bit
smarter not by watching dendo but by
watching a
different video
on 10 things you didn't know you could
do in Echo of wisdom with
Echo you
know wait wait no I don't care
my aim is
[Music]
off for
example no sorry I my controls I'm
confused I need to a what I I didn't
press up I pressed right bro um did you
know for example I didn't know
this but I think most people know what
how do you oh okay cuz there's no prompt
to that says jump in
but okay but now the the enemy sees me
though
um I guess it because it saw me already
before what's the point yeah okay some
of you guys didn't know well I didn't
know either there's no prompt that says
jump in so that's why I just didn't
realize that you could jump in but there
doesn't seem to be a difference in the
pots as there is a difference in the
beds in how good they
work the pots are just all the same I
think ah you just wanted to hop on the
podt that's yeah you learned
[Music]
accidentally so what ah n hide in the
pot can I oh yeah okay when I move my
head comes out so then they can't see me
I
suppose so we could do
stealthy uh sections like that but
there's another thing I wanted to show
oh so none of the Rifts are shrinking
yet I see thank you for your report get
some rest before get some help uh before
you return to
patrols thanks for coming Zelda let's
talk over here
over
here cat cat getat some help ah came too
quiet okay okay
sorry the water here is so beautiful
don't you
think this place holds holds many
memories for me the chief my mother used
to play here with me when I was a little
she would tell me to look at the Serene
water to keep my mind and art calm like
so
water foret took up my training rather
than my mother because mother was busy
as Chief why do they capitalize it once
and then not the other time H foret
train other true Mercy to her and mother
we are the gudu you see today oh I have
so much respect for the both of them but
I Can't Stand By and Watch things get
worse we wish at
them mother as a
[Music]
position
okay I wonder how we can prove to my
mother and facet that you're being
honest aside from the big rift at the
sunction there are also three small
Rifts elsewhere in the desert I'd like
for you to see if you can get rid of any
of them they're in the dolphin o is blah
BL BL blah want to know more
no I'll find it no
problem and if I don't I'll come back
but
here uh no is it here uh well that's
probably one of the Rifts but uh wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
I don't know why I'm going out of my way
to find these things again the readed
where the hell are they
no
[Music]
map I think they're
there I passed
them I will tell you my
[Music]
wisdom would
aan not be more fitting probably but I I
don't know how to do such an acent so
this will have to
[Music]
do will you turn yourself into a rad
please
[Music]
no ah okay okay one cool thing for
example this thing is kind of uh
slow or okay it doesn't look slow right
now but you can control where it
goes uh and more efficiently kill
monsters like
so instead of R okay I'm not showing it
the best way but instead of relying yeah
on it to go where you want to go or
waiting for you to go where you're
locked in you can just like control it
yourself
no ow
let me get back into you you're up too
high I can't reach you well
whatever just open up a new
one if only my aim was
better yeah and you can just like run
around like
this and uh protect yourself have a
shield around you so so to
say wow so going cool Strat right okay I
literally can't find the RADS but
basically
what I found out is you know how the
RADS stun
you when they scream if you oopsy if you
are inside one even if your head is out
there they will not stun
you and they're really slow so you know
you can get by pretty fast uh pretty
safely anyway even in the
pot oh my PE wants to
kill have I been in that
C oh oh hi I was not willing to talk to
you but okay yeah I I know a few other
tricks too but I shall show you when it
maybe becomes
[Music]
relevant hi
not sure if you were in there yet or not
yeah we'll find we'll find
out hey are you hanging in
there wait who has that me I don't speak
yes so of actually actually no I'm not
we're defeating wave after the W of
these things but they keep coming and
they don't stop coming and they don't
stop coming and they don't stop coming
and they don't stop
coming and some more yay
yeah I understand oh it's a side no it's
a main quest you want me to kill those
specific ones
huh let me get an enemy
out
um there was something interesting too
with like enemies like the dark
nut so you know when you let him fight
on his
own you have to like you know he'll get
hit a lot because he just stands close
mostly when the other enemy hits back
but if you control him like this you can
dodge you can go back a step and then
you know wait for him to lift his axe
when he's ready for the next attack you
just ow okay I get interrupted because
of this but ah no yeah okay you can move
away the enemies too I
guess oh well [\h__\h] but you know what I
mean yeah basically
you
can pretend that you're the one
fighting time to
heal and keep him from getting hurt too
much and die too
early I don't know but sorry I'm
confused
today you need this game even more
now spawning the de plant will Instant
attack every time you
summon uh yeah yeah yeah you can reset
even with the bed you can reset like
instead of just lying there you could
get up each time and it heals you faster
if you like wait for one heart and then
get up and then lie down again wait for
one heart apparently it's faster but
those are that's a little bit too Min
maxy for me I
guess so are those enemies going to
respawn again or are they still out here
no not the r that okay let's let's let's
try out the
pot although when I'm in the pot I can't
control
my my dark nut let's take a cheap
PT hit him hit him see I'm not stunned
[Music]
yippe
so ha ha yeah yeah yeah aggro me I don't
care yeah it seems like they can't hurt
the dark nut
noise can't believe we're the ones being
saved well at least the monsters seem to
have mopped up for the time being no if
the rift would just go away I'm worn out
from all the realness fighting let's
take a break for a bit again didn't you
just take a
break but okay that was like one part of
the free Rifts
I can't create a w entrance here so we
won't be able to get into this
[Music]
one weird how that's so
specific and which ones we can get and
which ones we can't but okay looks big
enough to
me but
okay yeah but what about the second
break exactly what about a third I like
breaks
too uh all
right
so like there was another freaking stamp
somewhere I can't find it I can't
remember where exactly it
was
somewhere
there okay
so
here do I have the
right is that the right SP no that's the
wrong
spider oh wait does the spider do the
same thing
I oh wait
uh no that's the wrong spider right I
need the other spider there's a spider
that will uh just walk around up onto
the walls and then you can bring
yourself up easy and fast that way but
that's such a cheese if you like use it
constantly
M now another thing that I have learned
is like for example um actually I guess
it's better to explain with this if I
want to build stairs you know you would
normally like do it like
this
right but so what you can also do is
push I think did I push too
much yeah build it like this p push uh
create an object whatever can be
trampolines too to push it a little bit
then it will be on like the
half uh Square yeah half push and then
if you yeah do it like this you can have
half stairs whereever than you know you
you you you're wasting one item like
this you
know understand you you don't have to do
it with three you can do it with
two wow okay with all this knowledge I
only know because I watch some
videos go half push oh damn
it and now we got some trampoline stairs
that we could do with only two
trampolines if we wanted
[Music]
to does it mean you can also extend the
bridge using beds I would think so
yeah make an even longer Bridge with
less beds
what's there
oo ah now
I uh remember
that
um one spot where I there was like a
stone on top of something and I really
wanted to get the stone off and I was
just too dumb to get it
right by the way I
wonder if I get a fish out
no wait that wasn't
here now there's one um
enemy which is quite useful for or
several enemies maybe which are quite
useful for traveling around
[Music]
fast um but that's a little bit later in
the game I
think where was this one spot
with the
stone must have been quite far in the
beginning I don't know why I keep on
pushing
[Music]
that where was
it no no no there wasn't really spoilers
I mean seeing a few future mobs is not
really I wouldn't call that a
spoiler was it here ah it was here okay
I was like really
stupid at this
point I don't know like sometimes you
just have empty brain moment right we
all have that
sometimes well I could
do just oop see cuz I was just trying to
get directly up
there but all I got to
do
is this just get a a little bit higher
up here and then control the
stone oh yeah oh this
works wait there's supposed to be
something up there I
think huh don't take my
money wait maybe if I go up there
something will
appear I already got it wait I did
manage to get up there I thought I
didn't manage to get up there
[Music]
attack I guess I did manage to get up
there is that my money that I'm
losing even though I'm not being the one
who gets
hit I jump with link
ah well that was a very smart thing of
me to do as
well okay
let's warp over here to the next
Rift thank you thank you thank
[Music]
you I did watch the regloss 3D by the
way I watched
it it was so nice they all like did
their best it was so sweet like the I I
just felt the the M the
generation Bond was so sweet but what
the hell l
l why did she like sacrifice her musical
solo to do freaking
entertainment she she sacrificed herself
to do a variety
section maybe maybe the staff was like
Hey guys like so we filled all of this
up with singing dancing actually would
be nice to have some variety does
anybody want to sacrifice their slot for
that she just wanted to eat food no but
I really was looking forward to seeing
her dance and sing a solo
man
man but their 3D looks really good like
both the group outfit and the you know
default outfit it look looks so good Rin
was so cute her her mouth movement is so
accurate to what she's saying what the
hell and her hair is so pretty
especially in the Twin
tails and this was so cute with her in
the
[Music]
museums yeah I really like the reg glos
white
outfit they're so
[Music]
cute they're so cute
H thank
you sorry for not listening but what
what wait what I'm not fighting here
like in
eh I thought I was just going to fight
again uh there's some soldiers in the
South and guda desert who are so parched
they can't move give two chili cactuses
to the Oasis smoothie shop ah and have
them make a cactus smovie for the
parched Warriors okay the ones that are
right here right okay we'll make we'll
make a smoothie for
them
with two two chili CAC
te isn't that the isn't that the
plural
cacti not Cactus
SE yeah didn't they
[Music]
wrong English and I recognized
it smovie please smovie
[Music]
to so two
cacti equals a chilling
drink is that
[Music]
so oh looks good
looks good that's should we make another
one or are they sharing the
drink I mean just generally maybe we
should make some for ourselves I wonder
if it will will come in
[Music]
handy caught by the my
speaker
yes my speak
[Music]
Oban I've been feeling so bad
I I saw like two videos separate videos
of a freaking leopard trying to attack a
was the concubine or what you what do
you call it again not
concubine the spiky porcupine what the
[\h__\h] is a concubine a porcupine like the
one with the family and the one where it
was just one single
porcupine wait what is that a word what
I I
said wait let me look at
them
conine a woman who lives with a man but
has a lower status than his wife or
wife that's not what I meant why is it
so similar
ah man
amen hey man um no but like it was two
different WIS how often does this happen
that a leopard is trying to attack
porcupines in the wild
desert and I just I I mean amazing how
the porcupines can protect themselves so
well but upon reading how how like rough
it is to get a porcupine spike in your
body as it has like these things that
stick out and then it rips out your
muscle flesh that is so bad I feel so
bad for the leopard but why did the
leopard just not stop attacking like you
must have been so hungry or just
stubborn as [\h__\h] you had the
barbs I feel so bad for the cuz in the
in one video you saw uh when it was
fighting the porcupine alone you saw uh
the the paws of the leopard were really
really
bloody I felt so bad I was like please
stop for your own sake I feel so
bad big cat got to
eat let me feed big cat let me give it
some proper cat food I
would I would I don't
know I'll cook you a big ass wagu steak
anything if you stop hurting yourself
[Music]
please if murder Kitty why cute must
weed
Pizza what the hell I'm not why would
I Seeker
Scorpio no
what I did not see koba's commercial you
mean a real commercial or did she just
mess
around you're
[Music]
welcome a real commercial I saw
something else uh she has a freaking
Honda like a car
commercials what I I saw that she had
like
uh a commercial like a pretty cool big
tie up with uh like basically Indonesian
Amazon tokopedia I first didn't really
the first time I heard it I wasn't
really aware of like you know how big it
was and then I saw a clip the other day
of cobal
um almost
supposedly probably I don't think it
would have been that serious but
supposedly about to lose her sponsorship
because there's a uh a rival company to
tokopedia and and there was a
notification sound of that that is very
recognizable and it played during her
stream during the Minecraft uh like
thing we had with
ID and it played and she was like
playing it off and just pretending as
everything was normal but her chat
everybody was like haha you're going to
lose your sponsorship that was not toia
was it cuz like she's been promoting
tokopedia but that was a different
notification
sound and the way she was like uh
playing it off like R is that the right
word just pretending is everything's
fine but so funny and then the whole
chat kept on roasting
[Music]
her but yeah it's really cool that she
gets some big deals in Indonesia I love
that for her
good job
coo proud of you coo I am I am proud of
[Music]
her there's nowhere around here for me
to create an entrance into the rift
either what a
surprise of course it is the one that is
the furthest away which will be the
accessible one
no problem I liked helping you out guys
before getting to the real
[Music]
thing red commercial right I know I
know there's so many things that I I I I
feel like a should have been
me like the dandle merch
lineup I was
like merch Department did you forget
that I
literally have a d
[Music]
outfit and then it's not only me now
it's even CeCe you know German and
Austrian traditional outfits but we're
not part of it okay think I think they
forgot about
us but they look really nice and really
welld designed the artist must have done
a lot of research they look really
pretty there's d yeah like there's a in
they started some like seasonal merch
thing where certain members will be
selected to do like some merch that is
themed after a specific season and they
started it off with October
Fest and they chose uh four Japanese
members uh that look gorgeous in the
dles and that day um I've been told like
connect with like beer for examp
sampai and norai you
know and I think they forgot about me
and CeCe
existing it's literally our traditional
outfit
uh we're right
here yeah
anyway let's
[Music]
go but they're so pretty look those
dresses makes me think now that October
Fest season I guess it's like coming up
I don't know I maybe I should use it as
an opportunity to finally get myself a
proper high quality dandle
IRL I've always wanted to buy myself a
pretty
beautiful uh high quality
dle like a nice one they can get quite
expensive you can get a really cheap one
or you you can get a quite expensive
one I don't know why I even think so
hard about this
ah
ow if you up so high that's just not
fair buddy but anyway does it want me to
where am I oh I'm very wrong no wait
what no that's a side quest oh wait
where am I
that's the quest
[Music]
marker where am I on the map am I just
right there and that's why I can't see
it huh oh okay
ow ah he turned off the
light can you do that here too will it
actually do
something I can do it myself but I want
you to do
it like Yukata well Yukata is usually
also pretty cheap uh kimono is the
expensive one I I wish
people would know the difference
[Music]
more but I noticed that you revealed
yoga outfit in a song um no I think
you're getting things
wrong
um I basically turned the outfit from a
music video into a live Tod outfit
it was never planned back then at the
time but I just did it because it's
cute yeah teast it two years early I
spoiled spoiled my own outfit 2 years
early oh my God she leaked it she's such
a leaker she can't keep things to
herself Tak cannot be trusted she leaks
her own outfits two years in
advance no I did not plan that but um I
just felt like it would be a nice outfit
to actually have as a
uh life to D outfit and I guess I'm also
just running out of
ideas
[Music]
yeah what so we're just going into the
dungeon
now the Torches in here have all gone
out what am I going to do
[Music]
with the rift in here I can't get near
the grave so I can't light the
does and without Z lead our ancestors
won't be able to rest peacefully yeah
don't you think that turning off the
lights will make him rest more
peacefully just
[Music]
saying also couldn't I just build some
beds over there in Fury surely they're
not making that
possible
yeah I see that's where they block our
abilities from using it to its full
extent what your plug outfit what are
you talking about oh what are those cute
M uh how to fight
them m
no I wonder yeah
no go get
him just disappeared completely are you
for real how do we get
them what if I forc them move
this so what you're not going to move
change location guys you're just going
to stay
there he smells very cheeky yeah
okay different
strategy get out of there oh no I feel
bad that was such a mean move ah my fish
is so freaking slow and
useless oh wait let's get a different
enemy or actually let's use a sea urchin
and just drop it on top of it once it's
out hey what are you
doing no
[Music]
no needed more
distance okay now drop that drop yeah
yeah yeah yeah
yeah just absolutely spamming these
little
[\h__\h] because why not get sea
urgent whole Mill
cute at the right
angle oh yeah oh yeah figured it out
surprised it didn't dig itself back
inside
quickly but it's a welcome
surprise all right this room was clear I
guess I didn't have to fight those moles
at
all now I wonder if there's a
special oh yeah sure only
like a preferred way of using these in
this dungeon surely they gave us these
for a
reason oh it's
digging what what
now oh it's there uh perhaps I should
control it I don't
know no not like that follow do you drag
me through the sand
wa we're just walking over
it I want to I want you to drag to dig I
mean oh wait you're making holes for
me all right I'm
stupid make another one then right here
please no not there what are you
doing they don't have menu brain cells
do they just like me there there there
there there there there there there
there
there there right there I will not let
you go any
further thank
you okay but when I want to go back
up how do I go about that I'm all the
way down here can
they how do I I get
up I don't think I can get through the
sand on my
own can I only go
down fire maybe
fire is that a
hint
fire fire against sand is that a
thing but I can't even reach it anyway
[Music]
oh ow yeah no idea well now my head is
burning I don't know I got to go back to
the beginning somehow new pots I'm not
going to try to learn that one or do I
already actually know that one I think I
know I wish I could unar things because
I don't want three different pots in my
memory heat turn sand into glass IRL
right I know thanks to Minecraft the
things you learn via
Minecraft is of Great
Value I guess just spawning like
respawning them will immediately create
a new
hole so you should just like instead of
waiting for them to create create a new
hole spawn a new one right away a golden
egg this item can be used to recover
Hearts but is more effective when mixed
into a drink
oh golden
egg I
feel like they are particularly speaking
to me directly with this a man can you
please not
get him get him
tacy take him down no mercy why are they
all so
weak oh my
God you are really weak no wonder we
could not beat that big
monster is there another valuable thing
that I should go back for I feel like
there was just one more like green
rupe I think besides dad not worth
it oh ha wait what are you doing
there why can't you light the
[Music]
fire H you're not talking to me you came
out of the rift and became mute as well
or what or are you the one that they
talk no that's someone else that's the
one that is in the
city well oops see I'll do it for you
then I don't know what the issue was why
she couldn't do
it ah peace once more and now she can
talk I don't believe I've seen you
before well Mercy B for lighting the
Torches with the fire burning we can
rest peacefully now yeah please go tell
my descendant that always fell that one
over there I think she can hear you
[Music]
is this the Dead the one at want a
piece I feel like they should give her
some kind of effect then oh that makes
sense the way she's talking too but they
should make her like a little bit
seethrough or give her some kind of glow
[Music]
I yeah I lit them up why did they
automatically transport me back here
wanted to like check out the grape move
it see what's
inside what do you mean how did you not
watch just why didn't you see why didn't
you look while I was doing
it yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah is that
so weird I thought I was the only one
here well anyway Mercy for the help I
really appreciate it I'm sure the
ancestors are happy too
mer what what I'm not seeing anywhere I
can create an opening into the
[Music]
rift that's the third
one I thought this one was going to be
it mini dungeon
then Zelda how has it been so far were
you able to get rid of any of the
ribs
no which means getting you into the
sanum is the only way we'll selling
but we don't have any way to do that
right
now Captain donor we've received a
message from lady facette she wants to
know whether or not you've been able to
see evidence of zal's powers yet
oh if if they need to see evidence why
don't I just spawn some cool [\h__\h] in
front of their eyes like plot hole hello
suck she commands that you bring thean
and provide her status update it's so
[Music]
beat a hole in the
logic well the Rifts well they should
ask the people from the other region
just call them why are you making her
French why not El me you have do you
have a personal problem with that
huh why not because I want to give them
a nice interesting accent
I only half of them because I'm
lazy no crunch it's
chocolate but I'm pleasantly surprised
that this isn't the main dungeon and
that they just like made a little tiny
dungeon
for the sake of a
quest um what where am I
oh it's choco bom bones chocolate you
know those those Kinder bom
Bones the little
balls milk chocolate with like milk
cream inside
[Music]
those are nice in moderation they're
also nice when not in moderation trust
me but got to be in the mood for it like
now
[Music]
any kind of Kinder chocolate is just too
good to
[Music]
resist they're so
mean why are these people so mean
yeah they're
[Music]
evil anyway no she doesn't for what
reason would she be deceiving me to what
end she's been working with me to prove
that she can get rid of the rift since
we last spoke would she be running all
over the desert like that simply to have
a laugh at my
expense I know she's telling the truth
and I'm feeling to give us the
opportunity to prove it to you
too I can't stand by while my Warriors
my friends are being wounded on the
battlefield I trust Zelda and I know she
can get rid of the
Rifts how many times have we said this
like specific phrase we just have to
give her
chance I'll take full responsibility for
whatever happens please ship s let us
anxious the Sun
H Don you're willing to risk your honor
as a warrior to place your trust in this
[Music]
person I am we we
bucket get rid of the ribs rid of the
ribs L of
rinks it sounds when you capitalize it
like that the RS it definitely sounds
like a TV show rid of the
Rifts wow rings of
power you've gone so strong my daughter
I too can no longer stand by while my
people suffer seeing you put your honor
on the line inspires me to place my own
trust in this
person what the
hell if we remove the sand from the
sanum we will once again be overwhelmed
by
monsters do you forget that I am a B for
said I will hold the monsters at
Bay you're being ridiculous do you
really think you can hold back the waves
of monsters on your
own oh she won't be on her own they
say of course not look at those L those
ladies they're holding together
strong why is she the only valo cuz
she's
mean we over all your discussion CH this
young lady has helped all of us you mean
me right right she helped me at the GI
of our
ancestors and she aided us as well if
she's able to read us of these horrible
Rifts rid of the rfts then we'll do all
we can to support her Captain Don we
stand at your
side let's
go finally finally we're getting
Justice facet your are warious are you n
willing to e this Zelda out this
specific one in our universe of course
not what are you saying what I want wed
excuse for chief she's trying to deceive
you to take advantage of you can you not
see her true
character gosh this girl has ill
attentions and it's here you have ill
attentions
[Music]
bro are
you oh okay they're not listening to
what facet is D I thought for a moment
this girl was going to try arrest
me Chief Sarah we've got
trouble what is it a rift that's the
ruins that we haven't get rid of yet in
the Eastern desert grew and a bunch of V
we're taking by
it take me there at once
Soldier yes Chief
[Music]
sah
okay is it what is it the big one
CH please you must wait you can't go
ring into free like this so equipped can
somebody just like shut her why doesn't
she shut up like she's the only one
who's opposing
us doesn't she
realize the rift expanded I might be
able to create an entrance there then
let's follow
them well thank God you can create an
entrance there at least
[Music]
Hallelujah ah so there it is did you
guys know you can get this this puv this
bird puv if you push the right
stick W it looks like a classic Dela
game now
[Music]
W put a porcupine on her
face h or make her my
concubine
[Music]
confusion where are we going ah over
there was that always there no that
wasn't always there
[Music]
crazy I'm going to make all these ladies
my concubines
[Music]
all these G old
ladies actually I feel like I've heard
this term also used um in like medieval
shows before couldn't
[Music]
be
ah wait I should have bought those
stupid shoes
where am
I well now I don't know where the hell I
am but I need to go up here
[Music]
so
no no hi container what the
[Music]
hell isn't this where we were fighting
the big boss
monster where am
[Music]
I Dam it let's
reset well let's go from here might be
easier no not here yeah I guess not it
was more like
South down in the South
[Music]
Region
okay oh [\h__\h]
no what oh yeah they did say they were
there were several of these
monsters in the
desert oh great I don't want to fight
them I'm here for something completely
different please leave me alone all of
you oh it's right at the
dungeon makes
sense oh there we are what are they
fighting
about oh
inside don't get too
close we've got to save them but
ow ow what what hurts you Dona what's
wrong fet following your counsel we have
tirelessly worked to defeat the monsters
tell me then why as this re gotten
bigger perhaps we have yet to defeat
enough monsters
Chief Sarah it's dangerous here let us
return to the Palace of
haste don't be absurd our soldiers have
been taken do you really think I'd leave
them
[Music]
behind she's just wasting her time this
girl endlessly now let's waste her time
we should throw her into the rift get
rid of her through the rift and then get
rid of the rift
[Music]
can we all have them watch how we enter
this
Rift yes thank you paying attention is
very important ladies you see this yeah
cool huh cute cute little Kirby star in
the rift Zelda is
dead yeah of course it is I've been
telling you you can enter the rift here
and get rid of it rid of the rift oh my
god let's go
into the rift R of the
rift
[Music]
oh this is the still world but this area
isn't connected to the big rift even so
I can sense my friends here they're not
moving at all I get the feeling they're
trapped or something if we rescue them
we'll be able to men the rift and R the
rift I can sense my friends in five
different areas they are somewhere in
this area here let's find them and
rescue
them hell yeah five different like not
all in one like before with the uh boss
oh hello
there that's one of the Warriors give me
that thing thank you
ooh what the what is that that looks
special maybe I can try reach that with
some beds
classic bed Strat now we can
try pushing them but no Maybe not maybe
you can't push beds wait how am I even
going to ah oh wait I can just fall down
here I didn't realize I was going to say
how am I going to make it over there
should have used ah wait a second I
thought there would be an invisible wall
but I should have gotten the
shoes how do you get up
there do I really have
to make some stairs that high that looks
really
high yeah thank God there's no fall
[Music]
damage maybe we'll get back to that
MH never mind I want to
try um with our trampoline Strat
[Music]
maybe
D wait I want to put one more there can
I do it while I'm bouncing
ah no cuz I can't move that
one
uh how to get up
there
no I I want to become the
bat
no maybe the bird
no come down Bird come down at
once I know that you can follow them and
you can have them carry
you come
on um well okay another thing you can do
is just drop the enemies which is nice
but a there we go now
fly let's go higher higher higher higher
higher can we get much higher come on
birdie I know you can do it is there
nothing motivating you to get up
there come
on aw I need that
spider where where the hell how do you
get that spider why don't I have it yet
hey go back to where there's safe ground
under me
hey yeah I don't think it wants to go
much higher unless there's an enemy
there to motivate it to do
so cuz I only
have this one spider dad creates the the
strings but it wouldn't have anything to
latge on
to and then in terms of
height I'm not sure how high we can
really
get well let's try a combination of
tables and
trampolines no further
oh
oh um do I want to push this one I guess
so can you fly from Higher
Ground I guess I
could like if we fly from Up
there oh
man oh even from
here I feel like I should be able to
reach you but I it's hard to tell how
far apart we
[Music]
are oh yeah know I know you can also
grab on to this bird too right how how
do come
here come
here oh wait I should look at the
shadow
Keys yeah don't go there how do I tell
them what direction I want to go
to
wait how do I hold on to it ah lifting I
guess ah no I tossed
it
uh just let it
go ah ah that was
close that was close
a little bit more high like literally
just like maybe if we start on top of a
bed or or something like
that or even I wonder if we can can we
jump while I don't I don't think we can
jump while holding it
but let's see if I can hold on to it
while I'm on the
trampoline free bats come on one of you
guys
I don't think I can hold on to that but
we can start maybe from top of
the
tree
oh uh what what am
I so
confusing uh
yeah ah
what okay now we need a bat again close
to me preferably
although thank you this is better
because uh the tree kind of creates a
little bit of a fense
there okay but we gain hide but we're
like further away than before so we will
maybe lose the same amount of hide
again where is it where is it ah so
close man it's got to be maybe from the
right side where I originally came from
can I go back
there try putting a table up there I
guess
so all right this is this is where we
started
off one of you guys
okay let's
go
oh it was so
easy and yeah we really needed to get
those it was
necessary all
along okay think with Echo guys make
sure to think with
Echo okay there something up here
too should we go down here
first ooh what are
those not an echo
[Music]
right not be but looks
cute can I control it
[Music]
ow I can control it and kind of pull it
down ow
we need to be more careful it
seems of more aware of my
surroundings
squish squishy
[Music]
Wawa is this really faster is it worth
it oh my bed is stuck there now
oh wait this is interesting I moved it
out of its frame and now it just stops
functioning
huh ah but I
wonder
stop can I bring
it here and then it will become a
platform for me
yeah it will always go up as far as it
can oh maybe not completely true but it
became a platform for me like these
nice okay there's nothing up here
though
sadly but we can do the same thing
here can I pull one out
no I don't
want there we go
I don't want two I feel like I don't
need to ow go up you get stuck there
damn
it
[Music]
okay I they move with me when I jump I
know I know I know I know I know does
this perhaps not give me enough hype to
get out of here ah okay wait we don't
want to get out of here there is no
exit but I got what I wanted pretty
much why does this this one not want to
go down
anymore did I glitch him cuz all the
others are happy to squish me into a
pancake should grab its Echo wait oh one
of them does give me an
[Music]
echo I don't think any
anyone offered it to me
K of
pancake k fried
pancake no I don't think you
can get these as
echos I can kill them wait I can kill
them they have HP they don't seem like
that type
of
thing uh okay okay
then
ow
nice see it's really good to be able to
control this one big
recommend you learned to Plat boom
Echo so I wonder if you use it in the
Overworld because it always seems to go
quite high like if there's a
maximum a set maximum of how high it
will go
we can try it out right here I
assume
whoa who thanks for Lifting me up at
least a little bit I needed
that so we can like skip a little
section here too maybe no cuz
I'm I'm too small wait come back
down my jumps are too inefficient ah ah
[Music]
that's going to be a handy elevator not
if your jumps are so weak that you can't
even get on top of the
base oh interesting it's in the enemy
section makes
[Music]
sense we'll just do it the basic way now
is this the same
fish or a new kind of fish I've seen
that similar enemies they they
sometimes have newer versions of them
that are like a higher rank they're just
like more
buff and more powerful sometimes
too thank goodness for bed
heels yeah agree
I want to get rid of this
fish can I
send my own fish it looks the
same actually wait wait it was just go
into the sand
please go into the stand don't be like
that so is it a different fish then
[Music]
maybe a wall fish fish versus a ground
fish fish is pretty useless yeah reminds
me of a certain Pokemon
[Music]
fish can just try to don't touch me okay
no I hate this fish
[Music]
come here come
here wait I just realized I could have
just controlled it though I could have
just tried to could just Tred to control
it I think I can make that
jump
myself ah
you know what we'll place a
[Music]
bed wait no no no I'm stuck
no
no this is getting ridiculous I just
want
to place a bed there thank you
and right now it removed my trampoline
which is fine I don't
care let's stay with the
beds go back to the bed thank
you it's just boring to always use bed
strats I don't want to use the bed
strats always
[Music]
is there anything
here oh yeah it are there some of those
lemons inside of that
too let's find out
wait it's a stone I thought it was a
cactus ah there it
is just hidden
underneath yippe I saved you aren't you
happy about that basically we could use
this as a free object to find our way
back um without losing all the beds over
there bed I love my bed I want to be in
bed all day it's so hard to get out of
bed this game gets
it good jump
Zelda mood right are you guys watching
me in
bed being
lazy it's okay guys it's okay to be lazy
your so far yes no
yeah yeah
yesterday good I like you guys being
comfy treat yourself with a comfortable
lifestyle that's
fine I didn't want to go up there
anyway oh my God
you want you want me to be comfortable
too I will never be
comfortable I'll never be
comfortable n just let me get back up
there please my jumps are too short for
I today is not my day for Zelda I keep
on getting stuck
I feel like I can make this jump I
just need
to go the right way about it but okay I
will put a trampoline
[Music]
there o I'll go up
first and then
down that's the right way to go without
being triggered by this
fish you're not getting a playmate today
mm- oh there's more souls
there Dark Souls
specifically a
wait there we
go she's in here which means outside is
an
[Music]
impostor what do you mean you wonder
just put one and one together easy
math is this the last one yeah it is oh
there was a little bar
there we found all my friends in this
area now we can me this
Rift watch everybody as you witness
history in the
making and of a rift to be get gotten
rid of look at those cute faces on those
lemons
witness me as I close up this Rift rid
of the
Rifts Ridder of the rifters that shall
be my title from now
on my friends shant some of the power
with
me I thought that would be
more that oo ended pretty early
Zelda let's go back to your world
now fine with me I hope I didn't miss
anything exciting in here I feel like I
saw
everything there's always this one worry
in the back of my mind did I miss some
item some
secret yeah this wasn't like a big rift
was but it was I would say it was a
proper Rift it was just smaller in size
Zelda oh my God where am I last I
remember I was putting a you're aake I'm
so reled everyone is back safely oh she
really did it the rift is
R we start it with our own eyes what
astonishing
powers faet where are you
going we shouldn't leave the palace
unguarded I must hurry back
oh oh wait is that the real one over
there she'll be very confused to see a
twin of
herself what what happened to
[Music]
me sh Sarah Captain Dona what has
happened wondering the same how did you
get
here I was I was looking into the Rifts
here in the
[Music]
desert and and then oh yeah then I was
pulled into a
rib I
see do
[Music]
you they all see Chief
Sarah I recommend Extreme Caution she
came out of the rift after all she could
be some kind of monster just like
me you don't actually think I trust you
do
[Music]
you
whoa I thought we would have to fight
her she just went for it no mercy all
right girl let's go wow wow proving us
why she is in
charge so she was AF fraud after all
foret yeah what would you have done if
she wasn't and you just sliced up a
human H
oopsie apologize afterwards
right like her saying so she was a fraud
after all seems like there was still
like a tiny bit of doubt in her
mind oopsie
facet made many questionable remarks
ever since the Rifts appeared she spoke
of a legend that promised defeating
monsters would eliminate the
Rifts burying the entrance entrance to
the S was also her
idea and she only suggested it once she
heard that the rift in the forest had
been eradicated now that I reflect upon
it uh she must have intended to keep
Zelda away from the rift but why uh oh
because she didn't want the Rifts to be
fixed all of her deceits were to that
end obviously Zelda although we were
deceived by the force for said I
apologize for how we treated you you
have my permission to restore the
entrance to the sanum and you have my
blessing I know it is selfish for me to
ask but you must use your power to help
me and my people you
must you have no
choice thank you so much chief
the entrance to the sanum sits at the
base of a quick sand flow in the sou
desert the cave that drains the sand was
plugged causing the flow to submerge the
entrance go speaks to the guard at the
cave and tell her what has transpired
and then spend 400 bucks on our local
shop to buy shoes so you don't have to
walk with too much trouble of
s you like my
friend thank you for one of the few
accents I can prop relatively properly
do better than my other accents at
least wa did
it once you ready please add to the S we
counting we counting on you Zelda
although I'm sure there's still many
mistakes in there and it's too
exaggerated of
course and obviously not every French
person talks like this or any for that
matter okay so I will buy those shoes
now I think I have the money for
it 2
s what does that mean are you
French that doesn't sound like the most
basic phrase people would
know you are the best oh thank you are
you
friendch yeah wait I don't have the
money for it wait wait wait wait wait
wasn't that closer to this before why do
I lack the money
now what to sell French Canadian ah the
Canadians they've got some
Advantage uh the drinks sell quite well
I could sell one of
these I'll sell both of
them and I'll just make
[Music]
more
ooh oh
yeah I'll just make more I still have
[Music]
ingredients oh wait never mind got to
buy
directly this doesn't look like my shoe
size it looks
like at least 20 sizes above my shoe
size but I'll buy it I could wear it on
my head or I could use it as a
snowboard yeah let's use it as a
snowboard
can Advantage from no just knowing more
languages yeah I keep on forgetting
about that
Canadians
okay how come is it because a lot of
French people settled in can Canada back
in the day back long ago they just
happened to all go
there must be yeah
mhm why did they
choose the
north where was I going to go ah okay
the main quest wants me to go here now
let's go I guess from just from the
city
F
interesting fzy and fluffy
fur I
see wait should I make some smoothies
though let's make some smoothies now
that I sold them
all apparently smoothies are really good
income
Source
beavers
[Music]
cute okay I wish I knew more recipes
though M now want to waste my things
like experimenting too
much but let's make you know another
Cactus
smoy maybe we'll need it in a dungeon I
feel like they would warn us if we
needed
it probably won't need it until we get
to the stone
people oopsie yeah uh I
think that is like way too many I wonder
if you just combine two grapes if you
would get like a less intense version
than this oh this say like okay it says
five and then another five does that
mean you get five extra hearts and it
heals five
Hearts try butter and milk
interesting what could that be I would
say that wouldn't make a smoothie but
like some kind of food but okay oh what
I'm out of M
[Music]
Hy oh I heal 10 Hearts but I don't get
extra Hearts
right you for
real I could sell this movie I just made
and I think that would mean
profit can I sell to you
yeah no Golden Hearts okay m I
see profit let's
[Music]
go now let's make
more yeah we made 15 bucks profit I
think what is
this better be something
good a I just milk okay milky Radiance
smovie what is it what is that this
movie is delectably creamy packed with
nutrients gives me a glow ah so like in
the dark I can see myself better when we
get into such a
[Music]
situation
uh resistance to Dam ooh I want to do
something with the mango can we just put
two mangoes together
probably gives me defense Maybe
okay it worked oh that's cute it has a
different glass than the others yeah I
like the the cute artwork for all these
drinks yeah a full body sweetness
highlights this pulpy fragrance movie M
Yum Yum Yum Yum damage reduction for 1
minute and many many muchos Grande
Hearts now I'm almost out of money
[Music]
again produ stronger effects greatly
Boosty effects potato
grants Drinker boost of uh wall climbing
speed restore some of the drinker's
energy energy as
in not the hearts but do you mean the
blue
energy wait do you always have to
use two things
[Music]
minimum I guess so
try mango and Horn I think that's good
okay you're wedding next week I've had
so much one traveling
a keep an eye out for samor photo what
are you bringing the puppets you should
dress them up
too weding why am I not
invited the hell
okay I'm out of money I'll make the
other drink again some other time let me
know when I'm making smothies again
remind me of the recipe
please yes water congratulations that's
exciting W I wonder what kind of wedding
you should show me
pictures I want to
see I want to see when it's
time I need to put on the shoes in the
inventory right
iPad
guest I mean big
celebrities sometimes you know they let
themselves get paid and invited
to normal people's
events especially weddings and birthday
parties but especially weddings so I
feel like
[Music]
it's not too crazy that a vtuber would
show up but it would maybe be kind of
weird would it be
weird was meant to invite the boss but
that must have gotten lost in the
post I've been checking my M BS every
day the plug is in
there
okay thank you for always summing up
everything
tree oh what the hell is that I'm sure I
can control that
too oh but it's a monster
right what the [\h__\h] is that how do I
fight
it this shoot
it
faster what
Don okay okay cute so it's uh not an
enemy um in this case
okay don't what are these ropes up there
do they have a
meaning why bother with like
blocking
anything I just drop him like it's
hot these things those are the ones I
saw that are really good for traveling
fast if you attach yourself to them oh
no not RADS I always try to like stay
away from them so far maybe these are
good against rad somehow like they're
going to just like slash them up slice
them
up well we got to kill one of
them if I drop them it's probably not
going to count as a proper kill
right oh maybe we can maybe we can smash
him go
up timing
no perfect easy way to get rid of these
[Music]
suckers oh wait I don't have to wait for
them I can just um try to spawn It
wait yeah on top of yeah just just
spawned on top of them
easy killer
[Music]
Roomba not recommended for usage at
home
sh sick oh did I accidentally activate
this with my platform I didn't realize
but that's
awesome I might use this a lot from now
on let's see if it works against the
ret oh hello you want to come over
here is he dead or just did that do
damage I'm not sure if it did damage but
let's send in oh no that definitely did
damage but not enough
so this one when you drop it I guess it
will always just go into One
Direction
well
go don't cut me though well this is one
way of doing it for
sure oh wrong
direction are they read think they are
right oh yeah this is this is fine
they don't do much damage but at least I
can stay away from them and I can have
relative good control over where I'm
placing
them
nice
learn they're in limbo a type of read
yeah the
gtto I saw those before in a different
Zelda
game I remember
them some money very appreciate it is it
a key or
what oh it's a key
K gift those are so tough we are not in
this game anymore nothing's a challenge
for
[Music]
us
oh oh dear oh that one looked bigger to
me because it dropped from the sky but
they're
[Music]
not all right how do we want to fight
them
uh I don't I want it on my other side
but okay it's going to work
anyway this is so
overpowered I feel like it's really this
game is one of the most m
one of those games that uh reward you
the most to play other uh to to watch
other players play
it there'll always be an aha
moment
and yeah you don't have to do it the way
others do but you know everybody has
their own ways of doing things
surely but it's just fun to see yeah how
other people exploit it
yeah rewarding to watch other let's
plays ooh dark. level three with a
spinning attack
[Music]
interesting um I'm just going to drop
you
bye I almost dropped
myself oh did they respawn oh they
respawned
how
mysterious mysterious things going on
here that I don't know the answer
to weird room just some just a ladder
[Music]
okay Clos door this will be the return I
guess wait is this a
dungeon no right it's just the thing to
turn something on to
[Music]
uh to open the dungeon I think right or
is this the dungeon is it another mini
dungeon to bring us to a big dungeon
what's the best way to kill these I'm
guessing they're immune to each other
like if I send in another of the same
kind what's the best way to fight them
like okay the plat booms but they're not
going to work in here there's not many
there not much space to do that I'll
try well it
works it gave me some space
here why is there a p because of the
Fairy Oh thanks for the heal I already
have a fairy I guess one is maximum
[Music]
oh blow me over there please
oh didn't work okay
fine I use my platform
again is it going to blow me no yeah
yeah not the best way to do it but it's
a way thank you so smart I was actually
today I was looking up IQ
tests where where to take aute tests
like online cuz I I feel like I've been
playing with this idea for a while now
but I kind of want to take an acute test
on stream but then I'm too worried that
what if I what if it turns out I'm
really embarrassingly
stupid
then I would regret doing it cuz people
are going to make fun of
me so maybe doing it off stream but
recording it and if the result is good I
shall put it up onto YouTube yeah for
Content I mean genuinely I know I I saw
coming that uh people
would kind of make fun of me well not
really make fun of me but be like like
baffled by me not by me saying I didn't
know how to read a clock until
recently um the reason I brought it up
again in holot talk is just because I
thought it was you know funny for
entertainment and really just did it for
the entertainment but yeah I saw I saw
it coming and it did happen there again
there were people like why the hell does
she not know how to read the time what
the hell this like
Unthinkable and some people were
saying like they would understand it if
I was from a different generation that
is like even more
digitalized yeah but you know you never
you never know like what kind of
circumstances someone's in you know when
they grow up and so on and
so yes to a certain extent I definitely
just like was able to avoid every
situation where I needed it
and I was never
really how to
say in in our household it never seemed
to be an issue either or it
also never came up to like teach me that
I guess but I don't even
think that it was
known that I didn't know
it but
anyway I know it's weird I know it's
crazy and normally I used to be so
extremely embarrassed and scared to be
like confronted with some situation
where I would have to read the time or
so was like quite
the
uh what's the
word nightmare for me not that's that's
not the right word that I'm looking for
but it's a
word um but
yeah I was always able to
just avoid these situations
[Music]
well yeah then the other way around I
know like I I I meet a lot of Americans
who can't read a digital clock which I
see as so much easier like military
time like I genuinely don't understand
that either but you know the culture
okay can't write my problem up as a
cultural thing I would I would agree
that's like
different but I feel
like it's kind of crazy to not know that
you
know but
I'm I'm not one to
judge how the
hell how did I get rid of that thing
over there I'm too stupid right now
right now I can't get rid of my own
thing it's bothering
me
wait oh yeah I should just send my
little wind Pokemon there you're
right but
first get rid of the thing with a
platform but is it going to fly to where
I want it to go to
yes it will okay I appreciate
that
who
[Music]
oh oh what am I
doing yeah I generally don't like
to like be seen as stupid or so
[Music]
but just with that I thought you know at
this point I have to see it with humor
my own inabilities I have to see it with
[Music]
humor yum me leave me
alone
[Music]
nice go for it attack attack yeah slice
them
up this one's strong huh even stronger
than the other one we just
[Music]
got Beyblades ooh double double
Beyblades
deadly
W oh they don't hurt me anymore oh
nice we're all a little dumb in our own
ways right there's this surely something
like that for everybody or almost
everybody something that's so basic but
you don't know how to do it for the
longest time I also didn't really know
how to ride a
bike
like I'm like I mean I could
probably once I'm on it and it's running
I I could probably stay on it for a
while but I was just really scared of
that too
didn't get taught properly how to ride a
bike when I was
young um well what was on the
right yeah but the traffic just really
scares me I wouldn't want to ride a bike
in the city in the park it's nice and
fun oh that's the plug I see wa there
goes the sand
that's understandable
right I didn't learn how to tie my shoes
until I was 11: yeah I do hear a lot of
a lot about other people who don't know
how to tie their shoes until much later
or I guess rather than how to tie shoes
I
also somehow come across a lot of people
who mostly men who don't know how to
make a
ribbon which is basically just like how
you tie a shoe
[Music]
tying shoes was my Crypton night
too yeah I think I also waited a long
time until I taught just ended up tell
teaching myself how to tie my own shoes
because that was another thing I didn't
know for a while I think
yeah and then at some point yeah I just
looked it up one thing I don't know but
this is I think just because I don't
need it usually I I I will never
understand how the hell you tie a
tie I looked it up sometimes try to
learn it for specific
things tying a tie man that's some kind
of science guys how do you do
it how do you do it I do not
understand love velcro SHO haven't worn
a Velo in a long time
though still can't do it
neatly it's
difficult yeah I tried with video
tutorials but even with video tutorials
M well it certainly doesn't turn out
great
[Music]
all right we're in the Garuda
s let's go
in into the rift and let's get rid of
the
rift yeah ties are magic I agree you
still need a visual tutorial I guess you
don't do it very much then like I I
guess people who have to wear uh suits
to work oh they certainly have it down
cuz they got to do it every day
are you guys pretending you don't know
what you just
saw a person in a green tunic Zelda
wasn't that link
duh obviously of course it was well
perhaps not the real
one what's up
there oh okay that's for climb okay
wasn't sure if it was a wall or
hey okay we'll go right
first that what you guys want from
me you got to just drop from the top I
guess no
hey can I press that while I'm
climbing oh I
can but it's
far it's too far I wish I can just jump
willingly but no no she doesn't hold on
ah wait I have to press up to hold on
again
right a I forgot about that I thought
she would hold on
herself that's not the case
case all right puzzle
solved wow I called it a puzzle and not
a
rle she learned I I I I don't know I
just when I think of a puzzle I think of
a puzzle not of a riddle so that was a
riddle in my mind
no no that just feels
wrong you know what I mean you call
those puzzles the puzzles with the
puzzle pieces that's a puzzle it's
really puzzling me how you guys can call
a riddle a
puzzle he they
respawn what I can just get endless
fruit
here
cheating hack farming time
oh [\h__\h] I found the dup Str for real
though it's not a bug n it's not a wait
to fruit
really actually it was an I accidentally
went back down didn't want to find this
kind of oh this time no
doors are faster maybe they are
yeah but will they respawn oh wait maybe
they're out of fruits now is there
really a limit or did they just life fix
the
bug oh well we got some money maybe the
rate is actually lower and I was just
really lucky the first few
times hey someone
[Music]
now I want to test it for
science huh
nothing do the chances lower the more
often you crack the same pot oh wait we
got two
again is it like a circle
how is this
coded
mommy got to do this for 10 minutes guys
no oh wow okay more grace all right I'll
stop here but if you guys need fruit you
know where to
go
could is it an exploit I wouldn't say
it's an
exploit that's not an
exploit I've seen exploits where you
like do stupid kind of like in different
games you do stupid kind of key
[Music]
combinations weird jumps and stuff
that's an
exploit is this an
exploit open up Nintendo
FBI it's no that's just normally
breaking pots normally it just responds
when you leave Thea that's not an
exploit that's not an exploit that's
just being smart A smart business
lady yeah no for sure like you can do
that anywhere in the world oh flying
tiles shut the we can crash those too
probably
right wait they're crushing themselves
but
wait I just had to wait for
them but aren't you supposed to be able
to learn these too so I need to kill
them properly I didn't get to learn them
[\h__\h] can they come
back can't you only learn things when
they're dead oh there they are again oh
yes ah ah they're bullying me oh wa ah
ah oh I can learn them before they're
dead right before I'm
dead yum yum
stop what that sucks that sucks that's
not
fair that's so mean that's an exploit
Nintendo you're
exploiting me
oh dear what what are we supposed to do
here first I need to understand do I
just
run do I send the flying tiles for some
reason perhaps possibly where are they
are they an item or an
enemy they are an
item so I get on to
one oh
oh one more wait to do it speedy
delivery of takanashi Kiara what is
this first try yeah first try even
though that happened so
[Music]
fast
Apple okay
so many fruit in
here Smokey
get oh we have
to go back
again going back is
easy
k Why helping what happened with the
economy oh dear what the hell is that
wait I can learn them
what are they I it's not an enemy it's
just a statue huh would be funny if we
were facing an enemy that looks exactly
like that soon after and it was going
to you know they were trying to deceive
us into thinking it's a statue but then
it turns out it's attack us y anyway
what there's there's some kind of riddle
here yeah riddle me this uh
uh what can I just walk through oh I can
huh what was that then
nothing what are these
[Music]
Pokmon you know
what what I used a [\h__\h] fair for
these [\h__\h]
[Music]
get stomped no
no oh they're attacking
it no you have to
spawn above them it's spawning below
them I see I see how it
is this is my shield now
[Music]
I need
healing I need
[Music]
healing
um Mama Mia stop following
me should we use a flying enemy but we
don't have many strong
ones just these stupid crows I don't
think they're very strong I'll just use
this one
again yeah you can do it on your own
actually yeah yeah you you'll do fine on
your own
actually or should I help it just needs
one more
maybe
spein again actually if I leave it alone
it will go up to their
height it won't do that if I control
it is it free Echo work this enemy cuz
it seems pretty
[Music]
strong it
is
morula m m Ms are m m Flappy
mobs um attack you stupid
Flappy
[Music]
Bird
yeah oh we got to pull the plug
somewhere else too it seems because
there's a door that is blocked by the
sand Dracula plus b Mo
oh I mean don't mobs sometimes actually
have fangs like that or is that just in
my
nightmares um I
say
straight it's not very
straight oh you stopped that you don't
go
over Oh I thought you would
what does this
mean why are
these running treadmills there I you did
flying tile right I forgot about the the
systems of
them very
[Music]
easy
y I wouldn't even call it cheesing
because I mean they're introducing them
in this dungeon
so they want you to use
them oh dear oh how
fun can't get me is that a leveled up
armadillo seems like
it I have something
similar a beblade
I stops
there
oh damn that armor Dill got some Tough
Armor oh there it
[Music]
goes cute Cyro Millo level
two
what that
was y
wait leave me
alone it just stops okay you don't want
to roll again huh huh don't be shy
now I fell into the
abyss wait why don't I just sleep in the
bed
[Music]
forgot ah
I wasn't
sure if he would just not like bounce
off of my
bed I was hoping for
that come on sleep sleep sleep sleep
sleep harder sleep
harder uh what was the thing again the
molf there
[Music]
nice oh no we go down to it again I
don't want to face
that treacherous armadillo
again
again maybe yeah Aro Arro that thing
first thank
you
[Music]
bye another golden egg can make some
fire omelets with that I'm sure oh what
is this
room we get a
checkpoint this doesn't feel like a mini
dungeon guys feels like a big dungeon
though seek two distinct tributes Clues
to the desired tributes are recorded
somewhere on the floor wouldn't it just
be the statues that we learned
elsewhere or do I need two different
ones
all right then I'll go looking for the
[Music]
hints uh what are
these what is that flame that he
produced attack m
you can do it don't get burnt there I
don't know if that's actual fire
but be
careful yeah good job maybe one more hit
I believe in
you yeah good job oh there was only one
and that was a
challenge must have been a powerful
Pokemon yipp it was a good choice good
choice of
Pokmon we got the
up I'm just going to call it Pokemon
now a PO a PO I like the
design looks pretty all of the designs
are honestly nice maybe this game can do
a little collaboration with Pokemon you
know like a like a tie up and they can
put some of these Echo as new Pokmon in
cas Pokmon ran out of ideas they
probably you know would appreciate some
free ideas
for
Pokemon just put some of the echo in
[Music]
there hey
look Hey
listen that's got to be link but where
is he
going let's see what's what's something
that could be a
Pokemon this thing for sure could become
a bigger candle or like a triple candle
but maybe we already had something like
that
before this nah this thing nah hopefully
not these could be a
Pokemon this one we already have plenty
of snakes this one could be a Pokemon I
would
say this one if there's not already an
existing one the bat is just boring we
already have bats probably already have
something interesting uh similar to
this we don't need any more fish do we
have something like that maybe could
become bigger when it has an
evolution this this thing I don't really
I still don't really know what this is
but it would be cool if that became a
Pokemon this thing yeah yeah oh
Octillery I see these two these two
maybe could be a Pokemon
especially the
PO these two probably
not you say all of these already are
Pokemon pretty
much
H you
secret I'm not just going to let this
[Music]
stand let me in
oh
money oh [\h__\h] I'm robbing the guto seum
I don't feel so good about
this not
anymore is there something up here
[Music]
too ooh oh yeah there is I don't oh
where are you supposed to come up here
eventually because there's a safe point
wait what are the triangles on the
map oh my god oh there's so many enemies
ah [\h__\h] right it doesn't spawn above
them do
something do something attack
them what are you
doing what is it
doing I'm
[Music]
scared ah from so far
really more more more faster
faster don't give up kill everything in
your
[Music]
surroundings come on come on protect me
what are you here
for fly like a
butterfly all right I think that's it
over
here let me get some
wind or is this just going to produce
more enemies please no
[Music]
oh Treasure
Chest
nice worth it hopefully money no a
monster Stone we still don't really know
what those are for but I feel like uh
those existed kind of in a way in
different Zelda games
too come here come
here kidney
stone now do we want to go up here too
there's nothing up there but
it's kind of
[Music]
sus no
nothing okay but I got the safe point
the
Waypoint
um what's that mean ah it's part of the
dungeon ah ways to get into the
buildings again
openings all right then let's go over
there cuz it seems
like perhaps even the more apparent
path K welcome to the
stream a reference hell
yeah the other day I went to K with my
friend cuz it was birthday of one of my
best
friends
and one of the songs I sang was um I say
yes to and I thought nobody would know
another song there but I'm surprised
recently not just herb but people
IRL recognizing zon Nota songs makes me
happy ow
and then one of the people uh like
friends with my friend that I didn't
know sang Two Yakuza songs I got really
hyped let's go
y good song
choice where very good song
Choice One of it was of
[Music]
course oh the fish is on
top are they dead
now finally
no I can't get
up you want to hear me sing 21 like all
these songs like it's difficult because
I I know them slightly vely from playing
the games but not enough to actually
sing them in kok yet at least I don't
feel quite so
confident uh to sing them in K maybe I
could but I'm not sure
there's certainly one or two that I
could
probably sing quite well besides d
[Music]
that so
slightly ah well
maybe link I'm sure there's better ways
but it's not
enough It's never enough
all
right another
[Music]
idea yeah that would fall down
trying to min max things
but just probably should
think in a simple way but hey just kind
of worked out oh there's like upgraded
versions of the wind
enemy the
wind guy is it UPG it looks a little bit
different color to me
H let's see might be the same and I'm
just
like so
[Music]
rude Revenge me avenge
me quick
quick oh come on at least I'm not losing
HP wait is he gone now in my did you do
it in my absence well now I don't know
if that was a new one perhaps it dropped
it fell
down no but I think
actually nice
Dodge perhaps it's the
same
y okay they're going so far I don't care
anymore where are we
uhhuh this area is unexplored or no we
were't there right this was the part
where I used my platforms a
lot in there oh let's test our shoes oh
yeah we can really walk normally
here what is this area though
what's I'm questioning it but maybe
there's nothing to question
maybe just to get up here oh now we're
on the roof again oh okay everything
leads back to this area I've explored
all of that did I explore this part or
is that where I came from nah I probably
got to explore
it let's check it out
I love the ground pound Echo is just so
brain free
easy hey y' wait what's in
here yeah this is
new I think yeah
sick look at those
skills oh oh that's the second statue
that
I'm need I thought so because the way it
was phrased it did sound like it might
need two different ones but the one I
have is certainly one of
them yeah let's bully them like
that why the hell not
oh wait I can't use my platform in here
there's too little space ah unless
oh
no
[Music]
no why is it not working now guys what's
the best Strat against the
rad maybe another rad
no okay but I'll I'll I'll bring out my
gibo level two
they're attacking at the same speed but
mine has more HP it seems so that's good
hey and they're immune to the scream so
yeah probably that's the best
match for other red Deads
andos I haven't learned this one
yet
sorry flying tiles h usually fire not
sure this
game Fire H all the fire things I have I
think are pretty
weak cute
C almost Cheeto
cat why is never go where I wanted to
go there was nothing underneath these
sand pillars
what do we have
here a safe
point
and maybe a mini
boss it's kind of sus a safe point and
like
a yeah that looks like a mini
boss then I should probably sleep first
yep don't worry I had the same
idea almost went in without
[Music]
sleeping this game is Dela developer
mode
ah you could see it like that
yeah oh definitely yeah okay oh are we
finding link as the like in between boss
again this one doesn't look
evil did he always look like that oh
nice wait that just thank you now you
look evil that just made me realize
something I didn't realize before we can
dodge uh like any kind of bullets or so
by turning and
twisting what do we want to
use does link get stunned
buy our rad screams do gios scream I
don't remember maybe the gios don't
scream only the
Reds he surely gets stunned but I think
I got to use a read it and then I could
since I still have more energy then how
much do I have right now five I could
still throw something else into the
mix I have five right where can I see
this right
now
[Music]
maybe
maybe just one oh what maybe I have four
oh yeah we went from three to
four
okay actually with his Arrow
a dark knot would probably be better cuz
I'm guessing the dark knot blocks the
arrows quite
[Music]
nicely
uh-oh you know
what [\h__\h] this oh he runs away from
me I get
wrecked oh he comes back I don't need
any of my helpers
anymore stop running stop running stop
running oh
easy with someone like link you might
just want to become link as well but
will that be useful for the second round
too or we not getting a second round
this time no for sure we are triple
link oh no way wait
y let me throw in perhaps say cuz the
read was not screaming at all and kind
of useless let me throw in a dark
nut as a good
[Music]
Target okay
nice he's charging
it from
oh the music is kind of
[Music]
Epic oh did I have Full Hearts
already you scared of my dark knut
huh you feel like he tends to run away
once he sees
me Darkness help me out here bait him
please oh yeah we can Corner him
[Music]
you little [\h__\h] can't get away from
me
oh oh yeah our link will get to use this
now okay for a moment I thought Z gets
to use it of course not and we have to
turn into Link in order to learn how to
use the
bow but cool
this is like what happened with facette
and your people at the Castle link was
taken by the still world and replaced
with an impostor to maybe we can help
the real link by fixing the
rift it's a good first
step was there anything to gain from the
sand I heart
link is dead once
again by the hands of Zelda don't take
this out of context guys it's just
within this game Zelda kills link
several
times does this sound wrong to you
perhaps but it is the new reality that
we live
in and I like it
ah yeah I was about to try to remember
what that was what that
spawned speed us
[Music]
no will we be faster than the spider
spawn I guess not
oh oh wait that's
genius wait that was genius we can place
him in front of each other and I I
thought that maybe one of them would
like not go through because the front
one would block it but no that wasn't
the
case oh look at all these
like uh licorice
gum leftovers we have to get rid of it
but I have to make a platform
first yeah I'll just make B
platform oops wait should use cheaper
bed what the
hell wait I could shoot
it right I don't have to get so close
out but I mean isn't there a ladder for
a
reason sorry took me a moment but I
figured it out that I can use my bow too
yeah yeah yeah don't worry don't worry
[Music]
you have to go down again or is there
nothing there
no it all takes a little bit of time in
this game you
know realizing the simplest
things it's okay it's
[Music]
okay fire fire fire if I can learn how
to create wind machines I can also learn
how to create
these oh I can turn it I that's not even
what I was trying to do but
okay
H well how will I get to learn how to
use was that how you guys did it I
wonder
look can I learn you from like here no
maybe if I'm on
you okay no I was literally right next
to it I can't learn it
yet do I are they
killable the wind machine wasn't
something we could kill
right oh what there's another another
statue
huh another statue now we have three
statues
huh okay somewhere then there's a hint
probably we'll learn one more to have
four statues in total and somewhere
there's a hint that tells us which ones
to use or we just brute force
it I would just put something on the
other track to block the pl yeah that's
also certainly a
way where there's a will there's a way
but I
like what we just go
back I guess
so there's still a couple rooms here I
want to warp there maybe that's what we
should be doing
anyway cuz all the closed by rooms have
already explored
and we got a new key now yeah we're
probably supposed to go here
anyway where are we we haven't tried
this but that's just a rate to return
perhaps ooh the armadillo
place should I just try placing them or
I feel like there's a fourth one let me
turn this
[Music]
yeah we haven't done this room yet have
we you know it's nice to have these
pretty statues for this dungeon but I
really wish cuz we probably don't need
them ever again afterwards I really wish
there was a way to get rid of them
afterwards
ow you never know oh ah that's probably
the hint that tells me which statues to
[Music]
place yeah they should have really
fought the menu through a little bit
more
like at this point I can't see them
adding anything like later in the game
that would help us like why wouldn't you
add it in the
[Music]
beginning a Tok uh I wouldn't even say
is as bad as this in terms of this kind
of quick menu
you can kind of brute force your
favorites menu by just spawning
something a million times in a
row but I don't know like still having
others in that same menu I just want to
make my own menu where I can choose
specific ones or just get rid of old
ones that I don't want to use anymore
just to clean it
up I just want to clean it
up it gets so cluttered especially when
there's
okay well actually for
beds there's good use for both beds and
I think there's still one more better
bed but like the older bed I will use
for building the newer bed I will use
for healing that makes
sense but what's with the freaking
pots it stands quietly in the sanctum it
is blue in color with large tusks and a
long nose Okay blue
elephant eh so you're just telling me
one of the things that need to be
[Music]
placed I could FR Force the others
should I do that maybe I missed a note
somewhere but is this the boss
room
cuz oh wait
no this room leads into this unknown
room and then into this unknown
room ah this is the boss room ah then
here is the boss room key then I guess
it's okay to try the Brute Forces
now did it say on which side it should
stand I feel like
no how about cat and
elephant
no how about cat and snake H cat
elephant and snake no h
well is it both
elephants does the side matter
okay maybe the game
knows yeah I'm still missing something I
knew there were four I knew it well
where but where I've entered all the
rooms
[Music]
outside I all right cuz we did get one
thing outside did we did
we yeah but why would I go
[Music]
outside what if I want to go outside now
how do I go outside
where's the
exit on the way
points out
[Music]
there I need
a thing but wasn't I everywhere here
too oh let's check out the right
side how did I get up
before probably my
beloved ground pound
[Music]
machine there was a way point near the
door which
door well it's okay I'll just go this
way Sur me there was something here that
I
missed ah now this is where I went in
right let me
check um
[Music]
maybe
stop [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] leave me
alone leave me alone w
that looks like something
new they look
scary should I attack with link or
should I just try to crush them
again
[Music]
ah oh
[\h__\h]
ow well a lot of most ah most of the
things ah you spawn can't hurt you I
think but these ones certainly can it
seems take that as a
reference I hate them I hate them yeah
attacked the platform right why do you
keep on attacking me I don't even
understand
I'll heal soon enough once my platform
is done with
this
party nothing Pat a ground
pound stop screaming it won't help
you won't help anyone
[Music]
they should let me voice one of these in
a future Dela game if they need a good
screamer let me know hit me
up my screams are some of the best
screams in the business they
say in the industry I mean what is this
place something sussy behind these
stand kills if I could only hit
them okay but there was nothing oh but
there's another one of these like weird
Towers all
[Music]
right oh wait you can't summon when you
Linka D ola
[Music]
oh is it an owl or a hawk you guys said
hawk it's a bird in any case cool bird
looks like a superhero
bird
yippee now we got them all
in we go
again uh oh but how about going straight
here
again if next is boss key that means
we're almost through of this dungeon
right and we already fought the mid boss
so do we just get the boss key for
free wait I didn't read a note though do
I have to guess the other well I guess
it's the
Hulk oh now it's glowing did it Glow
before it didn't it just
knows it just
knows calling him mid yeah cuz I forgot
what it's called again when the boss is
not the final boss
[Music]
um what's it called again
he's in the
middle mini boss he's certainly
small okay let to eat a chocolate the
last one I have on my
table I brought a limited amount so that
I wouldn't eat too many
[Music]
oh sand coming through
MH oh boss
room or the room before the
[Music]
bom
oh ah oh oh wow that's fancy which it
has some kind of puzzle
mechanism do you
nuzzle calling the mid bosses for now
you you can you're welcome please use my
words I share my words with
you happily oh this one I have to grab
on my own unlike other
things that was easy you kidding me
[Music]
why
ah this one I can turn by
myself was that what we wanted all right
was okay just like one
turn with my ultra hand will'll kind of
get it off of that
Rhythm what a cool
Stage
B is this shortcut to boss
room it is oh now the abyss
Give me the give me the
energy give
me I get it lemon
Chun there's a locked door I
[Music]
missed
no I shall return
[Music]
how did I miss
it do I have the
key do never got to use
it you know you know what we should have
called that thing the thing that you
called exploit some of you guys called
it explod we should have called it Fruit
Loops can
it thank
you matter Peppa isn't a
fruit nothing ever matters
oh will they teach me how to get the
fire machine here or
what I guess I don't necessarily need
[Music]
it you shall be
sacrificed I see where the issue
is Maybe
do we really have to go to the
[Music]
machine
ah can I shoot the
box I can't
wait if I shoot through the fire with
Link's Arrow or maybe I'm too small
but okay I'm too small but I can shoot
while I'm jumping okay my aim is do so
let's just do
it
differently yeah let's go that was a
good riddle
oh that's just the other hand what
statue is
needed oh that sucks I thought we would
get a treasure
[Music]
chest all right I will do the fro Loops
then I need some kind of reward for
this one
rupee hey we're already back to 200
goes got some fruit I
guess so this all right tele oh wait
there
unopen where is
this what the hell why am I missing so
many things how do you get there
maybe it wasn't accessible before
because of the
sand I see it right in front of
me is there a secret door I can
pull head this
room there is
ah from the
top so from outside
maybe it must be from
outside where is that outside
[Music]
interesting let's go let's go let's go
how do we get
[Music]
outside I will not leave this dungeon
without all of the treasure chests in my
hands especially after that scam just
now where I didn't get any
treasure even though I went all through
all of the trouble to return
Lear to fulfill my
destiny this is how I get
rid oh wait that is like suspicious
right is it this
[Music]
porn I'm out of energy
no oh oh it
hurt stop stop
[Music]
wait
mama are you for real what happens
now my first game
over is this just
basically it reset us what happened
here just like we lost no progress
right I never said this Zelda game was a
kids game I don't think I ever called
any Zelda game a kids game I only called
Super Mario games the kids game I think
[Music]
first time I've seen link run like a
chicken
[Music]
hey kill for me
kill it for me my servant do
it end it
now now let's focus on the task at hand
it will be kind of dumb if that's not
the right point but I just assume I
didn't press
up I I this looks so
right
okay money okay 50 R we really seem to
need money a lot in this game so far
so I accept
it ah here we are
onto the boss we go what kind of boss
will it
be thank
you thank you I wonder how many dungeons
there are there's probably already some
people who cleared the game who could
who probably already put the information
online
I'm
curious dropped in at a perfect time you
call at a perfect time I guess
so usually d games have eight usually
well that tradition hasn't been upheld
for a long time
now
oh what are the stat is doing here
what is it a bear is it a mole is it
a I don't freaking
know what if we fight it with its babies
I I I I just want to use my platform
Y no can it not spawn on him
ah I think
[Music]
it's still trying still trying okay no
won't
work
um different
idea yeah you just go for it oh m
what's it with these why are they here
why are they here
block why don't I just turn into
[Music]
link I can shoot him from afar
don't have to get so close to
[Music]
him ah I see he y so they were for him
to
B run into oh oh oh welome ah if you
don't have the shoes you are [\h__\h] here
he has wings he's
a don't don't don't H
me really good to have the
shoes
tornado you for real
[Music]
now I have it
to I always like the Happy jingle it's
so Random
[Music]
can I
please what the best way to fight ah
shoot but I I don't have enough energy
though at least I got to do it when the
tornadoes are gone this is kind
of wait perhaps there's energy in the
[Music]
Hills oh he's focusing on my mobs for
now that's good I okay um
just run a little bit but the tornadoes
I don't want to I don't want to do this
with the
[Music]
tornadoes a I need a lot more energy oh
oh oh heart oh did I not need it all
right he's going to dash
no oh he's going to do the other
thing
ah he's going to do it again
ah oh there's barely any time to
shoot it doesn't give me much time not
much
leeway please focus on some other mobs
of mine please thank you although maybe
those are the worst ones to choose cuz
they don't really
attack
um but something flying would be
nice let's give him two crows
[Music]
and maybe what is he never mind
Dash okay come out
please oh okay at least now he's
shooting towards the pros but I'm
already out of energy
y so I need my wind machine again
not what I was hoping
for that on your own statues oh to make
him Bonk into it nah it's okay we don't
need the statues anymore not in this
phas one single piece are you for
real that's really not enough
[Music]
oh does he always spawn in the same
areas I don't even think I can put
my statues into the sinking
[Music]
Sam give me some s there we
go
a
that
mmy it's like
all right all right all right all right
I place some
statues which one
bird does he Target them though I don't
think the tornadoes destroy them
yes how dare you destroy this this is
historical monuments St you need to be
respected okay he didn't care about that
one I just want to put him so that
they're ready for him ooh they blocked
the slashes at least and he's back to
tornadoes I don't know
[Music]
man let me just check the sand FS again
hard no
no okay got some energy all right it's
filling up again this is good
ow this is good this is a decent amount
we can now probably shoot
okay I did as much as I
could but it's not
enough do I really need
those statues
[Music]
really wind is needed again fish could
bite underground I wonder if they would
even if they do they have really low
damage
[Music]
uh sometimes I press the wrong button oh
thanks for getting rid of that for
me wonder how much more damage he
needs maybe it's worth it already
[Music]
[\h__\h] what do you mean Dad I'm doing
fine I tried to get him into the statues
I've placed them several
times not my fault that he doesn't want
to go where they
[Music]
are just give me some time have
patience did they sink yeah they
sink no
[Music]
it's just hard to coordinate that he
goes into this uh
statues so honestly I don't care for it
I'm just going to do the
W I've got a good amount but I'm just
going to wait for the
tornadoes and place some other enemy as
a thing for him to focus on
probably just Spam my own tornadoes
again oh no no it's not visible
[Music]
now [\h__\h]
no not why are you why are you trying to
shoot
ah why would I why would I shoot
the my own creations
[Music]
yeah chat you need to
chill I don't even know what you mean
with Fon Strat if it is the statue [\h__\h]
I tried it I don't care for
it he these are kind of
buff it's all going to work out
[Music]
well it's a bit longer than I would want
it to be this
[Music]
fight now he's going to immedately let's
wait let wait
wait time
[Music]
how strong is he and how weak is my
arrow I don't get's too much information
now you tried guys but I I don't want to
actually no no no why are the buttons so
close to each other
[Music]
I'll transform into link but I also want
to throw out an enemy I just wonder
what's the best one
[Music]
M they all suck they even too
slow or too low
damage and I don't have much link energy
anyway
though beblade beblade is hard to get
the right
direction I was thinking of the next
too but they're so
weak they attack fast at
least wait they're sinking no they
sink oh well Snak you tried you gave me
the em support that I
needed they're not look at them drowning
no they're not uh desert
snakes poor danger
noodles look at all the
lemons yay free the lemons
[Applause]
[Music]
lemon
dance first try oh
[Music]
yeah this time the link fight was easier
I think the first time the link fight
wasn't it more troublesome
maybe not necessarily but it was like on
par with the main boss fight I feel
like everything hurts everything hurts I
need a massage a real one and I just
honestly even massages don't help I just
need to rip out my arms and my head
yeah the first link fight is just
difficult because you don't really know
much yet I
guess this time it's more
right
yeah mhm a full
bar yay what Echo at The
Distance by pressing and holding y to
charge power like I don't have to create
them right in front of me
money what what what no exra oh what we
didn't get it what I would have
preferred an extra
slot my friends told me something while
we were mending the
rift they said that
monster they said that monster captured
them it was the first time something
like that happened to them but since you
defeated the monster can get back to
work Yi there's not really anything else
to do in the still world for now so
let's go back to your world
Zelda just trying to manipulate me into
leaving the heart container behind
there's still something to do it's
taking the heart
[Music]
container new
heart yippe
yay going to take me
back stream height container best waa
song to
date love
Comer oh hey
there surprise it's a me
W you're
back all of the Rifts are gone now
including the big one that was here you
did it Zelda everyone in town is
awaiting your return come on let's go
together I am just that awesome I know
time to celebrate the Rifts going away
come on it's on me it's a r of Rift
party you're going to come kind to me to
help you play the bin again aren't you
just at that moment the faint shadow of
a warrior arose out of the
darkness wait who's talking right or
left looks like everyone conveniently
forgotten that it's time for training oh
come on now this is a time of
Celebration the rest are gone training
can happen
[Music]
tomorrow every one in good spirits
they really
are they really are zeld allow me to
express my deepest
gratitude
gratitude thank you mer for helping
us we we thank you so
mucha
Mery because of you we took decisive
action and our dessert is served safe
dessert is sered I would love to serf
some dessert now
P your determination and your love for
our people have Saed this
down oh
mother you've grown so much in fact I
think you are already capable of being
shfe what not yet right I mean there's
still so much I have to
learn but Mercy B feels good to hear you
say
that Zelda you intend to continue
traveling and fixing gfts I will I will
pay pray for you but pay I would
appreciate that for your
success yeah don't I get like a better
reward from these people what did I get
nothing not even a discount on the
shoes I saved this whole region
did they give me
anything don't think
so
[Music]
bro turned out that your father wasn't
here
either but there's still another Rift to
check out it's far to the east in a
place with lots of
water let's should they be
British so let's go take care of that
now
[Music]
I can practice my British accent there
again that's so true kitty cat you're so
right you're so wise what a wise
[Music]
cat we owe you a great app you're
welcome to visit so you aware that you
owe
me and what do I get just an invitation
to come
again
wow I shall take all your fruit
loops why did you empty
[Music]
them wait should I get rid of it are you
freaked out talk to me actually she
won't talk to me I thought it would be
cool to get up here oh oh wait now ha
who you scared me how did you get up
here I'm impressed mhm I fell asleep
during training so I've got to repair
the hole in this roof as punishment oh I
feel it was sand and that pluged up it's
kind of sloppy but it will fine can you
move aside so I can dig my way through
it you say it's
sand authorized person that won't let me
in maybe later she'll be somewhere else
and then I can dig through and I feel
like there might be some treasure
there can I go through Windows if I make
myself a
[Music]
platform I feel like it's too
small what's with these
anyway chill
[Music]
move her move her you think I can move
people I've never tried wait we can try
with you
first I can't try uh can't do it on her
maybe only specific
[Music]
no okay I feel like for now perhaps
we're done in this region
we can move on to the next
region what is this
sausage oh wow she's hot someone told me
you got rid of the r here in our
desert and here I thought you were just
some scny little thing I'm
impressed okay I'm impressing the ladies
but what I'm not what like I'm still I
don't I want
something I impressed the Ladies by
default there's not much of a change
from like def status
[Music]
quo Zelda rism up and then and then what
did I miss anything
interesting well what do you have to say
now nothing nothing
special all right I'm leaving you
girls I shall move on the next area is
over there so perhaps we want to start
walking there either from here or from
there I
wonder perhaps from
here I impress a lot of women you think
[Music]
so yeah the girls girls girls section is
over no more girls girls girls
only it will be mixed
again oh
sad wait that's a spider that I
need
uh that's the op spider
oopsy oh
[Music]
no hopefully it doesn't create a million
more spiders the moment I kill it oh how
dare you crawl on top of it
no is kind of cute
oh it's pretty there you
go her reactions are cute craw TOA
Echo have I been here before or
[Music]
not so laggy right now on my side yeah
okay I've opened it before so been here
done
that looks at chat for one
second get squished by the random Echo I
placed randomly
[Music]
maybe are they too fat yeah they're too
fat for me to place it on top of
them all right all right I'll use more
proper ways of
[Music]
fighting or I could just run by them I
don't need
them I really don't need to bother
myself with
them what is
this oh there's a heart container okay I
see I see I
[Music]
see oh you want me to help you all right
I can do that too we love side quest I
love side
quests damn I didn't know they could
scream like
that
terrifying the squish is very funny it
is the eye blade
yeah yeah I remember
[Music]
it we love 8 Hour streams what do you
mean this is very far from an 8 Hour
stream
still by the way the extra stream that I
said might happen I don't know if that
will still happen might might be
difficult actually
[Music]
oh
man I just checked the DM from cie cuz I
saw that she's she has this performance
in this like Coca-Cola thing I don't
know what that is some Coca-Cola live
concert and something might sound
familiar to you guys there because I
taught you one of the people there is
new jeans performing as well and the
moment I saw that I was like what are
you meeting new jeans and she said she's
not sure but if she meets them she'll
get an autograph for me but man I will I
no I'm going
to I'm going to Mor I'm going to
Mor that's not fair I want to meet new
jeans I'm going to die I'm literally
going to die I'm going to die
I'm going to
die I'm going to
more they do have a Coca-Cola song new
jeans
[Music]
cocaa that's the new jeans Coca-Cola
song they had a sponsor
[Music]
Shing I'm so
jealous like I can't even
pretend and I'm fine cuz I'm not like
you saying that you're fine but you're
really not fine because you want to meet
you J and you can't be there because
you're not even in Japan and you don't
have the record label de so what can you
really do so you're say you're fine
you're really not fine no matter how
many times you say it you're fine you
you keep on doing it even with an
autograph it's just not the same because
you can't get to see
[Music]
of claim that you're her Korean trans
she doesn't need a Korean translator
it's happening in Japan
[Music]
anyway I Boys in Japan maybe you know I
could like be her plus one or whatever
but it's in October the one month where
I am not
traveling and I'd like to keep it that
[Music]
way yeah now I saw the guy I'll probably
end up there eventually anyway
H but I will tell her to like just I
don't know not just get an autograph but
show them maybe a song of
[Music]
mine I just want them to be aware of me
and then maybe maybe she maybe they'll
tell her oh we already know
Taki we already know her of
course I mean who knows maybe they
do maybe they
do you know they're young and zooming
maybe they know Zoomer
things and if they're like performing
with a vtuber then they might already
have been uh informed about what vtubers
are and in that briefing maybe
they me I
[Music]
don't something similar happened to me
while my friend got very close to me my
was you oh
[Music]
man one day I should debute at mnet I
want to I I really wish I could somehow
get into those Korean music shows but
don't have any context don't have a
label that would push me in there I
don't have the power or any kind of ways
means would need a label at least a
label
yeah at least we finish putting up one
posters in the west but nobody seen
Princess Zelda yet first we we ordered
to save her now we're order to capture
her it doesn't really should right with
me to be treating her like some sort of
villain he's a good guy I mean it's is
weird to me too but ERS are orders no I
guess anyway we learn nothing out
Eastern Seaside vill's Patrol here for
now I guess where did
[Music]
they oh is that where I'm
going they're basically telling me it's
safe there no patrols
there good soldiers follow
orders yeah
like it's it's just thing like just now
in rings of power there was a situation
like that too in the episode that I
watched
yeah like especially if you
know whoever you're following is
corrupted by some evil magic okay they
don't know that these guys don't know
that but they surely if they think of
their own brains wouldn't they notice
that something's going wrong really
badly and maybe they
should you know not lose their integrity
and think of their own brain for
once but it's their job their swor their
sworn loyalty but then at the same time
you know I'm part of that royal
family but first and foremost they're
sworn to the king
so you know but I feel like you can
break an O like that but if you're the
only one breaking it you you know you
need more people to break it in order
for there to be any kind
of change and a change that is not your
death so yeah
but if we run around with lefta now yeah
the one that We rescued would would
perhaps maybe not um that be
enough me together like Zelda together
with
lefta lefta being one who has opposed me
before wouldn't that be enough to get
people to
listen where was the I
here I want to go back once and check if
I can get
upgrades so just be like that they're
normally trying to not think with their
own brains and situations like this yeah
I guess
so y too bad too
bad I
mean well but it must be hard like if
you in your heart maybe you're thinking
this is not something you want want to
do this is not something you someone you
want to go up against or
whatever must be really tearing you
apart to go against your own
beliefs because of what you swore
loyalty to has changed so
much oh wait what I don't want to learn
about Wing
[Music]
sorry he's a
yapper I want to use the machine
uh huh previously we upgraded the energy
right cracking my hip maybe the sword I
guess we're so close to getting another
upgrade damn
it I feel like more energy would be even
better but oh
well just stay in the form longer but
then then it will have to take more to
uh to fill it
[Music]
up yeah I'll be
back 10 is
expensive isn't that ultimately an REO
herbs plotline is
it is
it I don't
know oh man I didn't find any wayo there
[Music]
walking is
healthy am I going the right
way I think
so from here we can go right I guess
[Music]
he's loyal to the evil
King she was right in being loyal to
crony though right she she did believe
in
crony Tim Tam Tam ters Timmy
[Music]
Tammy ah there's easy enemies here in
case you go here first huh and different
FES are those
piranas oh
[Music]
god oh I can cut grass with
this
nice CL mow her did not support
CR n e but isn't that how we got along
so well she respected
my beliefs in crony didn't didn't we
both support
crony have
I I been
miss all right but I don't know my memor
is I guess very
wrong ah all right here was like like ah
I
yeah I like you
but you're rooting for the
wrong king/
Queen but was also
wrong oh um say have you perhaps seen
the Great Fairy around
here the Great Fairy is a Divine being
known to gr people mysterious poish
after pouring pouring over old writings
about her I have the reason to believe
she's hiding here at lakeia in these
writings they say she's beautiful enough
to take your breath away that she'll
Steal Your Heart the moment you lay eyes
on
her I'd give anything to catch just one
glimpse of the Great
Fairy can I find her
already maybe she's in the
rift where am I supposed to go where so
far
oh this is like Kia let's go for a swim
[Music]
uhoh can s Pia swim in the
water
no you're not much of a fish are
you what do I have that works in the
water nothing an
OCT it sits on the water nice oh good
job
[Music]
quick kill tangler Echo
tangler so many fishies I will cook fish
today I think I got my next H fresh
[Music]
order yeah and I got a lot of sausages
those white
sausages because it's that season again
it's sausage season it's sausage
fest because during this time we like to
eat the vice
versa with some
sweet
and what call
again my English vocabulary is bugging
out today mustard yes sweet monst the
one where you have to peel or you should
peel off the skin
i
[Music]
s Sweet mustard is so good yeah by just
means white exactly why is the stone
here always question weirdly positioned
objects now we can get the third upgrade
[Music]
where am
I getting
[Music]
there could you just like in breath of
the wild go straight to the castle again
and try to confront the
king and everything like Gan on right
away prob probably not in this game
right like I would think you would have
to regain like all kinds of links things
first and then regain link make link
normal
again this one's more linear
okay I would I would honestly appreciate
that I mean going straight being able to
go straight to the boss in breath of the
wild is fun and cool and you know
but
[Music]
yeah
snck
[Music]
sorry oh why did I hurt myself
I don't think you can even do any
dungeon you want the first your hard
blocks I don't have a problem with that
though I think that's fine if I sent War
to King of
hyro maybe if you gave me some money
then I would consider it
grny grny Conny no don't kill the crab I
guess it's find to kill the crab cuz I
want the crab what a cute crab it's so
cute those are some huge pincers
[Music]
yo let my lawnmower through
please
man there you
go crabs in the chat crabs everywhere
oh it's doing its job on its own not a
good lawnmower
ah what is that kelp bubble
kelp makes it more effective okay
[Music]
cool safe
Point nice we're pretty close oh there's
something down
here a little
village
oh
oh ah jabble Waters this is here oh wait
those are not fish
people where are the fish
people o is that where the fairy will
show up maybe maybe not maybe that's
where the dungeon shows up
[Music]
we need to find a spot where I can make
an entrance into one of the Rifts how
about we try to find the giant Rift I
saw new here and search
[Music]
there of course my sweet
lemonade oh I need a bomb do I have a
bomb something that blows
up or is it enough to roll an armadillo
at it
[Music]
no I guess I don't have anything
yet yeah thought
so I don't have bombs yet a link upgrade
oh yeah right yeah he gets to use bombs
eventually cuz we already saw
it I've never heard of Lord jable jble
acting like this before oh there is Lord
jble jble fish person
why is why is jabu jabu always out of
control wasn't he out of control in
tears of the Kingdom or birath of the
world
too oh hi there welcome to the SE
Village jble is a great spirit who lives
in jable
waters really quite Cal but he's been on
the Rampage lady lately I think it all
started when a rift appeared in his den
yeah as the case where the came for a l
j j rest you'll find it across the
bridge to the east can't miss the
entrance has a specific
design what there was no jabu Jau well
like a well an equivalent though
[Applause]
right
n that might be new to Giant Rift that I
spotted in this
area oh I wonder why he's acting so
weird and he also is nearby a rift M
mysterious so mysterious isn't it oh
look at fish I
what sorry for stepping on your
fish that you're just putting there to
sell or
dry kitty cat a little bit too close to
the
fish here too like have you guys seen my
tweet questioning why there's only cats
not a single dog outside of hyu is that
a metaphor for something
is there a deeper meaning to it I'm
curious I feel like there is a deeper
meaning to
[Music]
it maybe the
dogs
um maybe the dogs are like a metaphor
for you know the Impostors and The
Intruders among
us because my home has
been in you know I'm not saying the dogs
are
evil
[Music]
but why don't we see a single dog
outside of hyru
Castle is my
point they usually link to
loyalty
no
no All Dogs Go to Heaven I would agree
with that
[Music]
I don't hate dogs I like dogs I I
literally I got myself a garden with the
F that in the future I might want a
[Music]
dog you know
it they say I can't leave the vage
because it's dangerous but I want to
play with theora oh the fish people
theora theora some up in the river and
others are out in the sea they all play
music great oh and their teams are
always
squabbling can I get this fish probably
not look at the crab oh wait how do I
get that oh will I learn wait I I
already know how to
dive I'm like will I learn how to dive
just like I learned how to walk in the
sand
[Music]
I for go I for
Gore crab is very friendly crab does not
want to attack crap does not see me as a
snack
ni oh oh that before was a single
Crystal now we got another single
Crystal now we're up to
10 what is that bomb
I'm like a fish in the
sea wow that's
pretty let me
hands that's so
pretty the stone
texture wow okay what
you I was out at the sea when attacked
all of a sudden I barely escaped with my
life oh as I was on the waves minding my
own business when he hit my boat hard
I've been too scared to go back out to
see ever since oh you seem fine still
you still have so many fish to feed
you okay what are they selling surely
they're selling a specific item here for
this area something to swim fast no just
[Music]
potions
cute should I take one of these blue
potions with me just one on for
[Music]
emergencies
bye-bye potion
[Music]
Mansion yeah I could upgrade again I
guess cuz I have the Waypoint here I can
go if I want
to yeah should we upgrade the arrows
right away look at the seagulls they
don't look like seagulls at all because
they're all using the same Bird model
and just recolored but
[Music]
cute H wait energy level two is same
price as and what a is there no price
here because he's blocking me from doing
it
early probably
H well I will do my bow we should do it
in the same order one at a
time let's bake my bow make it
stronger one day we'll turn into a
machine gun the looks Chang too huh I
didn't notice with the sword but I
noticed definitely with this bow of
Might oh VI sword s final form press X
to send an errow flying hold X Char ah
to get the free arrows at once ooh you
can also use dead L to Target and
release arrows in a specific
Direction
what ah ah yeah that is just targeting
yeah locking in oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay okay
okay
[Music]
awesome yeah just like link already did
against us he was above our
level ah all the way over here oh my God
I went so
far wow we already uncovered a good
amount of this
map really hard for me to notice the
changes the bow was easy for me to
notice because the main part of it looks
so
boring before the upgrade
all right then let's uh wait I want to
take the side quest that I saw
here maybe we do that
first your
son my son
Anu hasn't come home in a while the
boy's TR sleeping in the woods to the
north again why did I bother to make him
a meal well if you're heading that way
could you take some grilled fishing oh
okay
nice a delivery Quest
wa oh I I learn
it I have to learn
it theyve been hungry monsters lately in
the wood oh it's like the the piece of
meat I can't eat it but the monsters can
eat
it maybe they eat longer on this
one Uber
fish is that the only side quest
[Music]
all right to the
north wow there's so many pretty flowers
here didn't see many of those in the
first
area right or left guys well right or up
I
mean Zelda the
diver I love this Dave the diver I hope
one day they bring out Dave the diver
too and that's maybe I'll play on
stream yeah the pillar does look good
and they did say North so maybe the boy
somewhere here oh is a more or less dead
ends ah there's the boy yeah this is the
right way to go
first wrong direction
let's fight with something
else I know maybe something I don't
always
[Music]
use oh strong oh well he already had
some damage right no but all one hit
[Music]
cute
what oh do I cook them
no that's not I feel
[Music]
bad good morning should I wake you up
with the the
smell maybe he wouldn't even wake up on
his
own that looks so good it's so
fat doesn't look healthy it must have
been stuffed or
something wake
up
what wa what he reacted to it not like
Mom's are you the wrong boy
are there several Lost Boys no his name
is
Anu what she wants me to bring that
specific one instead of
create nah no
way what an what an annoying Pap
[Music]
how
okay
okay it's the same it's copy paste how
can you tell the
[Music]
part what a spoiled
boy well how do I get up
[Music]
now
man how
do trampolines I guess
[Music]
got to carry it behind me
maybe you did the same you thought wa
what did it go wrong is it possible if I
carry it behind me because I don't know
how else I don't have like a like a
wait where did the fish go can you make
another one thank
you I wonder where the fish went I took
it I'm the one who took
it at least the monsters are gone now if
I would have gone there first with with
the fish then who knows if the fish
would have
survived lift it normally what do you
mean lift it normally can't lift it
normally
how come it didn't fall apart when I
jumped off here but okay I'm going to
carry it behind me
now
okay ah my trampolin are
[Music]
gone with
a oh
but then I can't jump I could toss it
but it's probably going
to fall apart
[Music]
right I don't want to B
it okay see all good all good I just
probably
accidentally crashed it against
something
ah he has such a like adult
voice I have to tell your
[Music]
mom what you want something else or all
right I'll go
back it is a kid I'm pretty
sure just had one of my worst days at
work what the hell what happened who
hurt you I'll hurt
them you that gr face to my son thank
you so
much what that little [\h__\h] decided to
just stay what's wrong with him well he
can just stay there forever then I'm
going to turn his room
into my new wine
seller oh I'm still getting a reward
okay I thought it would continue and she
would like make something even more
tasty for
him well then you can live in the forest
forever honestly that's what she should
say that's what her attitude should be
look how
pretty let's destroy the beautiful
flowers
[Music]
Adora I want to live here I want to live
by the beach oh
[Music]
smovies I really stting it this time I
don't have all need to open sh are you a
customer well I'm great for you drop by
the smothie shop isn't open yet see I
ran out of bubble count because what I
what but I'm not sure what you do it
only grows in the sea and sea doesn't
agree with me I don't suppose you've got
some for
me oh my God bu Buble Buble C oh let's
go thank you oh now I can open my movie
shop oh he actually gave me money
[Music]
can you please teach me recipes
though Mama
Mia Ena it
wait you're really going to make me turn
cute little
seahorses into a
drink ew that's
disgusting that's
disgusting milk and
salt was was it milk and salt yeah
probably
salty
[Music]
milk that turns out bad usual
room
oh okay it's like the same as the other
one but it has the salt on
top huh
oh oh it recovers
energy also a lot of Hearts I feel bad
like using these when I don't have so
many hearts
yet okay so I guess two of
these that's brutal it's probably
disgusting 42 recipes I didn't even see
oh my God
42 that's such a great
number okay at least it looks
adorable a rapid
[Music]
movie uh enables the Drinker to hold the
breath longer on the one E I have to
hold my breath so
far I guess so so do I make the kelp
together or mix with something else
[Music]
yeah when smoothie got the doomies she
has some crazy Zoomies
today she ran around so much like she's
a running
horse faster than any horse out
there wow that looks
nice it's just
water it's just
water a't it
oh well maybe it's more than 42 because
who says that that's the last
one bub you won't be able to get enough
of this bubbly mixture of scrumptous
[Music]
flavors I'll make another one
Fe
[Music]
and I want to make something with the
potato but I don't know when I'll ever
need wall climbing speed anyway
potato
juice potato and
salt o I don't have many potatoes I hope
it would
be I hope it's going to be something
good wait what does the restore some
drinkers energy now I feel like when
there's things with two different
effects it will cancel out the one with
the second uh the second one's effect
which is fine
but potat and butter yeah
but I feel like I don't want to risk it
no I'm going to I'm going to probably
look up some recipes in the
[Music]
future all
right probably not the right direction
but look at this pretty bir
what are you
[Music]
SE a pretty
one
[Music]
a
brutal it looks it kind of reminds me of
the bird from that little indie game
that we played I think
look at this
go I think the was it
the uh a short hike game is that what
I'm thinking of
maybe
so anyway let's go here where the game
wants me to go
you come to visit car Plaza got a
question Plaza allora and jble come to
be together the sea J and the river J
join here to play music for Lord jble
jble that's how they ask him to keep
watching over the waters but lately Lord
jable J is on a rampage and zor Chiefs
are squabbling in the worst way there
all going wrong that giant Rift since
the giant Rift appeared
I
understand ooh can
I even get
there I maybe need a fish to guide me
let's
try do you think a fish will do the
trick where are my
fish I'm
blind
here with let's tribe with the
tangler m
go wait go straight up no I don't think
he goes
upwards yeah that's probably a different
route uh
uh should I go for somewhere here or for
the
left you say to the
east it's not a salmon need salmon wow
okay you think this game would be this
realistic to say that only salmon may go
up that
way
[Music]
H there I could be
but ah shoot
they kind of
strong oh my God there's so many of
them wait you come on land let me shoot
let me just destroy you from here
[Music]
I don't like
these they trigger me these blue guys
are the worst right thank
you try holding them in place of it
which my what ah yeah you mean those
jumpy spiders water spiders right I
could have done that I'm not thinking
with Echo
[Music]
there we go that's the
Strat it's too easy too easy this way
let's put one more here oh W you hold
you can still spawn new ones I didn't
think that would be
possible wow good job go
[Music]
bullying no it's just the smartest way
to handle
them and new safe Point teleportation
unlocked ooh that's very close to the
rift I can smell jabu jabu from here
stinky
[Music]
fish very stinky
fish that's the giant rip that I spotted
earlier let's
[Music]
investigate can I really already I don't
believe
it something will stop us for
sure Dabble [\h__\h] Where Are
You
O I have some statues I could place up
there probably not the right ones do you
have any amiibos no I don't own a single
amiibo I wonder are there any good ones
that would do something
interesting I can make the rift entrance
back there let's go further inside Zelda
if you can
is it going to be a thing
where oh yeah looks like this place got
swallowed up bad by the rift who's
coming oh what the hell are those Zora
they look very different from bre of the
wild are they Zora they're River Zora oh
are they so different from the ocean
Zora classic St
Zora I guess so H they're kind of cute
cute I bet you came here because you
worried about Lord double double huh I
know we are he's been running wild all
over the place since this Rift spread in
his den yeah we got here fast as fast as
we could to see here fast as we could
shouldn't it be as fast as we could I
don't know to see what's going on with
him huh you want to get in his
den oh to open the door the chiefs of
the river Clan and the Sea Clan must
play music here
together got it no okay explain more
then oh we're in the river Clan you know
us being River Dora and all our village
is no for Fe and you should visit us up
River
sometime anything else you want to
know the sea CL here are all seora as
you might have guessed they're Dora who
live in the sea their Village is sou of
here at an island with a huge fish tail
sticking straight
up now we know if you want the Chiefs to
play music here you'll have to go to
each Village and ask
him but we in a
hurry well it's not all that easy
lemon you know what you should know by
now that we don't get into the Rifts
that easily you like my fish
accent I was pondering if they should be
British maybe the seed Zora can be
British the river do just talk I don't
know kind of
cute and like Stompy stomp
stomp where would this path lead
me I hope to a place where I want to go
to are these new fish they
look no same
fish drop a fish in the water see what
happens oh my God that's not that's not
good fish Behavior wait they look
different I think no same never mind
what are you doing oh there's are both
my fish now okay that's why they look
the same what are you doing why are you
so dumb
[Music]
here
attack
yeah I don't see a new Echo drop so I
think that was the
[Music]
same
St
yippe give
[Music]
me one full page what do we get will the
guy come by oh he's coming I don't
remember what what kind of voice I gave
him must have been something energetic
was he screaming was that did I make him
scream yeah hello again step guy here
I've Lov stamp since I was small fry now
I'm H's biggest collector oh you found
five of my STS and filled your stamp
card here's your reward as promised
that's probably not how it was but good
enough fresh milk oh thank you someone
you think you like the stamp
[Music]
yay I worked so hard on this I could do
a back fli yipp everyone's going to see
how fun stamps are that's why I'm
traveling the world spreading the news
about my big stamp friend don't you're
the only one
[Music]
playing then we going to continue here's
the next St
[Music]
C look at those little Doodles it's a
dog dogs are sus are you evil you're sus
in this game let me tell you
that yeah I was saying I've been last
time that he looks like an animal
crossing
[Music]
villager bye-bye stamp
guy keep your chin
up don't be so
sad I love your stamp R it's great
that's a new fish do H I was going to
say looks like he has a bomb in his
mouth do not disturb the
bombfish well what if I
do my my fish is so dumb oh there we go
it's going to blow up it's going to blow
up what do
you okay when he blows up that that
means he's going to die too all
right that is a unfortunate way of
living yay bumps but only in the water I
would assume I can't spawn in here can I
I can oh and he's like immediately on ah
explosion timer all
right o
okay should I just swim over there and
see what's
there
oh but the boulders make me think that
they want me to blow them up oh they
don't blow up I blew up the
ah I blew up the um Shield the sign in
instead Shield because in German sign is
Shield
so I say
that
[Music]
unfortunately why could you not have
blown up a little bit
later come at me
bro no
no whatever
[Music]
yeah normal Shield is also
Shield o
[Music]
air how do I activate it guys
it just
dies pass a touch spin into it
oh ah that's a good idea thank
you cuz touching the wall is difficult
like it's you can't really spawn it that
close to the
wall oh they keys they keys
[Music]
kiss
again sorry got a little bit too
excited but that looks
funny n you're too far over there
[Music]
H yeah I forgot they told us about like
being able to spawn things further away
now oh wait my heart oh my God I'm out
of breath I didn't
realize you B yeah B can I sleep on the
water oh God no not with so little help
wait wait wait wait wait uh uh
maybe it's time for
Smoothie was there air in here in this
room
uh uh dive time swim speed yeah let's
take one of these why don't we why don't
we use them we have them for a reason
hello thanks for the
[Music]
raid thank you ow no no no no no no no
no it's like they're attracted to each
other wasn't too bad all
right thanks for the raid
yipp I want to sleep in the bed to heal
up they kiss bomb fish
kissing you love to see it nice ears oh
thank you
elf
ears I always had them I was just hiding
them behind my
hair it is
true oh CH
too wait
uh how do we send the bomb
up I guess I could build oh a trampoline
for the bomb
or I could just build you know a higher
platform for it it was a collab ah start
you oh yeah yeah yeah I saw that on the
schedule stard you
[Music]
Valley
what no no wait no
[Music]
um well okay uh certainly this is
not the most popular way of doing it I
would assume but I'm going to try with a
trampoline oh I don't take damage okay I
right because of the amount ah it
replaces it okay if I don't take damage
then
wait can
I toss wait I can't toss it
upwards why not can only toss it
sideways yeah fish takes for a cute
outfit thank you I'm
Zelda can you burn the wood yeah but why
would we have to burn it if all that
this hole is about is this um bomb fish
that's two let's put it
on a
table and
then the
fire still not
reaching put it on a box if I
[Music]
can yep
maybe
ah if I'm up
here there's no way what is the right
way to do this and it doesn't
work what
[Music]
Break It come on oh I broke it what why
no no I just lost grip of
[Music]
it I know I have a fire monster but if
this doesn't work
[Music]
to and I can't jump when I have it and I
can't toss it
up what the hell bind The bombfish
Climb
ah it's
[Music]
already I
see another golden
egg get so many
eggs ruining the economy of all these
golden
eggs are you for real that was the way
to do it I mean it makes so much sense
now
but okay I admit the feast that one was
too much for me
I tried a lot of different things
though and I knew you had to do it with
the
bombfish yeah but you just like tend to
forget so many
things are these the oh that's still the
river Zora H okay we can talk to the
river Zora first egg egg
indeed oh they have cute Huts in the
water Welcome To The River Door Village
we're friendly hello and good times
Flo at least not normally Lord jable
DA's gone berser now we're all just
scared they have a door Zora who greets
people how nice what a good job you
have you use the
torch I guess you also just controlled
it like while going up what
do some crazy kind of Crocs from a
crocodile because it looks like
crocodile feet get
it Sora has flippers you can swim faster
350 Mama Mia all these items cost so
much you kidding
me okay I'll I'll sell you some
[Music]
smoothies I don't necessarily need this
one that one's quite expensive
[Music]
W I'll give
you I'll give you a bubble
Smo let's go actually I could have sold
should have sold the swim speed smovie
that I
had cuz this is giving me swim
[Music]
speed egg
why didn't I sell this
one oh well then oh yeah I should change
my worn item my accessory into them cuz
there's no stand
here that loaded little bit too long for
my
taste wow I must look so fashionable of
these
[Music]
flippers okay you can stop with the eggs
now I can go underneath what
see I found where you store all your
money you should probably put it into a
bank a sand Bank
perhaps double Waters have been full of
trouble lately I like to eat my favorite
Foods at times like this got to keep my
spirits
up what are your favorite foods what is
this what is this
fish looks tasty teach me how do you
cook
it Banger up Banger
oh we still don't know how to swim up
that
sucks can they teach me please teach me
your
ways I really like this design of this
Village wow isn't it super
cute I want to play music too once that
says I have to wait until Emma gr up
though at the end of this C he said that
playing music is secret Duty little
minow like me can only
[Music]
watch one day one day you'll perform a
freaking buan if you want
[Music]
to the idle dream yeah oh froggy waa
would love to be here
yeah froggy waa would feel right at
[Music]
home is this worth going there at all
where am
I oh
here I'm wondering if there's something
there but I'll probably get there at
some point when the rift is
gone
here exploring is this where fogi waa
grew
up
no I don't think this is it
ah I
fell I don't see any other frog here so
would be
[Music]
weird you really love clowns
here seashell she sells
seashells seashells
[Music]
SE oh seash she sells seashells by the
seashore is that the full
[Music]
sentence yeah oh it gets easier by the
end of
it any side quests here haven't seen
[Music]
any oh that's a
look like that sign I've seen in places
in other games or so
before an
interesting Hut looks like from maybe
from the
chief she sells seashells on the
seashore she sells seashells on the
seashore I'm
sure for if she sells seashells on the
seashore then I'm sure she sell Seashore
shells oh she sell seashells on the
seashore she's oh [\h__\h] she sells
seashells on the seashore the shells she
sells are
seashells she sells seashells on the
seashore the
shells she sells seashells on the
seashore the shells she s yeah that
would have been right she sells seashell
she sells seashells on the seashore the
shells she sells are seashells I'm sure
for if she sells seashells on the
seashore then I'm sure she sells seash
shells yay
[Music]
what a shelf
woman better than me and Ena selling so
many seashells by the seashore because
on the seashore you could get your own
seashells why are you selling seashells
by the seashore you should sell them
elsewhere where other people potential
customers could not have easy access to
them that's actually a weird business
model that this this lady has
[Music]
can
you well I've already done it I think
when we were
watching um the
[Music]
anime I don't remember now
she's a wholesaler she sells seashells
and bulk yeah but why on the
seashore makes no
sense all right people I scared BS the
huge Rift opening your double double on
the
Rampage not I have a plan when have I
the great Dr ever let you
down first I'll get Lord jable nice and
relaxed
again good thinking bsh but how will you
do that with music of course River music
that'll stop his Rampage which is that
good no challenge Tak will finally
B finally B to bow down to my Superior
skills hold on bus why are you still
squabbling with the SE Jo Chief your CH
usually makeup right away it's really
dragging on this
time squabbling this is a big deal she
mocked my music I'll never make up with
her oh she oh I'm feeling eventually
they'll maybe make up and make
out happy ending if you know what I mean
fish
fish o
o I'm not going to just sit around I've
got real problems to deal with
in
okay who are you that's matter it's got
to
wait
[Music]
okay
okay did you need our CH or something
sorry D is busy and the boss has a lot
going on right now doesn't help that
he's having his worst sble ever with the
SE Chief their fights are usually small
then just fizzle out this time it's
blown up completely they used to get
along so well yeah this fight's really
gotten
bad you know I want to hold up we've got
to get to crossville's Plaza hi okay I'm
coming sorry the bus G I see
you see
[Music]
you squabble what a strange word I don't
understand what it means but I do know
that will'll never reach the rift until
the two chiefs hear out our
request seems like it indeed oh I can
sit on everybody's Thrones in their
absence any secret money stash down here
no should have sold more seashells by
the
[Music]
seashore don't care thanks for the
membership
Simo in
in
in in
[Music]
wait where how where where where did
they go how did they
go
huh where do I
go down from like the seaside
village maybe cuz that's the ocean I
guess is it probably
[Music]
y y
y almost 5 hours
whoa doesn't feel that long man we can
blow this up now oo I'm excited at the
prospect of that
yeah I don't even remember have there
been any other things to blow up so far
that we just didn't have anything for I
actually don't think so I don't remember
anything nothing comes to mind
[Music]
Zelda goes by fast yeah sadly I don't
want to like rush through
it
but who knows how long it really is
but I hope it's not going to be too
short we already the two full dungeons
right was that a full
dungeon that we did did we do two
dungeons or three uh uh one no minimum
two we did two for
sure two the first one in the first
stream and one in this stream right
those were like legit legitimate
dungeons I
assume you're back
yippe thank
you oh a new pony is that a water
Pony does it create water so far it
hasn't created water
proba about this
one did I do
anything
H more the
[Music]
classic like we're playing Zelda and
Risa or like any ATO game at the same
time it's like Zelda at the
Zelda that's what this is ky what was
Kyla
dreaming
welcome thank you for the raid wo that's
a big one they can get this
[Music]
big it's
bouncing hello thank you welcome welcome
welcome we're playing the new daa game
which is so good it's so fun
how do I get rid of these
big watery jiggly
punies thank you have you guys been
playing the new Dela game it's so good
oh let's send in the
bombfish go
in
wa go in no it's already dead I need to
burp it in the
water oh my God what are you doing
you got to explode when they're tall
yeah yeah yeah okay I'll just I'll just
do it like
this blow him up bum
fish thank you thank you welcome Raiders
thank
you currently we are in the land of the
fish
people yeah and there's two different
kinds this time in breath of the wild
was it specified which Zora type they
were oh dear oh am I supposed
to ah maybe you can immediately counter
yeah easy
[Music]
counter let's see what they're trying to
do here am I am I supposed to turn these
off
actually Zelda is always it is are you
going to play the new game
K have you played any Dela game on your
stream so
far is it your kind of
game is this new yes it released uh two
days
ago and it's really interesting it's you
know giving you this opportunity to play
Zelda for the first time instead of
Link and Zelda has magic so she can like
learn how to create object she objects
that she has met
before like this bomb
fish which blew up at the wrong space
no stay
there yeah okay nothing yeah you should
check it out it's so cute it's
new and having being able to play Zelda
is just like the best sales strategy
ever
is the left room the one that I should
be in
[Music]
first what wait that's where I came from
ah
[Music]
no
oh all right I think
I'll lay down for a moment cozy
bed wherever I
want the burning chicken emote is just
too
perfect oh H that's what we
get I don't know what I expected but I
don't think it was
that let's go well a piece of a heart
container at least
Y how many I have which can I see here
or I need two more for another
heart heart heart heart heart heart
heart where are we where are we on the
map oh there's a there's a ship
here interesting Treasures to be
found it's a [\h__\h]
shark scary me should I do you think I
can kill him maybe how many piranas can
I
summon the the bomb ones probably will
will work
right where did he
go where'd he
go I'd prefer to know where he is oh
there he's circling the ship
no he's not coming
back hi here look look here oh
no
yum oh come on that took you a
while at least it has a a good amount of
Health to be able to tank a couple of
those shark hits
wow oh we already got him
yo chompin Echo
Chompers wait how much four oh okay same
same same and the monster
Stone I
[Music]
wonder he's just chilling kind of cute
wait let me control
you okay he's not really
fast
nah I need something to move really fast
in the water that would be
[Music]
nice over here is where I need to go but
okay we're
exploring my Shark seems to be only in
that
region if you don't go there you might
miss out on the shark
[Music]
seagulls do I look like food to you I
don't think you can eat me I'm a little
bit too beig for
you oh dear what are you going to create
in the
ocean catch a
Lun I already learned the
seagull oh here we go the
[Music]
seoras our seedor
Village is re really close swim south of
here a little more and you're sure to
see
it I don't
know it doesn't really sound fitting
does
it what I thought I would get
help whoo
[Music]
did that sound ausy no
Irish Irish I'm
[Music]
Irish you guys look
funny dad looks more like the Zoras from
breath of the wild t the Kingdom so I'm
guessing they were seed
Zoras they didn't look like River
Zoras oh that son of mine he's always
going into this cave to pretend he's an
adventurer but it's not safe out there
with little jabu jabu running wild what
your mother to do how how that sound
what was that
like a lake Dora not seora I think
they're SE
are
squish that's
fine hi I want to T hunt but don't tell
my mom I'm
here I'll tell her but I want to see
what's here is there something
there ah
die
[Music]
oh what is this a
lamp a treasure oh it's going dark
here Zelda is such a good diver oh this
is where I might need a the the light up
thingy oh there's light up fish wow you
try to fight my tiger shark how about
that oh wait I got I'm Lear
it new fish obtained I if I if I lead
that one in front with me then he can be
my light on the water and I don't have
to drink the light
portion and he can fight for me I guess
let's
go yeah let's get closer
[Music]
together this is fish abuse I
think he's very confused he looks very
stupid he he doesn't understand what's
going on
all right sorry I had to take you out
the
water is that it seems like
it poor fish just wants to go home home
is wherever I create you at so deal with
it where are we now oh oh pretty close
jellyfish oh are they elect string oh
they are oh be careful
ah sorry
yeah okay um yeah
MH sorry about that timing Bey oh be
Bey there you go are you okay
buddy that was quite the shock
huh okay your son is in
there mhm mhm
oh I guess it's not a quest so it's like
[Music]
whatever are we going
there I wonder if you have to dive into
like some
underwater place because where else
would they really
be uh I want to get rid of
[Music]
that yeah yeah one of my favorite anime
is rail
[Music]
gun beautiful this
this this kind of makes me think of
Super Mario
Sunshine the
[Music]
water here and the corals I don't
know the graphics are very different but
I don't know
the
saturation makes me think of Super Mario
Sunshine I just love Super Mario
Sunshine yeah Serena Beach Serena that
[\h__\h] hi handmaid tail be like Serena
that
[\h__\h] hen I'm impressed you were able to
swim all the way out here do you have
business in our village if so and you'll
find the entrance down there why does he
sound like a cowboy low key
I don't know anymore
guys going back to finish it I don't
know how
cute it's like an underwater cave huh I
thought it would be like way bigger but
I guess you know we got to stay small in
this
world the music
[Music]
that's so refreshing and
pretty hi old there everywhere love
music so and so
D what all old allora everywhere love
music and so does the great spirit Lord
ja ja that's why we and the river Clan
get together to offer our music to Lord
J J but right now he's behaving so
wildly that it' be difficult to stage
performance for
him what are these
accents what are
those cute look at those instruments ah
making something out of the
pincers
cute that's
cute that's cute the trumpet is
cute is that a coral or something I
don't know how robust that really would
be the accent is nothing but the Cadence
Cadence it's pretty awesome you mean
like the intonation you got to use more
simple words with
me a
tu tu Lake and ocean
Z wait can you imagine there's like
people who play instruments on YouTube
right so like some people play the piano
upload piano videos but what if there's
surely a tu a tuba player who can call
himself a tuba
[Music]
tuba tuba
tuba thank you for laughing thank you
thank you oh Uber Hopper that must have
really hit your funny
bone you guys are
laughing hey I did it what was that my
best joke today I don't even feel like
it was that
funny pretty good let's
go I am happy wa she's
cute she's pretty I didn't think I would
fall for a fish lady but oh my
god
um let's speak English this is a grave
situation first that Rift now Lord jabu
jabu is going
wild Lord jabu jabu is the spirit of
Alara but it falls to us to call him
this crisis is without equal and now
it's time that I Kara of the SE is all
it I forgot how to do my English
accent J what is inspiring words please
tell me how you plan to do it huh L Chop
Chop loves her s music don't they sound
sou
American like
taxis that's not s that's Mid West right
I how you're right I know Jaa Jaa loves
our same
music so I need oh get him to listen to
ason and then drag the tuneless
Buon will have to up my
performance I take it that you haven't
resolved your L es quel there we go well
your L
quel you is is uto Pandora still here
help me
out with the auto Chief yet H and why
would I this quel is one for the ages
I'll never speak to him again he
insulted my music I will not tolerate
his presence
it's like he leaves to provoke me Mama M
oh we'd be fine if he agreed that I was
more
talented oh she's got to meet and greet
I see never mind all that we have to
leave immediately
ran oh let's
go so I didn't have to come here at all
I just had to Bear witness to them
leaving all
right
bye-bye she's so spiteful the yeah I
sound like a s b I'm not really sure
what that means but I feel like I've
heard of it
before
before I'm sorry to say that I'm sorry
to say that until she's resolved our
problem she won't have time to help if a
great crisis wasn't bad enough a chieve
is sing with the RoR Chief they often
have the little C but always make up
quickly not this time what the say a
squabble a day came so friendship and
play A sble A Day brings two
fish together at Bay or a squabble a
day lets you play in the
hay there we go oh oh some spicy lines
day makes you
gay I don't think that's
true they went off to the crow Plaza too
why do I speak like a St it's like you
infected me with
something then I guess it's time we join
the two chiefs there as
well lemon what happened to you lemon
John Lemon look at this fro it looks
like it's made out of
Play-Doh but it's cute it's just a star
kind of playful kind of cute kind of
childish but very
[Music]
mindful yippe
yippee this is like a water park look at
that it's the doodle suck it's a water
Doodles
suck looks funny
[Music]
yeah the whole game no no I don't no the
grass looks too good to be
Play-Doh and the sand texture no they
did a good
job it's all very cute and
shiny so now we go
where ah
why is it making chicken
sounds I recognize a chicken when I hear
one did I activate this
before I didn't what is wrong with
me what is wrong with me like literally
oh my
god oh look at them they're here
you shouldn't have come here I take care
of myself get lost my F's precisely all
of
you now I
Tak
am I would say a very good third wheel I
am the best third wheel there is in the
bicycle
shops so I shall now help you to
to love each other as you were destined
to get slimy
together in between the Kelps on the
water and the coral
reefs K you can stop your plan H will
you have to see will'll bring home to
Lord T tble our music and quiet is Right
ridiculous we'll do it not
you at it
again it was only a matter of time
before these exploded but not here it
now the way you play you just enrange
him more with your C honking so we'll
play insult always it's insult says more
about your music than mine but sure
let's do this your playing is weak it's
puny it won't have any
effect what now you have done it there
are some things you can't take back you
know I am a really good wing woman yeah
I don't know if me being a wing wing
woman will be good for fish though
usually I I guess it works better on
birds or so but I'll try with these fish
they have like underwater Wings it
should work it's time we s this one last
performance to see who's playing Super
wait is she saying that yeah so she said
that no problem when on the count of
threee we both play the best player wins
oh they will play together all right ooh
steamy steamy hot iy
concert my chief with all due respect
you can't hope to put on a great
performance this
way it's no use there's no stopping them
when they get like
this oh what is
that wow elegant demure mindful
wow oh never mind the first tones
sounded
nice you're not like
[Music]
collaborating uh sound like like
[\h__\h] they didn't play in time with each
other not at
all you have angered the underwater Gods
greatly oh what the what are you you
just a
fish is jabu chabu just like a
completely different race like this is
not a Dora is just a fish a big mutated
fish is is a different type of
Dora he's a fish God oh he was a god
oh he's a
whale he's there god wow
wow he looks funny he needs some
chapstick his lips look dry how can your
lips look so dry when you're always on
the water I don't understand you came
when you heard my performance didn't you
how did you like it
ah there's no question that my planing
was what brought him
here shut
up uh oh
[\h__\h] get sucked
yeah oh no not the small
ones oh
uh-oh he's happy now huh is she is that
enough or you want
more he definitely is on the Rampage
uh-oh I shall offer myself as a
tribute there's no time to delay I'll go
Pur to Flo ja Jau and rescue wait let me
latch on to you if you can go
Upstream no fa no head starts
flash our friends are danger forget this
talk of heads
me first he's so stupid and
cute hey you
cheater Dr looks like a strawberry from
behind oh I got to I got to keep that in
mind next time I see him this is getting
out of control and we still haven't been
able to ask them what we need they've
got to open that door in the den for us
but that will never happen at this rate
what a
[Music]
Miss bre do you think he's heading
toward your
village I bet you're right no I've got a
bad feeling about this all right how do
I get up
there how do I get there actually maybe
we should end it
here
Spin 5 and 1 half hours I need to cook
still cook the
fish I was there I have a war point
oh
okay I want to check it
out on this Cliffhanger there's a lot of
cliffs here in this zor land I have no
choice but to end it on a cliffhanger do
I
now splash
[Music]
oh will they stand on those platforms or
what are they
there we he not here heard him behind
the
door not like I can walk in there must
have gotten something wrong I thought
they would be in
here what they're in the
village the V Village the seora a
village or the normal people
Village North so
probably here
why they both go there did jable jable
go
there I suppose that would make
[Music]
sense I'm coming wait for
Wawa where exactly is
[Music]
it oh there Shake no
don't their home got
destroyed no I was about to stop my
swimm
practice I always tell everyone that the
Wonder is scary see I was right I'll
never swim
again I heard an outsound and then saw
that my neighbor was in real trouble or
jble jble headed east of here is
everyone else all right no mixing the
two
accents the K is traumatized for alive
it will never swim
again wait where how am I supposed to
get
there what's the preferred
path they said East so I'm trying to go
this way
but can't there wait it felt like I was
up there for a moment
[Music]
no ah doio
doio how to get up there wasn't was I up
here
before there's an opening between two
houses on the left oh the hole behind
the broken house okay that makes a lot
of
[Music]
sense what was there before just a
normal
wall
oh
W oh how
fun there we are wow so pretty
[Music]
Mya it's all right I'm here to help
we'll find your father
[Music]
and something something awful happened
here the hello
again CH I follow Look chief D and I
follow behind Lord ja ja as he Rampage
through here
your jble jble wasn't himself he struck
my poor
Papa fell into the
r that's when Chief dad and I got here
only to see the r suddenly
grow TR save the J from being cled but
was then swallowed up
itself can't say where little ja jab was
gone but D oh it's all too
terrible 20 memberships he y
come
come thank
you now is the question do I want to go
in there now or should we go in next
stream I feel like maybe
next stream would be
better I wonder how long this
[Music]
is I'm drinking a capri
St P grenade and
[Music]
Cherry
smoy hi hi what yeah is that
so yeah good morning did you have some
Nice
Dreams hey don't scratch yourself so
[Music]
much
s yeah yeah yum
yum I shall save here as smoothie also
seems to think that I should stop
here yeah yes she heard say I should
finish like what the hell she's such a
such a crazy cat like she has an
internal timer for when my stream
ends oh look at that little broken tree
no but uh I really should still read
some super chats
regardless
of anything um I just Saed right I did
not just imagine that
[Music]
let save
again yeah I think we made a lot of
progress again that's
good getting pretty far in the game the
third dungeon I guess is upcoming am I
really already ready is this the third
dungeon that I'm about to
enter
h next week perhaps two telda streams
again very likely
should be
wow yeah good bun good chunk of the map
also already uncovered I got some cute
items for my shoes for my
feet two two different feet
Footwear double RPG we're so
back I don't think we would finish it
next week that would be too fast I would
[Music]
say but we should also schedule mon t
for next
[Music]
week so ooh hey a lot of people stayed
from Kyla's
raid thank you sorry that I'm ending it
but you can stay a little while longer
while I'm reading super chats I did
finally finish those uh what was it the
concert super chats
all right I think I finished
those let's move
[Music]
to where should we
go maybe the pond should we go to the
pond because where we just ended in a
water
region does that make
sense
oh is
that monitor and out okay
you have to go that's okay thank you for
watching oh never mind I guess that was
the ra CC
raid that I see in
the yeah yeah yeah thank
you w banish into the swamp it's not a
banishment I choose to be here I like it
here it reminds me of frog bird you know
froggy waa likes frog bird but I also
quite like frog bird frog bird was a
nice
fellow to be
around a good fellow very green very
nice little bit stinky a little bit
slimy But A Good Man gentleman yeah
definitely way more of a gentleman that
than froggy waa is a gentle woman she's
not a gentle woman she's not demure
she's not mindful she's
crazy what's I would say she doesn't
even deserve someone like frog bird but
somehow they like each other it is a
mystery to me H well they can do
whatever they want with their slimy
greenness who knows maybe this whole
Pond is full of frog eggs
already I better stay on this Lily
Pad I don't want to know what kind of
stuff is in this pond
ah Kyla's stream was a membership stream
ah wow that's sweet of her to raid me
with a M
stream thinking of
[Music]
me okay so what did somebody say where I
am right
now JD
J
[Music]
J Save the Last BL best dance I like how
um do you think I was did I spread it
did I spread
the the
oopsie cuz a lot of people a lot of
girls ended up like later on I did and
but I think people thought I
accidentally was saying it but I always
totally um uh purposefully fumbled over
it I always pretended to accidentally
say it there was always on purpose but I
think they thought I did it
accidentally save the lasbians uh the
liest of course I I I meant the
lestans
oopsie yeah crony even used it in her
title all right let's uh wait this is
quite fun and all but we should listen
to the game music while we have
[Music]
it it's quite
quiet
[Music]
oh it's louder when I'm out of the menu
but it's like wait never mind I can just
make it louder here
[Music]
that's
nice how about this kind of
[Music]
volume
nice save that there we are
okay so the first enigmatic recollection
stream I did read cuz this seems to be
the second one
[Music]
okay remember to lower the TV volume
later so you don't jump scw yourself
well it's not TV volume
but it's just the game capture card
volume okay here this stream day two I
tried my best to use all of the
available
art the in these
thumbnails this one looks so cool made
by
sve who made my warrior alter kiata
outfit I didn't even know that swaf was
commissioned to do any of the art for
this project but I'm glad I would I
would say I put sve on the raadar of the
company I'm pretty sure about
that I'm glad to see sv's art
again
yeah very noise
all right let's see what we got Jacob 47
D Jim Tracy
D vas D
J thank you for the rain almost rainbow
yeah it's pretty much a rainbow if I
could wish for anything for my birthday
tomorrow it would be for your happiness
Tel a time where your aches melt away
your fears don't invade your dreams they
do a lot your stress evaporates and you
can smile of satisfaction every single
day before years you've continued to
transform my life in the best of ways I
truly feel blessed for being your fan
and not just because you're cute as a
button sing like an angel cute as a
button cute as a button button sorry
that sounds Midwestern to me sing like
an angel dance like no one else or make
me laugh but because there's no one else
who makes me smile like you
do
but you have a big great big heart T you
thank you for being patient with me over
you years H and welcoming me here where
I can be happy well I can be happy darn
toon
Ro so thank you for na a great tra
around the sand but then again I've been
revolving around the brightest star for
a while huh stay shining waa oh and
thanks for the early release for the
usual room did I do
[Music]
that oh thank you oh yeah together with
that it's 100 thank you for the rainbow
D and happy birthday sorry I am so late
I am so incredibly late but that's so
sweet of you that you want for your
birthday which you want me to be happy
well I want I want
to what's the word badom flip B boing
flip I want to boing flip that back to
you it's your
birthday it should you know
it should make you
happy I want you to feel all of those
things are you here right now I don't
see
you never heard that before it's from
scrabs yeah Bo
flip if you've never heard of that then
you're so UN based
man s will not here who is at work H
working hard at
kpace well I hope you catch this in the
archive later on thank you so much happy
birthday to you Ro to D do happy
birthday dear job BR happy birthday to
you let's
go congratulation thanks for the big
generous rainbow M and the sweet words
very
nice why is it doing that okay Studio R
thanks for the
[Music]
pink Mund D oh people are writing about
House of the Dragon in the these Super
Chat that's how long ago this is I
mean September it's still within this
month okay beginning of this month how
not that long ago House Of The House of
the Dragon was running was that the last
episode or
so even rings of power is finished soon
I don't even know at what episode I am
but I feel like I'm pretty far and I
wonder when it's
ending like
I'm where am I I'm at the part ah right
when the the queen of numor basically
gets
reinstated that's some crazy tradition
they had
there to make that
happen crazy [\h__\h]
[Music]
happening haven't seen that one oh I'm
I'm further than
you episode six Maybe M yeah I guess
probably but next episode 7 maybe I
don't know here at episode
4 how many will there
be I'm waiting for it all to be out to
Bing you're going to watch it let's
go episode seven is very
long
[Music]
eight eight episodes okay yeah ending
soon but okay one is very long what do
you mean long they're already long by
default so 1 hour normally so this time
2 hours or
what I'm waiting for mon watch along to
be done so I can B watch rings of e
those two things are
separate you stream too much for me to
watch it I need a break day to start
okay then I'll take the day off the next
days have enough time for you to watch
it eh I shall stop streaming
then you see another ad game is coming
out next year
what what is it a phone game or
something why would they release two for
like the main
[Music]
consoles which
one it's kind of edgy
edgy AIA what's it
called what's it called what's it called
is e what we already know about that one
no from a long time now single player
spinoff from the
gcha no not the yumia one that's the
other one that we already know for a
while now but you guys are talking about
a new new one reer
reana no that's res Lana with a typo
well this one has been known for a long
time
too wait so do we all are you talk is
there no new one
the red Alchemist and the white
Guardian the red so it's a spin-off of
the phone
game ah one day ago reveal the Tokyo
game show wa it looks different the the
the art style looks different from the
phone
game 57 seconds
teaser wait I quickly got to watch it
I'll post the link for you guys
I have been seeing a lot of
like footage from like friends being at
Tokyo game
show yeah everything has been looking so
cool I like Tokyo game
show okay we're going to watch this in
three two one
go it's just a minute don't worry guys
cat ears where is it a
ribbon
that
whoa
whoa she's got cat ears has she always
had cat
ears adier isana the red Alchemist and
the white
Guardian
cute she's cute in that
art it's a new character
oh I don't understand why they would
wait 2025 well maybe yumia is at the
beginning of the year and this one is at
the end of the year
maybe it's kind of weird to release two
in one
year they added a d lead why why would
you do
that well there's always some guys in
there what's a good game to start with h
ask motion did I miss the add trailer
where the hell were you you had one
job
[Music]
Mia I would be happy with two tailes
games yeah sure but it's like kind of
concerning like oh you're pushing out
two games are you really putting all the
resources you could into one game or are
you kind of splitting them and then
they'll be like hop ass or so you know
it's a bit
concerning but they both look like
judging from the trailers they look like
the usual aier games doesn't really look
like but I guess you can't really know
until you play them but you
know yeah they're releasing so many
aelier
games now they need to promote two adier
games releases at the same
time good luck with that
H that might be the real challenge like
one of them is going to fall under the
radar and it's definitely
resana especially cuz like why does it
have this
name I feel like that's not a good name
for you uh for an AER game it's like
weird it's not
memorable it should be shorter and like
easier
like just sounds weird
[Music]
yeah you can't spell it you guys have
been putting uh having typos when you
were writing it res Resler what res
resan Les
resana what
Rana if they they could just change the
name now for this for this like spin-off
they didn't have to keep the same name
[Music]
well like aier Risa just catches you way
more than aier
[Music]
resana um what was I take Monkey D Cru D
AC D Satan's film d d welcome back
home oh no you got sick oh no what the
hell
but
Jones m l m thank you for the pinky I'm
loving this episode of The Chronicles of
lesbians the outcast the S and the
Pand yeah I I think I read this Super
Chat when you first sent it I was like H
who's the outcast and who's the
[Music]
Sim I still don't
know naan coton face of the pinky and
this is the story of an of abandoned
Phoenix who knew to trust her instincts
for such beloved hidden treasure but she
can find the most beloved and hidden
treasure but can she find the most
beloved and hidden treasure of them all
the
lesbians you're a good story writer
Nathan good one I'm curious tell me more
about this abandoned
Phoenix Sky d resine d for the pinky
great job Tel those jrpg senses were
right loving the adventures of Wawa and
her cat and fellow flame sword holder
fellow flame sword holder
herb does her sword go up in Flames too
or is it just her heart
[Music]
H come on
her heart going up in Flames poetic true
right but she has that flame thingy in
the middle of her chest so that's not
where actually her heart would
be weird
spot what's what's
[Music]
there she has
heartburn uh Sky nction oh wait no
thank you and hu thanks for the CH
ticket pay oh was I singing at the end
of that
stream why thank
you check 47 the
gamer P
action oh was it because I was playing
the reflect and the Cali no not was it
reflect already on that day I was
playing the CDs
that's what they
mean we were singing in the
tavern yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay those super chats are phito
Basta
finito did I read Return of the Phoenix
grinding heart waa POV yet probably not
like uh Day
free probably didn't read
[Music]
it these are a bit more than the other
one
so get ready D thanks for the red chat
thanks for working ah yeah this is after
I was gone for two days thanks for
working so hard on the big 3D recording
also Shameless plug for your back to
school voice pack I loved it KY if you
like me and you're taable telling wa how
much you love her you need this voice
back yeah it's got tips and wa's cute
voice thank you dog Hood yeah I put some
of the things that are out for purchase
right now in my loading screens recently
to remind anybody who's lost track I've
also been losing track so it's a good
reminder you liked it it was
[Music]
cute thank
you I'm I was just happy to be on the
art that that was so cute we look so
cute meow
even though I'm like one of the adults
on that picture the art style still
makes me look so
young
right anyway thank you so much for the
support and listening to The Voice
packs very much appreciate
it next is Honolulu with a red Super
Chat as well thank you in Korean uh H
says yeah is awesome awesome awesome
awesome so cute so adorable Charming so
sexy and awesome and awesome
[Music]
W well I feel like there's a bigger
variation of words in the Korean version
somehow in the English version they're
just repeating awesome awesome awesome
[Music]
why do I get so much praise
ja7 thank you don't worry at this point
I don't remember it oh wait I think now
I remember roughly something was there
but it's
okay Tanaka D you boy Steven Adams D py
thanks for the red chat y Yay good day K
I hope you've been well yesterday was my
birthday oo I'm so late I may be late in
super chatting but it's still by
birthday somewhere right you don't need
to be worried about your lateness look
at how late I am I just want to say how
much I appreciate you and kfp for making
my life a vital Place filled with
kindness and
positivity if it's not the one TR can
you please sing happy birthday for me of
course thank you for all your hard work
and for always doing your best while
best oi I know there's a back look so
don't worry if you didn't read this on
my birthday reading it at all as
plenty how did you know how did you
know well
Psy happy birthday to you happy birthday
in your shoe happy birthday in your
pants to happy birthday to
you thank you so much you've been so
devoted and dedicated in kfp traveling
over continents to see me in events
thank you so much it's always always a
pleasure and an
honor
yeah the world traveler yeah getting
around the World Around the World Around
the World Around
the I hope one day I can return the
favor and come to Australia
no more come to Brazil come to Australia
is what I want to
[Music]
hear yeah I really want to I want to go
St
l i really man if I were to be invited
to an Australian event I would go snel
the [\h__\h] out of your Coral reaps
guys I would be all over that
a barri a reef is that in Sydney
though is it by
Sydney I want to
go no oh
[Music]
man you too asking me about my diving
lessons yeah no time next time I go to
the moldes Maybe
[Music]
I got something to do then although I
wonder like diving license I feel like
maybe I would have to go during um the
on season cuz if it's like super super
[\h__\h] stormy like it often is during
the off season then I feel like they
would like
cancel the appointments every day
because of storms
oh sorry today I guess we can't do the
diving lesson again because it's stormy
oops
oops Yeah
H definitely would want to go in the on
season
then what was the collab that you were
talking about adding well I feel like um
you know we were just hoping for it if
the time allows but I think the time
doesn't allow so it's m M yeah probably
not going to happen good that I didn't
say who or
what there still a small chance
[Music]
but got to be
mukashi do you know what stonefish are
I've heard of them
yeah those are dangerous
right are they out there in Australia
H but probably not in like when you go
snorkeling in the coral Reeves like only
if you dive low low low
low well don't worry
I'm you know if I learn how to
dive I'll I'll have an instructor and
and if I ever dive elsewhere there'll
probably also be like a
guide I don't think I can like dive
alone probably
[Music]
years afterwards what the
hell stone fish are you guys all say
stone fish don't step on them do they
act like stones on the
ground I think a general good rule for
diving is don't step on
[Music]
anything you're floating in the water
why would you step on anything anyway
[Music]
M yeah I can imagine I'll be fine I'll
be
fine there's a lot of dangerous [\h__\h]
down there don't worry if anything
probably the first thing that would
happen is that a shark would eat me no
okay I guess that's more unlikely maybe
uh Jellyfish would kill me probably
[Music]
wow I
know shark are chill well take the
moment I see one I'd probably be so
scared they would smell my fear and then
they'll be like M
chicken wait no please I'm not that kind
of chicken I'm only a chicken in in the
terms of being scared but I don't taste
like chicken I think think I mean I
can't maybe I do
[Music]
but see chicken see chicken chicken you
see
chicken getting a cramp and drown is
probably more likely yeah I could see
that happen too to
me no but I I would be fine I will learn
I will I just okay first step learning
it okay and then it won't be so
dramatic how many times will I even get
the chance to do it h not many probably
and I will never probably never dive
alone it's fine I just want to pretend
I'm Dave the diver for a little
bit and see more of those beautiful
underwater
[Music]
sceneries okay where was I a Psy thank
you so
much Cru D D D D Hood thank you for free
oranges got to make some orange juice
thank
you and naan content thanks pinky ah yes
the return of my true main monitor
content let us continue the story of
tanaki Shakara of the oranges Shakira
Shakira a I'm on your main
monitor thank you so much I'm honored to
be there maybe you should put me on all
of your monitors
though hi fructose corn syrup G action
thank you burn burn burn
burn succession crisis no there never
was
you D jail D jail bird D quack d d d dou
Jones dun I'm here for
SCU dun Unity CH dun Kafka on the shore
dun moon dog D Nathan thanks for the
pinky another one you'll get a kiss
you're too generous you always send
pinkies you should get many more kisses
One does not simply walk into L door the
L
doors those were some good low
doors except for mine I kept on talking
about freaking
Burgers they did me
dirty nah it's funny it's
okay d d random collusion thanks for the
red chat appropriate jpg boss ending
what dungeon did I do here
probably my
own and ena's dungeon right or maybe
maybe I even did three dungeons on that
day
oh wait what indeed of course it must
have been mine because mine had the best
boss and more or less the only
boss
so kind of must have been
mine yeah for all the dirty they did me
they at least gave me a sick
dungeon
[Music]
yeah I shall accept the apology
and the
exchange trade offer when I sacri
sacrificed myself jumping into the lava
for the final hit which was totally on
purpose for for
[Music]
drama she hates hamburgers well I really
don't um
normally like I like chicken burgers
sometimes Okay so hamburgers in the
sense of the classic hamburger I would
normally not order in a fast food rest
like in a chain I feel
like I would only normally go for a
hamburger with
bath and in like a proper
restaurant where it's not a
chain because it just tastes so much
better better better I don't know what
I'm why I'm talking like this
yeah cuz I don't know I also I told you
about this before but in the fast food
chains I'm
like I don't know and I don't want to
know I don't quite trust what they put
into the beef
patties I trust the chicken patties more
which maybe makes no sense but I don't
know it always also says like ooh 100%
beef from Austria or whatever but I
still don't trust it
[Music]
so yeah and and I don't I don't know
they don't really I don't like the taste
usually I haven't tried any in a long
time
but I'd prefer to have a really nice one
from a proper burger
[Music]
restaurant even the most basic ones they
have on the menu usually are so good
I can't usually get anything besides the
most basic one anyway because the the
other ones would always be too big and
too
much yeah where they grind to meet
themselves I don't know I just trust in
more like more than a big
multi-billion business fle
chain yeah it's probably fine you know
what's in there but N I don't know
and the Burger King crispy chicken is
the best the best of them
all I like f Burgers to be honest but
they're not equally good for sure I can
kind
of see it as a different food and then
appreciate it as
that but i' still always go for chicken
burger I don't know I just kind of
prefer
them would you eat cver wa didn't didn't
I eat
cver wasn't that cver what I had in in
New
[Music]
York but those weren't Burgers those
that was just
chicken was that was that not C what was
that
[Music]
again what was that again what what did
cie get for
us
canes yeah similar with the
sea
can yeah I love to try
Culver apparently narissa is addicted to
it anyway thank you random collusion
laziness
than Narita thanks for the red super
chat Ki your dungeon was so cool I know
many people loved it the best including
goba and it's very fun to watch people
try to tackle it and die over and over
yeah that was good
ah sorry my throat hurts my not my
throat my
neck I wonder if something's just wrong
with it should I where would I what
would I let's
Google front of neck in
pain front neck pain is usually caused
by a sore throat or a muscle cramp H
probably muscle cramp then depending on
to cause the pain to get better within
one or two weeks H if you were recently
in a vehicle Collision Collision or
random Collision or if you think you're
having a heart attack am I having a
heart
attack heart
[Music]
container could be a sign of many minor
conditions such as sore throat swollen
lymph nose no I don't think so it's just
muscle strains such as Whiplash or from
bending over and staring at your phone
for too long no it's my [\h__\h] pillow
somehow I don't know why it's doing it
now
[Music]
though but I swatched swatched swapped
switched swapped swatched to a different
pillow last night I don't know I don't
think it would get better immediately I
just chose a different pillow that I had
at
home um maybe the next few days it will
get better in combination with my
massage thing and maybe taking a hot
bath
it's
terminal
hurts it's just weird I never had it in
the front of my neck before
pain I don't have a sore
Thro my lymph
no I'm fine
[Music]
all right guess I'll die no guess I'll
wait I'll wait it out anyway what why
did I stop reading the Super Chat oh
because I was in pain and it's very fun
to watch people try to tackle it and die
over and over the lure cut scene was
also pretty badass but also very cute
and it was a good dose of V back on my
birthday it was your birthday on that
very day
stretching and balanced neck muscle
exercise for yeah I really should
strch don't die we die
too we do you do oh when the dungeon
came out was your birthday
oh congratulations to you too then happy
birthday to you happy birthday to you na
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you in your pants
to jam in your
shoe happy
birthday
congratulations what is that cute new
profile picture you have that looks like
a dorky fight
waa
cute m
[Music]
thanks for the
pinky thank
you Bo
7 Nathan cotton and another
pinky you're
crazy wait if you don't want to be known
as the burger lady then what are we
making all these burgers for what is our
purpose not because I want to be known
for it that's just my business that's
just my way to become a
millionaire I would to be known for
okay you know I don't mind being known
for burgar but I want to be known for
more than Burger not just Burger that's
that's the
problem I want to be known for Idol and
Warrior strong scary suy intimidating
strong
Phoenix not just Burger chicken burger
yeah Fried Chicken too so but that's
just food I'm talking about more than
just
Bon the full package yeah
wow wow the dancing
[Music]
queen I'm
you guys that's probably how you're
going to act once you get
RGB
um badge then you're just going to
constantly trigger
me I see it coming
already just because of usual room
immunity you're gonna pretend like you
can say anything you
[Music]
want maybe maybe then I'm just going to
turn off chat forever so that you can't
trigger
me what are you going to do then huh huh
yeah g didn't we um I I announced it
yesterday you
crying yeah I can just turn you off like
that so don't be don't be a little [\h__\h]
constantly put it on
plus 5 years plus no but then it's only
RGB and they want to trigger me I should
put it anything under five years if if I
could just block out all the fiveyear
chickens
purposefully and we just got our s
back don't abuse your immunity
I could just make a different room
that's the same as the usual room but
legally just different
name if you act up that is if you act up
too
much so be
careful for now yeah legally distinct
you exactly for now I'll let you have
that once you get to 5 years and we'll
see how it happens but if you act up too
much
then you don't want to
know the conventional spin I like
[Music]
that well jino you're still far from it
you better
[Music]
stay okay let's go where was
I water
[Music]
moonight no I don't think it
will M creeper space
water D the gamer
cre P
unknown and I read two pinkies no need
to read it aloud but I
will hi K by the time you read this the
Ari Super Chat is
rare oh my God I hope you've had some
rest from all your hard work recently
kind of Ian has had some eventful times
lately and it feels like the community
has been more alive than ever M that is
true makes me happy to be a kfp today
fifth PDT is my birthday I'm 26 now and
it's crazy to think I've spent four of
my birthdays with you already yeah oh my
God I'm sorry I look forward to many
more I hope you have a good day and
night love you my Kami oie thank you for
saving us
lesbians you're
welcome yeah you're still so young such
a baby
no happy birthday
Arie happy birthday to you happy
birthday happy birthday to you
happy birth I'm trying to come up with
something
new happy birthday to you
[Music]
happy birthday to you may lesbians
surround you happy
birthday and continue being gay happy
birthday to
[Music]
you do you like it do you like
it why are you gay
yay happy
birthday
AR this reaction makes me
[Music]
nervous why are you
K thank you so much for your support for
such a long
time you are a great chicken to have
around
m you know what I'm talking about always
you get it you get me yeah thank you so
much I hope I hope to have you around
forever and ever and ever and ever and
ever especially because you got to turn
RGB one day right now you have your
armor so first you got to turn gold when
are you turning gold
Ari when are you becoming
[Music]
gold [\h__\h] ear
November oh that's soon okay okay okay
so RGB is not that far you know one year
and like two months or
so that will be your final
form careful K too much
lesbian I'm sorry
but but for Arie for Arie
[Music]
yeah 60 months
Jee that's going to be crazy to see that
pop up on my uh uh
chat not
enough Never
[Music]
Enough okay
I thank
you you're so sweet
even telling me I don't have to read it
of course I'm going to read it I have
to 48 months
yeah 48 months well but like 60 is going
to round it up nicely you guys got to
aim for the 60 50 is also going to be
nice
number okay I'm going to end there it's
almost M yeah halfast 10 p.m. I'm going
to cook even though I don't want to
yesterday you know I I still had so much
food in my fridge but I really didn't
feel it didn't even have to cook all I
had to do was warm it up and it was
actually good the Casp noodle but I
didn't feel it so I just
got frozen
[Music]
pizza I just ate frozen pizza you know
sometimes you just don't feel it what
you have so I put the caspis noodle into
the freezer at least I didn't throw them
away they're in the freezer now perhaps
another day they should be
consumed but today I think I'm going to
cook cook the fish because probably
that's the first thing to go bad in my
fridge my fridge is so full right now
Mama M I feel like I'm going to I think
I'm going to turn off hell fresh for
next week it's just
overwhelming let me see or did it
already like oh it might have already or
did it no maybe not
[Music]
where is Hello
fresh hello
[Music]
beep at least the fish recipes are
pretty simple like the last time I had I
I cooked fish I think I uh that was my
Revival for kiwa's kitchen
recently that one was uh pan fried fish
most of the time when I get fish
recipes it's oven baked which is so
simple was mid yeah it was only mid
because it was lacking salt I bought
properly like Finly grained salt now
again the hell was
that thank you don't worry 30 MS is
planning like you guys are all so
supportive any any amount of months
is uh big
[Music]
support yeah yeah I got normal salt
again um wait what was I going to do uh
what's the next one oh no I don't think
I can cancel the next one
[Music]
anymore oh I can't even change no wait
did I choose these recipes no maybe I
did they're at least edible there's
nothing I don't
necessarily
[Music]
like the next
one should I cancel I don't always want
to be cooking I'm going to cancel the
next next
one I don't I don't know it's too
much it's just too much
[Music]
the end of an era no no no no it's
coming back again after can you order
less per week no there's a minimum of
three dishes per week which for me is
like six dishes because it's uh the
minimum is like two portions per dish so
when I say three dishes is actually six
but like the caspr noodle for example
that I made the other day I got so much
out of that that's not two portions for
me that is three or four honestly it's
four portions for me
so free
dishes uh yeah sometimes things are
really just two portions but a lot of
times it's like threee portions honestly
and sometimes it's four portions but
most of the time it comes out as free
portions
yeah which is a good thing I guess
usually when it's something with like a
pork filet or or so then it will be only
two portions and honestly not that
filling in terms of meat they don't give
much
meat but if it's any kind of pasta dish
or so then it's usually a lot or any
kind of vegetarian dish usually a
lot they're definitely saving on how
much meat they're giving
us which is okay like I I I have a small
tummy I don't eat that much
normally it's filling for me
mostly especially with the
sides yeah what I don't like is like
when the sauce like for whatever pasta
dish they want me to make like often
it's like uh the sauce is there's not
much sauce like when it's a pesto dish
they don't give that much
pesto sometimes sometimes it's like make
pesto yourself sometimes it's pesto
already packaged when it's already
packaged it's like very
little and when it's making yourself
somehow I really struggle in making it
like
Smooth
difficult I want plenty of sauce me
too yeah but sometimes I I add onto it
like the other day it was like uh this
like red pesto that they
gave for what dish was it I don't
remember but I just added um what did I
add some tomato uh uh paste a little bit
and a little bit more
cream
yeah to make the sauce more and that was
a good thing to
do p your salt no I don't think I ever
tried it
[Music]
yeah yeah no because I saw German
comments saying something I've been
thinking all this time
yeah yeah nine n
nine understand for sty
do no I understood order that's the most
important part by the way I'm I'm not
going to say it too clearly but you know
something's exciting is coming up that
I've been preparing you and I had this
like amazing idea for the opening
um not going to say yet what it was but
I thought this is so [\h__\h] genius I
have to do it so I've been cooking the
opening and now I got the opening and
it's so long though I think the life is
going to life it's going to be over an
hour cuz without the opening it's
already uh like 58 minutes I think which
I'm honestly so glad because I think the
last time I was really struggling and
trying to like fill it up with um the
ending and so
on um but this
time thank God with all my hard work and
squeezing in as much as I could into the
schedule uh
yeah and doing more MC's I feel like
I've done more but maybe in this like
all together it wasn't
[Music]
more but it's going to be slightly
longer I feel like what I'm definitely
going to do is I'm not going to start
the stream on the hour I will start it
like at least like 5 minutes
early if not 10 we still got bloopers no
I don't think
so oh I was originally planning to do
bloopers again but um I feel like I
would have had I already like I did
mention it uh during the recording too
but I think now my director has moved on
without uh like preparing the bloopers
so asking now is probably a little bit
too
[Music]
late but
yeah I need
to to
download them and see what's
the what's the full
amount of time that this
opening takes up
yum
yum but yeah um whatever I'm talking
about I will put out a proper and non
MOA soon I like the bloopers too
[Music]
yeah maybe
afterwards maybe I can still kind of
make it happen
afterwards like even if it's not
included because it will make it too
long even if it's not included in the
live maybe something to up load
after making off oh members only I could
make it members only cuz I don't that's
the thing I don't have a members only
[Music]
part basically the schedule would just
not allow it uh
unless unless you do it
live you know pre-recorded kind of uh
yeah forces me to sacrifice it I'd
rather do it pretty quick
[Music]
to have things end up be
perfect oh yeah screw it we're doing it
live no we're
[Music]
not yeah membership that's a good
membership
extra I'll actually bring it up now
before I forget it um
[Music]
what
some you
[Music]
what did you hear that
you
didn't oh what the
hell it only download one
video oh no it's
downloading what ah it's downloading it
in two Zips okay one video was way
bigger than the others okay anyway
anyway anyway any I wrote the message so
now I can't
[Music]
forget are you guys still
there could also work well as
[Music]
shorts I don't know we'll see we'll see
we'll
see I'm deceased so no what the
hell why we're all in your
imaginations no
[Music]
no promote the merch promote
what I'm hungry I'm
[Music]
hungry come here come here come here
come
here ah
[Music]
I choked on you guys the
hell you're spicy I don't know something
was choking me
[Music]
disgusting yeah you lucky I SP you out
cuz you're
disgusting ow I was supposed to pluck
you first damn it and also there was
like liquid gold somewhere mixed in
there ew poisoned myself
almost
[Music]
BR n it's probably not that you're
disgusting it's just love some of you
are too spicy some of you are poisonous
right now it's just not a good mix
yeah some of you still had your feathers
on some were raw
eggs what a weird mix some of you had
armor
on some of you were in a bucket those
were the ones I should have eaten I
should have specifically just eaten the
ones that were Fried Chicken in the
bucket I how can I I can't sort you out
[Music]
yeah only the one year
gang very specifically just
you eat
me but how to just eat
[Music]
you need to separate you
the Hat stick sell like
popcorn
true true you do look if I squint my
eyes you do look like popcorn I'm
crunch she hates the old Camp no you're
just
like not made for eating
anymore have to sadly say goodbye that's
okay me
too time to
say
goodbye I'm going to go now it's almost
the end of the week guys or it is the
end of the week more or less uh
tomorrow uh is in the night time after
midnight for me will be the
[Music]
my don't even get me started I don't
actually even know what we're going to
do I uh I remember in New York I was
talking with Amma and I I made a
suggestion and she was like oh that's a
good idea and we're probably going to do
that but I don't know what else we're
going to do I'm is planning something
nice I
think and during the day I'm going to
finish that piece of art I'm to try
haven't made any progress so
far but I'll focus on it during the
daytime don't know if I can cry anymore
I feel like I'll probably be chill
unless somebody else starts to cry but I
feel like I won't cry because I'll be in
streamer
mode I'll probably I'll probably be
emotionally
unavailable I'm not going to cry no I
probably won't cry no I can't I probably
can't like I want to cry but I won't be
able to cuz like I'm nervous or so I'll
probably be very nervous
[Music]
Amma doesn't want me to cry
anyway
so I'll
try yeah so uh most likely 100% it will
happen on am's channel so I'll see you
on am's channel tomorrow is she
streaming now can I raate her again
we've been like daily raiding
her let me
see probably not streaming now cuz she's
not doing any more marathon is
she who's streaming herb is
streaming right
yeah I'm oh I'm uh stream is very far
what's B
doing we want to play with raran is that
a Super Chat reading that she's
[Music]
doing yeah I think that's that's what
rabbit
is okay okay one Kata stream later
okay I'll rate
herb cuz she's been raiding me and she's
sweet she's
cute wait can I rate her
Elizabeth
yes all right in German M Vina in wish
me luck for motivation wish me
motivation thank you for
I had
[Music]
fun yeah see you
tomorrow don't think about it too hard
don't think about it too hard don't
think about it too hard don't think just
don't think let's just not think I'll do
my best with my drawing yeah thank
you in German we say in no fa head empty
[Music]
yeah e