[Music]
hello everybody thank you for
waiting hello welcome to the spelling be
going you want to do a drum roll
[Music]
get that thing out of here what thing ah
away I'm sorry I didn't realize we had
an audience right
now uh uh thank you guys for waiting um
in the theater in your comfy
seats did you find your gift bag
underneath your seats everyone did you
there's a beehive underneath your chair
everybody check
a select few of you have been chosen to
find a complimentary beehive pre- shaken
just for
[Music]
you hello hello okay so yes today we're
going to have a spelling be we have our
12 participants standing by our 12
brainiacs yeah I I hope they studied
because uh we did some studying right
right a little bit we don't need to
study uh wait
we're the guests of our we don't need to
study the judges yes so good and I will
be judging and keeping track hopefully
with the help of chat please please we
need your help you are also an honorary
judge just well no you're an honorary
scorekeeper which is like a judge but
less important yeah yeah that's true
that's true okay yeah so we have three
judges
technically you are one you are the hive
mind you guys you are the third as all
together work together chat let's go
work together okay well uh without
further Ado Let's uh go take a look at
our
contestants look at all their beautiful
faces oh wait what everybody's Frozen
what the heck and they're not speaking
what they're so quiet maybe maybe
they're like Frozen in time or something
maybe we have to shoot them or I don't
know with like some type of special
weapon get it should I CU my special
weapon I think we I think that's the
queue for the special weapon oh T I'm
pulling my special weapon out but you
can't see I can't see it I'm going to
use it do I use it now uh well we got to
decide who should we shoot first who
should I shoot
guys uh let's see who do you think I
should shoot um uh uh
should we just start a row maybe that'd
be easier okay first
Up 3 two
1 oh wait hold on I think I I think you
missed uh can you do one more time
please what do you mean I've only shot
this thing once my entire life 3 2
1 did get hello hold on can you shoot
that thing again I think we need to use
like a enlarge Ray I don't think she's
supposed to be that small let me try
again hello hello oh uh contestants when
you become un Frozen can we get an
introduction who
that I'm
I'm I'm going to do my best
[Music]
today oh oops sorry uh I didn't shoot it
that time I swear I didn't shoot it that
time I think you sat on the trigger or
something okay oh
God so cute okay all okay I'm already
ready I've got my finger on the booger
hook I'm ready I'm going to shoot the
next guest who is it uh let's take a
look at what we going to go
next I think this thing is broken uh can
you shoot that one more time please it's
shooting blank I'm going a
dragon yeah uh uh yay
y who hi hi hi little guy what's your
name oh hey I'm so small hey h b I am of
course I beu sparkling y h life English
and I totally don't make typos every
other word that I type so I will be so
good at this game perfect perfect
contestant
you love to see it yeah next next okay
next up let's see I'm aiming for that
big pink cat oh
[Music]
okay
hello I'm ra panta from horor Life
English Justice the artist with the god
eyes Big C means big
[Music]
trouble big trouble should I get ready
to shoot
again beg for your life beg for your
life please um I I have C this candy
what candy pasta okay you can live oh
okay yeah the pasta
okay we should boost her volume cuz I
can't I couldn't hear her begging for
her life very well boed there we go
better boosted up next up next do I have
to shoot this one I'm going to feel bad
you have to oh no what
happened there we go okay yes okay I'm
sorry do
it she shot me I'm bleeding
out you're so tiny though
hello it's me renowned rapper and
speller of words hello hello
hello hello are you excited for this
spelling be you feel confident I'm
scared I have stage fright it's like
with the the debate and the spelling be
I'm like why did I sign up for all these
public speaking events in a row improve
your intelligence you can do it oh no
are you the smartest vtuber no no no
wait where's your com confidence no
confidence
no okay uh well we still got a a lot of
contestants left so let's go to the next
one next H
up wait hold on I'm sorry
I'm wow girl was really excited to shoot
me
there a v a c a d oh that's how you
spell
avocado my my name is Mory kipy and I'm
the Grim Reaper I just have a couple I
have some problems moving my mouth
sometimes speak with my mind yeah we
hear you hi hi cool I'm going to take
this thing home for the dead beats let's
do it you look so excited to be here uh
I studied my whole life which is
billions of years so shove that in your
juice box and suck it oh okay okay cool
I excited to see your talent yeah oh you
know all right you know it what what one
second while we fix that one one second
it's okay I I don't mind using telepathy
to communicate with the audience I mean
yeah they can hear you anyways yeah yeah
it's cool don't worry about it oh yeah
make me nice and big yeah I'm using my
enlarge beam you just can't hear it
right now thank you
[Music]
she used it it worked it worked all
right nice all right well we we we'll
move on but uh I think uh bit in the
backstage is uh working on fixing that
should be okay be buzz in
away wait wait wait say something now
maybe it'll work hey I guess not okay
well W
back okay next
[Music]
next all right I'm ready this I'm going
to get this first try ready
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah I need to uh enlarge over here can
we get enlarge do I have to I like the
size the way she is
now just keep keep no I need to remain
small or else I'm going to be Target no
okay hello what's up I'm B haers number
one Aussie rat from Down Under and I'm
so confident I have uh I have Superior
spelling just because I'm down from it's
not going to be a debuff
right um I mean you're spelling I
mean I think we might make an exception
we we'll see we we we'll have the chat
decide we we'll vote on it your a
witness
me so tiny
though all right uh let's see we still
have six more contestants left
[Music]
so I'm going to shoot it
now
okay hold on I think there's a delay on
that
hello hello a b c d e f g I can spell
and you will see
[Music]
y cute I'm Cecilia hello spin spin spin
spinning spinning thank you
hello okay is that let your introduction
spin spin spin yeah yeah okay but who
are
you I'm see green from
Justice and I spin today I'll spin I'll
use all my burin power I have low
confidence but high energy so it'll be
okay okay well luckily out it'll be
great yeah luckily I think uh everybody
here is not really the uh best speller
but we'll see we'll find out
today yes I resent that oh hey your your
mouth's working hey now I'm constantly
speaking
100% time y y y only one
way yeah she never stops
talking all right well let's go to next
contestant T the big blue lady
wo wait I'm
sorry
okay
um it's Oro cron and I I am ready to
crush this spelling be because my brain
is so chubby with knowledge let's go
[Applause]
wo yeah wow we're the same species yeah
crazy what a coincidence wow crazy right
wow world that he I didn't do it there
can only be one
sorry just kind of unall for it's a
little violent out
here okay um thank you moving on welc to
the
show up next we have okay are you ready
are you ready for me to shoot now uh yes
okay
shooting oh my
God I Darlings this is H life English
Advent devil is Shiva the one and only
narissa Raven coft or socken coft it
seems to be today happy to be here I
hope we can all have a fun time
together y you look like you're just
saying cute very very cute all right
next next
[Music]
my aim's gotten so
good I'm Ready
toell Grand
today was so cute
okay thank you uh you were cutting it
and out a little bit but I think I think
it's okay kind of fixed a little bit B
boost that audio yes uh we'll get a bow
B boost
boosting boost all right bow B boosted
[Music]
complete get one more little B
B okay yeah that's good thank you nice
all right only two contestants left to
see their special for
here now the orange ones okay ready
orange uh
yes te
M I
am the little yapper I am GG mood of H
life Justice I am excited to Beast here
I liketh the longest the walks on the
beach and I seeketh to take home the
gold of the bee I am quite the
intellectual and you will fall prey to
my mad spelling skills are you going to
fist us yes I will if if you want only
if you want can oh
god I think I'm in the wrong competition
can I go wait guys I I look I se consent
sorry that was for
your punish okay yeah just just just put
a flesh
wound I hav to run out of ammo I can't
shoot them all okay okay and last for
disciplin last but not
least I saved my biggest bullet for
you the biggest bullet for me thank you
projectile I don't know what it
is I am Tak from life English I am the
myth speaker of Ian and as long as
there's no rhods Island I'll probably be
fine that was definitely something that
we were thinking maybe putting in a
Rhode Island but uh no no no not again
it's
traumatizing we wouldn't do that
Theodor I'm scared I'm
shivering H okay I mean everybody's
nervous right guys I mean you guys
you
nervous I'm nervous
okay nerv we're going to explain the
rules so maybe that'll help you guys
feel a little less nervous let your
nerves motivate you to spell right and
do mistakes yes so good yes let's go all
right so just to
exp just to explain the rules as I was
saying um we have lives up here so if
you guys see these Stars
that means that each person has two
lives and the blue star is a lifeline
and a Lifeline that means that anybody
can ask another contestant for help now
uh for the contestant that replies to
this Lifeline you can sabotage but would
you really want to do that to your
beloved holoen you know
[Music]
friends
sabotage totally not you're too
wholesome to do that that would be a
crime illegal I
disagree anything for the crown this is
a
competition not choosing crony or Ba got
it
yeah all right do you guys have any
questions
sorry no questions looking for what's
the pr good
Oh's A priz breing R A be what's the pr
think of a prize
uh good there a priz right we get you
get a uh yeah all right can you do like
a a drum
roll get a trophy that we don't have an
image up right now cuz we forgot but
you're definitely it's going to look
really cool we're going to put
[Music]
it we promise yeah yeah
do I get to keep the sock that I'm
wearing oh yeah oop sorry you do get to
keep
why all right uh we are going to start
but if you guys could just uh talk about
yourselves for a moment while I get rid
of this gun that is randomly shooting at
people y y y y y y y y y
[Music]
warm up it faded out so nicely yeah nice
work
chus
yay uh okay so uh to get started uh just
to explain the rules a little bit more
there will be uh three rounds of uh
different varying levels of words so
there's going to be an easy mode there's
going to be a medium mode a hard mode
and then extra hard mode and we're going
to see how many we have left at the end
kind of like a battle royale I guess
spelling be was like the first battle
royale
okay let's
[Music]
go yeah
die it might there might be some
violence that if if you lose your stars
if you lose your lives it's
possible I don't know well guess we'll
see what happens right you might die
[Music]
[Applause]
no death for
now
okay all right well if you guys are
ready we're going to start um good
should we start in a specific order
maybe same reveal order or what do you
think we can do that if you want okay
we're going to put somebody on the spot
who is it who's it going to be
[Music]
hi I'm nervous already don't be
nervous be something
else I'm God that's the spirit that's
the
spirit all right so uh good you want to
you want to start off I'll leave you in
charge of the words a word
Master Okie doie ready
then ready are you ready for your first
word okay here going okay your word is
abdomen abdomen a b d o m e n all right
correct oh
[Applause]
nice she got an easy one
nice okay you survived you survived this
time all right that was easy that was
the first one down see guys it's not
it's it's not that bad it's not that bad
I had to double I had to think twice
about that one I'm
screwed me too I was like
uhoh all right this is an extra hard
round right no this is easy we're
starting easy it's okay
abdomen oh no are you ready oh no uh can
I spell it in rock rock is my first
language uh I know they are good to we
going to accept rock as a language what
do you think I don't speak that language
H chat chat do you guys speak that
language yeah yeah chat
right I
guess there might be some rock stuff in
there we'll
see all right are you ready good to I'm
ready are you ready B I'm
ready oh it's abom me no no no no no no
no
no people don't cheat people your word
is squeak
oh oh wait
s
q
e
wait
is we'll give you
one wait unfair wa chat chat s q
u e a
k
okay
H y'all can't help chat that is
correct I wasn't looking um but but the
Kiara gas did indicate
something Kara Mia thanks
Kiara oh I I thought much you like once
you make a mistake it's already over
anyway uh well I was thinking we could
give people like One edit uh oh oh yeah
I
Kara one edit each time or in total uh
maybe in the first round cuz we're still
learning how the game works just really
nervous do they have to notice
themselves that they messed up then
uh yeah I think so okay okay
um I do just want to point out to to
everybody watching and everybody
participating that uh if you would like
to ask for a definition of the word or
if it's a noun or an adjective you can
also do that yeah if you guys want to
hear it used in a sentence maybe you
know easy easy mode we already know
those words I think but as we progress
you guys might need some hints so don't
don't be scared to ask yeah
yeah okay thanks contestant
it's
me are you ready I am not okay wait um
so what now
um I'm going to give you your word
anyway and you're going to spell it okay
okay okay your word is
buts uh can you say again
buttox it's
it's
it's can can you can you tell me what it
is or like the definition what used for
yeah
definition uh it is a noun and it's two
round fleshy parts that form the lower
rear area of a human
trunk but
B okay uh
B
okay a no U
[Music]
okay
t a
okay you can do it I don't know this
it's hard it is it is hard okay um is
that your final answer we will allow an
edit if you
want uh okay I think the X is not
correct
okay can you say the word again
buttox
buttox I sit upon my
butttock to grab a squishy
butto uh then it should
be this but with a a no with a e at the
end
I know after the what you're so cute laa
I don't know I never heard this word
before I'm trying though you're doing so
great yeah you're doing amazing you're
doing amazing I'm so proud of you you
can use a Lifeline don't forget you have
you have a blue
star I use my blue star okay all
right she's going
to who do you want l who do you want to
give you a blue star to I
[Music]
want
hi hi all right I got I got you on this
one Rara butto is b u t t o x
butto wait what did you say b u t t o x
yeah
[\h__\h] all right is that your final answer
no it's not my final answer
oops I saw you I saw it be Ty front of
me and I decided
to so here's my question I need to
clarify
something uhhuh yes is it but talk or
but talks like is it multiple plural
plural plal always needs to be plural no
it's always plural right no it's
not have one but you never
know but buttox is b u t t o c k s s not
Double S I said s because I'm pressing
pushen
I'm no I'm using push to talk so I had
to make sure you heard the S because my
fingers went off the space bar all right
is this your final answer for final
answer final answer okay judge
[Music]
[Applause]
correct you survived but you I'm
spelling butto b u t a x from now
on but but but it it is
a but all right you survived woohoo
y why so much harder than the previous
two it's hey man I'm just reading the
the chart I've got yeah that
was all right uh you guys ready to move
on okay yeah all right you mon you there
oh boy are you ready ready as I'll ever
be yeah okay okay your word is orang
Tang oh come
on a n g u t a
n
orang excuse me that's an easy round
what do you what do you no right that's
is that a hard word I would say so you I
would say that's at least medium
right medium congratulations can
IUN don't have to go again no we have to
go we have to go to next contestant skip
skip all right Kelly are you are you
ready oh yeah all right oh yeah oh boy
okay
wait you said you're ready right yes yes
okay let's run it your word
is
Hospitality can I get the
definition the friendly and generous
reception and entertainment of guests
visitors or strangers is it a noun
adjective verb a noun can you use it
in gee Callie the hospitality sure's
been great since I've been crashing on
your
futon who came up with the word she's
buying
time word I'm sorry Jesus okay
Hospitality h o
s p i
t a l okay that's the hospital part um i
t y litty hospit Hospital litty
Hospitality
woo good
job all right so chat chat you guys are
keeping track of the points right right
yes are you is anybody are we keeping
track of the points I wasn't keeping
track of the points are you there a
point system okay yeah it's in the
system don't worry we got it all right
nice job
K thanks yeah okay
so
next ready bring it bring it bring it
bring it bring it bring it bring it
bring it bring it bring it bring
it all right I'm
ready your word
is a
kidna a kidnap what did you say like
Knuckles the Akida Knuckles exactly what
the can I get definition please cap a
spiny insectivorous egg laying mammal
with a long snow in claws native to
Australia oh K all right okay spell
sound it
out
e
[Music]
see h h
and wait hold on a
kid oh sorry e c h
i
d
n yay okay kid now final
answer yes for answer thank you very
much nice
it is a Amel yeah it's an animal it's an
Amel from Down Under they have some fun
facts about them you should look them up
yeah I was just about to say that yeah
animal maybe don't
yeah I know the exact fact you're
thinking of I'll check it out visual
description Feed Us Feed Us kid what
does it look like
ga uh
um uh
red
and shoes I think and what I don't think
he goes fast but I might be wrong okay
okay moving
on next contestant are you
ready yeah okay okie
doie hello your word is is
laabi laabi like the definition
please a quiet gentle song sung to send
a child to sleep okay laabi
l
u l now it's the question is it one or
two l lulling l LLY another
L Lal Lal Bo l a b y l l one L please
remove one L are you sure okay really
yeah okay
yeah
okay little boy all right back no no
okay final answer okay all right
judge you've let us you you you had
it it just didn't look right there were
too many elves me down why were there so
many elves L always looks wrong the oh
no the Stars
disappearing oh
no there it goes how do you feel uh like
half my heart is
missing I'm
here not that one
um it's okay I still have two more one
more heart I'll I'll get him next time
yeah yeah yeah all right that was pretty
good try though was a pretty good try
and moving on to our next
contestant hello hey hey oh
damn look so funny
jeez hey I'm ready
I love this
crony okay
crony your word is
creatine
definition an organic acid that helps to
supply energy to cells particularly to
muscle cells okay I'm
ready c r e
a
t i n e final
answer yes okay damn
she
[Music]
nice nice job nice job thank you thank
you wow all right nice job yeah we're
almost done with the easy words there's
only one round of easy words guys so uh
don't don't get too comfortable
yeah okay uh it's r r
no all right next
contestant hi
ready yeah I
guess your word is
kumquat kumquat can you please use that
in a
sentence the juices of this kumquat are
getting all over my
fingers oh it's a it's a it's a
fruit okay
um uh um is it is a fruit a noun I don't
know I don't know English actually yeah
I think yeah isn't it oh I I don't know
um
okay uh can can I use my star to ask
someone for he you want to use it now on
easy okay
yeah I never heard this word before but
you know who I think if if someone's got
me I feel like I feel like fauna Mo
mother nature
would would know what this is so would
you help me um I'll try unless you want
to rethink you're giving it to no no I I
trust you okay oh gosh okay I think it's
k
[Music]
u i I feel like I need to go quick on
this next part because I don't want this
to linger on the
screen what does what comes after is
it
um
mq
uat all right Final Answer final answer
okay
nice nice yummy mother neigh knows her
fruit thank you thank you all right
nobody uh lost a life this time but one
Lifeline is another Lifeline God M all
right next for the difficult
rounds all right P you ready I'm ready
ready okay
your word
is
sprinkle sprinkle I love sprinkles oh my
God
excuse why you e easy sprinkle
sprinkle s p r i n k l e sprinkle
fuz sprinkles
sprinkles nice
work Chad is saying rigged they're
already saying rigged oh no oh no we're
in
trouble you know there was a secret baby
level huh baby level a secret bow B
level it's random okay it's randomish
right
random is yeah yeah yeah it was it was
random okay no more questions on that
right no no I would never doubt the
organizers of this
event all right next
contes hi hello I I have question before
yes when you use your lifeline and you
give your star to someone and then they
physically have your star does that mean
what is that mean does that just mean
that they were a Lifeline or we can't
use them anymore or does that mean that
they get two lifelines no they don't get
to use it again it's just like a it's
just uh you know to show it's like a
sheriff badge of honor type of thing
you're awesome yeah are cool I like some
I will move it down below though they've
collected these it's not it's not like
Mario party it's not going to count for
extra points it's just a that looks cool
means you're freaking sick a l less
go I not the
prob all right was was one last question
yes do the judges take
bribes what what do you think going
to maybe depends on what you're what
what are you offering yeah this
explicitly a little bit of under the
table I I'll message you don't don't sh
hey all right that was ba and
you now get explosion I get to shoot I
get to
sh
her ready to spell the world word now
guys a judge okay did ready M yes okay
creature here's your
word biome bi can you use that in a
sentence
please the green one is my favorite
Minecraft
biome yes definition
please a large naturally occurring
community of Flora and Fauna occupying a
major habitat for example a forest or a
tundra I see I see I am ready to spell b
i
o m e
biomi yes sound like I do what the h
what orange girls
orange all right congratulations you
passed the easy round all right our last
contestant for the easy
[Music]
round bring it on I'm scared all
right okay you're randomly selected word
is rad
Island Road Island not roads
island island that's not a that's two
words that doesn't count aition it's on
the
chart yeah that's two words okay
definition there's no it that that
doesn't count oh this seems like okay
they are not agreeing the organizers are
not agreeing with this one I got to go
talk to the I my be okay we can do a
different word we'll do another word
Revenge okay your word
is
restaurant oh okay r e s t a u r a n t
yes that's what she said yes are you
sure let's go
okay
okay round over
baby nice on everybody
nice how did you guys feel about that
first easy round
huh easy some of the words
were a little a little you know uh I
could have could have maybe been a
little more simple for some people is
not that hard of never heard of a [\h__\h]
quad I would have known how to little
orange it's easy you eat the skin it's
like GG also I see you in chat saying
typing out the word I'm going to ban you
oh uhoh wait why
you you're looking at chat no I'm not
looking at chat I'm saying if you're in
chat and you're typing the word I'm
going to ban you ah okay understandable
it's different you have to be in the
chat to ban them you
can't never
mind anyway so from this second round
onwards there's no more correction was
it like it has to be first try Dodge
what do you think this is our trial R it
away the what do you think should we
allow edits on the words or no no edits
um um you don't allow
edits to be wrong all right no edits no
edits uh that was edit we know how the
game works now yeah
[Music]
the all
right we are now moving on to the medium
round
woo okay all right we're going to start
again oh at the
beginning really we're going to bully me
again hi no no no no
maybe
possibly are you ready for your medium
word no but yes but
no okay here we
go your word is
codependency
what is that a hint
hi I feel like there's a hidden meaning
with this
me I can spell okay c
o let me
think
de let me think okay if you're laughing
I can't think
okay p
e I'm spelling it in my brain
okay
[Laughter]
huh
what
what NOP wait you said no
said oh it depends
d a n c
y Dy Dancy D Dany is this your final
answer would you like to use your life
say that out loud the
pendan called a
p sounds about right yeah sounds right
right all right do is it do you want to
use this as your final answer or do you
want to use a
Lifeline Co depend
see can I change the a to an E they we
said no no you said no but you changed
the there's a cool down if you if you
think it's wrong within the first two
seconds then I'll change it what was
that always
a it it kind of makes
sense all right no edits let's go all
right final
answer yes okay
so close though yeah so
close I love the moment when we saw
exactly the confusion in moko's
brain stop laughing and
then you did good yeah question so
basically the The Final Answer once
you've come up with your final answer um
you're basically only asking us if it's
our final answer because we can use a
Lifeline at the very end right wait I
didn't know that I said we said you did
say yeah they did say do you want to use
your Lifeline you're the blue star over
your head that's a Lifeline which means
you can ask any of the contestants if uh
they could spell it for you
instead it's okay you're still alive
yeah you're still alive you still have
you got one
Lifeline yeah all right next contestant
T helloo hi
hi ready are you ready oh uh
yes okay
ready your word
is uh and I'm going to read the
definition of this one for you oh your
word is
compliment a thing that contributes
extra features to something else in such
a way as to improve improve or emphasize
its
quality
compliment yeah compliment yeah how was
that
mean compliment that's you got this bi
boo you can do it compliment hold on I
don't want I don't want to a
compliment
oh if I get you get it
if I get this right will I get
complimented yeah yeah
okay compliment
[Music]
C
O
M compliment comp
P comp compliment compliment c o m
p
l
comp compliment
i
compl m e n
t all
right
parizer
uh
yes that's why was so important why
there's the word compliment and
complement you bu complement different
was helping you with that one she was
trying to help you out can I get a
compliment anyway you're so
cute thank
you wow I feel so much
better all right
me uh that's a good try though that's a
really good try uh it's confusing yeah
it
is I don't think I would have gotten
that either okay oh wait can I that's
what the spelling was oh sure c o m p l
e the chees compliments the
strawberries it's kind of a trick one
it's a little a little tricky I wonder
who put that one there
Bo's beautiful gray hair compliments
Mor's pink hair we look like we're from
the same
world a cute okay where we on next
contestant
let's
go all right ready I'm I'm
ready okay your word
is fed
[Laughter]
Genie oh my
god oh no I will never spell this right
f e
t p wait I have a a question yes do you
say fet or
fet how do you
sayy f
but f f I think it's kind of like the
same yeah okay
you
[Music]
c
c e no I I I sorry I want to say I
and and you say F in English yeah okay
so it's e
oh final
answer
yes go
what a coincidence that she's
Italian that's
[Laughter]
wrong all right nice job uh moving on to
our next
contestant ready I'm
ready
okay your word
is Callis
can you use it in a
sentence or definition I
can't I'll give
you showing or having an
intensive showing her having an
insensitive and cruel disregard for
others is it spelled the same way as the
one on your
foot c a l l o u
s final
answer okay oh Bango
Wow
nature all right nice that's
crazy uh just by the way chat I'm
dropping a little frames cuz my internet
but it should be okay um I think we're
good to move on thank you fa nice work
than you're nice all right
let's go let's go
then give me that
word okay why are you laughing all it's
a it's a your word
is
decaffeinated definition
please having had most or all of the
caffeine removed using a
sentence I can't believe kimori is
decaffeinated today all right I got this
I used to be a
barista d e c a
f come on
Barista
shut you got
it did you did you get my extra F oh
there we go okay e
i
n so you spell caffeine
right no one's going to help me
a
t e d
decaffeinated all right final answer
right I don't
know is that yes or no do you want to
use your
Lifeline no okay final answer no
yes
yes sorry I was double Che Bingo boingle
nice
[Music]
job that one was so
long it's medium medium round yeah
yeah about the caffeine spelling for a
bit I was like caffeine
I all right thank you Callie moving on
to our next
contestant ready
ready your word
is
scon uh definition
please a candle holder that is attached
to a wall with an ornamental bracket
[Music]
oh can you say the word again please
what
scon uh can you okay can you use in a
sentence
please the dinner is so beautiful
beautifully lit by that scon on the
wall wouldn't it be the candle on the
scon girl the scandle on the
scon thank you key thank you key got
you and double checking this is a noun
correct
yes I've never heard of this what the
who has candles on their walls I'm sorry
okay
scunt uh
SC o
n okay is it a c or is it an
s scon
s c o
n c
e okay final answer or Lifeline sure
that looks like a word Final
Answer nice
job I thought you said scone I was like
oh yeah I thought it was that too
Crossing help me animal
CR Animal Crossing nice good help
yeah all right so educating nice nice
nice we're going to go to our next
contestant but we're going to go this
way oh let's go oh God oh God oh God
okay we're changing oh wait actually no
no no wait wait wait wait uh we're going
to go this way okay we're
changing I have a question yes yes if I
lose this one am I dead is or is it like
one star and then one star is this like
over it's over uh judge judge uh any
thoughts in there um well we can see if
you survive the elimination process and
we can go from
there yeah so um I think uh yeah if you
lose it you're done but maybe you have
to use your Lifeline I'll use my
lifeline okay okay okay okay so I should
use my lifeline instead of risking it
okay yeah I think if I think you can't
die with your Lifeline like it we'll
just have to ask somebody else and then
uh if you lose that one then you die oh
okay okay like an extra hidden life in a
way cool thank you I'm ready
okay oh right sorry uh okay your word
is
brochure sure please use it in the
sentence
a small book or magazine containing
pictures and information about a product
or
service okay
h for sure u r e and now not final
answer now I will think if I should use
the live sure bro are you sure
[Laughter]
I think it looks right but it could also
be bro sure so if I use my lifeline now
then I still have my heart but if I lose
I lose my lifeline and my oh no I keep
my heart uh do you have
confidence
[Music]
um yeah
you're
surving you just so good yeah nice job
thanks all right our next contestant
cron let's
go ready
yeah hey ready okay your word is
elliptical a
what
elliptical uh
definition a low impact weightbearing
cardio workout that uses a stationary
machine to mimic walking stair climbing
or running
oh
okay come on bro you got this your to
the gy I mean I don't do that is the
thing okay uh maybe you should have okay
I'll
go e
l i don't know if it's double or not
um
l
[Music]
i p
t i c a l
elliptical okay fin
answer
yes oh take that very
nice nice I thought it was one
L yeah it's confusing oh this one you
know but not
comat oh
my all right hi I'm ready
okay okay yes yeah yeah yeah your word
is professional can you use it in a
sentence
uh I like the clown we hired he's really
professional I see okay well this one's
easy p r
o f
e SS
i o n l a
yeah what I'm sorry I Mard you no no you
heard it you heard her
wait sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry are you
kidding
me yeah yeah professional okay this has
to be your final answer yeah
that's way too easy but you can't spell
[\h__\h]
quad come quad I was going to spell it
in a way that I didn't want to spell it
on on stream I didn't want to do
that so you made fun to do
it Mama all right uh nice job next
contestant
[Music]
all right I'm not
confident okay be okay
right um mhm sprinkle I'm good for
sprinkle it's over for
sprinkles your word is
refrigerator
a okay oh oh wait oh okay I think I got
it re I'm thinking about the animals
inside of the
refrigerator
okay it makes sense okay listen listen
listen
refrigerator r e f r i d
g
a t o r refrigerator
all right is this your final answer
would you like to use your
Lifeline
refrigerator final
answer what there's no
refrigerator refrigerator
refrigerator what wait
refrigerator can we have this as the
official spelling though I like
refrigator there's animals in the fridge
you know sometimes they're
Gat put Gators in your fridge F nice try
nice
[Music]
try all right I like
refrigerator all right that's a good a
good effort though was pretty close all
right next
contestant greetings Fair maidens I am
here to redeem myself from my earlier
showing are you sure about that yes I am
sorry for suggesting such a evil thing
such as colluding
collusion I like the use of your seword
are you ready for another CW oh yes I I
am quite
quite your word is
conasur
connoisseur can I would you please could
you please you connoisseur in
sentence I am a connoisseur of orange
creatures oh she do be
oh H can I have the definition of
connoisseur
please an expert judge in matters of
taste oh so just like you I
see I I see I am I am quite ready to
spell c o NN con conoy conour of of Fine
Art o i s of a double cono cono s s e u
r final judge yes double s please can
you spell the rest again sorry e you
are all right
whoa Final
Answer there's a big brain in that
one kisur
kisur what dinosaur that coin kind the
theur
kind all right nice job uh G nice okay
our next
contestant yay yay let's finish this
round baby
yeah
ready bring it on your word is
spigot
what can you use it in the
sent uh and pronounced it
correctly excuse me ma'am I just
listened to Google say it and and they
said that I was correct
oh spigot spot
sentence no oh I'm a sentence Oh yes uh
please go to the spigot to fill up your
water
balloon uh uh
oh a
definition a small Peg or plug
especially for the insertion into the
vent of a
cask okay I've never heard of this
before I thought you mispronounced
spaghetti um okay can you say it again
one more
time spot
spot
H
uh uh lifeline please all right you like
to use your
Lifeline yeah choose your victim I mean
who would you like to give your Lifeline
too uh uh quason
please very solid
Choice oh wow she's excited about it I
am excited cuz I was like spaget that's
a meme
that's but but now I
know I am ready okay s p i g o t oh I
trust her I go with this
okay
nice
nice let's go all right perfect spelling
crony SP thank you
spaghetti all right you lost the
lifeline but uh at least you still your
lives yeah easy easy all right that was
the um second round uh the first round
of medium words I think we have some
more medium words and then it's going to
get a little bit harder here so
[Music]
uh all right back up to the top to our
anx
contestant are you
ready I'll do my best I don't have
confidence but I'll do my best
you got you can do
[Music]
it I
believe okay your word
is
pterodactyl
peroda that's so fun I don't like
dinosaurs
though what it's okay they're dead no
yeah they can be dead
welcome okay
p p e r
o d
a
see wait wait wait wait
wait
t y
l
pterodactyl right that's how you say it
right yeah it is final
answer okay final
answer to arrange the things in my brain
okay good job job nice job I love how
many words I'm just shocked that I would
spell wrong I thought it was
a I'm still stuck on
connoisseur yeah that was a
t all right our next contestant peo yeah
a you
[Music]
ready
okay uh okay your word
is
necessary
oh oh can you use it in the sentence
please
[Music]
uh I stubbed my toe I need a Band-Aid it
is
necessary like
that it's like free
sentences the compound
sentence give it a definition
please needed to be done achieved or
present I think it is necessary for for
me to use my
lifeline oh
okay who would you like to give your or
use your lifeline
on okay as you know I want to use my
Senpai tax
GG wa what if I spell it wrong on
purpose I I believe in you cuz you want
to play games with me right oh so if I
get this right you'll play games with me
forever yeah okay and
oh one second I am ready to spell J
ready she she said n o n e n o p just
kidding n e c
e s
s a r y it is necessary that you play
games with me now final
answer I play all the games of you G I
will never call you Senpai what do you
mean
oh no reason nothing wow all right nice
work beo with uh one her last life on
her last life no okay you're okay until
the next round yeah okay our next
contestant
yay all right ready I'm I'm ready okay
let's go
okay are you ready am I ready are you
ready okay are you ready are you ready
okay ready yeah your word
is
champagne
oh ooh okay
ah
champagne see
champagne
H
uh
e sh
shamp
m
p
e uh uh uh uh G like uh yeah
n
e I'm
Lancer
[Music]
yeah all right nice nice good job good
job
all right to
[Music]
now I'm
sweating Jud are you ready don't giggle
don't giggle give me an easy
one okay ready yes okay your word is
silhouette okay s i
l
h o
u e t t
e Final
Answer
damy nice speed running yeah okay nice
ice work Callie next yep throw it at me
I'm ready
okay all right I'm going to read you the
definition for this one okay okay
your word is
carrot a measure of the purity of gold
pure gold being 24
Karat can you use it in a
sentence my chain is so heavy because
it's 24 Karat bling bling of gold
[Laughter]
I think she's thinking are you goog
sorry oh my God I'm sorry I thought okay
push the talk I'm sorry k a r a t
carrot I said should I spell it again
everyone was dead
silent dead
silent a final answer the money on my
mind yes my final answer let's go nice
nice with
a yeah very close to karate but not
quite karate you used this word in one
of your lyrics no I haven't used it in
lyrics but I do know that it refers to
Gold you got to wait I thought carrot
was spell with the c yeah that's what I
thought that's for the one you munch
rabbit's munching no I thought it's c a
r
a apparently when when you're looking up
gold watches it says like 18K or
something like that
is Carrot like seeve with like different
gems what really
oh
wait
oh wait why why the
why all right don't question the judges
Okay Google says for exle would be C A
though for the definition itself was
confused cuz they used it both times
interchangeably so I don't know they
said one thing and they did another well
done EV right
so my goodness H it's you I think it's
UK uh uh United States difference so
United States is K and that's what I
found at least only seen it with a c
yeah me too both exist both ex
wow okay see okay it's too late she got
it right let's go
[Music]
wow I'm learning as we're streaming this
is
great give me my word okay okay your
word is
exquisite Divine [\h__\h] I'm
sorry uh can I get a definition
please extremely beautiful and
delicate in a sentence
please this rat is exquisite a than
thanks mate I just wanted that all right
Exquisite
e
x exqu
q ex
i s i
t
e Exquisite Final
[Music]
Answer nice
okay but this is just Divine exquisite
exquisite
marous marvelous tell you morous all
right on to our next
contestant I'm waiting ready
okay your word is
doppleganger oh no you can do it you can
do it can you say it in uh uh in a
sentence
[Music]
please Jud oh should I do it okay um
wait what was it oh
doppelganger
uh uh bit is My
Doppelganger okay um okay I'll
try
d o p
p e
e
l
g a n g
n g dou gang e r dou ganger D ganger D
Ginger dble D okay yeah Final Answer
final
answer okay
[Music]
so what happens now
judge I guess uh uh I get to shoot my
stops
spinning
ohel she cannot spin anymore what was
what's the correct spelling Oh e it's l
e l e like this right oh I see okay I
thought you were so close what wait what
I thought wait wait what
no no no
no think about the accent or something
that's why it was wrong I'm pretty sure
yeah yeah it's e l and there's an accent
either on o or a it's on the a a I
thought we didn't do accents since this
is yeah I think that's only if it's
actually German no in English spelling
double will be without the accents
yeah okay I guess we to accept if you
spell it in English it's with a
e that's what I thought was the wrong
thing I'll get my pencil I'll pencil in
my CH a e instead
of all right uh I guess free star bag
yeah we'll give you your star bag I
don't think I away I like a free star
back too we should
get wait so was it wrong I'm so confused
oh God you're right you were right you
were right you're still in I live you
live
[Applause]
okay thank you you're thank you I
honestly thought it was did the judges
get Stars can the judges lose
Stars yeah no no okay we do have stars
down here but you guys can't take
them we paid a lot oh yeah is that a is
that a threat yeah you guys have like
five stars eat them we we have a gun
okay so stay
back okay
yeah all right next contestant crony
hey I'm ready I love how she rizes when
it's her
turn
Okay one second Amy can you distract for
a second yes um how's it
going how's it like up there it's pretty
Breezy actually we get the AC's right
above us so it's uh you it's actually a
little cold what what about down there
we have it's getting pretty hot actually
can I turn on the AC here's your AC yeah
okay thank
you you want some to do you want some to
no it's I'm good I'm good I'm good I'm
good I'm good judge judge are we
ready I'm ready all right we're
ready
okay okay your word
is
arelo
[Music]
ah AR a r c h
i
h
archipelago
P was it a e or E God damn it a r c h
i I'm going to go
insane you can do
it use
feeling what's up feeling I don't have
feelings ar
ar
okay e i don't
oh e okay not like I can change it l a g
o
oh it's
okay final answer okay final answer I
don't
know wow good
[Applause]
job what a big brain you did so good
you're the goat you did really good yeah
to be honest I think you guys are doing
better than we expected we might have to
go into a sudden death round you know we
don't want to here too long but uh we'll
continue for
now what is that word what is it what is
it mean help yeah judge uh you want you
want to defition a it's a group of
islands yeah yeah islands oh yeah we're
learning okay I'm learning I'm learning
this a learning stream this is a
educational it
is all right did you change the category
of the yeah I
did my turn again let's
go I'm all ready when you are
Judges okay your word is preposterous
Preposterous could you please tell me
the definition of the
word contrary to reason or common sense
utterly absurd or ridiculous contrary to
reason or common sense I think I typed
this twice absurd or ridiculous I see so
it's me all right uh this should be easy
right uh P pre p r
e POS
hostus p o s
t
Preposterous e r o u s
Preposterous that's my final answer are
you
sure are you sure it's not Preposterous
yeah I'm pretty sure it's Preposterous
Preposterous it's correct it's correct
nice job
very nice my God that was
difficult all right F you
ready I'm going to do my best no
refrigerators
please okay your word is
ACAA H can you say that again
please
ACAA
acan AAA AA can I have it as a a
definition my favorite oh wait never
mind I thought you said
sentence a tree of warm climates which
Bears spikes or clusters of yellow or
white flowers and is typically thorny
who's typing
a I see could I have it in a sentence
please uh heos Bale's favorite Minecraft
tree is
a good good times memories that's what
you're talking about it took me
forever ah well then I'm going to use my
life line and I'm going to ask
B
yeah pleas so by my life is in your paws
now yes um
how do you pronounce sorry
AIA how do you how do you pronounce
it'sa is I still haven't learned it's
been two years I still a AC
AC a wait sorry one more time I got
confused wa wait no that's right a c a c
i a
aaia are you
sure you doubting your Senpai right now
there's not extra season it and like
surprising no I can see you okay I'll
age with b and by because I trust him
fully with my life forever and ever all
right Final Answer
[Music]
wooo this was 2 years redemption in the
making thank you so
much all right nice job paa or ba rather
thank you thank you yeah as a team
please remember
this all right to our next
contestant
uh give it to me my next word my my fair
lady I'm scared to say this word I don't
know how to say this word okay will you
send it to
me just writing it on my hand oh okay I
epitome epitome can I have epitome in a
sentence please I suddenly came to a
realization you could call it an epitome
wait wait I think I'm it wrong
epiphany epiphany no no
epitome which epitom EP
um this stream is the epitome of Comedy
thank epom or epiphany
the word just so that we're sure which
one we
using definition please wait was that a
definition or sentence that was a
sentence Oh okay definition
please a person or thing that is a
perfect example of a particular quality
or type yes yes the stream the epitome e
p i t o m e
epitome final answer
[Music]
y
nice
[Music]
epep guys
me last contestant of the medium round
we're going into hard
mode are you ready yeah
um okay contestants every one of
you shut
up okay your word
is
compliment
definition a polite expression of Praise
or admiration c o m p l i m e n wait
slow down can you do one more
time c o m p l i m e n t
one more time of course final answer
you're going too fast one more time what
oh
what yeah NT at the end nt Okay do you
have an extra e at
that what no are you sure c o m p l i m
e n
t absolutely sure yeah yeah yeah 100%
yeah of
course I'll I'll I'll I I know this word
it's easy
okay I was hoping you I was hoping
nobody would go into the other
compliment one and then I'd be able to
get you on a Goa but I couldn't get you
on a how could it be that when it we
already had that word because everybody
everybody they pulled apart my my
scheme they pointed out the different
the different ones bambo no no no no
a super hard one next time yeah give me
a hard well we are going into hard mode
now
guys get ready all right hold on let me
DJ really quick we're going to change
this into hard mode
song whoa oh no all
right let's go to our first contestant
of heart around
[Music]
how about I I I I want to survive I want
to I want to live you want that trophy
right you got this I want to
live oh my your live more than the
trophy your word is
discombobulate soor
what discombobulate oh my gosh
definition to confuse someone or make
someone feel uncomfortable
huh
sentence
Army well I can use it in past tense
like oh I'm feeling very discombobulated
right now that's accurate the judges are
trying to discombobulate you yeah I'm
always
discombobulated you can do it okay I'm
going to you got the M trying to think
okay b i s
this this c o
m b o
b
u l a
t
e Final
Answer
not yes no maybe I should use my
star cuz then I can make it somebody
else's fault huh yeah use it use it yeah
use it use
it maybe okay I'm going to use my my my
special star okay you sure who's going
to be my special star then who do you
want to give it
to
um no she knows the same stuff I
do good idea no it's a blue star it's
got to go to
[Music]
for be
boy what
yes I trust you
be what is the word again
what this combobulate it was at this
second Moco knew she [\h__\h] up I trust
we would
this oh yes okay I will do my
best
d
i this discom disc compul d i s
c this
discombobulate
discombobulate this c o
m
b o this
b
[Music]
u late l a t e this is the same spelling
I spell oh well I I think it's that must
be wrong that's my
conclusion oh
we'll go down together I
guess okay go down together together
only she only lose a life we won't lose
a life so yeah final answer
though answer
yeah my eyes you're so good at spelling
yeah nice job
nice
nice fail you you didn't fail me before
I love you but you didn't fail yourself
either this
come all right you warmed up B boo
oh can I just have that
no it's your turn now and you don't have
a Lifeline
anymore okay all right don't mess it up
Bab
okay uh your word is
randevu
R oh oh it's French I know this it's
French um can but I'll ask anyway
I just
like sentence use a sentence
[Music]
pleasey let's meet at the R Vu
Point okay oh I'm so glad I took
friendch
r e n d Ronde
rondy
e z and Vu v o u s RI vu all right final
answer yes Final
[Music]
Answer
y r
mer all right nice job people moving on
ni nice
nice all right let's go okay your word
it
is
fuchsia
fut
fuchia uh a
definition a vivid purplish red color
like that oh of the Petals of a typical
fuchsia flower okay
f
u
c
s i
he all right no more Lifeline so this
must be your final answer
yes
yeah so close oh so
CL what is the correct
spelling f u c h s i a
oh damn it so
close it's so
close this
is yeah it's tough It's pretty hard it's
okay you still have one life left go
yeah you still have one life left yes
it's okay you're still in it Mama it's
okay
all right moving on to the next
contestant
FAA okay let's
go I'm
ready
okay your word
is
sacriligious do I know how to spell this
s a c
r
e
l
i j
g o us
s final
[Music]
answer no I thought for sure that was it
yeah me too
sacriligious s a c r i l e g i o
u
e that's tough you know that does look
look much more correct hard
yeah all right nice try we lose a card
this
round okay moving on to C
I'm ready I will prove my existence Here
and Now by not asking for the definition
of the word or for the word in a
sentence let's go
sure okay well if I need the definition
because there's different spellings then
please give me the
definition your word
is hemorrhoid are you kidding
me this randomizer is great isn't it
it's not a randomizer she's picking on
me no I'm not all right you know what
don't don't ask how I know how to spell
this word okay h e m o r r h o i d s
sorry
singular you go slow huh no no
s you're not going to trip me up she
wants you to start over you went too
fast for her oh my
God the
word hemor ho
s h e
m
o r r and it's not
plural h o
i
d I should have asked her to use it in a
[Music]
sentence planal
answer
wait you use your
[Music]
Lifeline no I don't trust
anyone you know what you don't trust me
no it's not like that well not any of us
all
right
but no I no it's because I love you I
don't want to give you this word all
right yeah this is the final answer okay
final answer
ni all right nice job
Callie thanks sorry moving on oh scared
all right
B let's all right
ready okay your word is
ambidextrous God damn it Ambi am amby
dextrous and
be M dextrous um
a
m
midex
ambidextrous ambidextrous a am
ambidextrous r o u s
and be dextrous final
answer
yay no
nope
ambidextrous oh
damn we're going to do this people this
last round and then we're going to do
sudden and death round cuz I know we've
been keeping you guys here for a while
and then we'll find out who the is from
uh our sudden death
round all right no no Lifeline calls
um uh yeah you can use uh no not in
sudden death you can't use lifelines but
still for the rest of this round
contestants can still use their Lifeline
all
right
ready yeah
okay your word
is
Halo what can you say that again please
halloon can you use it in a
sentence Oh uh what's all this
holoo
God I got this can you give me a
definition
please a commotion or a
fuss okay can you say it one last time
halalu Halu Hal halalu Hal Hal okay I
would like to use my lifeline okay who
will you use your Lifeline with okay no
one said anything while we were talking
so I don't know if anyone knows
this silence was so loud yeah why was
everyone So Silent all of a
sudden Hal Hal okay GG take it away do
it for me please help me help me what if
I get it wrong and kill you help me I
trust you okay what is all this Holo
about H
hullabaloo I am ready to spell judges
okay we're ready stand behind me kitten
watch How Daddy spells this word h u l l
you have to admit I am daddy after this
or I'm feeling it
wrong
[Music]
agree agree
animation is nodding I okay he's
rding
hey
e h Balo
a oh oh
oh all right Halo Final Answer Final
Answer Halo I trust her kitten in woo
y thank you father thank
you all right nice
job let's go to our next
contestant
cron gron dad all right
ready no too
bad going
toate gry hello
gronie hello how are you not good oh
yeah how's the
weather hurry just end me okay here's
your
word your word
is
Aqueduct oh oh a q u a d e c
t
wait holy
heck wait no why did I say that so
confidently
no what the heck is wrong with me oh my
God why did I just say
that no no no no no no no no no no
no do you want it well you know what
yeah you know what I think I need to cuz
after this round we're not going to be
able to use the blue star anyway right
yeah yeah yeah okay I want I want oh
yeah yeah
yo please please please please please y
I know this a q u e d u c
t it's made with duct tape duct
tape Final
Answer yeah
yeah
really oh oh she decides
you know you know what I trust trust
okay whatever yeah let's
[Music]
go
Al all right moving on to our next
contested hi hi no Lifeline for you huh
yeah okay
ready good okay here's your
word der
a
derer what did you say can you define it
for
me euphemistic term for a person's
buttox oh NOA yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah uh d e
r
derer is it
French
r
i
[Music]
e very sound fren R
E I
think final ENT yeah I guess so
[Music]
nice
there there
[Applause]
[Music]
is all right that's a butt nice work
like butt yeah yeah it's your butt butt
so many
but randomize guys yes randomize random
is all right for
ready po I'm scared
hi
scared I'm not scared I'm H I'm GNA do
my
best
okay your word
is
affidavit o what is that
nice can I get a definition
please a written statement confirmed by
oath or affirmation for use as evidence
in
court oh usually David writes this could
I get uh in a sentence
please oh man please oh yes uh I must
get this affidavit signed before
registering so it has nothing to do with
amphibians no no it doesn't
he sorry what was that it starts with
the
E are you saying e or a an a
a
ah
f
ala
alpha
alpha is it an a is it an e is it an i
ala I it's
I
Al ala David is that how you say it
could you say it again for me please
Alid David Alpha David David David Alid
David Aid a aidid Aid how do you spell
Aid h a could you say it once more
please a
could you say it slower once more please
spell
[Music]
it D please
a a
[Music]
f
t all right it's very fluffy lots of FS
yeah f for
fuaa and F for final answer because you
have no lifelines and this is your last
life close so never use that word I
don't need an alpha David Alpha David
oh yes the correct spelling alha
David I think
[Music]
it's you think you don't know
it a v i g there we
go close that was difficult I was close
though deser to St is getting away huh
oh
no no now it is time our first
contestant is out officially you know
what that means I have to shoot my gun
yeah well no we have this button
remember oh that's right I forgot about
that yeah I wonder what this button does
can you make it bigger uh okay make it
like really
big okay cool
I wonder what it does want to do the
honors you don't need
to I'm going to do it I'm going to do
it push push it push it
[Music]
[Applause]
byebye fire it keep going
perect Eternal torture oh
no see all of these in the end well all
right going to happen all yeah that's
going to burn forever yeah I guess
so Eternal Flame she the right she
should be okay yeah yeah that's true no
I'm even more intimidated yeah I don't
want to die I'm too beautiful to die
well death round is coming soon so we
all face it yeah okay GG ready hello
judges I am prepared for my next word
but there is a burning flaa next to me
really we need you to good motivation I
feel like my job performance is going to
go much more
down she's beginning to G you have no
risk of dying you have everything yeah
okay I'm I am ready for the word
[Music]
judges
okay your word
is
biopharmaceutical is that a two-parter
it's one word that is a word one word
can I have the word again please
biopharmaceutical iio pharmaceutical iio
pharmaceutical I
pharmaceutical can I have the definition
please oh
I'm sorry I had
that a biological macromolecule or
cellular component such as a blood
product use as a
pharmaceutical sentence please of
biopharmaceutical you want to take this
one Jud I specialize in the study of
biop
pharmaceuticals plural yes do you
suppose you do in the usage of
biopharmaceuticals that we can bring
fuaa back to
life
um
good but she looks so
perfect that's I know I know from the
judges oh okay okay I am ready to spell
I am prepared all right the word is biof
Pharmaceuticals one word p i o
bio Pharmaceuticals
p h
a r
m biof
farmaceutical biop
Pharmaceuticals
a CE EU u c
c
EU and then
tickle t i
c a l s are you taking yourself one more
time stop tickling yourself I'm
tickling t i c a l s plural okay we'll
make it
plural I am
finished waiting for the judges to
review
yes y shoot
nice this Gamlin can spell yeah call me
the
spell auto spell the spell all right I'm
going to send you some things to spell
check from here on out GG oh
no I'll do
anything ready last words this yes okay
what might it possibly
be okay your word is
luminescence oh luminescence can you
define it please the emission of light
by a substance that has not been heated
that's what I thought l u
m i n
e
uh luminent s c
e n
luminous wait
luminous can I oh can
I luminous ah no luminous sense luminous
sense see hi yes all right let's check
H how can you not spell Rhode Island but
you can spell luminescence because I B
of roads I don't know
sorry I mean I mean ask M she cannot
spell codependency but
pterodactyl okay okay I just messed up
okay what is the this Bobble yeah this
you
he did spell it right actually the first
time all right so that was confidence
hard round yeah confidence is key and
confidence we're deleting our blue
stars yes no more blue stars let's take
those off except for the people who to
get some at the yellow stars they stay
yeah uh yeah well it's de in dead so I
don't think it matters anyways yeah if
you die you're dead yes oh no that's
nice oh my God there's going to be so
much flame on the screen let's go fire
fire like that fire fire fire not my
fire all right so sudden death um it's
let's let's explain this uh we kind of
yeah we did work this out so your guys's
word you are going to spell a very long
word and whoever gets the furthest in
the correct spelling of the word gets
added uh to their current points which
uh we will have to uh calculate at the
end but um yeah do you do you guys have
any questions do you get it we're we're
going to spell a long word and uh you're
going to get as many points as far as
you can get well do you spell it
together at the same time no we're going
to go down the line one by one and uh
kind of like speed run this a bit Yeah
is it the same way for everybody it's
the it it's going to be the same word
for
everybody okay can we do a random order
uh
everyone will learn from my my correct
answer okay sure uh why don't I'll pull
up a randomizer really quick and then
it'll be truly random one second you
guys can uh we can have them what if we
have them mute and then
only yeah only
the that's nice all right uh don't mute
in
Ord but wait how how do we know when we
can mute uh don't worry we're going to
move into another Channel and then uh
yeah we'll take the contestant in there
all right oh smart we'll start backwards
this time since we've been going forward
so we're going to start with
kiaha yeah all right kiaha jump in this
Channel with
us okay where are we
going all right don't worry guys we're
still
here and so is K Mushy Mushy I have a
feeling I'm like I know what word you're
going to go for really but surprise me
please okay we're just waiting for judge
G to get in here yeah can't do it
without her after
all sorry hello sorry hello hello hello
hello okay so the word is uh do you
remember what that long I do remember I
do okay so going to focus on on spelling
and then I'll focus on uh like writing
it down here okay mhm all right try your
best all right Kiara so the word is
super califragilistic
Expialidocious I thought
so do I get to see you writing it down
there yes yes
okay ready can you say the word again
super califragilistic xalid docious how
many times can I ask you in between to
repeat that um three times done okay
none three times we're done wait only
then no more yeah just one more time one
more time before you start spelling is
fine but not Dury okay all right super
califragilistic XP
alidocious
XP
[Music]
x i I can't see the screen yet oh sorry
okay super frag
x uh uh just watch my spelling try to
compare it in real time and then do the
if it
if yes yes yes
[Music]
yeah you're not going to show me the
screen yes here we go ah okay I see it
super califragilistic XP dois okay all
right here we go uh s u p e
r c a l i
super uh
f r a
g i l
i s
t uh
I uh C but this is where it gets
difficult
h
[Music]
xious e XP
xious
XP
xedos can't be
xedos uh we're going to run a timer on
this
uh
uh uh exp
uh super Calif fragilistic xia that
sounds weird super cal fragilistic XP
you got 30 seconds my
God d
[Music]
a
uh exp l i
c oh oh oh well it's probably wrong
anyway can I go back one no okay it's
over okay this where you stop yeah just
stop there okay all right we will take
note of this and tally the score at the
end yeah yeah I'm I'm a phoenix I can go
up in flames and just come back it's
fine it's fine yeah okay will you send
um whoever was next to you uh G okay
I'll send the other orange one bye
byebye
byebye and now we wait should we give
them like 90 seconds yes okay
you want to time
it or I'll no I'll time it I'll time it
okay yeah I got it I am here Fair judges
hello all right hello so we can repeat
the word as many times as you like
before we start but during your spelling
we cannot repeat it okay I'm happy that
I don't smell burning anymore oh yeah
it's burning fur my faor yay
yummy okay so you have 90 seconds to uh
get as far as you can okay okay all
right so the word is super Calif
fragilistic X
alidocious I won my third grade spelling
be with this word really oh w w I would
sing this song but I don't want to get
you guys in trouble I am ready to spell
okay you have a minute and 30 seconds
starting when you start
s u p e r
Super Callie c a l
i oh no no a there c a l i fragile f
r a g i
l
istic i s t
i
c
XP e
[Music]
xpi Oh e XI
Ali
a
l
i noes b o c i oh us super
frous
okays nice all right we're going to save
this in our records and calculate and
get back to you after we do the rest
thank you fair judges very nice job
thank you oh could you send whoever was
next to you oh oh besides fuaa who was
after fua and cron crony all right can
you say crony in here please I will
summon her thank you farewell
farewell oh my god
wow I'm learning how to use an she in
real time hello hello is it is it my
turn or is it Cron's it's your turn
sorry hello hi so you have 90 seconds to
spell this word as much as you can and
uh we can say it as many times as you
want before we start but during spelling
we cannot repeat it okay what is the
word super califragilistic xad
docious
oh okay let's just let's go all right
ready yep time begins now s u p e r uh
califra k k no no no sorry not k c a l i
fragilistic f r a
g
i uh l i
s t t i c super
califragilistic XP alidocious ah e x p x
[Music]
p i a l XP
alidocious uh um sorry I'm thinking my
brain XP
alidocious
X
XP uh i d o c i
o u
s I think
all right sorry it was supposed to be on
the screen but uh I was focused on
typing I didn't realize no no no problem
all right this looks pretty good though
I think he did a good job thank you I
try my best uh job all right we will
save this and
love yeah it's a good
musical yeah okay good luck great work
today judges I'll send
in yes please thank you thank you byebye
bye
I couldn't spell this word to be quite
honest with
you I think I would mess up towards the
end I
mean
[Music]
Hello so for this sudden death you have
to try to get as far as possible in the
spelling of this word you have 90
seconds we can say it as many times as
possible uh before you start spelling
but during spelling we will not say it
again
okay
any the word is Super califragilistic X
alidocious oh uh s u p e r c c a l i
Fred f r a g i l i s t i c e x e e x p i
a uh L
ious uh d o c i o u
s all right thank you wow that took you
30 seconds okay we will
uh but yeah to do it again you're good
you're
good all right thank you crony okay
super cal fragilistic does y can you
send in slay yeah is that right uh we're
going to calculate yeah we're going
toate okay gr okay bye
byebye wait does she know to send in
uh oh uh I think they know I think they
get
it I think it's Cece Cece okay oh hello
hi hello hello can I can I watch The
Stream again is the word gone yes okay I
am watching well okay I'm watching so
the word is uh oh so we'll tell you the
word you have 90 seconds to spell it as
much as you can
90 and uh we can't repeat it while
you're spelling and yeah are you
ready yeah you can do it okay so the
word is Super califragilistic X
alidocious can you say it again super
califragilistic xad dois super CIF
fragilistic EXP
docious okay ready okay I'm starting
okay timer starting
now s u p e r
Super c a k l
super I
super f r Super CIF f r a
g
i this doesn't look right super
cifi l i
s t
i super
fragilistic
xous e
x p XP XP Alle XP e a x
listic
XP
i d o c i o u s super frati
xous all right that's a good try yeah oh
good good good job we're going to
calculate it after we get everybody so
if you could send in the next uh okay
who was um who was the next the one uh
oh ba ba ba okay bye thank you thank
you I'm saying it right right I hope I'm
[Music]
saying H hello hello I think so well not
really hello hello hello hello here so
sudden death round we are going to give
you a word and you have 90 seconds to
try to spell it as much as you can okay
all right the word is super
califragilistic XP
alidocious all righty here we go you
ready uh I had a 30
33% chance of I thought it was this word
all right I'm ready all right timer
starting now super s p e r Super cie C A
l i sorry Super C cie frag f r a
g
frag
fragilistic
I frag l i
fragile s i c fragilistic
XP ex
ex ex ex ex p uh super cal fragilistic x
p p
i XP
Al XP
Al wait Super Color fragilistic XP l a
l Super Color fragilistic XV l l
i and I remember was
decious d i
super cal fragilistic XP Aly
do wait
do wait 10
seconds do
oous D oh wait
wait o u
s okay all right thank you we will use
this and calculate if you could send in
please
[Music]
call I the screenshot
oops hey
hello hello all right I'm I'm back
welcome back so you have 90 seconds to
spell this word as far as you can go M
and we're going to calculate your points
based off that all right M so the word
is super califragilistic XB alidocious
oh my God this is the easiest one all
right whenever you're ready I'll start
the timer go okay let's start okay here
we go s u p e
r c a l
i f r a g i
l i s t i
c e x p
i a l
[Music]
i d
o
c i o u s supercal fragilis to xous oh
thank you sorry we're went have to
screen a little bit okay I think that's
it we going to use this to calculate if
you could send in the person next to you
all right they're not going to tell me
okay who's next um who was next to you
uh was it or AA yes okay fauna right
I'll a fa thank you thank
you a few more left oh my good and then
we'll know hello
hello all right you have 90 seconds to
spell this word as much as you can and
we going to use that to uh calculate
your points okay all right so the word
is Super califragilistic X
[Music]
alidocious uh S U wait wait wait wa wait
sorry sorry okay all right we'll start
in the timer and no let's go sorry s u p
e r c a
l l i
f r Super l
a g
i l
i c
i
o u s Calif frag delicious
exp uh foral frag delicious X
exp
i x p a l
i
d Cal delicious XP l oh that looks wrong
we go with it
okay d
o sh how do you spell sh
sh c i o u
s okay all right we send it send it all
right thank you we use
this wait who's next oh uh who was next
to you was it uh
ra yes yes please send okay thank
you I'm going to need help with that one
I don't know what happened in that I I
have I have a screenshot of it we'll
take a little bit of time to calculate
oh
hello
hello he okay so for this sudden death
round
uh we are giving you 90 seconds to try
to spell this word as much as you can
okay and uh all right so the word is
super califragilistic xalid
docious super super cut you know there
is day Talent version of this which is
similar but different so I'm I need to
concentr okay when you're ready are
you can you can you say it again super
Calif fragilistic
exposis
yes
s okay u p e
r c a
s p e not t i
sorry uh
c
e super super
[Music]
fragil can you say it again
sorry super cal fragile
xous X
he
yeah
XP
[Music]
i
a
d oh
[Music]
uh
c
i
[Music]
o oh sorry we R out a time okay okay
that's fine you got pretty far though
nice job
sh thank you all right can you send in
uh who is next youo I think okay B yeah
thank you
okay all right pretty far F yeah I think
this is like as far as I would get
probably
hello hi don't look at that okay hi all
right so we're going to give you 90
seconds to spell this word and get as
far as you can so last night I practiced
three long words I hope it's one of them
okay well the word is super
califragilistic exid docious PR for this
I did okay wa wait wait one second let
me start the timer ready ready okay here
we
go okay super uh s u p e r uh Callie c a
l i
FR f r a g i l istic i s t i c fragile
is fragilistic XP ales
uh e x p i a l i
x dois d o c i o u s done wait sorry uh
I I got lost somewhere after
here the end this D okay
o c i o u
s okay
thank you nice yeah looks good all right
we'll use this to calculate if you could
sent in send in moreo please okay thank
you
[Music]
we did we see fuaa am I like losing my
mind oh she remember she's on fire oh my
God that's right
okay
I'm I'm last H yeah you're the last one
want okay no pressure no pressure no
pressure really are you sure yeah I mean
you know a little bit yeah I'm either
first or last time sorry pressure it is
a lot of pressure and uh more pressure
because you have a timer you're going to
be timed what for 90 seconds we're going
to give you a word and you're going to
try to spell it as long as you can um
until the end or until the timer runs
out okay so I'll do my best good luck
the word is super califragilistic XP
alidocious ah question before we start
the timer can I ask you to say it again
one more time like a different later
time not maybe right now not during
spelling you
can't okay can you say it again and then
I'll start okay Super califragilistic X
alidocious okay I will start okay super
s u p e r
c c a l l
i fragile f r a g i l
e sorry
what g i l e Licious as in delicious l i
c i o u
s super cal frag delicious
s s e s p
i that's all I
remember okay that's pretty good yeah
you're
all we're going to use this to calculate
thank you did I I get the full word uh
maybe
mm you want to add more letters
can you say it again no
no no I can't remember what the rest of
it
was okay well well we are going to use
Stars that's going to it's going to help
you that you have a star left yeah so
we'll see we'll calculate it okay all
right could you tell everybody to wait
while we deliberate and then uh we'll be
back we'll do byebye
bye all right hello
hello okay we're we're finally done with
the sudden death
round oh my goodness my brain
is all right so let me ask chat chat um
I did read the I did read what you guys
were saying while I was typing out faas
did I misread what she said or mishar
what she said was there anybody that oh
FAA had an extra
eye I see it okay
so okay what I did for this is because
we had a handful of people that
literally spelled it perfectly yeah is
it
just we get they're like what do we do
with that we have cuz oh sudden death
okay my my idea was that we take their
stars and we use it as like a multiplier
and then uh we multiply with how many
stars they had left for
example ah yeah if we take look here fua
oh no Moko had one star biu has one star
VA has one star FAA has one star CI has
two stars B has two stars waa has uh oh
sorry uh CeCe has one star crony has two
stars Nissa two stars Gigi two stars and
um huahua two
stars okay yeah so we we'll use that
yeah chat is already saying but uh okay
so let me let me take a picture of this
sorry guys we're going to figure this
out if you don't mind if I can grab
this should they be listening to us or
should they be listening to the group
yeah uh okay we'll go back to the group
and then you we'll have them chat and
then we'll we'll we'll calculate it in
our DFS okay welcome back oh okay
okay all wrong anyway
so hello
hello all right so we're we're still
deciding on to winner if you guys don't
mind just uh you guys can chat here for
a little bit you could just killing who
you know for sure is not the winner so
we can see their cute their cute fire
start shooting flames we're not ready
yet to start shooting but we will just a
moment so uh I will be right back okay
in the chat please is no one going to
put fuaa out no forever
Bur hell fire bow B
sad every time it zooms into her you
just hear
[Laughter]
like she's just so close I can smell her
we should make M mugle John imitate fuaa
scream you you scream
like I can't cuz I'm
more I believe in you you can do an
imitation
I can I can tell you how she bow bows
but I can't tell you how she screams can
you tell us how she bow bows we miss her
voice
[Music]
B how would you how would you scream if
you were on
fire that's probably how she
screaming let's go down the line and
hear everyone
screams bi boo what how would you scream
if you were on fire oh um
yay
yay a
[Laughter]
li H I would do if I have to be
happy no no you're burning you're on
fire why would you be
happy because I'm hot I'll be happy if I
was hot oh thank you it's a bit too hot
don't you
think uh
well I'll do
like yeah that's more like
it or or oh my God yes I'm smoking
hot go go go
[Music]
go and for not come come extinguish my
my fire
and oh my
good someone
have she'd throw it at her
no show me your fiery scream fa okay if
I was on fire it would probably go like
this you are my brother Anakin I love
you I hate
you you were the chosen one F you were
supposed to save the something not
destroy it she is the most flammable out
of everybody are you flammable death me
I love fire okay well scream for
me
ah she sounds like she's enjoying it
everybody's worn out from spelling we
got to bring the energy one character
voice
ah someone help her someone help her
she's in pain fire really
that make it
worse well surely surely chaos will
bring the energy with a fiery
scream this is s you're burning yeah
you're burning you're on fire like fuaa
is you're inflamed I'm not caffeinated
enough of
this she is
decaffeinated no I am caffinated
just I haven't got any coffee yet had
one I hope B burning one meme with like
Elmo like raising his hands to the sky
and his behind him oh yeah I know what
you're talking about yeah God I love El
I used to rewatch Elmo's uh what was it
the interview with Rover over and over
again Rover
over he has no R right no no you don't
know send Bale's hios over that one no
not Rover sorry on
Ro no wait you guys don't know ro oh my
goodness isn't that the trash
dude Rover oh okay no idea who Rover is
then who's Rover I think you're talking
about Grover no it's
Rove it's Rover no it's Grover Grover
sounds more it's Grover it's Ro gr gr oh
no wonder you guys don't know it it's an
Australian late night talk show I was
like no it's definitely
Ro it's an aussy thing sorry Oscar is
the trash yeah just down under
things judges you got
it I ain't they still working CeCe
scream next CeCe going back
the time oh ill calculating almost
finished oh that's pretty good I have a
question what happens if you burn when
you're not wind up like what's going to
happen well the thing is this was method
acting I actually don't feel I'm very
durable we've been on stream this entire
time I thought we were
muted God damn it thank God he didn't
say anything weird sorry I didn't
know no no I
I was trying to not be bad dead on
stream no wonder I thought you guys were
just streaming screaming for fun I was
like wow you guys have so much energy
I'm not
caffeinated we've been witnessing you
all along Bae oh no you witness scream
scream scream
[Music]
Bae thank you that was
someone not that was nice thank you
crazy surprised that Discord didn't mute
that well yeah thank you thank I was
trying to not be that dead on stream
I've been
exposed wait how long have we been on
stream the whole time 3 hours
[\h__\h] sorry we're almost done we're
almost done ever since they came back
yeah oh I
see it's okay all right crony you're
trying to scream
who me yeah yeah yeah oh okay oh blood
curdling or something blood
curling
oh oh my God is she okay oh my gosh that
was
impeccable if you ever in trouble it's
good I'll be
saved yeah who turn I results so
shouldn't we uh just one more minute and
we'll have the results sorry okay I
think it's still they're still
calculating sorry that's a long
word
yeah did my scream cut out yeah did you
scream scream again um one more can you
oh my God it did it get cut out again
are you actually screaming yeah are you
screaming oh she's tricking us oh yeah I
think I see she's trying see it's
cutting out what a nice
I can't believe an ice
cream we heard we
heard we
heard almost done I can't wow it's
okay okay I'm going to turn down my mic
a little bit so it sounds like I'm
screaming from another room and I'm on
fire okay you guys have to save me
that's the plot okay okay
okay she's probably
fine she's okay
fine
prob
sand I feel compelled to call the
police thank you well it's Kiara's she's
fine okay good can I get a countdown
three two
one ah not
again a because she's aen
[Applause]
for
it I love how it took us a couple
seconds the hesitation with I knew I
want to make it more intense you know
she gets
it uh I have a question for K Senpai
yeah what um when are you like when you
get burned like how does it work I
revive no yeah like but how like when
when when that happens every now and
then or it happened before uh uh in my
first year in whole life how long did it
take maybe a few hours until I was back
oh so not very long yeah I turn and then
I revive could you imagine burning every
single month burning to
death do you feel pain does it hurt a
snake
uh well it doesn't hurt me it would hurt
you guys for sure so don't try it at
home kids don't try it at home her
nerves are all singed off already from
the fire I have another
question yeah you want to know how we
make babies with phoenixes no no no I
have a question when you burn when you
burn what happens to your clothes and
what happen when when you reir are you
nak are you asking this to like dry it
afterwards you should because well the
cloes are gone and I'm just like NY and
I need
I
oh yeah yeah maybe you should maybe
should dra draw it I don't know to keep
it in your
memory were you born from an egg Kiara
Okay I uh no um my debut stream lore is
actually inaccurate I was uh even though
I drew it I was not born from an egg um
I see I mean we're all an egg in a way a
way in ways I don't lie eggs I I uh I
lay eggs I I only sit on them
occasionally I
see why are you sitting on other
people's
eggs because weird no no I'm I'm
bringing chicken eggs to life who don't
have any other chicken to sit on them so
I'm you know I'm helping them
out ni yeah that's how I build my whole
cult around me when you burn and then
you come
I didn't
mean I told you I told you all nobody
listened that's fine my ears didn't
deceive me I definitely heard cold no no
no no no no no no uh I mean I meant uh
my I that's how I build uh my uh yeah
cult yeah okay that's yeah that's what
it was I can't cult confirmed cult
confirmed 4 years later wow already here
thir oh no I meant Club I meant club
club you said Club no Club sorry she
just pronounced it strangely you know
English is second language right so fine
don't
worry for the
safe no one in whole life would build
such a thing as a cult I would I would
like to have a cult yeah me too same
really this is a safe space Kiara you
can talk about your cult Ambitions here
we won't judge
okay uh all
right I think uh we're going to have a
our special guest is going to join um to
announce the winner yeah Special A VIP
guest special guest special
guest winner but we just say wait for
her for like a minute or two if that's
okay sorry
guys
okay almost special guest thank you for
waiting special guest I'm excited are
you going to make me spell a word
yes
antidisestablishmentarianism a n t i e s
t establishment I'm
lost uh a e wait no I give up wait hold
on I have to I have to count one last
one star I almost that word I almost
gave it to you Callie yeah let's hear
you call come on I can spell it
maybe I know how to spell
it okay well you practiced all those
words you stud it oh
a d i s e s t h uh uh uh B there's no
for Ace mm i s h mint m e n t a a r i a
n i s M I can't believe you know how to
spell that but
you
yay you hesitated spelling squeak all
right I do have uh I believe I do have
the results but uh I will convene with
our special guest and then I will come
back to announce in like 30 seconds
hopefully okay okay okay
oh chat sorry it's just me uh yes I will
convene with the spe I'm convening with
the special guest uh who is the special
guest you
ask and she will be here any
moment but in the
meantime is um finishing up our our our
last calculations hello chat who do you
think
won it's the eject button the eject
button is not the special guest
heck
okay I didn't even know we had a special
guest
what yeah it's
a you'll see you'll see it's not it's
nothing weird she should be here oh here
oh she is here okay hold on one second
let me fix something let me adjust
something and
then our special guest I'm going to give
you um instructions in a
moment
okay all right w
wow there we
go okay I'm anticipating
all right I'm giving the results to the
special
guest oh boy oh boy oh
boy sorry for waiting chat thank you for
waiting okay
[Music]
be
be be can I shoot my gun again yeah yeah
oh we can shoot guns at the end yeah
y I have all the results now s it's just
our list is like a kind of all over the
place all right so special
guest um you're going to announce the
winners here they
are are
you is there music playing right now yes
I think so
oh okay it just oh let me add the
special guest to our
thingy not that that's not our special
guest taada okay oh there she is okay so
you will announce our
uh announce our our thingy but let's go
back to the uh other Channel with
everybody so we can announce why you
look so
Shifty okay here we go we're going back
okay all right guys s sorry to keep you
waiting uh we're ready now oh good okay
just burn me already all right so we are
back back and is she's no longer burning
congratulations Miss back it's loading
loading loading loading we back yeah oh
we're back oh I
think
way making you announce the uh you know
third place second place and winner I
sure
can all right
everybody I'm sorry I just you're
anoun I didn't look at myself
okay um sorry about that that was not
professional in third place we have Miss
Siri's
fauna place what
yes very good very good um thank you in
second place we have
narissa very nice hey hey and crony
they're they tied
[Music]
very
nice so because there was a tie I
[Music]
win I'm I'm just josing I'm just josing
I'm sorry I went off script in first
place we have
[Applause]
very
nice truly GG she's smart g words from
the
winner can I ask for one thing from the
judges uh one request yes can can can
you blow me a k
kiss kiss can you just just like you
don't just like a
just send one over it doesn't have to be
on one condition okay you have to call
us
[Music]
Senai
please okay you get a che for that yeah
we're going over there oh my God the
hands are floating what's going on okay
we can't actually go over there right
now but wait my arm K
[Music]
here does m have to blow kiss too yes
M extra wet yes one on my forehead
please M can go over there El had moving
over there okay yeah I'm I'm heading
over
okay I am the luckiest person in the
world yeah I'm
jealous ready yeah I'm ready
M nice
three
kisses all right thank you quick
question can I have please yeah oh yeah
uh yeah you can have fourth place we
actually have let's go I think you there
also oh yeah I'm sorry what was it yeah
we have something special too there's a
special mention to be mention special
mention honorable mention B boo
boo what did you do bi boo what am I in
trouble what did you do
you got 69
points
nice nice good job honestly the real
winner of today's stream can I can I
request
something um I mean for 69 points maybe
if it's something small something can I
be set on fire oh yeah we could do that
yeah you do we should
you have a budget for that yeah we have
fire tech n that's where all the I get a
prize I was on fire the longest of
course oh
you sorry what so much
buling here you can have all the stars
that are left on the screen here you
[Music]
go there you go big finale I do kind of
want to see everyone's fire animation
yes yes got to shoot the thing we'll
start at the
top
[Music]
bye that's it it's it's not that it's
just think for was was the only one that
was special the rest just had fire
that's that's why it was so
crazy okay well in that case yeah you
guys can set yourselves on fire really
to beon if he just mute did we just mute
yeah
oh everybody's on fire except for
fuaa now it's really silent cuz
everybody's muted no
fire dead
[Music]
muted all right well while everybody's
muted thank you guys for joining sorry
it ran so long we wanted it to be like 2
hours but
uh yeah yeah cuz I got to I got to say
things
yeah thank you M for joining and
announcing the
winners thank you for letting me yeah
any
time thank you to to all the artists to
who who worked on this project thank you
so much thank you thank
[Music]
you good job
artist thank you also thank you for
organizing you guys are crazy thank you
so fun it was so much fun
thank thank you very much thank you all
right I gu we we'll let you guys go be
free
[Music]
okay what the heck is going
on e
[Music]
pap
a
[Music]
e