[Music]
e
you're
[Music]
where
hello
[\h__\h] who you
what's up what's up I know
that why do I know
b b
I
am where am
I who am
I what am I
[Music]
let me
out let
[Music]
if I don't see they don't see me if I
don't see them they don't see me if I
don't see them they don't see
me stay away from my corner you come
near me I swear to God I will knock you
down like a bunch of
brick my corner is safe my corner is
safe my corner is safe
w
why is why is why
is sudden RPG
music did I
get
isai wait think back what happened what
I was what I I just I was crossing the
road and then I saw the lights the
lights ba that's right my name name is
ba remember the
lights and then in that moment I
saw it's not how stay away
enigmatic
recollection did we have
we I've read about this I think I've
read a manga like this recently is this
one of those
situations where they take members from
another world
I got nothing if you want me to be a
hero and save save your world kill the
dragon or stay
away you want me to kill your Demon Lord
I'm not the one for you send me
home let me out send me
home I have no
skills I am but a I think am I a rat I'm
a rat I am b a
rat I have negative
HP negative
intelligence 100 luck I will be
absolutely useless in your Conquest let
me
go what you looking
at what are you looking at huh what are
you looking at h
right one corn is
taken why are you guys
here I hear the voices so many voices
s
voice
what
you are you here to
help
hello
hello where am I where where are we oh
hello stay away
Scar's who is who is
everyone stay away oh are we supposed to
lose our M already why is it why is it
so
pixel what happened to my beautiful bud
if you guys are going on a conquest
count me out I want to go
home where am
I what happened I think I hit my head
what happened
what a coincidence I also hit my head
you hit your head too w w w i i just hit
my head I don't see any cracks these
these people
weird
hello you look hello hello are you guys
also heroes from another world hello did
you see the lights did anyone see the
lights wonder if you can hurt did you
see the lights what lights can I hurt
you the lights stay
away crazy am I hurting you what's going
on I don't I don't know I feel no pain I
feel no I feel no no nothing in my bones
oh my I don't have a BL
button did you see doesn't hurt where
are you from did you see the oh
the lights I see the
lights I see the
lights the
lights not the lights
the light oh my God back so R am I
dead I was trying to
I I have this feeling that you might
want to massage me so I was turning
around
and you
look are I don't know why but I have the
sudden
Earth what about you I look I don't I
don't I'm a
rat it is really
[Music]
loud you will have
I go back to my corner I will sit here
and
brood this is how the life ends I don't
want this anymore I don't need this life
it's all right I'm just waiting to be
kicked from the conquest I could just go
find a little cabin in the corner in the
middle of the woods just about myself
it's all right I don't remember much
about my old life and you know it's fine
you can't miss what you don't
remember it's fine we can we can build a
new life we can we can build a new life
where we just live in peace and okay I'm
pretty sure together we can find peace
in this new
world hello
hello hello did you hit your head
too I think
so kind of
loud truly is really
loud really loud I cannot perceive would
you like to join my corner I like the
corner you like to join my corner I was
just s in here thinking about how I
don't I don't remember where I came from
but that gives me a sense of peace I was
thinking of going into the woods to Joy
to create a new
life a new life in the
woods do you think we're stuck here
forever I think it might be for the
better if we're stuck
in who do you think is going to start
eating people first
person that trying to get you in my
right
ear you don't want she's going to leave
my
[Music]
corner you get oh this is also a very
nice oh my corner brings me such
P did you adjust it like in your head
[Music]
I don't know if I can be a dad though
sounds
a this is
my this cor is for me look at the beauty
line look at the beauty of white are but
why why is ba also in my ear I mean who
the heck is that she just looks like a
ba socializing huh she does the letter
floating above her head are
you those
my corner co co
co what do you call
thyself
be
name should call
the the
B capital T Capital my name is the bay
okay
you okay yes
I'm who am I the world I live
in and B than anything
the people I hope most
dear face with
Oblivion I
feel
empty relieved
sticky keys perhaps
Destro I do not
know so much I do not know I don't know
and yet and yet why do I hear oh my God
are we all having the same thought the
bright lights to me bright light it
calls to
me that bright
light go to the
light is anybody else concerned about
this symbolism of going into the bright
light I've gone into the light before I
guess it wouldn't hurt to go again I
everybody's going so go to the light
go go to the light light
thank you go to the
light the light is this
it oh we got to shoot up do we shoot up
like the
light it say do they
have take me
now take me up take me take
me so many voices I don't know why alen
how many voices do we go can we go up
can we can we go we don't go
up should we go towards the
light oh what's that that looks like an
egg this
is
that that looks like a soul a broken
what is soul is this a hole but what
came from oh my God don't turn around
it's not a hole it's not a hole not a
hole
I don't want to
fall
fall make of you
[Applause]
you there what are you doing
here you have a look of Outsiders about
you wait could it
be quick send word to his
majesty it wasn't me it wasn't the the
heroes have arrived at the second your
majesty you've been mistaken I am not a
hero I I
humbly request right away
no disabled sticky notes how do I
disable sticky
notes
okay welcome Heroes this is the kingdom
of lione and I am its king the gods who
brought you if inform me that you
remember not but your own names
your highness my name is the
bay I am not going to be any use to
you a side effect of travel between
worlds no
doubt this must all come as a surprise
through but hearken well it was I who
summoned you here you see an
unprecedented clity now threatens our
world it has sewn the Earth with
corruption and driven us from our
homes this blighted land now gives rise
to creatures of Shadows known as stains
this Kingdom of Livingstone and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us liist but should the clamity
be left unchecked it's the only matter
of time before it consumes the entire
world your
highness face with this Prospect I
scared the ancient test for a way to
combat the clamity and therein I found
one
the ritual of hero
summoning you who hail from another
world have been summoned here by me to
become the saviors of
lione only you have the power to save
our
world your
majesty so I will ask Will
you you you meny what what is it the
great host of stains are broken
throughout the fence
Lawns
no we are Rush amount of Defense but the
situation is D Your Majesty we must get
you somewhere
safe who are these
strangers what say you Heroes will you
accept this destiny the
Majesty you've been mistaken I hold no
great such power I just want to go home
back to my fig what my figurines
what R my name
I in my
head this is yes I do sense a Myster
this is a mistake oh my good my name is
Ru did you make the king I feel the king
might have been
mistaken you guys the king I met the
king he's you met the king the king is
most mistaken if he thinks that I can
become
a of
this are we the same sword
though oh thank you I a her from another
world I think the king made a mistakes
with me to be to be honest a great
mistak I
don't voices so many
voices that facial hair is
that toet you
[Music]
CPA you should might broken this one a
little just a tiny bit little broken
this
one what kind of
that what I am
I don't we don't
remember don't remember we don't we
don't
remember why
you this situation is so funny to me I'm
no here it's a mechis I
see exactly you have to
stop CU I'm in the same situation I no
hero what is King has made this great
mistake to me said will you and then we
got cut off I think we were in the same
spot you were L for the I did not
realize I'm in the face of Royal your
highness honestly your your highness
could you maybe go back to the king and
get him to change his mind because the
bab is I am not I just want to find a
cabin in the woods live a quiet life for
the rest of my days I know I understand
my my little peasant
however peasant you I I was going to be
crowned as Queen but like I said I was
rudely interrupted by one of their
servants but I promise you after we save
the world
I will make you have a good long
retirement oh
you generous I would sck with you any
distress we got to go
safe I regret that you must face such
danger so soon after danger no why did I
feel like I
was explain to you
our Majesty
why does this this using so many
difficult words I don't understand these
words I me come from a land of simple
words it's too late to save this
world too late to save this world from
destruction it is our duty to defend our
King it's your duty not my duty this is
not my king
Brave World Heroes us go for without
defeat and
my it's between you and my life in the
woods I choose my life in the
woods the bottom is quite helpful
no way it's impossible oh
goodness oh I am hurt I am hurt I am
very very hurt oh goodness oh goodness
oh we one slain oh perhaps this wooden
sword could could be useful
some am so hurt it hurts oh it hurts so
bad I me this is
them oh
[Music]
goodness believe in yourself believe in
the me who believes in you but why is
the but why why does the HP lesson isn't
that how it works in these in these in
these in these
inmortal there's no way oh B has been
slain
L why do you keep
spawning I'll help you it hurts oh God
goodness it hurts you've been most
helpful n FOC Focus oh this the Kake oh
the caning us the
beam is it this is this what they call a
scripted loss shout
Revelation hold your weapon and left
Revelation
re revelation
[Music]
a
revelation
Revelation
Revelation this is why I told the king
that I am not a worthy
hero oh merciful King I told you I was
not worthy of such
power how many times must I tell you
please let this be
aide just choose someone else the
Revelation maybe the king came to a
revelation and sent us back all to the
our relative world when I wake up I
wanted I want to regain the memories of
the ones I once had
I want to go
back I want to go back to the
days the days of this music
is this RPG music is f i just is a time
for self-revelation
I just want to go
back to the to the nice days of where I
remember who I am or I felt like I was a
part of
something where I felt
love
happiness and the
life where I met
but now no matter where I go the voices
don't
stop thank you for the I'm here having a
self-revelation trying to regain these
memories and all I hear in my head is
thank you for the gift what gift are you
speaking
of what gift
I
feel
cold I
trapped The Gift of Sight is
this is this a message from the above
the gift of sight I see nothing I see
there is but the void
friendship are you telling me that these
new people are going to be my
friends I've never known love nor
friendship people felt sorry for
me enemies best friend enemies best
friends
do I
trust trust is a hard thing you know
it's a hard thing to come
by I feel so lost the inside of me is
just
torn of feeling
pulled into a new
dimension that one person there was that
one person that made fun of my accent
asking me where I from of course I don't
know where I'm from from just comes
naturally to
me maybe this could be a way to
ReDiscover to backtrack to
remember I'm hungry I feel hunger
e I'm running out of
Revelations what do I
know the B is the
name the last thing that I
remember
e is the
lights but we were fighting the stain
King have we Fallen back into the
void are they sending us back because we
failed if we what is my homeland can you
tell me where I came
from I need to know these and
say I don't think this melody is
appropriate to sing at this moment I'm
breaking out in
song You Came From A Land Down
Under down under what does that
mean I must find the ANW
the an Set Me
Free can't find the
answers I don't know who to trust nor
who to
fight am I doomed to wonder through the
night
I
feel a little thing
called
confusion am I trapped down
here is this an
illusion will we never go back to the
days so
where I st at the
wall didn't need to worry if I
fall down down
down
down we're falling
down I think I'm Lo
[Music]
loing Revelation
Revelation
revelation revation
ration revelation
[Music]
my War we're
back was that but a
[Music]
dream was that a dream we
failed that was that was the that was
the world
time wait is this like a
different
I turned back the time your
highness your highness maybe we can you
can go back and His Highness finish the
proposal and you can get me out of here
that is very correct if this is a Time
Loop then we can go back to where the
king is and I'll I'll call it off save
the world you hi us you can't call off
from your your marriage if you call I'm
not going to call off my marriage we're
going to call off this journey and
you're going to go to your retirement
and I
will hail you with a
kingdom you the tile of Jes oh your
highness I must most humbly refuse that
sounds like way too much pressure and
responsibility I just
I can
you do you laugh why do you
laugh it's I find it absolutely adorable
that you and the King you similar
vocabulary like
mayhaps your highness than I will sit by
your side until this Loop finishes your
highness no need my fellow
peasant is fine peasant the bay is fine
your
highness your name is peasant B peasant
the bay there is a the in there
somewhere in the peasant the bay your
highness all me I will
be I mean
that the
B you are so my B they've taken a weapon
your highness oh
well I need my
my w w crazy red
one you're crazy she called you
crazy crazy
L she's not very nice is she the B it's
you again oh be you I saw you were slain
I thought you were slain I saw you di we
were all SL were we all
slain is this a Time
Loop Who I Am the
world they why do I feel a sense of
familiarity with this more than
anything the people I hold most
dear faced with Oblivion I feel empty
yes empty
relieved Nana m i I feel like I don't
know what I did to that one I really
don't I don't really don't I don't know
if I've offended her in some way but she
doesn't seem very
nice so much I don't know
you there has to be a skip button then
oh I going toward the light again oh
you're welcome back I
oh I feel like I've been here before oh
hello ma'am hello m m Madam have you
been here before it seems strangely
familiar I will say would you call it a
sense
ofu D Vu is absolutely what I would call
it sense of deja vu as you took the
words right out of my mouth accent oh
thank you madam I just I it's so I'm
trying it's it's the first step into
regaining my thoughts of who I am my
head told me call youo I
I to disting it but it's very dis thank
you mad yeah I don't know what AO is
they don't like that I'm never
heard is don't like that
no no I don't like that name at
all you're you're first on my the hero
I'm going to assassinate you please the
hero can you expl what's going on you
said you were the hero yeah so uh we
kind of failed to save the world ones oh
but the the almighty forces have turned
back time well I can't say I didn't warn
the king I said from the very beginning
that it was a mistake I am no me not a
hero me is just who believes in
you hot wom let's go I feel a tingling
in my my senses when you said
that there it is
again say it with
me what is that word it's a magical
phrase top in my family throughout the
generations your family yes the family
of Heroes I
am believe in yourself my head
believe it we save
[Music]
you what's your I
believe your highness
we've come
again
what you us I told you from the second
this you hidest
please I know you were in the middle of
proposing to your fiance please just let
me leave we failed you once and perhaps
you were right you said there was an
unpresented corruption and honestly if
it we're probably all going to die but I
don't want to die your highness if you
could just let me go on my Merry way you
can die first and he can get me later
all
right d we've come to bargon we I don't
want to keep doing this you Royal your
Royal
[Music]
mustaches so I don't think you took any
of it seriously back to the
diver why are we
back I thought her harness was going to
I should be hearing Wedding Bells at
this point where is her Royal Highness
everyone wait I know what happens
there's going to be en yeah there's
going how you know how do you know
please don't tell me did her Royal
Highness I've been here fail at the at
the marriage proposal again what a
player what marriage proposal
oh so actually if this is just a secret
because I don't think she wants her her
identity to be known to the rest of you
know the peasants um I'm I'm peasant by
the way peasant the bay nice to meet you
um hi hero I know you're a hero but I'm
just I am just one of the Lonely masses
her Royal Highness is actually amongst
one of
us so apparently his Royal Highness was
in the middle of proposing to a Royal
Highness when suddenly you know we got
all thrown in here so you know in the
second time Loop her Royal Highness said
that you know she was going to continue
on with the marriage get the king to to
finish off you know the uh to finish off
the proposal and then she will she will
give she said she will give me she'll
make me a duchess and then I can I can
just live out my days in peace but we're
back here with the weapon
and I don't know what's happening we
don't know oh
[Music]
oh no the the hero why is the No One
Believes Me I feel like I'm losing my
mind if I'm talking to myself here we're
looking for Heroes
okay thank you what
[Music]
happened
iant the bay I do not wish to talk about
it yes I would love a massage I see
I well you see I did my best he was
going to give me a a nine karat ring n
ring
unbelievable but but Fate has pulled us
apart I knew pulled pulled he he was he
was being so romantic and said only you
can save our world together and I was
saying I do
and
verusus is a villain and that is so that
I will put my life on the line to
protect you from enemies your highness
oh oh thank you
peasant call now you they should be they
should be here any moment if me memory
serves me correctly just call me Shak
just call me I'm sure
dreams that I think I would up take the
sword to protect the land that is even
my
own have you faed
that I will that hurts me made have F me
me have
fallen God are the days of the walls of
white in my corner today I will uphold
The Sword and protect her Royal Highness
from what is she looking
at oh goodness
oh okay
oh it's happening
[Music]
again follow the cran don't don't HT me
anymore wait I'm ready they they were
right here I remember from my past
life they were right here happen I
remember is it here with the land here
remember I remember you
late dra please listen
hero you hit your head pretty I all I
know is my name and now this is glorious
I know how they move for the
queen what what a what a what a what an
amazing for the queen you mustn't hurt
the queen
oh I feel so much power could I
potentially be a
[Music]
hero I don't want to be a hero I don't
want to be a hero I don't want to be a
hero it hurts I don't want to be a hero
whatever that stain's made out of it is
one I want to
[Music]
be ohing around you're not even doing
anything looks like Australia here
what's up
Australia AUST
Australia that
has got a little
tail yes I remember the big one has a
beam the big one has a beam
jum kill the king the king with the
King me
don't hurt my
wife why is there a c in
here hey stop
that watch
out there's more over here get the
r for each I'm scared better not lose
this Loop
then
Ohad this bird is smly
fabulous or did we meet the fluffy one I
don't
remember look at the
hero is a
time what is
this revelation
the stain host has been rounded why did
I get a
one I got a
one you fought a bravely kind Heroes I
pray you are not
injured that Mighty armored one must be
their leader the stain King fascinating
Most
Fascinating well I see why they call you
Heroes we' been a rock pick without your
help we sustained minimal damage thanks
to your Valor our kingdom is in your
debt thank you I must hasten to inform
His Majesty of your Victory will you
accompany
me did
I am I all this time
no no maybe this is my true call calling
in
life I heard the news though we called
upon you suddenly you Rose to the
occasion you are my deepest
gratitude what interests me most however
is the strange power you manifest during
the battle with which you were able to
defeat the stains that power make well
be the key to saving our world from
Annihilation according to according to
the heroes the power came from them like
a forgotten memory when they spoke the
word
revelation but once they use the terupt
the stain host it seems the power vanish
for not
chice well that's BL brilliant in it so
what are we supposed to do the next time
stain's
attack revelation we must uncover the
secrets of this phenomenon if we are to
Prevail against the Calamity many
questions remain but one thing is
certain the kingdom of lior still stands
today thanks to
you yeah here so Heroes I ask you once
more will you lend us your strength to
save Lio from
ruin that was did I nod my head I I
don't marvelous on behalf of all liist I
thank you
we are blessed to have your Aid kind
Heroes allow me to introduce the four
Great guilds which are responsible for
ensuring the Kingdom's peace and
prosperity The Haven for the Curious
where knowledge and creativity are
valued above all the Scarlet wand the
home for Glory Seekers with ambition and
vision where closest allies become
fiercest Rivals the Amber coin the
sanctum of healing where the spirit of
empathy and devotion thrives the celan
cup the beacon of righteous and loyal
with great threads of face with even
greater courage the Jade sword one of
these guilds will become your home
during your
time am I being
sorted am I going to be sorted in Beyond
this door lies the room of Truth therein
the will of the ancestor will decide
your guilt
I don't like this don't like this at
all Fe not introspection is a vital step
on the road to Enlightenment Exel as
always say ever
higher time to roll the door say be
seeing some of you lock down at the
Amber
chap let us see save this world
together the room of Truth AWA go forth
with
Valor step on to the platform received
the will of the
[Music]
ancestor
I
I I
I admidst the countless sparkling like
seek enlightment and with the Scarlet
Fe I am the
[Music]
ambercoin how how do
I Dawn the
cloak how how do I Dawn the cloak
down the
cloaked UN mer unwavering will seek to
defend the soul of the
Jade J on the
cloak w
title
drop speak
to hello
oh it's hello weirdo uh don't tell me
are you in the same Guild as art as
me is that what this means is that why
we are together now uhoh please to make
your acquaintance my name is the B I
still don't know your name unfriendly
stranger
I will tell you I'll try to be friendly
from here on you don't need to force
yourself I don't believe in changing
character for for friendship but it's
called character
development dummy my name I think is
Cleopatra
isenhower Da Vinci thei no the great the
third I'm just going to call you three
from now on
righty I think oh my goodness that was
the cutest I've ever seen I'll come to
hello have I done something to you
three you weired me
out H where are we I think we I think
were we supposed to talk to the are we
all in the same Guild do I really have
to be in the same Guild as this okay you
do righty you've been chosen that's
where where is the lead oh the lead is
the leader over here oh Oren's over here
we have to go Orin who is this who are
you how do we do do we oh I think I'm
standing on or do we have
to on the table on the table T hello
there
yippe oh wait it's oh it's our Guild
sorry keep you waiting oh that's
perfectly talkie oh what yeah you also
got a recycling bin why I forgot to
recycle got a map oh yeah we got to
recycle for sure oh my goodness how do
we talk we got to speak to the Gil
Master how do we talk to the
master wait we have the British
one oh we totally do oh I I can talk to
him how do we you speak British oh yeah
you speak right click he says watch out
this a is the Amber corns little den of
operations uh name's all running on the
CL thing in charge around
here Orin we have the British joining
the fight for liore straight away after
you were summoned but we appreciate it
now you one of us meaning We Fight
Together against some stains maybe do a
little world saving while we're added eh
perfect first things first he's Canadian
too first Canadian so you ought to get
to know this a town we're in learn how
to accept and perform
quests see there's a quest board out in
town where missions get posted might
want to take a bches out and see what
the quest M has to
say I don't understand are you because
you doing this so well I don't
understand that that that wasn't me that
was that was the M that was that was
speak it wasn't me master next go to the
quest board go where's the
quest wait where's the quest master
honestly that conversation took so long
it's already night time I don't really
like being out at pass by bedtime my
bedtime is 7:00 p.m. if anyone was
wondering but I don't think anybody is
I'm kind of I'm a little bit uncertain
slow down you what was your name again
the B um I'll follow you the B okay the
what's your what's your name ah me yes
what's what's your name I am uh nice to
meet you I'm takasa of the oranges
it's your
name all of your your my name is
panta yeah I already
adopted nice to meet you nice to meet
you both my name is the bay and this
over here is three very nice to meet you
that's not nice to meet you the lazy
version of my name
three Catra Eisenhower D Vinci the great
the third for short three just call just
call just call her
three she not she's not very nice so
just try not to get on a bad side all
right no I I just treat people the way
that they should be treated that's
all these are very nice I don't think
we're going to get
along yeah I want I think that I think
that there'll be a Twist in this story
line and we'll be the bestest of friends
I hardly doubt it I don't I also don't
know where we're supposed to be
isie the quest guy perhaps uh we're very
we are we've got a map I'm sorry I think
the first thing you need to understand
is that I have no idea where I'm going
we're going we're going the wrong way
everybody everybody we're going the
wrong way we're going this
way where are we oh you're right we're
not supposed to be here're we're not
supposed to be here we're not supposed
to be there oh no we're going to get in
trouble we're going to get expelled
got here expell like is this a school or
what I I I honestly would like to be
expelled please just leave me alone wait
I have an egg why is you guys also have
an egg I do have an egg it's it's quite
heavy it cuz I'm running out of
bread would you like a piece of bread no
I still got two but like just wondering
for you know future if I can eat the egg
well I have five
so five eggs or five Brads you have five
eggs five wait we lost our cats it's a
little bit
kitty kitty kitty here kitty here kitty
kitty kitty kitty kitty kitty kitty
kitty kitty kitty
kitty so um three
what I guess we got off the wrong foot
um
how what Lovely weather we have
today how was you know it just
started oh all
right uh we found out kitty
cat oh we found out kitty cat please
don't leave me alone with three thank
you this
way cat needs to be on a leash it seems
no I'm
free can we please have a leash yes we
need a leash for all cats no I'm free
KY guil cat I am
fine free cat where are we going the B
uh according to this map I think the
quest Master should be right over here
wait have you have we find the quest
board this is the board I think this is
the board is that's a good board nice
board let's see looks pretty oh you must
be one of the heroes then you master
told me about you I too here is the
quest board to most jobs and requests
here
understand need take to help some
[Music]
citizens Guild
intr good eye you have your name sweet
one look at
that oh my God your sword
ising I don't know are you special I
mean it's not about
honestly
that's it's about how you use it of
course for the sake of improving our
relationship no I've never going on I've
never felt special in my entire
life I don't want you to feel special
you think I want you to feel like a
loser I mean I I've awoken only an hour
ago I don't really remember what what I
feel and how I feel but so Jonathan you
have
I
do more than you
think perhaps we're not so different
after
all are what team are you guys perhaps
we
are hello there we are part of the amorn
I must go back to our Guild and speak to
the guild I don't know I just toide
one you sto it you must have stolen it
where do you check the where do you
check the
quest
my this here looks like a perfect
job
a complete the side quest to the quest
board first oh where is the side quest
apparently we need to go to
you can help
us materials needed at the SM I'm The
Apprentice at
the I've accepted a side
quest maybe right click onto the quest
board maybe I don't
[Music]
know materials needed at
thei where is the
where is the
Smithy no we have to complete the
quest we're on the
way I've got the map we can go to the
Smithy yeah let's go all right I don't
know if I should be in charge of
directions I mean maybe I feel like I
can help maybe
uh oh
oh my good it's it's South did they say
I'm I'm coming oh what happened to three
I don't know what it's free maybe we
also oh we want to cook K
too come here come here actually uh
receive one of your remaining breads you
may because I have more than you thank
you I have zero at this point wait I
give it to you oh we made trade oh how
do I accept
like this yes like so okay one one bread
for you did you did you get you are so
kind uh I guess I oh wait no this here
we go wait I can't
what I can't I can't put it in your box
oh
yeah I must
exchange oh wait I lock into to tra we
got to uh click the red uh thing in the
at the bottom oh I need to eat
she is one more time one more time stand
still do not
move
my
huh the golden icon the red icon yeah
but the the bread are you missing the
bread
onward we
March onward we March to the Smithy are
we going let's go know we can go with
the horse too oh you ride hor are you a
horse r Wait what the heck how' you get
the horse where did you get the the egg
just have eggs in this
world that's so fast all right where I
don't know where I think I I that is so
fast SMI it Apprentice of blacksmith is
that The Apprentice oh we got it's up
there oh I
see I may have lost
them
and hello oh cuz I it's over here we're
in the wrong house ladies oh I don't
think we can get it all right how do you
get off the horse shift shift shift sh
okay a shift all right it's this
way how did you disappear
this the house I was just it's just the
power inside it makes I think it's just
gave me endless speed is it in air um
it's it's it's just this is the Smithy
but we don't really know what materials
we need that's the only problem I think
it's up
there it's here so this is the Smith
Miss but I don't know what materials
we're supposed to have Hello can just
ask you saw here we go we need 10 oak
logs bunch of trees we can
oh
okay what okay good do we have axes
girls oh let's us go how how far do you
think is far is this far enough I know
how far is this can we take
this can we take these trees I don't
think so I don't I don't I don't think
so maybe we can go a little bit further
out maybe this way okay okay
okay how far is
out
y I don't I don't think okay let's go
okay oh they F I shall remember it this
time out
how far is out this is your chance
to is this out
enough this
my I don't think this is out
enough there they are here they are okay
this is not out
yeah this is not considered outside this
is not out it respawns right away
but here who even wants these wait how
far is out then yeah
can do we have to go outside the wall
even
further we may have to leave the
wall Maybe
problem I think we need to leave the
wall uh how do we leave how do we leave
the wall how do we get
out we get out
here do you
believe I think we going to die if we do
you there fall damage do you damage do
you
believe those must be the trees
right you need help what happened what's
wrong what WR am in a dangerous
situation how youing up here how did she
do that I might die how did you do that
don't die please don't die I'll try to
go step by step yeah yeah yeah I look
Qui I've just realized I've been muted
in the game this entire I mean I've been
muted this entire time oh my gosh we've
been a mute this entire time this entire
time I he before oh my goodness where
did she respond I don't know perhaps
there's another staircase closer to
where these trees are there's an exit
I'm assuming these are the trees how do
we leave
hold is there a way to get down can we
jump on the roof mayhaps
going jump on the roof
no is that not
possible go to a
gate
oh no I was me it too all right I think
this may have not been the
way uh
uh I've come to understand that
directions are not my main
Forte why did you stop riding your
right if we go back down here there has
to be a gate
somewhere maybe it's on the other
side um has to how do we get
out where is she are we trapped here
forever is that the
gate
oh oh
on is this the gate yeah there's a gate
here
where where she
go hello oh where did we are we are
scattered we've lost our cat oh is this
the gate oh
yes oh my goodness oh I see oh my gosh
and there's more people here oh I
see
Revelation Revelation oh I see there's a
time limit
oh thank you kind thank you kind sir
ma'am all right we need I will take this
I will take the one above oh it works it
does Works be careful do we need 10 each
do you think the Smithy seems a little
bit desperate for
wood I you know what just in case we can
do 10 each we can
go we can also sabotage the other people
oh is it
respawning oh never mind no
sabotage um I've got eight I've got 10
already do I have all the what I need
there's so many
speed she she hello she really stuck to
her word she she went and she used her
oh ah I I found you oh my goodness the
radio that's not where are you we we've
gone outside the gate wait are you
hearing the voices of our kitty I'm I'm
call I'm calling to be at the phone is
it through the radio wait a sec wait ba
where are you we outside hold on we are
defeating oh H how how did you R outside
um look for a blue spot on the map you
should be able to teleport outside the
city Gates you're in my way sheep you
talking to look got money
oh I was muted I'm sorry
K I know how to go outside we have to go
to the blue spots come
here you need more wood okay let's go
double check right there we go you can
call people in
this don't
worry I'll protect you dang it
owie that hurt raw in the
nut it's making very sad noises I don't
like
that not a fan I want to hear something
fun oh Deary do you think we get extra
for defeating you don't we get coins do
we
extra coins how many how many blocks do
you have I'm ready to go back to the
Smithy and get another side quest
because we need more money I but don't
we need like what if we need 40 though
why do we need
40 if um we need 10 each well the the
other two are coming to to get to get to
get their wood anyway but we could just
get the wood for
them you would do that three for someone
else well overall it's for me oh speeds
up the process You' be wrong about that
I would like to make it to your make
make it known that I am protecting
you thank you the B you're welcome
three say
the yes what is
it you think that if circumstances were
different we could be friends
cuz I
don't honestly I was about to say
something
heartwarming what I've just gotten a
phone call
you and I scared the b b out of
me yeah three maybe if you were a bit
nicer to people maybe they'd call you
what what do you want kitty cat where
are you
hello sorry I'm
sorry no mind we found it I I'll be
right
back she just caught me for no reason
she made me terrify for no reason she
made me lose 10 years of my life that I
just started for no reason Bad Kitty I
found it yeah let's go Bad Kitty you
made me lose 10 years of my non-existent
life that I just started for absolutely
no reason hello I am back from the dead
oh hello welcome back have enough wood
we have we have a lot of wood we can
leave now oh I don't have enough wood
it's okay I have
wood I have 30 you want to trade once
again I can do
this yipp
yippi wonderful would you
like so generous I don't know how to how
do we trade yeah accept how do I
accept press T then then click on
except oh okay done marvelous let's go
back and get that
coin we finished the quest
yeah you
go thank
you how do I get it think you click
click the red the red yeah thank you y
wait actually I haven't got it you
should have I'm going to oh no no no
he's on the chest yeah
oh all right let's get out of here
[Music]
here wait ladies should we create a
should we create a
party h no there's a party leader right
now she would have to invite you cany me
to the party please I invite tree as
well
there you go I invited hey hey hey hey
hey
hey all right let's go
back is that why we can't hear anybody
else
um I'm going
back what are you looking at let's get
out of here let's get out of here let's
get out of here okay
woo all right we made it we made it we
go back to
the
blacksmith we're right here we
go is this is this house I think it's
over here all
righty yes it seems we cannot no you got
to buy
things you guys got don't know here
I don't I'm not comfortable should we
just people I feel very un right now I I
don't feel
comfortable are you sure they're not
going to attack us should we should we
should we come back another time we
should come back another time maybe we
should introduce ourself maybe we should
make more Ali some more
friends the Amber coins we may not we
must not
beared no
one coming we do cobblestone
oh o how do I make a
pickaxe the if you bring the material
can the tools and think I have to go get
more mine was made immediately do you
have the required
material
pickaxe completed wait what we we need
to master where is the it's completed we
can go to the quest Master where's the
master especially if you need co wait do
I have to do something with
them where's the m
gave
you right yeah yeah I think they're in
the Box still right yeah I open it and
then
okay we fail to purchase you do not have
the required materi and sticks all right
I made okay we need plank I have planks
and we need sticks all righty I thought
oh I was I was trying to skip the
process I understand I'm sorry so we
need to make planks okay see I got this
one perhaps got it don't worry how many
I can do that yes a gold
pickax oh okay I got all of it and then
what what do we have to do now
complete what we do now okay I made the
pickax cost
money be able to make completed we
completed thank you so much there you
bring the next c a wooden pickax I made
it
too many people are speaking to him at
once
we is this all of our money am I am I
using all of
our I do not think so my money has not
decreased I think that's your money okay
I'm rich I have your wood how much money
do you have
three now I have
93 than
ha
I did just being old three is not really
all right that's not what that
means they don't live that's
sh I keep hearing hearing something in
my ear but you know it's just three
Cobblestone is here I'm three I'm just
sometimes I
wonder just
wonder careful it is it is a nightly
time where many danger awaits Us in the
outside Fields what is uh what is our
current uh Quest here uh ter
Cobblestone T Cobblestone T
Cobblestone I still don't understand do
we all need to get cobblestone right you
got 10 cobblestone
each one of us needs like I don't know
how many 10 10 Cobblestone 10
Cobblestone okay yeah oh that makes oh
sorry that makes sense because then we
can upgrade our tools I'm predicting the
next the next going to
happen so every time if if we get if
they ask for 10 we collect 20 you know
that's the what you know Amber coin is
always about about think ahead you got
to think ahead plan for the future I
think you're very smart be thank you
three was that a genuine compliment
coming from you I'm I'm going to get
extra extra cars I really don't think
we're going to get a long three if we
don't hey stop fighting you two I think
I think we got slowburn going
on it's morning good
morning
righty I've got enough I'm ready to go
back are you all ready to go back ready
yeah ready I'm
ready how much I need
right
need
yeah
okay okay and we go back to the back
me call them I don't know why but when
they
say oh yeah is here all right when I
check my inventory I don't know here all
right so what do we need I have a trade
box hi come come
here talk to the
blacksmith oops uhoh all right uh talk
to my mouse okay more to his his we I
already got a wooden pickaxe you have a
wooden Pi would suit your best here some
materials you can use for St tools and a
bit of coin to show my
need
Rich okay open the trade box right I've
been trying to do that a we can craft
stuff
now what cool I am no longer I don't
have enough coins oh oh oh oh my I
enough coins either we need to go farm
maybe how many coins you want I am no
longer rich I am no longer Rich right I
have 21 coin I'm poor what what do they
want us to
buy than buy
now
I I don't know's your rival all losing
oh what are we supposed to do now I
think we have to go back to the uh maybe
the the quest board okay
maybe oh yeah qu master master
right do you know how to open the trade
box you should it's oh over here all
right I can't
remember here here oh a new face is here
hello can you guys hear
me can oh thank God hello there's so
many people I have no idea who are you
why are there so many cute girls all
around me all of a sudden H are you in
me lady oh I I don't know what I'm doing
you sound like someone I want to get my
nails done
with true I haven't gotten my nails done
in ages my name is Iris and I don't know
anything else besides that name oh Iris
he sounds so helpless and weak
TR you didn't honestly do you know what
cup you're in my dear off you go a cup
what do you mean cup I got a new Quest
what quest what what do you mean cup
what group are you in my dear I I seem
to be in The Blue Team oh that is the
seruan cup that's what I was asking oh
goodness all righty another one I got
some gold is there a problem with that
is there a problem in the blue team is
it cuz you're red our matters he number
three I haven't said it what have I done
to these people I don't understand
first keeper you know you have an
interesting it might be you he did you
not get a quest that says so build
something you're asking the right
questions what have you done I don't
know what have you done everyone done I
I don't want to know what I've done
empty lot we're all heroes but I'm I we
here supposed to be the special one they
said I was the one and only is
interested
Inu time
IT jobs and
request yeah oh my God I'm rich I'm
assuming
you're oh I'm rich oh I'm so rich I'm so
rich wait I mean the bay oh yes the
B um no no I got the same Quest though
um I'm the you'll
find oh yeah there are many close enough
but sure must be tired of my
PR I'm I'm only mean to you because I'm
insecure
three I have a lot of toxic masculinity
that I'm
just depressing wa I don't know
three I am Sor can you tell me what I'm
supposed to do with my cobblestone
you gone give me some of your
money don't think I can give you have
you gone and and gotten your Cobblestone
tools yet no I didn't know that was an
option oh go go back and talk to the
I'll I'll come with you three it's going
to be okay honestly I knew there was
some I need I need the
stone I honestly so it wasn't me oh okay
that makes me so much more so it's it's
kind of both like it can be two things
at
once do you want me to help you on all
three
honestly Mia this isn't the right place
this is definitely not the right place
um I don't I think we just barged into a
family eating dinner I don't know wait
why did Iris join our party I don't know
Iris you're not enough
you think these two are
happy honestly they seem pretty
happy you know the king talked about
some great Calamity but these people
seem to be living in peace I know this
is a really nice nice neighborhood I
know right all right um do you know
where the blacksmith is cuz is no longer
on my map um no I think we're just going
to have
to if I Rec
this one thing called a a movie about
someone all right can you pull out your
map please let's let's stock this person
you think oh I'm talk I think you were
wrong this isn't where you're supposed
to be wait I'm just kid mind what oh hi
what's
up oh I think it's that house three is
that one I think it's that
one let's go it might be this one
together did we just steal a party
member by
accident we might we might have okay we
we were lacking
anyway I think everybody else had five
we're the only on a all right so talk to
the pr you got it right this time good
job are you a
shopkeeper oh I can upgrade my weapon
how come I can't upgrade it won't let me
upgrade have you talked to talk to the
blacksmith first The Apprentice or the
blacksmith apprentice apprentice
apprentice hello wa you about the cop
brought call if you talk to my real okay
wait what wait I missed it huh it's
still not working what did he say shoot
babe what did he say he said I could
upgrade but I
can't bab I don't have enough sticks oh
do you have yeah do you have money and
sticks bought the Cobblestone how much
money do I need
50 I have 90 okay do you have sticks
wait I got it I
had completed the quest what do I want I
want a better SW unbreakable stone sword
wait 100 coins oh but I have 100 coins a
stone pickaxe but I can only
get hey just in case I can't use rest in
peace I'm going to go outside and make a
phone call three I'll be standing right
there all right I'll be coming worth
you really strong my God my hideous hair
you oh my go three is
what what what
we did we just steal another party
member
no why is there another party member in
our party are we causing Guild Wars I'm
so proud of you oh she hung up on me all
right um how'd you call it uh you you
have a radio right cck private call I
see okay okay um hello Iris why did you
hang up on me I'm sorry I didn't
understand you were calling
me the heck you call me sorry my mistake
oh my goodness I'm not three I'm not
talking to you I'm talking to kitty cat
at at the moment I'm talking to Irish
oh do we do we just do we do we just
kidnap a are we causing Guild
Wars yeah but that's okay I'm so proud
of you yeah I'm talking to
B all right I'm done with my are you on
our team now what's going on I'm
done
okay are you talking to me
I'm going to hang up now get me out
of what' she
say I don't know she she like said
things but they wen't very helpful oh I
see all right well now that you have
your Cobblestone we can go back to the
Guild Master and you can get your coin
and we can be rich together three
okay a lot of cobblestone that's all
right we'll need it later maybe you
don't like it
because I spent them on the sword I got
a cool sword and I I don't want this but
I have
anyway I have a good sword and you got a
good sword that's great I'm so happy for
you three honestly uh you know seeing
you like this makes me like you just a
tiny bit more you like me here you like
this oh that doesn't work wait hold
on trait request for what
come find out yeah we speedrun all of
this I bet maybe we could go to a
dungeon that's not how you accept you
click on yeah I want to fight in a
dungeon with you guys and see how good
you
are did you pick up another
Quest you can only have tra
okay I was going to pick it up after
visiting the shop I want to buy from him
why don't we pick up Elizabeth has now
click on the red block May the
shopkeeper has something for I'm a
little confused because it just gave me
the option of getting another
Quest oh the quest Master why do you
have a raw pork
chop because I killed a pig I'm so proud
of you go talk to the quest leader
now okay we waiting on hello
hello hello hello there
fuzzy my mind was up the and in the oh
FY that's all right 500 oh
500 500 smack she sounds like me fuzzy
the 500 smackaroonies we got the 500
smackaroonies I'm for
me have you got the 500 three
wait wait what have you got 500 500 what
500 what
coins yeah what all right now we can go
buy stuff we're rich oh wait no I'm just
kidding I don't I thought that was a
trick question
what I need to go to the I need to give
my for who do I give my Cobblestone to
no one just talk to him oh
okay hail hero I see we've you you've
gone and finished the cluster citizens
are in your dep I you get the grave duty
of fighting the Calamity but I hope you
stop by the Quest for from the time to
time and your hi to the Comon F if
you let's go crazy
crazy hello who hello team oh oh hello
hello sweet little lady hello there
hello my name is Iris Iris hello there
yes hello hello Iris hello what may I
call you to my name is the bay the
B I am Cleopatra eisenh Howard D Vinci
the great II Oh W that's a very very
call her three
three C you can't you you can't do that
but what am I to do about
[Laughter]
it you're right I'll I'll just call you
three and there's nothing you can do you
could call me mumi or something oh that
came randomly where' that come from I
think it means no name so I'd rather you
just call me that instead of no you have
no name I thought you had a name I
thought you had a really long name three
I do but you guys were acting like I
don't oh not a
hold what okay I'll call you I'll call
you mooms
okay just to shorten it you know we need
even shorter than that just to shorten
it moms all right oh my gosh wait what
are I've got to know un three so I'm
going to call you three from now what is
that that's fine what are you have the
Naruto thingies they're not Naruto
thingies what are nar what's Naruto no
no they're not sh I mean I don't even
know what you're talking about I don't
know what shurikens are no they're
they're Stars they're they're the power
of the of my angel devil
uh they're my halo it's my it's a part
of my
halo what Halo what Halo did did you
understand that I didn't understand a
single word I she's I think she might be
the town Looney or something I have no
clue what she
say see I thought she was like the cute
sweet little weak girl that you were
going to do on but no she's just kind of
weird why they said why am I suddenly
being judged so much wait am I just
supposed to admit that these are
shuriken or something is what I'm
supposed to do I mean what do you mean
Halo you think you're an Halo honestly
you just got to tell the truth we are
value honesty in this group well do you
think sure can do this
what honestly yeah this happen yeah they
totally could do that what what else
would they do you could totally see that
happening in Naruto what what else would
they do Nar what is Naruto what exactly
what it sounds like I don't know what it
sounds
like the first thing that comes to your
head this is my Revelation my Revelation
is
a no no I would never I would never not
Str that one movie do you know that one
movie where they sing and make Prett
girl hey Jonathan yes I thought you were
about to say do you know John Cena I'm
sorry
I'm
johnen can you see around here I can't
see him I who joh Cena who is Jonathan
John Cena Jonathan Jonathan is to kill
the king Jonathan it goes is this an
inside Jonathan is it is it
is you know
right your highness you have to get your
G are you going to make him gathan we we
have
swor no it's no it's
Jonathan Amber if you kill him he'll be
gone
us he would be G I put my my name on the
line us ambercoin nothing to do with Jon
you Amber you on the Amber team are you
of Amber she's of Amber you
Amber Amber understanding you're not
even Amber what are you talking about
I'm in your team I'm in your party why
don't you are on you
li no you shut huh huh I mean you you
shut your humble
mouth what did you just almost say to me
I did not say anything I thought you
supposed to be a part of the empathy
team huh you too you guys have fire do
not defect yeah I I don't even they they
they're the ones who reached out a
helping hand you're supposed to refuse
it man you're in Cilan Cup oh well I
mean I didn't know you guys were in
[Music]
celan we should we should we should
remove ourselves should
[Applause]
I I'm
not want go crazy have to let's go
before they ask any more questions that
I don't want to
answer right I don't know what happened
abandon or hope who enter
here
what let's
go all righty I think the shop should
just be around
shop I have to P oh thank you for saving
this town welcome to my humble little
shop what can we get what can we get all
right all right just give me give me
give me the guns give me the guns give
me the guns
[Music]
in free dear I didn't ask for wa you
think I'm a free what the heck wait why
do we have to talk to a kid I just want
the goods oh so far we don't have money
to spend so far the way we dressed
little yeah okay this is a little too
much a little too much uh Small Talk
looking for the child child I see
it
guys I just want to buy stuff we we're
going to go see a
[Music]
if you have time yet why not visit the
what the heck he's just he's what do you
he has nothing he's just he's just maybe
the child has something for us going go
crazy I don't know buy the child do you
think we could buy the
child can we you want a child can we buy
the child oh don't
know where world this is I think I've
gone the long way
oh the child PR Aces is it my job is to
keep an eye on scare away birds and
stuff let me know you want Heroes boy
this is my lucky day this is the
child building empty P you and you heres
can build whatever you like you can work
get to build
birding can I tell you a secret did you
know there's a place called The Pit the
P mom says that's to but I can play
really fun game you're here I to let you
maybe can check it tell me what it's
stop any time if you want to do some
building or gardening the pit can I tell
you a secret did you know there's a
place in town called the pit isn't that
where the Amber coin people
go kids aren't allowed to go really fun
[Music]
okay oh wait it's over
here I feel like I
belong the pit where's the
pit it
pit pit hello pit oh
pit
[Music]
pit oh excuse you lucky lady lucky lady
I've got a game for you your new face oh
my gosh stop it stop it you're one of
them arrows what saved the town aren't
you I want to get rich three we're
getting rich I want to get r i want get
promise it's nothing Shady see how I run
with the Jade sword before I join the
Amber coin where the G Master took us
out to un some stains they told us how
to work as a team just point yourself at
your mate and right click and then you
can select where to invit your oh
what huh he's just teaching us how to
trade and join parties not realizing
that way ahead we're so ahead can you
keep up with the program pit Dorman
please you
ever feeling too l or too heavy maybe
come down here to the pit and play
around or and if you ever see some por
saw walking out of your penis don't
worry about it that won't happen to you
are you Lu oh is this gambling it is
there's a gambling thing in here please
meet him at the jadea Guild Hall all
right where's the Jade sword Guild Hall
oh goodness it's really having us going
around in circles in
it I don't know how I feel about
this just running
around running around and around and
around oh my God it's on the other
side why is it so far
away woo
is it
here huh I've lost it
um oh there he
is did I think I think it's here I'm not
sure okay is it here is it it
oh there're the members where's the king
oh there he
is I mean not the king the Guild
Master this one I see you returned Brave
hero I hope you familiarized yourself
with the town and learned about
venturing we all liament what has
befallen the lands that's out our
kingdom the Calamity in stains it has
born and turn most of the world into a
wasteland you must be shaken to some who
found yourselves in another world but I
pray you will Aid us in our fight
um f PR is a way for you to regain your
powers of
Revelation to that end I have just
received word from one of our Scouts
regarding a POS lead while investigating
the Calamity near the pl our comrades CH
Upon A mysterious
anent they observed from the r and light
to the the Revelation which we used to
rep the stay
King SC stationed at the ruins the
I ask you
my to go forth
with exit the Town Gate head to the
plane and speak to hes of the chain
sword I feel like we're speed running
this eai adventure I suddenly have a lot
of bread I get this bread from say why
do I have so much bread I'm going to
call
somebody I'm going to call see I'm going
to let's see where kitty cat is player
is in a call she still made a
voicemail all right speedrun it is all
right we go to a what do we have to do
go to a where do we going we go outside
we go okay we go outside all right
outside
outside how where
where how I go outside
again I've forgotten how to go outside
it down
here
oh how do I go outside three oh oh this
is the oh um what uh
what uh
what the
gate you think I remember where the gate
is where'd you go I'm
here
where I hear a voice cuz I'm calling you
oh long
distance um I don't know I'm back at
there I I can go back to the guild the
Amber coin
Guild where the heck is that I don't
know can you come uh where are you I'm
in front of where we just were together
okay oh no oh I've reached the gate okay
hold on where are you we are supposed to
go to the gate
over okay so it's along here somewhere
okay oh oh oh there you are there you
are hello hello the gate is over here so
we're going back to the gate we're going
back to the gate back to the gate here
we
go all right all right all right all
righty all
righty I'm being BM man get out of here
get out of
here got The Lost
Child we will help
you uh you're
welcome that's the last time I'm helping
anyone goodness right where the heck is
my
validation absolutely ridiculous all
right head to the PLS is this the right
is this the right oh I just realized
we're still on a call together oh even
though do we get charged by the minute I
wonder she
just just stay on call all the time stay
on somebody's hurting you oh no I hurt
them back thank you my power is so weak
that I can't even kill a
cow I think mine is too don't worry I'm
getting money I'm getting money I'm
getting money I'm getting oh that's not
very much
money right right right
ow we got to go speak to H this of the
giant sword oh yes okay
okay okay we both got money I think if
we work together we get more money oh I
didn't get money did you take my money
three okay let go
okay I don't know where I am burdened
with is that
gold Wait no that's I three three we got
we got three iron
I want some I do just in case yeah you
know nice nice
have all right later all right all right
we good all right well we've reached the
fork in the row three I don't know what
to do here do we go left or we go right
uh uh we go this way which way this way
I think this way
where we really we're going all the way
out here really oh we have to then we're
going to the
planes Hest of the oh there he is Hest
of the kitty
cat what the heck what the heck we found
you we found I didn't you answer your
phone I was so worried we're on the
phone why are you on the phone next to
each
other well because sometimes we're not
next to each
other I call you I love how we we
thought like all right we got talk to
you our initial for determined that the
portal has been yet to be sealed there's
no way to enter the r where at last now
to proce you mut again my reporter
hearing
strange I don't know
why way anyway I was saying um when I
was done with the quest it appeared on
the bottom left
the
compl it still doesn't say it for me
have you guys completed the the quest
let's try again then guys we're going to
go kill people we're going to go kill
people
now well they're not people B I'm sorry
I was muted by mistake it's okay have
you completed the quest yeah we we're
doing the one with K now and then we go
to the dungeon oh we going to go
together yeah we got to kill stuff
too why
all right
one
two right
three say one right doesn't keep do we
have to count ourselves four I think
so I've done four done with it I'm on
four right
now please resp
done please
respa I need
enemies over here
oh what the heck you
cheated five these are the thingies
right squid hurts squid hurts hurt okay
we I can make a partyle one sec okay I
think I I think you you guys may need to
accept
okay right I don't know how many that
is
six is it
six I'm just going to kill as many
as seven
hit
this
eight
nine
oops nine one more
I need one
more no it's mine mine it's it's our
ours K
kill dang it dang
[Music]
it oh I just realized you guys haven't
been able to hear the game volume this
entire time I'm so
sorry but that was mine
oh I've got 10 I
don't slow
P
hey got it did you do it I got the quest
finished yeah nice nice
nice oh after the hero slow those stains
a key appeared from out of thin air
could this be what the voice meant by
the SS of stains open the
way perhaps this key is What will open
the portal into the ruins you want to
take with you hero we shall secure the
surroundings and you may proceed
undisturbed the secrets of the ruins
awake I'm excited for the dungeon oh is
this the dungeon we're dungeoning now
yeah we're dunging now here
here when you finished yeah let's go
okay you you have a you all proceeded in
the quest right yeah yeah what the say
just to double check it says investigate
the underworld dungeon right yeah okay
good we can go then let's go let's kill
this
okay let's go it's actually right there
huh is it let's go
yay woo battle
ches
no let's go time to fight time to fight
guess yeah let's go we're ready we're
ready we're let's
go is it is that the
dungeon W ready to enter the dungeon
enter dungeon ready yeah ready I'm ready
wait oh wait enter oh ready ready yeah
I'm ready yeah every click ready I
clicked ready I'm I'm click I clicked
ready okay standing by to enter dungeon
okay oh enter dungeon no player standing
by what what do we just click enter
now no player stand by it says no player
standing by
though I think could it be uh La can you
like in your party settings cuz you're
the party leader can you wait wait wait
wait you can click out wait click out
and then go back in cuz then it says
that I'm waiting now oh wait wait
wait wait I click
what do you see it
now wait how do I how do I get
back wait how do you know how do you do
that
ready B how do you do that well well I
just walk back and then walk closer to
it it says no player standing by um wait
do you want to disband the
party now I think it's because iris is
in it so disband and then we can remake
the Party Irish
Irish how do you just band the party now
oh here right
click and
then
uh invite to invite wait you kicked Bae
from the party yeah I'm out oh oh I see
I see I see I see see I'm out I got
kicked okay now I'm out as well all
right let's make a new party yeah your
party party you invite you guys yeah
we're I see your party says l and m
think B an invite yep I'm
in okay you in wait hold
on the party or ready to oh I'm in the
party okay right okay here we go let's
try this is one out of one is that okay
okay I'm ready oh now now it's working
oh now it's working yeah I'm ready too
okay ready ready M press ready press
ready ready yeah it looks like you
didn't press ready
yet it sounds that I did though like
what oh no no I did uh three hasn't
pressed ready
yet three has gone three three
oh three
where is
she where' she go where did she go
mysterious uh
three oh did she like fall for the world
or something oh maybe three what
happened three talk to me it appears
that I did not accept the party invite
and I entered the dungeon by
myself she entered the dungeon
what okay we got to enter all right
we're entering Al by accident I guess
but you may not you okay I'm going to
going to go now are we going are we are
we entering hold on hold on hold on can
you not exit the dungeon I don't think
so maybe if I kill myself you guys even
hear her cuz I don't hear her oh I'm I'm
calling her I'm calling her I kill
myself maybe do you respawn back at the
when people talk to themselves
[Music]
buds in their ears and you don't realize
they're on a call hold
[Music]
on let's see you already look how
that
uhoh do I have cap lock on I can't tell
maybe I should leave the game I think I
do yeah it's probably glitching I'm
going to leave party stuff the mind I
I'll be right back all
right confusion has entered the chat
what are we doing are we waiting for
tree yes okay here come
oh yes try again this she is it is nice
to see you once again hello hello we
have missed you yeah we miss you very
much miss all of you
too I in party you always in the party
you just need to be ready I was ready I
was not right now but hold on hold on
don't click the sword click the yay yeah
we
ready
[Music]
time where we explore don't ask why but
go here to this door the under world the
domain of boundless oppressive Darkness
as fear it is unavoidable it holds the
final resting place for every creature
that walks the Earth yet even in this
realm of the Dead those are who live and
call it home oh my this feels like it
was written by the hands of death oh my
goodness what are we going to do um we
must explore orange
juice oh goodness
I I don't think that's oranges um which
way are we supposed to go maybe we go
another that you really like the fire C
but maybe this is not the kind of fire
you I missed the jump you can do it jump
no oh wait wait wait hold on which which
which block is it
from it can do it excuse me big jump big
jump let
jump like
that oh it was the wrong oh I see hold
on the buttons are different I mean what
buttons I mean oh I just forgot how to
run for a second hold give me a
second yeah almost
almost here
oh got it there we go let's go it's a
different button storry where did they
go I don't
know okay we got to jump
again
okay wait why
this I don't know where they
are three where someone's calling me
sorry the voices we're here we're over
here we're over here where's over here
did you see them okay okay okay okay
okay here okay we need to jump over here
first I think wait wait oh over there
okay yeah over there and then we go in
the circle okay yeah and we jump over
here now
okay parkour all
right oh okay we're good okay we're good
jump oh be careful
guys where are we
going are we just
exploring got our own blocks I wonder
can we place them oh we can
try I have Cobblestone no we can't
a that would be
cheating this is giving me high blood
pressure
new checkpoint unlocked nice yes I I'm
not sure where we're supposed to go from
here perhaps towards that castle oh that
would be that would be a marvelous idea
I'm going to follow you
perhaps can I place any box right no
hope I don't die
okay easy all
right jump here ow sorry we have full
damage
too yeah careful
careful be careful oh I messed
up no no
no we she probably respawn on the
checkpoint oh that's true that's true
that's
true it's okay it's okay oh thank
goodness we thought we lost you forever
so wored that I have she's back she's
back I heard the answer to the dream
question the dream care question you
ever uh dream about
flying where ow ouch that one hurt yeah
okay let's have this other checkpoint as
well yeah yeah let's go let's go go to
the check oh be careful here
good checkpoint checkpoint all right
let's wait for the other two before we
succeed y
oh remember to eat food because if you
don't have the food
bar you're not going to run no someone
from the Lava Girl Shark with look
checkpoint oopsie
oop it been checked not again not a
shortcut shortcut all right let's go
let's go to the
castle oh my goodness gracious
me wee
um I think it's this way I'm not
particularly sure do we go
around I don't know which way I think we
go this way we go around want to try
that one we go up maybe I don't know oh
goodness um yes and then you run you run
yeah's right
all
right up up up up up up up up
up
up up up up up up up up
up up up up up
a three we did it we did it they just
kill themselves so they can come up here
that's the Strat speed Strat wa is it is
it is it group is it is it group
checkpoint yeah oh it's all right they
there I see them you're doing great you
can do it you can do
it look at them go look at them go
she could not do it it's all right but
look look she'll be behind us hello yeah
you you figured out the strap know what
it's a group it's a group checkpoint
let's
go now just die just just
die yourself just jump jump I don't
think she can hear us hold on let me
call her real
quick you can also try I just jump
Thea the
lava wait jump further
yeah yeah there we
go we ready are we ready everybody F
everybody F all right let's go let's go
oh that's mine let's go wow wow my oh my
right I just realized weren't we told to
go in like not just our group in
dungeons weren't we told to go with like
few groups um I don't remember no they
only said like there's
a can be in the dunge at the same time
okay so we don't need anybody else oh
I'm still on call I'm sorry I was on the
pH one of the orange care
nice check the corners check the corners
are we doing
go next time I have let's stick to each
other because we're going to get lost in
the dungeon yeah we found the to wait
what is this we found something what
checkpoint oh I got a triangle someone
got I got a triangle wait what we can
take it wa why how did you take it how
did you take you filled it up or I I
think we I think the zombies are going
to drop those so we got to kill more
okay so we need to find a star and a
circle to fill it right ccle I found the
circle nice nice nice let's go we got
the star we got immediately brought it
to us okay we need a circle now I'm how
do I put the circle in how do I put
yay wait we had several circles
yeah sure to
stay Che woohoo remember to eat yes
remember to eat
everybody
wow what does this say checkpoint
another life expired leaving behind a
tiny flickering light a soul
representing both a legacy and an ending
I
read for us read for us the veiled
figure cradled it in her hands and with
a hint of melancholy she whispered is
this the right thing to do it's if you
need to ask it's never the right thing
to do
okay let's proceed
Maiden Amber kind Amber kind
am Amber Amber
Co wao there's so many stairs I don't I
don't like there so many why are there
so many stairs I know my fo
is what is this
this is this a a puzzle it's a
puzzle I'm going to be absolutely
useless all righty um one two oh what
what Chang is it I don't know I just
touching it how what are you are you
right clicking it oh okay to coordinate
well uh maybe each each person takes
charge of one side or so yeah I was
supposed to put all the lights onto onto
the front face
maybe I think you just want the whole
thing to light up yeah I think all of
them have to light up I
see I love these kind of riddles I hate
these kind of riddles I hate them too is
this okay hey oh oh wait mine was full
for a moment yeah it's uh each each side
affects the other side it's not just one
face ah I see um wait hold
on that's we should just observe for a
minute I'm not sure if this might not
actually be un riddled to stop every
Guild from
proceeding we can do it I believe it's
just a distraction no a distraction that
would be funny okay I really have to go
to an idol meeting is just not this is
probably not the best
time maybe try to figure out one side
I think I can't change anything
anymore H can I use up my
tries okay
oh I can't do
anything difficult it seems like a good
time is it a good time I do need I'm
going go to an idle meeting and let you
guys figure this one
okay I'll
be again oh oh I F I thought I F I F S I
just got a little bit
frustrated give me the power to press
the lights I don't understand the the
way they change I think it's like it's
um okay so it's
two I'm just going to keep pressing
until something works oh my goodness oh
wait I think I I think I understand
someone goes in the other side and
follow my instruction
yes uh up on the top top top top left
top left click on the top
left okay nothing happened no it's the
adjacent ones it's the ones next to each
other that turned on and off okay they
got it
oh I was able to it so like maybe it's
better like if two people just do that
cuz maybe like we can coord better I'm
not sure oh I have also lost the ability
R you're on your
own no oh God okay okay no you run you
run okay I I'll try I'll try let me let
me do
it what's is
that
weird press too many
times I pressed it too many times okay
here Q are of the
orange K of the
orange no
without doing anything helpful
I
I'm I'm trying to I I I try to regain oh
no it still doesn't
work still can't press it I I am trying
you're doing
great I am
trying okay this
one do you have any kind of strategy l
no I'm just like trying to understand
the pattern that's how I would do it
honestly
so if you have any suggest you're doing
great no they can't use it anymore
either so it's not do we have to make
just one line
or okay one side is oh
nice go one side I hope it stays like
that I hope is like that
yeah looking good though looking good
looking
good let me know if it
changes uh yeah left side is still safe
and full okay okay let's let's keep it
as it is we still at it and L is the
only one able to press things what oh
yeah you want to probably keep those the
way they are on the left side we've got
one face down we just need the other two
to
go other three three yeah I feel like
just in discriminately pressing them
without
communicating not work what do you mean
that sounds
amazing nice it's working it'sing uh one
sec this is just
like nous come on Kitty
doing great
Kitty I'm trying to
understand oh no we've lost the
side
no wait it's it's changing on itself oh
no I think I think three is also
pressing that was my bad my
bad what you want me to do
I don't know I feel like everybody
working on one side maybe doesn't
work oh okay okay okay
gr send
help send
help
maybe to that only one person I wonder
how the others going otherwise it's 2K I
wonder yeah one group apparently solved
it so far oh wow
what we can do it well I wish we could
press it yes not you guys can't press
it is like maybe a specific way to make
it I'm not sure another group made it
apparently
no a there should be a a reset button do
you mean there really is one or are you
just saying where where's the reset
button
just got to see which one is I don't
think there is one
oh they're not the opposite yeah let's
try actually can you tell me actually
okay let me see we probably need to face
the
[Music]
other sorry this is like so on
you no it's okay
okay let me check this PO actually let's
try to understand the logic of a like
this yeah so I mean there's like I know
if there's a simpler way of just like
being like Oh you click and see oh
you're clicking again okay you can click
then okay let's do together I can click
yeah let's do
together oh I can't click anymore almost
almost
almost you I can't C
yeah it looks
good okay going to
no okay now I I I got an idea
oops mhm she can do
it adjacent blocks adjacent
blocks keep on
clicking keep oning at it oh nice nice
nice you got this one oh wait H you had
this
side
oh how that works I really don't get the
logic of this
game if you wait so now this side wait
wait wait
wait do one side out of time because you
can if you I don't know how to exp I
don't understand why you're not able to
click it though maybe it's a b there's
no way that it's a limited been clicking
at the most yeah yeah it's probably B
but it's probably better than all four
of us doing it at the same time so that
is true yeah but the way to do it is
like you just keep track of like what
each like one block what it
fills but you just got to be mindful of
the ones that are on the side because
they'll affect the ones that are on a
different face yeah so like careful
touch like so here's
good this is probably good but you can't
can't touch
these oh there you go there you
go yeah yeah pretty much good job good
job all right you're doing
great
yeah oh looks
good something like
that I feel like you're you're very
close you're doing you're doing so good
oh
oh in the kitty
we let's
go did she did want to
MVP
yay the gold cat all right time to be
useful again
let's go oh my
godington oh my God underw so dark they
chandelier
my as can you
see oh my God oh my
[Music]
God I don't know if we should have gone
this way is he getting rid of the whole
Bridge
I feel that might be what he's doing we
go the other
way no no no no wait what a checkpoint
oh this is a new checkpoint okay oh
supposed to happen script to death all
right okay what is this don't eat it
it's a mushroom um um um
um
um the mushroom meanwhile is that
decoration is it just decoration oh yeah
I know what to do I know what to too ah
what' you do oh wait someone someone
received bone
meal yeah oh okay can you use
the and then ow more and then we the Tre
more more bone
meal can we make it bigger I'm going to
die more B
meal have this is hard to
ascend come here come here die on
this if you have B me please use
it okay
okay this or becom oh I think we can
climb not hold there
mm kill on the thingy kill on the thingy
nice nice nice nice nice
nice oh I got
you there you go nice nice wo it's so
big now oh it's like spawning the the
okay what you call it
again a this is so cool
fire fire get them get them to die like
on the tree can we go now if you can I
don't know can we maybe maybe we can
yeah maybe let's try oh I think we might
be able to ascend there's a button here
oh how do you climb there's a button on
the
tree just press press face jump into
it I said I would several
buttons but I guess they don't do
anything
no I think these might just be stairs
[Music]
oh are you going up yeah but actually we
might oh no it's already reaching the
top I can see from
here yes it's reaching the top both
sides actually I can't get it oh I got
maybe just from
hereid weird I don't
know thep oh wait wait these thing it's
the vines right yeah yeah
maybe
yeah I can't
button here I don't think the buttons do
anything oh it's just there just there
okay yeah it's just there this face bar
it doesn't
work fell
oh
then I made it okay up here and then up
here up here here
oh jump on the on the yeah that one
first on the side
okay I'll catch you thank
you okay two
more I'm a fire starter mhm oh my
goodness oh okay we got to do it again I
see let's start killing skeletons first
then okay meow meow meow meow meow come
here's a good skeleton nice
who oh
no think do we want them to die on on
here you made it yeah
welcome oh oh more okay follow here
follow me hello over here I feel like
maybe wouldn't we only need one of the
trees to grow why is there two platforms
where did my oh my bone meal disappeared
oh it's over there okay okay how come
here are you collecting bone meal in
your inventory you have to kill them on
the thing oh I you have to kill them on
the
thing I
see come here
nice behind
you and
I'll
woo we need to also do this
one not enough though not enough there
only one skeleton out of this is pretty
difficult wait wait wait it has to die
on the tree it has to die on the tree
yeah
this one he's fallowing come
here drop him oh wait wait wait wait
wait don't kill a he's going to kill me
wait doesn't drop the bone meal it has
to die onto the tree onto the tree he's
going to kill me oh
okay come here come
here
nice another one and another here come
here come here come here where
did a bit more over here come over here
oh no yeah no no it's okay no no you
can't collect it it has to be on the on
the tree on the tree on the tree yeah
yeah yeah okay okay I'm going to
wo come here come here good oh what is
that oh you you dice
yeah is that enough wait I think we need
maybe one more looks almost enough maybe
for safety one more one more okay okay
okay maybe on the on on the left
side okay going to kill kill me don't
kill me there you go okay uh fully grown
at this point then
[Music]
okay
yeah I think welcome back I think this
should be okay
now let's
try H whoo whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoo whoo back up buddy hey buddy
hey buddy pal buddy pal get out of here
oh I see it I see
it
okay
it you
go where do I got for
here I think I think over there
yeah no get her oh she has to come back
now all right okay does this then
connect ah okay wait maybe
not
um oh up here up here up here up here
okay now go uh wait and then wait no not
this way this
way oh god um
I am confused
uh oh maybe from here up here up no oh
follow the buttons wait how do I go up
from
here up here maybe
oh the buttons the
buttons oh my God I'm just seeing I see
red uh no we can't there's no way up
here uh maybe on the top go back down go
back down go back
down oh
here where yeah yeah wait wait where
oh
oh and now I don't know uh oh do we have
to go to the other tree do you think
probably I don't see the other button
yet so oh maybe down there it down there
yeah you can do it I believe let me go
to the go in front of you in front of
you there's one over there can't you
make that
one the one that's there
uh hold
on no this one over here not this one no
the one to the right wait batt can you
jump yes I will not be able to forget
that there's no over here is this just
not taking me down or should I go this
way I thought it was this way and then
we go around
I don't know down maybe there's multiple
paths speaks to
woo
oh um and then we go my
here I see that okay I just didn't
follow the buttons but
yeah that's what I mean guys I found it
you got it you have to go down to go up
no just die just die just die I got the
checkpoint woo let's
go
yay yeah you guys made me feel like I
was being stupid for thinking you got to
go down a little bit oh no that wasn't
so hard at all woohoo I'm going to read
the next part okay I'm going to read
this
bye to the din the the N of the
Underworld the
light emanated my soul was vetal V vital
vital you got this you got this do s
well okay now I cannot read anymore for
some reason oh
oh I cannot read anymore I don't know it
doesn't mean doesn't on next page it
doesn't work no it doesn't
work I don't know yeah you can be the
other the other ESL will
continue they needed it to survive in
this ever cold and dark environment yet
among them there was a heretic who
called their Customs into question do we
really need to take others lives to
sustain our own stain wi no there has to
be another way and so she stepped into
the plane above oh plane which plane
this
[Music]
plane is the
last
woo your power Revelation is gone
stronger we recovered the prop of your
[Music]
members I
remember I
remember
oh hold
on is it
beo this this this's a video
hold on
[Music]
a Reaper's job is to end people's lives
and take their
souls that's how it's always been the
spirits of the underworld need their
[Music]
sustenance but I keep
wondering is this the right thing to do
no it's not
[Applause]
[Music]
what's going
[Applause]
on look at
that turns out we can also use people's
emotion we don't need their souls at all
[Music]
Reaper should help the
living that take away their future if
the others can't accept that that's
their
loss I'll do things my
way NY
what what was
that oh my golly
gosh oh my golly
gosh who was
that I have no idea who that was but oh
my goodness that was absolutely amazing
I've done
it oh have you done it I've watched it
yes oh my goodness have they watched it
too I think they're watching it I'm done
you're done okay M doesn't seem done
then three is watching it probably at
this moment as we
speak
okay it was funny is that first time wow
you saw it right yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah it was so cool is that the memories
that they they've told us about yeah
that lady didn't we see her already
running
around actually I haven't talked to her
it looks familiar where was that oh my
God she was like slaying oh oh my
goodness I'm her fan now when I see her
again I must talk to her yeah I that's
it we've done the first dungeon let's go
I'm so happy
yooo good job good job
everybody but it's so good actually how
do we return is it is that light up
ahead where the Moon is I'm going to
return by leaving
oh hero hello who are you the heck
hello hello travel pleasure to see
everyone are you leaving or are you
incoming we are
incoming I wish you luck fellow hero
this isn't the right way it's not the
right way you have to fall off this
Cliff back yeah yes oh wait you
otherwise yeah it's over there you have
to
jum down there pay your taxes yeah just
down down down as a member of the ceran
cup I easily yeah yeah all the way down
all the way down you don't want we don't
want that death you want this death
there's a move move further move further
follow the light it means you're not
ready I can't jump oh it's not allowing
me to she's not ready oh she is not
ready to to to face the
dungeon oh my my weapon is so cool
actually three I have a regret to say
that the bay may be crashing all
right so is Catra Eisenhower you want to
head back to let's go back back to back
head back the B is losing
Consciousness
uh okay okay that's the bridge so around
here this area where we're waiting in
front of the dungeon pink
lady red CR lady I just saw we just saw
you pink
lady this no we just saw you were doing
something oh yeah I just saw your most
inner thoughts I we saw the inner
workings of your brain I know what you
are I don't know what they're talking
about I know know who you are I know
what you are I know your deepest darkest
seone I know I know everything about I
know all right good night I'm going home
goodbye
my goodness I I'm
so we we have to wait do we have to
speak to the we have to speak to do we
do we have to speak to the Jade sword
Guild Master
again I I have I I have
questions get out of here
you guys doing to my honorary ENT gu
[Music]
M Valor all right well me I guess that's
it for today all right I don't know what
to do now do we go back and speak who do
we speak
to oh we go back and speak to all right
we go back and speak to him all right
all right right
okay
okay we speak to this verus we have to
speak to
veridus oh Lord
Mighty I have
returned Brave hero I'm had to say and
you have returned unharmed pray tell
what transpired at the
ruins I see to think the ruins held such
Secrets a crystal deep within that when
touch returns a fragment of your
memories to you memories in which in
turn reawaken the power of
Revelation IIT at only a fraction of it
its potential that's your summoning and
the discovery of these ruins should
coincide so closely there must be some
connection between the ruins and the
power of
Revelation Brave hero seek rubius the
guil master of the Scarlet
one his Guild has been sear for strange
ruins in the lands of listo mayhaps they
have discovered something
I am going home and never returning ever
again thank you very
much never again I'm going
home and
sleeping for years to
come I have dece I have
defeated
one such dungeon for you and I simply
refuse to do any more than
that I am
going I am
going to enter my internal
Slumber andless
that thank you all for joining this
marvelous
adventure the B bids you a do
and
um
goodbye
farewell S Help
[Music]