[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
he
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
la
a
[Music]
no
[Applause]
[Music]
n
hello hello
[Music]
[Applause]
hello Mary Mary among us among
among
us about
those welcome everybody to the uh
Christmas or Holan holiday Among Us
stream we have gathered here today with
so many lovely cute girls and we're
going to have fun choking and stabbing
each other right yeah sounds like kind
of fun it's a sh
[Music]
let's go awesome well we're going to um
do it without proximity chat by the way
guys uh because you know we have some
first timers here I think it's Advent
girls's first time among using
here first timers
that's we're not s yeah find out how
they act when when they're imposter we
can't tell yet like for others maybe we
already know a tell but for these
newbies we don't know what is their tell
maybe that's maybe you could tell us
would you be so kind in your
introduction tell me what your tell
is please nah you got to find that out
that information is classified you need
a little cash money up front first I'll
try well okay then let's start with
introductions let's start with the only
one who's a real astronaut Here Am
h Hello Amilia Watson number one
astronaut
detective yeah I like Among Us so I'm
excited to play let's go let's
go because maybe there's some new
viewers at this point who don't
understand why is am able to wear her
own clothes in the game and why am I
wearing P's clothes and is wearing man's
clothes am do you want to explain uh yes
we have H we had a collab with Among Us
where you could get a few uh Hol live
outfits and items in the Among Us shop
but I don't think it's available anymore
I too bad if you miss out me and are P
right
now I thought this was a keyboard slam
you guys are actually you guys are in a
room okay oh yeah okay I thought you
just slamed the keyboard
ke keyboard slam I know that's what it
looks like code looking like a slam
you're giving them hints you're
giving and slam welcome to the slam jam
please join thank go fertilizer who is
calm
spam all right well I guess
that's all
right yummy a Spam color that was
amazing nice box oh while we're at at
Callie's uh you know bullying her for
her name Callie please introduce
yourself so we know that's
really oh yeah if you insist me a it's
me Mor Kip H life English is hardworking
Shinigami uh I'm in a place with very
terrible internet so I can't stream my
POV but I'm very excited to be here with
all of these lovely ladies as a sheriff
completing my tasks and making sure that
we win the day let's go yes he wouldn't
kill anybody she now known
as calm
I guess it's now but yeah I'm so happy
you're joining even though you can't
like stream properly thank you so much
the dead beats they trained me well I
wanted to show off my new skills that
the dead beats
have fairly recently oh we got to watch
out she's good at the
game thanks to the dead Beast you just
ask us how you kill people in this
game okay I guess I didn't help at all
that you played it recently was
unhelpful well okay moving on to fun
where is she where is she I can't
find I'm in hiding you can't vote me as
the Imposter if I'm hiding
right there is fun Hol live English
promise hello hello I'm here does it
feel does it feel like normal now like
it still feels weird to me to hear that
introduction
promise
yeah I think so fresh still it is it is
still pretty fresh but I like it think
boat yeah not boats I feel like
everyone's been traumatized by boats
Rec Trend in the whole lot of English of
watching school
days no it
was last
year told me about the tree there's a
family
stair
why do you like it there's a staircase
did you know there a stairc I know there
a stair I know now
thanksa I have no idea what these girl
are talking about good I'm so confused I
wish it's too cursed yeah it's nice that
everybody is having fun school days and
all that fun a jolly season it is great
piece of Cinema yeah all right Iris our
number one Christmas lover hello yes
you're number one Christmas lover here
hris it's Iris from H live English
promise you're one game the game we just
we just won't we just won't kill people
um uh I love this game but I I I really
suck at being imposter but yeah so so
yosu yeah but I'll do my best are you
really bad at it I don't remember I I
was horrible imposter last time I played
this I screwed up so she gets imposter
maybe you just need a better mate to
work with cuz you're dumb d
m on my face of a poopy
head's what you talking about the lobby
will fall apart it's no problem we's
take our time okay yeah by the way have
you guys speaking of Iris have you guys
all seen the yesterday and today's
episodes of the Holo Ian Adent calendar
cuz Iris was very involved in them I was
very involved in them yes just and they
were both in
3D space yep so Iris why did you do it
um oh it's cuz you know we needed some
light to bring up the Christmas spirit
you know what better light than actual
fire right yeah oh that makes sense and
you know it was my whole plan so that I
I could become the Christmas tree in
order to become the Christmas tree you
needed to burn the actual Christmas tree
first true you burning Christmas trees
that's kind
of it is the master plan it's pretty
late yes it's very
lit it was
fire indeed fire fire light the fire
fire fire light the fire fire light the
fire fire fire like the fire okay uh
everybody's uh joining again in the
lobby I think I'm coming I got my name I
freed Comm spam he doesn't exist
anymore more com spam I'm sad is it
going to hide the code if I have
streamer mode on yeah yes yes yes it's
hidden for me it does hidden people self
introduction please hi uh bomu I'm K beu
sparkling Gem of Hall life English
Advent and I'm a space Rock but that
doesn't mean you're allowed to Stellar
Stellar me out of the ship so I am not
sus I am
nice
wow okay that was pretty good be
nice no no that doesn't here doesn't
work
here man so you have to prove yourself
prove the truth you can't fool us be
you're sus dang already you're already
sus already why are you
doing I think I think it's
her I think it's guess it's bio it's
definitely
bi okay let's move on to F
please I'm I I'm
I'm
together
your voice okay M
Coco sometimes I become a dragon
sometimes you know but as long as you
know I'm not Chihuahua I'm not Hua
I'm there we go together we make the
best crew mate you know God dogs a good
crew mate not an kind of unfair it's
kind of unfair oh yeah if you're
impostor it's two it's two of you guys
I think I think we should vote them out
right away every time I think so
too well let's not do that but indeed as
a crew mate they might be very helpful
cuz it's two brains for one I guess I
guess who's on the keyboard who's
controlling contr I'm the legs you're
the brains who I'm also the the pointer
finger yeah nice looking forward
to
a I'll be nice to see one one day they
will play separately but today is not
today isn't this game on mobile maybe
somebody could play on mobile I I don't
know I think there is
conect doesn't on this
[Music]
side well okay and then now we
stop
definely an imposter hi Darlings this is
H
adish diva is Raven CR I'm an impostor
today because I'm pretending to be M and
Cal yeah I
guess oh my go bre it till you make it
it till you make
it we're we're a nice couple in there so
I know how ironic you're guys I should
be running away from
you I don't want your child narissa good
luck even if honey Works made a song
about our child I don't want
it okay and
then
please
or from live English Pro what H live
English
promise um please don't arrest me I'm
going to be a very good egg for today uh
cuz even if I want to be an impostor I
never get it I will never get it so you
trust me I believe her I trust her 100%
yes I trust her 100% I trust everyone
100 what are the chances
thatth I look so kind pretty high none
of none of us will get imposter probably
yeah probably none of us yeah that's
how many how many imposters are we doing
I set it to
two cuz
we're I don't know should do three I
don't know no two is good two is good
okay and I I have in case you're
interested uh two long tasks and five
short tasks uh as well as two common
tasks I don't remember what common tasks
were that's
suspicious why you you don't remember
yeah oh yeah cuz imposters don't do
tasks well it's been too long they had
rolls or something right like you can do
stuff now or
something like
rolls oh yeah wasn't there something
besides crew mate now like um uh
likees help imposter like the Spy or
something like that's
not they're in the bottom yeah keep them
on that's fun okay yeah I don't know how
does that work though I don't know it
tells you at the beginning so wait yeah
there's four roles there I don't know
you girls can probably see them in the
settings uh on the on the computer here
there's a scientist who can access a
portable vitals panel so they can check
at any point of time if there's somebody
dead so they always see the status of
the crew and then there's an engineer
who can use the vents even though
they're not an imposter but then you
might be sus to be like I'm not the
Imposter I just vent because I can oh
that's pretty cool really and then the
guardian angel uh is the ghost of the
very first one of us that
dies oh is that how it works the first
person that dies something like that the
garden Ang the ghost of the first Dead
crew mate they can temporarily shield
and protect other living crew mates so I
guess if you're the first one that dies
you become the guardian angel and then
you can protect somebody else oh so that
they don't die yeah if you do it
properly and well timed you'll be able
to prevent imposters from killing their
victims sounds amazing me throwing so
that I can become the guardian
angel
a already are yes no wow and then
there's a shape shifter who can who can
change the appearance and disguise
themselves as other crew mates why would
you do that though that just confuses
everyone impost
it's supposed to make the impostor
harder to find too because then you know
the Imposter can say I'm the engineer oh
no I'm the shape you know like please I
promise I'm not a murderer yeah it
doesn't say that it's only impostor but
why would why would why would a crew
mate do this I don't know let's turn
that one off but I like the other ones
yeah should I should I keep them or
should I
is
oh it is okay yeah it just doesn't say
so so wait does only one impostor is
only one imposter The Shape Shifter is
that how it works uh I can set how many
there will be I can
say I can say we want two or I can say
we I want one or zero I can set it in
the
settings but if I do one then only one
of the uh imposters will be Shape
Shifter but only 50% chance the one will
be oh yeah I can I can make it higher
too we have one for sure I default is
good right it's probably bad
default okay okay default then let's
keep the rolls then let's go we're
going before
we before before we go um can we have
the visual tasks off because if we have
it on it might be too easy visual tasks
off oh
true yes very good okay and before we
start I'm Tak I organized this thing the
logos and the thumbnails are
commissioned by me
[Music]
so don't kill me because I I pay for
this okay don't kill
me
we byebye byebye bye
byebye
hell
yeah
okay uh I've never played this map
before um I don't remember how to play
among us if I'm honest you guys can
still hear me right they they can't hear
me
okay what is
this what do I
do h
how do I do this
ouchie get away from
me I
okay not
me oh this map seems big I wish I had a
map of the map I probably can't access
that
somehow what
the you know I do quite like mushrooms
so I'm not going to complain about this
mushrooms are
great no
no miss you the only real you guys tell
the only real astronaut you know what
that means we don't have a chance of
getting back to our own
no unbelievable so who saw Watson I
didn't see her at all I didn't see her I
didn't see her at all oh I can see who
who reported just now me I did tell us
about it did tell us about it where was
the body so I was going around
Communications um trying to figure out
the mushrooms and what not and I went
down uh the the little zip line and then
in the storage room Amy was
dead storage
room we saw around the
[Music]
Busom wait so F was also in the storage
no no we were at the mushrooms and we
were having problems with that and crony
Senpai was around and then crony Senpai
went down but was there too yeah yeah
mococo was chasing me
around confused I don't know what's
going on I have mushroom problems yeah I
had like a meat problem I don't know
like it I suddenly turned into like a a
lighter pink and there was like a chunk
of meat chasing
me did any get the cuff and then they ch
to people or something what does that do
is that just an effect to freak you out
or does it do something I don't know I
don't know I think it I think the the
the mushroom like if you touch it or
something um it hides the the people so
you can just like kill them and run away
and it swaps my skin or something like
that yeah know I had that happen to me
too oh did I why you know that
hot yeah my skin got swapped as well
yeah me too it swaps the skin became a
wizard and then I had a little worm next
to me for a moment and then poof it was
gone and the light was back
on weird I I don't know what what goes
on in this m I don't know I feel like I
trusted crony Senpai and now I feel like
I don't trust cron yeah you know huh I
will say I passed by and I was actually
running away from crony because it felt
like she was chasing me and uh then then
she didn't follow me where were you aha
you wait followed me I thre the zip line
what do you
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
mean
there bye okay goodbye oh my God that's
so crazy the fact that she had like her
own like um
name oh oops oops
oops
I've got to go water water my
plants got to go water my plants but
yeah I don't know crony just kind of
sused me out because it really felt like
she was following me oh no I think my
plants are over here but apparently
they're down
[Music]
here I don't know how to do
this oh I have to physically click them
[Music]
okay wait wait I saw Nissa like 5
seconds ago though Nissa is in the south
M with a she's giving away in a hallway
I don't know this
map Iris just passed me and then bi
killed me I saw Nissa around like next
to the greenhouse when I
was she's above the she selfreported I
can't believe her I saw her walking
around I didn't see anyone near her I
didn't see anyone else yeah I only saw
Nissa when we went up to Communications
and that was the last time I saw
her we didn't see anyone except for FL
this but and I think he's b boom I ran
away instantly I will be honest I don't
trust anyone who voted for crony in the
last
rounders were trying to get her out
because they
wait is
dead up by tell us before huh huh that's
something important when we're going to
start yeah oh
who did it I can't believe bi killed me
and immediately
recorded think
ad really oh that's true two imposters
still crony could have been an impostor
though honestly like I don't know did
you guys turn off it doesn't say who oh
it doesn't say oh I wouldn't put it
behind if she self-recorded because look
at her look at her um her icon like she
it's all why why are you so suspicious
of her for no reason
I don't know I feel you wouldn't be this
suspicious unless you were the impostor
and you're sure not I swear to God I'm
not I I I I said out right that I saw
like narissa pass by just 5 seconds ago
before death if it was actually I would
say thata I didn't see you though U no I
was pass I passed by her when she was
going greenhouse and I I'm currently at
the meeting room I went the opposite
direction that's why I think she was
like stuck on a that biu and Irish Senai
are suspicious I think so wait why I
swear I'm not what were you doing not I
was walking around I was in the LA the
lap wait where's my the LA and Thena was
on like the 10
seconds I don't have
enough I swear it's not me why did you
vote for Iris it's
B oh my God
was
enough did we get
him oh my
God I can't believe
you I thought we won yeah
Tombstone I hate this excuse me you
didn't even notice I was dead
guys literally Iris passed me and bioo
killed me
immediately a
good report good team you two that was
pretty
tomb impr I was surprised well you know
what we learned from that because Calli
was pretty quiet SS out was the quiet
quiet on the fooled me cie fooled me
too
strategy I was just confused cuz like my
voting was super rushed I was likeit why
am I suspicious
I thought it was a little for people to
vote you out round one it was peer
pressure pure you don't have to vote if
you don't know well I'm surprised with
just two votes they kicked Iris out that
was so weird I thought it needed to be
like majority vote to even get anyone
off I thought two I didn't think vot was
enough to kill me it was it was only a
little bit of us left so two was
enough
yeah we're strong at this H yeah we're
good pretty good doing our tasks wen't
you the ones
[Music]
who I guess we're S no matter what can't
be
helped well that was a good first round
let's let's try to be you know we for an
extended voting time oh sure of
course yeah uh it's currently 9 seconds
should we do 120 or at least yeah at
least 120 120 is the
max Chad says apparently we can vote or
skip the vote if you're not confident
like who it is you don't have to
vote pretty confident
confident you were right about certainty
there pretty confident voting out all
yeah I was pretty
confident well now you now you know then
you maybe cannot trust your confidence
yeah true
enough all right then let's start a
another round yeah let's
go even though this is really fun here
thank you crony for finding this
yeah see you on the other side bye bye
see you guys bye two imposters Among Us
I am a crew mate let's go my favorite
okay um let's see tab
okay storage
room is this a storage
room okay
use why is peip standing next to me I
don't trust
her okay cafeteria okay cafeteria is
over here bi Boo get away from me you
killed me last time I don't want
anything to do with
you I don't want anything to do with you
bi
boo bi Bo sa following me like that you
can't pretend to be my baby girl
anymore get away from me I I don't want
I don't want it I don't want it bi
boo why is bana just standing
here
good leave
me
okay oh my God little seash
shells oh
a k my
love oh crony deserves to kill me if
she's the impostor she can she can kill
me it is
allowed uh how do I get this
out nice
okay
um okay right here there's more
digging there's a a pizza slice
what something here
fire I get to roasted among go
marshmallow oh my god
oh that's so cute
okay
what
he
sorry people get away from me I don't
trust you
I guess if she wanted to kill me she
could have by
now and she hasn't so maybe maybe Boo
Boo is not doing anything
wrong no not again come on yeah come
on what all right I'll break it down for
you yeah please what I did all my tasks
you guys could see me I think some of
you saw me watering things in the the
mushroom place I moved some storage
around roasted some marshmallows went up
to do my tasks in the communication room
and what do I find Watson dead middle of
the floor I didn't see anyone leave
though was anyone near Communications
recently commun top you take a little
like a what is it a wire the zipline
zipline
I I'm far from it for a little bit but
we didn't see mine I just
lad yeah I was just in the jungle area
yeah I know there was there was like oh
oh okay these white white things are
okay yeah the line you can go up and
down but yeah I wasn't there yet um in
the bottom right um there was a lot of
shape shifting I don't know who is
[Music]
who what happened with that the mushroom
is that the mushroom stuff everybody
everybody got a skin shift right
yeah we don't know who is who and then
we can't prove like oh that person was
there or whatever but we all look
different like not like each other right
so it's not shape shifting yeah no it's
just the mushroom power yeah is that
somebody doing it or is that yeah I
think you have to activate no idea I
haven't used it yet but when you pass by
a mushroom it does
it I can vent but I'm not the The
Imposter just saying I didn't use it yet
though
recently was anyone around upper engine
Lookout or mining pit because the
Imposter may have tried to escape by
going down the ladders nope I will check
it out I was walking that way but I
didn't see anyone I've been down over in
the left area for the whole time doing
my tasks so I haven't even gone over
there yet I've seen the WR I haven't
been up there yet I have tasks and
communication like I was going to go up
I'm currently passing I was passing by
the greenhouse I was going to go up but
and see anybody run past well no I
didn't hard to tell still at least hard
to
tell yeah but people was kind of
quiet just saying actually bi boo passed
by me and didn't kill me yeah bio
followed me for a while didn't kill me I
think first time I'm doing task I can
tell you I've been doing water with
narissa and then I did the marshmallow
thing and and I video game I shot
asteroids and I haven't been up there
yet so I I have task up
there okay we'll see we'll see close but
keep your eyes open
yeah maybe don't don't go alone don't go
around alone guys go with a
buddy we don't need a
buddy
[Music]
okay back at it
again I want to fish okay so I feel like
I'm pretty
positive I'm pretty positive it's
not
kiata
or
cie or bio I'm not 100% sure that it's
not C but be being that she's quiet or
we're talking a lot I think there's a
possibility now Iris Fu
Moko crony and
fauna are
pretty sussy wussy I don't
know I some for some reason they're
sussy wussy to me yeah Callie's 50/50 it
could have been a self-report but I'm
not
sure so there's still a lot of people
like I feel like it could
be it's fine it's fine it's just a
mushroom mixup mushroom
mixup is's a a okay
okay okay task completed I'm back to my
normal self uh where next let's go down
here none of us I think
[Music]
oh I knew she was innocent
was the
only was a little bit suspicious though
she was I passed her going down the
ladders from communication to the lower
part she pass me maybe went up the
communication where'd you find her so I
was going up the ladder to the
communication and I didn't really see
her body but um I saw the the vent which
is the plant kind of opening up and then
closing so they vent
yeah they vented to wherever it is from
Communications oh does anyone know where
where the vents from Communications
connect they can go anywhere right I
think all the vents can only usually I
don't know in Old Maps usually vents
only connect to certain other vents yeah
see I should have checked and then I
could have told you but too bad no
idea I I can kind of say I think crony
is not self-reporting at least because
was like I feel like I was I was running
around with her a little bit alone she
could kill saw yeah and she didn't and
then I saw cie running around I think we
were alone for a little bit but she may
have been on cool down as well but she
yeah she was coming down from that she
was she was coming down from that area
yeah I told you I crossed paths with her
oh yeah okay but yeah and Cory said
someone vented
h where were you a good question we were
at the beach the beach we're just kind
of going around but we don't really
understand I don't know going on the map
here if you hit tab it'll show you where
you
are oh tab yeah hit tab the map will pop
up oh okay there's also the map icon on
the top the map icon right yeah the top
right there's a settings see a map but I
don't understand it it has a lot of
marks on it
yeah L the marks that is that is it
exclamation
marks a lot of marks on it does it have
some x's on
itous question not the marks I mean I
don't see so many marks on my M
yeah what does an imposter see maybe
does a previous impostor want to tell us
what they saw like Callie yeah Callie um
I saw some x's with circles on them one
time and I clicked them sabotage
a lot of marks on the screen oh no um
well a lot of
marks do you have anything to say to
defend yourself we're just doing our
tasks
would
anyway
do it I couldn't P
the by
[Music]
goodles I hope we don't regret that same
see you later I'm scared okay I need to
go up I think I will go
up okay I bet it's FAA she's coming to
kill me I I can feel
it I need to run fast she's going to
kill me she's coming for
me oh no she's doing a task okay
trust okay trust trust my Hollow promise
Oshi she will not kill
me
right hey
um okay eh what am I
doing I don't
understand I don't understand what's
happening Aris don't follow
me where am I
going
oh I've done all my
tasks okay
uh okay fixed Greenhouse record
temperature and jungle collection sample
why aren't they coming up on my
map
I would like to see that because I'm
very
confused I don't know where I
am oh my God it wasn't call who's dead
cie
wait I just saw her like yeah I saw her
just saw her too I feel like saw her
body right underneath the the
ladder the the left
ladder you can check the map you can
check the map and see exactly where the
green house like close to the greenhouse
yeah wasn't she just with me at around
like yeah I saw everyone at
communications and I was getting some
stuff done there and uh and also the
lookout and then I went down and I saw
her she moved
fast and then
died is there anyone around there I'm in
the lookout right now
I'm in the mining pit I was around I
think when everyone was
around yeah we all went to
Communications home yeah everyone like
uh everyone
except uh who was it like R Rissa
and uh I think they were around like
Communications and like Lookout and then
everyone else went to the other coms
yeah
um I am sorry FAA but it seemed you were
being just um you know a little very
cautious I don't know if you were
careful about being stack killed but you
moved away from the the radio like where
everyone was trying to fix it oh that's
well you needed to go do the other thing
right to fix it I was the first one
there in the radio and I tried to put in
the code but I think you have to put in
a second
code yeah also I two tasks that I did in
Communications
oh I went and did them cuz I was I was
in Lookout I was putting the code in I
think it was the first who arrived and
then nothing was happening so I I
thought I would go to the other one and
I saw Cali was like doing the code at
that point as well so she was like she
already arrived and then I left her
alone there I was about to go up to the
other communication thingy but then uh
it was already fixed so then I went back
and I saw I think I saw crony again or
so yeah but I didn't see FAA and I
didn't see Iris at all I saw you Kiara
saw all of you guys I don't know I don't
know I saw all of you guys in
Communications I was I was with fauna
alone for a while and she didn't kill
me yeah so I saw narissa go
down I didn't I was going to the
greenhous saw you going down where are
you right now um I ended up in the
lookout because I got lost and I was
very
confused aren't we all yeah little
suspicious of crony cuz she didn't vote
for
fuok we're running out of I don't know
if I'm suspicious enough to vote [\h__\h]
yeah I don't know I I I don't know
either I'm going to
skip you're going to
skip
skipping
we
good luck crew
mates there's not a lot of Us Alive cron
is going to kill me isn't
Shea Iris looks like she's actually
doing
something okay I see I see I see okay
and then I need to record the
temperature of the
greenhouse isn't this the
temperature no I don't like that crony
is just like walking
around as if she's waiting for something
to happen something about that really
irks me it's really getting to me in a
negative
way
you know what I
mean it's really affecting
me I finished my
tasks I I finished my tasks so I feel
like I should get out of the danger
zone but some of you are saying that I
should check the
vitals of everyone and see if if
anyone's
dead um I don't think anyone knew is
dead for
now but
something is happening for
sure something yeah no one's dead
yet I'm scared of
crony I'm just going to
say
here
I yeah me and kiata
H what's she going to try to
say uh hello hello hello help me I think
no is trying to kill me ah you are so I
can't believe you I was not I checked
everyone's vitals and I decided to go
back to the meeting area canell and I
saw her and got a little scared so I ran
back but then she chilled so I thought
it was cool but then she hit the
emergency meeting button much to my
surprise no the thing is there's a
little bit of a backstory I was running
around there's a back
story I'm done with my test what do you
mean
backstory I was running around I was I
was you know I I I was running around
crony alone she didn't kill me I was
running around fauna alone she didn't
kill me and both of those I kind of
fought were sus and then I found you and
you kind of followed me and now I think
if it's not cron if it's not I didn't
even follow you what do you mean I ran
into you and then I ran back to the
meeting area you are so fake
Kata I was also around crony and she did
not kill me either uh even though she
could have and as I was doing tasks I
could have killed crony too and I didn't
which I would have if I had the
opportunity to if I was the
Imposter tell me everybody tell me Iris
uh and tell me fauna what are the
remaining tasks that you have I'm done
with tasks and I was with virus yeah I
saw yeah B was sorry if you felt like I
was chasing you I I I was kind of scared
I was kind of scared you were like stick
to me like little time yeah I have I
have a task to do at the dock okay and
then I have one at the cafeteria then do
it and then we win task Queen let's go
guys we have to do it also I think
people who are done with the tasks can
let's just wait in the meeting area or
follow yeah I mean we have to do the
test you can't just wait in the meeting
area like people who are done with the
test can follow around can I on I do
think I do think nissa's a little bit
suspicious Nissa you and me Let's Stay
Together exuse me I'm not staying with
you hell no you're going to K we're
staying together no I am not staying
with I tag along with you guys if that's
okay just to see if one of you I'll feel
saf is there wait then maybe you twoo
are the imposters no I'm done with my
tasks as a thing I don't you want to
kill me it is kind of scary oh my God I
didn't kill you when you were around
yeah what the heck yeah oh you two
didn't kill each other because you're
both oh my God you why are you pting it
on the blue
women yeah let's just all stay together
and let's see what the blue women do oh
my God can we follow iron does anyone
else have no I'm done we should follow
Iris we should PR follow let's follow
Iris okay yeah yeah you can totally
follow me
okay nice hey who voted for me
me I don't trust you wait am I getting
okay okay good good you better you
little [\h__\h] love you k please don't kill
me okay she's totally the impostor it's
definitely they're going to double kill
they're going to double kill I can feel
it it's both of them they're going to
double
kill they're going to they're going to
try to double kill I'm not coming close
what the
[\h__\h] I'm not going close to them oh my
God y y task win what who was it excuse
me I was it was desk what who was imp
impost though yeah come on Iris I wonder
who
was Iris
Andis I know it
[Music]
was doing so good on the
spot doing mhm I'm sorry I was
suspicious of you FAA I'm sorry I was
suspicious of you Iris didn't kill
FAA why didn't you kill
me I wanted to keep someone on my
side and because crony was susing fun in
the beginning I was like maybe I should
keep her on my side and kill crony
instead and like I I saw that Iris was
uh going into the same room as uh
narissa was so I was kind of waiting
outside the room to see I saw I saw I
was like oh no I think she s I was
trying to kill I was trying to kill you
actually um I when you were inside the
lab I was I was following you and I was
going to kill you but then I noticed you
were moving weirdly and you were like
running away and then Marissa came comes
in right away I was like oh never mind I
can't K you over
here up went back I think I was playing
a little bit too cautiously but um so
difficult only there's only me that's I
I was I was worried like it was still
pretty good
yeah still impressive yeah I can't I
can't believe you suspected
me all well it ends well hopefully when
we're together alone in the males I
won't kill you don't
[Laughter]
worry Don't Drown me in the ocean mhm
please we're missing Mo yeah
Moy oh sorry I was stuck at let me just
I'm here
sorry um I don't want to like you know
make any hard rules because you know you
just kill whoever is conveniently there
but please do not kill Amy right away
next time yeah
please poor taste a
ghost no no no we need our we need our
space so now yeah kill me first I love
being the
ghost no pressure yeah no
pressure okay we complete I changed one
thing I changed that the votes uh you
can't see who voted that makes it really
hard for me to try to vote
someone oh boy let's go
go side see you later okay bye yeah I'm
a crew mate W let's go
W yeah let's go okay let's see where my
tasks are I have one over here in the
Splash
Zone yeah get some
shells okay next task down by the docks
and in the
kitchen so in the kitchen what's my task
here
oh over
here yeah
yeah this is what it's all
about okay and now I fish
with oh that one's
ugly fishy fishy amoga fish
yeah well Fu Moko is safe they're
probably not even here
anymore we're both cooking oh my God
Advent
cook Advent cooking
together I love them no one better
interrupt this I'll be so mad because
this takes so
long ah
hello oh for a moment I thought you were
dead
again oh no
no well all right hope is dead I just
saw her alive like less than 30 seconds
where must have just happened I just
found it in the meeting room but I was
up in the Dropship if you look at the
map and then I went down and I found her
body there and bioo was up there and
fauna was up there and bi looked like
she came from down below so I'm a little
sus austral you because I knew no one
would kill you so I thought it'd be
safer with
you but was following the both of us
though so I'm kind of s a i was just
making sure no funny business was going
on who was I I was alive like less than
30 seconds before she was found dead
like I it felt like like 10 seconds
before so I'm
I'm like What's Happening that was a
really fast I only passed by in that
area it was like bioo and fauna and
that's it I think in that area
specifically do you see anyone like
coming from that
direction I don't know I know storage
room and then I was using the
zipline and like wasn't taking the
zipline up with me
yet oh well people would you like to
defend yourself
what I was following Amy because I no
one was going to kill Amy so I thought a
was a safe but a saw you didn't she not
following her but coming from a
different direction no I was following
am this entire time you follow you the
entire
time running away from you so I didn't
see you well I was following you the
entire you want to kill her why you
following
her this is
okay T I've done one task so far it was
asteroids I haven't done the rest
because asid I was following yeah the
asteroids the video game you do
asteroids in the last one too yeah I
have what does the asteroids like yeah I
haven't gotten that one maybe she has
her favorites I went straight to
Communications I mean I will do
my are we going to skip for Bio
out I died the last time I am too I
don't want to
die I don't know have enough by the way
Iris I don't know if you know but you
mut oh it's because she's dead oh
[Laughter]
there but she is
dead I just wanted to make sure she
joins the conversation you know if
I or if I die is or F sus one of them
out if I
go byebye people this the last time
following I didn't vote for I voted I
just I didn't vote for you people it
wasn't me oh thank you I just like say
by what you mean byebye
people
God okay I got to finish cooking this
fish I don't have any idea who it could
be but I'm kind of
scared
we're safe we're cooking fish
together how does this go down how do I
get rid of
this how do I get to the
kitchen bioo Advent together strong
bioo
it's VA I watched her kill FL [\h__\h] it's
wait what I
knew I knew why is dead though she's
dead wait she's dead the switch the
mushroom
switch no that makes it so much worse I
went I know it's not bi boo because I
went down because I saw bi boo pass us
we were both waiting to get into the
kitchen because last round foko and I
were frying fish together right so as I
was waiting I went to get bi boo cuz I
was like Advent together strong and then
when I came back thank it was right in
front of the kitchen it was right in
front of the kitchen is where is where
the death just happened and I saw
someone running up to the Splash Zone so
where was everybody and don't
lie wait you found which which of the
two bodies did I don't I don't know
where I don't know where it it looks
like then I have something to add I was
just up at the very top of the
communications and there was crony and
there was fauna first there was fauna
and me and everything was cool then
crony joined I left and now fa is dead
okay and then you confirm this crony um
after I was uh doing the ladder task I
went down to the zip line again after
that was done so I didn't really see you
saw Kiara up there yeah I saw Kiara and
FAA up there and then after I was done
with the ladder I went down the zip line
and I couldn't see anything else aside
from that maybe someone vent I'm not
really sure because it's kind of a short
maybe
you I mean I
know I I'm going to give my alibi really
quick and I saw bi Boo and we were alone
and she didn't come after me or anything
but I was in the Splash Zone in the
beginning I collected shells and then I
left okay where were you though at the
time of the murder
it just happened I reported it
immediately yeah went to Splash Zone and
I collected the shells and then I saw
bio and she didn't hurt me and then I
went back to storage okay and then crony
FAA and kiata were over in
Communications yeah so Watson where were
you I was at the
laboratory laboratory I I am Su of Amy
because Iris was around me fa and am
yeah I am too and and now so now I'm s
it seems a bit weird right trying to vot
someone off no cuz the last the last
murder the everyone who was present we
know that it wasn't fa now and obviously
iris is dead so it's only you or bio but
I know where bio was the time of the
murder you're forgetting that the first
round I reported the body and both biu
and faer were with me and none of them
said that they biu even said that she
was following me the whole time but she
didn't see me kill anyone huh V for
crony trust me
[Music]
I mean I think there's obviously two of
them who are we voting
for selfreported
[Laughter]
no V yes oh my God are
gone
byebye say no I don't know kiar is
really suspicious right now sorry okay
see you later I don't know I'm pretty
positive that it is is
um I I don't know if it was crony but
I'm
pretty okay someone has
my who's near me right now they're
changed who's
vitals the person near me is currently
kiw hi
kiw okay got to
change the
log
okay we got each
other okay I'm going to leave her
alone I don't think it's
kiata I don't think kiata would leave me
alive okay I'd really like to how do I
get these mushrooms to go down
seriously I don't think it's bi booo
this
time I don't think it's bioo or kiata
I'm pretty positive it's but the only
option I feel like is biu and um am and
seeing that someone voted for me and the
only person I implemented was a and
there was no proof it could have been me
I know we couldn't see who
voted who's
this hi
Moi how are we
Moy Kaa P let me into the kitchen okay I
need to get to the
lookout I can't get anywhere everywhere
is
locked okay I guess I have to go
down e on the
mushrooms
e oh nice reactor
meltdown seems a little more important
than what I'm trying to do right now so
maybe I shall try to go over
there
um
K
Tak
Tak the light of my
life my little guy is just sitting there
Mari find my body
my
Mory I can't believe it she's totally
tricked
me she totally tricked
me oh no reisa I I wanted to check if
anyone and re's dead yeah I was
wondering too I can't believe it I can't
believe it I think Kiara is safe yeah
we just did the emergency thing together
yeah and then joined right I really
think ran away both of you guys can't
believe this I can't believe this I
can't believe this
no I you think I really because the
first death was Iris and me FAA and Iris
were the ones that were closest to each
other
and yeah well that and now I'm scared I
know it's not Kiara because kiar didn't
kill me K so yeah I still have three
tasks left by the way so what
diding because I was wondering if
anybody di because we're about to finish
our tasks and you don't want us to
finish our tasks dressed I was scared if
anyone was going to die and I thought
like might as well chat and like tell me
what were you doing I went down to
mushrooms mhm and what's the last task
you did the swording the mushrooms into
the jars and the
crystals Telly has been quiet yeah sure
I mean ask me any questions you want but
if you talk too much you get sused out
too so just ask me any questions and
I'll tell
you what's the last task you did wait
she's saying she's in I don't remember I
was in the that's weird I can't ask chat
too cuz I can't even look at chat um I
know this sound suspicious but yeah I
don't remember I'm going to I'm going to
vote for am I think you're the impost
you're just you called the Mee him cuz
we're so close to finishing our tasks
that you're scared no [\h__\h] I'm scared of
dying aren't we all I mean I saw cie and
she didn't kill me and I was running
away from you guys cuz I thought you
guys were going to kill me that's my
defense yeah
okay voting okay oh okay you guys if you
guys vote for me you're wrong just so
you know she's betrayed me uh oh K's
going to win for
Kelly okay
or you s cuz I
saw together and you guys didn't die so
unless you're both the impostor assuming
crony was not the impostor uh oh my God
exact takamori isn't it it's totally
takamori it's if if there was two
imposters alive we would lose by now so
there's only okay that's true so one of
the previous was well crony I guess was
the one that got knocked out right so
would that yeah yeah yeah I don't know
IR no I say we just Skip and continue
doing our tasks unless you guys are if I
was the Imposter i' try to vote one of
you guys out right now and then I'd
probably
win so I'm going to skip you guys are
wrong regret your decision it's over
it's
over I'll miss you
faker no she's
burning are we winning please what all
righto wait right how many more oh sorry
she's so fake
sorry
unbelievable I thought it was am me was
it Amy I don't think so oh was it was it
be then I was following be after I died
is it cie it shows you if you haunt them
it it shows you who it is oh my
God yeah oh no wait oh my God how did
I'm so lost okay anyway
wacky it wasn't me oh my God Callie
posing as you then killed me that was
wild I was
shaped so actually I turned that's her C
she was quiet oh you turned into fa I
see we thought was quiet too
but I'm so sorry how do I ever redeem
myself to you I'm sorry
toate
believe me yeah I toally
too oh my God I'm not a real Amy
goling I tried to protect her and now
I'm the one that killed
her I can't trust Callie anymore yeah I
can't trust cie either I'm sorry I can't
believe I got imposter twice
why lying why is everyone so good at
lying yeah I don't watching Prof
Among Us players recently
really everybody the whole time
[Music]
practice you didn't listen to
me damn it and I still didn't get
impostor a single time
man maybe next time we still got more
time right yeah be there's a little more
time then let's go next round let's go
next oh I saw I by the way the ghosts uh
were going in their own channel did you
have fun yes
yes recommend it it was fun I don't know
why crony was probably too guilty
toad voice CH oh wait a dead voice chat
know voice chat I was like why isn't she
joining I was like oh probably cuz she
feels guilty oh no I don't feel guilty
at
all Absolut
shamey just randomly get voted off too
cuz I don't remember like everybody I
got was Reas for
thata knew yeah cuz I told you yeah I
told you to believe me see oh it was
actually good what I did was right you
were so right love you easy way to tell
easy way to tell if if Callie is
imposter she's quiet she's
imposter I'm imposter so I don't know
bye you are the
wa
no
[Music]
no this a
vent oh my
god um blue team this is a mistake I'm a
really bad impostor I'm going to get
sussed out
immediately I'll pick the mushrooms I'll
make it easier to get around so people
maybe won't sus me
out I don't want to kill anyone you
think I can kill the Hol live
girls cuz I can't I don't have it in me
blue girl power
no
is both of
us yeah crony let's go
together I'm so scared
crony I don't know how to kill
someone hot girl club
I can't kill fauna I just can't do
it I just can't do it I can't do it you
guys I can't do it I
can't
I I'm not strong
enough I'm not strong
enough I'm
weak okay I'm
weak I didn't even see I didn't even see
I didn't even really see I didn't I see
she was just there wa wait wait what
what happened was that wait who you see
no no no no it wasn't me I was where
where were you where were you when you
pressed
it who pressed it
I I pressed it I was oh my God I was so
in my tangent oh my God I went up to the
top right to the communications and I
was just Tangen thing and doing a task
and suddenly I see a dead body but on
the same spot I think I saw at least one
more person maybe another maybe two
people I think so it's Kiara Iris fuo
and then I just came into the room and I
saw call
outside body I just the moment I went up
the ladder all of a
sudden I was Ling communication
went line with almost the same time and
then I was trying to go in the way to
the mushroom door but I got rid of the
mushrooms but uh maybe killed by
accident maybe it's just am miss him by
being silly uhhuh wait
what wait I'm me you were there right
when I reported right no I I just walked
into the room like after cie she was
already in there like alive and you guys
were all doing the power thing or
whatever and I was also starting to do
the power thing putting in the code but
then you guys finished it and then
somebody reported Call's body so I
didn't even see it wait so you're saying
besides me there was Cali and you I
was went inside the communications the
reported all in there no one was on the
other side of the mushroom wall so I
don't think they could kill her on the
other side of the mushroom wall but I
don't know yeah I just went up the
ladder was how it went and then all of a
sudden report there might there was one
other person in there but it was hard to
see cuz everybody was bunched up I think
I saw purple yeah purple was Call's dead
body no no purple is
beo that purle we do have something to
report yeah
H we
heard okay you are the and the mute we
were thinking maybe this amaz being Sil
you know that's good thing that we were
that I heard that I thought she was
saying it to someone else and now I'm a
trying can we have someone who hasn't
talked talk please me me me yes so um I
was at communications I saw a bunch of
people there and I was trying to like uh
do my task and like I was still on the
task when it happened so I didn't really
see anything oh so you were also in
Communications
m
okay wait you were there even now when
when I reported you were still
there um yeah yeah oh so you were one of
the other people I saw then but I wasn't
sure who am I seeing oh [\h__\h] I voted for
well I remember this I will remember
this but oh shoot you
guys a
joke
uh guys I can't do this I'm not strong
enough I'm so
serious I'm so
serious what wait
what
sorry I'm
sorry there was like a crowd of people
in communication wait did did
you my you guys go yeah how you
yeah wow see The Quiet Ones it's all
quiet on I hasn't said
anything last
round innoc sorry to be fa I didn't
kill
sounded I didn't
King suing Amit right because of her
statement but it
wasn't yeah I said that on purpose
[Music]
being Sil two impers but of course vote
for
fuok I didn't vote for Fu I
tried sorry oh my God this is what
happened okay next we we got
to you want to do a I'm
sorry don't give it to the blue people
yeah please to the blue people
No Thank God I'm a crew mate I'm so
happy okay where are my tasks finally I
feel safe I feel safe
again I feel safe cuz I just have tasks
to do I feel so bad I can't believe I
killed fauna my Hollow promise Oshi how
could I do such a thing I don't deserve
to be forgiven for my
transgressions killing bi boo is
something for example cuz bi boo you
know is my teammate we're we're in
Advent she'll forgive me
but wait where's my task why are all my
tasks
gone I'm going to be honest I don't care
that comms are
sabotaged only two people need to fix
that let me do my
tasks I'm going to wait over
here oh
[Music]
he
why was there like a car
sound do I have any kitchen tasks to do
no myy
again
oh I I I ran up because of the
communications thing was down and she
was right there in Communications in
front of the the thingy I don't think it
was I was at the other I was with but I
didn't see her I was down by the dock I
was in the
labs oh me I'm oh yeah I just met crony
in the labs
yeah Iris and I are doing the other task
power thing yeah we were kill each other
I think we're
safe pushing
up
narissa I was down by the dock I I
figured that you probably all were going
there and I wanted to keep doing my
tasks so I just went down and I was
doing a sand castle and then I was
checking since yeah don't the um I pass
I passed to check the tasks yeah they
disappear but if you pass them you can
still do them oh okay yeah so I was
checking
manually okay I or if you just still
like remember where they were before it
went down
yeah well M
reactor
that's what task what are you doing at
the reactor we're doing our task we're
just
trying doesn't want to use the map I
like the map I like finding the little
yellow mark on the the screen it's more
fun now you
know the
yellow what actually haven't done that
yet the yellow there's a yellow is so
cute it's a little Among
Us uh the marshmallow the marshmallow
[Music]
yeah so but but what task were you
doing yeah the marshmallows are nowhere
near the reor yeah so what were you
doing in the reactor that that was yeah
but what were you doing
today huh we doing a bunch of in the Rea
what what were you doing what were you
doing in the reactor what are you doing
in the Rea kind
of
a i for now I'll give you guys the
benefit of that thank you please don't
kill us
[Music]
again they live to see another
day they shouldn't
though for all intents and purposes they
should be dead right now I'm pretty sure
it's
them I'm pretty
positive I love them very much but my
girls are
um that that is exactly what I would do
if I was trying to claim 69 nice let's
go um that is the same thing I do when
I'm the impostor when someone makes me
talk because the issue is I don't
actually know what I'm doing and I am
not good enough to remember the tasks
that are going on when I'm not present
somewhere so that has the inverse effect
as well of uh I will not be able to say
anything that I've done and I'm pretty
sure Fu Moko would know what task they
were
doing if they were doing a
task but they
didn't they weren't sure lying is not
their thing they're very uh cutely
obvious what's
this what am I
doing nice I don't trust them stay away
from me sorry
puppies see when I'm actually doing
tasks I remember that I'm doing tasks
you know I don't forget the task that I
just did you know I can be like oh don't
look at me get away from me
okay let's head back to
[Music]
comms um 71
03 okay 4 1 7 8
okay yeah okay hi bi
boo okay I don't know where I'm going
and I don't know why uh
Watson
it wasar it
was killed don't believe her do you see
I saw people kill am I am medic I am
medic I can see people's vitals yeah and
I can see you kill am is that how it
works I I Amic I can see people's V I
have three battery charges every around
to see how many people are this is the
first time I have medic I saw Kiara kill
no
beo this is hard for me because I had
just I had just seen bio and but I did
not see kiata and I was going down and
she didn't follow me so she might have
realized she was alone with a but uh
bioo also when she killed me
self-reported and then immediately this
is literally the first time I've gotten
scientist and I have this is the first
time I played it so how would I know
that I have three charges of scientist
to check
my where is the body in a while uh the
body is up the stairs by communication
okay I
saw who was it you probably just looked
up some guide about those no I didn't
this is the first time I have whatever
scientist whatever I can check people's
but I was I was so often alone with
others and I didn't kill them so why
would I you know can somebody vouch for
me cuz I think I was Al alone together
with a lot of
people come on
oh I was alone with for a while but I
was not alone with Kiara yeah I saw k
for like a split sorry I saw several
times alone and I saw crony several
times I think alone and I saw narissa
like maybe one or two times
alone yeah it felt like um either Kiara
or fauna was going to kill me cuz like
they were just kind of walking around so
I stuck around one of them to make sure
I didn't get k um it would kind of check
out if Kiara was I'm instantly voting I
saw the K I believe I believe this time
wow okay who's beu I'm
[Music]
[Laughter]
sorry goodbye forever thanks forever H
what was that I I love you I'm thank you
forever I thank you
forever well
somebody's not
voting I just accepted that you guys are
voting me me out but I guess you'll now
you're running down the
clock it's so sad I I was always with
you
guys I love you
K
byebye goodbye goodbye I will go up like
a phoenix and I will rise like a phoenix
she's going to [\h__\h] kill me when she
sees me in the Mal Dives I can feel it
she will kill me uh she will have my
head there's no way it's crony she's
been it like twice hasn't she there's no
way it's
crony with that
logic okay where am I
going the mining pit I need to go
down going down down in an earlier round
sugar we going down swiy
I'll be a with a bully a loaded G
complex cocky and P sorry what am I
doing here oh a shine shining the
gem like I would not forget that I did
this in a round you know that is so cute
I love
that where am I going okay
here
okay 5 1 5 70
okay comms have been
sabotaged which means we've got to go up
and fix
them oh okay I can't get in question
mark
use one more got
it why' she just
leave okay 3 5 4 1 3 one okay 3 five 4 1
three I don't think it'll work I think
it has to be the other
Comm okay let's clear this out for the
time being make moving around a little
easier for us teammates oh
hi why were you all sitting out there
that's so
weird yeah where is fuam
Moko has to be both okay well I guess I
will sacrifice myself to potential death
because foko might just be waiting down
here to kill me okay 4
6911 okay there you guys
go I've got you
covered
oh okay let me clear
it we got it ladies
okay H why did crony go this
way anyway oh why emergency
meeting oh why the
emergency no I I cuz I I I believe it's
what I think so like when we were going
to when comms were down we were going up
I see I see like um many of us were
going up I think it was like I think I
saw fa beu um I Al saw I was also with
crony and narissa alone none of us
killed each other um and we were all
going up to comms but then I see Fu
coming down from comms ignoring the fact
that
comes do the bottom one first right we
just try to do the C and you at the Top
If you were at the top you would do the
top one right but we're just counting on
we're focusing on our top yeah you can't
see the tasks on the map when comms are
down you yeah you yeah you can't but if
you walk around you can
find did last time too no you're just
copying me cuz that's what I said
earlier I think so to call once and I
can't that's how we play
a tell me tell me a task you did this
time what's what's a task you did what's
a task you did the green house okay what
were you doing in the green
house why' you you you come came back
down from comms even though comms is
sabotaged all the way back down to the
greenhouse greenhous is
pretty green is pretty you got a f
[Laughter]
for who are the cutest puppies who are
wow look at the Little Liars look at the
Little Liars
oh c Little
Liars just B
bowing of
usal to
Prett I love you
puppies byee
byee by goodbye
come on F cast your
vote yeah don't don't um delay your
death it's yeah it's inevitable it's
time to
go what excuse
me byebye
puppies go
y that was funny that was a funny
round that was really good susing out
Iris that was impressive
amazing from the reactor too even the
last round when when we almost voted
them out cuz they didn't know what they
were doing at the
reactor that made me 80% sure and then I
saw them going down from com oh yeah
yeah definitely what this we crew me
will do
the
be
yes I'm so sorry it's okay you were just
trying to survive I understand I I think
out of this whole group of people me and
foku are like the worst Liars so it
wasn't a good
combination doing my B your B my B we
were so bad I
[Music]
was makes me
laugh think love to you see see I I had
a good the good life you know I did the
marmell and then she goes oh we did that
last
time oh my god well at least I finally
got imposter do we don't want to do one
more
yeah I think one more hide and seek for
the last yeah hide and seek hide and
seek hide and seek oh you'll see
hide-and-seek sounds fun it's like
hideand-seek like you really think
hide-and-seek I don't think we have to
for hide-and-seek wasn't there an actual
setting for hide and seek though yeah
there there is there is computer uh you
might have to make a new room though
maybe um if you can't change it in the
settings um on the computer
yeah then you might have to make a new
room is
it yeah no I don't think you can change
it
here okay then I'll make a new one we'll
watch for the new
code okay it's kind of like it's pretty
much like playing tag yeah
cute um any preferred
map let's do the original the OG oh yeah
yeah let's do OG yeah
nice I'll send you the link in the group
uh the in the
group there you this one's chaotic but
really funny thank you I've never done
it before oh it's fun and it's a short
game too so okay let's go
perfect man this is scary this one M
this is like the only time I actually
want to be
imposter
yeah I never want to be have to mve for
this same we don't have to mve for this
you oh no I don't think
so
okay try not to give away your location
on accident I guess we can mute if we're
done uh we don't have to
right I'm not
yeah hi wait we can we can hide in vents
oh is there only
one oh is this like
zombies we can hide really slow do tasks
the timer goes down
quicker we have three minutes to hide
left she got me minut minutes too high
she's in the med
Bay she's walking over she's in the
upper engine she's coming for your
food what wait
what oh
man yeah she's
[Music]
green everybody's clumping
together where is she right now you can
make down quick oh my God no oh
no is that
[Music]
call wait how does this
work so
over do your best crony you can hear the
music come close to you when she's close
by that's
scary crony where's crony don't ask her
oh don't say it
yeah
oh that's fun that's so quick too that
was so short another one
one I want to be impost EXC for both the
impostor and the the the the crew
mates can we increase the speed for both
crew mates yeah I want to but also I I
uh I think I have to make a new Lobby
because I don't think I can change the
amount of uh
Seekers there's only can only be
one yeah I it's fine to leave it at one
we just need the speed up so we're all
running really
fast here okay
Max go this is how it should
[Music]
be yum let's
goit do I get to go that fast to I think
so oh I
hope I'm G to be Unleashed for
my honestly why are there Tas I did okay
oh God where do I go don't forget to do
your task do your
task Tas I don't see them I see tasks
but I don't know what I really want to
finish those
sorry it's
good
why do I
have I'm scared I'm scared I'm scared I
hear I hear the base we got to win we
got to win this I can't find you guys
what heck's
everyone task task task task
Tas got her going to the vacation with
her
you even he
you a horror game all of a sudden
[Music]
on terrifying screams
here
[Music]
going
louder this is so much more cha louder
yeah it's so cha
get the you hear the guitar RI you're
like she
[Music]
coming
together my eyes
[Music]
seconds oh you're going to be even
faster in the final round I'm alive okay
should I do tasks
yeah I need to run around like a
chicken get one more
minute stand because it's going to your
location ler it shows do you guys know
where show location it shows location
there's a there's a red dot uh that
indicates where the crew
is
iies I see dead bodies I see dead
[Music]
people [\h__\h] does she see me from the map
too she gets
closer 10
[Music]
seconds that was so
[Applause]
CL that was impressive I let's
go I don't know how I just didn't really
see her on the screen that often so
thank God everybody was so
fast
that was close though telting across the
map couldn't even keep
more
[Music]
more is who is it this time let's go who
is
it go today I think she's going to have
fun run run
R does doing tasks do anything like we
could get an early task win if we do if
we finish them all yeah and we could get
lucky and I was being very proactive
with the task hide it's hide and seek
you got to
hide I can't oh
no okay got to go got to go got to I was
about to the thing I'm
sorry I'm sorry
nice nice
J
was oh no what you guys on you guys damn
it I I do wonder if doing tasks is even
worth it I know right I think I feel you
just kind of standed easy
bait my G cck she ran fast she ran
[Music]
fast
she's going on going to cafeteria wait
can we tell her location it might be a
little
unfair oh okay I felt that was the wrong
direction okay you know what um let's do
a tasks squeak I'm too scared to move
around at this point I die whenever I
use do tasks it's
just in
4k only has only three
left what is the danger me there come on
guys one more one more
minute such a good hiding spot though
she's going at a good Pace very good
Pace
oh 30 30
seconds that was a really good hiding
spot yeah that was a nice hiding spot
what I ha it's so lously all the time oh
no whoopsy you guys
areast is there
overtime so
[Applause]
fast you got to
survive us no pressure oh man
[Music]
you have 30 seconds left you do
it got this you're
Phoenix
theall have 10 seconds 10 seconds
SL easy easy she won't get you she won't
she won't get you Oh
No 2
[Laughter]
1 that was
[Music]
amazing last
second seconds left one literally
one a
millisecond second
though that
amazing
that was the clutchest ever what
yeah can't escape time at the end of the
day was really slippery yeah really
slippery oh my God that was exciting
amazing I mean ex I'm I'm pretty
exhausted from that but we can do
another one if you want I'm down for one
more finale
finale actually you know wait wait oh no
before Oh I want to I want to speed so
fast yeah it's fast oh good
okay me Queen how do you kill people the
whole time um there's a kill button so
don't you worry okay oh my God no way I
don't want to be it no the she has
awakened she has awakened I'm coming for
you
nobody's using my hiding spot right oh
no that's a good idea don't use my
hiding spot might go use it that no that
wasn't your hiding
spot she's on a rampage I thought you I
only saw one
person
overlapped does the music get louder for
me too I feel like it does I don't know
it gets louder when you're near someone
really even for imposter
you little [\h__\h] get out of there get out
of there you little
[\h__\h] what's going
[Music]
on
[\h__\h] where are
they my hiding spot oh
[Music]
I oh no that's that's the
stack I still got time I still got
time I saw someone where is
she that hiding
SP
[Music]
that's
oh my God that was no no I haven't found
anyone in my CES you passed by
[Music]
somebody someone's here no oh
[\h__\h] where are you
hello I'm all
alone no hints no help oh what was that
there was some button popping up there
the use button
yes in
[Music]
time even see you that's lame what the
heck see you well I saw you that's all
that
matters turned around
quick oh
[Applause]
no oh one more one more more
run no no no no
one minute there's still one more
minute they're literally run
run you can throw it through a loop just
run just
[Music]
[Applause]
run
wow
my doie
doie that was again pretty clutch I
would say
get good
game she out foring after all Mama Mia
that was wow that was fun that was fun
that was merry I'm too excited to say
anything so let's start with the with
the goodbyes from everybody but me um am
please
yeah this is really fun I'm glad we
could get together and have like a
little Christmas Among Us
[Music]
celebration the perfect holiday SE
holiday game right
for just red
with and some blood when I think of
Christmas I think of Among Us Violet and
death ornament yeah it's pretty festive
the colors you know this makes me want
to play this makes me want to play on
Project winter yeah
yeah that' be so much
fun yeah I know
[Music]
C wow thank I'm sorry you died so often
I'm but that's okay it's still fun call
what about you you had some good good
kills was fun it was nice getting to
dust off the old Scythe for once and get
back in the game for a little bit that
was nice
yeah I had a great time with everybody
here everybody here is fun to talk to
fun to argue with in a fun way really in
a fun way yeah in a fun way I guess
that's about it we should argue more
often yeah let's do it let's do it no no
I can't maybe not yeah no we're just
stay T but wein among us we can argue as
much as we want right and then outside
of Among Us you know we're different
people among us changes us
but us
us
us all right and please please tell me
about your experience today science
Rules science science Bill what science
science gu science rules and statement
thanks
great interesting interesting I don't
quite understand but I agree oh I don't
think Kiara knows about Bill it's all
right don't worry about
it don't worry about
it we'll tell you we'll tell you
later
okay Mrs Mrs Santa Claus Mrs CHR yes
yeah know this was fun I'm glad I was
able to lie better this time
yeah you need some good
lying we need to learn from
IR suspect yeah everyone everyone was
great I love how bad F was at
[Music]
L tell it's their first time you can
tell their
first it was the same as me when I
played for the first time wor was always
like that it's great I love it thank you
very much that was they were so lucky
cuz like in that one round they were
about to be voted off and I thought I
was going to be alone but then somehow
somehow they survived they
surved we couldn't save
you okay we couldn't save each other
even if we wanted
to well thank you Iris and then
people I was happy to be able to kill
people I wish I was able to kill more
people people but I satisfied with the
amount of people I was able to kill this
time thank you for your service that's
the spirit that's the Christmas spirit
let's go let's
go it was solid solid reaping good job
again I'm so sorry be it's okay a trail
it what stays in Among Us stays Among Us
don't worry exactly
exactly
[Music]
well we l a lot of things today we
really good at lying right yeah that
was and uh we have fun we we yelled a
bit screamed a bit and we did a lot of
lying yeah but most importantly we had
[Music]
[Applause]
fun so true let's
when I saw I was imposter with F I knew
I knew that you weren't going to be good
at
[Laughter]
lying s yeah it's all good true it's
funny I had so much fun thank you so
much for putting it together Ki
[Music]
waa I'm sad I had to be the impostor I
don't like it brings me no joy
yeah murdering me no I so bad so good
though you were good at it was over
right away me and me and crony we made a
good team blue women blue women are
scary women blue women I always say it
it's the blue people the avatars I
always say it m yeah thank you for the
fun
I'm glad you had a good time let's
continue this in the males yeah yes
peacefully the other Blue Woman
quason yeah it was a lot of fun I'm kind
of surprised that I actually got
impostor twice U because I never get
imposter yeah I never get these rules go
yes and thank you for organizing this it
was a lot of fun
I love among
us I guess you know there was all sorts
of drama but like we said earlier what
happens Among Us stays Among
Us wow
beautiful well said Thank You
Quon well yeah that's pretty much it um
but Christmas is not over yet I think
there's still members that have like
special streams upcoming so check them
out every everybody and I just want to
make one quick announcement about the H
Ian Advent calendar some people may
already know but the last day the 25th
day will be delayed a little bit so uh a
few days uh the it's out of my hands out
of my power now but please check back on
it next week we'll all tweet about it
when it is finally up uh so stay tuned
stay excited and thank you for spending
Christmas with us viewers I say to you
viewers thank you for spending it with
us and thank you to the girls for
spending it also with us thank you for
getting together
[Music]
at Merry Christmas
everyone merry
[Music]
Christmas had a lot of fun that was
really great and I hope everybody has a
nice nice holiday season e
cookies yay Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Okay add
some protein milk in my
fridge very
Christmas maybe Sant Santa will come to
drink your milk oh protect your milk I'm
going to end my stream I don't know if
they're going to stay in chat uh but
thank you guys so much for coming and
hanging out jail birs and watching my
perspective I hope you had so much fun
I'm looking forward to seeing you guys
tomorrow for my Koke just a quick
reminder my birthday merch goes out of
sale soon if you haven't gotten a chance
to get it pick it up now before it's too
late and I will see you guys all
tomorrow have a lovely night jailbirds
bya
[Music]
Darlings