[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
um
[Music]
uh
do you hear this
my
i think
my room is emptier than before
because it really sounds
uh
different do you hear that
do you hear a difference from usual i
feel like um you can hear what's what's
in what's the word
um
yeah i'm like not an echo but
it sounds empty and the acoustics are
weird i did indeed take out the cat tree
and put it somewhere else
uh
[Music]
that's not the
that's not what's different the
acoustics are different um
uh
right now it bothers me because there's
no other sound but hopefully it won't
bother me when
uh
when we play the game i can i could
bring back the tree but
oh sounds exactly the same it sounds
very different to me
but
that's probably because
uh i hear i hear
[Music]
i hear it here i hear my voice reverbing
reverberating
through the room man
uh
maybe maybe it's not so bad uh on your
side
um
i can hear it
you hear that there's an echo
echo
you don't hear it
you hear it now
do you hear it now
[Music]
what happened with my acoustics
[Laughter]
[\h__\h]
i messed up everything i sound like i'm
on a mountain
damn it well okay i'm probably just um
too too used to how it usually sounds so
no it really bothers me
[Music]
orange juice i yodel
yoda
i don't know how to yodel
i never practiced before i think if i
practiced i could i could nail it i
should practice it so i can i can flex
it you know gotta have some skills
[Laughter]
how to yodel uh what's the shortest
video oh how do you look explained by
the very expert expert in two minutes
oh wait let me let me listen
what do you say
what i mean i don't hear it [\h__\h] my
audio is all messed up my audio is all
messed up all my audio sources i changed
them all for the vr stream
um
[Music]
a system here and then
windows
sound settings
you know what's so weird
um
when i go to windows sound settings
at any time even when
everything's fine and normal
at output you know where their speakers
should be
it always says even even when it's
disconnected that's the spooky thing it
always says elgato
sound capture speaker
which elgato is my
is my capture card
and even when i disconnect it it says
that and when i want to switch it to
something else like i don't know
headphones
uh it will like i click on it and then
the drop down menu closes and it still
says elgato sound capture still
yeah i know it's the capture card but
why the [\h__\h] is it there why can't i not
change it but the thing is like even
when i hear things from my
headphones it will still say elgato at
any time like it's just always elgato
sound capture there
it's so weird um
but uh
system here
see i did it again i changed to system
and it still says elgato but wait it
should be system right
and then
here uh uh okay
let me test this
i forgot i needed to change back
everything again i had everything um
changed for vr uh for the vr collab uh
and also
changed the microphone to the
new extra separate microphone so let me
listen in here does this work
oh yeah
okay okay okay your audio is fixed now
let me listen how to yoda
[Music]
it's so beautiful beautiful okay i'll
take some time to practice to imitate
that
no they do something with like flipping
over their voices
um which
i think if i practice i can do it
um
flipping over if you know what i mean
uh
but anyway what's y'all is my controller
fun
i want to play some game now
are you playing the game or what shut up
yes i am
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes
uh we will be immediately surprised by
some story because
because
we we literally closed the game
at the end of a chapter last time
what happened i think there was they
were about to show us a flashback of
what happened
last episode on yakuza
with
kidu yeah yeah wait i don't hear audio
shut them up
you don't hear any of her wait what is
this is this is this opening
just opening right
i'm not missing anything right now
speeder
uh [\h__\h]
sound
sounds doco
oh god we're getting the booby scene
again and the kittio naked in the shower
scene again here
autumn
uh
i can't hear it
we might just do that on pc
i was able to hear the youtube video
why can't i not hear the game on youtube
and and vlc i was able to hear uh
windows settings everything changed i
didn't change
that why did that change
[Music]
and then i go to
where the [\h__\h]
[Music]
she's team
how about i still i can't
oh wait how about how about i
have you ever tried
restarting it
close and open
close
oh yeah i hear it
because i had it open when i was
switching the settings i guess and
elgato didn't update it okay
[Applause]
okay
oh let's
go i think it's a bit noisy
ah
sorry to keep you waiting
my dear yakuza friends
and becomes
can he really use magic more on that
later
what
yeah this is uh yakuza 0 collaboration
with star wars episode
chapter five an honest living
this is really uh helpful that they're
doing the
the reviews of what happened before for
streaming purposes
because we also usually have a couple
days in between where we don't play
that
um
[Music]
foreign
my chair is shaking
does anyone else have um
you know they keep on talking all the
time there's so much story so i need to
stop the game in order to ever get to
talk ever
does anyone here have um
uh one of those chairs that i have
what's it called again uh herman miller
or something like that does anyone have
those chairs
is it is it just me or do they
um gather an
insane amount of dust under the sitting
uh uh
thing i guess no one has that [\h__\h]
chair damn it can't
relate like yesterday i was like
yesterday evening i was putting away my
vr [\h__\h] uh to bring in my chair again
because i rolled it out of the room i
bring i brought in my chair and i was
like kind of
looking at it and i was like
i looked closer at the
at the
i saw a few people say yes
to to having the chair yes mine does the
same you took i really am
because like you know the sitting
surface is like a mesh something
something
and underneath i looked like
i i suddenly saw this really fake layer
of
disgusting dust and i'm like what the
[\h__\h] is this
huh
it's not even cat hair it's like insane
dust and i'm like i don't even have this
chair for that long and how how my yeah
my phoenix ashes must be
crumbling out of my butt every time i
sit on it
yeah i guess it's phoenix ashes because
holy [\h__\h] i was like where the [\h__\h] like
all my other furniture that that just
stands around and should be the one who
gathers dust doesn't get this kind of
dust it's like a crazy a crazy type of
dust like a
what the [\h__\h] is this crew disgusting
dust
oh
yeah was crazy
and then i tried to clean it but my my
vacuum cleaner couldn't it can't even
fit properly under that there's like a
like a kind of like a space in between
um the the chair where you sit and then
the thing underneath where the dust
gathers it's like like a few centimeters
and i tried to squeeze my
my
my my thing in there
my vacuum cleaner
why am i telling you this because i was
just so fascinated and shocked and
disgusted and how much dust is down
there sorry it's probably no one cares
but
oh yeah power washer um
let's play a power washer simulator
looking online it seems like a thing oh
thank god i thought you know for a
moment that when i saw it i was like eh
has this chair been like this since i
got it and this was like a used object
and it's just been dusty because
i already like someone already used it
before
but no in the
it really just gathers an insane amount
of dust there
it's disgusting
i just cleaned my erin recently yeah
this dead skin skin cells it doesn't
look like dead skin cells though
i think it's i think it's uh my
chihuahua phoenix uh ashes
it's a dust magnet it really is
it really is
anyway
[Music]
well you did touch
time to cut off your finger fingertips
these your your
shave it off
uh
[Music]
do you have time for that [\h__\h]
what's wrong with your clothes
the only thing that makes it look like a
yakuza is that [\h__\h] maybe that necklace
if you just uh
pull up the buttons then
let's go
why
why wasn't that a complimentary
[Music]
um
tuck in your shirt close the buttons
take off your necklace and you're done
like for real it's a normal suit
it's a normal decent color
i'll have to walk slowly for you
come with me
music
what is it with these three business
ladies
one that really stands out like what is
that knee on the skirt you need to go
shopping too
if someone doesn't fit into the business
world it's you lady yo you look like
ridiculous what are you wearing how do
you think you can go to the office like
that oh my god you go with me right now
we need to buy clothes for you too
these are cute though kind of lame but
cute they look like um
the right one at least looks like
shut up the ramen looks like like um
like from big bang theory what
uh
what's the girl the the the one that
sheldon kind of like
hangs out with
uh what's her name i'm watching uh
no no no not bernadette amy yeah amy she
looks like doesn't she look like what
like exactly like amy would dress
with those long socks with the
underneath the long skirt
with the loafers and the comfy
yeah exactly like this this is exactly
what she would wear maybe not that
colorful what does that mean she does
wear some colorful clothes sometimes
well i'm really talkative today i need
to shut up
kill me
we were going um
what do you
think i'm a kid okay what do you think
what do you think
okay
oh my cat what do you think
oh my god
[Music]
he does end up wearing a white suit
doesn't he
but
can we be honest for a second
the white suit looks much more like a
yakuza than the normal suit that he's
wearing right now for [\h__\h] sake
are you trying to not look like yakuza
oh come on
you had one job just keep on you old so
this looks so much like yeah
i didn't what what am i thinking
this looks more like this looks more
like mafia even it looks like [\h__\h]
italian mafia
[Music]
exactly it was better before
it makes so much sense that i have the
handcuffs now yeah i'm back in my role
of the fashion police i need to arrest
both of them because both of them are
involved in a huge fashion crime
he even has chains in his on his t-shirt
like what the [\h__\h] oh my god
choosing this when the previous one was
just fine
[Music]
although i mean
i gotta say when it comes to suits i
like the striped pattern uh on the suit
and i think in general suits are really
really really really really really nice
looking
yeah i like the striped pattern but
please use that on a gray or a black
suit not a white one holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
was almost speaking of much can i ask
you one quick question
um
you're gonna do you guys guys wanna
brainstorm with me for one second
one second
um
merch
merch idea i need one
more
merch idea and i have some of my own but
i'm not quite happy with them
uh
helper
um
i was thinking uh so
i i don't want to give any details but
the members already kind of know about
one thing and then i have one more thing
that doesn't involve any art
um
[Music]
it is like something you can use like
all of you can use it
uh
and then one more thing
i want one more thing that
would include art as well
but like
something where i can display
one more
a piece of art
[Music]
april i already have an apron oven
mitten
glasses
frying pan frying pan
[Music]
keychain i was thinking about that too
but that just seems to i want something
more special i always try to make my
merchandise stand out and
have it be something special
oh god
um
[Music]
i have one visitor whenever that visitor
comes to my apartment they're always
like you allah do you still not have a
shoe horn and i'm always like no
no
actually that's my brother
uh
socks socks
hmm
songs
socks sounds funny but i want something
more like um
easy to display art or smee
um boxing gloves bowling ball what are
you talking about
it's a serious question
a lounge box or bento box oh
that would be cute but um people
overseas don't really
use
lunchboxes much
um
although that would be cute
necktie
what about the girls who don't wear
neckties i don't wear neckties
but i guess
switch switch case nintendo switch case
i mean stuff like that like i iphone
cases and and switch cases or ipad cases
or whatever it always is something like
that
some people can use and they'll be happy
about it but so many others won't be
able to use it
um a stress ball
i was thinking about that too chicken
stress ball but i want something that
that can like feature art you know
like like nicely um
one idea i had was
well i probably shouldn't reveal it in
case it ends up being that
umbrella umbrella umbrella like a small
one you mean true
[Music]
totally not writing that idea down one
second one socket one moment
um
huh
umbrellas are no according to inna what
was she asking about a big one or a
small one
because if it's a small one
well did you say what reasonings i don't
see a problem with a small one you know
the ones that you can fold together
coast coasters coasters
coasters hmm
that just sounds a little bit cheap i
want something of better quality
i mean you could i guess make
coasters out of good quality but
who even uses coasters i don't use
coasters
uh
chessboard
we don't we don't play chess in here no
more
mouse
mouse and keyboard pad ah
we already had that last time if you
mean like something to put under your
keyboard on your mouse
last birthday
but
but you
you gave me an idea
[Music]
a wallet a walnut
what is
i think it's difficult to
[Music]
i'll just write a few more ideas of you
guys down
[Music]
i don't know how keyboard caps work
shower curtain
uh
a binder a binder you mean to put like
documents in
plate um
[Music]
uh
chair is a bit too big
[Music]
wait maybe is there some item
that i wear that people could
built
nah i want something of art
[Music]
gaming footrest oh
um
think think think chickens think do we
really want a fidget spinner as
merchandise out of all the things we
could have
um
[Music]
egg cup
hmm
um
[Music]
oh
oven mitts sounds
really cute
but that again would be something where
i can't really although i write it down
in case my other idea gets turned down
[Music]
is again something everyone could use it
seems like i'm i'm leaning towards
making my merchandise all kitchen
related
[Music]
sleep mask
cookie jar
yoga pants
wind roller
[Music]
that's difficult because you got to sell
those size of the right size of the
paper as well
and make it reusable
rice cooker guys that's too too like
technically difficult
too advanced
cookie
cutter hmm
dust collector
echo reusable shopping bag
um
but that's something an echo bag i've
already seen a lot within whole live
merchandise
so i don't want to repeat something that
like everyone else has already done a
million times
no you know
i don't know i want something special
[Applause]
brass knuckles
chihuahua hat but that's again enough
nothing with art
uh
egg mold egg mold for frying
a pizza cutter flies water morning stuff
your ideas are getting crazier guys
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's taking too long and um
i feel like i feel like
um
[Music]
okay i think
for now
[Music]
i acknowledge some of your ideas and i
don't say some of them out loud because
i already fetched those ideas and
there's a high chance that that might be
one of the merchandise things and i
don't want to say it out loud if there's
a high chance for it
so
[Music]
okay
okay for now
i might come back to you guys on this
one
[Laughter]
i am
oh
i'll kill you first
[Music]
by the way today
i kind of wanna
we might not do two full uh
uh chapters because
i think we're gonna spend quite a long
time reading super chats and i wanna do
some uh side quests today as well and
that might take up some time so just so
you know
definitely do like one chapter
and then we'll see if we have some side
quests to do
oh [\h__\h] do i remember how to fight let's
let's test it out
[Music]
i'm so slow right now
oh that's uh
this one
and then how do i r1 was r1 the focus on
one person i think yeah
there we go
ow
yeah i want to lock okay okay
and then
zero now zero circle to hold shut up
this is what i wanted to do okay
in your face
okay okay we're warmed up
we're warmed up oh my gosh oh my gosh
warmed warmed up perfectly
[Music]
you both look like italian mafia
not even japanese
m
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait is he trying to make him less
recognizable or just make him look more
normal if he tries to make him less
recognizable yes totally putting on
those glasses i will not know anymore
who that is what where where did kid you
go where kill you guys someone's
thinking
he i saw him just a second ago now he's
gone
[Laughter]
[Applause]
no more
foreign
at the police
[Applause]
the amount of business cards i've
received in japan is insane like they
have this whole i don't know if you guys
have that where you live but in in
austria we don't have this whole
business card culture
there were some times where i had some
two but usually i wouldn't have one day
yeah i would just take the business card
and be like somebody must say and i
don't have one
um
yeah yeah yeah
and give you the business card and you
look at it and you're like
oh and then you put it in your business
card collector or in your purse or
whatever
yeah gotta look at it and then exchange
but i didn't have anything to exchange
usually
not a thing you're in la time not a
thing in the u.s
not in europe either
is it in only in japan or maybe also in
korea
yeah i can imagine it being like an
asian thing
apparently in korea yes
in korea yes
not in korea and someone said korea yes
not necessary oh
so just a little bit in korea
hmm
japan really is very serious about their
business cards man
i guess i guess they like card games
so they also like business cards
exchanging business cards as if they're
playing i don't know pokemon or magic
the gathering or shadow verse or
yu-gi-oh or something like that maybe
that's how
what they feel they're doing
it looks good on classes though
you know
did you see
anyone i like where is good to talk
business look look
oh but that's matcha furuto not melon
furoto
where's the good spot to talk to the
business conversation
not in the front no no no no no no very
back
[Music]
how many people are we gonna see one
person what are those tables
gaming tables
what game is that
it's a shootie shoot game or just and
don't get hit that looks like a dunk and
hit game
i don't think you should have a business
meeting on one of those
i want to be in the back but yeah
it should be
one on the one on the wall in the back
would be good
dori moyoconai
um
maybe this one
just looks as good as any yes
this is the best i could do
ah um well if you're the one receiving
um
a guest basically then i think you
should be in the fire fighters in the
back uh facing the wall while your
guests should be facing the door like
the outside basically is what i would
say
personally
but i don't really know anything about
these kind of things
but i think this asserts dominance like
this is this is my cafe yo it's my
business it's my my city
honey
you got a problem with that
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh well coffee
or we should wait until the other person
comes up
[Music]
sorry sorry i know that
shut up
[Music]
i didn't have the controller in my hands
[Laughter]
i know that i know that just like me but
he he does it differently though even
though he knows it supposedly
thank you wait what's d-day
oh you mean saturday
because of the concert
yeah i gotta get up early for it so i uh
also because of the expo
the program at the expo so i won't be
up for too long tonight
foreign
[Music]
uh
do i look like
how does he even believe that story
is
i gotta say
i gotta say they did a better job at
majima's storyline because like this is
the third chapter
and eve and even now we're doing like
kind of it feels like a side story like
a filler episode because we're not even
we're not even doing yakuza [\h__\h] we're
like they said we're just working
for the company now doing real real
estate stuff
um
so the build up is like really slow
while with majima's first two chapters
they captured my
uh
my attention and my immersion so
strongly and then i was so mad that i
leave us with that cliffhanger but it
was so hype everything and then we go
back to this and i was like well at
least if we go back probably then
nikita's story is really going to take
off but um nothing's happening
so far
we yeah i guess we beat up a lot of
people in the building but still but
still
it's it wasn't as exciting as majima's
story
[Music]
what do i look like
my family here so i know it pretty well
but i don't remember any place like that
might be tucked away on one of uh the
smaller streets of tenkaichi i'll have a
look once i've got this gift box uh gift
box bye
oh wait is it telling me where to buy it
soup on street here
is it telling me to buy it right there
all right
uh yeah all that flexing on being a
senpai now now that we we're
employed at the same place
maybe no i feel like poor people
wouldn't have it but let's check it out
that's the building i made in that okay
well yeah
um do you have a set do you have what i
need
no of course not sushi set
bento box
uh
then my other guess would be don quixote
from the m store all the way north
not don quixote
the m store
genuine korean barbecue
i'm so oh there okay oh no problem
let's go oh tissue
thank you
azamas
let's go let's go let's go
mask
did you guys watch it chan's stream uh
john was like explaining some more and
showing off some pictures
from
uh the expo
she was showing off some first looks
yeah if you didn't watch it you missed
some exciting uh look into what the expo
looks like the expo not the concert
[Music]
wait shut the light i need to pick up an
item is there air here how do i take it
[Music]
i thought they pick it up automatically
ah wait wait i need an item
i need an item when i'm in this forum
there's literally nothing here [\h__\h]
[Music]
no more [\h__\h] around okay now
[\h__\h] yes
yeah
why did i press square
it didn't feel like it was doing
anything anyway
bye-bye
um
yeah i also uh
i watched atm's stream uh
not all of it
but i saw i saw some of expo
as well looking dope i'm i i've got to
say like it feels really
regrettable
you can't i can't just walk around the
expo
yeah
yeah we've seen though small ammo
will be part of it
small ammo can walk around and then see
the convention
i wish i was small ammo get
my
yes miko daniel will be there too
so
mikko dania and smallama can take a
picture together
oh fukai it's literally an offline
meeting between mikko daniel and small
uh bird guy
let me and let me and let me and
oh this is not a restaurant that you can
actually get into oh [\h__\h]
well we can get into here
i gotta say though they missed out on
putting
a pudding for pudding
they miss out on putting
um the kfb bucket fried chicken or a
cafe burger into the official
convention menu
did you see holo yen
is
a cookie
and i was like um
a cookie huh
could could have uh
could have maybe done a kfp bucket or
or something like that
[Laughter]
a cookie
i hope it's as good as the chocolate
cookies that i made at least
if only exactly if only whole life
english had a food themed youtuber
ah but unfortunately we don't
unfortunately we don't have such a thing
it's okay i'll assert my dominance
somewhere else
ah is it gonna be dangerous
now we're fine
no
kuka
no it's not about forgetting me
ian like it's not like anyone else got
like a
their own food
it's just ian is one thing and that's
the cookie
i love the indonesia bento though
but that was a really cool idea and gets
people to get to know indonesian food
although who knows if it will be really
authentic but uh like tasting but it
looks cool
i think a lot of people will want to try
the indonesia bento um
thanks we brought stairs
looks
somewhat comfy in here he made himself
[Music]
give us back those cookies though
i want the snacks back you little speech
um
[Music]
oh so intimidating
i'm shaking i'm shaking
[Music]
hmm
um
ah
[Music]
70 000.
foreign
especially now that we're wearing
glasses
we're even stronger than usual oh he
takes it off oh here he took off his
limiter
oh no the other way around
not wearing it is his limiter
where are those glasses
uh-huh
it's bad to crack your neck
do i need to bring in my
my chat to tell you that
that's what you get from cracking your
neck
oh
beautiful beautiful
[Music]
oh
hey
is
[Laughter]
that's just how it is
um
[Music]
sorry
[Laughter]
foreign
why am i mean to you i didn't what
and the way he went to like what did i
do
no i would use
um
[Music]
um they'll be crying in the closet for
the next couple weeks because of that
roast
was too strong was a [\h__\h] critical
hit
yes
that hurts so much they'll turn into an
anti
empty auntie
we're besties now look at us two besties
forever
love love
love
i haven't gone bowling in a long time
bowling balls are just so
heavy man
so heavy like you don't even know
every time i walk by a store like that
in real life i'm too embarrassed to look
oh hello
yes
[Music]
foreign
god
hmm
being a millionaire or a billionaire in
japan
means much less than
outside of japan like in america so
there's just so many zeros
so many zeros
in the numbers
sorry
yeah japan is trillionaires yeah
[Music]
let's roll
we should do that song but do it with
yakuza goodbye terms
who the hell was that his little pet
called him the laser king with a
straight face they definitely mentioned
yamanoido and i don't like what i heard
i'll need to check up on him right away
uh-huh what are yakuza goodbye turns
well
let's roll and
um um
uh
i'm sure there are a lot i just can't
think of them because i'm not badass
enough
[Music]
um
what
hi
[Applause]
[Music]
um
yeah let's go to the gaming kingdom
foreign
[Music]
how slow are you
um
uh
so
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
sorry my jug is so heavy i have like two
liters of water in here
questioning
i just realized
foreign right no timeline the present
let's get you up to speed on the basics
of our business
but um
sorry i don't want to do voice acting
today
oh it's a bit distracting with the place
in such shambles i'll call my secretary
to help me straighten up secretary
didn't know you had one yeah
i'll introduce you later she's quite the
charmer and i think you'll agree kitty
son
can i ask you to step out for a bit
while i get the office put together it
shouldn't take too long
okay
oh my god next time we're stepping in is
like a completely different universe
and we'll be like magic
yeah i'm always cleaning up the office i
should go for a stroll and check back in
later
oh there's an izakaya this looks like an
izakaya
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
we going to the terracotta again
no
what is our mission now just wait
nothing to do
um
video as uh all you all you wanna all
you can watch uh
um private room
video
hold up um i guess you can watch uh
you can get my friends all alone there
if you wanna
hold on
[Applause]
hello um friends what kind of group are
you goons okay
[Music]
he's bleeding he's literally like
bleeding to death holy [\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
today i'm supposed to tell you some
stories guys and tell you more about
my
[Music]
my disadvocation
don't make me forget that please uh
here does not kill totally no never
never never the protagonists in these
yakuza games even though they're yakuza
yakuza they're too good for that they're
good people at heart they would never do
such a thing
they'd rather get killed themselves
before
it says tonkatsu up there on the second
floor
nanny
[Music]
yes
[\h__\h]
i want to use the heat move i keep on
seeing it popping up
or is that not
no
no ah
what am i supposed to do right now just
wait or should i go back into the office
already or or or do they want me to pass
a certain
alley
[Music]
barely any any times gone by okay he's
probably not done yet so that yeah
well
it doesn't knock them out too long
enough oh
perhaps
oh hey those dudes are gone
we can grill some marshmallows here oh
what did i
say i spy with my little eye
me ho tono wait let's watch videos you
guys said something about those videos i
didn't want to watch a lot last time but
okay
uh
uh video play stucco
where are those videos
is it not one of those stars
ah is it here
oh
enjoy erratic videos here
i mean what else to do without precious
time
but watching some
erotic videos
miracle
doesn't that seem like the most logical
thing to do
ah
i have so many things to tell you guys
but but i feel like i'll never have
enough time
in this game to tell one full story
man
uh
uh one second where are we here
i'll tell you
after watching the erotic videos i'll
watch you one i'll tell you one thing
well first things first
oh
oh you again
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah here um
have some pocket tissues
i have pocket tissues
you probably should have kept them
because now you're going into the erotic
store
um
huh
second one
we got a pair
we got matching ones like how do i get
into the where is it
this one
what
this one this one this one
ah this one
video boobs at gandala you can watch
videos of varied cast of gorgeous girls
as you meet these women out in the city
under certain conditions new video
content will become available search
every corner of town and find your dream
girl
[Music]
let's see what we can watch so far
hello
uh-huh
800 that's pretty cheap
can we watch one okay
i need
only i only i okay
yes
i hunted them
enjoy the video thank you sir
look
[Music]
oh come on
no
no no no no no no
no no
no no no no
say so idle this suit
no no
don't look at me with those eyes
where did you get those shoes though can
you tell me
um
wait didn't you just have different
nails a moment ago
oh that's that's that one that one
pointy finger
only that one has a different color on
your other hand
yeah um
[Applause]
i never want to see this ever again
i never want to walk into this place
ever again
no
i can't when if if i have to be safe so
you guys my audience has to say so too
so
delete that out of your memory right now
[Music]
oh no you did not
oh didn't agree to this contract of
course you did you didn't read the small
small letters
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
i am i just i don't know what i'm
supposed to do they just want me to
spend some time
but like do they want me to go somewhere
specific they're just not telling me or
[Music]
check the page ah i was wondering about
that
aha
new
uh
i'm trying to read the
yeah
i guess i didn't have to try to read it
myself that's written in the
in the
in the message
89 is all set
why
uh
ha
oh
if you don't understand what's happening
it's um
japanese
uh
numbers
can be read in different ways and with
that you can like make special secret
codes and then read it like like a
phrase like a word it doesn't work with
every letter
um not every letter can be turned into a
number but but you can kind of like
scuff it
i can stretch it
and be like
putting together
some things that sound somewhat close to
what you're trying to say
okay apparently now it's already time to
go back uh
to the previous building
where
is the shortest way having this way
[Music]
hey i don't have time to fight right now
i need a new tissue please guy
no you don't have tissues for me [\h__\h]
you have tissues
thank you
i gave my tissues away to the weirdo
uh
sugita building wait wait
it was
ah here
this small one
yeah like lead speak
but it's um
not
not uh
like what the numbers look like that one
it's not like what letter they look like
but what letter they sound like when
spoken out loud in japanese
anyway you're the secretary
oh cute
she's too cute
marina
secretary i look forward to working with
you
i feel like you might have a video on
that
in that video booth as well
don't you
all right katie good to meet you what
are you thinking your son the place
looks great doesn't it
yeah i know it i knew suddenly it would
look like completely different place how
did you put in that floor in that short
amount of time
look at that floor look at that ceiling
light look at that wallpaper
[Laughter]
i knew it
you cannot use the office in the city
the building as your hideout which also
serves as your business headquarters as
the story advances you'll unlock the
ability to switch protagonists using the
hideout telephone
as well as change clothes into any of
the outfits you've unlocked
now how about i walk you through some
business basics this is a good time
sure
uh of course
in that case oh thank you for the money
in a video thank you i don't wanna watch
it i don't wanna i don't wanna even if
it exists
let my secretary take it from here
there's a lot to remember but if you
forget anything you can ask me anytime
for now i'll walk you through the whole
process once
uh oh dear
oh god no
nine pages
[Applause]
commodore joe real estate royal in real
estate royal you purchase and manage
properties build up your funds
is this like the this is not like the
last thing that we had in
[Music]
and like a dragon right
it's actually pretty easy yeah probably
after reading all this [\h__\h] and grasping
it
with the ultimate goal of bringing down
the five billionaires manage your
holdings from kiryu's office by
interacting with the city model on the
table
you can also check the status of your
properties by selecting business
[Laughter]
can someone read this to me
manage your business
managing real estate from the office you
can do the following for the office menu
start payout collection for each area
uh-huh collect profits from each area
assign a manager and securities area
synthesis properties
manage your properties using these
options and you will soon be ranking a
huge profits
starting payout collection select real
estate royale management and press
trial to display a payout collection
confirmation window if you have assigned
a manager or security guard to the area
you want to click from the salaries will
also be listed select yes to confirm
uh-huh
see nothing's entering my brain right
now i'm reading it out loud but it's not
like i'm reading it mentally just
just on the surface
profits sometime after collection is
started the cost will fill and you will
be able to collect your profits the
funding gathered is based on private
progress and economic trends
however sometimes
ah things will not go smoothly
promise me arises and the collagen
process will make me challenge still my
battle i'm collecting your profits
uh collecting problems if a problem
occurs the clients and gods will freeze
you'll be unable to collect profits
until you go and find the person and
pick a fight with them
money battles sometimes when you collect
your profits one of the five billions
will challenge your money battle
the managers assigned to that area will
try to counter the effects of
[Music]
billionaire's aggressive investment
fighter
kiana do your best come on photo
i need i need i need you guys to cheer
me on
cheer me on
i need a big yawn
[Laughter]
thank you
thank you yes defeat reading
let's certain dominance above reading
managers
but if their hp runs out you will lose
their targeted property protect your
property hypothetically and then it's my
property
you're going to sign one manager peria
they have the following
abilities financial saving
currencies hp during money battles this
only recovers when your manager is not
in use so switch them out often
switch out managers often economic
influence shows the manager's effect on
economic trends the higher the value
better okay
on the left is the starting one and the
one on the right is the final one
i can't i can't do a full yawn
that was good that was good
[Laughter]
and signing stop security in addition to
the manager you can also sign the
security
am i making you guys yawn too
sorry
uh you can also sign the security garden
area each security employee has the
following abilities problem solving oh
save the influence
if you're violent encounters will
transpire when walking in an area the
number on the left is the starting value
sending advisors to properties sending
an advisor to visit the property hippity
hobbity to help make improvements
upgrading its rank in the process
select the property help you and then an
advisor and you will have to pay for
their services but the earning potential
of a property help it will improve as
its rank and prices and each advisor has
different
abilities and areas of expertise so
select the right advisor for hippity hop
putting you now my property
i think that covers about it
girl
hundred percent
i remember i should change my managers
often
and then sometimes we fight um
and yeah
yourself is able to access access to
real estate royale manual and choose
real estate royale management and then
select laser king aryan press blah you
can review the rules and control anytime
you need to be a help in the same menu
is this necessary for the game to
to
proceed
is this necessary
your attention's property
huh
one
[Music]
what
okay focus
focus focus focus
just keep on pressing x probably
alright i need staff do i have staff it
looks like i have staff
[Music]
what
do i say okay
[Music]
yes
yeah yes
optional but money
okay
we needed a lot money and like a dragon
but i don't know if it's like
as we're if we're that desperate for
money in this game as well
yes always invest
[Music]
okay
cool
did i do the thing did i do it
did i do it did i do what i needed to do
[Music]
um
okay
triangle
[Music]
yes
no
don't i need to assign people down there
[Music]
brain empty style very much so
huh
what happened
what
[Music]
is not that hard
yeah sure once you get it
i wait five minutes
press r1 on that screen on this one
hmm
cannot change staff during payout
collection
[Music]
hmm
oh i
i will i will understand this
another day
not my type
ah
close and explore for five minutes oh
okay what
we need to let the secretary know
you gave that collections order like a
pro yeah
now you just need to relax for a bit and
the cash will come flowing in oh and
yama noise left me some funds to serve
as your initial operating capital i'll
give that to you now
five million
no
this is a fortune are you sure
yes that nest egg
and duty suck it down on the first floor
of this building are my little send off
to you please use them with my blessing
though relying on a single shop's profit
is putting a lot of eggs in one basket
why not buy another with that cash oh if
you want to sell it started i'd
recommend sukiyaki muranaka on tenkaic
it's a pretty popular spot but still a
comparable affordable acquisition
we'll go have a look just
use the operating capital yes how do i
how do i get it in real life or like in
here
i have to look at it first okay okay
okay okay
fine fine fine
okay real well
not everything can be done
online apparently
is it this like here
what should i do
i can just just buy it like that
okay
yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
he's like how about this money
yes cannot say no to that ho ho ho
wow
okay
i bought it
i i just went there showed the money at
the building and the building said yes
that's hope that was necessary
apparently no signing of contracts or
anything like that nope
no i just had to ask the building
because i mean
yeah you know it's just fair buildings
have feelings too why why do we ask
people who think they own the building
but what what if the building
wants to own itself and make its own
decisions yeah yeah yeah yeah they never
ask the building they always just ask
the people who supposedly own it but you
can't own a building like that the
building is its own person okay respect
that man
poor building man everyone always
forgets about the building about their
feelings
yeah
those questions you ordered are in
the money is ready and waiting for you
oh a set time after giving the order to
begin collections in a given block
you'll be able to pick up those profits
access the menu with yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum yum
hey out ready
[Music]
and then i just start again
do i just start
again
[Music]
didn't but didn't i already assign stuff
about to the sukiyaki
no
[Music]
what happened
did i is that considered a sign
huh i need to assign the same this one
again as well
a r1 huh
[Music]
huh
okay
uh i need to invest in both right
[Music]
i'm already invested but it doesn't it
only says invested in the sukiyaki one
you see the invested stamp on it
[Music]
wait which one is selected anyway it's
so confusing
it says i'm already invested
ah
ah okay so it was confusing
okay
[Music]
now i start
now we start
and it's optional to invest in
properties to upgrade them but it's very
recommended okay
[Music]
yes
okay
bye bye
ah
nani
looks like those profits are in this is
exactly when you need to keep watch for
one of the five billionaires picking a
money battle if you lose enough money
battle you lose ownership of a property
so be sure that you always appoint a
manager oh
and definitely a lot to keep in your
head mm-hmm i'm sure you'll have it soon
your son basically you want to expand
your holdings grow those
ichiban holdings remember grow those
properties and enhance your personal
loss roaster
roasted rooster
that will build your share and earn you
greater profits the bigger we get by
repeating our processor closer will be
shutting down
yeah okay
in this line of work you end up spending
money in all sorts of ways and rest
wisely that includes integration
and i don't see how i'm going to spend
this much money anytime soon my vegas
i'll use it well i hope
i trust that you will mr president
no but as the secretary just feels not
supposed to call the one making all the
business calls the president does not
really feel secretaries to you does it i
wouldn't really know but yamanoi sounds
the president here isn't he well yes
officially but what's the harm if money
nassau wants to call you that i say let
her it's actually my first gig it's a
secretary something here to be
secretary-ish as possible
are you first time at this too
what did you use to do before
yamanui-san hired you
that's a big juicy secret okay girl okay
chill
you can't really care what you call me
so knock yourself out
same for the top here mr prince
okay
cool
yeah i see a lot of headaches in my
future i want i agree to do this i'm
going all in
i also see a lot of
headaches but that's okay
bet you'll find one of the cards soon oh
i was going to meet oda for that drink
he said the place was called serena
on tenkaichi street oh serena like go to
serena
oh [\h__\h] serena
from
oh wait what was that dude again was he
one who teaches the
fighting moves
no you weren't the one from that side
quest
yeah crazy cute
oh
what voice did i give him i don't
remember
goalie it's kid your son oh i mean yo
how is it hanging
crazy kill from the
silvers it's hard to tell if you're
acting like a gentleman or yankee as
usual so let's bring you here today
uh i'm sorry actually i want to work on
my hooliganism with you again
part two of that cyclist huh
at my office
he wants to work in my office
okay
he doesn't even want money what the [\h__\h]
if you're going to apple pay your salary
even if we know each other business is
business
you bitching can you sign you i think i
just learned some [\h__\h] about being a
hardcore who we're getting right now
aha an advisor
ability rank two
really
okay
thanks for helping me get my pieces
perfect
okay cool
[Music]
um i'm here serena i'm here to meet
oh
executive lunch i'm here to meet my
bestie
my bestie
[Music]
hello
gosh he looks good
you look okay too
nicer
nice
nice eyelashes
nice lips nice beauty mark
what a lady
oh no i thought i was meeting my other
business
[Music]
thank you
um
[Music]
oh
that bar makes me think yesterday you
guys know what i did yesterday
you know i had that kitchen counter uh
my new kitchen counter that that where
you can sit on the other side um but i
didn't have i didn't have chairs yet and
i was thinking so long about what chairs
to buy and then and then yeah weeks have
passed of me thinking about the chairs
but um i got them um they arrived uh the
day before yesterday and yesterday uh
while i was cleaning i was like
okay wawa
believe in yourself the reviewers even
said it's super easy to build those
chairs so kiwawa
you can do it you don't need to ask
someone for help to put together two
uh bar
chairs basically stools two stools
basically
so i assembled them yes and it was easy
so now i have chairs on
on a kitchen
counter where i can actually eat
something so yesterday i ate my dinner
and today i ate my breakfast
there instead of eating it in my bed
incredible
yes
like a normal person
yes and i was watching a series uh on
disney plus with my ipad so i got some
entertainment there as well
oh my god i mean honestly it's
ridiculous because the chairs were
really like
basically four screws
and the rest was just like putting like
you know three pieces together without
any tools just like
um yeah
inserting one thing into the other
it really was
not a big deal so it was good it was
actually really good that i didn't ask
anyone for help because otherwise it
would have ended up being really
embarrassing like girl you could have
done this yourself
yeah thankfully those chairs were easy
mm-hmm
yeah it's like a bar now it's really
cool
but i've also
um even though i wasn't planning on
doing this when i moved in because i was
like i never have guests anyway and blah
i'm happy if i just have the kitchen
counter but i finally decided i'm gonna
get a proper dining table and proper
dining chairs as well because i have
this space and my apartment looks kind
of empty without it i guess and and that
way um i can have like dinner parties i
guess
if i want to
um
so now i'm also actively looking for
a dinner table i've been keeping my eyes
open on furniture shops
[Music]
yeah i want to get a nice looking one
not something from ikea i love ikea but
i want a nice
nice dinner table
that not everybody else has
yes
and i hope i won't regret it but it's
really difficult to make a choice like
if i buy a proper one it's going to be
pretty expensive i don't want to buy the
wrong one now i'm like unsure if i
should buy a round one or a square one
um
kind of
kind of leaned towards a round one for
like a few days and now i want to square
one again i don't know i can't decide
yeah and like if i want the surface to
be like wooden or if i want the surface
to be not wooden if i want it to be
a wooden color or black
blah blah oh thank you roman there
welcome back
thank you thank you thank you
nice to see you
a triangle
[Music]
yeah but i am i'm i'm trying to finalize
my freaking apartment because i've been
just slacking off and waiting
and waiting and waiting and waiting and
waiting yeah i want to make my apartment
look nice and comfy and finished i've
been living here for a while and it just
looks like a work in progress forever
because i can't do [\h__\h] alone man
but as we as i've proven to myself
yesterday i can put together
at least a [\h__\h] chair or a stool bar
stool
that's that's something
that's something
for a big dining
table i'll need some help though maybe
maybe wherever i buy it maybe they can
put it together deliver and then pay and
put it together
oh no no no
go go go
there we go i need to pause the tangent
properly sorry in this game i can't do
it otherwise
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
okay
hi
hi hi
[Music]
hey
yay
[Music]
is
bum
[Music]
i got worse i was better before
but at least i got that video that means
i at least um i reached a certain amount
of points i needed right otherwise they
would would they have played that video
yeah 84
yay
[Music]
i got a video yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's my best so far
they always called me a bozo until
[Music]
i was pretty into it in the first half
pretty pretty focused
foreign
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
you [\h__\h]
i'm gonna rip out your balls and your
heart
i know which one will hurt more for you
little engine i'll enjoy
[Music]
m
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
like did some superhero
let's go
go next go next is in alexis
[Music]
no
he didn't do anything
please don't
beat him up in a mom
hold
m
[Music]
all right
okay
don't complain to me afterwards after
you're missing one year
cause i rip it out
um
he doesn't realize he's just a [\h__\h]
npcs
hey
[Music]
uh
hey
smash
[Music]
get up get up get up
we're not playing baseball here buddy
we're fighting a fair fight okay
oh no nothing really about this is fair
but yeah
but you don't really understand that do
you
because you don't fight fair fights
cause you're too weak to fight a fair
fight
uh
where did i get that from nine
now let me go let me go let me go no let
me go let me go let me go no i want this
cutting it close there
cutting is closed
[Music]
aah
get up
get up [\h__\h]
alive
[Music]
cockroach
okay
you'll give me back my
oh [\h__\h] do i have to fight him
[Music]
um
foreign
oh
um
[Music]
foreign
you drunk i are you drunk
drunkard
can't speak normally hong kong
[Music]
foreign
[\h__\h] off already
he must have been a pirate in his
previous life because he asked so much
[Music]
oh we finished your chapter that felt
pretty quick
um
wow
that's a lot of money
so yeah
we got the cutting cutting money money
there is a loan yeah it sounds like a
shorter one
in that case maybe i will be able to do
two chapters today
next chapter is very very short oh this
one too the yakuza way is this one short
too
oh maybe we can see some uh of matchima
then yo um i swear i will show you the
what happens after the cliffhanger no
matter what
i need to see it
you still alive
i'm back i did my business
i avenged you
hi
is
[Music]
damn he's so [\h__\h] up
um
[Music]
mmm
[Applause]
so popular
[Music]
you can both have a piece of me
so passionately
the ladies probably like the whole time
she's like has those question marks
above her head like huh
[Laughter]
foreign
this is confusing and i don't know what
they're talking about but these boys are
hot so i'm going to stay here and look
at them and and pet oda's the head and
supposedly heal his wounds but in
reality she's just really really into
him
so yeah
she takes this as a chance to
become his guardian angel
it's my fanfiction
um
yeah they call them these ladies these
bosses then these bars and mama which
you know
what if it's uh
[Music]
i would not
go
this is what your clothes look like when
you try to get the last few
squeezes out of the ketchup bottle
or anymore
ketchup bottle farts
the only farts in the world that smell
good are ketchup bubble farts
he's the protagonist he can pull off any
stunt
a grab okay
okay okay take or steal
a puma capture
all right
let's get kusan that kuzu
back to claiming my name huh come to
think of it i still haven't been back to
give the empty lot a proper once over
what does that mean now the cops may
have cleared it out by now could be
worth going to take a look
go to the empty lot
the empty lot dokodaki where the hell
was that again
[Music]
up here
apparently
okay
all right
interesting stuff yo okay i have to talk
about this every time
every time i walk past this one second i
need to turn it up really loud for you
guys to hear probably
uh
listen closely
but every time i run by that it sounds
to me
like um when sup when mario in super
mario 64
uh lands in lava or something and then
goes like
you know that sound where he's like
and every time i walk by this i hear a
sound effect that sounds exactly like
that
is it just me it's just me
oh yeah i remember that you remember
that
every time when i run back not now
because i already triggered it once i
think
um
at the payouts hey i'll pay out uh where
where where was that where was that uh
is it here ah this is here
are you going insane no i hear it every
time
hello hello oh you're just chilling here
now okay
[Music]
oh
some so much for that
i can't collect anything until i uh
resolve the trouble really there's
always gonna be trouble in this town
there's trouble there's always trouble
travel trouble trouble
okay
where is the place where you can get
better healing items um
where you guys told me once
i don't recall
ah the drugstore made me
the pharmacy yeah that's so that's the
pharmacy right i should go there
okay so up okay
good healing items
i need good healing items
[Music]
red marker
but that's behind the backlot
if it would be behind that i would
understand you think you mean dad has
something to do with the trouble
somehow that sounds
like it's not true
yeah
oh okay
uh
here
it looks so tiny
it is tiny it's so narrow simmer
you're not sure you must say hello
um
i would like to buy
significant wait which one do i have uh
do i have
this is my strongest right now
so let's get
i can't carry
[Music]
i don't want to throw them away the ones
that i have but i get a second
get rid of the pocket tissues
um i don't want to waste anything so
yeah oh adam box
oh [\h__\h]
these are expensive i'll just get two
that's all i can get
we'll be fine
put them in the item oh you mean the
tissues
can i do that anywhere
i can't do that here right i need to go
to an item box
not too lazy
i should get rid of all the small heels
and get like 12 royale's way smarter
we'll have it
[Music]
yeah
once i use them up i'll buy royals only
[Music]
that kind of love just ain't for us
crave a different kind of love
i'll be your role
[Music]
i think those lyrics are wrong
looks us ah that's where the dead body
was huh
they didn't get rid of that blood stain
[Music]
foreign
but i think that people will make you
disappointed
[Music]
uh
foreign
um
guess i don't have a mobile phone
okay
[Music]
staying alive staying alive
all i can do now is wait for word from
tati banana
what
um well everybody you're too fast
huh
such success you're planning to just
walk past without a word
you don't even have a partner to dance
you shouldn't be dancing once alone no
no that's against the waltz rules
oh god
what is that
you look like a
kappa with that suit with that smile
with that hair
kappa daniqua it's kappa
he's a kappa
shank down what
ah a mute or something blondie if you
don't want to get hurt let's see some
cash already
ah if you insist just be sure you pick
it all up
[Music]
a weird guy
never seen so much dull in one place
damn
he had my hand on that one first keep
your grammy mid self mono
shut up move your legs
presents truly are restored lot
calls them
yakuza peasants
he he has the control he has a
controller in his hand
did you want some of my money as well i
mean i mean if you're asking me like
this of course
and i shall be on my merry way until
next time cheerio cheerios
you always wear wags of gas just to
clear the road like that oh but of
course what
at the point you cough up the money it's
no different from getting mugged
yeah but you do assert that you're just
the you're in control kind of and you
get them on their knees i feel like this
would be yeah the better way
you see
when you're not just wealthy but
obscenely rich physical capital is like
dust it just accumulates gets in the way
really that was loose change i won't
miss it
wow okay
impressive
on the other hand having my precious
time wasted by bass ruffians like them
as a serious loss if i can buy that time
back with coin why i'll pay as much as
it takes
buying time literally
wait is he going to teach me a skill
where i can get out of fights by
throwing money in the air
and save time by now
well he is teaching me a skill
apparently
truly have you never been out on the
stroll and felt the other pedestrian
wait can i not escape a battle normally
is there no option to normally escape
the battle
[Music]
no worry i'll make you finance you this
one time is especially if you need focus
only on enjoying the rush of fleeing
cash confetti
you can run away
normally you could you have to run here
ah once in a fight you can't play
well okay
uh
and now in exchange for money we could
press square while walking around the
city to take a handful of your money and
fling it into anyone near your bible
flock to crash
oh no wait so this is for outside of
battle
still not for inside the battle
try using it to attract the woman behind
you oh
cash machine
yes yes get on your knees
just pick up that money huh
a nervous reasonable is you will often
find your way completely blocked by
punks eager for a fight walking around
them simply isn't an option in these
situations distracting them with amount
of cash however is they literally leave
by the chance to fill them to fill their
pockets give it a try now save yourself
a headache i mean i don't mind fighting
at all if they're right in front of me
but okay
take it
take this
what a weird thing to do now simply
strap past them while they're busy
scrabbling over you didn't have to teach
me that
okay bye bye green dude
by
judiciously wasting money you can buy
your way out of the most unnecessary
conflicts keep it in mind the next time
you're in a hurry
okay
yeah it's like it's just a huge flex
oh it's really magnificent money
blasting for moon i completely forgot
you were merely another plumbing
no i have one look at mine look at my
millions
is that what being rich is like honestly
i can't say it feels very good to waste
it like that
perhaps but aren't the times where you
when you farm to the hurricane to be
immoral in the petty squabbles of the
underclass
time is money and it's an other buffoon
time is the far more precious resource
it's finished
it
no time is infinite bunny is spin it
i mean
we'll probably
does that make sense what are you saying
time is not really limited
until
the earth is sucked up by a black hole
for you oh i was more thinking about
time itself not specifically for one
human being
time itself will never stop time time
just goes on and on and on so
it's infinite
anyone probably thinking too deep about
this
[Music]
uh can someone arrest that taco dachi
for asking too many questions get them
out of here
time and day is 24 hours but that's just
because we decided something like that
to give it a system but
it's not like time really has
like a
you know
we decided a day is 24 hours we
we did that
anyway
probably thinking too deep about this
ah
very epitome of irish character it's
been my golden goose and now i dine on
diamond figure for gra
handful of fear despair if you're truly
a man of means you'll find your way from
there
you'll know it when you see the paradigm
is exclusively reserved for the upper
insurance of wealth and taste
well naturally that is my only source of
income i've collected the diverse
portfolio or should i say we put most of
our capital to work in a certain system
that gives rise to considerable profits
if you wish to hear more about that as
well drop by vincent you'll find me
there most of the time
okay
tata
just made of lines it's made of circles
that's why crony's clothes round
but they
what are you talking about are you
pulling that out of your ass
taxi banana may have you until tomorrow
but that doesn't mean everything will be
over then i should tuck away as much
cash as i can now so i'm ready for
whatever comes
okay
is there going to be a reason for me to
get a lot of money
where i'll need a lot of money
[Music]
it had to be like two hundred thousand
yen
that's like two thousand
dollars
one thousand eight hundred maybe your
family isn't that right what's going on
how dare you poke around my purse
[Music]
high school couple that was pretty wrong
i wouldn't really pay attention to that
to be honest but okay let's listen
okay
well what there's a taco duct in
they're [\h__\h] everywhere
who are you
nobody's special i wear your spat and
then like what i was hearing
we were really going out of there and
i'm sorry if we made you uncomfortable
that girl meena is my girlfriend but
she's been acting strange lately
all of a sudden she started turning me
down a lot we almost never go out on
dates anymore
sure if that was all i could understand
but she's also been throwing a lot of
money around lately we should probably
learn the same skill that i just learned
and she's just trying to get rid of you
and on the rare occasion that we do go
on a date she always wants to go buy
lingerie lingerie by the bathroom
[Music]
that's that's that that you don't want
her buying lingerie are you sure
i got suspicious and went through her
purse i found at least 21 10 000
thousand year notes in it
unless you mean it's from a very wealthy
family that sounds fishy
i worry that mean that john is selling
herself
but wouldn't that explain why she's
always loaded and buying new laundry
maybe she's maybe she has a side job
and saved some
good money a little while ago
doesn't necessarily mean we have to be
that
would you mind checking up on me now
please
none
if i had to see me not selling herself
it would scar me for life
okay
sure we'll check it out but it's
probably not going to be such a big deal
or maybe she's part of that telephone
club
i kind of want to know why a girl would
be carrying around that kind of cash
myself
san leo avenue okay
[Music]
don't worry
don't worry that much where were you
supposed to go there okay
the dance floor is calling me
did you guys enjoy speaking of dance
floor did you guys enjoy the dance
collab i gotta be honest like i saw a
lot of good feedback from you guys
seemed like everyone was like mostly
happy with it but i felt
like
because because i took it quite
seriously
i felt like i couldn't do much better
um
yeah it's kind of sad that we still
didn't really figure out the
the
um sync thing even though we tested it
out but i guess
yeah we we kind of
you know forgot to do it before the
stream properly but i think even if we
did it before the stream we still would
have had issues during this stream
because like even if we sync up the
audio then i guess my moves are not
synced for them or something like that i
don't know
uh i mean we need to think of a a
different thing no but we had like our
hands full before the stream i was i was
there like an hour before setting up
things and you guys don't even know
but at one point
um
before the
um when i was setting up my new
microphone and [\h__\h] and my vr i had to
restart my pc
and then
i couldn't turn it on anymore it would
actually not start properly anymore
and i was like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh no come on come on
i would restart it several times but it
would always stop uh at one specific
point in like loading up the computer
um
yeah
but but but i stayed calm and
eventually uh figured out the problem
it was because i connected the vr
goggles to the pc and then when starting
up the pc the pc was confused about you
know having the vr and the hdmi so free
free monitors and vr goggles
confused my pc so much it couldn't start
up properly
yeah almond was also like oh yeah it's
probably because
because you had that connected and then
it's like what the [\h__\h] is this
resolution or something like that um
yeah thank god thank god it was nothing
um bad or so nothing uh that couldn't be
solved
it was an easy fix yeah but i was i was
getting really nervous and at the same
time ina was having issues for much
longer than i had you know had issues
with her trackers
i had issues with my pc
and then and then once we got in there
were some good i had issues with her
fingers
uh we had to troubleshoot because
suddenly her hand movements didn't work
anymore so there were a lot of problems
before the stream that's um
that's why um
yeah
always especially for vr chat streams
always need an extra amount of time for
preparation
but but but but it all ended up being
fairly fine
fairly okay
and we just delayed 15 minutes
it's okay
um
ian chris
no
no no no no not me and curse
it's just
it's just um things like to go wrong all
the time
yeah but i i felt like um
i don't know during during the
collab i didn't feel like it was going
so well i was feeling like oh [\h__\h] after
this after the stream is done i'm gonna
read all these comments that are gonna
be like yo this was so boring
last time was much better
why was this one so much more boring
i don't know i was getting really
worried um
i think i
perceived it completely differently than
you guys did
yeah
weirdly enough
um but but but i did my best anyway
like for example
you know i i asked them to do all these
things like i wanted to do i wanted to
do the one the thing where we all put
our hands together i was thinking about
that before the stream i was like i need
to get them to do that and then we'll be
like hey hey oh
cause
i used to do that too
it's like a motivational
like as a group get get into
get into the spirit
you know and and then i wanted to do the
i got them to do the
dancing and the line thing
uh like one after another and i got them
to do the macarena
and i got them to do that stupid thing
with with the legs to make a star
yeah
i got them to do a lot of
things
that i had in mind
one thing that i forgot though
um but i guess that's not really quite
possible
in vr you gotta imagine it but one thing
that um
when i lived in japan i
i
uh me and my friends used to do this
before
but in order to give
uh someone courage to perform an action
[Laughter]
um my my japanese friends
they
taught me
i don't know if you guys do that in
other countries as well but i heard
about this the first time in japan
um but they taught me to
um
one one girl would like uh
literally with with an open hand with a
with a flat hand punch the other
person's back
really strongly
in order to i don't know give them like
motivation and courage it's just like
let's go you know
and you would do that to one another
flat hand punch we do that in america
you do
oh you're doing football oh yeah i can
imagine you would do that in football
yeah it's pretty strong
so my friend would be like yeah yeah
that can punch my back and i'm like
okay and then she's like you want to
have it too and i'm like oh i'm good
oh i guess i guess okay okay but not too
strong
yeah i hope i hope one day i hope one
day biff uh meet some person i can i can
do the thing with the aao and the punch
in the back uh before like a big stream
or something together
when we're in person i want to do that
together
yes a new weapon you like my new weapon
anyway that's a slap yeah no but no it
sounds more like a punch when you punch
someone's back
with your with your flat hand it's not
really it doesn't sound i feel like a
slap must make a slap sound it's more
like a punch
because it makes a really dull sound
like a push no not like a push
you're not pushing them you just
punch their back
on
is not so much a thing
hugging is so intimate in japan
i i i tried to hug my japanese friends
and and some of them would accept it
because they understood that i
come from a different place but usually
it was awkward and they didn't really
want to hug
but here in austria sometimes even
strangers give each other a hug the
first time they meet
um
anyway
mommy
that was another tangent
i did hug matsony but that was okay
because matsune she's like she's like
pretty open to that
but with the other
before whole life of the other
uh girls that i hung out with in japan
japanese girls they yeah you
they would be kind of like
reluctant
righteous ways to
money money money
a rich looking guy and the homeless guy
walking into a bar
oh
another couple
okay
what are we getting ourselves into
enjoy your stay
it's like a bunker
where does that door go
indeed where does it go
sorry pal that's not open to you yeah i
see that can you open it
what's in there
you think i'd come right up and say it
well once you say it's a paradise for
men
a place where dreams come true
yeah real life wonderland god interest
up
you just made me curious what do i have
to do to get in
i'm the decider actually i say who comes
in you want in you gotta win my approval
this place is a paradise for the wealthy
if you don't have the bread you can't
afford the dessert i have to say that
you've got enough cash
how much do you want to see
prove that to me and let you in you use
your nogging and figure it out
oh i know how
[Music]
i know how i know how i know how
i know
[Laughter]
what do you how you're doing have you
lost your mind uh i was showing your
style and my cash
mm-hmm
exactly
well i never thought i'd see a guy
literally toss money onto the pavement
you go to screw loose i like the cut of
your jib though how did you not even get
that that was cool
i can come in noise
easy
hey
cat japan cat fight club
how are they i mean okay i understand
that they would enjoy that but the way
that they're in the bag like
um
supporting it like almost as if they're
supporting a real sumo or wrestling
match or something like that
doesn't seem so realistic i don't know
is that how you would support this
whatever is going on there on on that
stage
i feel like they
they are
um
behaving
incorrectly
i feel like they would just
maybe
um
observe
while drooling maybe
uh do i have to read this
sexy little vixens
vikings
scrap it out in an arena filled with
beauty and ugliness and men bet big
wages on the winner that's what this
place is about
a piece for you guys an exciting chance
is to double the fun by making money
laying bets a pleasure palace for men i
call them and that's what it is
not exactly still not entirely refined
but who cares
wow
eh
oh you got you gave me money back
okay
hmm you mean the butt
butt uh butt ground pound
anime
it was a real joy to watch it floating
around so i scooped it all back up for
you use it to have fun in there pal good
luck okay
let's try to make some money how do you
judge this is there a correct way to
judge who's gonna win the round
[Music]
are there like stats
oh my god
i say the the the girl in the bikini is
currently looking like she has the upper
hand
it's rng
rock paper scissors
uh-huh
okay if it's just orangey that's kind of
tough why why didn't we leave
why he says he wants to sleep
no oh [\h__\h]
there's a different guy deciding who
gets in now
oh should i have saved oh well
somebody lost a lot of money here
holy [\h__\h] francisca
uh
how to play
well this one i'll read in the cat 5
tournaments eight contestants viva
beautiful victory place your bet on the
one you think will win the payout
depends on the odds and the wage and
amount there are two ways to bet bet on
the contestant you think will win the
tournament predict the winner of each
match measurement isn't that the same
thing in the second case there's a set
free set fee to participate
[Music]
okay
what do we have
[Music]
oh there are stats but you say it
doesn't matter
oh my god
[Music]
she said i'll give you a special lesson
because she's an english teacher
she's just chilling on the floor she's
not even motivated to fight
[Music]
okay
well uh
bet on a fighter to win
wait win the whole thing or win
one
like round
[Music]
this
is the first thing beside the whole
thing
yeah that's not even like 50 50.
i thought it was a 50 50 chance
it and you say the stats don't matter
she uh
she seems to have the highest stats out
of everyone though
you can stop after one run okay
[Music]
okay let's see
stats do matter but it is
orangy it's pure
rng
ain't nobody got time for saving
well if it's rng
[Music]
it's really rng
if it's orange and i'm just gonna i'm
just gonna pick the
one that's the cutest outfit i like i
like oday
okay
[Applause]
do i
fight are they fine
[Applause]
[Music]
take her down
two one
[Music]
i always lose that
i'm so young
i'll always lose that
we can't push that fast
[Applause]
why did i even not even
people coming into the stream now will
be like what the [\h__\h] is going on hey i
can't you can't i can't
no what the [\h__\h] is that rainbow attack
[Applause]
look
where did i have the choice of playing
paper rock scissors
eh
i saw i saw so many but i didn't
understand it
[\h__\h]
[Applause]
one more
ah
i thought you guys were just saying that
to like tell me how high like that is
like really just rng because rock paper
scissors
i thought you were just like
paraphrasing
okay
um
[Music]
um um this time betting on monogol
but how do i decide which one
which buttons were there there to place
are you ready for cat fights
[Applause]
d-pad
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
oh i only get to push x when i uh pick
the right
element
even
again
will she go for a fist one more time
will she do it again will she do it
again
no she won't come on no you won't no you
won't
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
yo
i didn't see that coming
[Applause]
yes
a very relatable reaction very
understandable
[Applause]
i think this is too sensitive i will
have to play this game off-screen
[Laughter]
okay i'll i'll continue though uh
5 800.
wait i got 5 800 from that
huh
i'm losing money
[Applause]
okay round two
[Music]
like a dead expression though
let's wait
[Applause]
oh no i won oh it's good it's good
i've seen that somewhere before
[Applause]
holy [\h__\h]
pressing the button against them is
pretty tough
holy [\h__\h]
step on her
yes
don't disappoint me don't disappoint me
or write a bad review for your airline
i'm the airline [\h__\h] for your school
[Applause]
[\h__\h]
yeah i'll stay with fish this time
yeah
dominating
[Applause]
[\h__\h]
but we have to give her some kind of
chance right
we can't go too easy on her
come on one more
[Applause]
[Music]
unbelievable
what
i pressed like a [\h__\h] million times
in one second
that's a [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Applause]
yes yes yes yes britney sure finished
her finish
[Applause]
i don't know
[Music]
[Applause]
go back to school girls do your [\h__\h]
homework
do your goddamn homework
oh
tough battle
and number one
are you ready no
oh
[Applause]
holy [\h__\h]
she's gonna kill me
[Music]
police oh i am the police
[Applause]
no i'm weaker than everything
[Music]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Applause]
i only have a chance of the scissors
please do paper please don't paper paper
please don't take it please
[Applause]
you didn't get every single
[Music]
hate this game
shut up
never coming again
i'm never coming again sorry about that
experience
i'm sorry too
at least we have nice visuals
[Music]
how would i know what they're least
likely to use it's rng
iron jesus
ah
just gotta pray more to r jesus
anyway
oh you saw mr shakedown i didn't see him
we're going to continue the story
i want to continue the story and then
see what happens with majima
walk past him oh yeah yeah
totally completely unfazed
do i look like a giver [\h__\h]
i wanted to put some money on the bottom
i need to get good man
why do i always miss it
i know i always miss that button i keep
on pressing it
and i literally wait for it i
anticipated okay not this time
there we go
is it because wait you it doesn't matter
if you're focused on the enemy or not
right
it doesn't matter it works both ways i
think
[Music]
okay well it works sometimes that's good
enough
english teacher versus flight attendant
yes it's an interesting combination
uh how's kid you're doing he's fine
i turned 20 today
happy birthday
[Music]
20 huh
happy birthday
hope you're having a wonderful day to
you today
congratulations
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
we're
[Music]
yeah it's fair to expect the family will
be looking for me and they if they find
me there's no getting around they will
come with guns blazing but i make sure
i'm ready now before things go down
anything left i should do before hitting
the sack
um i would say i'll call it a night what
do you guys think
[Music]
hungry
um
[Music]
foreign
he's not amused
oh
i'm scared mommy
i'll need to kill them
you're giving each other a very obvious
sign
very obvious shouldn't have maybe not
done that when everybody already left
who is covering you up
if i'm gonna look into the case while i
wait for tatiana to get in touch i
should stick to places with without a
lot of people around
okay
and even then i should be ready to run
into dojima's men at any moment
okay but do we have a goal
like where to go no
we're just
running
until where
i guess the money trick doesn't work on
them
where am i going it will lead me i don't
see anything leading me
like i still the men being in certain
corners will lead me
no way they didn't see me just now
okay oh
can i go
this way
that seems like a fairly oh no they are
there oh so those are normal people
these are these just men in black
boys
are these just men and blacks
okay
well then
yeah the white suit makes me stand out
so much like his trademark
i'm not very smart of him but okay
why are you guys so annoyed
[Music]
oh um
are they getting up again no they're
dead right
hey
man
i'll send you the bill from my doctor
all right
no [\h__\h] you oh yeah by the way yesterday
i went to get a
another blood test but
it was kind of
oh
oh you're making me really mad now
it was um not the best experience as you
have seen on my twitter probably
probably
um
it was kind of ridiculous actually
on i'm holding our one are we playing
elden ring again or what
don't tell me to hold something i'm
always holding you don't even know what
i'm doing
you don't even know
which way should we go
over this way
no no i guess we could go disco now
keep rolling stop rolling
yeah um
are we going for the narrow street
um
so this was the
wait i guess i can't tangent now
oh man you need to play minecraft or
ellen ring or something in order to
tangent properly
but at least i have so much
so much
stocked up by now i have like a stock of
tangents
for a while i was like worried that i
wouldn't be able to have anything to
m
no problem
get up
get up faster oh my knee oh my knees
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
um
is there an item here there's no item
here
let me let me go here
hey yo we let's go
oh there's a nice like a little bottle
there but okay we'll take this one again
what is that bottle
what is that
it's a tiny little bottle
oh [\h__\h] wait i want to try that no no no
no
[Music]
your dentist bill is gonna be a big one
i'm angry
look at me being very angry
when this
[Music]
oh i haven't done that in a while wait a
second holy [\h__\h]
wait what two minutes
uh
i don't know
what
[Music]
damn this [\h__\h] is expensive
here this one for example
oh i won't remember that or will i hmm
okay
investing in myself
and i am scared
[Music]
oh no we are fighting
okay within i need to kill him within
two minutes is that it
[\h__\h] i hope i can
[Music]
is there like an item i can pick
i got the up i could pick up the bikes
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
no no no no no no no uh
let's go
okay
you annoy me
[Music]
what happens if i run out of time
uh
[Music]
oh don't be a little [\h__\h]
there's more people while i'm still
[Music]
ah
i am holding it
you have no idea
[Music]
he's feeling like eleanor ring now with
those
comments
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] hell
oh [\h__\h] you
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] yeah
um
oh is the timer going the diver's gone
does have to end this or what
i'm so mad
get up
[Music]
30 seconds
pick it up pick it up and
pick that [\h__\h] up on the ground
why are you so stupid
huh
[Music]
so much right now i'm close to rage quit
after this
[Music]
didn't someone say right before this
part started someone in the chat was
like oh you're gonna like this next part
were you seriously saying that
well why are you sarcastic i think that
was the serious comment
why it's literally down there next to
you how are you so stupid you had it in
your hands you had in there
what's going on why are so many
[Music]
is now with this one
because at least within being so fast it
doesn't make me [\h__\h] rage
no no they didn't mean to cat butt it
was right before this
at least we have no time limit anymore
hmm
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h]
i'm hungry
i'm hungry let me
let me eat your eyeballs after frying
them in the fryer
come here
for you you got a problem it's a present
i'm santa claus take it
be [\h__\h] thankful where's my milk or
my cookies
i'm even fine if it's just cookies
welcome back to hell it's never [\h__\h]
ending
it's never [\h__\h] ending
oh wait
wait
no no
finally
[Music]
eat the [\h__\h] pavement
eat it
and
[Music]
sure reasonable that's reasonable
once again i'm too stupid to pick up
anything
sledgehammer versus this triangle head
for the ground it's the hat for the
ground yes that's what it is
always happened
well at least no time limit again let me
get let me get out of there please
what you get that's what you get
[\h__\h] that basket
[Music]
what is that on the ground here
didn't see that one coming huh
huh
[Music]
they think this is fair
no wait oh wait no time limit coco coco
[Music]
[Applause]
why is he so clumsy
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] drop cake guys
[Music]
can you [\h__\h] look to the front i'm so
mad
[Music]
not fair not fair not fair
no
that item immediately immediately
[\h__\h] off
oh my god
wait let me get out of here
[Music]
so done i'm so sad with this
are they like never ending like how are
they still all here
[Music]
yes
hello
hey
[Music]
i know
[\h__\h]
[Music]
hmm
ah
[Music]
oh
with my
bare hands
i'm gonna say hi to my cats for a moment
hmm
c
hey
underground
i guess
i don't have any options um
um
oh
thank you
[Music]
all right are we gonna see some
um
ladies
i'm going through
are we going for the strip club
no we aren't
[Music]
wonderful
another thing to add to our list to our
to-do list
oh that was a trap
that was a trap
she's being paid
by the miako
[Music]
oh nice scene
why are you down here with your bikes
there's water
my mother
[Music]
big entry doesn't he
what a [\h__\h] idiot
because it's funny to you
oh no
ah
uh
yummy
what style what style should i find him
with
okay
you're ruining your leather shoes man
[Music]
um
to me
[Music]
i didn't say if i died this battle
i can repeat it though no
oh wait
oh [\h__\h]
i didn't even get a heel i mean okay i'm
good but i didn't even get a heel
i'll be fine
yes you can restart okay
[Music]
oh man
alan ring let's go
alvin ring style
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] but he gets up so fast
oh is it
going he wouldn't get up so fast
there we go
soccer
welcome to the world wine championship
in soccer
where austria is never gonna be part of
the lineup never
[Music]
i mean it's fairly easy to fight but i
guess it's gonna take a while
[Music]
nonetheless
because it has a lot of hp
damn wait
look at his lucky guy's penis is gonna
take an hour to find him
i don't understand the bar in this game
sometimes one bar left
did we already get rid of one because it
looks like we got rid of nothing
oh okay okay oh that's okay then we're
good then okay
remember that was like
[Music]
you're no match for me
all your underlings were like more
bothering than you are at least this is
a one-on-one fight though i'll respect
you for that i'll respect you for that
he always falls so far behind when i
push him down
[Music]
even though i was looking the opposite
direction he still got that loop
okay
[Music]
however he is using a weapon so
that's not so cool
he's really mad does that wear off after
some time or is this just his current
state until the end
oh man
be careful be careful
[Music]
this is phase two
i know how to log on i'm constantly
logging on
[Music]
yo he got the upper hand now holy [\h__\h]
holy sh
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
i feel like i'm fighting like tekken i'm
playing tekken right now
[Music]
foreign
running out of healing items
[Music]
oh we're finally fine it's fine we're
finally
i was like oh he must be there somewhere
but i didn't have time to change the
camera
almost there almost there almost there
almost there almost there i went there
stop it
[Music]
[\h__\h]
don't worry kirill doesn't kill people
even though his name is like a japanese
way of saying kill you
ever thought about that
hmm
let's take that as our
uh award
oh
bunk him bunk him he's been a bad bad
boy
are we letting gemma do it instead
that joke was so bad oh come on
yeah probably
[Music]
um
foreign
hmm
well maybe he'll end up being nice
maybe he'll change his mind after this
maybe he's like inspired and fascinated
by how cool i am we're not killing him
maybe we won't regret it
i mean there must be a reason why you
guys like him so much so
i i was about to say too the light suit
is ruined but it looks still looks okay
it was fine i guess
i mean
it was a rainy day or something
[Music]
[Applause]
majima majima
[Music]
this is a funny situation
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
anyway
um
foreign
[Music]
yes we don't even have country clubs in
my country people understand not really
i only know country clubs
um
[Music]
oh
yeah i know i know what that place is
plenty
um
[Music]
public relations
me
foreign
[Music]
um
hey
i like that
don't get yourself threatened like that
oh oh cuz that
he couldn't shoot him
no oh
if a cousin came back and shot i'mma
know something what the [\h__\h] why would
you
london
why
[Music]
then why would you have to kill me here
is it
if you have people outside waiting
anyway why would you do that dirty boy
[Music]
no way that i have to fight against her
no way
foreign
[Music]
um
probably doesn't even have bullets left
in his gun
there's no one outside dude there's no
one
you i mean normal people
there are normal people
i told that was a bluff
girl though what the [\h__\h]
why
he just wanted to scare me he could have
used that shot on me
i guess he didn't want to kill me
because he was still hoping that his
threat would work
[Music]
maybe
um
[Applause]
[Music]
is that why i should have gone to my
business one more time to pick up the
money because i won't be able to go back
for a while oh well oh well
come on don't read check
is someone going to die
i think i saw a spoiler before
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
are we in um now
reminds me of handmaid's tale
you're trying to kill me
buddy
what creeping me out right now nishiki
yeah okay
uh you wouldn't betray me
your brothers
now he wouldn't do that
what no fire um
yeah this really feels like something's
gonna happen
oh
how do i not end up being a dead one in
this situation
foreign
[Music]
um
that's kind of yonder though
[Music]
foreign sorry
god
[Music]
i thought he would end up killing
himself but
[Music]
what
oh he missed
oh i thought someone shot him from
behind
[Music]
as a team
foreign
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
um
give me
[Applause]
[Music]
the car
dude
where's his car
uh
but you know what that means we'll see
in the cliffhanger continuation now
which is what i was excited about
let's go
i thought i thought they would just go
to osaka and then meet majima i'm like
continuous like
i'm like always waiting
for the moment
where those two characters will end up
meeting
well at least this didn't end as badly
as i thought it would
i thought one of them would die
probably in nishiki because kiryu has a
couple games afterwards so
he's got some places to be in
yo much more
so temporary no your
foreign
hey
so we're just gonna look at the
beginning of this
and then end it
chapter seven a dark escape
the torii has decided
[Music]
okay
um
is her
[Music]
huh
you really don't know
it was blushing because i was happy to
see monty mom
um
[Music]
he has to protect it
he's so cute
such a softy
um
[Music]
tell us what's up
um
[Music]
is
um
[Music]
hmm
ah
no it's not like that the [\h__\h]
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
interesting well of course it couldn't
hurt the girl
that was not a cliffhanger it was
obvious obvious outcome
anyway i need a safe point or i guess
it's safe before the cutscene but i
wanted to save after the cutscene
i see one over there
excuse me sir i just wanna save
please
okay okay i think we're good
nine million yeah but no um
previously i was told i don't really
have a chance
i mean could do
after saving
i guess but no
now we're good we good not today not
today
all right we're going to read super
chats now i need to need to read super
chat um
uh besides that one [\h__\h] stupid fight
that one time i have fun today besides
that that yeah besides that area
hope you guys had fun too
you guys
yeah um tomorrow i'll be doing a watch
along um
for the day one of the concerts so feel
free to watch it together with me so far
it looks like i'm the only one doing it
still
um
and uh
i'll also be
um
in one program point on in the in the
expo
tomorrow only tomorrow um
only oh
oh well okay
well i'll be
also trying to maybe translate a little
bit for you guys
but ah
i wanna i want to experience that moment
together when we see the day one en
girls on stage oh i wanna experience
that of you guys so yeah
that'll be nice
um
i gotta get up early for that so let's
try to get through the super chats
somewhat quickly and sorry i still
couldn't
uh
tangent much maybe i'll even do a
chitchat stream
but i feel like
i wanna i don't wanna waste my tangents
on a chitchat stream i wanna use my
tangents for long-ass streams where i
don't have anything to talk about maybe
i should do yeah minecraft or else in
the ring next week
um
yeah
yeah anyway i should stop exactly
uh we're gonna go to my office
ah [\h__\h] yeah i [\h__\h] everything up here
i don't know why sometimes when i when i
uh
when i change something on a different
screen then everything's [\h__\h] up on
the other end
because it's kind of like connected like
why why
why why why
everything looks
fine here
this is it
has it
and there was one layer on top of it
that
[\h__\h] everything up
okay oh i'm being
oh so big
wonderful
yeah
oh my birthday i don't know i know what
i did um but anyway let me close the
game
and then with your song
btm
bgm btm
btm btm
what do i want to listen to
i want to listen to something calm
right i don't know about you guys but i
feel
i feel like i need to listen to
something calm
[Music]
a good night yes yes get some sleep
before the concert
[Music]
oh i like this it's not very calm
but i like it
it's fresh
you do be fresh
[Music]
okay
okay i need to reach the budget from
a last time
[Music]
the dance stream yeah
uh let me turn off the super chats now
[Music]
that's so cute
sounds like something out of little
mermaid
oh i don't even remem i don't even
remember that one
but yes i guess so
i could see that
um
[Music]
well done today despite the frustration
you have
thank you
yeah that really got to me i haven't
been this angry at a game in the long
time like that
i was i was just
i don't even think that might have been
the angriest i've ever been at the game
and really
got my grind schooling is that how you
say it it was worse than mario sunshine
at that point i was shaking yeah
i was shaking with anger holy [\h__\h] but
my cat gave me an instant heal like the
moment i touched her
the moment i looked at her it was like
everything was nice and beautiful again
grinds my gears what did i say
what did i say
[Music]
[Laughter]
there were bad
moments before in other games but this
felt like
the worst it has ever been
even though even though i feel like
other games may have been more difficult
but this one really like it just didn't
end and it was stupid just stupid
oh i said you got my grinds going does
that exist though it have a different
meaning
it sounds like sounds like um like i'm
saying that you turned me on or
something new mario kart maps are oh
yeah let's play mario kart next week
then
let's do it let's get to know the new
maps
that sounds like fun
uh all right
thumbnail
i have so many discord dms but i'm not
gonna look at it now
[Music]
when will they turn them on is there any
is that it why is there any news on when
what
i pretend i do not see see what
is there something on the screen that
there shouldn't be
everything looks fine to me
after the 21st
under the 21st
okay wait the 21st okay that's soon
that's soon that's in a couple days
love the dance stream so much thank you
i
i'm glad people liked it i
um
one thing i have to say
um even though i was 100 happy with how
that stream went down i feel like uh
always me
i feel like
uh in the past few months
with like snack box streams and crafting
streams and cooking streams and vr
streams now
i feel like i found something
to do
um to
capitalize on
that
not many or like barely anyone else does
in at least in whole live english like i
don't know about anyone who does these
kind of crafting streams
really and snack books is also something
original
so
i gotta say i'm proud of my
content recently and um
you know how people
have this who don't watch me much
i i guess it's true anyway but uh people
have this impression that i always
stream so long and i stream so many rpg
games that are hard to like join midway
through and all that so for me those
streams um like the snack box streams
and the cooking streams and all that the
hand cam streams
um are my way of giving you like um the
option to
get to know me um if you if like i'm
sure that there's a lot of people out
there who didn't want to give me a
chance in the beginning
um either because they didn't like the
way i sound or the way i look or they
didn't like
the way i
behaved at the beginning or they didn't
just didn't like the games that i played
in the beginning um but but but with the
um and i understand i did play a lot of
long games then
and uh they were maybe
difficult to join into although you
should have just given it a chance
anyway but still anyway so for those
people i feel like
i want them to give those streams a try
the the ones
with the hand cam for example or the
dancing streams and all that
so
since those are short relatively short
and you don't need to know any
previous story
any context or anything you can join
anytime i think
so
yeah
i think i think it shows well
what kfp is about and represents me well
too
so i hope it can reach a lot of people
i mean
it's
probably not gonna be as effective as i
am i wish it would be but
um it's a start and hopefully eventually
a lot of people are gonna realize oh
kiwawa
is doing some interesting stuff there
man
she's working hard
putting out content that's different
from others like
i i think i i managed to
[Music]
make a little bit of a category for
myself
um
with streams that are different from
what the others do
yeah
i think it's important to find something
um that not everybody else does because
because everybody
plays games everybody does kadoka
streams and all that
we all do that
you gotta find something to stand out
with and i mean i have whole talk but
whole talk is mostly about
the guest and not about me
so
that doesn't quite work that well in
promoting myself
the kiwatiguri
[Music]
thanks for making the most fun seven
months of my life oh
thank you
you can't remember when i realized i
want you interacting with chat so you
were my first membership thank you
you need content yeah
[Music]
i've been having fun with
the streams i've been doing
and um as i said i'm proud of my
content ideas i do what i can within the
limits of
of my skills and all that like
i feel like if i had for example like
amis skills i would i would also
be able to do so so so much more but
with with what i am able to do now
i'm doing my best with my abilities
i'm glad you guys are here for that to
enjoy that
[Music]
and constraints are very unique kiwa
content they're all so much fun thank
you i i think so too i mean i always get
very nervous during them and i was going
to be kind of careful um
but
i think they're
one unique way of um
you know getting myself out there
[Music]
and putting out content
um
so i hope more people can enjoy it
[Music]
been here since october 2020 wow so long
thank you
i'm kind of hungry man
i don't think i can read all of the
super chats today
i gotta sleep somewhat early
and
still
[Music]
i think it's rad and you're always
thinking of new content but you should
know you've been making really really
good streams thank you
[Music]
thank you i'm glad you think so as a
content creator
especially
after
a certain amount of time after doing it
like every [\h__\h] day for over a year
it's like
uh
sometimes sometimes there may be moments
where you don't know like have you have
i reached
like a
a wall
that i can't overcome can i not come up
with anything new it's like a like a um
creative block
sometimes
sometimes just ideas don't come as
easily anymore
as they used to and
even i sometimes feel like
huh i'm out of ideas man
but thankfully
i still have i still have my
handcam streams that i can
work with and make something interesting
out of
[Music]
but it's tough as a content creator
that's so active you always got to think
of so many
ideas so many
yeah
concepts like as a
as a video creator
who maybe puts out a video like once a
week or so the pace is just not that
fast i mean they work hard by by making
the quality of those videos really
really really
high but
as a streamer who streams every [\h__\h]
day you gotta be able
to make to keep an audience interested
enough to watch you every day
that is quite the challenge to make
someone feel like they want to see you
every day
no matter what
[Music]
it's pretty difficult
anyway
yeah
yeah of course there's people out there
who do the same thing every day and and
still have
tons of people watching them
that is true
but not everyone is that lucky i feel
like once you reach a certain amount of
viewers you
you just have this fan base engraved
that's gonna watch you no matter
what you're doing you have to save
pillow i mean i have a certain amount of
a safe pillow as well i guess like a
certain amount of people who will watch
me no matter what but that's just still
still a small amount
but like those twitch streamers who get
thousands and thousands and thousands
and thousands of viewers
just
by sitting there and watching a few
videos and interacting with the chat a
little bit
they they must have a really really
really great personality
and have
brought uh created a lot of great
content until that point to be able to
now just be themselves without trying
too hard man
no i mean really great personality
[Music]
she's a cute phoenix oh thank you
anyway
blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah
[Music]
oh this music is so good
uh let's start pepsi dancing doug joseph
i stick my hips out but i can't eat 40
feet in the air like you teacher
what am i doing wrong oh wait
wait have you called me or someone else
called me teach y'all again and i was
wondering like why tea
but now again it comes from teacher not
from tea
ah
it took me a while to understand
oh the realization
thank you what are you doing wrong
you're not believing in yourself enough
yet
yeah
you need to believe
and to believe you can fly you need to
believe you can touch the sky
hey
mr vic thank you soon jason dreams down
because you know rev re pro
[Music]
about that um
um
[Music]
did you guys
get document tickets anyone who wanted
to maybe go
is that anyone here who got dokami
tickets for this year
saturday is
and full weekend is sold out
yes i did really
oh there are some people
there are some people
[Music]
no particular reason why i'm asking
uh
[Music]
what i remember last year
i was like
tickets sold out before i was announced
[Music]
i will
i will demand that that never happens
again
if if
if we are in a situation like that again
anyway let's continue open the mic thank
you for the pinky checking in before i
go to sleep here while the engineering
degree i'm pursuing is getting real
though tough i need to fix my sleep
cycle oh that's understandable
[Music]
when watch the vlog oh my new lecture is
a professor and should i try some pickup
lines in german no
no don't don't try to flirt with your
lecturer don't do that
[Music]
don't do that no no no no no
wait do you mean me
no you don't you mean you're real
lecturer no no no don't try to pick them
up in german they i mean they probably
wouldn't even understand
no they don't have weekend tickets
anymore
but i heard that
i mean it's not it's not um
[Music]
finite
because
uh
they might open it up again
like in the twitch i was watching that
twitch stream
that they did to follow up
um
yeah it's not final it may not be final
there's still a chance that there will
be more tickets
well
not that there's any reason
i just want to go there privately you
know
[Music]
i i like i
i want to go to dukami like you know
back in the days i went to dokomi like a
million times
just i just want to go there privately
my friends i also want to go there i
think
well no one will get a ticket but to be
honest though
that's okay because
me and my friends never
[Music]
never got tickets
there's so many people who don't get
tickets and just chill in the park
um
[Music]
you can do that yeah
there's like a huge park um like
actually it's like this was a lot of
conventions in germany and austria
a lot of people just is it not normal
for you guys i guess because you guys um
with your venues it often doesn't really
work like that huh
but here
most venues have like a big park or
garden or something
attached to it so a lot of people will
just not buy a ticket and just chill
outside
and hang with people outside and maybe
borrow a ticket from some friend who has
a ticket every once in a while to just
go inside to do an idle meeting and
maybe buy some food and then go outside
again yeah
often people would just
a group of six people would share one
ticket or so
in conventions where that works the most
convention networks
i think nowadays uh like last year for
dokomi they had the name on the ticket
but it wasn't always like that it's not
like that for every
convention
borrowing a ticket yeah
most do not allow the games come yeah it
depends on the convention
it depends on the convention i've never
been to gamescom there's this huge
games convention in germany
um
but i always hear that it's like so
[\h__\h] crowded that is like kind of
terrible to be in
uh even for content creators
or performers or whatever but also as a
guest
so it's not really not really a
comfortable convention to be in
can't be raising comic head
uh i think from like the density i mean
i've never been there but from what i've
heard i would assume that the density of
people is like pretty close
but
comic cat is maybe more
organized i don't know
[Music]
it is terrible unless you go on a trade
day about more than 250 thousand
visitors go there
yeah okay but i don't know how big the
venue is i can't really
imagine
tanaka i heard about that
anyway
the gamer
[Music]
thank you for the heart
thank you for the support
it's so kind of you
thank you no text with it just empty
thank you very much i appreciate it hope
you enjoyed the dance collab and maybe
vibes together with us dance together
with us
disco disco party party
let's say you can't walk into the
nintendo you're all standing against
each other
ah
[Music]
let me try to remember call me cat i
mean call me kid
[Music]
there's just so many halls for comic
cats that
there's always a flow like
in some areas it gets a little bit more
crowded than in others
but
yeah i guess you um like outside getting
inside from outside is tough
waiting line
hours and hours and hours
waiting
um but once you're in i guess it's not
that bad anymore
but i
i always kind of
enjoyed comic cat in a different way
than the usual the normal
the standard
uh consumer
did i guess so my my experience is a bit
different from others i think
daisy duncan pretties rock tankish in
boss three four five dangerous and
[Music]
there's no thinking in huawei mode ah
true yeah
true
there is dan j p r s n s r duncan duck
attack thank you for the ransom thank
you soon
thank you all the hype for the concert
is making some of the kfc staff and
customers
spontaneously combust
what does that mean as per company
regulations we're gathering the remains
and preparing oh
oh like compost
you're like just falling apart
we're gathering the remains and
preparing them as the oh my god hi pot
chicken
i smell smoke people
[Music]
oh you just catch fire no
oh didn't i did i not tell you what to
do in that situation i told you about
how little kiwawa used to do it when she
couldn't control her fire just put your
head in the toilet bowl
just put your hand in the toilet bowl
when you're on fire
ah remember that i told you before two
times at least i told you that story two
times
[Music]
the toilet bowl
yes
cool your head off a little bit
no panic just call
thank your dog attack
it's understandable though that you're
so excited i'm excited too it's kind of
surreal though
like i had i had some moments today
uh and that maybe last night yeah where
i felt like excited but at the same time
it feels surreal
so real
i think the whole virtual aspect makes
it feel surreal
um
yeah
not being
in
japan uh makes it feel surreal
but uh who knows how i will feel
tomorrow
when watching day one
i can't
[Music]
are you guys gonna watch day two
live or are you guys gonna watch for the
members only watch along with me
i think both is fine you can you can
watch it twice if you want
both
both both
live
i mean i guess yeah when you say life
you mean both right you're gonna watch
it with me too both vofo okay so you
don't wanna you don't wanna wait huh
you don't want um the members only to be
your first experience i see i see okay
i'll kill you
understandable understandable
can't wait no i'm not impossible
[Music]
you understand the book
we want the live experience hell yeah
hell yeah the hype the hype the hype the
hype
[Music]
oh but you guys could watch day two with
ollie together the live one unless you
want to watch uh
watch it alone once and then enjoy it
with me i mean that makes sense too
could enjoy it alone but if you feel
like watching someone else
i recommend watching it with ollie on
day two
[Music]
need to cry alone first understand a
little understandable do you still want
us to record our live reactions eh i
mean um just from my performance yes
kind of yes but you don't know when it's
gonna happen so you gotta be on standby
it i think it will be interesting to see
but
maybe it will make you feel awkward
about reacting i don't know
if you feel awkward about it don't do it
but if you i don't know if you feel like
being a reacting uh reacting youtuber
then go for it
too shy to do that that's okay
i get it
um
i just wanna i just wanna see the pen
lights the audience oh you know what
you know what
i might i might watch all these vlogs
afterwards
to see how her chat reacted to my
performance
i usually see some reactions some live
reactions
while i'm dancing i won't have time to
look at the chat yo
while i'm performing
anyway
continually not applicable young kissing
mr big thank you
daisy thank you for the pinky
there's no purple heart
what do you mean you're literally typing
a purple heart in there and into the
super chat
[Music]
you mean there's no purple
super chat color
ah
a little pink yeah i think it's pretty
close
you could send a pink and a blue one
immediately afterwards and then it would
mix into a purple milk
go into this dancing jacob 47
buy another player duncan but that would
probably be too big brain for a chicken
[Music]
oh that reminds me wait it cool freaking
you sound very excited
i'm excited i'm so excited
[Music]
that's you that's your jesus
thank you
please look forward to the concert
um uh i was about to stay because of
potions or whatever because of alchemy i
watched
that
playstation state of play
uh with the harry potter game
and i gotta say
it looks it looks like a lot of fun
looks really cool
hogwarts yeah
it looks like they put so much work into
it
um
the flying
like the graphics when you're flying
look really nice
[Music]
and uh
yeah everything looks really cool i
don't think i would stream it um
but
yeah
looks like a great game
um
for the people who don't know it's a
harry potter game but it plays like a
long time before harry potter so
there are no
no characters no really except for some
a ghost or so i think uh but usually
mostly there are no characters from the
actual harry potter timeline there
but still um not really interested in
the series i wouldn't call myself a
harry potter fan at all either like i
haven't read the books i've watched the
movies but
once only
and i thought they were cool but i
wouldn't call myself a fan but but that
game looked really really great you
should at least watch the the footage of
it
because pretty impressive
[Music]
i i remember um
it reminds me of long long long long
long long long ago when i was a child
and i was getting into pc games
one game i played was i think some kind
of lego harry potter
uh
and that was the best thing ever
that was so cool i mean i never really
got far
at all but
i kept on restarting the game
from the beginning
yes
that was fun
[Music]
all right lego games good stuff good
stuff
[Music]
money
bionicle heroes
bionicle heroes that sounds familiar to
me bionicle heroes
that sounds really
familiar but no i didn't i don't think i
played that no
i played a lot of these kind of old
games
but
no
no probably didn't
probably didn't but i heard of it
[Music]
but
yes
thank you for the pinky hello kiana
sadly i won't be able to watch you and
the girls in the big concert for your 3d
d models reveal maybe next month but i'm
really glad you're giving us this
amazing 3d collab with myth we've got a
helmet thank you yes you're welcome
you're welcome yeah um
it's a nice nice opportunity to get to
get together before the concert once
yeah yeah i was also kind of thinking of
asking the girls that they want to do
like uh
after
um like
looking back on the concert after talk
collab
if we wouldn't have done one beforehand
before
um
yeah i decided to
not ask after all
because you already got a collab before
[Music]
i don't
know
let's see how i feel
after the concert
if we all feel super hyped and wow
like emotional afterwards and maybe
maybe we'll do a spontaneous spontaneous
one
how about i think
i'm gonna
amazing around this [\h__\h]
i'm busy again
[Music]
you don't know
i'm nervous i'm sweating
i think we're all
supposed that she's sweating a lot
oh that miss terry is sweet
yeah yeah mysterious isn't it she
dropped her phone do you mean that
it was cryptic yeah what does it mean
what does that mean
[Music]
um i wonder when she means she posts oh
you shouldn't tell me about that that's
members only knowledge that she's
sweating
[Music]
i shouldn't even know that her body is
capable
to sweat
now you shouldn't tell me
that's confidential sweat
confidential gamer sweat
[Music]
anyway uh thank you dinosaur i hope you
can watch it afterwards i hope you do
[Music]
um but i'm not sure the the vaude
doesn't it have a like a deadline again
is it
is the like the spawn bloods are they
like one month or how long were they
available
thank
20th of april april okay well then the
other side don't miss it okay
jesus alberto duncation twitching boost
dancing for the raid super chat thank
you
it says cali oh wait you're also doing
colors for everyone ah
yeah yeah yeah yeah thank you it looks
like
like a rainbow
thank you very much twitching blues love
for the beautiful rainbow each each one
got uh one of our names in it i see i
see i see what you did there
thank you
[Music]
hope you had fun watching a collab
i hope you also know the choreography by
heart now um i expect you chimpkins to
bust a move as well
[Music]
aurora rainbow dankester neo matrix
happy birthday
related but still
leo
news reborn
jake 33
yes sir this time it was hot out of you
guys i gave the girls some other choices
uh i gave them the choice of for example
merang koriku
and
what else did i say we could do
i also offered
[Music]
where is it i am i offered uh
uh
perfect sans
too
i wanna i wanna teach that someone to
someone one day
the one that goes like
[Music]
because i think the choreography is a
fairly easy and it's a fun song
it would be perfect wouldn't it
yeah
it's john's birthday
today
[Music]
what's up
raina said she wanted to join your dance
school ah
if she has some way of using your chant
i would love to do something with her
good ah yeah i'm sure good i would love
dancing that song but everyone shows how
to you guys this time which i think is
good for all of us together it was it
was a tough one to teach man
i
kept on forgetting some
moves um i practiced before the stream
and i was like fine whenever i would
dance the whole song
but i think i was too nervous i was
really nervous
um
and that made me forget the moves when i
was teaching it
slowly
yeah
[Music]
that's why i feel so bad about it you
know
oh well
[Music]
but at least this time i i tried to
improve it from last time
by like
um separating the parts
i prepared all that
beforehand
made videos for each each one
to upload on youtube oh i need to delete
those i just remembered
there there are they are um um uh
they're not public they're just so we
can put them into the player in the vr
chat thingy this needs to be a youtube
video that's why
yeah
yeah i think it made it
um
the whole flow
was better thanks to that but i was a
[\h__\h] teacher anyway
anyway yeah
next angular's 405 danger and i remember
when this dance was so popular that
there were people all over the world
doing it yeah there was even a video
of inmates at a women's prison somewhere
in indonesia what
[Music]
what
damn
duke from distance thank you thank you
so happy to see you collabing like this
ahmed and the amazing team have done
such an incredible job with all the
reaction stuff yes they help it's so
much fun to see attention in dance
teacher mode yay
yes
um
it kind of gave me another purpose gotta
say it made me pretty happy to be able
to teach
someone something even though um
uh like you know
just like when i teach people german
it's like i'm not a teacher so there's
other people who can do it better
obviously who do it as a profession
but but within myth
i'm happy that um this can be one of my
things i'm gonna be like this is my
thing
um
[Music]
still a great teacher
oh thank you
thank you
if i wasn't so nervous i would have done
better yeah
but you know having all five girls on my
channel
in vr i knew that there would be a lot
of people watching and judging and makes
me so nervous i was less nervous when it
was just america
i felt some pressure there
yeah
it's okay though it was fun
and so many great screenshots and uh
gift shifts gift shifts
again and videos yeah
and and this time no glitching yeah
although no body glitching but i i
this is one more thing that made it
difficult for me i kept on
well i think there was like a buckle
contact what's the english road
i think some some somehow my vr headset
cable
was loose somewhere because
i kept on
um you guys didn't see that because i
was streaming the desktop
to obs
um so you didn't see my point of view
but
yeah so often
just for like a millimeter millisecond
yeah it was like flickering but like it
wouldn't turn black it would just it
would turn to that like default screen
or something
but just really really really really
shortly just for like
0.5
milliseconds or so
and every every time that happened it
would stop the the audio in my vr set
headphones as well so i wouldn't hear
the music or wouldn't hear the girls and
it happened when i moved a lot so
sometimes not even when i moved much but
during dancing was pretty tough and i
tried to not make it so noticeable but
it happened the whole time
but i didn't want to like stop there and
try to fix it because you got to keep
the party going
and yeah it was still something that i
could i guess endure
no
it wasn't like this last time my cables
were properly connected but for some
reason
they were
it was really unstable
[Music]
yeah
that made me feel dizzy while dancing
it was so uh i [\h__\h] hate those we are
goggles they make me so dizzy like
there's there's like
[Music]
if i don't have them like
in a very very very specific
very specific position
then the whole view is [\h__\h] up you
maybe you guys know what i mean
[Music]
but i feel like with my vive pro
um
it really needs to sit
in one really specific perfect way if it
just
moves slightly
then
the view is blurry and it makes me feel
sick too
[Music]
but then i try to adjust it and it's
really hard to adjust it back to the
perfect state
[Music]
i don't know
yeah the focus is so precise
but when you're dancing obviously it
will like move a little bit
so you gotta you gotta count that as
well
so i'm dancing and first of all it keeps
on getting blurry and it also keeps on
glitching out because
the screen is disappearing and the sound
is disappearing for me
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's [\h__\h]
it's like i have a i had a lot of
debuffs on
[Music]
like a poison debuff and a drowsiness
debuff
[Music]
a paralyzation
so many limiters man take them off
[Music]
oh man
other things were fixed but other things
were worse again i don't know nothing
can ever be perfect apparently
is that too much to ask
[Music]
just got here oh i played the five hours
today i
think um
tomber 44 gun question for the pinky one
of the best dreams to have on my
birthday thanks kayla let's go live oh
another birthday congratulations
[Music]
that was indeed a great way to celebrate
it mmm you're welcome and thank you for
supporting all of us thank you soon
derek sito dan kashim thank you our
ronin danges
thank you for the pinky good i saw that
hit that nae nae on the chin
did she nae nae
i i don't remember that
thanks for the pinky shin
the very beginning of it has the quick
start of you
and but then it's supposed to have oh
you were trying to
someone's boxing the choreo and the
super chats you know what
[Music]
that is helpful i guess in in a
different um dimension because
when when i do vr chat the um i the
chance that i will see your super chat
is
so low
i think that person just wanted to flex
the fact that they know the choreography
choreography backseating
man
[Music]
damn i did not see that one coming
the chance that in that very moment when
i needed i would see a super chat is
little to none no it's less than zero
ah that's a new one yeah
cocoon thank you russell dingles
you know i tried to read that super chat
even though it was not a pinky or red
one i just tried to read it because i
wanted to read more
other super chats in between and then i
get stuff like this
anyway russell dingles is sending a
pinky this brings back memories of
learning choreography for theater in
high school and college can't wait to
see your moves at the festival bus thank
you
i'm gonna assume you weren't learning
anime dances in
a theater
i'm gonna assume
but that sounds cool i wasn't there uh
class 2 in junior high but
i think
we mostly just did like
if i remember correctly we mostly just
did like um
the
uh
like a what's the word [\h__\h]
a religious play
uh you know the one with um
the three kings we did that for that
holiday
the three kings who bring some [\h__\h] for
the jesus
baby some presents some offerings
yeah
the nativity scene oh
yeah we did that
pretty often that i was always part of
it
that's the only play i remember that we
were doing i'm sure we did other plays
too
but this is the only one i remember
um
and we also
yeah in crafting class
man that really shows me how much the
school pushed religion on us but in
crafting class we put together
um
you know the the place
with the baby in the crib
and the the hay
and the the
the wooden house and [\h__\h] uh
yeah
yeah the man girl whatever that is you
guys know all the words you guys know
all the words the stable
[Music]
the bear and the hay
that was fun to craft though
it ended up always looking really cute
because we were using like i think we
like glued
like moss and stuff onto it yeah yeah
yeah that is cute
[Music]
then i brought it home i think proudly
my mom probably said yeah that's good
nice good job kiwamo
but i don't give a [\h__\h] about the
religion
that's probably what she was thinking
but good job kiwawa looks beautiful
i just i just don't care for the meaning
behind it but good job kiwawa
nice good job bud why did you bring it
home
she was more happy about um the ashtray
that i made for her in school everyone
made an ashtray
yeah made an ashtray out of like a pink
stone
what was that stone cold
[Music]
yeah oh no that was
ah with an ashtray and a and a candle
holder i think quartz yeah quartz um
really pretty
we never made an ashtray in school i
think i think the the school let us like
choose between an ashtray for the
smoking parents and something else for
the non-smoking parents
don't worry they did not make every
student in junior high school make an
ashtray don't worry now that i think
about it it might not have even happened
junior was that really junior high it
might have been
the one before elementary elementary
not sure
beginning of junior high or sometime in
elementary i know
the ashtray we made in elementary i
think
yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's so european why
why
how did you carve cords but we had some
tools for that
like uh
[Music]
like the thing to make to make things
smooth
i hated using that that paper that
smoothing paper it's probably called
smoothing paper right
i think that one is called smoothing
paper
[\h__\h] sanding paper [\h__\h]
sandpaper i hate it i hate it and i
still would hate it now i hate using
sandpaper because um it gives me the
shivers makes me feel really
i have this weird reaction to using
sandpaper
because the
the feeling
like when it touches something and rubs
on it it makes me feel like
i don't know why everyone else was okay
using it but i just
felt so bad using it
like nails on the chalkboard yes yes
exactly
i get that too hallelujah
let's maybe we're stirring for it what
what's
when you touch it
but it doesn't do anything
which start styro stewart phone it's
fine for me
you shouldn't be touching it touch other
things what no you use it to to rub
something into a more smoother version
of itself
of course you have to touch it
[Music]
yeah smooth stone or chalkboard yeah i
hate that [\h__\h]
yeah
but sandpaper is the worst
[Music]
it's the worst
where it's rubbing on something and
makes a noise that gives me shivers
styrofoam string reform form foam really
[Music]
it's interesting to see how certain
people
um
can't handle certain things but are fine
with other things that others can't
handle
[Music]
weird humans be like weird
what else i don't remember anymore so
long ago
so long ago
and have another stream and all the
knowledge oh go go go go go [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
um but trust me i'll be very awake for
that just by the hype
no of the situation
the hype will wake me up
i don't know how to [\h__\h] to read that
i can't read that
ah
something something foodie
me
probably not how i was supposed to read
it elise mcclary duncan ezekiel thank
you for the pinky clocking into workbox
put me where you need me i need you here
with me wherever doesn't matter wherever
we're meant to be together just be here
in this room
and chill with me
yeah
just as long as you're here
and i'm happy
bootsy thank
[Music]
i wish i could do like a heart sign with
my hands and give you a heart back but
i'm just i can only give you kisses
spanking thank you for a red super chat
as well
okay this is ridiculously cute a prop
small cat is very confused looking at
you guys dancing though
yeah my cat as well she was like so hype
so zoomy before the stream until the
very last moment even until like when
the stream already started a little bit
she was having the zoomies
but your cat was just confused huh
[Music]
maybe next time i need to bring a cat
onto the dance store floor for your cats
to be able to relate
i wonder how that would work
i saw people putting vr trackers on cats
but then i would need a cat model i'm
sure it is free free
cat models
though
sounds too crazy thank you second time
[Music]
rick snyder for the right super chat
spelling out myth with the hearts thank
you
[Music]
thank you for the pinky great first full
concert ladies are was in the concert we
weren't singing or performing
can't wait for more soon and thanks for
organizing these dance collabs andrew
thank you but yeah with your stuff
dancing dancing
[Music]
but
thank you very much i i'm glad you liked
it so much and enjoyed it thank you
perhaps there will be more in the future
but the reason there were um two of them
so close to each other was first of all
gouda guda was really hyped to do it and
then after the first one was such a big
success amen was like yo yo yo yo yo yo
yo yo we can we can squeeze
another one in before the
uh
before the concert she was very
motivated and then we quickly got the
inna and kelly models ready the cali one
she didn't even start working on yet at
that point so it was really really fast
make making the impossible possible but
it's not like there will be so many
dense school
vr chat things happening so often now
every week or something no no no no no i
wanna keep them i wanna i want them to
be something special you know
but we need to do it yes we need to do a
solo dancing stream
where i
blast out those moves
try to remember those choreos
[Music]
it has to be songs though that i can
actually uh
use an instrumental from and so on
um but when it comes to vocaloid and
idol dances there's actually a lot that
i can use
thankfully those are usually are
archivable
so yeah
when you want to see your dance look
look at night fever that will
i will never forget how to dance look
look at night of night fever never
never look like a night fever is like so
burnt into my brain
[Music]
i never thought i would have enjoyed
this as much as i have i never thought
you would enjoy that much either
i love you all and thanks for the hard
work
i'm crying inside of happy tears thank
you what
why
[Music]
it's really weird like you guys see it
in a different way than i did see it
the game agreed
on
[Music]
um
beautiful
[Music]
no text joe had nothing to say huh you
were just speechless by
the great collab stream that we did
speechless understandable have a nice
day and thank you for the support
[Music]
cyber toast
dlc
tony bones thank you for the pinky thank
you kiara no thank you for watching
thank you guys thank you tony bones
thank you soon notorious bs g82
dankeshin great to see all five members
of home live together indeed yes
i know for men
rogan striker
nomination
james duncan jim jordan
mary poppins can you stand
why the frick are you girls so cute
thank you i'm sure you are cutie pie too
thank you
it was a while since your last collab
is that song
i guess so maybe the last four collab
was a while ago was it was it new years
or so
um
probably
the collab after the kimono reveal
probably was the last one
good morning tanjo i'm late it's a dream
stream
i'm late it's a dream stream
can't wait the concert coming i will cry
uh
well i'll send you a box of tissues then
exciting
you'll cry good tears you cry proud
tears
feeling like a parent probably you'll be
like
i raised that girl not really but i was
with her for a long time on stream yeah
yeah
[Music]
thank you fafa
please look forward to it get some
popcorn ready
date
the day one concert
is happening in way less than uh 24
hours holy [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
[Applause]
oh [\h__\h] not too late to buy tickets uh
online tickets yes you can still buy
online tickets on spawn spwn
[Music]
look up link your wish
is the concert name
less than 12 holy [\h__\h] okay
shadow pencil thank you soon
that's all of the carefree dance school
super chats
[Music]
oh wait i want to read the
the field in the beginning of the yakuza
one
mr cat speaks down kitchen
harbor line duncan
[Music]
thank you
so duck joseph sent a
a rainbow that i wanted to read
should i read this one out loud or do
you feel more comfortable if i read it
quietly
[Music]
i should rest off
you know but i i feel bad leaving down
behind
okay i'll read it after my mom passed a
couple of months ago
so recent [\h__\h] i've been spending a lot
of time taking care of my dad
[Music]
rest in peace to your mommy
my dad's not a gamer so whenever i want
to enjoy some gaming i whip out my phone
and watch your game
i can enjoy gaming and assist my papa
what i'm saying is i can still be there
for my dad but i don't have to give up
the things i love i'm so happy about
that that includes you boss you linked
my wish thank you
thank you
i'm glad you can still find time for me
maybe did you did you try introducing
me to your dad
i'm sure he caught a glimpse of my
streams by now
i wonder what you thinks
are you listening with headphones when
you do that or
uh
i think it's hard to hide at that point
it's not his thing uh understandable
yeah i'm just okay okay
he's probably like uh
my son is such a weirdo
what a weirdo but i love him
uh
yeah there are there are definitely
some parents out there who just will not
understand this kind of thing
but that itself is also understandable
we must understand that they don't
understand
yes
[Music]
uh i have my streaming ticket so i will
fit in a reaction video what when i'm
not doing papa stuff this weekend really
you're gonna do it however i will be
totally fine if you don't see it it will
be cringy not red like kitties dancing
what kino's dancing has some cringe
moments though
but really i want to watch it maybe i
should um do a hashtag where people can
send in either youtube links or upload
it directly on twitter so i can find it
easier maybe i should do that
[Music]
chickens also rock by the way let's
cheer so loud that no one can deny the
glory of kfb
thank you
oh yeah cheering i want to hear those
cheering voices
forgot to ride free out of freaking
orange i would just say the part three
is everything after the pinky
no problem i understood everything
perfectly fine
thank you thank yourself
thank you very very very very much
of course you should always prioritize
your dad but i i think you know having
something to
um cheer you up yourself up you know
occupy your mind with it's also
necessary so
good for you
thank you for your love and your support
wait there's one more super chat that i
need to read today because i've noticed
yes i've noticed someone has been
working on something and i kept on
seeing it in my even my tag search on my
ego search
and um i still know what
is going on but i just know that person
worked on it for a long time and they
sent a super chat oh you're here i see
it
and i feel like it would be rude to not
watch it today because you seemed very
eager for me to also watch it before the
concert no i have not been spoiled i
just kept on seeing those tweets about
i'm working on it i'm working on it and
i'm like what are you working on
so apparently it's on your channel the
project is complete and ready for you a
little bit of scuff that but i will fix
that later we hope you like it and have
an excellent stream you can find it on
my channel or on twitter since i can't
post a link it seems okay is this
something that i can play the audio off
uh on my stream you reckon
[Music]
no copyright or so
yeah
okay
um so i'm on your channel ah there it is
nine minutes
a letter to kiara from kfb i'll give you
guys a link
if you want we can sync it up
or or wait how about i quickly download
it without watching it from youtube
download
you know what i'll download it
i'll give it a link too but i'll
download it and then i can play it on
screen on the streams tweet screen
screen
no [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
which which one do i use
here this one probably
not
[Music]
go
download
[Music]
okay almost there
once i put it in here it's gonna be
[Music]
a bit loud i think
and
i'll immediately adjust
[\h__\h] now i'm here oh well
oh well
let's look at it
a nine minute letter
it will be loud for a moment probably
maybe
three
two
one
okay stop maybe it didn't make i don't i
don't even think it made any noise now
now let me change the audio to
[Music]
monitor
was it this one monitor and
no
i think it was
this one
am i supposed to hear something
ah no
really quietly
okay
i've seen this before the art
you guys hear this is it double
[Music]
cut
is copyright free
music
[Music]
yeah
no phoenix
[Music]
supposedly
huh
hello
[Music]
the music is way too loud
what what are you saying
[Music]
i think that's germany
this is his punishment for failing to
protect you from those peace he keeps
unionizing children
let's do twilight
this is also under the assumption that
you can die to live with this we're not
struck with something shiny
[Music]
please accept this humble gift from all
of kfp at least this is a little hard to
translate the cheek and scratch from all
over the world
[Music]
mama
hello
should i watch this privately
feels really intimate right now
it feels really intimate right now
hmm
and countless greetings further still
we your little chimpkins of kfp from all
the world have come together to write to
you about someone who we hold most dear
and close to our hearts to whom that
deserves all the contents of this letter
and more rewriting to you about you
though much cannot be expressed in words
of any tongue in any way that would do
you true justice it is hoped that this
will suffice
from the day you made yourself known to
us within our dimension through the year
more you have stayed you've shown us and
the world who takanawa shikhira was and
is
throughout your time this dimension
you've brightened the world by being all
we could ever ask for you
you have taken us our guest to kfp
whoever they may be
your senpai your kohai and most of all
your gen mates and friends on a journey
that only you can provide
each and every moment for every etch in
our minds and hearts a spark to those
who are new and a roaring flame to those
who have been here since you arrived
a flame that continues to rise higher
and higher burning brighter and brighter
a flame that will forever burn within
all those who you have touched by being
you
you express so much to us
love
courage humility
excitement
and kindness to name a few
you gifters as well each and every
stream
nay each and every day with your humor
your energy and your creativity
all these things that were passed from
you to all of us
it lifts us up
inspires drives
this in turn we pass on to others with
you giving warmth to our hearts
passion to our spirits
on and on
you are the core
of the fire to this kfb
so intense in this heat and light
yet you do not burn
or blind us
you have wanted and want still nothing
but the best for you in the past
now and forevermore
may fret
panic
cluck
i mean we are going because after i'll
come now
but we do this out of love
chickens
bring like to your day
all the things you give to us do the
same for you
you'll find a way
art
videos
music
messages
chats
leave this letter in ways we can give
back to you outside of attending your
stream thank
you if there was a way to send you the
warmth of my love admiration
hugs
and our thanks
surely we'll rival your own phoenix fire
how much more will you do each provide
some wonder indeed
in your first original hinatori
you asked about your destiny and if any
can tell you what it is
your destiny well
you're already living it by being you
expressing your creativity
with your friends in the world
heart challenge and sparks are further
examples before being a show of love for
us all deceived admire and cherish with
you
the ladder to get up live our lives and
look to the future getting behind the
wheel of our own vehicle of destiny
driving onto what comes next at our own
speed
recovers now with all your gen mates
as well as your solar performances take
us on a journey and see bond with your
friends as much as to show off your
talent as a fiery idol
it's getting hard to hear again wish you
all the best of more in the days
weeks
months and years
[Music]
secondly lastly
as you once said to another in a way
some time ago
listen to your heart and follow where it
needs so long
you want your streams to be
no matter what it is
it's really hard to hear
we also want each note better so while
the past few days before the concert
have had some ups and downs we know you
rise above them
they'll still
if we could you'd happily be like him
and without pause take away all your
doubt
sadness
pain
all that brings our mom alone casts away
however while it upsets us
makes us worry it also humbles us and
finds something more
as while you are majestic phoenix in
human form sharing these emotions and
thoughts with us really good or bad
makes you human
life in this dimension can be rough but
your worldwide family is here with you
always
so rise our beloved phoenix rise and
take your rightful place among all the
stars in the sky
bright as the sun you are to us all
he
become a son
one last thing we should say and we mean
this through all their hearts what's
this
though being on stage may be scarier or
at least make you anxious come the
festival
i know you can do it
and we'll shine like you always do
plus with the japanese are there to help
with the plum feathery flesh
you're surely sore
what is this remix thanks
[Music]
to you who made that with all the love
warmth happiness we can muster
yours in this life and wherever next
yes
some chimpkins wanted to add this as it
would be
criminal not to
will never give up our tenshu
we'll never let down our oshie
we'll never cluck around yeah form a
union
shut up
and in german we say
i'll feed
hey smart
when did i do that
well this is remix i haven't i don't
think i've heard this one before
thank you
yeah
wow that whispering
uh rickroll it's hard
thank you very much
[Music]
okay i'm just waiting for it to end
three two one
there it is oh
it i heard it was a it was a group
project did you like
were there several people writing the
the
text together or
was the group project putting the fan
art together
a beautiful letter from us all oh you
did write it together
did like people write several sentences
or
how did you do that
you did each person write a paragraph or
what
both um
yeah i mean the fanart is
from a lot of different people
i wrote it alone oh
never heard of it
you wrote the letter alone
oh
misunderstanding i thought it was a
a community project
huh
thank you it's like a very very very
very very long super chat
or a digital letter because sending me a
normal letter would take months to
arrive months or maybe even a year
a year about a year yeah that's a good
estimate
this way it arrives way faster
i didn't know what to expect but thank
you for the sweet message it was a bit
difficult to hear sometimes so i had to
really focus so i got quiet because uh
without subtitles
in that audio volume really really need
to focus
i'm thank you very sweet of you thank
you soon
good timing to watch it before the
concert yeah yeah
we'll fix it tonight don't worry about
it i think i got
most of it
most of it i understood
or i mean if you want to upload a
quieter version
um
would probably be good too
yeah all right
thank you everyone
for watching today
uh i'll put up the stream reservation
asap um just gonna throw in some uh
rice into my rice cooker
and then and then i'll see you guys
tomorrow
for day one we'll we'll still get some
time i'll still get some time to lean
back and enjoy the show
ah
in some way i don't like being on day
two because i gotta wait longer but
in another way it's it's a cool because
i can just
you know
watch the others do their thing first
what about the rest of super chats yeah
i need i need some um preparing time and
i need some
uh sleepy time and all that because
stream tomorrow is early
and
yeah i'll try to read some after the
watch long should be possible
uh and then
yeah and then the rest will be red on
monday
sorry about that
the stream today already is six and a
half hours so
i said i did say today that i can't stay
for too long
short stream today yes this is shirt
totally
thank you everybody for your sweet
messages also shout outs thank you for
the sweet message and thank you for the
support everybody
i'll do my best
and but it's not yet time it's not your
time yummy ah
aren't we all feeling really impatient
right now like why the [\h__\h] am i not on
day one [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
kind of
impatient but
it will feel even better than on day two
[Music]
yeah
my skin is
[Music]
you're same same tbh
tbh
um
all right then uh
thank you guys for watching and in
german we say au vina vin
i am going to keep the rest of my
tangents for another time i guess yeah
um
but we did some good progress again
today in
yakuza going smoothly so far um
[Music]
um
totally waving my hand here
oh
oh no bgm oh
how about this one
i think i muted the wrong thing
that was awkward
[Music]
do
you