​​​ ​Together with friends we believe in​ ​​
​​​ ​shinji au nakama to issho ni​ ​​
​​​ ​We light a signal​ ​​
​​ ​and take on the challenge​ ​​
​​​ ​chousen no noroshi o ageyou​ ​​
​​​ ​Of a neverending​ ​​
​​​ ​owaranai​ ​​
​​​ ​Youth​ ​​
​​​ ​seishun ni​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive IDOL PROJECT - Seishun Archive​ ​​
​​​ ​Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement:​ ​​
​​ ​HoneyWorks​ ​​
​​​ ​seishun ni​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​Vocals: Tokino Sora,​ ​​
​​ ​Shirakami Fubuki, Minato Aqua,​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​Vocals: Hoshimachi Suisei,​ ​​
​​ ​Amane Kanata, Moona Hoshinova,​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​Vocals: Airani Iofifteen,​ ​​
​​ ​Takanashi Kiara, Gawr Gura​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​Boys & Girls​ ​​
​​​ ​Throw away your inhibitions and hey, jump​ ​​
​​​ ​shuuchishin wa sutete Hey Jump!​ ​​
​​​ ​Together we're cool, jump, jump​ ​​
​​​ ​minna de soroeba Cool Jump! Jump!​ ​​
​​​ ​As the glittering drops fall to the ground​ ​​
​​​ ​hikaru suiteki koboreochite​ ​​
​​​ ​On this dog day of youth and energy​ ​​
​​​ ​seishun kanjiteiru moushobi​ ​​
​​​ ​Super hot!​ ​​
​​​ ​acchu~!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna show off my growth​ ​​
​​​ ​seichou shita sugata o misetai​ ​​
​​​ ​The rehearsal was perfect​ ​​
​​​ ​riha wa kanpeki​ ​​
​​​ ​For the real deal,​ ​​
​​ ​I'll go all out and go high! High!​ ​​
​​​ ​honban wa motto zenryoku de High! High!​ ​​
​​​ ​(High! High! Foo!)​ ​​
​​​ ​So many precious memories​ ​​
​​​ ​taisetsuna omoide​ ​​
​​​ ​(High! High! Foo!)​ ​​
​​​ ​But it's not yet time​ ​​
​​​ ​takusan aru kedo ne mada​ ​​
​​​ ​There's no time for reminiscence​ ​​
​​​ ​kanshou ni hitatteru hima wa nai​ ​​
​​​ ​The summer of the century​ ​​
​​​ ​konseiki saidai no​ ​​
​​​ ​Is upon us​ ​​
​​​ ​natsu ga hajimaru​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​A peak beyond the wildest dreams​ ​​
​​​ ​souzou no hate ni aru takami​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​This view we've seized​ ​​
​​ ​for ourselves is priceless​ ​​
​​​ ​kachitotta keshiki wa toutoi​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't run away,​ ​​
​​ ​overcome your limits and that wall​ ​​
​​​ ​nigeruna genkai no kabe koete​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​We remain challengers​ ​​
​​​ ​bokura wa mada charenjaa​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​Even when we​ ​​
​​ ​drown in a sea of cold voices​ ​​
​​​ ​tsumetai koe ni oboreta tte​ ​​
​​​ ​We grab and hold on to a sliver of hope​ ​​
​​​ ​kasukana nozomi o taguriyoseru you ni​ ​​
​​​ ​Someone laments that we're duds​ ​​
​​​ ​kitaihazure da to dareka ga nageku​ ​​
​​​ ​The pain and the desire​ ​​
​​ ​to belong always do battle​ ​​
​​​ ​itai to itai ga itsumo tatakau​ ​​
​​​ ​We wanna believe in ourselves​ ​​
​​ ​as we fight relying on our pride alone​ ​​
​​​ ​puraido dake o tayori ni aragau jibun o shinjitai​ ​​
​​​ ​Hard work does pay off​ ​​
​​​ ​doryoku wa mukuwareru​ ​​
​​​ ​If you wanna laugh, feel free​ ​​
​​​ ​waraitai yatsu wa warattero​ ​​
​​​ ​There's no time for sentimentality​ ​​
​​​ ​kanshou ni hitatteru hima wa nai​ ​​
​​​ ​The summer of the century​ ​​
​​​ ​konseiki saidai no​ ​​
​​​ ​Is upon us​ ​​
​​​ ​natsu ga hajimaru​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​Not enough buzz, need more​ ​​
​​​ ​hankyou ga tarinai motto motto​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​You won't regret it​ ​​
​​​ ​koukai wa sasenai​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​A peak beyond the wildest dreams​ ​​
​​​ ​souzou no hate ni aru takami​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​This view we've seized​ ​​
​​ ​for ourselves is priceless​ ​​
​​​ ​kachitotta keshiki wa toutoi​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't run away,​ ​​
​​ ​overcome your limits and that wall​ ​​
​​​ ​nigeruna genkai no kabe koete​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​
​​​ ​We remain challengers​ ​​
​​​ ​bokura wa mada charenjaa​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow​ ​​