​​​ ​Kikkeriki!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hi, everybody!​ ​​
​​​ ​I am Takanashi Kiara​ ​​
​​ ​from hololive English -Myth-!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​And I am hereby​ ​​
​​ ​starting the countdown...​ ​​
​​​ ​of 10 days until the​ ​​
​​ ​super-exciting, anticipated...​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive English 1st-ever concert​ ​​
​​​ ​"Connect the World"!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, these 10 days, you can​ ​​
​​ ​basically count down with your two hands.​ ​​
​​​ ​You can start now.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's 10!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh my god!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, so...​ ​​
​​​ ​By the way, if you want,​ ​​
​​ ​please use the hashtag #holoENConnect​ ​​
​​​ ​for anything concert related,​ ​​
​​​ ​if you wanna talk about it​ ​​
​​ ​on Twitter or other social media.​ ​​
​​​ ​And I'll be checking it out, too.​ ​​
​​​ ​So that would be​ ​​
​​ ​very useful if you guys use it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Um, yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Also, don't forget!​ ​​
​​​ ​Stream tickets are still available!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you haven't gotten one yet,​ ​​
​​​ ​make sure to get one in time​ ​​
​​ ​so that you're ready and all set up!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's gonna be so worth it!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm sure!​ ​​
​​​ ​And, yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​For my beloved KFP, and all the​ ​​
​​ ​other fans as well who are maybe not KFP,​ ​​
​​​ ​I really wanna thank you​ ​​
​​ ​so much for all the support​ ​​
​​​ ​that you have given hololive English,​ ​​
​​​ ​because you made it​ ​​
​​ ​possible for us to have this​ ​​
​​​ ​super-special​ ​​
​​ ​hololive English concert!​ ​​
​​​ ​Our very own!​ ​​
​​​ ​So far,​ ​​
​​​ ​we've always been​ ​​
​​ ​part of, you know,​ ​​
​​​ ​the big Japanese senpais concerts.​ ​​
​​​ ​But now, this is​ ​​
​​ ​our own thing and, yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're gonna make it our own!​ ​​
​​​ ​So, let's have lots of fun together!​ ​​
​​​ ​See you guys there!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's gooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Connect the World!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​