[music]
N
child
[music]
a
[applause]
[music]
DET
JAa
[music]
H
T
[music]
[applause]
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
No, wait a minute
hand
hello voice
[music]
YOG
evenknoware
wearwebacksoback
[music]
Can you hear me?
No, it's okay, wait a minute.
to watch your own broadcast
Wow, that voice is normal.
[music]
There is a certain voice
Ah oh oh oh
BACK
[music]
Myooooo
Chichi
Oh wait a minute
Minecraft
I'm starting up. Excuse me, that little PC.
I had to restart my PC because it restarted.
Sorry for the inconvenience, Minecraft
Start
Start Minecraft So
Right, it's Makto, right? Yes, yes, yes.
yes start minecraft start
Start mcraMC
start minecraft
Masu
Oh yes, yes, yes, yes, I'm here.
I came
Come with this
It's here
It came, it came, it came
[music]
OK
Why
[music]
Never I
knowyouguyssay
something givemea
signyouguysgivemea
sign
to
okoksign OK
OKyouguyssignthat
meansguysaredead
thatmeansyouguysare
deadguysareG
[music]
What, it ends at 9pm
It's over, only 10 minutes left
No, only 10 minutes left
[music]
It's not over, it's over
Ah, it's finished
Cale today is oh my oh my magnes
Oh my gosh today
[music]
teeth
BBknowknowwhat
I'm
Baby, what should I do, Bon?
senior
[music]
Hello, it's over. I'm not ready at all.
What should I do now?
mosquito
[music]
Is it okay to use this equipment? I only have that iron equipment.
There isn't.
But the sword is that sword.
Masu
Oh okay, okay
[music]
Okay, that's the one in the front, I understand.
Yes, thank you very much.
I wonder if it's okay to have terrible equipment at all.
I don't understand at all
I almost don't have it
Well, I guess I should just take it here.
Maybe everyone will go to a bar when it starts.
I wonder if there is?
I see
Well, it's hardcore, so be careful.
I'm worried and worried
[music]
already
cormorant
I can't do that, I can't do anything
[music]
I can do something
I wonder if he'll come back?
[music]
I can do something
I am also equipped with a shield.
[music]
Anne Shimoru is working hard at translating in various places.
this
Oh, this, this, who wrote this? I'm sure it's Polka-senpai.
I feel like you wrote it here.
Hey, it's called a message board.
I had the pleasure of doing that.
That and the journal inside too, yes, yes, yes.
Oh yeah, that's what Anya did.
That's right, Polka Senpai is Anya's English
I told them to write it in English.
I made a sound because it was
Yes, I work a lot.
Aya, you're a senior, you're a senior, you're a 2 coke
Senior: Oh, give me a diamond.
Rutte
I see, Pecola-senpai is some kind of diamond.
You'll give it to me, Yayaeko.
This is a quest diamond.
There are no translation diamonds
a
Senpai, what's wrong? What are you doing? What did you just do?
So, seriously? Oh yeah, yeah, what day is it? It's the 2nd day.
Our eyes are the same, let's do our best together.
Let's do our best, even though we're beginners.
Thank you very much Gomemon na Egome
I don't think it's useful, but I'm wearing it
Isn't this really good? Oh, this is different.
Sorry I got this, I got this too
No, it's so embarrassing
It's okay, I'm a beginner too.
So something disappeared
Did you two go there? Ubu 7 also has Arne.
Return
What is this?
equipped
[music]
[applause]
Dao Need
[music]
R
sleeping
Masu
helpus
willemcome
[music]
help
sorthink
[music]
OK
This is the biggest right now
a
I heard
[music]
of
the ah
Is the attack starting now? Or is it starting now?
Let's go. I was wondering if A-san would go.
I won't go, I'll go, only that iron sword
Is that okay? Wait, maybe Subaru?
Then I might be able to make about 3 of them with diamonds.
Wow, that's amazing. I surprisingly have diamonds.
The diamonds were amazing today.
character dement
Yay Banchou
Bancho Bancho don't go home, he's afraid of the enemy.
I'll bring something from home.
I don't know if it's true, but I see.
Ah, I wonder if Senpai is here. I have a lot of bows and arrows.
But no, I can make what I want. Make it.
I thought I could make it, I thought I could make it.
Hello, I think I can make it, I think I can make it, senpai.
Good morning senpai, I'm going to die from "Good morning"
I thought so. Seriously, I was just born.
Oh, I guess I was born, there's a shooting event starting now.
It's okay, it's okay right away. If this dies, I'll die.
That's right, I'll give you this.
I'll give you this too.
A little fly
Thank you for this gift
I'll give it to you
I wonder if it's me. Thank you. I can make it.
I already have the iron, but...
There is a crafting table
crafting table a crafting
Thank you very much for the table
There's also a birth, wait a minute, that's it.
Teshi
The debt is terrible. The debt is terrible.
What should I do in this little blue world?
Yesterday I could end up in debt.
I was playing Chinchiro.What do you think?
Where should I go?
I lost a lot here.
I'm just talking to you, senpai.
I tried to kill a certain senior but failed.
I'm dead. Ah, let's go even if I think about it.
The attack event starts in 3 minutes!
I was entrusted with this, so I can go.
My 96 ma who is making seeds for me
It didn't click, huh?
Haikuma96
96 has also become stronger, I'm going with 96
Let's do it
960 My 12 years later, it's impossible, impossible, impossible.
I can't, I can't, I can't wait, I can't wait because blue is strong
At times like this, use Maina 96 here.
Wait, I'm talking about the x-axis.
Because you said something similar elsewhere.
I thought it was around here, but here it is.
It's the opposite, but it's negative.
I was told that Iro-chan Iro-chan looks like this place.
But Ma96 means this or this.
Dekocchi
Can you hear me? I went the other way.
Autumn Senpai Autumn Senpai is not here Maina 96
Is that the blue one? Maina96a
It seems that's it. Which one is it?
Because it has
No, I don't understand at all either, sorry.
I'm also a newbie to Minecraft, sorry.
Yeah, do you want Aka-senpai Arrow? Yes, yes.
Let's go, let's go
Hey, Aka-senpai, have you gathered all the arrows for your bow and arrow yet?
There's a lot of candy here.
This is amazing, this kind of feeling, this kind of terrible
I wonder if it would be bad if I don't connect here.
A pretty big enemy is coming. Where will the enemy come from?
I wonder how this is going to come right in front of me
Please stop coming in front of me
Are you saying you want something and fighting for it?
It's okay if you climb up
Kae
run away
Only you will survive
I only have two diamonds that look like Rika.
There was none
Because I only had two from
Thank you for always seeing me again
thank you
hey
That's right, I'm going to die. When I die, it's over, so don't worry.
That stubborn person died in the dead room
Survive until the last day
I swore that day that I was going to do this.
Do this on your own, so try not to die.
I'm going to go up by myself, I'm going to go up, I'm going to go up
Is it better to hold the bow and put the bow body above yourself?
This sword is special because it's the only sword I have.
A golem that's not messing around.
I want to make a golem with an iron block.
Come on, let's see what you were doing earlier.
The hollowed-out pumpkin 5 and the iron block are now
there is
[music]
Mbi
mlyOhYeahNothing
[music]
happen
mcra
Oh yeah
[music]
wait
Hey, how are you going to climb this? Here we come.
I can hear it
[music]
Taacchi will also use remote control.
Is it impossible without a bow? It's difficult here, too. It's a dream that's coming soon.
Even if it's tough, I'll just wait, wait, wait.
The golem is hitting the golem.
This is the first hit with Ubu.
Amatsu is a nuisance that hits Go.
124T Oh wait, that wasn't the face
It wasn't, so I can't do anything.
This is it, I don't have the strength to get off.
Yes, that's it, that's it, then I came here.
This was a nice, nice ending.
Okay, okay, I can do this.
I'll take it if it's not there
I haven't been able to do that since I failed in a series of battles.
But
The attackers came, maybe they didn't come just now.
It's coming, it's coming, six here, this one, this one.
I can't make more than that
Where is Mr. Marat? Mr. Makuto is nice. What flowers?
Everyone who grows because it's beautiful and makes you happy when you plant it
properly happy happy
That's nice
Yes, that's nice, likeit
impossibleto
with
likeunderstand
Nothing
Good
It's okay
[music]
fight
Ooooh
[music]
battle needle have
SLEeh
I want to give it to you when you sleep or sleep
Naerusui-chan
[Laughter]
It's scary, scary, scary
It's nice to have Ru as a senior.
Ponai nice
Bona, be careful, it's a group of golems.
Something is burning, it's burning
It's burning
That and that
Well, there's nothing else to do.
do not have
Fire
[music]
I don't know if this is ok, but I got some kind of logic.
It's come, it's come
Choyaba
Go
terrible
Oh no, I'm under a bad curse. I'm under a curse.
I can't cast a curse on Teru.
died in
Dayabaku
[music]
scary scary scary scary
What a scary book
That guy is disgusting
[music]
senior
Hey, that's scary, nice
[music]
I became a nice hero
I was just trying to make fun of it.
Polkapo senior polka dead polka it's true
Polka died, same goes for Mex.
I died as a hero, so this is definitely true
He will come back to life.
[music]
Hey, dying on the battlefield is a good thing, it's the best.
Kotona
Overwasuseless
[music]
[laughter]
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
terrible
key
raw life
Thank you
I'll give it to you
I want to be Polka-senpai's Polpe here
[laughter]
A little longer
It's long
My hands are like that plus element, a flower
I'll be with you. The arms and legs that help my stomach are amazing.
It's long, Pol-chan, it's true. Hand throw at 9pm.
Touch it, touch it
Maybe I'll give this one too
[music]
Soyame
I made a picture that I want to add
I have to
It's amazing.
Rutte
picture
After all, it was home.
difference
My face won't be revived because there's no trial anymore.
episode
You can only do this until the next time or once.
I liked you, you like this, you like this
It was
Hey everyone, let's take a photo.
Thank you very much for your help.
Tel
Later
[music]
be together
[laughter]
[music]
[applause]
Karaimashi
[music]
It's delicious
Polka Polka I've done this, let's finish it.
Because I've used it up
[music]
Miya
PE boots
[music]
Tess money equipment is gone
I put on my boots
From now on, polka will make a comeback.
mosquito
Isn't that the diamond system?
Is that so? Is it no longer a trial?
Is that okay?
hand
a
Yes, I think it's better to protect it.
[music]
Alright
picture
[music]
Because it was Ada
ni polka-chan
[music]
I see.
that
That's it
Interesting, that's interesting.
My luggage is packed, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this.
That's what happens when you die.
Ah, Anya-san, this is probably it.
There's some ice in that Subaru-senpai's chest.
There's a block in it, so this is Subaru Senpai.
It's not the ice block you have when you die.
I don't know, but I'm sure this diamond
The block is different, but this is that one.
I have to get that money into
Everyone's like that, why don't you change that?
Does this contain ice blocks?
Diamond block dive ah, it's a diamond block.
It's not an ice block, it's a diamond block.
Well, I haven't finished repaying the debt at all.
I can't finish repaying my debt. How many more are left?
Do you have any debts left?
He gave me a diamond sword after I was saved by him.
I'm thinking of going because it's all over the place.
I guess it's 120 because it's possible.
First of all, do something with someone.
That guy used to pay his own money.
I borrowed 200 in one day.
I'm talking to Da
What, what, what, Mikochie actor controls and equips
Because I was told to start by receiving it.
All the seniors are like, ``Are you going to go to college?''
Anyami Senpai Emiko Senpai Chichichue What's going on?
I hit you so you don't have to give it to me.
Well, I'll give you something nice.
Yeah, it's an iron sword, right?
Should I give you something?
Well, I came late.
There's nothing wrong with that.
I got it in blue
I'll give you this, it's red.
It suits Poppy Mikochin
I'll tell you where the iron is, so I'll wait for the iron.
Please tell me the rules of the lever rulebook
B
I want a rule book that I can read.
Didn't you read the rule book? That's a lie.
le
This is a rule, thank you, this is a rule.
There are changes, but please read here.
Deamoshima
Well, I see, if you read this
It's okay, that's right, that's right.
Suri-senpai, that's good. What's my voice like?
What is this signboard? What is this signboard? Bulletin board
Or what do you think about your own voice, here or here?
Micha
[music]
Is it true that yes?
3 Seniors who are not included and Lu seniors are in debt.
There's a voice telling me to go this way.
Sharpness
ah
That's another one
This has to change
This is it
Wait a minute, I'll get back to you. I have money.
There is a sword
No, this is the house I read. This is the house I read.
I was so worried, I thought it was someone I didn't know.
[music]
I don't know what to do
likehaveanyWord
[music]
[laughter]
let the fores glow stone remain
I can go to glowstone
Egrowth Asoka
This is new, Glostone in hand
I'm going to put it in and create it. It's a bit scary.
I'm new to clubbing and don't know how to do it.
I went to pick up something with a stranger.
I'm going to put Grown in that one.
Because it's inside, there's a dangerous high at the end.
The level is too high, this skeleton knows that.
Skeet was those guys.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
I wish I could get a distorted mushroom.Distorted
What is a mushroom? A distorted mushroom
What is Ko? How is Poshin?
create it
How to get growth
get the growth
I've become a big dog, so I'm going
Let's say this English text frog egg size
I mean, please tell me this seriously.
Please, I want it too.
How do you make Aikerue frog eggs?
Where are the frog eggs? Yeah, they're distorted.
What is Kino's English version of Minecraft?
I've never forgotten where the mosquito eggs are.
Can't you see the Nether? Wait a minute, it's a swamp.
First of all, use the diamond vine as a wetland body.
Looks like Silk Touch is here Sue Silk
I don't have a touch
I didn't do it on the first day, I died.
yeah
He died and became the dog of that management.
Well then,
[music]
Oooooo
okok
[music]
GOODGOODIDEgood
IDE
mesok
[music]
M
ENGknow
[music]
ENG
Gust
[music]
War1
potion time
Not that
Or shovel locally made skeleton
[music]
That Run?
I won't go back
[music]
When there is only one wagone, it returns to a golden grain.
same like this
bread in
That's why emeralds are so precious.
Meow yes
This is what was called just now.
[music]
think
OK, I can understand Japanese, but I can't understand Minecraft.
I don't understand, I'm just a beginner.
Te-chan and Sa-chan, seriously Minecraft
Do not write the English version of Nema in the English version of the words.
[music]
Toan
recommend
[music]
Funk good and senpai
Yes, it's me. Yes, take a peek at the Nether.
I'm thinking of doing this.
Let's go, I think I'll just go for a little bit.Okay.
Okay, wait a minute, I'll translate this into English.
But wait a minute, wait a minute
You did such an amazing job that I was waiting for you.
is
Wow, I'm at work.
Do your best and get some iron.
Masu Funny Retsu Retsu Retsu Ofanny
funny walks
FYWORKS
FYWORKSOKyouplay
WouldI wouldassumeif
youplayMinecraftyou
knowwhatisaWordFY
likenotlikeis
GRWRyou
[music]
knowWeWord
engok
otherthink
SPENG The rest is just that normal space.
It's good
[music]
Yes, there is probably no space for anything else.
This means I'm alone now.
If it's food that's turned into something, then who is it?
of
Emerald, someone's
I picked up an emerald
[music]
some
me
Something
Yeah, it's really someone's something.
I heard a voice, but somehow I heard it wrong.
I thought it was, oh give me the emerald
Tano
He gave me an emerald there.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry for being so enthusiastic about that translation, thank you.
Who is this?
[music]
You gave it to me, didn't it?
You gave me this, really, seriously, really.
TRUE
Nie really
Seriously, seriously gave me
I didn't pick this up by mistake.
I didn't pick it up by mistake.
Really
Ma
[music]
Well, you gave me an emerald.
Mahonma
[music]
Wait a minute
Tesusu Senpai gave me this
Ma
[music]
It's not a mistake
Espar Eye Arrow
[music]
fromaskthink
Goingthatmeansneed
survive
[laughter]
[music]
EasyTAS
sayTAS
[music]
sayWhat is emerald used for?
I don't know about enchantment, but I don't know.
Not though
Amiko
How do you all get all the diamond gear?
Let's just leave it there and get diamond equipment.
Maybe everyone went to the ground and dug.
It's probably because there was a dick yesterday.
Chinchiro, after all, do Chinchiro.
Chinchiroe I don't know if it's there today.
Yeah yeah yeah where is that chichichi?
There's also an attack point or something like that.
I wonder if it's there, O-kun, oh hello.
If you know a lot, please take a look.
I bought this lucky Tsuruha.
I have a double Nada diamond.
That's great, it'll be doubled if you do it.
If that's the case, give Miko half of that.
I can't help it
It's okay if it's just a little bit, but if it's this much
You can give it to me next time it comes out, real diamond 3
3 diamonds and 3 diamonds
I wonder how many diamonds I have now?
Oh, I don't have one right now.
I can't use it, I can't use it, it's a different Lyrica-chan
I don't have one question because I saved someone who died.
I'm giving 30 yen to Arabe-chan.
That's fine, Miko-senpai, Miko-senpai, yes.
What what?
Oh Anni
It's a shame
Is that okay? You are okay.
You?
I'm the one who has 30 diamonds, okay?
Is it true that Thailand's number one equipment is the
No, I'm sure it's fine, right?
Mama asked me if I could go to Neza.
Ah, if you're going to Nether, you'll definitely need this too.
Isn't that right? I'm going to Nezha after this.
But Miko-senpai, how about we go together and put this on?
I want to go, I want to go, I can't get hit, so I'm going
I want to go too, sister.
I want to go, let's go, Nether from there.
You can go, let's go, go to the Nether.
Where can I go?
If you pick up this sand or something, you'll get diamonds.
Yes, yes, yes, by the way, the fortress.
I mean, I didn't find anyone, but I guess it's just a matter of finding someone.
I have never heard of such a discovery.
Seriously, this is one of a kind Miku
I want to reach 30 points, but 30 is serious.
I really want to go to 30, if I'm really lucky.
I guess there's one thing you can do.
What is it? If you go in the opposite direction that everyone went, you'll be fine.
I want a little block that has no change.
But there are stones and other things everywhere.
Isn't it a stone? I have a lot of stones in my house
Yes, it's not really cobblestone.
I would like this stone if it were like this.
I want a stone like this, I want it.
Please, please, I also like this.
Yes, I want it too, of course I'll give it to you.
Please do my best to infinity
Don't say ruttende
What is lost is love
There are only dangerous enemies, there are dangerous enemies.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
The one with the head color is really real
Let's go
[music]
It's okay, let's go!
There is E and there is E.
That's not correct.
Hey, yeah, we're both beginners.
But hey, I can't help it, it's my first time too.
I'm a beginner, so it's pretty much within the range.
Well, I heard it around here.Oh, I see.
Around here
Is he really okay?
this
Hello, thank you for your hard work. Are you okay with this equipment?
No, I think that's definitely dangerous. Me too.
I wonder if it's the first time now, so why are you talking about everything?
Even Subaru is equipped with tires all over its body.
I'm 4 years old and want to get close to Nether.
[music]
Hey
Let's do this
Also, I'll beat Gust and all of them.
Defeat one monster in the mountain.
Octopus, yeah yeah, maybe if one person defeats it
I want to
Petting Ichinita
It's okay to be aloof, right?
Maybe I'll find it in Dana instead 30303333
Isn't it worth 150?
Tara
I've lived my life because I'm good at whatever I do.
It's true that I've been living on just that
Subaru also had a lot of fun yesterday
I'm sure you can do it if you ask me a little bit.
It doesn't say there are 30 people, right?
Yes, but originally
Can't you give me some yen? There's too much snow.
But okay, snow too.
With momon
Let's go snowy, let's go snowy, let's go snowy too, let's go snowy too.
It's okay to look like a tree too.
Hey, it's a bit steep. You're a snow genius, aren't you?
I'll wait for a while and go to sleep once.For now, 1
Do you sleep once or once? Oh yeah, that's right.
If you say sleepover, you'll talk
Let's see, what would you do if you were given 30 yen?
Let's talk about it, it's decided to pay off the debt, right?
I'm in debt, I'm in debt.
Apple had zero plastic yesterday.
Just pick up a little bet
Who picked it up? Don't sell it yet. Yeah, but...
I'm going to go get some stones, but I'm at home right now.
I haven't won, I haven't won, oh look
I'll go get some stones and come back here.
I'll bring some stones for measurement.
Wow
Cobblestone, I'll give you a cobblestone, wait a minute.
I didn't have enough cobblestone to die for.
Wait a minute, I have a lot at home too.
That's right
[music]
Japan has become clear
PRIwithher
towithI
meancouldknowGU
body sayingin
JapanesemeCanAlways
foryou
[music]
but
hey
I heard a voice for a second, but it was Kira.
Is it a voice?
Nano
[music]
her
iDIAMSWORD
OhDiamondSwordand
Diamondpicknice
enchanted let go
enchantedhowdoyou
enchant
stuffsosoBlindabout
Minecraft You area
Minecraft
[Laughter]
Noenchantedoren
Yourselfwithlike
BOOKSandstuffIgenin
havenoideaWhat
talkingaboutthere
theresomegoodBOOKS
andsomegood
enchant
BOOKSBOOKSBOOK
[music]
I'm in my first house
Are you going? Are you going?
[music]
I can't just do it tomorrow I'm sorry, what, what, what?
I can't lend it to you for free, but now
You have 5 diamonds, so this too.
It's the final diamond
Hey, Final Diamond, Inalfa, hey.
me final
from fire
As long as you say yes, that's fine.
too
It looks like it's going to be tough. I'm equipped with about 1 item.
[music]
Oh, if I try hard, I'll probably get about 10 of them.
I'll never get it
[music]
It won't crawl.
Isn't it okay?
[music]
1, I'm sorry, it's blue. 1, the moon, what's wrong with the blue?
I'm sleepy, blue, blue, how far can I go?
Neinai went to this place all by herself.
I'm so sorry tomorrow, that Ina-chan
Let's go to that Nether together.
Let's go, can we go? Let's go, okay.
Okay, okay, okay then Hina
I'll probably go back home later.
Thank you for coming
Thank you very much, Senkyuo, it's okay.
Miko-senpai is not bullied by Subaru-senpai.
No, it's okay, I'm trying to lend it to you right now.
Tenka Soto and Nemikochinami Edore
About how much
About
No, I can't bring it out now, by the way, that unknown
It's in good condition, but it's hard.
The core is experienced people, so yeah yeah
I think he'll survive.
I don't know if there are 4 days left, but then
Is everything okay? I'm holding onto everything.
It's time to go home
This is ready. Chiara, welcome home too.
Ina, here, here, Ina-senpai Aoku
I told Ina-senpai to go too.
Is it okay? It's okay. It's okay.
Well then, Ina-senpai, Lee-senpai is probably going back home too.
Yes character that I think will probably come later from
Thank you in advance.Thank you in advance.
Thank you very much. I've been waiting for this.
I'm not very good at Japanese, so I said that a little bit.
Thank you all for your support.
There is no such thing as becoming good at something.
I don't want to lose to Ani-chan
No, that's it.
Kiara says no, its not like that.
It's so amazing, Japan is amazing
Everyone is amazing I can't speak at all
Not talking right now
It's like rounding.
Yeah
Yae's evil is fine, wait a minute.
hang on
[music]
No, no, it's impossible, isn't it? Your face is fine.
But no, I'm not a monk.
This is Karamin
Kodo
By ear
How did you do it?
Satoshi's hat skin on the hat stand
It becomes more certain when I remove it.Oh no.
It's probably a Minecraft setting since it's a different setting.
Ran-chan's memory is so round
Let's all curl up. Maybe this is also true.
a little bit
It was there
[laughter]
How did you do it? How did you do it?
Tatekoe and that setting.
Customize settings
How can I get my head from
Wow
Replying to @Terujira_san
Masu
I'll go
Kink option
Options are already gone already are already gone
What?
Teru is so bad
But
It's too much, it's too much
Do it too, you're going to live from now on.
My senior's determination
Mota-chan baby
Big
Janmi
Group photoGroup photoThis is it
Kuruteru
It's just the hair
[applause]
[music]
It might be the last time
Name included
Teru
You're getting too gay. Let's all go to the garden.
Let's do our best, let's go to Koen this year
Keep it up
I shouldn't have waited so long.
Yeah yeah yeah
Aina-chan will come too, after she comes.
Let's go, let's put the guy in the corner first
Moe, what are we going to do here now?
Go to the Nezha and explore.
I haven't found the Asae I'm looking for yet.
If we all play together, everyone will be the first.
I think it's possible. There's one person here.
It doesn't say "only" or something like that. Look, what's your fault?
Stop it, come here
I don't have to work, so I can hang out for a while.
is
It's a bit of a pain, so everyone's Noe
Here you are, Samiko Minami.
[music]
If I get two more days, I'll get a plate too.
I can do it quite well.There is definitely something about it.
That's it
I'm wearing senior clothes that I have to sleep in.
If you haven't come to chat yet,
Well, wait a minute
hey
Pon
[music]
Bemission
I'm sorry but it's gone now
Yo, what are you going to use? I need a little more of that equipment.
I thought that was it, so I gave Tsuba a diamond.
I borrowed money and now I have plates everywhere.
I can only get this one, there's only one left.
what
Thank you for that
stomach
Thank you, 10 times more in one day.
nice to meet you
Definitely before I forget
forget hello
Hello, thank you very much.
Make a wish, stop being a monk.
[music]
Terudeshi
When I say it with the feeling of
Immediately after death
[music]
me too
can
Yeah this and that
Impossible
Suss aako
Thank you very much, sir.Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, please
Please, you're fluent in Japanese.
different
Like
Japan is so fluent, isn't it?
I don't understand Japanese
is
Japanese
Ohhh, Ai-chan, wait a moment, around the corner
If I don't, I'll do it again.
yes
[music]
I only have 10 pieces of meat.
I don't have 203 I have food.
I'm sorry that Jimochi-senpai died.
That's right, I wonder if it won't be revived?
Ramy's food someone's Akutan Super
Made by Akutan
It's inside the Nether, so let's go.
Thank you so much!
Via Rigozaza I have food, Ramy.
I went from my senior
Seriously, I received 303 pieces of food.
I wonder if 10 pieces of rice and meat will be enough?
I guess it's not much, then I'll give you some, senpai.
Wait a minute, I'll get some milk.
I wondered if it would be better to
I already brought an infinite number of cobblestones.
I'll share the seniors with you, okay?
Thank you so much for the cool black stone
I'll give it to you, thank you
Thank you half
I did the key
I'm sure you'll be okay, I'm sure.
It's okay, it's okay
[music]
Hey, I want a bow, but I got the bow at TT.
Is it better? Maybe it's possible without a bow.
Let's hit back, yeah, I don't have a bow either, I don't have a sword anymore
Let's go with the sword okay, I'm Oradabi Yumori
You can make one if you have one.
Yeah, it's okay, it's okay.
Good job, what's going on when you come back?
Oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
Wow, you're seriously coming at a tree from that distance.
What should I do to open my eyes?
The shrine maiden
I guess it's like the original, but now it's a blue pumpkin.
Even if I don't have a home like this, I'm okay with my head.
I'm wearing this that doesn't turn into a pumpkin.
I don't mind if I meet his eyes, that's true.
That's true, but Anya-san is no good.
If you look at him, he's probably looking at you.
So, everyone turn your head towards the ground. How many balls are you flying?
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
It's okay let's
Go Okara
I think someone with something like that could use it.
Nesenri Hinayuki
[music]
The popi holder I received from Su-chan
Toko
Yoisho Karets
go go let's go
Go, there are too many people, let's go.
let's go let's go
There are too many people, right?
Let's go, let's go, please go ahead.
Let's go let's go I see
The fortress is still that junior portal.
I've heard rumors that there is one nearby.
However, I had a junior close to TTT.
There was a portal, right? It was on that side.
do not have
only prepared
Available book
It's lame
It's a mess, that's helpful, isn't it?
trap
Is this you?
can go
Now, which way should I go? What should I do?
I think it's good that it hasn't been fully explored.
It's true, it's a little scary
Please go first
Thank you very much
[music]
Thank you so much here
I'm scared of this one, this one, and that one.
It's dangerous to dig, but the voice of the gust is loud.
If I don't kill the gust, then it's definitely a gust.
If you kill it, it becomes diamond diamond, so it's a gust.
It's very loud, but even when there's a lot of people
There are quite a few in the middle, so I'll do one line.
Good luck to your seniors who will take care of everything.
Do your best, do your best, Omatsu is coming.
Helpful, helpful equipment is thin, but it's okay
Anyway, my feet are fine, my feet are fine, money is.
I thought, oh, that's the entrance, oh that's the entrance.
It's possible, so it will sound like magma.
Wow, where is the fairy?
Is that the upper path? What kind of path is that?
That's different, that's different, isn't it?
There's something wrong with this.
It's different, but this is different, it's a different brick.
It's something like Rega.
I understand, I understand.
I understand, it's okay, Kanamiko-senpai and Hori Suru-senpai are Matsu.
Hey, you're doing this!
Is it dangerous? It's dangerous, it's dangerous
[music]
I understand, this is a good game
Yes!
let's go let's go
shift button
Saved from Let's Go
Denji Digi
[music]
It's true that the only job left now is to deliver messages.
What should I do? This can't be good. I have to do something.
teeth
Ria is saved, saved, collect this, collect this
I don't know what's going on
What is it, Pink Pink Pick Danger?
Pick Danger Pick Danger Pick
njajapickupic
deja pig
Oh no, are you okay?
[music]
[laughter]
Oshishi okay equipment
The more go-go equipment you have, the more you can go!
A solo horse is out, a horse is out!
[music]
What is this?
I see
Is that so?
[music]
Nai nai ah, there it is, right in front of me
Guy
Pick a fortress
To Takore
let's be a fortress
Mora
different
If you take photos of the orchestra, you'll definitely take screenshots.
Let's all join together, let's all join together.
We all watched Everyone's Futtle's Goft
Let's go screenshot
Screenshot self frets
[music]
I don't want to go, but it might be better later on. It's just a place.
Well, if you understand
[music]
This is Roston, which doesn't have any good things.
I wonder if I can go there.
[music]
It seems to be a little higher up though.
It seems a little dangerous, but I'm sure
You can go
It's my dog
[music]
Tanaru
IC I see.
It's 30 per person, so it's 1 person.
It's true that one person is in his 30s.
Go a little further and go to the side where you killed the gas
I want to, but it's scary gas here.
It might be a good idea to go and have a look.
No, the one on the left is closer to the one on the left. Going left.
Masu
Take it, you'll get a glowstone diamond.
There's a hole here in Gloston, so be careful.
Hey everyone
Good luck Glowstone
Just put it in, it's too springy and the inside falls out.
[music]
Thank you very much
Thank you, it's okay, I'll go
Zote
Tete
I'm so scared
Nopon seems scary but it's really scary
I can't say I'm scared.
Hey, there's a grotto right above it, but this
That's an IQ of 100. That's a little high.
I got a diamond for the twisted mushroom too.
I'll get a distorted mushroom as well.A distorted mushroom.
There are mushrooms, but be careful with those red ones too.
It's dangerous, isn't it? It's a little better than mini.
I went there and saw a red saw that was a distorted mushroom.
A distorted mushroom.A distorted mushroom is blue.
Are you going to call me blue, blue, and blue?
Hey, you're ignoring me, you're ignoring me, you're ignoring me.
You don't have to worry about it once, it's blue.
You get a little startled when I call you by your first name
Make sure you have enough time
[music]
Collect blocks around here
So scary
scared
Namiko is one-chan Miko is always
I wanted to go upstairs
Hey, I also have an infinite number of cobblestones, so that's it.
I can go
Collect this and go up
I'm going to the red forest.
[music]
Chauteru
Tethered
[music]
You can block it with four pieces, that's silk.
There was no touch.
[music]
Can I get the blowstone?
It only says that, so make it that way.
Just when I thought it was okay, I brought it home in powder form.
You can make a block out of it.
I feel like I can probably make it now.
I wonder if Glouston will be able to climb it?
Let's go for a while
I also need soul sand.Soul sand.
Oh, it's here! It's amazing, so please take it!
Please, please go get it.
Kakamito-san, let's go get the poop.
Is it possible to make anything better than this with your hands?
Yo four
Looks like I'll have to pick up something that's falling.
That's what I'm saying. It's raining. It's raining.
Yo
here is tomorrow
Tadeki
Who doesn't have roasted octopus?
I made it to Glouston.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, there is.
Oh, there's Glostone.
It's a waste, so is this okay for everyone?
It's okay, everyone get it, everyone get it
Nice, I need a sole sandwich too
That's right, Hapi. The easiest thing is sole.
Sandwich is okay
[music]
Thank you for coming from somewhere
Masu
Wait, I was surprised, it's alive, it's alive
Michi is alive, is alive, where did it fall from?
Forget about losing there.
[music]
If it weren't for diamonds, I'd die.
Tayomiko-chan
I think it would be better to have this and that instead of losing it.
I think it would be better if Miko-chan had it.
If this is dangerous, please drink it.
Oh, if it's too bad, please drink it, then I'll move on.
Huge
yes
Maybe it's better to go through the red forest.
I don't know
That's why I think I'd better go.
I tremble
It's a red forest, it's better to avoid it.
[music]
Yoshie, what should I do about this?
It's okay here
Are you okay
It's so safe and secure
Let's go, let's go. This place is empty now.
It's becoming
It's true
I'm that green one, all the green ones.
I have no choice but to do it
hey
Oh wait a minute Ina is fighting Ina what?
You're fighting, you're a sink girl, so it's different.
I'm fighting
The distorted mushroom should stay in the big green one.
It's true, it's true
It's amazing. Every single one is true. There are distorted keno.
You should also pick up those things that are growing.
I'm sure it will make you money
Let's stretch it out, the throw that stretched me out
Should I build some stairs there?
Maybe I should make this floor here.
It's possible to pass above this, but be careful.
I'm going to pass that way and go all the way there.
That's right, that's right, you're a bit of a pig.
If it's really too strong, I'll make it here as well.
It's true that there's a pig, a pig.
There's a boar, it's scary, so here it is
It might be better to go from there.
I don't know what to do.
A pretty strong pig
I have a bow, so I'll wait for the fight too.
I'm sorry God you're cleaning so much now.
Who is that?
Who is this? Maybe I'm the one who threw it.
I don't want to overload the lag with the lag.
It's getting worse, wait a minute
It's rag rag rag rag I'm alive
I'm alive, it's stuck in my butt
I did rug gu gu gu gu rug rug.
senior
Ah, maybe it's a lag. It's a lag.
this
push
Don't push it, don't push it, drop it
I had a good time.
It's too dangerous for me to play on the stairs.
That part will turn into magma, that's scary.
scary green mushrooms over there
I discovered that this time I feel like I'm in the prime of my life
I'm going to kill a pig, okay? That's not true.
Wait a minute, Lee is alone downstairs.
I'm too scared, should I do this from here?
It's not true, it's true, it's true.
pig
It's hot
From there
I can get off
Oh
Ooooooooo
[music]
Let's get on there
next
There's one behind Koacchi Baba.
I have to collect enough for everyone.
Cat, can we go in this tree? Okay, I'm here.
I can go from here if the road is extended.
Where is everyone? Wait, Gust's voice will kill you.
Do you want to kill Gust? Gust's voice
If all the killer ghasts kill one
That's enough
Kamosa is the only one who hasn't written anything yet.
Chan looks like he's all one body.
Is it possible to confirm it with certainty?
It's really scary, why is it only 1 piece?
It's great individually
Thank you, Senpai, for giving me one.
I don't have any more blocks
Shall I ask you a favor?
Just a little ahead
Please block me and I'll go.
I'll bring some text. Is it okay?
Hiroko Hishiko Yaba Hiroko is waiting for Kasae
Come back blue
It's okay, it's okay, it's the best, it's the best
duty
[music]
grass
Should I cut straight through?
This is quite red in the red forest.
All I can do is walk slowly, passing over the mushrooms.
I can't run out of it. There's one more. There's one more.
I'm passing by. This guy's life is too light.
How to make a lever in the nether
I'll do my best, so I can't do it.
Right, I'll wait for you, I'll give it to you, Senpai.
I'll give it to you because it's a little scary
I'll drop it in that safe place, that's right.
If you drop it, pick it up again
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but I'll put it next to you.
Sorry, it's a bit scary around here.
I want it to be a little deeper
Isn't it better not to do it?
It's better not to do this over there.
There was some, so I grabbed some.
That's great! Keep up the momentum!
Okay, I'm going really far.
be
[music]
Right uah yeah okay blue uah yeah fell blue okay
I want to fall blue, I want to fall blue.
I'm there, go home
There are 2 of these, I'll give you 2 of them.
There are two more left, at least one pig.
There are pigs, so if you can defeat the pigs, you'll be fine.
[music]
Buttaga
all
That time I went straight away.
It's okay
I feel like Naikogune is good.
[music]
It's almost time to block
No bi
The box block is almost gone.
[music]
Rely on this
Narumo block
No, I wonder if this is okay.
do not have
[music]
Something like that
Oh, are you okay? It's okay, everyone.
Create a block of gratitude.
[music]
That doesn't make sense, right?
I don't think there's a need to go to Akakino.
It ends here
This this mushroom world mushroom world mushroom world
It's also the first time I've heard of green mushrooms.
Oh, there's also soul sand, soul sand.
I want to collect them
I'll go back once in a while, so
Thank you very much and do your best
I did my best and got a mushroom.
It's okay, Mr.
Ah, are mushrooms okay? Are they okay?
Thank you very much. Good luck.
do your best
Please, that person is a dog.
It's a dog
Hey, pig, pig is on the bridge.
It's okay, it's okay, I killed it, I killed it, I killed it.
dead dead dead
[music]
Let's squeak
That's dangerous, isn't it?
Senpai, any number of sole sandwiches should be fine.
Maybe I should get some soul sand.
No, what's the target? Mission target?
Soul sand is included in this mission.
I guess that's right, there's only one.
It's okay to have one piece at a time
There weren't any, so that's scary.
It's dangerous. You fell too boldly.
Isn't it okay?
Let's predict who will die today.
So who will die today?
I guess that's who'll die first in the movie.
But I don't think Ao will die unexpectedly.
Do you think you'll survive till the end?
Survival, right? About 23.
It's okay now that you took it, right? It's kind of horror.
The type that looks blue in the movie is usually the last one.
Survive until the end, survive at all
This is something out of a horror movie
Wait a minute, what a surprise
[music]
I made a water flow elevator using this.
Come back!
Shio
[music]
oh
Wait a minute, wait a minute, it's okay, it's okay
It's totally fine. And Iooo, yes.
I went, okay, let's go. It feels really open.
It's spacious and open.
what
wow what kind
It's too bad, but I'm going to climb up.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, if you go to the top, this is the one in the back
It's scary, right? Is it the other way around? Yes, it's the other way around.
I don't know what's going on and I'm scared. Wait, wait.
It's scary, it's scary, it's really scary By the way, what is it?
but
Yes, it's scary by the way
Emiko's
Intuition goes up and up, it's like magma is falling
Thinking about coming, I went over there.
the soil is green
Eh, somehow the soil over there has turned a little green.
I guess that's it, green and red shaped terrain.
That's right, green terrain is no good.
Hey, it's not even in the green area.
Yes, I have to avoid that area.
Oh no, close, close, close, very important, very important, certainly
It's important to close your eyes, Anya-senpai is holding a torch.
Leave it to me to do it
It's scary
Hey, it's scary, it's scary, it's scary, ok
Yay yay
[music]
Hey, this is a pig in my stomach, yes it's behind me.
Not what's scary behind here here
Here you are
[music]
Are you okay?
It's the red forest
Other than that, I don't like anything else.
Kanade
What do you think? What do you think?
I shouldn't cross this to the left. This left.
red
Well, even if I go straight, there won't be anything.
No, it's a bit scary
I can't see what's ahead so I'm not going
Then it's better to go left and go straight.
I see, you can see a little bit of that once.
Well, if you have the courage, go straight
Even my little finger is holding my little finger
I'm sure you're holding it down with your little finger.
I'll take a look at the half block.
Okay, then we'll all go.
I think it's going to happen, isn't it?
If you say that, I'll follow you when you die.
teeth
We're in Dangerous Bridge together.
Dangerous
[music]
Will Rita return on the bridge?
Isn't it clear? There's a slight shadow on the left or the tip of the left.
I can see
There's a forest here, and there's something beyond the forest.
Masuyo
The one on the right probably has a forest behind it.
If I go straight to
It looks like there's something real on the other side
I don't think there is one over there.
Hey, wait a minute, let's prepare the blocks.
Certainly please, Bro Micone, quite now
I'm just wandering around, so I guess that's it.
Kasoumoi
On the way home
Let's just follow this way home
Yes, it's true that the road looks like an artificial object.
I'll leave it there
Wow, I almost got home without getting lost.
I mean, blue is really strong in terms of terrain, it's strong.
It's so strong, I really don't want it, it's serious
Seriously blue, blue for swords, seriously.
Kuadeku is amazing, so it's a little different.
Please leave it to me
I'm getting worried and worried.Wait a minute.
I'm starting to worry about it. It's a break. It's a break.
This way, this way, this way, this way, the gust
I'm going to make a sound, but it's about time.
There may come a time when we have to fight
Maybe it's okay
If not, maybe I'm not good at reading stairs.
It came out. There's a little noise. Pigs are scary, aren't they? Pigs.
Open it a little, open it! Oh, I'm scared, I'm scared.
everywhere
Let's open it. I'm feeling a little ok.
Cat, I understand, I'm scared.
I found a green tree near me.
One mushroom per person
It certainly looks like it. I only have 4 of them.
It's not in there. Thank you for doing your best to collect it. It's dangerous here.
As expected, it's just a little far away.
This might be a bit far, so wait and see.
hand
Look, mushrooms aren't there yet.
I'm collecting them for people who don't have them. Yeah, that's scary.
scary scary scary scary
[music]
Come on
Pig, Pig, wait a minute, the pig makes a pig sound.
pig's voice pig's voice
Pigs!
Oh wait, I'm shooting something. I'm shooting something.
I found it very reliable, Chiara.
Nea
[music]
Oh, nice, nice, wait, I'll die instead
[applause]
[music]
Dangerous death is too close to home, Dangerous death here
Short
Come back home with your baby
Go home properly
Let's have a pig, a pig, a pig, a pink pig.
It's coming, it's coming, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
a little bit
Wait, wait!
death
death and death manufacturing confirmation manufacturing confirmation manufacturing confirmation dying
I'm alive I'm alive
alive
Seriously
I'm still awake, but I feel like I'm still alive
I got scared because it was okay.
Good length
It's okay, it's okay, it's really nice, do it now
No matter who you are, let's have fun and only have a sword.
I don't have one, so I'll do this.
Ta
Wow, you are so helpful.
It was a real key panic.
There are a lot of times when I think I'm going to die, so there are a lot of times when I think I'm going to die.
Maybe it's true
But for some reason, it's nice to be alive.
I'm so glad it was so good
Takore is infinite
I want a bow like that forever, right?
I have it, it's dangerous, yes, it's dangerous
The ones with dangerous bows are Chiara, Ina, and others.
What do you have? A bow.
As expected
What should I do? Do I want one? It's broken.
I have a bow for hanging, but I need another one.
What the hell is this here magma mama mama mag
A Koji Zone that looks like Deja Danger Zone
Deja zone, go straight to the sky
We can go straight to Masukagu.
It seems like everyone else is watching too.
Aja Subaru road with blocks and blocks
Shall we pull it? Hey here, magma.
Apparently, Miya is a little broken.
If so, I have one more.It looks like it's going to go somewhere.
I have it, so I guess it's time for me to die.
When I die, I'm sure it's already gone, wait.
hand
At that moment of danger,
When I run out of gas, I run away.
Maybe all I can do is light a fire
Maybe the only thing you can do is fight back
No, if I could throw back the fire, I would be strong and perfect.
It would be dangerous if Yokokosa came in. It's normal.
It's definitely digital
Nice nice thank you very much.
That's too much, I'm grateful
Thank you so much
Before I knew it, I was in Netherrack.
It's getting crowded now
Hey, it's okay, you won't get lost.
I remember the way, right?
How
Somehow I understand, maybe it's okay somehow
Somehow I wonder if it will happen
I can see that it hits me physically
Hey, I might be a little worried.
It's true, it sounds like a pig.
Go, there's money, money, money, pigs, pigs, noses.
Senkyuu
I don't understand Senkyu.
For now, it's Ghost Rate, Ghost.
I'm sure the rate is good
to
Gorse, what should we do? Open a hole and get some magma.
If that happens, you should definitely run away.
Block it up
[music]
Yeah, but it's like it's going through a wall or something.
There's a bit of this. It's connected to something.
Yeah, I don't think this is connected somehow.
It's true, it's making some strange noises.
There's a strange sound.It's strange.
Sounds Mysterious sounds What kind of sounds are they?
Maybe it's open, wait, stop the sound.
stop stop strike
Too much lol everyone
Stoi Niner Attack Iner Attack
It's not good now
Takuo, seriously, I'm so grateful.
I laugh about things like flights, but somehow
Please give me caviar tender, please, in a loud voice.
Attention please, a big helpful voice
But it's still a forest, it's still a forest, the forest is too deep, it's red.
Right, it's red, red, red, it's too red, it's flying
This squishy light-like thing is red
It's that red color, right? It's not red at all.
There are a lot of reds that I can't escape from.
Wide
Hey, Ina, I found the fortress.
[music]
Is it okay?
It's amazing that he has all subjects. I say all subjects, but all episodes are
That's different.
I wanted to say that I can rely on you.
That's not it, Red Red Forest.
Red Frest Red Frest Red
Leave it to me, Forest voice, please leave it to me.
Please Koahonmaya Red
[music]
Forest Red Frest Agaiariino
Oh, there's a mushroom. Wait, is there one time? 1
I think I can go get this.
Blue is not blue
[music]
hair
You have too much flying momentum, don't you?
It seems like it's that durable.
It's not a good thing, right? Diamond equipment.
Come back, come back, come back
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm eating food.
I'll just put up some pine trees here and there.
It's okay if you don't have enough Matsu.
Thank you, I still have my house.
There's still plenty left, so that's a relief.
Okay, okay, that helps.
[music]
Okay, there are 7 of us right now.
Wait a minute, it's scary, it's scary, it wasn't right at first
There are so many mushrooms.
The number of mushrooms
There are 123,456 minutes.
Now we have enough mushrooms for all of you.
Takita Noko Mushroom Mushroom Clear Mushroom
mushroom
Clear If no one dies, it'll be perfect
But stop it, Ah-san, that's scary.
Don't say it, but the stairs are amazing.
It looks like this, it's so spacious, it's not popular.
It's so cute, hey hey hey look, someone is there
It's definitely us
Oh, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back
It's coming. It's there.
Hey, come back in the comments
I mean, I'm back. I'm back.
I'm back
I don't know if I should go back now, but it looks like a fortress.
The only thing I found was mushrooms.
Now, if this thing dies, it'll be a joke.
I don't have any, so I'll just deliver some mushrooms.
I also went to Glowstone and Gust.
Well, I'm pretty sure I can go to this area.
And I don't think there's a gust, Emiko-san.
That's the road I was thinking of going on just now.
It's a straight place that you can take a quick look at.
The cat is a bit straight, probably with Gusto.
It's just a fortress. A fortress is fine.
Is it just Gust? What kind of fortress is it?
It's dangerous to take out a kitten.
It's not a sighting of Notoma Fortress, it's just a sighting.
Just because I saw it, it's okay. Chat because I saw it.
reading
I don't want to go to 4 years old depending on how interesting the chat is.
That's right. Just look at it.
That's fine, I'll be the first to discover it.
Well then, it's dangerous here, I'm surprised.
I'm surprised, I'm surprised
Surprise, surprise, it's really gust
What can you do today just by defeating Gust?
It's over. We're doing this as a team.
It's not just one person, it's a team.
What the heck? Maybe that's the case with the team.
I defeated it, so it doesn't seem like it's over. I defeated it as a team.
Isn't it okay to just do it, everyone?
Maybe I'm suffering from hay fever, but I'm going to stop by today.
I've been playing Minecraft since noon, so I'm sure too.
It's almost time for it to end
The time has come for me to really show off.
There are people here who should fall down like blue.
Are you going to fall or do it there?
Yeah, either way is fine, everyone should be pretty early
I don't need the nether that I've been doing since time though.
Why don't you just say it's important, Ao?
Well then, Gust, what should I do here?
Naede but gust one chan, that's it, go back
I thought he might be somewhere, so I just followed him.
I heard some gusts over there.
I'm sure this is just Wachigust.
If you defeat it, you can definitely do it in the Nether.
Where did that go? It's okay, it's okay, this is it
It's down here. It's scary. It makes a pig's voice.
I'm scared of the pig's voice.There's a match here.
It's a match
But what is this road? It's not here, it's someone's
What is this, what is this road, whatever is down there?
This is probably the path Miko-senpai is currently trying to develop.
That's right, that's right, that's right, that's right
Okay, if I go down to the left here, that's right.
Is it okay to pokotto ooi around here?
here
[music]
Wait, the pig is coming, the pig is coming, the pig is waiting!
Waiting for it
Yaba
I'm coming back, I'm coming back, I'm coming back
Kukocchi is coming to the top
go back up
Return
Because it does
[music]
Go back, are you okay? Come, come, come here quickly.
Let's come all the way here
Kun
Are you okay too?
[applause]
I'm glad I came this far.
Good, thank you very much
Thank you very much
You're even better
Don't worry, I have a bow and arrow, so feel free to do so.
Ba
Open the one above where you can kill me.
If you give it to me, I can aim like this from here.
Can I go?
Singing to the left, this is to the left, wait, from there
I can see it here. I can't see it. I can't see it.
I'm going crazy from here
[music]
There's definitely a Karae, wait, there's only one.
There may be some gorillas who said, This is not going away.
Hey gorilla, it's Mori.
Wait a minute, then I'll go out for a while.
Look, everyone should step back a little!
Okay, okay, okay, show me.
[music]
It's on top of Kuruko, on top of this, on top of this, on top of this.
You're on top of this, okay, okay, bow, bow, bow.
in
It's okay, this is true
Wait, where are you?
Is it okay to be there?
You
Nice nice nice too nice nice
It's over, it's over, it ended in a very nice book
I thought it was over for a bit.
Wait, it's dangerous here, it's seriously dangerous here.
I'm glad I have fingers
We're separated. We're separated. We're separated.
But I want to stretch that part, huh?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's dangerous, dangerous, dangerous.
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming back
Go back, go back, this guy is fine, he's coming.
It's okay, it's okay, hello, excuse me.
death
I thought it was seriously blowing up
[music]
Hold on, they're gone
But seriously, here and there
This is the time to go home, this is truly a real time.
Let's stretch this to the limit a little bit.
That's right, I said I want to grow this.
It's true that there are no people who have gone before.
Wait a minute, this is hidden.
Damn, I prefer half blocks.
It's better to stretch it out with half-length hair, but this
Okay, let's wait a moment.
I'm completely separated from my group.
Should I wait and do it anyway?
road
where where where
Separated
I'm getting separated from my destination.
Are you okay?
I feel like I'm separated, but that's not what I'm talking about.
But that means I went back even further.
This is where I was fishing, right? I'll come to my destination and pick you up.
I went
Even if you can't come to pick me up?
I'm coming to pick you up. I'm already home. I'm going home.
I guess that's the way to go, but I'm half-hearted.
Even at the block, here and there
It wasn't here, it wasn't here now.
No, maybe this is what's going on here.
I thought Subaru was talking about this too, but I can't hear it.
I thought it was here too, but now I'm looking over here.
I'm lying, but no matter what, he can't come.
I'm so happy I'm scared of pigs
The volume of Sugi is too scary.
Apparently he's up ahead
Apparently this isn't the place, the destination is here.
I thought it wasn't there, it's definitely here.
I thought so, but should I go further?
Wait further, it's a green forest
Hey, did you find the green forest?
There was a time when it was a green forest. It was a green forest.
I didn't notice it. It's a green forest. It's a green forest.
If you stretch it over here, you'll get one shot.
Looks like it's on the left side
It's true, have you ever found a green forest?
It was a red forest, it was always red.
I didn't notice it, did you notice it too?
I didn't notice it wasn't there
It's just that, this is a one-chan green forest
There is
All you have to do is find the coordinates of where the green forest is.
It's not the coordinates. It's blue.
I guess I found Gusto.
I found Gusto at the beginning.
Ah, I'm going to the coordinates. Yes, it's the coordinates.
372 Wait, there's no gas coming here either.
I got it
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, it's close
No, I'll just go back to the hole once. I'll wait here.
Where should I go?
I think I'll go inside this hole once. Wait.
Oh, are you taking that?
Yes, there is a gust, right?
On the way home, I could definitely hear the sound of someone there.
Wait, wait, wait
I can't beat this, so I hit 34 for 302 tomorrow morning.
302's 3 yes 302's
I'm at 34
But please let me know
Yes, I'm in the good place.
Egas and I can use this together.
Here's the ghast to defeat the ghast
Andmaou-kun has a bow, and we use swords.
It takes 33 people to subjugate this, so it takes 3 people, 3 people.
Do you want to subjugate it? I have one more bow, so it's far away.
If it's too much
Well, over here
I decided to hand over the bow for the subjugation.
I'll take a look at this eggplant. Here's another code.
Different code here, different code here
I think it's good too.
There's a Yankee, there's a Yankee, when we meet those eyes
It's so dangerous, that's right, that's right.
I'm here
I want to wear a pumpkin but I'm far away
If it seems too much, I'd wear a hat too.
Oh my goodness
[music]
If this is too far into the future, I just went there
The future is too far ahead, the future is too far away
Too much future Amiko postpones the path
I quit
There is a half block where there is a half block.
The future is so far away, it's scary
Sure, the future is too far, the future is too far, a green forest
hey
Even though I'm scared, I just said goodbye to the place where we just broke up
It's not a separate place.
I can hear the voice of a very Yankee voice
Yankee is terrible
It's 2cm tall and a little on the right.
The place where Ire fell higher than the Yankees
There's a lot of people on our right.
There are so many people, it's so scary, there are so many people
There are about two of them, no, they live in the green forest.
Ki 2 It's not dangerous. Wait a minute.
Wait, come on!
Wait, I'm following you even though I can't see you
There's something wrong with my eyes
Before, it was right in front of me, it's okay
There's gas here and there too, but Miko.
Chiki Senpai Miko Senpai Kore Mikochi Mate
How is Miko-senpai and Chiara together?
33 groups are currently separated.
Emiko-senpai, who is breaking up with
Teru Kikiara and I say something is gust.
Probably because Chiara and Lee were together.
I thought Temiko-senpai was with Chiara.
I completely understand that, then this
Even if it's all over here, it's all over here
I think I found a way back, right?
Yes, go here.
If you go this way and then turn right, you'll be on your way back.
Hey, I see.
This cat seems dangerous.This one seems dangerous.
Yeah, I remember this, I remember this.
This is on my way home. I'll go back for a while.
Gus and I'm probably going to beat it up now, Miko.
Chan, I wonder where he is in the forest over there.
But where did they say that the pigs are probably dangerous?
I'm not in Mikomori because I'm in Mikomori.
To
There's a green forest there, and it's a gast.
Understood Gust Understood Gust Wait a minute.
I heard the sound of gas.
The gas that was being targeted at that moment.
It might be gone, right here.
Well, let's break up now and live our lives separately.
I think it would be better to go home.
Well then, it's impossible for us to meet, it's impossible for us to meet.
So I'm going to go kill some ghasts and then go home.
Where is Gusto's Bogi heading from now?
Where is Chiara heading now?
Terua is on his way now
I'm waiting for Jamiko-senpai to discover the gust.
I saw a momentary glimpse of Gusto.
Play with Mikoto Aja, who has an upward voice.
Ask me what happened when I met up with Arenemi.
First, let's talk about what happened after breaking up with Kia.
Let's listen, but then I'll listen to what happens next.
It's better to decide.
Mikochi is here now
Well, it's probably not moving because it's trying to merge.
It's better, I understand, I understand
I almost killed a one-chan gust.
That's how I feel, a gust is right in front of me
Don't breathe with the feeling of hitting a cod
Gust's voice is really loud though, Gust now.
Isn't it from the right? I heard a voice from the right.
But I did it from the right. I did it from the right.
Whoa, whoa, who's on the top right, top right
There's probably an open gust on top of that.
Right in front of you, Gusto is right in front of you.
I understood this before, it's so bad
dangerous
No, Gust is right in front of that.
too far
There was a senior-like name on it, seriously.
I'm probably on that floating island. I'm on that floating island. I'm on that floating island.
There is at least one person in
If that's the case, Miko-senpai will win.
Which of the seniors is probably being targeted by Gust?
Maybe you're on the right It's better not to turn to the right
That Ender is on the right side.
in front
I'm Gusto's senior in front of Gusto.
Hey, I went upstairs.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, it's too bad
That guy is dangerous.
[music]
I saw you for a second, but are you okay?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
But it's too dangerous now
What kind of Yankee is this yankee?
give it to yankee to yankee to yankee
Give it to the Yankee, give it to him.
Just wait one more time, I wonder where I am now?
Endermen cannot enter areas 2 meters high.
It seems safe to stay here.
That's right, if the worst happens, come in here.
That kick, right?
I heard Nemikochi is okay. She's upstairs.
come up to
Ta
I'm halfway there, and I'm on my way now, but I'm only half way there.
The half and half I'm heading towards now is the one above me.
Who is it? I can see it from the ridge.
I can see you on top 3147
I can't see it now.
There is no person who said that there is a description distance on the description
Not 35 Ogami wears diamond clothes
There was a man in diamond clothes and a head of gold.
I thought it might be Shrine Maiden-senpai because she looked like her.
But Nanemiko-senpai's mind isn't about money.
Who is that? It has to be Emiko Kin.
That's not who I think Chiara is, Miko-senpai.
Maybe because I don't like
It's not like there's someone else on top.
I can't go there, please go with the pig.
[music]
It seems like Subaru and his friends are going to Gusto to pick them up.
Do you want to go there? Please tell me the coordinates to pick you up.
I'll go pick you up or go the other way. It's getting dangerous.
Let's kick this one too. It's the worst.
Understood, can I kick it? I'm going to pick you up.
We are with Miko-senpai.
I'm with Mikoto, but now we're breaking up.
I'm looking for Chiara Chiara Senpai too.
It seems that everyone is Miko, Chiara.
Apparently they're together. That's bad.
He met me once when we first broke up.
Will everyone come together?
Go back to the beginning once and go back to the last point
At the very end, I'm so excited
Come back, okay? Well then, here we are.
Everyone who said they were going back
I just went back to where I fell apart.
He asked me if I could come over there once.
It's okay if you type it in English.
I was wondering if I could come if I could.
Tokona
The swollen area is just beyond the point.
That's right, I met up with Amikochi Ina.
Good, good, good
Tae then what should we do for the first time?
It's better to go back. I'll go back once.
It's better to be there first than to be here.
Well, that's where it splits at the end.
Well, that was the exit after all.
That's right, if you go this way you'll find the exit.
At the end of the first one, everyone died.
Eh, it's in the Piglin's fortress, isn't it?
But we found it first
Zoyo
It's sad, but I just found that one.
I was told to go there, but I found it in a different place.
Maybe someone on our team will say it.
That's what he was giving me.
It seems like it's going to go.
It seems that it is true
Okay, let's go there for now, I guess.
There are three people.
die
It looks like they're going, so let's go back too.
Are you going?
[music]
It's a little too big. It's okay. Ah, what about blue?
It's pretty cool.
Let's go back, let's go back, Louis is dead.
It's dangerous here, wait, there's a pig.
Wait a minute, please quietly press right, right, right.
Let's do it right
It's so full, stop being so blue, go back once, once.
I'll come back once and I'll come back once.
It's found, it's found, it's found
I found it. I went home. I went home.
Come in, come in, come in, no, no, no, here.
I can kill you if you get there, but I'm sure it's here.
Come on, it's 1 square here.
The blue Subaru will be in the cage, so leave it to you.
Okay, wait for the future, please wait.
Wait, do you mean here with a bow?
I don't have an escape bow, so I'm seriously asking for one.
Please, if you die here, we will too.
I'm pretty close to death
Come in, come here, come here, come here.
When I know it's no good or no good, I run away.
I know it's coming, it's coming, it's coming
It's coming, it's coming, it's here, it's here, it's squatting here.
A little bit of a little bit of a battle guess
Looks like I'll get it right in battle.
Why are we together? Oh yeah, Subaru-senpai.
It hurts when I lowered it a little.
It stings, it stings
That's a blue sting, that's a sting.
That's it, it's more, it's more, it's more, it's more, it's more and more.
Also earlier, earlier, earlier, oh, this, this, this.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Dangerous nice nice nice nice
Nice hoi oh
Nice, I have another one okay, I'll bring it.
Hey, I'm going a little far, so my butt
I'm looking at you right now, wondering if I can go now.
If I guess I'm scared of the one next to me that I can go to,
If a bad guy wins, a bad guy wins.
Wait a minute, that's dangerous.
height
Looks like it's going to be crazy
There are still some of them.
There are so many people in the world.
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here
nice nice
Nice pain ah, are you okay? It's okay
Go ahead
Nice one more one nice one more oh
Wait a mile please wait oh
Okay, let's go fishing for a little while and recover a little.
I hope so.
I'm coming, please do it.
It's coming
Teru
It's so good that I'm definitely going to die, so painful
It hurts, wait, wait, I'll cut it.
Subaru is cool
Senpai is in danger Onice is in danger Senpai is definitely stabbing me
It's stuck in the wrong place
Wait a minute I look like Cupid
That Chiara, that Chiara stuck in your chest
Kirata is somehow a portal
I'm back. Okay, then go back.
Well then, we and I will go back too.
Do you want to go back?
Well, senpai portal is that exit?
So that's the exit, right?
There's a group car ahead, yeah, yeah, I guess.
The way home is not here. The way home is here.
I made a staircase right there.
Follow this path until you can't get off the ground.
It's so scary
sticky gastogatoga
Gust wait
Oh no, I have no choice but to go from this side.
Wait a minute, let's kill the gas for a second.
Let's kill the gas, let's kill the gust.
Wait a minute, the field is small here.
Isn't it too much?
I was surprised to see it there.
Gust, isn't the field a bit too small?
It's not too much. If you're going to go now, just cross over.
We have no choice but to fight in a wide field.
Wait, Su goes first, is that cool?
I'll take it out once
Eat lots of rice
Lots to eat
[music]
Wait a minute, where's the gas?
Those who contacted Sanmiko and others just once
Look, that blue Subaru Subaru and the others are at war.
I knew from that that if we were going to break up, we would have to do it first.
If you have any questions, please let me know.
Something
Let's get along and get along
[music]
Thank you so much, I really appreciate it.
Let's make this place spacious. Yes, there's something here.
That's dangerous, right?
[music]
Is it too scary? Nether, wait a minute, yes, okay.
He was about to disappear again.
Is it good? It looks like it will disappear soon.
Gusto that guy is planting
Wait, come on, come on.
If you ride that thing, you can walk on magma.
Hey, what's your name, Kill?
I heard a voice saying "ru"
It's a bit far, maybe it's a bit far I'm back
I think he heard a noise.
I heard a sound from a little far away, so I was scared.
Well then, I'll go home soon.
I couldn't see anymore so I said sure, shall I go home?
Let's go home now. I lost the sound.
He just makes a sound and heads towards me for the rest of his life
Don't come, go home
Wow
Let's go
All right.
First of all, let's eat mushrooms with Mr. Sawatari.
Yeah mushrooms for everyone
I have to give it to you, so I can't die.
Well, we should write in that book.
Yes, that sounds like the worst thing. Yes, it's dangerous.
here
dangerous
It's dangerous here. This is the right road.
The one who made this road
It's dangerous because I made it. It's pretty dangerous.
Dangerous!
scary and dangerous
[music]
I'm too scared to go home
If you're scared, it's bad. Wait there.
For those of us who can't go, I want you to build a wall.
Maybe it's too dangerous next to the chair
a little bit
Wait, wait a minute, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, if you have a wall to keep you from falling, you can get out.
There's no wall. Wait a minute. It's dangerous.
Block, hey, I have it, you can take it.
Yes 64 Ah, that helps.
If there is a wall, I made a mistake, I made a mistake with the wrong diamond sword.
Throw it away
It's like a wall, okay, okay.
Wait, I thought of a damn good thing, right here.
[music]
Why don't you try making something like this?
It would be dangerous if I hit it from here.
The side walls here and there are scary, so this is the only wall.
I'll make it, oh, I'll make it on my side, I'll build a house.
It's too dangerous
Why are you here on this road?
It's crazy that you're saying you'll wait.
You can hit this
[music]
It's already getting dangerous
Tara
[music]
Are you okay? Everyone is asking.
Terue fell down, I guess I can go now.
No, go, go, go, go, I fell.
Look at the fallen chatro
Is it okay? But I'm still going. Half block
I'm stuck with you. I'll go pick you up.
enemy
Too many misplaced things over there
I understand the half block, it goes back and forth.
back and forth
If you're there
Okay okay okay
I'm so glad we did it. We'll be together for the rest of our lives.
I thought I couldn't do it.
I wonder if there are stairs near the entrance.
Made
Did you come up and wait for me?
No, I'm really glad.
Hey, I'm glad that things are going to work out somehow.
Zene
Airu
Michimiko
I don't see your senior's name at all, but he really is there.
Where are you?
Takashi
Wait, wait, wait, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
Danger, danger, danger here
It was dangerous, but it was really good, Emiko and Miko.
I've already been to some interesting places.
The communication was completely different, yeah, seriously.
We've passed each other, but we've all really passed each other all our lives.
Gus ran away, Gus.
It's gone, isn't it?
Gust finally reached that goal
That's the last place we broke up
I guess that's the case, so I'll move on.
That's just a mortal thing
I didn't say it was, but it's a little blue.
Can you just let me deliver the mushrooms for now?
Hey, hey, I guess he's going back to Seoul.
Sandwich yes ooooooo
Oh, I'm heading home from there, after all.
I guess they're connected, after all, this is a dangerous pig.
It was terrible, seriously, but Mimi and Momi both died.
That's what I thought, but Se-chan is there.
Let me do it.
Please, please, O-kun is here, he's not here.
It's not coming here, go back, go back, go back, go back
It's not here. Wait, wait, wait.
It's dangerous here
[music]
It's a dangerous lie
[applause]
[music]
You're so relaxed, aren't you?
It's the second time, so wait a minute.
This is my second time so I won't be coming back.
It's not coming back anymore.
girlfriend
[music]
[applause]
My colleague
[music]
Seniors Areou-kun, Oukun, Kochiou-kun
Akochikao
O-kun, there are a lot of them.
Kuku, no, no, no, no, it's okay
Thank you for the length
[music]
Nice like this
I wanted to protect it
If I killed that pig faster, everyone would die.
May the strength of the nanoko
I wouldn't have come here with such equipment.
[music]
It's not my fault, it's my fault.
There's no such thing.
I don't have a bow and arrow like this
Don't worry about it
[music]
Maybe
I only count my losses
[music]
Survive up to Nagaru's senior who counts machetes
It seems like there is only one
Hey, he lived well, he lived well.
I lived a good life. If I hadn't gotten so angry, I would have been like that.
thing
I died without dying.
Hama is
[music]
The pig's voice again
I can hear it, I'm scared of pigs, I'm hungry
eating food
O
Pig Pig Pig please please
Oh here
It's dangerous
It's dangerous, it's still there, it's still there, we can't let our guard down
I'll make you some dangerous roast pork.
It's Zoshiadeko's road.
It's dangerous to go home, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, wait.
It's dangerous, but it's just a normal boy.
Yokochi
This way, this way, the door, this way, this way, Miko
Senpai here
Okay okay okay ah
I'm coming back
Senior
senior
[music]
There is such power
If I had the power, I would have the power
Tarako bye bye
Let's be ugly
Subaru-senpai's grave is set here.
Let's build Subaru Senpai's grave here.
Masho-chan's flower stand
flower
[music]
Hey, I can't stand up anymore.
Tahoho
Ho
Oh, isn't it a little more beautiful?
That's a lie, I left that too.
Yeah, I'll put up a sign.
Subaru is getting crazy
senior
Woman, it's okay if I have the power, it's okay, woman.
I don't have to bother with the red one.
fire
Wow
cod a little more red red mushroom
If there is a red mushroom it
This is the last one, but this is it.
Oh yeah this
[music]
If so, thank you, I got this from Su-chan.
I will die with care for diamonds
Hey, I'm going to die
Hey, I'm already dead, Shideno. I can't make a sound anymore.
It's okay to do this
Isn't it a bit misleading to wait?
May I die
[music]
Chan
of
[music]
There's no way
There's a nether boat, but it's a nether boat
want
I've been trying to live as long as I can.
What are you going to do? I'll tell you.
I can't
[music]
Tell me what you were doing when you got home
Find 7 diamonds from Ze with Yosapsa.
Tare
It's a scary world with no boundaries
good
hey
Ah
Takore is different
[music]
Is there a place here? Wasn't it there?
I haven't found it yet.
I needed the piglin from earlier, so I used the piglin.
I found it
But there's no, this is so naked
Then I'll compile one and write one for everyone.
Chamo senpai swimsuit
Kachamo senpai
Hello, are you okay, Senpai, Senpai, all together?
Mushrooms and those mushrooms and sand.
Is it a fortress? Thank you.
Fortresses too, fortresses and mushrooms and that and that.
I don't know why, it looks mysterious, glow
[music]
stone glow stone glow stone
glow stone yeah yeah glow
Stone, Nether and Mushrooms, Here Comes the Nether
A fortress, a Nether fortress. Can't you defeat the ghasts?
It's too much, Ahacha too
Both Senpai-cha and Senpai-Acha are like this.
What kind of clothes do you wear?What kind of clothes do you wear?What kind of clothes do you want?
It goes beyond the level of the concept.
Senpai
Something
It looked like crap, that's it, that's it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait
[music]
Chichi chichi
Eh, wait
Stop it, hide, hide and go to sleep
picture
Hey, let's go to bed here.
a little bit
How about I avoid this? I can't put that anymore.
From the back like this, from the feet like this
Looks like Nikon
Naea, here it comes, here it comes, please give me one more person
Bye
Good, this is good, good, good.
Okay okay okay okay okay this is it
Being beaten quickly
Yo okay okay
Okay 5
Month 16 Wait, are they changing this year?
No, that's not it. That's that.
MissionMissionFor everyone
Thank you for the mission thank you thank you
Thank you for the mission.
Thank you Kiraina Anya is amazing
Miko Miko Senpai also Senpai Miko
Kia Senpai, Kia Senpai, I saw the fortress with Senpai.
Yes, we have seen the fortress. Yes, Aku-senpai.
It's not included, but I just saw it with you.
That's the only way I see it, so I guess that's the only way I see it.
From Inanis
Senpai, Inanis is in a difficult situation.
Senpai's weird typing
Oseeekore
what
vinegar
senior
Eato
Hamiko-senpai Ah, my senior has become a senior.
Well, I guess I should include A-senpai as well.
Seniors, seniors, seniors, seriously, this senior is not coming back.
brain
[music]
Ashii
Thats Senpai, Senpai, Senpai, Suba-senpai.
The boy I changed, the boy I changed
Don't forget about yourself, about yourself
Forget what I forgot, I almost forgot.
Oh no, no, this is the mission!
I'll do the mission tomorrow
I can get diamonds, I can get diamonds, but tomorrow
There's a diamond in my rocker, soul
Sand comes in
Yeah yeah soul sandwich
Yes, tomorrow the diamond will be mine
stone distorted
Thanks for the mushrooms, please apply.
Of course, Tamiko also attends university.
[music]
This is big, this is all glowstone
There are people who haven't received it, there are people who haven't received it, I have it.
Did I have a Graston?
be
Yes, it's Grosstorm. Thank you, Aoku.
This is it. I'm sure there's no mistake. Just put it here.
It's okay, don't worry, let's defeat Gust.
Give me a sword sandwich for Tanagast.
Of course of course
[music]
This is because I'm so excited
There's a soul sandwich on the side
And nice, here are the mushrooms.
I'm throwing away things like thank you, I'm me
I'm sure it's okay, I'll check the mushrooms, of course.
This is mushroom
Thank you for your support!
Thank you, this is perfect, that's perfect, mushroom
I'll give you the money you gave me.I'll give you the mushrooms.
I don't want it, it's probably a mushroom
Oh thank you thank you thank you
Thank you, thank you, thank you, that was good
Good delivery Asoka Soul Sand Soul
Sand, yes, I'm here today.
Senkyu Senkyu I see.
Senkyu
That's right. I think I'll do it a bit more.
So cute Nemiko-san Aun
[music]
Why did Chan suddenly come?
Diary Amiko Senpai Miko Senpai's house Kaua from now on
I'm going to look for Chiara and Gust, but they're coming.
Yes, I still want to go and find the fortress.
Nice job Miko, let's make that bow and arrow.
Well, I don't have a bow or arrow either, so it's a bit
Let's go, let's go!
Mote
I feel like I want to sleep for a day.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much for writing
Thank you Nemi
Yes too
Thank you thank you
Thank you for your hard work, Amimiko-senpai.
Mia, everyone is back, everyone is back.
The same thing happened to Asoka Su-chan, who died.
We were in a group. We were in the same group.
Subaru Senpai couldn't do it once.
Mario has gone already.
I don't know, I don't know, it's the second time.
Suru-senpai, what's the point of not being able to do it the second time?2
Please return it with a real diamond for the second time.
You said it was, so what do you mean by actual item?
This is a real diamond.
That's what I want you to give me back
Kotomata
fruit
Japan Kanamiko is a widow What is it now?
I'm starting to get a bow
Let's look for a fortress or something, Nether Fortress.
The first person to discover it had 10 diamonds.
30 apparently you can get it
3033 What are the three of you doing who aren't going?
After this, the iron source will be depleted.
I'm thinking of making another one, so I'm making a truck.
That's a trap right now over there 1
There's one, but there's another one in the back.
I'll make another one and I'm not good at it.
Thank you very much, thank you very much
I guess the lack of sweetness is on this side.
Use your head
That's right. If you find any details, please let me know the coordinates.
Please, just in case, yes, I'll do my best.
Please do your best, don't die. That's right, die.
I want you to survive without dying.
For now, don't die, everyone will be sad, church.
Even if it's just a compliment, 64
It's 30 hardcore, it's dangerous.
I think I'll go get another stack and a half
I was just doing that.
Got it, it's in the back, even further back than that trap.
Go straight ahead, it's fine if you have it there.
Alive at the attack point earlier in the meeting
Yes, I put it in that chest.
If you don't try your best, then try your best too.
I'm going to die over there, but it's white again.
Be careful of
I hear it's not in heaven, it's not in heaven.
a
If not, I guess I'll be lucky.
Be careful and avoid lots of slugs.
Be careful
Avoid it, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, I'm alive.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, Aki-chan, it's okay
Kia-chan, okay, okay, okay.
I'm crying, I'm crying, I'm still crying over Senpai.
I went to the Nether. I went to the Nether.
We're friends, that's amazing
Ako-chan has a lot of statues
I'm glad I came back alive, Rami.
It happened to Rami-chan
No, that's right, that's good, that's good, why?
I died, I died, I died, why did I die?
Noonami-tan and Una-tan and the three of us in the Nether
I was there and Gust came so I had to protect him.
When I was fighting a gust, it turned into magma.
I thrust into it, Wow, that's why I ate it and passed out.
The leaf that says
certain death
The adrenaline hits me as I keep streaming.
I don't feel sleepy so thank you for your hard work.
That's why I eat my meal before streaming.
Yes, come with me
Please
It's because they're so strong, it's like two girls.
Where are you looking? Where are you looking?
Teru
4 more days until the guy is cool
I'm a good representative, so I'm hungry.
give
[music]
Okay
I'm a senior, right? But I'm a junior.
Nadesu
or sleep
It was hot
What are you doing with your luggage? Before you start eating, take your luggage.
Organize your luggage for zombies
Don't organize it, go to bed, you guys jump
It's a jump
Go to sleep
yes
Yes, yes
[music]
nice
Miko-san asked me to go somewhere.
However, the group
Where is Kamiko-senpai?
Gomiko
The senior went
[music]
Have more time
Eat what you don't have
I'm still going to play this story and then do some muscle training.
Do you do muscle training? Yes, that's amazing.
I've been working out recently and I wanted to build muscle.
Yes, it's really amazing
But yeah, I've been working out and building muscle.
But all my body fat is gone and I've just lost weight.
What happened? What happened?
It's painful. I can't let it decrease any more. It's painful.
I won't be able to get any more stingy than that.
Even if I had to pump my muscles, I would have already lost weight.
It's definitely cool, so I'm trying to help.
The 15 videos on YouTube every day
Minutes of training
Even though I took a lot of it, it broke apart.
However, there is no death
Ta
Then I came back and my arms were too stiff.
I'm starting to look like Oda.
I have to be able to go home.
I've eaten some food. I'm off to Tampa before I start working out.
Can you take it?Do you drink protein?
Let's go, let's go, drink protein and become handsome
Narou Narisho Mini
I don't know the road at all
I think I can go since something was made.
Is that so?
Ouch wait, where did it come out?
Well,
Court of Appeals
That's the case with the court, but the court is here.
Without
I'm so glad I did it.
I didn't play Leathergate Gamer Thegate
You'll shout, thank you
Takoyoa and Chiara were both confused, so now it's okay.
Weren't you there just now in the grave?
It's here, it's here, it's here.
full
How many teams are there?
Thank you for your hard work, Asochi's Su appeared.
I went back and forth.
Save up
Negi's friend died already for the second time.
No more dryness
Even though this is the second time, what is everyone doing?
Where I go I come back I come back I come back
I'm back
Maybe I should write a mission.
What should I do? Bring this back.
Isn't it there yet?
Please use the T leader created by Butatatan.
Thank you, I defeated Gust.
After all, it's my first time doing something like that.
Or the one with the mission that teaches you the item.
That's the mission one
Please take a photo of that bed.
There's a commemorative photo spot so it looks like it's going to happen.
Please take a picture and sleep on the bed. Yes, that's it.
I won't die, right? Of course I won't die.
That's good, that's good, that's too good
Is it okay?
Yes, it's scary, I'm so tired
That senior Senpai-chanka-chan is on her way.
But can I go with you? I want to go with you.
Well, I want to come now. I want to go.
I'm going home, I'm coming right now, I'm coming now
If we all come back together, there will be 1 million of them.
Hey, it's a flag, come on!
Miko
Senpai Miko-senpai, that's a flag
It seems like it's from
I'm sure it's also a flag, so I'm going to ride the flag
Is it okay to have a flag too?
Will Kira come?
Na
lumpy
Lumpy MagmaGod MagmaGod Magma
god
Mamao, this way TT
Tetete
Oh for the first time
I'm going. I'm going for the first time.
Is this okay?
That
Everyone is here
Yo
It's okay, Kara and Miko-senpai.
What on earth are you flirting with?
Don't be flirting
Don't play around with it
If I cry, I won't fall asleep
[music]
hey
Okay, senior, let's go to the last door
It might be better to close the door at the end.
good
story
Dookuro Stone Okuro Stone Retrieval
I took the claw stone and removed the claw.
I took one stone.
Even Takoko is fast.
[music]
Oh LET
Yay, here it is, Jin
hmm
[music]
Wow, this is it
okay
[music]
IknowIknow
You're Acta's grave. Oh, it's a grave. Take a photo.
There's no way you said that, A-senpai, A-senpai.
I heard something fell down here.
Quite
I can't come this far
I visited the grave and died here, so when I played PT.
Wow, here's the iron
There are a lot of swords. Cloud's eyes are issued.
I have to have it
There is a mother
I want to make a slightly empty one. I want a nice infinite bow.
Nice, I have an infinite bow
Enaa's Infinite Enchantment is Ka
It's with you, I guess.
infinite
Maji Minadore
I have to change the cage.
[music]
As expected from Ka-chan's house, Mugen is here.
There are many other things too.
It's free, it's free, it's winter, it's free, it's free
Ra-chan
[music]
Can you get it without Rahas Ed? Seriously?
Scoo has changed, disdeco.
ja code senkyu decode o
ALC
blown away with a sword
It looked like a bow
I defeated this and that skeleton.
Well, it's definitely amazing.
Ah, everyone, take it, take it.
a
Nua
It can't be helped that everyone takes it.
I took it, I took it, I want to take it too
That's what I mean
I can't sleep because there are monsters nearby.
I can't do it
Hmm, take it!
Send it to me
I got it, yay, now go to sleep
I can't sleep, it's all over again, wait a second
Wait a minute, something is flowing.
What's wrong with that? It's just my imagination.
That's right, I was surprised again and slept here.
It felt like I had been washed away by water.
why here
There it is, where are you going to sleep on the edge?
This is a tourist spot.
It's a nice light spot that surprised me.
Okay, okay, good sister's photo
I'll send it to you
This is a warm cat and a cat.
yes
I want to make a good reading of Yumiya and Yumiya.
No, the clouds I created don't come here.
I'm sure it's special.
Because
I hope it becomes a place where bows and arrows can grow.
to
Nayahane
You don't need it, it's pretty easy to make
It's okay, bow.
That's right.
[music]
hey
Understanding is something you buy
Changing the bow
If there's a Neyashi, I'll change my bow. There aren't any villagers left.
There are no Kanama palms or there are no palms.
No, no, no
[music]
But I don't think I'll ever need a bow.
That's right. I'm about to learn the bow and arrow.
It seems like you want to make one.
[music]
Ah, there is a village device, so I'm sure it would be an option to make one.
I was able to make it pretty quickly
Memories can be created, but those blocks are simple.
It's easy, don't you think? Nothing comes out when you look at it.
That's right. Maybe these aren't even vegetables.
Yes, it can be made with fire and wood.
I probably have some left over at home.
Let's make something. Shall we make something together?
I'm just a little confused about what to do.
[music]
[laughter]
What's wrong with money?
I don't think it's worth it
thinkme
T.R.
think
I think it's a shame
I can get this for free.
You can use this old man over here.
Shall we go back to the village?
Where is Infinite Infinite's attack base?
The
Infinity Asonan Infinity
Mahasun Irahas Mahaskara's house
It's cool
Karakorekore or the place is Lago
[music]
Now Yaya Olet's Go
I can get lego
[music]
Can this help?
What a scream
[music]
Change
This is what it is
[music]
blur
Okay, it's okay, I want to do something, I scream.
I heard it but it's okay
picture
[music]
Haha it's okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Oh, maybe Miko is playing a live role.
This is cute today too.
Hey, my seniors are my seniors.
Dansan Sui-chan has become a little silly.
Takana, Sui-chan is cute today too.
I do, but it's a little boring, Nanka-chan
It's Chan. It's Chan. I can't seem to count.
Karase-chan doesn't seem to understand anything either.
Can be done
It's fake, it's fake
Bye bye bye bye bye to the colorful house
I'm coming, bye bye bye bye
Bullets
[music]
Gogoki yes
Susu tuttlehus oh tuttlehus oh
Talhassursur
Hasturtle House What is Turtle House?
I feel like it's just a funny joke
I feel sorry for you
[music]
Hey there
Olets Golets Golets Golets
Where is the house on the go floor?
na gust ah gust gust eh
This is not a gust that is running away.
Even though I died because of it, Gust is scary, it's scary.
Even if it's fear, the mission is the tire
I'll give you the tire diamond you feel, Gusto.
If you defeat me, that's definitely not the case.
Get the bow and arrowsTarama get the bow and arrows
After that, I defeated Gust.
It seems likely
There's no salvation in this world.
I was begging, but I was saved and survived.
There's no more Nekoyori, that's fine.
Can people become stronger through hardcore?
I don't know if
Looks like you're about to die
Make it a goal to do something
From now until it enters magma, Eo is like that.
[laughter]
[music]
Oh, I might need some emeralds.
I'll go to Aemera House to pick it up.
[music]
havemaybeckIR
Let's play
Good luck
Alright orchestra
hand
I can't get emeralds here or here.
ka iron here iron
[music]
How much iron do you need?
I'm running out of iron
[music]
picture
La Go
BackI thinkbeenough
knowback
[music]
Where is Rocka Rocka Rocka Rocka?
Take
Where was La Rocca?
Kerokka
Roccata
[music]
Oh come on
Oooh something happened
[music]
Look
I'll do my best, thank you very much
Kure Yago
I was fishing.I was fishing.
[music]
Tamino's
Loki wants the princess to look like him, telling him to live.
Everyone is running away and sleeping for a while because Loki is dying.
I don't have a bed without it, I have a bed
Hey
What do you mean, Pecola-senpai, you attacked me?
Ta
But I can't sleep
Hi
I'm sure there's no Loki
I'm going to sleep here. The bed is up.
What should I do? I'll cross over there and go to the village.
[music]
hand
Terume's sleep
[music]
Wait a minute
Menone
What do you have? It looks like Amolite.
Is Loki okay? Loki, Pecola-senpai attack
Loki, Loki, I can't hear if you're okay.
good morning
Good morning, it's me
Even Bubu Bunch is starting to say that.
Phyla is gone too. I'm in bed.
I want to have a baby
Tamiko-senpai and Kia are all separated.
Where is it?
It's gonna be bad
a
Amiko
[music]
Chiamiko Senpai Achiara Chiara Okay
Okay open let's go let's go
Nice oiye I got the emerald 17
Are there enough nice girls?17
I don't know if it's enough. Is it enough?
[music]
Na
Good job, good job.
Good day here
[music]
Ah, waste
No good
A certain wait
of the potion
material
Scary, scary, scary, jump jump
Take care of your seniors
Senpai Oki Senpai
[music]
Ah, senpai, are you okay? Are you okay?
It's okay, I was wondering what you were doing right now.
Go to Kakaraa
Welcome to Karai Cool Yay
Kino
Go ahead and make a tetratrap now.
Thank you very much.
It will be done soon, so
Thank you so much tomorrow I'm sorry today today
I want to catch zombies at night, so please help me.
I'll do it
I'll come and see you soon.
Thank you very much
[music]
Maybe a zombie, but I just saw Loki
That's bad.
It's true that Hiarakiara is gone.
Are you okay, Chiara? She's gone, Chiara.
Chiara's swollen skin
I'm ahead of the curve
It's okay, a town is being built.
Because it's okay
Are you okay
It's okay, maybe he's already gone.
Na
No, ok, it seems like he's on his way.
Looks like it's okay
1 Village OK OK
Okay this is Kaela
village kara village
Akaela
Is this the road in the village?
[music]
I want a Mobee portrait stand
oh look there
That's right, that's right.
[music]
Face
Chan
[music]
What is this?
Can I get it?Can I get it?
[music]
Thank you
haveneedneedhave
IRgive
theGiveGiveNo
Norightcckright
ccktrytock no
[music]
Ohhhhh
Oh my hair, can you exchange it for my hair?
Na
Nice Amoua Up to 17 pieces Up to 17 pieces
I got it, but I wonder if it's okay?
Diamonds are also very strong.
Oh, get diamonds with emeralds
Can be done
[music]
Gogo
Wow thank you
[music]
ONE
infin
inf
enthat
ONE
Yeah, I can dig this, I can dig this.
[music]
level god
is
have got it
no
I did it
You can ask that senior Ani to translate for you.
Oh, what's going on there, old man?
It's okay to turn a NEET into a vegetable right now.
Are you going to destroy that?
Selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling, selling and selling
That's how I brought it
[music]
Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
It's okay, it's okay, I'll block it soon.
I'll block you ok ok ah but
Yane villager
It's always going to be like that
I feel like there was no Nito.
But I don't know if it will go back to normal or not.
I'm sorry, I don't understand
What happened to Moe? It's not coming back. Wait, that's amazing.
It's coming out. It's coming out. I replaced it.
It looks like it might get fixed.
Will it be fixed if I don't replace the one I received?
I got it
from
Tityaoo SoIjustget
thisIneednormal
BOOKnoral
[music]
noral Is this it?
Where is it?
Is this okay, Kana-chan?
[music]
Old man's house
I'll have you wait there.
[music]
Chana it's true
baud
[music]
andSLE
Oh wait, I want to kill some zombies
No zombie killing oh
[music]
Oh
Oops, I forgot about it.
[music]
All
thank you
I'll save you, it's okay
The sea is okay
difference
[music]
This is Ooneko Senpai
After this, I was thinking of going to pick you up with money now.
I want to go to the Nether, so I guess so.
I want to make it and go to the stage.Okay, I haven't made the bow yet.
I can't make it, I can't make it, I can't make it, I can't make it
It seems impossible
yeah
ah
Oh dear, if I follow Kara, maybe Kara will use his bow.
I think I'll make it, senpai, it's true.
[music]
At Yeah La's house
Yeah, wait a minute.
Oh wait a minute
Wait a minute, Miko-senpai, Miko-senpai.
Read this in English above.
I want death
[music]
Nice, you can bring me.
Oh it's okay
[music]
lego a
come out
[music]
a
What you have any more
like
inthinkyouneedput
unbreaking
need have any
[music]
Let
meNeed
[music]
have
iokhaveenoughfor
need
think-chan
[music]
of
I'm so depressed
[music]
a
ah
Senkyu
nice
Kaka
[music]
NONONO
Kakaiei
Getznai
thank god
[music]
know
and
[music]
knowIthinkwas
Confused I was leading
Herhousewasalsocall
me
[music]
a
Ma
Eo, erotic, erotic, erotic, that erotic, erotic
It's not erotic, it's not erotic, it's Roeros.
No, no, no, no, I gave it all away.
Which Eros is which?
[music]
What did you give me?
Ta
[music]
I got the aroma
No, I have it, I have it.
Infinity
Infinite, a bit dangerous, but the reverberations are true
The "Bounced Arrows" sounds just like Eros
do not have
The surprising eroticism of Koyori
Even if it's okay, it's erotic anyway.
If you ask me
I was able to roll
[music]
This is this guy.
of I see
knowIfoundIjust
asking
help that Nobody
yet
knowsBUY
[music]
I can't hold this shield.Shield
It doesn't exist, it can be made from iron.
No, no
difference
No, that's right
[music]
Damikochi, I can defeat the pig myself. I can defeat it already.
Nice guy who will definitely kill the pig, no more.
Seriously, forgive that guy, I'll defeat him too.
It's going to turn into a hard flag, Gonezago.
Let's go Leather Golets Golets Goza
leather go
It seems like you don't have any.
There are places where you can get it even if you don't have it.
Karaso
I'm sure someone is going to die.
Don't die
stubbornly
Like that
No good
is
Waiting
[music]
Mim's Mi who knows Kae
It might be bad
[music]
HOUSE
narume
a
I see.
[music]
No, go back
Tereare
I realized that I came to the village. I came to the village.
Different village
Right?
In the village
[music]
Are you okay
mosquito
[music]
This is Senpai Pol Pol
is my senior
[music]
It was
Aremi
[music]
My old sewing machine mission popo went somewhere.
I'm confused
Oh everyone is there though
lego
Hey, sleep, sleep, sleep, no, sit down.
Did someone sit on me?
I'm going to get this and that from this village.
Oh, it would be really nice if I slept with you
You look like you're having a really hard time sleeping
The water is bad, the water isn't bad, it's not bad
Wait, wait, aren't you fighting?
Yes, Rami-tan and I are
I just saw a mysterious house with deep darkness.Darkness.
It's not deep, it's a lovey-dovey house.
Let's go together and get sweaty and refreshed.
[music]
a
I was surprised when I went, wondering if someone was on fire.
I thought so
[music]
I'm in Ripapolpol village.
Goodbye
I made a mistake
[music]
Oh, here or there, it's kind of stylish.
and here
[music]
a little bit a little bit
Hey, wait a minute, it's been 30 minutes.
Teru
[music]
Oh wait, I'm going to load you up.
No, no, something like that
I got separated
I'm back
Yo
nice
Nice, let's defeat Gust this time
About Tai's voice
Wait for Iku's voice, Pikki.
I want to make
But I have iron.
I don't have it
Yeah, yeah, yeah, there's iron.
Do you need iron?
You can give it to me. Yes, it's okay.
Yomomo was Chiara's iron
I don't know what to do
Yoshiko is ready
[music]
Good morning
too
Wait a minute
[music]
Please knowLove
That's right
[music]
Okay, just leave it here.
Hey, isn't the bed bad?
What a bed!
Also put aside
I put some really weird colors on it
This is a good product
Oh okay
Oishi Let's
Go, maybe this time I'll go around in circles again.
I'm sure I can't go to the bottom of this ttd
It looks nice that it's open over there, I understand.
Unfortunately I died
From safety first, today is not just today.
You can't do that, hardcore, seriously.
It looks like I'm seriously going to die. Now's not the time.
But seriously, someone is going to die, so stop it, stop it.
Stop this.
Stop talking, stop talking, stop talking, animal.
Bisayoshi
Okay, okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Is it okay? Is it okay?
Is it okay? It's okay
Are you okay
Orchestra
Hey, when I make a strange turn, I get stuck on the road I was on.
I'm scared that I'll join the
[music]
How it feels here
I thought maybe it would be better, so I went to the side and ran into trouble.
It looks like we're going to win, so we just have to go straight.
Maybe it's better not to have it. It's early, it's early.
Early danger
[music]
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's nice, it's next to me
Awesome you're going
My neighbor is dead, my senior is dead.
Senpai Sui
Chandou Eisai-chan
Emu Goodbye Nara Su-chan Senpai Miko
I think your older sister is Mikochi Luluna-senpai.
I thought
Then, sensei-senpai
[music]
a
senior
[music]
After finishing the bottom part, I followed my senior and finished the bottom part.
That's what happened
Stella has become a star. Stella has become a star.
Nteroshi
There are definitely people who write in diaries.
After all, when the nether opens, the chief will appear.
I was scared because she's a star
died from
[music]
But my legs
Run away, don't stop it, run away
It's true that there's nothing to stop a cough even if it's a cough suppressant.
Wait, wait, wait, gust gust
There's Gusto There's Gusto There's Upper Gust
Okay
Let's go back
[applause]
From Eko no Deko, you have zero remaining lives and zero remaining lives.
I'd rather die once more than this.
It's like there's nothing left to do, right?
Go, I'm scared, you're behind me, you're behind me
Aji-senpai is reassuring, Iroko is behind me.
It's okay, it's okay, I'll take the road
Shine on your senior, I'll lead the way
It's not a good idea to light it up, as expected.
It's like gold, you can't dig it up.
If you live like you're going to die, you'll die soon like that.
Put it away
Hmm, but it'll turn into a hole.
[music]
Miko-chan seems to have a lot of desire to live.
Nemiko lives
Dodge and wait, it will be a flag, so stop and wait
Don't wait and it will become a flag.
It wouldn't be strange if I fell down again, it's amazing
I'm stuck, so if one person leaves,
Everyone somehow slipped through, even if it was just me
Live
Oh, I'm a little sorry for the damage.
Well, if you're going to die, die and break it properly.
It's okay to still be there
There's also a Teuchi diamond ice ax.
At worst I'll dig it up, I hope there's a Cubgust
It's about time for me to get into that iron thing, so it's about time.
It's scary that it's going to break, but it's nice and new.
It would have been better to have it
I really regret why I left it behind.
Why did I leave this behind?
Did I leave my heart racing?
Yes, I'm excited, so I'll leave it here
It's a big diamond so it's really fast
It's better for Kia to advance than for Dami to advance.
It's so fast, I had it with me.
But it's early
Too much
fear
My heart is pounding
My heart is pounding, it's dangerous
[music]
[laughter]
Hey, Senpai, you said it was mine, but you were the quickest.
It can't be helped because I'm too slow
Wait, it's okay
It's okay, I was scared.
Senpai is no longer waiting
Well, everyone died, ah, died.
do not have
Don't just freak out like that, Mai.
craft
Oh, ho, ho, let's go, let's grill the calamari
Magma has been found, magma
It's gone now.
Strider is definitely scared of being pushed.
I was talking about wisteria.
Because I don't have any blocks
[music]
Oh, I didn't bring the block here.
block on the side
It's dangerous, it's dangerous
Let's go this way, it might be dangerous.
Should I wait?
I guess this is the end because I can't use water.
There's no point in it, you're water pake, everyone's squatting down.
That's right, squat down.
da
There's a way, right?
yes
What is that?
I just don't feel like I'll find anything.
That makes me feel good about my house.
The road is pushing and pushing over there
There's a kiss, there's a gust, but here I am
There is no gust
But don't push it, push it
Naru is here
[music]
Something came up
Oh that's nice
Nice Kiara Nice, what's this, hand, hand?
this
[music]
There are a lot of people who have a hard time
There is
[music]
Oh
Are you okay?
reduce
good
[music]
Thank you very much
Scary, scary
[music]
This is no good.
is
Hey, I made something amazing with Michi-chan.
I made this properly, it's really helpful
Messed up
But maybe if I went here I wouldn't find the same thing.
Isn't it dry? Someone else went.
It would be better to have a different direction here.
This white guy has been there before.
Someone is doing it.
[music]
Yeah someone
someone was doing it
[music]
Neon
Where are you going?
Hmm, I don't know what to do. Gust is here.
It's a gust, isn't it? Let's kill the gust.
Let's kill Gusto. Looks like Gusto is okay. Where is Gusto?
Kill Gust
I'm already doing another one.
So I haven't done it yet. It's okay if it's white.
That's right, I haven't done it yet.
Isn't it only fashionable to have one?
[music]
I can only leak it
Not a bit beautiful
Home is hardcore and stylish.
I can make it right away though.
[music]
There's a cat around here
I don't like it
Terukana or Kone is scary inside.
What are you doing here?
Around
[music]
of
No-gi
No pig to do
Eil
Nokoso, ah, it's because I took out the tree. It's no good at all.
Yes, I lost the money.
Miko-senpai this team is scary
I'm scared, but I'm also scared to go home
It's okay, it's okay, I'm squatting but it's scary
Which way should I go?
cormorant
Gusto, what's going on? No, his face is cut too sharply.
Who has this kind of heart?
Senpai wanted to kiss me so much
Kagu is straighter
That can't be true.
I wish I could say yes
I wish it was direct
Why is that so confusing?
My Japanese has improved so much.
That's how it happened.
I feel like I should have said it directly.
I read a little too much manga.
Even if it's a little no, no, no, I'm usually me
I don't read girls' manga. Where did I learn that?
Yay anime no no
Wow, I learned a lot from all the anime.
Thank you
road
Wow this is amazing I can jump
I feel like this is what's coming
I feel like I can go home if I follow this path.
Jump, sure, but there's a way in the opposite direction.
That's right, that's right.
Let's go straight here. Go straight here.
Let's
Is this safe?
[music]
O
It's because the road was created by someone.
Not TTT Not TTT
Or somewhere in TT
At TTT's place
do not have
[music]
I wonder if it's gone back
Right, this is probably on the way home.
It's dangerous, oh my gosh, yeah, it's dangerous.
dangerous dangerous dangerous
What, what, what?
What, what, what was that?
I think I'm definitely going to die
[music]
Another magma who was so quick
Why?
Nachi
I was laughing again Nether
[laughter]
I think the flag will go back.
The one from earlier
How about we build that road and go straight?
I think that long bridge is totally fine.
[music]
Also at the entrance
Ninnai
magma cube
[music]
or
Is there something like that?
This is Makube.
I'm sure someone will do it for you, please.
Masu
Nice, just take 4 of these.
Oh, I see, the glowstone isn't on my nose yet.
That's right.If you collect 12 of these dozen, there will be people.
I think it's ok to just have one E next to the one fighting.
Looks like you took one glow stone?
I only need one glow stone.
Thank you very much for your thoughts.
No, I'll go back then
There's no chance, so I'm seriously the only one who can run away.
If so, I can't do it, it seems dangerous.
This bridge is half-open, half-way
have great fear
[music]
Ro that can be done
What's going on here in Magma Kibbu?
That road was a little vague
Oh, it's dangerous, stop jumping!
Minute after minute, money dies, okay? It's okay to stop.
Stop length
Don't do it, it's no good. Prophecies are just a way.
I'll light it up, I'll show you the way, kyukyu
Senkyuki said go home.
This is the second time.
It seems that my senior called me after returning home. This is the second time.
eye
Oh my god, it's the second time I've shoveled dirt into the ground.
Come on
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
It's okay, I love Kiara, Miko makes me happy.
Miko-senpai I love you too Mikaa
I played games with Yatachi Chichiana.
Taika
[music]
I did it
Senior, yes today.
Something about this group is really about me.
I was worried whether it was okay to say it, but today.
I'm happy to be able to hang out with you for a while
I'm so happy that Mimiko has one today.
I thought it was going to happen, but it's okay.
Dragon Ball This World Dragon Ball
It seems like it was Dragon Ball and solo.
Yes, my friend
No friends
So I've never seen Dragon Ball?
Visible
There is something
Danger
It's dangerous
Doing it with my cousin and cousin is dangerous, dangerous.
dangerous dangerous shift
Shift, put a flower on it and it's okay
Do it in a larger space
[music]
a little bit
No way no no
Ah, I see
What a place it was
[music]
I'm going to make a nice senkyu mushroom.
What are you so scared of? It's the first time I've said something in private recently.
I saw the Indiana Jones movie.
It seems scary
I first saw 1 and 2. It's interesting. That's what I saw.
I haven't seen it all, I've never seen it, I've seen it all
I'm so excited when I saw Naimi
Did you see Noto 22? Did you see 1? Shall we take a look?
Naare-chan, it's fun, hardcore is that.
Emikomiko Roll of the Ring
I saw it, I saw it, I saw it all ...
I knew there was Gimli there.
But somehow I feel like that's the case.
Even if I look at it, I don't know what it looks like
Not at all
No, yeah, that's right. I'm much younger.
I've only seen the latest ones
[music]
Asui
The sound of magma The sound of magma Magma magma
It's okay, you don't have to run away too much, it's okay too.
A-senpai, who is the most scared, immediately blocks me.
Unlike those who leave me behind, I die
I don't want to anymore
You have some residual energy, don't you? Be careful with your money, be careful with your money too.
Attach
I'm going to die! This is Aji-senpai's work with money.
I'm even more scared because it's coming
What do you feel?
That's what I'm saying, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay
is
Yu-sama Cool Lue
Wow, I'm used to it. I'm used to it. I'm going home now.
Yarn perfect team perfect
Team This
Hamikochi and Mikochi's judgment and courage
Everything needs to feel good
Senkyuye leader Mikochi is the leader
Mikochi
Our team is a leader like Senpai Miko-senpai.
Hey, Miko-senpai, Amiko-senpai, its okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
[music]
Daifu is okay
It's early
[music]
Echa's super calmness is important.
That's right, I can't calm down
Are you okay? Gaki-chan, you're okay.
Kaki
I want to be told that I'm Chakicho.
Not
Ah, what I remember about pro wrestling is Tokoro and Gakidokoro.
I have a good memory of what I said.
Something
The first various religions that say omiko is a baby
Dano
[music]
I can't be your opponent anymore
Ze
There is a danger
[music]
Please lead the way so I don't fall.
It's not easy to get a fortress.
Hey, magma here is crazy.
This actual thing is magma. No, it isn't.
Miko also remembered that, I remembered it.
I remembered
do not have
[music]
Eternal Uncle Eternal Uncle
Eternal is a bit surreal
uncle
My uncle and senior say I want an uncle.
That's kind of interesting, isn't it?
That's what it is
Neno
I was wondering what you were talking about, so it was about my uncle.
Talking, uncle, uncle,
Nami-senpai today too
No, it's not like that, it's about my senpai.
I see it every day, so I can see how bad it is.
I'm there
behind
It's always been like that, no matter how long you live
There is a possibility that it can be drunk by magma, no, no, no.
Miko-senpai, please don't die today, Gastochia.
Gust chance Gust chance has come
A ghost chance is a ghost chance
Ghost Chance Gust Chance Gust
There's a chance
Are you okay
I want to defeat
[music]
Try defeating a certain
What? Senior, I haven't finished my mission yet.
too
[music]
Sorry Yochiruna
That's what happened
[music]
Wow
You can't defeat it with just one shot.
Hey, I'm right, I'm right, I'm right.
What?
[music]
nice
nice clear
[music]
I did the mission.
[Laughter]
As a senior, what are you looking for?
I feel like I'm looking for a fortress.
That's okay.
Foresta is aaaa
I would be happy if I could spend time with Miko-senpai like me.
It's scary because you're lying. It's scary here. It's scary here.
Yeah, it's scary here, okay, I'm on the right.
To the right
I'm here, but the road ends here.
Yes, this is where it is.
next
It's scary, what does it look like from above?
I did Mada-chan Gusto
I'm not playing Baby Gusto.
Even if you have it
[music]
Naku War
What is this? Who is 4 years old? Who is 4 years old?
I can't see down there.
I can see it, I can't see it, but there
[music]
There, oh, it's true, there's a bridge, 4, right?
Or that?
That's amazing!
Nice, ah, that's amazing, but it's really low.
Where should I go? How should I go? The road
I want to fix it. How do I go about this?
That's so low, that's a bone, bones, bones, wow, water.
I brought water, but there was no water.
Fall in love
When you make stairs
If I mistakenly thought there was only dregs,
[music]
Magma is a little dangerous
Seriously
So I got 30 diamonds, I did it, everyone.
Yay!
Ta
Nice, what's wrong with you, Gagagas?
Kill the gas, kill the gas.
I haven't killed you yet. I haven't killed you yet.
I can't kill it without it, I can't kill it without it
I don't think I have Kanade-chan anymore.
I don't have it, so it would be scary if it exploded while I was playing.
That's right, you should just lend it to me.
Is it okay to lend money?Is it okay to lend money?
It's totally possible. It's okay to die for money.
My legs won't move and it's dangerous. Where am I?
scared
[music]
Wow
gross
There's nothing
It doesn't look dangerous, I'm hitting back.
Oh, that's nice there
nice
Ume-chan
Yayaba
Yummy, yummy, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous
Is it dangerous? It's dangerous, I don't want to die.
Oisho
Wow, thank you Narinari
I can't wait
died
Nomad-ish
I can still hear you, so you can hide here.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Thank you so much I'm dying
Get in
There's nothing left to do. Don't die.
[music]
It's nice to say that Cal-chan died.
Senkyu
nice
Thank you for the nice sky
[music]
nice
Oppo
Tade Brave Brave
Oh, it's a purpose, it's a purpose.
Please make some potions for Miko too.
Let's all make it too
Mia Skeleton Skeleton E Skeleton
Because I have a mission
I did this
If you wait too long, you'll be rejected and you'll fall.
O
Skeleton, there's a skeleton over there too.
do not have
[music]
Yes, it looks nice and strong
Let's catch some fried potatoes
It's better if you don't do it. The greed is going down.
is
under the roof
[music]
Michi Kononi
Oh Senpai Ah
Ah, nice, nice, nice, infinite, so that's it.
Ah, I'm back here again
[music]
stairs
Ooooh
[music]
do not have
I don't know what to do.
Teru
of
[music]
Cho
terrible
Kinda nice
Nice, everyone is alive
[music]
It came all the way here.
But the mission is clear
[music]
Dangerous but nice
Nai Ayabai-chan is making it.
[music]
There's no danger here
Hey, it's dangerous
Nekotchika?
Thank you very much.
[music]
Wait a minute
Mr. Miss.
There's no Mr.
[music]
backup
Oh
[music]
Thank you oooo
Oh
[music]
queue
Koooooo
[music]
just
what
[music]
DownDROP
Down
[music]
OKthan
I want a Sekyuo head too
[music]
decorate the head
That's just how it is.
[music]
That's it
Kinotori
[music]
Takashi
Masu
Maybe it's not here. It's not here. Oh hey.
no understanding
oh
Wow, amazing!
There's something like this about McCraft.
This game is definitely a horror game
There's something wrong with this, even if I take the money
Is that okay or not?
[music]
Run away
Don't run away
I'm scared because it's
That's why I'm so scared.
Is it okay to stop?
It's okay, I'm going to get worried after this, Senpai.
[music]
I got a lot of
Ta
Go go
[music]
What should I protect?
Let's get this for now, Chiara.
Is this also a mission?
nether wart nether wart
Nether wart mission
Can I take it then?
Na
[music]
Make a potion, make a potion
A mission to make a mission
do it and make it
[music]
I took a lot. I'll take some too.
Hehehe, if you want to take it too, I'll take it too.
[music]
It's okay, you just have to have Momomo
I want so much, please leave it behind.
It's okay
Kaii no Kare
[music]
Also leave it behind
don't leave things behind
What is this?
[music]
Mama, I'm scared, so stop it.
Someone who is so scared
A scared person
I told you not to do it because it was scary.
Don't worry
or someone who is scared
What's wrong with being there?
[music]
Yo, its okay
Okay thank you
[music]
Please ask me
Tetta
[music]
It's over
can be
[music]
It's okay to jump, but it's not that bad.
It doesn't hurt
That's true, thank you. Nice.
I wonder where it is. I can see inside.
[music]
Okay
Naina
O
Yeah, I took it anyway.
[music]
What kind of sound did you get? Nice one.
Nice, but that's not today's mission.
I'm sure not
Niun
[music]
have
It's okay
[music]
It's dangerous, it's dangerous
Thank you for giving me that
Yoriseka
Oh, okay, your sister is around there too.
Okay nether boat search
[music]
to
I don't have that.
DeAmi
is
[music]
Seniors
Wow, it's going strong!
Mebi kept running away and meeting each other again and again.
I killed a lot of things
It's a red or red color, and there are others.
Nainae and Kara are already gone
[music]
Teruko Hello
hello okay
[music]
[applause]
Dangerous Under
curcurfrom
SK no no no no no
[music]
fellow
Hai Miko Senpai Miko
Senpai Miko Senpai Miko
Senpai, Wow, Im sure Miko-senpai, I can hear you, Miko.
My senior, Miko-senpai, is here. This is here.
Miko senpai yay yay yay wawawa senpai
I called it to Miko-senpai.
It was dangerous, it was too dangerous, Blaze
There are a lot of Lego characters.
Yan
It's great and good
It's delicious but the mission is broken
Ta
Yo potato potato There was endless potato.
Potato Endless Potato Endless Potato
scary cam cam cam
[music]
I wonder if I should follow Khao.
Oh, there they are, there they are, there they are, here they are
Oh, it's true, Rays.
Wow wow
circle
There are many dangers, dangers, dangers, dangers.
There's a lot of it, there's a lot of it, it's burning, it's burning
Are you okay?
I see.
Dangerous magma is dangerous, it won't attack you now
Wow, when I knock this guy down
sleep
[music]
I almost hit my head
Naruyoisho
Yes, I'm going to win by distance.
There's a small one
There are two. There are two. There are two.
Dada da it's true
[music]
Tano
There are two spawners, and there are gusts.
amazing
This is called Bray.
is
But the one you drop looks like potato fries
It's called potato because
[music]
It's hard to do doubles once.
yes
here and there
Over there
Hahahaha thank you Miko-senpai Good job
Why not put it from this spawner?
Maybe that's why it's leaking because it's connected.
On the contrary, come
Pain and pain
A dangerous, dangerous death.
I'm going to die, this is amazing, shoot me from behind
Oh wait, here, here, here, here, here.
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's shining, it's shining
Yes, yes, yes, below, below, a surprised orchestra.
Okay, okay, it's scary, thank you, it's dangerous.
Wait a minute, it's over here, over here, over here on the stairs.
yeah
Wow, I don't know what happened.
rice
[music]
Let's eat
Don't do that, sister, it's burning, it's burning
It's burning. It's just a little bit burning.
I know now that I won't die
Ta
love
If there is no grass, it will burn.
[music]
Teruo calm hikorena
Wow
burning
[music]
Is this your stomach?
Wow, now I have a block left
[music]
Kachan is also in the evening
Is it okay tonight? It's okay.
Are you okay?
It's okay though
[music]
Are you okay? It's okay.
[laughter]
Oh no
Why would anything good come out of destroying this thing?
Some spawners do not spawn if you place pine trees around them.
I see, but I'll go there and say something like that.
Torches horizontally to brighten
I want an item
Everyone is doing their best, will it be okay?
That thing
[music]
Yes, yes, yes, it's okay, on the left too.
All my seniors have died.
Oh no, back there!
Its so true!
[music]
Even if you do it all over the place, it's almost time to pick up some food.
It looks like we're running out of food.
I can give it to you. How many potatoes do you need?
Thank you so much
I want it, ah, thank you, cue, thank you.
thanks
[music]
Oh, even if I tried that thing, I wouldn't be able to pick it up.
potato
[music]
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it flows from here
I already know the name of that enemy, but I can't pick it up.
That's okay
[music]
Toa Gust
Who is Gusto who came?
or kill required
or even here
[music]
It was a hit, but it was a hit.
Next
Pick it up even if you knock it down
Naio
[music]
nice
Oh wow they're doing it
That's where I am
Nejia nice adana da
It's okay nice
[music]
There's not enough wood
I'll do it now
I got about 3, thank you
Thank you
Mas nice nice
[music]
Nice, yeah yeah, but it's just
I wonder why they put half blocks there?
why
It's easy, but I don't have it, so even if I write it once.
It might be a good idea to go back once, but I'm on my way home.
I'm sure everyone can come on the way home.
I'm heading back to the city, so wait for me to see the road so far.
I don't know
I don't know what to do, but I'm on a path that's not that way.
no burn
If you hang out, you'll arrive at that splendid bridge
Deoh
nice
It won't reach you. If it gets that far, it's impossible.
[music]
It's because I'm on my own
I'm in bed
[music]
Everyone be careful from
Tekete
It's okay if you don't take the difficult ones.
[music]
Then this is quite far
dangerous
It seems like this place.
[music]
Is it about the mission or is it a diamond?
It doesn't mean it's here.
Apparently there isn't a nether mote.
Kanade owns the nether boat.
I have about 23 of them, and one of them is amazing.
Please bring me up
Masuah
sorry
Okay later
Yo
One thank you
Not necessarily only
[music]
[laughter]
mosquito
I see.
This is what I have to cultivate
[music]
Where did you fall behind me?
I saw Withas, but it's over there, behind me.
I had a problem but
degree
Ah, I've already done it.
[music]
Defeat
Throw down the shed
Tamiko-senpai has already come this far.
Terumiko
Senior Miko
Senpai, senpai, oh, Helmi, Helmi.
What's okay?
he milk milk milk stinky milk milk
It stinks, it's there, it's okay
I was almost killed. That was dangerous.
[music]
I didn't need this, I don't know the way
If you don't have one, I'll tell you to make a new path.
Tandaa
Naru First Genius
Genius here
[music]
Eggplant
Oooooo
[music]
It might be dangerous
Hey, I need to talk to you.
It would be easiest if you dig at a distance that is not too far away.
I'm sure at first
Let's leave this to the mosquitoes We are sure
To the power
Let's leave it to you
[music]
Oh, it's dangerous, oh, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
Yo shift
shift o
[music]
Thank you, thank you, thank you
Thank you
mite
hand
[music]
Let's go home
To the promised place
Go home
[music]
Oishii I see it there
Hey, are you from there?
No, it's different
Wait a minute, I didn't open that part.
Monne
this
I don't understand why
[music]
I'm so excited for my meeting
Thank you senkyu sekyu senkyu
Brock has this
I just made a wall like a landmark, so look for it there.
Looks like I'll be able to go home
Hey Shifanononoe
[music]
Chibast
but
Fantastic nice
[music]
Storm nice
random
Po
of
Awesome, not this one
It's better not to use it.
Level conversation for Minecraft beginners
I can't keep up
Ze
Nice, it seems like it's a long way to go here.
Neidian or something like that
Even if I connect it there without a channel
I'd feel really safe if I could go on a good surface.
Oh, it's a great distance if it's Tadahara.
No, that's a really great distance.
think
Looks like something like Olafa 4000.
[music]
It's okay, no one will die now.
No flag?
okay that flag flag
Give it back, we already have it
Kara is related
That's what I'm saying, I'm returning Diamond's clothes.
is
Thank you for the debt.
Hey, that's also Radia.
properly wa
Jarita
It's just that, it's okay.
I can't get it. It's enchanted.
I'm making a lot of money now
[music]
hey
That's right
Didn't I?
[music]
It's okay, it's bad
If you don't mind, I'll do it on my side.
I understand, thank you very much.
thank you
[music]
terrible
It's dangerous, it's dangerous
[music]
character
before
[music]
let's go let's go
Yoisho LOVE na LOVE mi
[laughter]
[music]
Love Miko
Chat with different seniors
Chat-senpai's chat, yes, yes.
That's right, this is being criticized by everyone at kfp.
not scary
[music]
That's a scary 6
Ass happy
Hey happy happy hattie
Hattie happy happy happy hi
Haha happy happy then cat mim
If you are happy happy, use cat Mim
[music]
haha dangerous dangerous
Thank you, Danger, Thank you, Secure, Senpai.
I'm not scared I'm not scared
[music]
Wait a minute
Thank you very much
Thank God Danger Danger Danger Danger
Why are mushrooms growing here so dangerous?
is
It's because Akokin is stupid.
good
I'm going to Japan again this summer, so let's hang out.
Let's play. I want to do something fun. What do I want to do?
Are you a gold genius? That's fun. That's gold.
I'm not a genius
It's different
Wrong.
[music]
The idiot is Rigro.
Let's take a look at the educational background test.
Who would you like to go with Toun Recommendation Senpai?
I wonder who the person in the house I want to call is probably.
I'm so happy
Let's all go, let's all wait a moment
Wait, wait, wait a minute, it's okay
Oh mushroom, I don't need this mushroom
I don't want it, I don't need it, it's green, it's green
Noe is everywhere
blue
forest
only
That's right, that's blue.
[music]
It's better to look behind you, which only exists in pure land.
mosquito
[music]
Moko
Crazy o
[music]
It's about time
block is gone
Teru
[music]
It's not okay for me to be Ascent, I'm still me.
Block ascent is fine.
do not have
Then I have to give it to you, don't push it, don't touch it.
Please, please
Goajigo
What happened to Ao?
[music]
It was later added though
I don't even want to take a new direction.
[music]
Tell me it's not new
Eating Aichi rice
I want to eat in real life, but I won't eat now.
Looks like I'll have dinner when I get home.
Eat a lot, eat a lot of rice, right away
Eat enough food to go home
It's only 2, so please don't do it.
I'm working really hard today, but today's results are
Amazing, amazing leather
I'm also doing some nice missions.
It's great to clear a lot of missions.
today
What time is it in Austria?
Resta Osua is now 7 o'clock Osua evening 7 o'clock
It's almost 7 o'clock in the evening, yeah yeah yeah
Ah, it's Bolden time.
I usually start streaming at times like this.
Fran is streaming at this time, right?
I have an image of midnight in Europe.
I'm sure there will be a golden time.
It's Kara, it's the same as Kara, it's Kara.
I asked
from
I want to open the way
Oh my god, stop it!
[music]
It's fine, isn't it?
Get in
[music]
I'm scared to go in. It's dangerous here.
My
Meme
[music]
Sly slime is late, magma is rising from above
It's coming, it's coming from above the magma, it's scary!
Danger, Danger
Danger
Don't make it taste good, are you okay? Everyone will die.
everyone won't die
I won't die from it
Hot tourism in
[music]
earth
what
Come to Green Green where something happened.
All biomes in the nether
I imagined I got it because I went there.
Ta
What to talk about
It's a blue forest. I haven't seen just the blue forest.
That kind of thing
be
Yes, but I got a lot of them.
Aomori
[music]
Delicious
Aomori is abbreviated as Ao.
I still don't have the mission money.
Hey mushrooms still mushrooms mushrooms mushrooms still
But it's dangerous
Kotoiya
[music]
I'm trying to be careful, but I'm scared of the fall
I wonder if it's okay to pee mushrooms. This is no good.
Yo
It's okay here
Ki made the stairs
Please, nice
[music]
oh yeah
As long as you have 1 silk tachi and you can bring as much green clay as you want
I'm sure you can increase it
I guess they haven't made either this or the sill yet.
home
Boohoo
[music]
I got it
Oh, let's make it big
Oh, if someone gave it to you, you shouldn't take it away.
I didn't have it so I came here and got it
I'm making a lot of money today.
Masua
Oh, I shouldn't have fooled you.
[music]
Thank you
What is it?
It's about time
[music]
I'm sure it was nice
It's okay, it's dangerous
[music]
scared
Suva
kill
I fell down, though.
[music]
G.R.
we think the
lavOF
[music]
THENEVER
[laughter]
I'm scared of this
hey
Hey, it's okay
[music]
God's Deva God's Deva
Or something?
[music]
to
can be
Already have it?
Barrel
[music]
Re
It seems there is no place to put Terumatsu, so Iko Matsu
Recognition of Magma Matsu Ikomagma
Nama mama yeah that mission is strong and strong
It was so intense I curled up.
Thank you very much
Thank you myself
I have to report it.
Yo
I didn't know about the need for a pig's voice.
Pig pig pig be careful pig
be careful
know
S
It's scary, it's not scary. Even if I do this, I won't let it happen once.
It's too strong, right? That's the story in the first place.
If Moka-chan dies, you can do it once, usually.
I'm strong without it
Thank God Eacha died.
Come to think of it, I wonder what happened to Harcha and Senpai.
I'm sure the material will be revived though.
I decided to collect diamonds.
That's not it, that's it, that's it, that's it.
I wonder if it's Ten, right? I wonder if it's the usual Hosa?
Is it normal hosa or double lock? Yeah, it's different.
No different normal da or normal or soe but who?
There's no such thing as an ax or an ax.
Fight with an axe, senpai, I can make my own iron now
I have to have it
Yes, Matsu made a mistake too.
It's hard with my ice ax. It's okay, okay.
I guess if I do it with my PC, it'll probably do everything.
There's no more trial to destroy it, 4 more times.
I have to
That's right.
hey
Akanaki is calm, calm down
enemy
Why did Teru Ikeru Ikeruko Senpai die?
In this nether
There is someone who protects Gusto in order to defeat him.
in a panic
It just drips down and sticks in the mouth and burns.
Tara-chan can feel safe, someone will protect her.
Ei is being attacked and digging the road while looking at the mess
I see
I thought I had to do it.
That's so sweet, ahahaha
It's that guy, I bet he's cool
It's cool that you're being praised, isn't it?
I'm cool and cool and I'm a bride and a red
protect the phlegm
It was red and red.
Thank you for the queue
I'll do anything if it's nice
[music]
Is there a storm?
Support me, this is supported by my sister.
Teruo Kokokatsu
Tower
here
Kaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahh
No, we need a sign
What do you need a billboard for?
[music]
If you continue like this, you will reach the castle from before.
It's like
nice wonderful
[music]
Here, where is this?
Morning o
Yuyao
Yeah and oh
There are so many roads
Hey TTT, did Kochinaruga do it?
oh
[music]
ghost
I'm doing it
[music]
Rashi-chan-chan-chan
This small photo is so small that it's full of photos
I should have taken it, that's true.
I didn't take it because it was too good. How did you come back?
Daaaii
Nice nice, I got it
Thank you very much for the crackling
Io, let's go home.
Let's go back to the ground. I'm scared.
Let's go home, the life that came home
Teru Aoi Homi Arena has been completed.
When did I become able to do something nice?
Before you know it, something is happening
Done
[music]
people
back
have
LetDieIDie Hardco Training Center
Nice, I see. I wonder what will happen tomorrow.
I'm scared, what will happen tomorrow?
Don't look at me, I'm still in the middle of it
I'm pretty sure it was too dark to take a photo.
Sorry, I took the photo just now.
Is it okay if I ask you a favor?
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank goodness we made it through.
So that's awesome, thank you everyone
There is a book
[music]
Thank you thank you thank you
Thank you for your time with Kyu-chan and A-chan.
Don't forget to write the mission for the two of you.
I forgot to write the mission in the mission book.
Can you all draw it without putting it together?
That's right, both are fine. The voice draws everything again.
It's time to draw it all together and then write it down.
Masuhachamo
Write aa ko yo ko yo ko yoko
Rikako Hachate, Kako Hachakako
Hachama Jun and Ozora Tsujun I Akun Aukun
When we went there, our names were probably written already.
Because it was written
Mikone piglin festival story, gust gust too
I'd like to ask for something like Gusto or Gusto.
I want you to write it yourself, I see.
I don't understand, I don't understand
Well, I don't have any diamonds, so I'll take care of it.
Me at Ara
[music]
down here
This is the one going down
[music]
sound
Uncle's place too
Please tell me uncle
[music]
This one is strong
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, no, no, no, no.
terrible
It's so bad, it's so bad, it's so bad I can't sleep
I can't sleep, I can't sleep, I can't sleep, I can't sleep
[music]
No, I can't sleep, I can't sleep, I can't sleep
Come to think of it, wait, wait, wait
I left my bed somewhere.
Sorry, I don't have a bed.
My senior, who doesn't have a bed, is coming from my left ear.
If my voice is too loud, should I play that lottery?
Okay, now I can sleep with this.
Now I can sleep
do not have
directly
Give me a lot of money and I'll give you 10 diamonds.
Should I make it into individual pieces?
I said crawl, I don't have it.
a
Caught in a naughty trap
Is it okay?
[music]
Harlow and others are okay
make
[music]
POneed
you need to have
thethePO
[music]
Maker
havehaveHOUSE
[music]
Need
a little bit
[music]
But
But it's midday
[music]
I see, it's okay to make kami potion.
I haven't made any potions yet. I'm going to Anori now.
But a potion, a potion
Kara's house made an automatic potion making machine.
There's a statue in Kara's house.
It's on the flat side of the yoraka.
Think Automatic Potion
[music]
a
Where are you, Orego?
Leo
[music]
Oh it's okay
Miko-senpai, I'm going to go make a potion now.
But would you like to come with me?
potion potion potion
Position A
[music]
Senkyuou
Okey, if you put it over there, it will be automatic.
It will become
Amazing automatic
Is there an automatic in this game?
automatic is automatic
potion mecha
Apparently
Yes, you can clear the sewing machine too.
Yes, because there is a real mission.
That's right, Potion's mission too.
Clear it and
Too god too
Even Dain told me to wait for him.
I guess you just have to wait.
Chan said he would bring that.
I understand, I understand, I understand, I understand.
Right, Tomy
[music]
home Isn't everyone waiting here?
stomach
[music]
Why don't you wait here?
uncle
Uncle Hass
Are you saying this on your own? Who is saying this?
Which
I wonder if it's okay? Who is this, senpai?
Whose house is this uncle's house?
Is it?
Hey, someone didn't make this.
Irohada because I'm saying that my shins are red.
Iroha-chan's song
I see
Villager generation facility created by Ono
Seriously, the colors are correct
Amazing!
I think I'll report back.
Is it the Kingdom of Feelings?
west
Yeah
yesoh
yes
[music]
Lee JAOS
Erei
Doki A Maki Jake
Okay, it's rock-paper-scissors on top, so let's do it.
I'll live and play rock, paper, scissors.
Hello hello, okay, let's do it
Let's go rock, paper, scissors, oh
[music]
I've decided, I've decided, I'm going to go!
Makitsu no Maki is okay Tsumaki Tsuno Maki
Yes, let's go, please.
Tsutsutsu no Maki Tsuno Tsuno Maki
Rock, paper, scissors
bread
I won and lost
I'm a weakling. How many times have I won today?
Tae hasn't won, he hasn't won
I lost to Amichi as well.
See you tomorrow See you tomorrow Tomorrow Tomorrow
I'll go in tomorrow. I'll go in where I want to go.
I want to see you tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow
I'll win too, so be prepared
Get ready, get ready, see you tomorrow I'll wash my head too
Wait for me
Thank you very much. I will win. Thank you.
Thank you, please be alive again tomorrow, please be alive.
Let's live until tomorrow, there's still tomorrow
There's still time for rock, paper, scissors, so live until tomorrow.
I feel like I'm going to live, I'm going to live
See you later. See you later.
[music]
Where is that face?
I want the key
[music]
abandoned iron door
I have to
I got it from Kerakora-senpai.
Taa
Kabao another door
Otoba-chan
Sunwoo
[music]
Please report to Sandglow.
Did Taro report both of them?
As many as 3 people in one Sado
I can go, I can go
Wait, there are 20 pieces to find Pega 4.
It's a lie, it's increasing, it's increasing, it's increasing, it's increasing
I made a lot of money today, so wait.
Isn't this the mountain we came from?
Looks like a mountain
[music]
pyramid
Chim is
is
Yo, make a trap.
Too bad
[music]
It hurts, it hurts.
over there
There is something
[music]
Yay
Someone please sleep with me again
Don't run away
[music]
Nice to sleep
good morning sleep
[music]
Miko-senpai isn't sleeping, it's okay.
mosquito
good morning good morning
[music]
You can now make potions all over the world
Yo
Eiyann
[music]
Yeah, this is good enough
So what?
[music]
Made differently
Teruagomengomegome
[music]
Wait, wait, wait
hand
Ets off
Should be
[music]
wait
Wait a minute!
[music]
It's a potion. I'll make it again.
Yo
Let's go in
this