[Music]
w
na push the button let me know
[Music]
before
push the button let
[Music]
me sugar babes push the
button
yeah oldie old
song
[Music]
the Buton let me
know the wrong idea and you're
to
if you're ready for me you better P the
Buton let me know before I theidea and
go
[Music]
going
wait that was the push the button lyrics
here we
are yeah k
k oh my God my oh [\h__\h] my
head ah [\h__\h] my headache
a am I supposed to turn on like bgm for
this game CU I'm guessing they don't
have bgm I know I'm not muted I sang for
you guys I even pulled up the lyrics for
you guys I did it all for
[Music]
you okay I guess I guess we need some
bgm
K oh right the oh the latency is [\h__\h]
but it it it I think it kind of has to
be this
way
um yeah no I'll play some bgm don't
worry about it uh we should probably
hide the comments my comments or those
comments that how do I hide them Oh you
mean like just cut the
screen but then but then it doesn't fit
my
screen
wait like this is this all the game has
to
offer the comments are from eight years
ago no way the game isn't that old old
is
it zoom in oh okay okay okay genius
absolute
Geniuses how about is this is this all I
need to show can I cut like this is that
all you need to
see basically oh my God so what kind of
game is this do I need Derpy music or
dorky music or ponkot music or cute
music what kind of music do I need
cinematic
everyone's doing it like that oh
okay it's a browser game guys everybody
can play it for free isn't that nice
noise I just need these two lines of
text okay I didn't even read them yet by
the way but if I understand correctly
it's just like you make choices what's
so interesting about
it what's so interesting is there even
like a winning like ah sorry is there
even a winning and a losing
Derpy is the
best serious M serious epic music oh
okay I think I have some
epic oh wait I saved nothing as epic but
I have like I think I have like
Adventure or this one wasn't this
[Music]
Epic
[Laughter]
[Music]
sorry I don't like I don't I don't like
the positioning of my microphone is this
good is it that's game then then the
music makes me [\h__\h] nervous
though I I still have this migraine by
the way I did go
quiet I did go to get a massage but
let's play this is when there's a really
difficult choice to make or
so
and oh this is
good oh this is really
good yeah I got a massage which was
really good but I and I think it got
better the the migraine but you know the
moment I woke up I had it again I've had
it for a few days now and people have
been saying it's not ahead that gets a
migraine
interesting interesting I don't think I
really ever had anything but headaches
before but
yeah heating
21 okay does that okay should we read
this should
we should I get into this I first of all
want to apologize though sorry for not
playing the save the diver I really
wanted to and then I I this time I will
admit it it's my fault this one time
it's it's my fault cuz I I just thought
it would be you know um fine to play
without getting
like perms cuz like we have perms for
the game but then it's one of those
games where we have to apply in advance
and tell them when we're playing it to
play it and I didn't realize I'm
sorry cuz like most of our games are
fine to just play Whenever most of our
game library is like that so I just
assumed I'm so
sorry I guess that's because you know if
it was an indie game if it was a true
indie game we probably would have
permanent
perms but uh unas it's not an a real
inie
game
lies no even when it's not an indie game
that doesn't necessarily mean what I
just implied um but more often than not
the ones than that need extra permission
are uh not indie games indie games are
just like whatever yeah you can play our
game whenever the [\h__\h] you want you can
even make it members
only
yeah H it is is there a reason for it it
just depends on the publisher like I
don't know some of the Publishers want
to have like an overview I guess I don't
know why cuz they I doubt that they
watch the
streams I don't know why but you know
some of them just want to know what's up
I guess I don't
know uh but yeah I'll play Dave Davey
next week I promise Davey you can't
Escape me Davey Davey no no no escaping
for you but uh finally finally we are
streaming I am happy about that um I
feel like my microphone is I don't know
you guys haven't been saying anything
about it but it's actually I think
peeking like not really peeking but like
it's it's just turned up too loud
generally I like it when it's loud in my
years but I literally hear it
being um blasting too
much yeah so I turned it down a little
bit I hope that's
okay do you guys want to know what I did
to get the internet to
work I did two things I don't know which
one it was I think it's me just moving
the mobile router to a different
position cuz the the like how to say
the m signal the signal was just better
5 cm to the
left I think and then I I kind of
opened like the
curtains hoping hoping that it will come
through I don't know if a signal like
has a harder time coming in through a
curtain but yeah just moved it a little
bit and then it kind of works and I
think it's really that uh sensitive I
think it really
is in terms of positioning mhm cuz I
tested it with my phone and depending on
where I was standing and how close I was
to the window depending on that my phone
would have yeah zero bars to one
bar I really only get like one bar on my
phone maximum
so yeah currently I'm no no it's not
Wi-Fi I have I have like a mobile router
not I'm using mobile data basically but
not from my phone but from like an extra
router from the
provider you know to like cover the time
where I don't have have actual internet
and then from there from that router I
have a cable going into my PC but the
router is not connected to you know the
the usual
internet uh opening in the wall no it's
just picking it up from like the signal
from outside I guess I'm I'm guessing
it's the same signal as what the phone
would pick up right yeah the F shy the
Wi-Fi F shy was
off why
[Music]
fu yeah yeah yeah yeah it's like yeah
like that
yeah uh yeah it's like a mobile hotspot
basically so that's why it's so
unreliable and I'm so sorry like
honestly I'm I'm the most sorry about it
to myself like I say sorry to myself
every day I'm like sorry wah that
everything is so [\h__\h] stupid right
now and then Wawa says it's okay Wawa
it's not your fault don't apologize to
yourself
Wawa um but I still got to try I still
got to try and now okay we're going to
play this weird game I don't know is
this even like
I'm only playing this because this was
like one suggestion you guys
had besides you know to to replace Davey
for
today this better be good okay what is
this I want to press it your lifespan is
tripled o and you will remain in perfect
physical condition for the rest of your
life if you eat 20 life worms a
day all other of but all other food will
taste amazing but eating think it will
make you violently ill and bedridden for
a
month so if I say yes to that means I
pressed the
button but I can just lie and say yeah
I'll do it but I won't do
it I don't have to do
it uh but also this disgusting I think
like at some point you'll get used to it
right but like getting over the first
hurdle
[Music]
M I don't feel like
it also what's what's a triped lifespan
even worth with how the Earth is going
into the [\h__\h] recently and my cats
won't even be alive so although there
was a study recently did you guys see
that cats like somebody invented
something I think even a Japanese
person invented something to make cat's
life like double
[Music]
I I don't know if I should consider
looking into that deeper I read the
article and it was
like I don't know oh yeah something
about their kidneys yeah cuz like I
guess their kidneys are often the cause
of them not living so long I guess yeah
yeah and dog owners meanwhile be like
yeah what what the [\h__\h] what about us
why only cats nobody wants cats to live
longer make her dogs live
longer yeah 20 to 40 years well yeah I
mean 20 years 20 years for a cat is
pretty
long I mean I I wish mine will live this
long but that's pretty damn long a lot
of them just live 15
[Music]
too dogs get hip problems I saw this
huge enormous beautiful old looking dog
today who was being uh accompanied by
like an older couple he was so big and
he was walking like like an older dog I
could
tell so big G gigantis G what gigantis
gigantis gigantis gigantis I think my
first try was correct I
think am I doing am I playing this game
right by just Tangen thing off of what
I'm raing I do want to say I I I
witnessed a crime at McDonald's today
cuz you saw probably that I got myself
some
nuggies and I witnessed a crime there
and honestly I really wanted to tell the
staff I really wanted to so I was
sitting um you know uh I don't know if
it's in the like this in every country
or probably maybe it's like for
McDonald's is on the countryside maybe
it's different but here you have to pay
now if you want to use the McDonald's
toilet maybe not in every McDonald's but
in a lot of
them um you have to
pay and crime yeah a crime I witnessed a
[\h__\h] crime so I was actually like
sitting across the entrance to that like
payment
machine
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah it might just be like
really crowded McDonald's is
McDonald's do you guys say McDonald's is
wait how do you say the plural of
McDonald's is just McDonald's I know pay
to PE yeah oh seems to be not so common
no no even if you buy something you have
to pay extra even if you bought
something
there no it depends though on the
McDonald's so anyway like I've been just
eating my thing and then like cuz my
when I look straight I look exactly at
the payment machine so I've been
watching people go in and out and in and
out and then this one guy he walks up to
it and then he just he shakes the bar as
if like he expects it to open
automatically he shakes it for several
seconds and looks around a little bit
and literally like like I don't know how
you can miss it like it seems like he
doesn't even see the payment machine
which is right next to him it would be a
logical conclusion as to why it's not
opening opening
up uh and it's like pretty like in your
face and open and it stands out this
thing but he doesn't he just shakes it
and shakes it I was about to say
something or like hoping that someone
else says something like hey you have to
pay you know it doesn't open unless you
pay
and then suddenly he goes on his
knees and he just
quickly crawls under the
bar and runs to the toilet and I'm like
he yo did somebody see this and nobody
else see around me seemed to have
watched the situation and I was like
should I tell the staff cuz this this is
making me angry those 50 Cent that you
skipped out on without paying
dude doesn't matter if he's a tourist
because it was written there in German
and English and it's like a very obvious
payment machine with a a a a sign that
shows you with what cards you can pay
and also like how much it is and all
that it was very obviously written there
but yeah he just went through and I was
like hey hey crime illegal
illegal little [\h__\h] what a little little
[\h__\h] I was legit so
mad but then I was thinking should I
tell little McDonald's stuff and I I was
thinking they probably don't care that
much about 50 Cent not being paid and
like making a fuss about it cuz they're
busy like have you ever seen a
McDonald's that's not busy as [\h__\h] I
haven't every McDonald's is busy as [\h__\h]
they they never seem to have a
downtime so yeah
having to pay to use is kind of crazy no
I think I understand it because like you
know when when it's in a spot where yeah
many tourists as well and just everybody
also
like yeah everybody traveling non-
tourists as well like hotpots then the
toilet's going to be used much more
especially from like people even go
there without buying anything and just
want to use a toilet that's very Comm to
so I understand them charging money Al
also because like it's going to be way
way way way way more uh upkeep money um
uh you know cleaning it all the time so
it's being way used way more than other
McDonald's toilets I would
say yep yeah yeah yeah but I wouldn't go
either if if you have to pay I'll just
uh hold it
in try watching for you guys are still
so shook about
that
damn yeah I don't know maybe in American
like big cities hotpots might also be
like that I don't know like New York uh
there surely there's a McDonald's in New
York uh Time Square
right that's crazy talk they're just
greedy no no no I [\h__\h] understand it
is there anybody here who play who works
for
McDonald's I am I'm trying to defend you
guys that's really not a thing in the US
even in b c the the one thing I would
probably say is that you should um maybe
get access if you buy
something like buy some fries and get
access to the toilet that I would say
would be more preferable but
yeah that's super illegal how's that huh
no it's
fine paying to pee is ridiculous you're
not paying to pee you could pay H you
could pee for free anywhere else but
you're choosing you are choosing you
want to pay in McDonald's McDonald's
doesn't owe you a
toilet I would say so pay up if you want
to pee in the
luxurious uh
building of
McDonald's usually code is on the
receipt no they don't have it
there you pay extra so
anyway bathroom rights are human right
oh my God what is this
controversy controversy what if it's an
emergency well then pay up
pay
up yeah I see it in in like some other
restaurants too or like um in like like
M museums or like tourist
attractions uh toilets like public a lot
of public toilets too like also in the
subway subway toilet often have to pay I
think I I don't know I generally always
uh stay away from public toilets and I I
I I would rather hold it in also in the
train like ew train toilets
disgusting always very
disgusting if only I could hold it in
for a whole flight a whole long
distance long distance Long Hall flight
then I
would me using uh idle meeting uh
establishment in the
airplane in the airplane is only because
I
must yeah so anyway sorry I'll move the
microphone one more time excuse me I
don't know why it's
so right now should we make our
choice should we make our choice
now have you guys missed
me Park toilets are nightmare oh I don't
they don't even exist for me
ew e e e e
e I would skip can can I do I not lose
immediately I I will
say for a month no cuz as I said I feel
like you you get over the life forms
after a while also if you like can you
the life forms can you would it be
acceptable to like Grill them and put
some spice on them because then probably
they'll be fine you could even put them
in in a meat grinder and make like a
burger out of it they were once live but
no they probably mean like eat them
alive but if you could put it into a
meat
grinder I don't
know also ooh actually worms are like if
we're talking like those worms that show
up when it's rainy they're they're kind
maybe we should consider eating them
because they're kind of like an endless
food source cuz they like when you know
when you cut them
off or like when you step on them you
know and then you know one part of them
is [\h__\h] separate don't they like
recreate themselves like they become
more and more what do you call that they
fix themselves and I feel like they
they're like an endless food source like
uh never ending food yeah so maybe
that's the the solution to world
hunger
um
[Music]
anyway they turn into two worms yeah but
like they don't become much smaller do
like they become bigger again like first
they're small but then they're big again
right I mean I
mean they don't no they they
regenerate infinite footage exactly yeah
okay anyway whatever so you didn't press
the button 30% have pressed it
Liars
Liars or very outdoorsy
people and 70% did not okay nice I'm I'm
the
majority are there more like reasonable
prompts I wonder let's read
it no they don't shut up they have
limits that's okay that's okay I
mean how do they appr
procreate your lifespan is tripled oh
wait it's the
same oh okay uh just to look at it again
okay okay probably right
okay he you are giving you're giv your
dream car an unbreakable one but you
will never be able to drive in who cares
let's go even it's like even unbreakable
like [\h__\h] yeah
obviously
what asexually they procreate asexually
how do you Pro repr procreate
asexually do they
adopt wow
[Music]
wow I'm waiting for your reaction on
that
joke but you're still reacting to the
car guys I'm sorry this is like you know
shitty latency just to hope that that
makes my stream more
stable I'm streaming on mobile data
after
all what is Wawa's dream
car I've been thinking about that a lot
I don't think I have a a particular
dream car there's several cars that I
like
um I do like some Modern cars
visuals but I feel like driving a nice
old classic car ideally which like one
that is like on the inside modern and
like has like a modern engine just the
outside is classic that would be like
super
cute but I don't know like I like some
Modern cars
too I and I I guess I probably for the
sake of the environment would get an
electric car but like not now anyway I
don't know how much Choice there is
nowadays with electric cars how how many
different models and companies there are
is every like big car company making
electric cars
now Custom Classic yes a retro mode yes
please give me the sexy car
and
cute I have an electric it's much widely
available Than People you mean the
charging stations yeah I think I mean
that that will probably be fine at this
point they're making more and more every
big company
yeah okay well that's definitely I think
what do you guys think is electric cars
is that the future I feel like more
people should go for electric cars
because
um yeah
because I just yesterday I watched a
documentary about a
certain certain gas
station how I think there's probably
several gas station companies who do
this like you you you charge your car
with the
gas you fill it up and then you you get
a choice to like um what's the what's
the word neutralize your carbon
footprint or whatever and turns out it's
all [\h__\h] because yeah it's all
hypothetical and it doesn't really work
with like how you get those credits and
all that how the company buys those
credits the places where those credits
are coming from are kind of like
[\h__\h] um because those places that
they're trying to protect the trees uh
the assumption that those trees need
protection often is very like pulled
pulled out of your [\h__\h]
ass yeah
yeah like one of those I saw like from
that documentary I saw like one of those
places that they're claiming to protect
is like literally already like uh uh one
of those zones that is like protected by
the law like
already yeah already so you don't need
to protect it it's already being
protected yeah
anyway that's how companies are trying
to claim that they're better for the
environment by saying they're buying
these credits and they are indeed buying
the credits but the they're not really
actually doing anything like those
credits those companies that where
they're buying their credits from BL
blah BL I watched a lot of interesting
documentaries on my off time yeah Nature
Reserve yeah that's what I wanted to say
it was already a nature reserve Hydro
hydrogen H hydrogen cars hydrogen fuels
I don't know what that is okay
double pried yeah I guess double is
better they need to be regulated much
more heavily yeah like it needs to be
clearer it needs to be more clear where
the money is going that you are choosing
to so to say
donate anyway I don't drive a car I
don't have a license so that's for the
future I suppose will you press the
button you gain the ability to
communicate with animals but you lose
the ability to communicate with
[Music]
humans I might do it to talk to my
cats I do Wonder though let's say I I
I'm able to communicate with my
cats they're
meows would we be meowing at each other
or would we have like brain
communication because if we just meow at
each other I don't think their meows
actually have like
clear
vocabulary like uh words do cuz cats
just meow for the sake of the humans
attention and all that right cble raid
oh my God I rarely get raided at this
time especially thank you
[Music]
Bo B right what was Kobo doing I
wonder Kobo I miss you how's she
doing I will ask all these extra
questions yeah [\h__\h] yeah I will I would
love to talk to my cats and like ask
them do you love me or or do you know
that I love you do you know that you're
adorable and like do you really like
these Kibbles or should I get you
different ones and then like I want to
make a test of which KES they like the
most and get like a clear clear opinion
from them
I would I would really love to play to
talk clearly to them and I've been
communicating with humans for a long
time so I think like I could give up on
that and the thing is if a lot of people
press the button on this and a lot of
people be able to communicate with
animals they're speaking animals
language so can I not also communicate
with those humans again I could even
even if that doesn't work if that's like
not working under this assumption that
pushed the button yeah yeah I just have
to think really really really really
detailed about all these things I'm
animal sometimes you are definitely as
energetic and loud as an animal
yeah but like that's M that's matter
yeah like you're talking to you're able
to talk to a cat and someone else is
also able to talk to a cat wouldn't you
have to be able to communicate with that
human as well then but let's say let's
say there somehow preventing you from
some magical magic then we could still
use the cat to like I say something to
the cat and the cat relates it to the
other person who's also able to talk to
the cat so the cat becomes the
messenger for anybody else who can also
talk to animals but not to humans
so I honestly at this point I would say
[\h__\h] yeah I mean I want to talk to my
cats yes yes
yes what only 35 people H
35% K what would you
do I I kind of I mean if you think about
never being able to communicate with
humans again surely I should probably
think about it a bit
more but my heart says I should
communicate with my cats and everybody
else all the other animals do you know
how interesting thing now would be to
like talk to the pigeons on the street
and talk to the ants on the road that I
step on like here their cries whenever I
step on
them how they say like [\h__\h] you why' you
kill me this hurts so much bring me to a
hospital bring me to my ant H they have
an anunt Hospital there bring me
there okay anyway okay enough dant
enough an
gents no it would be so interesting
though you could also talk to
cockroaches and be like [\h__\h] you get out
of here and I could have talked to
Casper my rat in Japan who was in my
ceiling and then we could just be you
know so much more understanding of each
other and you know and maybe you could
like if if you have a cockroach problem
infestation in your home maybe you could
make like a like a pack you could be
like okay
I know it's cold outside I know you're
just seeking warmth and all that how
about you just always keep like space
for me don't get too close we we're
going to set up some rules of how you
will be allowed in this
place let's just let's just talk it out
let's just set some ground rules where
you can go and where it's off limits
you're not going into the bathroom
you're not going into the toilet you're
not going into the
kitchen m
honestly I also don't want you in any
other room but if you if you need to be
in here yeah how about you just go to my
neighbor
yeah go to my neighbor because my
neighbor can't communicate with you so
you can't even make a deal like this but
let me tell you Mr cockroach if you want
to stay here I will kill you I will
terminate you and your
family what's wrong with me I need to
stop
talking
next you become invincible but everyone
on the planet has a murderous hatred for
you well
no
no that is really unnecessary if the
current status isn't too
bad this only makes sense if you already
have everyone on the planet against you
and then you need to protect yourself so
you become invincible so no of course
not
why why did like so many people say yes
to that that makes no
sense do you want to kill everybody
being Invincible doesn't mean that you
that you're like actually capable
of killing
others I mean you'd be Invincible yeah
but like why do that why why why is this
necessary for
you why do you want to live this
life
this just
stupid this
unnecessary sounds terrible yeah Edge
Lords uh yeah I don't I don't know that
really makes no sense for me it's so
unnecessary because what can they do to
you yeah but like they wouldn't do
anything to you if you just say no to
this and stay not Invincible but like
it's not like they're out to get you
they're only out to get you because you
choose
that so I don't know maybe I just hate
people no that's so sad don't say that
you're part of kfp you don't hate your
co-workers right you don't hate your
boss right you don't hate the customers
right I
mean customers maybe
partially yeah I get it I get it but you
know you don't hate your co-workers
right you love kfp kfp loves each
[Music]
other
yeah they could still imprison
you I yeah see I guess so I don't know I
mean you could probably fight your way
out because you're Invincible but like
why even let it go to get to that point
I don't know you were able to read any
book by merely touching it
but that's perfect for me but you're
unable to enjoy fiction of any
kind what does that mean like I fiction
as in dead book like I I can read it
without by merely touching it but I
won't enjoy it or do they mean something
else of
fiction
I would not press this
button fiction like video games too oh
oh oh and like movies as well well then
I will not because this is the same
principle I don't need this because I
don't even desire to read books much or
I don't need to read books
so yeah it's not necessary like the
current status is fine the way it is the
way life is right now isine
F so no yeah I do want to enjoy a lot of
the Rings
so we're in the majority
again you can go super saan but you have
to put up
with vegetables
whining about how he never beat Goku
uh who
what you have to put up vegetables
whining about how he never beat
Goku
um super
san it's like I know it's like that that
super strong State uh of being strong
and like right but like what exactly
does
that
do like what can I do is it like being
Invincible am I Invincible are we are we
like able
to overcome everything and
anything oh 50 times my current
[Laughter]
strength well if I'm super syion can I
not just punch vegetable in his face so
hard that he loses consciousness
I feel like we say
yes yes in my book that works and we are
in the
majority I feel like
that's almost like you won generally but
then we were into the majority with the
talking to animals thing so that's
really confusing to me I think that's a
win but okay I'll get spiky hair let's
go
he's basically as strong as
Goku Goku Goku Goku Goku Goku Goku is
the sound Japanese s sound when you
drink or when like like when you swallow
something
gokuu
Goku how do you actually pronounce his
name is at least in English it's like
Vegeta Vegeta ve V Vegeta probably right
I feel like I I heard that before
maybe I honestly don't know
though my hair will turn gold let's go I
think I look good with golden
hair yeah Vegeta
okay so it is like vegetable you become
a star but you have to wear Crocs all
the time a
star like like like I don't know like
Mars wait is Mars is a planet I mean you
know like whatever star like Pluto or
so would be weird to wear Crocs as a
[Music]
star I also generally just don't like
Crocs why you guys saying GAA was GAA
[Music]
here you're already a start thank you
the sun is a yeah yeah yeah the sun the
sun imagine the sun weing Crocs they
would melt but not not every Star is
that hot
righta please what Pluto is also not
wasn't Pluto the the the planet where
they said he's not a planet anymore then
I thought you you become a star if
you're not a planet you're like degraded
into a star downgraded no goodan loves
Crocs I wonder if she collects them
um with that knowledge I could probably
gift her Crocs even though I dislike
them it would still be hot with Crocs
thank
you Crocs are nice indoor we indoor
indoor I wouldn't wear anything indoor
I'm the type of person who either has
just socks or
Barefoot right now I'm wearing cozy
fluffy comfy
socks that's just a dwarf plan I guess
so yeah okay okay okay but like what if
you get downgraded from dwarf planet
even
further are you then a
star CA versatile yeah I I could agree
with
that many ways to look like a like a
dork yeah very versatile many ways to
look like a dork
bare feed mention D is an upgrade okay
whatever let's not talk about this
anymore uh let's let's take it actually
how it's meant to
be
um it's difficult like what kind of star
like like a singing star like on stage
performing star cuz then dancing and
cross box is difficult I think I never
tried it
but I don't know
it's a weird combination it's not even
such a bad
downside
so I mean if I'm a star and people
accept me with my Crocs then I guess
it's fine Crocs at the Red Carpet well
we could have Crocs the comp it's a
company right that makes these
shoes don't they also make other
shoes wait they they have like some
differently designed Croc Cy Crocs right
so maybe just under the name of Crocs we
can have different shoes that look
better they can like specifically
especially if I'm a star and I only wear
Crocs surely will have like some kind of
partnership going on and they sponsor me
or whatever I become their Muse or their
their main promotional model so for me
as their m news they'll make like
specifically tailored Crocs just for me
that are just for me and I think
honestly that could look pretty good
I'll do it I'll [\h__\h] do
it my brain works in the best ways let's
go the loophole
yeah I mean for stars these companies
like Gucci and so on they make like
special
products for their stars for the like
the red carpet and all that
anyway yeah yeah yeah yeah the custom
Croc
mhm it may not even look like a Croc
anymore once I'm done with
it I just talked about
you you have a ticket to experience
walking on Pluto but the ride to Pluto
takes 10 years it really
[Music]
does that makes me one to ask you guys a
question a light here I looked up the
other day something cuz I read the this
article that uh there has been found
a another planet that seems to be
similar to like our Earth uh and could
possibly you know have
life on it or like at least has the
criteria to have life on it but like 100
light years away and then I Googled how
long it takes to get there in 100 light
years and I had some conflicting results
how long does it actually take if I am
in like
a a space
car to go 100 light years to that place
to check it out to see if there's other
life there because like if we found it
then we should [\h__\h] send someone to
go there right
uh a
light no just tell me a number it takes
it would take 100
years 100
years
o well some humans live 100 years so we
should just send a an
infant depends on your speed well as
fast as we can
go
100 light year the distance light travel
don't say like this how long do we
realistically need depends on how fast
we well however fast a spaceship will
go we'll die before we get there what if
we mate within the
spaceship and you know our lives are for
the sake of science will'll send like a
couple that really love science will'll
send them out and then they make baby
and die in the spaceship now the baby
doesn't know what it's signed up for but
it will understand that it's for the
sake of science but then we might have
to put two families in there like two
couples so that however long it takes
those babies when they grow up they can
also
mate
um
[Music]
50 plus
Generations worth it though I think for
like knowing what's out
[Music]
there une epical space
experiments would you say it's worth it
to know what's out there if there is
another planet that we found that's kind
of like Earth and possibly has life on
it we should
go
how can we not go or at least okay okay
can we send a spaceship without a person
can it can a spaceship be controlled
with person probably yeah right but for
that distance maybe not but like can we
send it and like like put a letter or
like a video message like a
USB hoping that they also have uh that
technology ideally just put some letters
in there a book or something write the
something in there to tell them what's
out there
and then we'll become you know buddies
sending letters to each other and it
takes 50
years uh no 50
Generations maybe 500 years to get a
reply we already did it we've done that
wa did we send a message to to whom well
it probably didn't arrive yet
right Voyage of twins that's the Voyager
probes where did they go
let me let me
Google where did the
voyagers
go as of 2023 the Voyages are still in
operation beyond the outer boundary of
the heliosphere and int Interstellar
space they collect and transmit useful
data to Earth Voyager did things no one
predicted found scenes No One expected
and Promises to outlive its
inventors okay so is there a specific
place that they're trying to
go mission status Voyager oh NASA has a
mission
status I should work for NASA because I
just came up with this idea without
knowing that it exists so it's like I
invented it like you don't even know how
much more ideas are in my
brain it only takes 10 years though now
that now that we talked about how it
would take like 50 generations to reach
the 100 light years away place then this
doesn't sound like so much
anymore I think maybe I'll do
it but not right now maybe like in a
couple years later I think I'll do
it it's not even that bad what what's
with these chickens don't you want to
experience something super special walk
on
Pluto
gotta gotta get it off my bucket list
it's been on there for a long time now
walking on
[Music]
Pluto there's nothing on
Pluto um there doesn't need to be
anything on Pluto Pluto itself is the
attraction and the experience and maybe
we'll build something on
Pluto
maybe maybe we'll build
something with scraps in a cave I don't
know
just go to a desert desert at night [\h__\h]
my desert
pronoun that's not the
same no I I will become an astronaut I
don't care what you guys say about
it the first Carey on Pluto yeah it will
be me build a s castle Yeah is there
sand on
Pluto who went and to Pluto did someone
else go to Pluto first before me prove
the
new who has visited Pluto
[Music]
ear uh what who Alan Stern did Alan
Stern go to
Pluto these answers are so
[Music]
unclear a small step for a man but a big
step for w and chickens and
kfp is a giant ball of ice Frozen s k
dot dot no
human why not it's only 10 years why
wouldn't you
go why are you thought ding me why
wouldn't we go it's only 10
years why is there no dedication in NASA
why are they not more dedicated what's
with these astronauts it's literally
their job
10 years isn't even that bad if if they
already fear and step away from a 10year
journey then they shouldn't be an
astronaut and and then we're never going
to see
aliens no
commitment 10 to go and 10 to go back so
20 in total yeah that's fine but maybe
just stay then you don't have to take
the extra 10 years then just stay
then it's only 10 years Step It Up
NASA step it up oh my
God what I really really hope you're
doing a bit K no I honestly don't
understand why nobody feels like they
should sacrifice 20 years of their life
for the sake of
science or is there just is it not worth
it is it like we've sent like drones and
whatever up there so whatever can be
found about it is or there has already
been found so it's not really worth
putting a human there because like what
what are you going to do there build a
house yeah [\h__\h] yeah let's build a
[\h__\h]
house let's build uh houses and all
kinds of [\h__\h] so that when the earth
Burns we can go
there it's not worth it
prison s imagine sending people can we
do that can we build a
prison God sorry for saying that Mars is
more useful while it has ice and the
soil can grow CR okay okay okay then
change of plans let's go to Mars then
how long does it take to go to
[Music]
Mars oh my God way too expensive it's
free real estate
yeah is that what they're plan it's what
they're planning for more oh are they
building
[Music]
houses oh okay then we're fine then
we're good I I will I will support that
I will support that I can give up on my
Pluto
plans even though that sounds so nice
the Pluto
plans I will I will draft something up
going call it the Pluto plant and I'll
send it to
[Music]
[Laughter]
NASA you guys are telling me to stop the
bit
but honestly I feel like this is all of
this has to come out of me first because
you know all this [\h__\h] in my head has
pent up and i' it's been too long since
I have streamed and I feel like I need
to understand again what's normal to
talk about and what's desired to talk
about if this is weird and weirder than
normal waa then I'm sorry but I think
I've lost like my measurements and my
understanding uh and my my you know
everything I I need
to be I need
to re relearn everything sorry sorry it
takes a while it's like I'm rebooting
[Music]
okay anyway we're going to Pluto so it's
already decided so I don't care if Mars
is better I already made my
decision you'll meet your true love but
same
gender okay this is kind of like
um uh a
question where it will be determined
whether I
am I have a phobia or not but I mean of
course uh I would do it but I don't know
um if I'll ever meet my true love if
anyone like there is out there but if
you say that they are then [\h__\h] yeah I
am not
homophobic ah let's go true
love true love
baby but I already met my true love and
they are the same gender it's just
they're not the same type of living
being AKA my
cats it's true love because true love
doesn't have to be a sexual thing true
love can be true love towards a family
member or whatever like true love from
the heart love doesn't have to mean that
I want to make babies with you love can
also just mean that I love you so much
that I want to spend my whole life with
you and I do want to spend my my whole
life with my cats
so nothing wrong with
[Music]
that
yes not hold all interesting
statistics wait are
53% maybe part of the 53% already have
their true love so they said
nah I'm not
switching I don't know I will give them
the benefit of the
doubt based Wawa basack thank you thank
you because of me choosing my cats
okay the
shambles Cat Wedding stream
[Music]
when
that was a Red Bull cat no that was
still the cup from McDonald's did did
McDonald's also stop uh giving you
straws elsewhere cuz it seems like here
they stopped giving out straws for like
even for like when I get like an IC
tea and I asked uh how could I get a
straw and they were like sorry we don't
give out straws
anymore they don't give out straws
anymore
not even paper straws they they used to
have paper straws and now they don't
even give paper straws
anymore no mm- they switched to P paper
straws ages ago but now even that is
gone you guys it's coming if if if you
guys still have straws hold on to them
dearly and in every future McDonald's go
you do ask them for two
straws so that you have straws for when
the time comes that there are no straws
no more they they're probably going to
step by step get rid of the straws for
probably for en environmental reasons in
Sweden too okay so probably in Europe
they're starting in Europe I could see
that we're probably the test object
because Europeans are maybe more
accepting and open to these
[Laughter]
changes you're supposed to drink from
the cup yeah they still give me a lid
though like it's it's like like a a lid
that seems to normally go on a coffee
cup but you can open it and drink out of
there F just fine
yeah
yeah yeah get reusable straws I mean I
don't know I I guess if every freaking
restaurant stops straws then that could
become a thing like bringing your own
straws but where will that end in the
end we we'll have to bring our own
Cutlery we'll have to bring our own
plates at some point we'll just always
carry our own [\h__\h] Bento equipment to
eat at places even if yeah even like
this is not even take out just to eat
there then drink there one day they'll
take everything away from
us bring your own food or bring your own
Chef bring your own Chef or you are the
chef although there are uh I think I saw
places uh like that where there's a
kitchen and yeah I think there's
ingredients too but you have to cook
something bring your own food
yeah no but food food isn't I don't
think it would go there because like the
reason they're taking away straws is
probably for environmental reasons so
then cups I can see how that could be
next especially cuz
everybody is [\h__\h] buying those
Stanley Cups or whatever they're called
what they called Stanley Cups let me
Google
yeah the Stanley Cups have you guys
heard about the drama of the Stanley
Cups I heard about it I don't think it's
a thing in Europe uh at least not in
Austria but I heard about the Stanley
Cup crisis in
America you guys got issues man you guys
got some issues with those Stanley Cups
what's wrong with
[Music]
[Laughter]
you I think it's um mostly
uh women who are part of the
[Laughter]
crisis you know there's this uh company
called Stanley and they make like
tumblers insulated tumblers and they've
always had like collaborations with
other companies and now I think it was
Starbucks yeah Starbucks they had a
collaboration with Starbucks so they
brought out tumblers to sell at at um
Starbucks which are like limited
editions so they have a limited coloring
and they're pretty cute I think they're
uh pink and red two
colors and there's like literally videos
out there go look it up of like women
fighting and screeching over the cups uh
standing in line or getting like a
ticket system and and getting a ticket
for the cup to buy them and it's like
people are yeah it's like it's like
Hydro Flask all over again
exactly everybody's like going crazy
crazy and like honestly they look really
nice yeah but like people like you know
start a craze over these kind of things
um and then they post them on like Tik
Tok and Instagram and whatever all those
influences and then other people also
think they need to get that to be cool
and then it just gets worse and worse
and worse and everybody needs a [\h__\h]
Stanley stainless steel Club but why
would you need that if you have the
takanashi kiar uh was it fry yeah fry
reveal uh anniversary
uh insulated uh tumbler thingy if you
have that why would you need
that so
true definitely sounds like America mhm
I mean maybe maybe Canada too I don't
know but it looked like a problem that
is more on that side of the
globe it's just beanie babies all again
okay I don't I don't really know much
about beanie babies but probably yeah
you ain't cool if you don't have a cup
honestly I I I I I I like the look of it
so I kind of get it like generally like
even they're non-limited Edition ones
they look nice I saw like one video of a
lady who literally has like around 40 of
these and like lines them up like a
collection and they're like rainbow
colored like wow there's like so many
different shades and it's actually
beautiful
I don't care what others do with their
own money yeah sure I mean no if you
really want it then why not but it's
just a bit crazy like it's like
a h how to say a CR
uh it's like a trend that just like gets
like started because for no reason just
people post it on Instagram and Tik Tok
and whatever and then you think you need
it like you you just forcefully start
this trend and yeah it's just like any
other of
these tumblers and cups and like
whatever yeah artificial it's such an
artificial Trend yeah like it's it's not
like you really need that color
specifically you could also just get a
normal one but no everybody wants that
color from
Starbucks uh yeah anyway this question
is interesting because I don't know how
to drive but I also never aced my tests
unless it was
like English the subject English which
in my case was not um my first language
so for me it was my second
language I aced those
tests but
honestly I would say I would like the
first option because I [\h__\h] up so much
in
school and yeah I don't I I I've lived
my life so long without knowing how to
drive my mom
also is uh
yeah she never she she never got a
license and yeah I mean it would
probably be useful but you don't need it
you get around without knowing how to
drive at least in a
city maybe not in every
city but here in Austria or like Germany
I feel like in the cities even in the
smaller cities yeah I grew up in like a
smaller City and everything was walkable
okay so actually in smaller cities as
well like damn yeah [\h__\h] yeah I I would
love to know how it feels to not be
scared of every [\h__\h] test that I go
to and just to do well and not be scared
of getting back to test and the result
and all that I would love to know how
that feels
man oh that would be
amazing cars are optional in Europe yeah
oo
50% we are barely in the minority
[Music]
interesting
Well w wow I'm I'm I'm good with this
choice I like it it doesn't take
anything away from me that I already
have except my
failures h parents scolding over test
was bad I don't really think my mom ever
scolded me about getting bad
grades I think I scolded myself more or
like yeah I just felt really really
shitty about it but I don't think I ever
got really
scolded cuz I I really tried and I was
really really frustrated and desperate
about it
H it's just like at some point I feel
like when you fall behind and you start
getting bad grades in a subject and it's
just like at some point at least for me
I entered a state where I was just in my
brain I was so far behind with
everything like I understood I already
like when you when you don't understand
the basics and then things like build up
on that then you so [\h__\h] and that I
think was my
problem
hey this is uh implying that I would uh
either be a guy to date a girl or that
I'm a girl dating a
girl
okay
microphone yeah it's so hard to catch up
man I feel like I didn't have a chance
after getting a couple of shitty tests
and like not understanding what the [\h__\h]
is going on it was already too late
H they know you're
European so you marry your dream girl
but she will cheat on you
constantly well that's [\h__\h]
up
no I don't think about thinking about it
I don't think I was ever cheated on at
least not to my knowledge
which is I guess really
lucky cuz of how common let me ask
Google how many um
people uh are
cheaters 30 to 60% of married couples
will cheat at least once in marriage is
this like uh based on America or the
world
30 to
6% 74% of men and 68% of women admit
that they would cheat if it was
guaranteed they'd never get
caught okay 60% of Affairs start with
close friends or co-workers and aair
average of I don't care about
that isn't that just normal what not
being cheated
on my dream girl would not cheat ah
oh that's a
that's uh yeah if you say if if you're
ideal dream girl if in your dreams this
girl obviously I feel like every
everyone's dream girl would not cheat on
you so isn't this like
uh
contradicting it's a
paradox I will report can I report this
how do I report report this as a
paradox exactly
[Music]
Checkmate out smart at the question yeah
honestly true like yeah that's not a if
she cheats on you that's not a dream
girl I mean unless you kind of like like
it are there people who like kind of get
a kick out of being cheated on probably
someone out there kind of enjoys it
probably because they also maybe cheat
on them but then that's kind of like you
know you are you're accepting of it so
then it's not really cheating then it's
just an open
relationship I guess so in many ways
this is this is not a question that can
be
asked I will
not but I would never I I would never
even consider such a relationship like
an open relationship
no
no nope I don't know about you guys but
[Music]
no it's a fetish being cheated on oh
yeah right right wait is that what NT
is well okay like maybe like in like
fiction and all that but do do do these
people who say that's their fetish
really think that they would enjoy it in
real life too I
wonder I don't know about that I feel
like that's a difference
then it's happening in reality and it's
happening in fiction or
so never
never I would you
would to my chat kind of of stopped
moving I see it on OBS
though this hyper chat right
now Hy chat um not going to lie recently
for me has been not so great
so I don't know Mr Harvard
student um [\h__\h] died it just died let
me reload
it
you'd be surprised there are all kinds
of people out there yeah I mean surely
there's someone who enjoys it there's
there's someone for everyone H just good
luck finding them okay yeah that's hyper
chat that's hyper chat
man okay okay okay okay it's working
again it's moving again if I marry you
will you cheat on
me I don't know depends on how it's
going between us
depends on if I'm happy I guess it's
hard to say that
now iide
not chica poo please what
[Music]
what what you're laughing wow
okay what if your wife cheats with your
girlfriend what how is that what how do
that mean
what
damn wow I don't know I can't really say
I've never been married so I don't know
and especially it depends on the person
that I would be married to I
guess
uh but ideally yeah ideally it should be
ended or not not even be married no
before know cheating
yeah ideally I don't know it depends on
the circumstances you know so moving
on wait people ah people mostly said no
right okay you get to have super speed
but you can't stop running unless you
slam into something really
hard
oh does it hurt though probably right
no no if I hurt myself each time oh my
God I'll [\h__\h] ruin my
body I'll get so [\h__\h] up choya no more
of this what's wrong igard what's wrong
with you just don't
run yeah okay can I
walk but then this is useless if I'm
going to end up walking
anyway
Sanic
I feel like I played a game where this
was literally
me you don't you don't even need to get
speed force what you don't even get
speed force what unless you're allowed
to slow down first I don't think I can
slow
down super speed also for reading and
writing stuff instead of h i wonder I
mean it's not clearly stated so if we
take it like super speed for
everything like
working and thinking and talking and uh
drawing and typing holy [\h__\h] most
efficient person in the
world Pizza Tower oh yeah Pizza Tower is
like that but did I play pizza oh yeah I
did play Pizza Tower but I already
erased it from my me memory cuz it was
not fun I think was it fun fun did I
enjoy it I was certainly not good at it
I don't remember if it was
fun okay I'll just say no because this
is
stupid I don't want my life to be Pizza
Tower most people said no anyway you got
everything you've ever wanted but it
will be one month before your
death oh so I'll get it one month before
my death not like I get it and then I
die one month
later
everything I've ever wanted one month
that's so sad I barely get to enjoy
[Music]
it that's not nice I don't like that
that
sucks I got triggered hard Rage Quit
yeah that's probably what happened
mhm no downsides to this one no kind of
sucks what if everything I ever wanted
what if at that point it's like for
example a child
so but then doesn't it start with
pregnancy but then I die one month
later so I don't really get it unless
like it just suddenly appears the child
the infant just suddenly comes out of my
body without me ever being
pregnant but then I only see it for one
month that sucks this is
terrible this
sucks no
it's a
miracle literally no onet of course
there is it's [\h__\h]
depressing but then I guess
ideally until one month before my death
I already would have achieved most
things I've ever wanted and gotten most
things I ever wanted and then the last
few things that would be left over would
maybe be something
like $20 million and a yacht and
whatever and then yeah I get to use it a
little
bit yeah maybe I don't even know if I
want it right now like right now I don't
have a desire so I can't say I want it
but maybe someday I want a child and
then I'll get it anyway way way before
my death so then that wouldn't be on my
wish list
either so then probably the few things
that I need that I want one month before
my death aren't aren that much and then
we could do it okay I could reink it but
we already made our choice and said
no you will have the ability to jump
into any story book TV show and be one
of the characters in there or be one of
your own characters but you can only
visit each one once
what
yeah but what if I just stay in
there and then even if something gets
shitty I would switch Yeah I would I
would [\h__\h] do this I want to be
like in the world of Charmed and Lord of
the Rings and all
that [\h__\h] yeah and The Great Gatsby I
want to [\h__\h] party with Gatsby I will
[\h__\h] party with Gatsby Gatsby let's
[\h__\h] go a little party killed
nobody [\h__\h] yeah yeah and the Lord of
the Rings like right before some [\h__\h]
orc kills me I'll just switch to the
next World for example or Charmed right
before a demon kills me I'll
switch amazing that's amazing think
about all the things we could do I will
save Gatsby and I I ideally I I will
have Gatsby marry me I will be the
object of his desire I shall be his
beloved
yeah [\h__\h]
yeah I'll fix him
[Music]
man
genius I I mean I wish that can we make
that happen can we make that true
please
this is such a stupid game cuz nothing
will ever happen it's all just like in
Fury I hate it nothing will ever
happen you could eat ice cream as much
as you want but you would have nightm
every
night I can already eat ice cream as
much as I want what do you
[Music]
mean this is a stupid one when I I
desire ice cream I eat ice cream now if
I had an unhealthy obsession with ice
cream where I want to eat it 24 hours or
day that would be maybe uh a health
concern but at the moment I certainly do
not require this in my life and I've
actually been eating a lot of ice cream
recently cuz I found um new ice creams
are being sold from milka which is like
a chocolate brand here and it's like the
purple one you know I showed you guys
probably times before and they made more
ice creams um and I tried and they're
yummy and before that they had Kinder so
many chocolate brands are making ice
creams these days you know it's just
amazing oh my
God yeah so exciting yeah milka ice
cream they have an ice cream from the
the strawberry milka strawberry there a
strawberry milk bar which is like milk
chocolate with strawberry filling
strawberry cream filling inside it's so
yummy and it tastes like exactly like
the chocolate
[Music]
yeah wow we're already living it without
the downside exactly I don't need
this ice cream in the winter yeah
recently I've had quite the ice cream
craving for real for
real mica's pretty
International maybe you can get it but I
don't think it's very popular like in in
in North America for
example I haven't seen it in the shelves
when I was in America so it's not as
common but you can probably get it
yeah here in Argentina milka is really
good milka is good everywhere [\h__\h] yeah
love
[Music]
milka you do have nightmares often
though
coincidence I used to have way more
nightmares when I was a child child
nowadays recently it's been fine is
haven't had so many M nightmares
recently just been having a hard time
sleeping cuz everything [\h__\h] hurts
that's my
problem I have it in the Euro section
oh you guys need rport as well then
[\h__\h]
dasb dasb is like
I don't [\h__\h] understand I will never
I will never understand why R SP got rid
of my favorite
flavor years ago and no matter where I
got I never see it being sold they sell
like all kinds of flavors that they've
had for years and then new ones as well
but they never sell the one that I love
the most buha
cakes speaking of buha cakes my my cat's
movie I think it was yesterday I was
sniffing her while cuddling her and she
kind of smelled like buta cakes Li nits
buta cakes like butter cookies from
lipets
yes which is not like uh I don't think
it's what you guys are thinking of when
you hear butter cookies she she smelled
exactly really slightly a hint of liit
[Music]
P
in should have it no I swear everywhere
I go they don't have it they don't sell
it anymore I need to go to the RP Cafe
in Berlin that I've been to Once where
they have like every [\h__\h] flavor need
to go
there I could probably also order it on
Amazon like a package of that flavor but
I don't even care that much anymore I've
been SE separate from that chocolate
brand for too long we've been separate
for too long and I'm kind of over
it I've moved on I'm back to kinder okay
Kinder
[Music]
and sometimes milka yeah I don't need
you in my life
rport I'm over
[Music]
you yes I mean the Kusa cakes flavor
yeah
they are super good I loved them I used
to love them anyway you win any car if
you choosing it is limited to 35 miles
hour yeah I can read that sheesh but how
much is that in
kmh at all
times it's not very fast in any case
right that's pretty
[Music]
slow let me Google unless you guys tell
me 35 M pH H in
M oh 56 that's not that slow I mean
that's not too
bad I would do it I would do it it
doesn't mean that that has to be my only
car in my whole life I would love to get
a car of my choosing maybe maybe I would
go for a classic car cuz I don't want to
go with the classic car onto the highway
anyway so that's actually perfectly fine
yeah that's fine just not going to go on
the highway because I would even if it
could go fast I might still not want to
go on the highway with that
car that might just be my my city car
[Music]
yeah yeah around town it's fine totally
fine you just have to drive like an old
jel it's fine I'll just bring it to uh
Pimp My
Ride not Limp Biscuit right what was his
name what was his
name what's the Pimp My Ride guy again
no limp is good what was
it
ex we've had that before we certainly
had that
before I bring it to exhibit and he'll
he'll manipulate so that I can go faster
if I really wanted
to nice
nice one of the best TV shows of all
time have a [\h__\h] aquarium in your car
or like a
disco yeah [\h__\h]
yeah and next up how many questions are
there how long do I play this
game you can read other people's mind
but while you're reading their mind they
can hear you reading
it h that's kind of
okay I would I I think that's kind of
good they should know they should know
that I
know what they
know and then stop
knowing
anything should refrain from thinking
around
me I want them to know that I know that
they're thinking shitty things about me
[\h__\h]
yeah yeah it's a
[Music]
superpower kinky not
kinky get out of my
head no I shall continue to live rentree
in your head thank you you can't do
anything about
it a lot of people said yes to that one
Metallica Never released
Lulu what metal but Metallica never
released I don't give a [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
what Metallica released or did not
release I I don't care well I don't give
a [\h__\h] I yeah sure whatever I don't
care what are they both really beloved
songs I guess I don't care at
all do you guys care a lot of people
said they don't want it to happen but
did they push that because they don't
care or because they really don't want
it to
happen don't care about Metallica [\h__\h] I
don't
care in German Lulu is kind of a cute
way of saying peeee no not peeee pee is
also a cute way of saying Lulu which
means um uh
peeing like do you you say to a child do
you need to go
Lulu do you need to go uh peee peep Lulu
again do you have to do peee or do you
have to go Lulu you it's like a childish
way of asking your child or a child if
they need to go to the
toilet
yes what
says
oh you know okay never
mind be best friends of your favorite
cele
celebr
celebrity what this sounds like sounds
like a vegetable but never have any
other
friends who is my favorite
celebrity
would it be Natalie
Dormer what is this
Spelling
City would it be Natalie
Dormer is she my
favorite could could honestly like also
be Lisa my favorite jaese
Idol I always wished I could be friends
with her but never having any other
friends sucks so
no n uhh wow I'm surprised 35% say yes
this is because they're hoping to have
more than a friendship with that
celebrity I are they adding extra rules
and and such things to this
to make it even more nicer what they're
getting away
[Music]
with most likely yeah it's only friends
it doesn't even say Friends with
Benefits no you're not getting that oh
[\h__\h] what Fedora you get a superhuman
physical skill a 20 times longer
lifespan uh oh uhhuh oh wow can change
your physical appearance once and you
become filthy rich but you now have a
cursed Fedora that you cannot remove
from your body it will always make you
look hideous and repulsive to everyone
including yourself no matter how good
you
look is this a dis on
fedoras I love hats I don't know how I
feel about a fedora but if everybody
else hates it but I become filthy rich
it makes me
repulsive kidos maybe doesn't matter but
repulsive is the problem like people
even if they don't care about my looks I
still couldn't make friends with them
probably because I'm
repulsive but a lot of rich people are
repulsive and they still have friends
because they their friends maybe want
their money or
something or even have
wives and and uh
husbands were just in it for the money
and they're still
repulsive I mean I would give an example
right now but that would be a political
statement
but so I could still have friends and I
could probably force myself to think
that those are real friends even if
they're
not I could pay them to act like real
friends they might do
it also look at a [\h__\h] superhuman
physical skill like let's go I live 20
times longer 20 wait 20 times longer
that's a little bit too long what's 20
times longer my lifespan I'm a Phoenix
so let's just say I have a normal
lifespan like a human lifespan let's
just assume
that marry a blind person oh oh yeah or
all my friends should be a blind
person only I would only have blind
people as my friends then they can't see
the
Fedora so I I don't look hideous unless
they can sense the Fedora who
knows 2,000
years I don't want to live that long
that might be the real issue
because yeah although then 2, years then
I could go to that planet that's like 50
Generations
away if I'm so repulsive anyway nobody
wants to be with me so with my Filthy
Rich money I'll buy a spaceship and my
superhuman physical skill will be that I
can breathe in outer space and my
lifespan will help you know for uh
traveling and then once I reach that
place you know there'll be aliens or
whatever there who look different from
what we look like so I will change my
one time only physical appearance I will
change it to whatever the people dare
look like [\h__\h] yeah I nailed it I nailed
it and then they will probably not give
a [\h__\h] about my
Fedora wow big rain I used all of this
to my advantage and I will go to a
different planet because you guys hate
Fedora so
much perfect
plan that's the perfect plan
y
y they might like cursed fedoras I don't
know maybe being repulsive and hideous
is a good thing to
them yeah or my Fedora may have died in
that
lifespan who knows who knows what
happens to the Fedora but in any case I
feel like I made the best thing out of
the best out of this
situation yeah literally Galaxy brain
you get featured on IE funny but you
lose your left big
toe [\h__\h] well why would I do this I
funny is that like a website that people
use still to this
day that is so 2010 I mean apparently
this game has been around for a long
time cuz there were comments from ads
ago
so I funny man is that still a thing you
guys check it out is that so thing I'm
not going to Google it
now is it ion.com or
what such a bad deal
yeah like why would I want to be
featured on life
funy no that's not my life goal not
worth it I prefer having my big
toe apparently you can get rid of the
small toe because it's useless
apparently but the big toe I think I
need it you get to go to any cartoon
world you want Pokemon Sanic My Little
Pony there's so many cartoon worlds that
you could mention and you mention
[\h__\h] My Little
Pony why mention sh back or something I
don't
know why won't you mention My Little
Pony oh my
[Music]
God oh my God yeah the big toe is for
balance we need it I checked you are
featured on that I
huh I'm
not what's wrong with My Little Pony
sorry you a brony I'm so
sorry
ah ah
ah oh
oh wait
[Music]
I
okay sorry I have flum
issues
uh but what what was the butt but you
can never go back or take anyone with
you I think I would and Pokemon might
even be one of the best
options [\h__\h]
yeah I think I would do
it I think I would do
it would you guys do it cuz
50% 54% wouldn't do what's wrong with
you guys why
not cartoon you know also this it's kind
of an Escape
Plan Earth will go down but
cartoons will just exist
forever have a perfect body I already do
but okay let's let's uh think that let's
just assume I don't have the perfect
body yet your face will look exactly
like your uglyest selfie and you're not
able to change it including
makeup
[Music]
well but that's kind of weird
because faces don't always stay the same
you would they're saying your face just
always stays that way you can't like
move your mouth and eyes and everything
to make it look
that's so
weird it doesn't apply to me cuz I
already have a perfect
body and I can't even take a bad selfie
I mean the worst it gets is like like
[Music]
this that's the worst I can
look I can't and even that doesn't look
bad like I don't I'm not capable of
taking a ugly selfie
clearly you use a
back yeah but I already have a perfect
body so I don't know it's just not a
good question for
me just not a good question oh 77%
anyway did not want to choose
that they don't want to be ugly or
they're just already happy with their
body at the
moment infinite gang Mone well I I I
would not want to have infinite Gangi
indeed
yeah flexing no it's just a factual
excuse me you can travel forward through
time whenever you want with no
repercussions but you can only travel at
the speed of 1 second per
second so I'm not am I not actually not
moving through time
then if I'm moving forward one second
per
second am I just am I not just like not
going any where like I'm just living
life as per
normal yeah okay I'll do it because
that's just
normal yeah what did they Pur ful have
that make no sense are they trying to
play mind games on
me that's so
weird the troll question
okay trick question you have unlimited
money to spend on whatever you want
forever but you have to watch the person
you love the most
die well that might happen
anyway I mean
mean High chance that that will happen
anyway but like
when in like a like do they is does
their death get accelerated and it
happens now or is it in death bed you
know me in the future with a with
Grandpa lying in bed and he dies in
front of
me I don't know if it's now then my
loved
one would be my cats and perhaps I guess
also family would count I don't I don't
know would that be now that's uh sad
that's to too early I need
specifications I would assume that it's
just um
normal normal time like not now
so then it's a yes because it might
happen
anyway
yeah says person oh kind of see my cats
as
people I kind of see my cats as people
to me to me yeah when I say my cats are
like my family I mean it like it's an
actual person to me it's a baby
and just it's it's a person like it's on
the same level as a person to
me okay let's go you can
have spicy time with your best friends
girl why is the this whole game always
assuming that I am uh either gay or gay
or a
guy
this game
can just it's assuming my
gender
stop this game is so it's for 12year old
boys what is
this okay I don't know let's just you
know think of it as
whatever
applies
because all these questions were sub you
can submit
questions submitted by 14-year-old
boys really
though it works perfectly since you're
so European anyway no I'm
not I am
Australian H so what uh but every girl
you have spicy time with afterward will
fake it
well will I be aware of that let's say I
was a
guy from what I've heard from studies
I've
seen
uh wait let's Google how many women fake
it
uh all research found that uh out of the
2,000 participants surveyed 68% of women
68% admitted to Faking It with their
partner this may be news to some men
however as 27% of male respondents told
us that they fake really did you
how but
um oh another study here says sorry guys
up to 80% of women admit faking it so
yeah I think like you know you know it's
already very common
so but wait let's turn this around and
apply it to me I don't want to have even
without
consequences I don't want to have such
relations with my best friends's
Partners I don't desire this at
all they are like great people but I
don't want to do that like they're great
great personalities and all that but
like
no never had a desire to do that no
thank you
no no
no no I don't desire that thank you I
turn it down I
[Music]
reject
not going to steal your girl or your guy
or your man I don't I will not do that I
promise you know everything in the
universe including the meaning to life
those God exist
e is there no spell checks like the what
but you can never tell anyone you know
well I already do know everything so I
don't I know all of this so no but um I
guess I don't know if aliens exist which
is why I'm going on my travel to uh if
100 light
here distanced place um
those
42 yeah but you can't tell
me don't tell
me you could you could make so many
people's lives better better with that
knowledge without telling
anyone
how I mean you could certainly make your
life your own life better like if you
know everything in the universe like you
have all the knowledge also
about everything wait this means I know
everything everything that I would ever
ask myself I already know so I would
know I would know
everything burpees did you hear
it I would know everything this could be
good and bad I I could know a lot of
terrible things too that I don't want to
[Music]
know I
I I guess I could know how to cure
cancer if there is
secure what if there just
[Music]
isn't but yeah M don't say don't say
cute burpees I did not it didn't
happen ignorance is bliss for real like
if I think about all the things that I
try to not know because they're
[Music]
terrifying yeah know maybe it's better
to not know everything I don't want to
know everything cuz like even even if I
know some good things too like I can't I
mean yeah I can I know all the answers
to the test questions in school for
example that would be a good thing but
besides that like
I
H oh you know what I would also know I
would know everybody's credit
card like security codes and I would
know your social social social security
number I would know everybody's phone
numbers too so I don't never have have
to ask ask anyone for their phone number
I I would know all the answers to a test
to get a driver's license I would
know I would know when there's I don't
know I don't I would I don't I don't
know I do know I don't I know everything
I would know everything I would
know I would
know everything I would know how how to
make you guys and everybody else like me
more I would know how to succeed in life
I would
know
everything but also I would know too
much
[\h__\h] yeah I would know when it's going
to rain I would know when the world is
going to end for real for
real but I can't tell other
people I would know if aliens exist but
that doesn't help me because they're not
going to contact me
I would
know every language in the world that
would be
dope why would I become less is she
saying she knows
everything you could take action on it
then it's all on me then that feels like
incredible in immense pressure if I know
when and how the world is going to go
down or or if I know like you know if I
know everything then then I know also
when some some atrocities would happen
maybe and then it's on me to prevent it
or to not prevent it and then if I
didn't prevent it then I would feel so
guilty about it
too [\h__\h] I have to say no this is like
too much pressure and too much knowledge
and that's not
good oh oh cuz she's the alien oh oh
that's what you're
saying her demons know everything
what you basically have no free will
left if you already know what you will
do and what will happen
[Music]
yeah you would know how to erase your
own memory if you need
to
that's not
good but you'd also know how to
indirectly tell everyone about
it but will they believe me because I
mean even now like let's say let's say
an atheist tells a non- atheist God
doesn't exist like doesn't mean that
they'll believe you they probably won't
believe
you and that's even telling them
directly telling them indirectly they
even more will not believe
you no they will only believe it if it's
written on the internet because you
believe everything that's written on the
internet
no nah Moving On Moving On A lot of
people say yes to that one
apparently they don't think hard enough
they don't think about the consequences
they just accept it like that they did
not think hard
enough you don't want to know so many
things trust me
no you would also know if there's an
afterlife or
not and you would know what needs to be
done let's let's say I don't believe in
it but let's say there's a heaven in the
hell you would know who's going to hell
and who's going to
heaven and you'll be
like if somebody's mean to you you're
like ah whatever that person's going to
hell
anyway
become
mea no I wouldn't become Muka because I
would know what the consequence would be
of becoming Muka already I would already
know it so I say no to you qby I will
not become a magical girl under your
[Laughter]
[Music]
contract you you you would know where my
second hat is I know exactly where my
second hat is and currently I'm also not
wearing my first hat but you don't seem
to care about my first hat today do you
you only care about my second
hat thanks for the
membership afterlife sounds awful
eternity is too
long yeah it's such a weird thing to
think about because it feels like once
you think about it like your brain is
going to explode
but I I will say I personally don't
believe in an afterlife I mean it's I
think it's amazing if people believe in
it because that certainly takes away
some fear of
dying but I don't believe in it and that
that's also what makes it scary but
whatever like I I trust
my beliefs and I don't want to force
myself to believe something
else yeah but it's great if you think
that an afterlife exists
I hope I hope it does but I don't think
so I think it all just gets dark and
you're gone and the world moves on
without you [\h__\h] depressing [\h__\h]
depressing that thought is so [\h__\h]
depressing I don't want to think about
it thank God I'm a phoenix thank
God yeah yeah it would be nice if there
was something but I don't think there is
no
yeah but everybody can believe what they
think they believe and honestly it's as
I said I think it's
more it's a nicer way to live to have
something to believe in really it's
nicer gives you more more I don't know
sense of security and uh maybe even um a
drive
to live in life and also to
die or like a relief about dying
yeah so good for you you can turn into
anything you want but you'll be stuck
like that yeah I mean that's fine let's
let's do it let's [\h__\h] do it I don't
know what I would turn into but you
know it's depressing if you wanted to be
depressing yeah true I mean
yeah yeah you you can see it just as
being you
know really
Le
yeah become cat yeah that's definitely
an option that I thought
of
but how about I become a cat girl Best
of Both
Worlds I can still do human things and I
might be even really successful as
that and people will turn me into a
science
study
I'll become a
Catgirl he'll turn into Natalie Dormer
for
me but does that mean the other Natalie
Dormer disappears are you the only one
then will you still be like her
though will you get her appearance only
or also her personality and her
voice first real
Catgirl do you have to transform right
then and there or can you save it for
later these are all questions that I
think you decide for yourself you you
make the rules in this game every single
human will be rich no more poverty but
then that's just the standard they
wouldn't be rich and economy would
adjust to that too and everything would
cost so so much that rich would just be
normal you know what I mean houses and
food everything will be adjusted to
that but Africa will be wiped out what
the [\h__\h] is wrong with this
question what the [\h__\h] is wrong with
[Music]
you who who did
this first of all this as I said
balances itself
out like what the
[\h__\h] what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] Jesus
Christ no this is why we said to censor
the questions nah it's fine it's not
like I I came up with that you will get
to marit the person of your dreams it
will be marriage of convenience for them
what does that mean oh like I'm just
like way happier like I'm so happy and
this my dream marriage but for them it's
like like they just like married me
because I guess no one else was around
or
so why I was their last resort and all
that yeah that [\h__\h] sucks [\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you did I need to go
therapy because I need to understand
that the person that is apparently the
person of my
dreams [\h__\h] hates
me and I need to understand that and get
over
it yeah maybe they also just want you
know my Austrian
citizenship you are fluent in I already
am but you can never speak another
language no matter how hard you try
honestly this is like fine but I already
speak more than this so it would be a
downgrade no thank you if I only spoke
English then I would take this
deal but I already speak more than
that so
no the Korean
Arc it already feels like the same
prompt but like with with German English
Japanese and then I'm just incapable of
learning anything new because I'm I
don't know I'm just past the point of
being able
to yeah take in anything
new you get free tickets to see your
favorite band including backstage passes
but they hate you and tell it to your
[Music]
face
um that is
depressing I don't
know did you practice Korean no I didn't
time passed by so
fast new jeans hates
Kiana I wouldn't say they're my favorite
I don't even know who I would say is my
favorite I don't even know who I would
choose then but unless you're into
[Music]
that you
see
yeah uh I think if they would tell me
that I think I would stop being a
fan don't know about you guys but if the
thing that I love
tells me that they hate me then I think
I would be very [\h__\h] sad and move
move
on I
think black ad pece huh I don't know
they're not active anymore I don't like
their current
state oh I think they are active right
didn't they get like they they've been
trying new singers and all that but I
don't
know you already hate your favorite
B what
happened music still good though yeah
but I don't know I feel like in a lot of
cases like for your favorite band it's
more than just the music that you enjoy
often often you also just like them as
people especially like for for you know
when I when my favorite band was my idol
group that I loved Betty's coal for me
it was way more than just the music it
was like the girls their their
personalities and all that so if they
would hate me then I don't know their
music wasn't even that good like their
music was dorky as
[\h__\h] so it wasn't even that much about
the music it was more about the
experience and the hype concerts and all
that I don't know they had some good
songs for sure but they also had a lot
of goofy ass
songs but yeah um
[Music]
why go backstage just to be GED G GED ha
it
on yeah but you don't know that that's
coming
probably yeah and any case
I I wouldn't know who that would
be but I'm kind of like the thing is
like back in the day when I was an idol
fan uh I loved going to concerts but
nowadays even the few artists that I
enjoy like let's say K-pop I considered
going to a concert before but I quickly
like deleted the idea from my head
because it kind of scares me to go to a
K-pop concert and yeah it's just like
kind of like
an a scary idea I I think I'm fine not
going
especially if that's the
consequence I don't really go to
concerts
[Music]
anymore
no why why
because I see like how like at the
chance like I used to know the chants
for for uh Jpop you know but I don't
know how to chant for K-pop so then I
don't know how to fit in and I don't
know it's just I don't know I don't
really need it in my life yeah
I don't blame you thank you thank you I
want to go whole live concert someday
please come I hope you can come to a
whole life concert
someday I only went to your Ian concert
wow yeah I think a lot of people just
don't
really go to concerts at all
[Music]
so I do have to say though like those
were some of the most fun times I've
ever had in my life going to BTY
or like hello project
concerts I got my stage one ticket
already oh my god let's
go yeah wait I I
know I'm going next year in person let's
go wait can I do a
poll who here is going to the concert
the Fest the Fest in person in
Japan me not
me all right let's do um I will watch
online I don't know if I will watch it
at all why the [\h__\h] let's just assume
that's money
issues because um I don't understand any
other reason why you wouldn't want
it let's go p p p p p p p p p p p
pa yo 10% oh it's it's getting less but
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait out
of 500
9% 9% out of 500 how how many people is
that now it's 7% out of uh oh why is it
going up and down 800
800 why does it go from 840 to 811 it's
like something weird is going
on a th000 votes 6% from a th000 how
many people is that
uh
60 6% from a th000 is is it 60 did I do
math
5% from thousand F yeah 6 that's quite a
lot I I have to say actually like of
course that sounds like nothing 5% but
if you think about it like these are
people who are probably traveling from
overseas to go to Japan to the concert
in
person that's that's a big amount I'm
excited that you guys will be there WAOW
that's
actually big way more than I
thought crazy
crazy crazy crazy
crazy you're mathed let's
go yo so smart it's because I have my
glasses on today
yeah let's
go yeah and in chat right now yeah
imagine how many people are just not in
chat right now I don't know I don't know
I think as a kfp you're so deprived of
kiaha right now that you have to be here
right
now it's kind of no choice we develop a
completely clean and efficient energy
source but all existing workers in the
power industry lose their
jobs well will there be new jobs like
here probably
right is is the power
industry is bad for the environment
right we should do this
yes you'll find new jobs we have to do
it because the world will burn soon it's
already burning Michael Jackson comes
back to life but the weekend
[Music]
dies
um I can like live without them I'm not
a fan I I wouldn't say I'm a fan of
either of them like yes there may be
songs that I enjoyed in the past but my
life wouldn't be any
different but probably probably a lot of
people would choose Michael
Jackson I personally don't
care I don't care I think the weekend uh
made a lot of bangers that are in the
radio like a lot of collaborations
also um but I can live without all of
them uh let me let me go on
YouTube the
weekend they
did
they
did uh blinding lights I think I know ah
isn't that the
one I think I know that one blinding
lights nothing nothing else comes
up the weekend Greatest
Hits ah ah ah I can feel my face when
I'm with you that's one of the songs
they made that I know also they did
something with Daft Punk I feel it
coming I think I know
that
uh 50 shade of gray song which one that
I can feel my
face that's a 50 Shades of Gray
song but I love
it
why do we why do we talk why did we talk
about that in both of my streams since
I'm
back anyway I really don't care um let's
just leave it the way it
is because that's
life oh oh H only
40% want Michael Jackson to come back to
life
H I thought it would be
more guess there a lot of a lot of
Zoomers you become a mathematical genius
I already am I just I just calculated
how much 6% out of a thousand is so but
you can only speak in a dead language
like Latin
[Music]
huh yeah that sucks can't
communicate unless I'm communicating
with like some
geek we can communicate in math or in
Latin the geek might also know
Latin uh but I don't know I I I'd prefer
not to I'm I'm I'm I already am not a
mathematical genius let's be honest and
I'm living life just fine without
it
[Music]
what what was that discussion I
had
what what was the discussion I had and
with who did I have it with you
guys or was it with an IRL friend about
what was it even
about do you guys know what I'm talking
about
[Music]
I had some discussion I just remember
this reminded me I had some discussion
about dead languages and I feel like I
was making a great
point
a what's it with narissa about Latin
yeah oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and the
mes and then people told me my point is
correct yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah what was the what was the
discussion that like uh I yeah cuz she
was saying we don't even know how Latin
or any other dead language was supposed
to be pronounced and I was saying I I
think we would know because of records
and languages that came from like Latin
as the basis but also records of how I
don't know written down records and I
don't know you know certainly there's
like ways of knowing yeah yeah that was
the discussion yeah I have a PowerPoint
it's such a strong point it's a
PowerPoint
presentation when you have a really
really oh my God if you have a really
really powerful
point the way the best way to prove it
is with a PowerPoint presentation you're
almost you almost have to oh [\h__\h] oh wow
oh wow that's when you miss make a
PowerPoint
presentation every PowerPoint
presentation is just a powerful point
that you're presentating present
[Laughter]
presenting you should learn Italian
uh I kind of wanted to in the past yeah
uh I think I did I did I did learn
Italian
before
yeah I actually did I just forgot about
it but I did for three years but only
this is the worst way to ever learn a
language I I was always saying like it
makes no sense that they're teaching a
language at this school cuz I was doing
this like program where you specialize
in one job so you do the job for you're
like a trainee at that job for uh 10
months a year for three years and the
other two months a year you go to the
school that specializes in that job so
for me that was like
hotel and uh we had to learn a language
during those two months for three years
so in total it's only six months but
that it gets
interrupted it gets interrupted by 10
months and you come back to school and
they expect you to remember what you did
10 months ago what you learned 10 months
ago it's crazy I know that some of these
like specialized trainings like uh like
unlike the hotel one depending on what
you choose some of them have it a little
bit differently where you don't go 10
months in one go and then two months to
the school in one
go in other cases there's like it it's
like spread out throughout the year I
think you go to the school once per week
I think something like that and then
that kind of seems
more effective
maybe yeah for everything else that we
learned I think it was fine but for
language learning I think it was really
not
efficient yeah and I was still one of
the better ones in my class learning
Italian but I was like really brute
forcing it man is not the way to learn a
language two months a year and then a
year later you go back to it it's just
really
stupid
yeah anyway this question we kind of had
something like this before you can see
the future but you can't change
it but can I talk about
it because talking about it like maybe
other people will change it yes they
might just not believe me but I'll make
them believe me for this one I will say
yes
because
h
yeah doesn't mean I know everything ever
I only know the future and in the other
one it kind of implied also just I know
everything ever ever ever that there is
to know I only see the
future yes it it's kind of
different and yeah I can talk about it
so in the other one I think it said I
can't talk about it I know everything
but I can't talk about it this is kind
of different
are you guys even having fun with this
like this this feels
[Music]
like I think we're going to end it soon
because I don't see the point anymore in
doing
this the more I do this is the more
stupid stream seems to me we can just
read super chats
[Music]
um really I make it fun is basically as
that yeah
yeah the tangents are
good okay
okay suddenly snapped out of it yeah I
don't know just feels
weird I do like the tangents that come
with it okay I like listening to you
thank
you thank you that's sweet your
reactions are fun okay you could change
your eye and hair color without dying it
or using contact
but you would be
fat
um what the [\h__\h] is this
prompt what the [\h__\h] is this prompt like
this isn't
even like anything that's so
desirable I mean it's not really
necessary and this is such a 12-year-old
boy's
prompt but but you would be fat
ew so
stupid Define fat yeah that depends now
I guess it would be like uh
scientifically like once you're
overweight once you're proven to be
overweight H oh you will gain superhuman
Powers this is like this is kind of like
this whole thing is like those super
chats that I get like uh uh imagine you
know
G speaks SCA becomes your cat but
you MMA hates you what would you do this
is like those super
CH is this where you get it from
huh this is the website you get getting
all your ideas from GAA becomes a
towel oh
man guys we really need to do that
Valentine stream eventually though
because gab was going to call in and she
was so motivated about it um and I'm
sure you guys want to hear GDA say
pickup lines to me
right we'll still do it
eventually I don't know
maybe I I don't want to do it right now
I mean I may be able to stream right now
but I don't really know about like
Discord and all that I currently have
Discord closed so I'm not sure how the
calls would affect my internet um I
prefer to just do it when I'm guaranteed
to have good internet cuz I don't want
to set up the whole thing again and have
people Reserve time in their schedules
to call in just for me to cancel it
again I don't want to do that again why
they oh yeah right that's exactly 1
month later yeah let's do it for white
day although white day isn't that
like during the
concert
uh isn't that kind of during that time I
think I'll be in
Japan I I'll certainly be in Japan but
oh the 14th is
Thursday so okay I could probably do the
stream and then
actually then time zones might not be a
problem because I think you know we'll
be in Japan
so I'll be in Japan we'll be in
Japan so everybody can call
in no
excuses everybody will call in [\h__\h]
yeah I did by the way I saw a clip pop
up from M I didn't even realize she was
planning on calling in I did not watch
the clip because I was
thinking um eventually if I do the
stream and she still can't call in I'll
just watch the clip and see how my heart
rate
reacts I didn't watch it yet so she can
still eventually call me and still say
the same lines if she wants
[Music]
to off collab off collab yeah it will
probably make me go more doy doie but
then I'd have to have so many people uh
gather I'd probably still just do it
over cins but yeah she wanted to call in
so bad really I'm surprised so many
people were so motivated about
it yeah I didn't watch the clip but
apparently it was really good like I saw
people go crazy about M's pickup line so
good
H as soon as you said you couldn't she
tweeted oh
really no she wasn't uh planning on it
back then I think
but could have been a surprise
visit yeah I don't know okay if we're
doing a d the participation list might
look very different but I think um the
ones who are planning to call in will
still probably call
in biu was excited yeah bibu was going
to call in too
yeah
I hope she didn't use up uh all her
pickup lines for that card that she
wrote do you guys remember I did the
same exact stream like what two years
ago three years
ago I think no I think two years ago it
was my my first Valentine's stream was
the one where I made chocolate and maybe
my second Valentine's stream was the one
where I made the cards I made
Valentine's
cards Le see still read our pickup lens
yeah I
mean uh I probably won't get to read
many so you can guys don't even post
anything under the hashtag anymore
there's I probably will only be able to
read like 2% of what's in the hashtag
because especially if if it happens next
time in Japan then plenty of people will
call in she saved the pickup line okay
good good good good
good
uh on that note since we're talking
about traveling I want to say something
uh after this prompt and then I'll go
tell you and then I'll read super chats
you will gain superhuman bows you'll be
able to regenerate mortal wounds you
will stop aging and you'll be capable
[Music]
of
fear doesn't mean farts is it a typo and
it's supposed to be capable of farts of
superum strength
then definitely a 9-year-old wrote it
but maybe it means feet
feet ah Feats ah yeah that's a word
right uh oh okay okay okay could have
been farts you never know you honestly
can't know you can't know what was
really meant to be written here it could
very well be
farts but you'll have to subsist on
human FL in order to survive okay so
I'll become a cannibal I'm a phoenix so
I guess that doesn't make me a cannibal
if you don't you risk turning feral
before eventually perishing any other
food will
simply okay guys I think I've outgrown
this whole game I I'm like just tired of
reading
this
I I can't I'm I'm over it I'm so over it
like no I can't answer this
this so stupid I've grown numb
[Music]
and I don't want to even think about
this this is all dumb why are we that's
doing Hy
prophetical questions at
all oh this is just a waste of time I
wanted to play Dave the diver next week
though we're going to play Dave the
diver next week
okay let's see how my room looks oh ah
okay I have to [\h__\h] I have to resize
everything or we'll just do it closeup
so we'll just do closeup
okay how about I sit on my bed I'm
totally sitting on my
[Music]
bed oh we can take down the Christmas
lights where is the chat
here
it was like that for M really do she
have like the same sensation after a
while there's not even like a winning or
a losing
so what's the
point so pointless I hate pointless
things like the older you get I think
the more pointless pointless things will
seem to
you the more evident pointless things
will
[Music]
be
I think all of them got tired of it
after a while okay did Kyla ever finish
all the questions just for the sake of
keeping her reputation as a
grinder it's not worth it Kyla it's not
worth it if she did then I don't
understand that's not worth
it there's better things to
grind and spend your time on Peak Jack
oh you're not that big you're slender
you look fine to me you look well
sized friend sized
actually too many questions she did she
did she she did do all of them or is
there I mean surely there's an end of
the questions but maybe they just loop
at some point and you don't even realize
it at that point cuz you already did
like 500 questions
and they all seem very similar at some
point website I went on casually when I
was 12 really how is this so old and now
isn't it kind of like ret trending as
like a streamer game now not even only
on whole
life friend shape yes perfect perfect
size did I miss the button this is the
button there's a more interesting button
that I like to watch
and it's embarrassing because you guys
will you guys will judge me so hard when
I talk about these kind of
things there's a there's a dating
show let's called the button on
YouTube from a channel called cut it's
it's funny
though sometimes really interesting
people show up that are so weird and
then there's some [\h__\h] Savage people
who are also [\h__\h]
weird it's funny and then I like I like
watching Cody Co react to the button
episodes cuz he's funny I don't
know I'm sorry I'm sorry this is one one
evidence that I'm a basic [\h__\h] I'm
sorry I'm sorry it's funny kind of grin
so you understand thank you
[Music]
but sometimes it's quite nice they make
some some special episodes where for
example it's the button but with Elders
or it's the button but with divorced
people because like normal episodes
they're so
superficial they don't even like give
each other a chance they immediately
press the button when it turns red you
can press the button and then you send
your speed date out and it exchanges to
a different person basically that's the
thing okay um if in case you probably
don't know what I'm talking about so
imagine a room a studio a table with a
button on it and two chairs and uh yeah
they put like people on there and it's
like a speed date and the buttons every
once in a while will turn on red and
then you can press it and if you press
it first then the person in front of you
changes to the next person and the goal
is to find someone that you like then
you get a
date yeah
you're our undying Lord oh my God it's
IRL dating apps yeah but it's like
surprisingly Savage like people just
push the button immediately sometimes
without even talking to them much um so
it's very superficial and then sometimes
they do blindfold it a button for
example they blindfold the people you
know there's like special types of these
things that's
interesting oh it's just funny
especially when C Cole reacts
[Music]
oh yeah speed dates yeah yeah yeah and
then there's like a it's funny there's
um like a spinoff there's an Australian
version of it and it's just so
[\h__\h] the Australian versions are so [\h__\h]
but only really because like they didn't
they don't have the same setup so it's
like so scuffed like they have the other
candidates
like audibly screaming in the back like
listening into the conversation and all
that and oh my God it's it's terrible
it's
terrible anyway anyway anyway anyway
anyway
so I wanted to say uh no offense but it
pisses me off when I see the woman
rushing for the you watch
it you watch it too I'm so happy when
they're barely talking yeah no it's it's
not only women though it's also like
it's both sides are
[\h__\h] really both sides oh my God yeah I
Cod Co I've only been watching Cod Co
for a few months now I
think sorry sorry
H there was a girl that was kicked off
the show because she kept rejecting
every guy of the first sentence yeah
yeah yeah like eventually when you
manage to reject everybody first before
they reject reject you the the the the
mods so to say will eventually be like
hey you rejected already like four
people sorry we're going to switch you
out next time you press the button you
going to be switched out instead of
them oh yeah and then the funny thing is
one time they switched it up so like no
matter how often you press like the
moment you press the button you're
switching out yourself not your opponent
opponent so to say your date and then
suddenly barely anyone presses a button
they just like even if they absolutely
hate talking to each other you can
observe this
awkwardness in them like like trying to
make the other person like them even
less by being extra boring so that they
will be forced they will be like just so
[\h__\h] done with you that they press
the button they purposefully like try to
seem even less attractive or interesting
so that you press the button because you
don't want to press it because if you
press it you're being being switched out
but you want to stay in the
game it's so interesting though because
it completely changes the dynamic of the
game you know it really feels like they
see each other as opponents like often
in these this show it really doesn't
seem like the the people even try to
find anyone to go on a date with they
just I don't know they just want to
reject people and literally sometimes
the button asks them like okay why did
you reject that person and then they're
like I don't know I thought they were
going to reject me or like I don't know
just because or like whatever they don't
even have a good
reason oh thanks for the
raid it's just a a look into the minds
of people is so interesting how people's
minds
work how how it just shows how you
become so
defensive like not even on this show but
like I feel like it shows how we as a
person as a soci Society we become so
defensive that we we even we want to
reject people or opportunities or
whatever just because we think like
we're going to be rejected or
whatever even if that wouldn't even be
the case we don't give people a chance
because we think maybe they wouldn't
give us a chance you know what I
mean we're just uh really defensive
creatures insecurities yep so this
now yeah get them before they get you
exactly that's the
mindset you don't want to be hurt so
hurt them
first that is such deep psychology
guys this is what it is we truly live in
a
society yeah okay so I was saying
because I was
saying I was saying because I was saying
uh uh that I'll be going to Japan right
next month
obviously
[Music]
um
uh so
H
this may
seem like
a bad notice because you guys missed me
and you guys are going to be Doom
posting um but I'll try to not make make
it a bad thing honestly it would really
not be a bad
thing uh
but pretty suddenly and
spontaneously uh a a trip has been
decided
on but just trust me that it will be
worth it and it will be
good uh that it will come with
good
things out of
it okay
uh so I I I personally would have liked
this to not be right
after I so to say came back from my
break and I didn't didn't even come back
from my break properly Because the
Internet is [\h__\h] me over um so it's
not ideal for me but uh trust me it will
be worth it
um yeah I it will not be a break though
uh it's also not a vacation no no no I'm
not going to Bali or
whatever uh so that will be however very
[\h__\h] soon which is why I'm like like
I kind of wish it wasn't right now but
it's something that kind of has to be
now and it was really suddenly and
spontaneous so it's not like I could
have planned it it's like now or never
like something like that you know you
understand
though
you'll understand I just want you to
know that that means I'll be uh away
from home which honestly probably won't
even make a difference because I feel
like I'm not going to have internet for
a long time um so it won't even make
much of a difference probably in terms
of what I can stream and to what
capacity I can
[Laughter]
stream yeah uh
yes yes let's just say wherever I go I
won't be alone and it'll be fun and next
exciting okay off collapse will
commence but I'll be around and I'll try
my best to uh be active mhm and I I I
also will try my best to keep it as
short as
possible yeah it won't be a full week
either okay it won't be a full week okay
I'm so sorry it has to be now like I
it's really inconvenient timing but it
has to be now
what if I prefer solo streams I know I
know I know there will be solo streams
but also you know you'll you will be
like okay I understand you'll understand
you'll
understand
yes
yes speaking of traveling and all that
uh so just a reminder
uh was it the
19th what was it
aai
concert with the w the
wa oh this is the first time ever that I
was glad to be conceived no
perceived perceived as a
chicken or a rooster whatever oh
tomorrow tomorrow no it's okay
um I've been uh uh permitted to say it's
a
pre-recorded yes yes yes
tomorrow and it's really good it's
really really really good please check
it out uh what
time 9:00 p.m. jst is like
oh wait do we still have eight hours
time difference I think we still
do six
7 1 p.m. my time I
think it's so funny yeah because like
she
chose the the a
German
City like thing like I don't even know
how to explain
it
right I don't I don't know I don't yeah
yeah it's a it's a
soan uh meden uh fairy tale you know in
Japanese fairy tale is meden which is
based off of German so interesting how
Japanese language they have a lot of
English words japanized but uh they also
have a lot of German
words that they brought into their
vocabulary like meden mhm wait really
really yeah they say meu hen and it's
based off
from German language which is
Fairdale wooo let's go let's go I'm so
excited
Yahoo and yeah I I I really love my
involvement so I'm really glad to be uh
perceived as a
chicken only for this one time I will
accept
it yeah it's come full circle
now so please check it out um if we live
for the archive whenever you're awake
check it out on Aki senpai's Channel I
will remind you anyway I'll post about
it on Twitter
too I'll change the music now because
we've probably heard this for long
enough
[Music]
right nice
too loud
probably is this nice
volume GL your internet is working
finally it's not working um it's not the
internet I'm supposed to be
using and it's not very like reliable as
in like speed there's not much speed
that I can use that's why you know when
I had to change from Dave the diver to
different game I for a moment I thought
about power world but then I was like
Nah Nah if I want to join the server
that's it's not going to work solo maybe
cuz that's I guess not online but if I
want to play on the server which would
be the next
step that's not probably not going to
work while streaming at least maybe
without streaming but not while
[Music]
streaming good volume okay okay thank
you how would would be fun would have
been fun yeah I'll still play it
sometime I guess if it doesn't take too
long to get my proper internet
[Music]
yeah time to grab the internet Cube this
is basically that there's no better
option for me right
now good I wanted to see you play po
word
again
go
ball fingers cross thank you thank you
g k a CH in the thank you right you are
helping me get
started oh by the way
so are there any people who would have
wanted to get a Valentine's Polaroid but
haven't been able to get the super chat
in because they just I didn't stream
long enough uh and they came too late or
so cuz like we already gathered a good
amount just in the preach that
so I could just go with those or we do a
second run on white
day if a lot of people are like hey I
still want one you got yours in oh yeah
me really yes oh
really a oh oh that's quite a few people
really y'all didn't get one in damn you
guys got to send it at pre
chat oh okay just a matter of time I I I
feel like I always have this like
feeling and I've always been right so
far with like oh I don't think this is
going to work I don't think this
solution is going to work I don't think
this is going to happen you know and I
was always
right my gut
feeling okay so okay in that case I will
finish the current ones before white day
but I will uh also open it up again for
white
day for any body who didn't get
[Music]
one but if you already did get one then
you're not getting a chance to buy
another one
okay I like a second run cuz I've been
at work constantly okay you have good
intuition I think so too but people
still don't [\h__\h] believe me when I
say I don't think this is going to
work cuz I'm not a pro and I understand
like I have nothing to base it off of
it's just my gut
feeling
[Music]
okay so anyway uh blah blah blah
blah let me
[Music]
find the game
was really just fun for a while uh but
I'm I hope you you guys had fun listen
to my
rambling my crazy rambling about going
to outer
[Music]
space I need a I need the same outfit as
I'm a um God I need like a space
outfit
who by the way I think currently my new
outfit um that's been in the works uh
that's supposed to be a 2023 outfit it's
probably going to come out around
[Music]
May and then frog
week in I'm currently finishing up the
merchandise for it um it will
be within
March hope I think hopefully before I go
to
Japan and I have a couple of new frog
games to
play during frog week maybe I should get
some updates for froggy
waa although she was perfectly cute as
is I wonder if I can get her like if
evolved like maybe new expressions or
new accessories I don't
know she was so [\h__\h] cute man for you
out you're so
[Music]
cute you want your tangents made for 90%
right I
know but you give 90% to me and 10% to
chat and 0% to the
game fair very fair play Doom on frog
how is that a froggy
game because of my
[Music]
gun is she going to get even stronger no
just
[Music]
cuter I can't believe like froggy Wawa
gets a tongue function before me she
always had it but crazy crazy
[\h__\h] what do you have anything to say
about being able to commission new
outfits on your own like oh I don't know
anything about
that
[Music]
what yeah I don't know anything about
that frog fractions is a great
game uh I don't know if that was one of
the ones I got permission for I don't
[Music]
know
possible
honestly I don't know I don't know if
I'm really going to make use of that I
already have a hard time deciding what I
want to do and then planning and and
like supervising all of
that is already quite a lot of things to
take care of
so I don't know I'm currently fine with
that she has a members only to what
what do you mean members only is that
the the Restriction you can commission
an outfit and it will be members
only
what or is that just her
[Music]
choice remember was that was her it's
her decision
he I don't know why that option wasn't
announced to us then when when was
this if they pay for it that's two what
about fredd that's the important thing
for me I don't care about 2D I already
have so many 2D outfits anyway what I
want is a fre a fry outfit of my
choice what the [\h__\h] happened man no it
wasn't doing my break I caught up with
everything that happened during my break
wait I'm opening Discord right now
hopefully it won't kill my
[Music]
internet
oh wow
okay JMA sent me a
prompt
uh that
I uh like thankfully it didn't come up
but I should have avoided it but it
didn't come up I with my sheer mental
power I avoided that
prompt not I didn't know there were such
prompts in there do they like what the
[\h__\h] question hey
chat told me
[Music]
about
I mean I feel like like a year ago or
more than a year ago I heard about that
being considered to be made a thing but
then that was just a consideration and I
never heard about it ever
again and then I said I don't want 2D I
want
3D I wonder if the one
that did she get one of those oh okay
[Music]
well okay anyway sorry I'm so sorry I'm
stalling like always oh my God it's just
like usual usual Wawa
stream you didn't have your gam no I
thought maybe if I turn off Discord I
I'll have better internet and I I think
generally that does help a little bit
[Music]
yeah
oh what the [\h__\h] you guys are writing
weird
[\h__\h] sto my
beloved crimeless Europe
[Music]
question
yeah yeah yeah yeah like normally these
outfits they take
like I would say half a
[Music]
year maximum maybe but minimum still
like five months maybe five five six
okay then maximum could be way longer
I've seen others spending way more time
on it just because they're slower to
reply so it it could be like 10 months
if you're slow but if you're fast Maybe
five months if you're on top of
everything and happy with everything the
artist provides and you're just like yep
that's fine and you don't want anything
to be
changed um no but that you know
basically that means that
that has been an option for a
while and I just didn't know about
it will you and cie collab While y in
Japan Calli is going overseas present
tense or past tense
I mean probably I don't know we've
collabed many times already so I will
say that like it's not my priority if I
go to Japan I generally try to collab
with someone who I haven't collabed with
before yeah
um but it's always a a
[Music]
possibility
no I'll never collab forever again
yeah that's
fair well am is always a priority of
[Music]
course you're happy to just hear stories
of us hanging out yeah I think like you
know it's nice to just do things off
stream and then talk about it later I'm
generally a big supporter of that anyway
let's start reading some super chats um
hopefully this is the right one let me
just bring up the
image I think I need to save this one I
don't think I have this
one oh guys can you help me any it
people
here a while
ago I I kind of tried to clean out my
download
folder and I deleted so many things
and then an issue AR arised that I
didn't have
before um where normally the download
folder would
[Music]
load no wait a second now it kind no it
didn't fix
itself now it kind of takes like 5 years
to even though I deleted things it takes
like 5 years to load the whole
[Music]
thing yeah
why why I deleted things I made it less
heavy it's not empty certainly not empty
it's far from empty but I deleted things
and how full is my drive it's currently
not even
red did you empty the recycle bin I
think I did but let me let me do it
again there's only 12 things in there so
I think I did it previous iously so let
me try to load it
again o yeah it still takes a long long
long long long long long long long long
long
long long I don't know I you tell me if
I have an SSD or a
HDD no it's not synced with a
cloud def frag and reindex would help
maybe an indexing
issue optimize for General right click
properties customiz uh I can
shap wait what's that in
German
unass
[Music]
ah I don't know what that is what you
just told
me how do I defrag and reender how do I
do
that don't defrag an SSD you probably
have an
SSD did you press a button I missed her
I miss I I I pressed a few buttons
yeah I very much doubt that you wouldn't
have an SSD RBF would no a you don't
defrag anymore don't defrag okay
okay don't okay I'm not def
Fring
[Music]
okay
well a local specialist I don't want to
know it's still loading by the way a lot
of things already appeared but it's like
still not done
loading and I I actually I have the same
thing with
my uh video folder it also takes
way too long to load it's so
[Music]
annoying what is loading like the you
know the the bar at the top that says
like where you
are that like loads in green
color that thing and everything inside
the
[Music]
folder
the drive could just be dying
no okay now it loaded the video folder
but
restart this is an ongoing long ass
issue how many times have I restarted my
PC in in between a million
times anyway whatever I don't see an
Immediate Solutions so whatever write me
something on Twitter if you want I'll
read super chatos
now my eyes are getting tired
too yo yo yo
yo I'm not used to being up so long
anymore i' I've had such a sleepy uh not
sleepy uh good sleep schedule I mean
it's already been kind of like ruined
again but my body is still craving to
sleep at Good
Times you
know BG I'm still kind of loud people
said it was good
but okay I'll turn it
down a little
[Music]
bit hard drives have a limited
lifespan how how
long okay I'll discuss with um RBF Maybe
my downloads full crashes sometimes too
when other folders with the same content
don't some sort of Windows issue
oh when do you go to sleep nowadays well
during my break it was always before
midnight but now immediately I'm already
staying up longer it's like some part of
my brain is just like functioning
wrongly it's like oh wa is streaming
again let's ruin her sleep schedule for
no reason but hey I've at least been
still cooking before
midnight and eating before midnight
that's still currently actively being
done yeah it's like I shifted into
streamer mode like my brain has I've
been doing this for so long with the
sleep schedule that my brain thinks oh
back to work then work times it
is
but like with me setting my Max to like
streaming until midnight it's just like
bound to be like that because I can't
immediately within 5 minutes go to bed
after I'm done streaming at
midnight you know I I may like the thing
is I'm always like tired at the end of
my streams but the moment I end my
stream I'm awake again and I would also
like eat dinner and that also wakes me
up and all that so it's like you know
I'm just like I think I think my eyes
and my face is getting tired yeah from
the light of the screen and all
that and talking so much but I'm not
actually that tired yet and then I can't
sleep because I just ended work I can't
immediately
sleep awake for two after work yeah
exactly like there's some downtime
necessary and then you can
sleep and I don't really want to change
it like it's not like it's affecting my
life in a way that it's negative me
staying up until 3:00 a.m. or so it's
not affecting my life negatively and I
don't really want to stream much earlier
because I think the current time is
perfect for
me I like how I am uh during streaming
during European prime time while still
somewhat like I'm not going to stream in
the middle of the night just to be
streaming during Prime prime time for na
but I still think it's somewhat like the
best I can
do
currently me streaming at this time is
the best I can
do for my na
people you get the fake tiredness
too na prime time is also the most back
time exactly like I'm I I I don't think
I I can compete
chilling in any time zone the best
middle of the road situation exactly
yeah so anyway this one's really short
Jacob 47 D jailbird Roadstar Dan
moldies Sonic Master than to the pinky
hi Tel hi Sonic Master are you in the
chat sorry I'm reading it now after a
long long
time M are you
[Music]
here oh yeah I don't want to do the
twitch thing yeah simultaneously
yeah oh I don't see
[Music]
him maybe he gave up on
me cuz I I was gone for too
[Music]
long there you are sorry
latency yay I'm so sorry you had to wait
for so long until I read your Super Chat
I've been a member for over a year also
got the Cy plusy from your bday merch
recently and it's cute today is my b day
if possible can I ask for a happy
birthday belated birthday I hope you and
Raa enjoy the M thank you I'm so late
I'm so late I'm so sorry happy birthday
though Sonic Master thank you so much
for your patience and for your sweet
sweet sweetness and your loyalty happy
birthday I hope it was a great
birthday I hope you feel great I hope
you feel healthy and I feel I think
you'll accomplish everything you want to
in this year you just have to do it just
do
[Music]
it very related now but you guys know
you guys knew ahead of time I was going
to go on a break so anything any super
chats close to my break you know we're
in risk of not being read for a while
it is what it
is just do
it so this n just do
it the magical free
words say them tell me tell me my
beloved the magical free
words uh just do
[Music]
it no that's not what I
meant why not why not
it's so
inspiring maybe wait it's not free words
just do no it is just do it yes free
words for a moment I thought it was full
words oh my
God I love you that's not what I
meant uh anyway thank you so much for
the thinking for the support thank you
soon I hope you're going to enjoy the
merchandise thank you so much for
getting it yeah and if you guys don't
know yet there's Valentine's merchandise
of the Wawa out there right now so um
maybe you want to get it I don't know do
you where did I save it I think in
downloads and thus it will never load
but let me check is it in my resources
folder the
pictures pictures of
you pictures of
me um it's not in there so it's probably
in my downloads folder oh
[Music]
no you already got it you already order
it thank you it's it's pretty cute isn't
it it's pretty cute yeah I like how we
all have like some original cute outfits
that all like kind of match each other
but they're all also kind of different
from each
other and brown is such an unusual color
I think somebody asked me on
Twitter what should they do with the
little towel uh it's a small towel right
honestly for me I see so many uses in
that um I don't know if you're if that
person here is right now here and I
would ask you though uh if you have a
pet because for me um as it is kind of
inev inevitable to get hair everywhere
from your cat uh what I like to do um
especially uh you know for like the sake
of doing makeup but even without that uh
I just like to not have cat hairs even
if it's just one you feel it tickling
your skin you know so let's say you wash
your face and then you want to dry
it um and you use a you use a normal
towel and there might be even one
invisible cat on there and then you get
it on your face and you feel it the
whole time and you you somehow can't
pick it off of your face that sucks so
for that purpose I have a few uh small
really small square little towels that
are like face towels to wipe only my
face with that only and there's no hairs
on there because I keep it like away
from the like any place where their
hairs could reach like even if the cats
can't reach a place they still fly
around and somehow reach also I I also
don't like um wash it with everything
else so that way it stays stays
[Music]
hairfree so that's how I would use it
and another usage is I don't know if you
live in a really hot country but in case
you do I've noticed that like especially
when I go to a country like Japan where
it's really humid and I sweat a lot it's
nice to have something to wipe the sweat
off of your face like a small towel
H honestly in Japan I really need
that I often end up not having a towel
with me and then always wish I had a
towel with
me yeah so these are two good reasons
why you should have a little a tower
like that so go get it
[Music]
yeah I think there's other uses
too
can swing the towel at Contest no it's
too tiny for that I think isn't it like
handkerchief size yeah I think so so
it's not one you want to swing in a
concert no no that's not the ideal towel
to swing in a
concert no no no it doesn't
have the swing it doesn't have the
dynamic and all that you know it's not
good for that no useless useless
don't even attempt it it would be
pathetic it's a
patic concert towel maybe to wipe the
sweat that has been created from you
know vibing in the concert but not to
swing it yeah no physics not enough
physics not enough uh you know you have
to have a good grip if you want to swing
it around you also need a good grip on
the towel and if it's so tiny you need a
good grip rib then you're like already
covering all of it with your hand
there's barely anything to
swing yeah so don't even think about
[Music]
it no different towels for different
usage three towels stable together no
don't do that that's stupid that looks
so
stupid
[Music]
your ID looks at you your towel it's too
small it's
pathetic you can't even swing it
well oh I want to say one
thing I very much heard that one but the
other one people have been making a clip
out of uh what was it me
saying ah something about the screws and
then there were in the comments people
people were saying for sure she knows
what she was saying I was really
innocently just being excited about the
screws there was no such
realization I did not the way it was
edited in the clip I heard it
then but I did not I did not while I was
saying it I was really just so like into
it my mind was so excited thinking about
the SCU and telling you about it there
was absolutely no such
intention I swear you guys should know
by now I think differently because my
brain is German hi
a I don't hear it the same way you guys
hear it really I really
don't I really really
don't
I was just so happy about building
furniture and having an I I thought you
know cuz it was such a fresh experience
for me I just I thought you guys maybe
like screws and tools and all that
probably you
know big part of my fans are men so I
thought you know ho ho ho Tim Allen you
know men often like tools and they build
more furniture than I do often so I
thought you guys would like it so I got
really excited telling you about the
screws and thought we could connect on
[Music]
that
yeah please understand otherwise I can
never do a screw tier list again in the
future if you if you judge me for my
excitement yeah no no that wasn't Santa
that was a Tim Allen
impersonation you do I know you
do stereotyping chat no only part of you
only parts of you not all of
[Music]
you I think one screw te list is plenty
don't lie to yourself you know you want
more
[Music]
one thing I don't think I'll ever be
able to do unless I get really buff is
using a a b
[Music]
Ma and bore into star
Bon maybe into a normal wall but I don't
think I have the power to bore into
ston someone translate that for me
what
St I know how to say Bor in English but
um drill into
[Music]
a
uh yeah yeah I know the drill I know the
drill yeah
yeah yeah
yeah reinforced concrete yeah so like
I've never tried it but like even just
watching and
listening to someone else do it was like
oh my God it's so [\h__\h] loud I had to
hold my ears because it was so loud and
I think it's really difficult I think
you need some arm power and I don't
think I have
that
[Music]
you know what was funny before when uh a
friend was helping me with
furniture and asked me if I have a Aku
sha not a not what we just talked about
that goes into the reinforced concrete
no just
a fast automatic screwdriver
uh I said yeah I have one and I bring it
out and and and then the reaction was
like oh [\h__\h] no I'm getting my what was
it
Makita if it's not a Makita then I'm not
using it I'm like that moment I was made
aware
of the like brand superiority in
apparently apparently nothing else can
be
trusted the [\h__\h]
and then like my mom also said she wants
to buy a
Makita for her own usage in her house
I'm like oh wow Makita again okay
something about this machine must be
amazing this tool brand Yeah Tim Allen
would
[Music]
approve drill snob for real for real
tool elitism for real for
real yeah [\h__\h] drill stops you don't
even try you don't even give it a try
what
okay he like tried to like he turned it
on and then he listened to the sound of
it and the power I guess I was like
nah I'm sure it would have been fine but
it was deemed not enough not good
enough I didn't know there was such a
thing I didn't know you had to have a
Makita they're like family
heirlooms if I would have known that
nobody told me that this is the kind of
[\h__\h] that they should teach you in
school don't buy anything by but a
Makita that's the only thing you need in
life
apparently needs more
power did you reveal the surprise I said
no
I I don't think I
can maybe next
[Music]
week
you got click baited
[Music]
well no
no
no no maybe the surprise was that my
internet is working today and I can
stream maybe or it was something
else let me read the chat
now yeah I'll keep my secrets for a
little while
longer
I I don't know
[Music]
maybe Uncle Frank
un
Eternal T thank you for the red chat
glad to hear you two are having a good
vacation so far my vaction you mean
vacation sadly ended last week so I have
to go back to the Grind D's work I'll
try to catch the rest of the stream this
week or streams this week so looking
forward to that hope you will continue
to have a great vacation thank
you oh yeah at this time we were still
there I was just thinking
today I wish I could go to the moldes
again and I was like thinking I don't
know why the moldes has this special
effect on you that even though maybe you
actually didn't have such a good
experience um because of shitty weather
I
guess there's like you you want to
remember
it in such much more of a positive
light maybe because you spent a [\h__\h] ton
of money on it or maybe because actually
in reality it really wasn't that bad I
don't know maybe or maybe
the fumes that they spray around on the
islands to try to keep down the most
mosquito amount you breathe them in and
they're like kind of intoxicating you
and uh brainwashing you to think of the
males as a great place when actually the
weather is so [\h__\h] [\h__\h] even during
peak season um maybe that's what's
happening
but maybe it's because of who you with
who you are there
maybe but I think for
me it's also partially I think it's it
do be like wishful wishful thinking um
or like this like Ideal Image that I
have of the males that I don't want to
be
ruined um so that's like kind of stuck
in my brain so I I I I was I would even
consider going to the males alone that's
how much I really want to go
there like one thing I felt felt really
bad
about it's like with with Wayne I didn't
even feel so bad about it because I we
both experienced it and like for the
first time and now this time was my
second time and I purposefully made us
book during peak season and I was
expecting that it would be great weather
but then I felt
guilty and for like possible
disappointment that narissa would have
have about the
weather so when it would start
[Music]
raining I I would feel
guilty
yeah but even when it was nice weather
nerva would barely go into the water she
would go into the pool more than she
like we should have used the pool more
we kind of ignored the pool the whole
time cuz like we had the beach rid in in
front of our doorstep right so I was
feeling like why would I go to a pool if
I have a pool like I can go to a pool in
Austria but I can't go to a beach like
an ocean beach in Austria so I I thought
I should go to the ocean most of the
time but the pool was kind of nice man
cuz there weren't crazy waves and all
that does she not like swimming she uh
she says that she's not a good swimmer
and I say the same thing about myself
though we can keep ourselves above water
and uh with such shallow water that's
all you really need in my
[Music]
opinion it's not like we would go out
really
far not at all and even if you go out
pretty far it's still [\h__\h]
shallow it's crazy it's so shallow so
nice I love
that she really just wanted to meet me h
yeah but you know I I just felt this
sense of
um uh what's it
[Music]
word what's the
word yes
responsibility yeah I felt this weird
responsibility which is I feel like
which is why I I I would feel uh like I
could go alone because then I don't I
don't feel like bad for dragging anybody
into this and then it not being as nice
as I advertised it
as cuz I'm still fine with it like you
know it it rains but then it clears up
again so just go into the water when it
clears up Al on like this time I was
really kind of disappointed even by
myself cuz I really thought it would be
much better but it wasn't so anyway
sorry I'm like barely reading super
chats
[\h__\h] anyway Tassimo I hope work isn't
too harsh and too stupid I hope you're
doing well thank you so much for your
Super Chat and I'm back for real for
real are you around
too do I see you
T I like your names so
much were were you from Italy you're
donating in euros and your name makes me
and the image makes me think
you're Italian are you
[Music]
Italian I do plan on going to Italy
already twice this year I have two plans
for Italy this
year short trips though don't
worry m
[Music]
selfless I don't know if it's really I
don't know if I'm that selfless I don't
think I'm that selfless but you know I
just feel bad if I get someone's hopes
up and then they're not as excited about
it as I thought they would be not
Germany oh
okay sorry
CH sorry he wasn't Italian but hey you
found a different it Italian MOS mobus
and poto Shake
Hands yeah she had a good time with
[Music]
me Nissa said she did enjoy of course
she said that of course she did she
wouldn't even even if she didn't enjoy
it she probably wouldn't say
it not saying she didn't enjoy it but
even if she didn't she wouldn't say so
probably cuz that that would hurt my
[Music]
feelings Italian here Italians my
Italians please welcome me in your
country twice in this
year
[Music]
whoa
I'm half tell I shake half a
hand my brain
worms brain
wors okay guys we have to like do
something about my
non-productivity thank you Tassimo
here's a kiss and
[Music]
of I am a beep thank you and then
finally we read one two three four five
six seven eight super
[Music]
chats next is off collab reading our
diary entries from the males which is
such a [\h__\h] cute idea right I'm such
a [\h__\h] genius all my streams ideas
stream ideas are so
good I should be given a Nobel
[Music]
Prize for real for
real such a good idea such a good idea I
am such a
genius and I honestly doubt that my BPM
would change much but my Valentine's
idea is also so
cute it's just so cute in theory if only
pickup Lins would really have a bigger
effect I don't think they will actually
have a big effect if they did have a
bigger effect that would be great and
imagine somebody comes up with a really
really shitty pickup line and I just
Flatline that would be funny just for a
second I would just Flatline for a
second don't
[Music]
worry that would be great 69 it's so
[\h__\h] rude that my resting heart rate
so often is 69
man why do I have a healthy ass heart
rate but why does it gota be like that
man
why no I didn't as I said I I didn't
hear the M ones yet because I uh
purposefully still want this to happen
and want her to say them to me
[Music]
anyway yeah yeah yeah so she still has a
chance to impress
me
paty dangan unknown thank you for free
pinkies my POV CT is finally arrived I
ordered five thank you PO is just the
best album ever I really love dark
Sparks yeah it's just called Dark Sparks
now it sounds so awesome I really wish I
could stream it though yeah it's fine
it's like a a thank you to you guys you
don't need to stream it speaking of
streaming music the total time I
streamed music on YouTube music and
apple music combined in 23 is about wo W
307,000 minutes or
500 uh 5,127 hours I think I could do
even better this year I just need to
never turn him
off I just hope you know that your music
is genuinely incredible and nothing even
come close to being as amazing your
music is the best thing on Earth and I
will never ever stop listening to them
stream all WS music forever thank you
I have
become uh relatively motivated about
making music this year um I'll just have
you know I'll be going strongly into the
K-pop Direction I'll continue doing
that um but in the end I mean K-pop I
say K-pop but in the end that's just
like normal pop music basically cuz
K-pop is just trying to be
western style pop mostly but it just has
something about it that makes it K-pop I
don't know what it is but yeah it's
basically just pop music
but you know I want to try different
kinds of K-pop I want to you know within
kop there's like these different kinds
of Concepts you
know that I think even pop music can be
so diverse oh yeah K pop yeah K pop
I don't know if you guys have
ever taken the sub Quest from takanasi K
that is listen to new jeans music but
you know I want to kind of try something
that goes into that direction cuz like
it's kind of like calm
Bops a lot of them are very
dreamy something like that I want to
try but then also something girl crushy
like black pink which isn't my usual
interest in K-pop at all but you know
still
mhm like a badass girl
crush and then simply just something
[\h__\h] boppy like twice would put out
like twice has a very special
sound something like that so all kinds
of different Vibes of uh K-pop that I
want to uh try out and my team has all
of
this like yeah like all of these skills
necessary sleep talking is kind of chill
yeah I love sleep talking so
much so
[Music]
good you need to clear a jrpg side quest
first ah
faster yeah wow angels I love them why
is the we for completing the side quest
understanding my
tangents the old retrospective video is
linked in your PV playlist into the MV
version ah
o
o put that on a list of things I have to
to fix like also putting up another link
for the members wallpaper I'm aware of
it guys I
just when I read those messages I'm away
from the PC
um if I remember after the stream ends
I'll upload it again and make a new
community post with a a new link for the
members
wallpaper this list uh this website is
[\h__\h] me over so many
[Music]
times you want the Discord to help with
that whenever that happens
what help of what what
Discord kfp Discord help with what
I already forgot what what we're talking
about what do you
mean the number of times I get a work
email and yeah and like okay okay one
thing guys I I I I I I I I want you guys
know I recently like today yesterday
today yesterday I've been trying to give
you guys so many likes but so many times
I read over your um replies and I just
answer in my brain
and I like it in my brain but I don't do
it like I I I acknowledge your Tweet in
my brain 100% I read it and I maybe even
think an answer in my brain
like because you're asking a question
but you can't expect me to answer all of
your freaking questions
guys but yeah often like I I really read
all of your your uh replies to me um and
then that brings me to another topic um
I said I stayed away away from work
completely okay uh in my break but I
will admit and and I don't see this as
work I was just curious and and it was
only like positive vibes
anyway but every day when one of my
videos came up that I prepared
beforehand I did check your comments I
just didn't leave a like cuz I didn't
want you guys to be
like
she's she's working no I'm not working I
wasn't working I was just just checking
the comments cuz like I put uh a lot of
effort into all these preparations and I
just wanted to see your reaction to my
little
videos so I did read uh your comments on
all of
those
yeah and every morning I would wake up
at like 8:00 a.m. and I'm
like oh right let's check the comments
from the video that came out at 6:00
a.m. cuz I scheduled them all at 6:00
a.m. no I make the rules I'm not
cheating why am I cheating um I made the
rules for me that was that was within
the
rules I didn't do
anything I just read some comments that
were
nice it was like my morning
newspaper
no no it's not work I didn't feel like
work it was just a small small amount
anyway of
[Music]
reading shut up it's
fine anyway did I finish this I feel
like I finished it thank you unknown so
much for listening to my music so much
thank you for being so passionate about
it yo I think you're definitely my
biggest listener I think you contributed
the most to my streaming
numbers
sorry which I don't know if it counts so
much from coming from one person if they
stop counting streams at some point I
wonder or if every stream counts but
yeah thank you so much you're amazing
I'm so surprised you're not sick of my
voice and my music
yet thank you so
[Music]
much and Le Jacob 47 J monkey spank
andhe
D and for the friend Super Chat welcome
back waisa hope you have a wonderful
time in the islands it's freezing here
so the kitties are being extra
cly isn't that nice nice that's so nice
that's such a nice thing about winter if
your cats get cuddlier I don't think my
cats get cuder just because it's winter
but they have they have generally been
um cuddlier I think they because I
wasn't working and I was more available
to
[Music]
them I cuddled more with them and we
just had so much cuddle time and then
they also after a week of me being just
way more available I think they also
just really like they got used to it and
got really really addicted and and
really
wanted themselves they wanted to cuddle
more I feel like especially smovie
became even even CER so
cute we bonded so
much it's like I'm James
Bond
yeah so sweet my sweet babies my sweet
babo bab I love them so much I carry
smoovie around so much I feel like she
started to enjoy being picked up and
carried around she got used to it and
she accepted it and now she kind of
likes
it hey I'm their Bond
[Music]
girl yeah cats are the best thank you
spanking time you know today I saw this
crazy cat I think on Instagram it was a
Main [\h__\h] which it was just a you know
we we we know generally main coons get
really big but this one yeah it was just
crazy they like showed up off the growth
of
it uh and even like at eight months or
so it was [\h__\h] huge and outgrowing
all the other cats is crazy they gu and
that was I was thinking at the end of
the video when they showed like the
final growth which I think it wasn't
even done growing yet but it was so big
at that point that it was basically a
dog when a cat gets that big it's is it
still a cat is it not a
dog W that wasn't funny what did I say
the the bomb thing wasn't
funny yeah well it was
true no it's funny it's funny
though imagine the bird yeah and one
comment said like H how does this cat
get when he has the
tumis
imagine I mean dogs also get zumies so I
guess you could take that as an example
but I feel
like dog zumies and cat Zoomies are a
little bit
different cuz
generally I don't know how many people
actually have this but I feel like a lot
of cat owners will have things uh up
mounted on the
walls imagine like when my cats have the
Zoomies they were like run up there and
swoosh around so fast like it's wow they
Zoom around they go up and down and up
and down and then imagine a a huge
[\h__\h] dog siiz man [\h__\h] would do
that wow it they would probably
destroy the mountain
platforms and I don't think a dog I
don't think dog owners make that for
their
dogs why not actually I guess cuz dogs
don't care so much about being up on
high places and observing you from above
they like to be below you this is
literally yeah the the psychology of
cats and dogs dogs want to be below you
cats want to be above you because they
are period
period yeah dogs don't climb but I mean
it's not
necessarily
climbing just jumping from one platform
to
[Music]
another yeah they just run
around sometimes when my when when
chunky wonkey is
dooming and and then like she Dooms
somewhere and then she she stops moving
for a while but she's like it looks like
she's about to go off again but like
she's just stopping and I stand there
and then I go like I just I don't even
do much I just like slightly move
like just slightly move my body like
like as if I'm about to charge at her
but I'm not and then she she she takes
it as a as a go and then she charges
somewh and zoom some more and runs
around it's so
cute it's so
[Music]
cute you do the
same it's like playing with them low
effort yeah I R them up I'm like go go
now same with my doo yeah I'm sure dogs
do the
same BR some more go go
go you do that too
good man I can't imagine like the life
without a pet like that's boring you
guys should all get a pet whether it is
a dog or a cat or a bird or
uh a guinea pig or a mouse or a
fish
anything just get a pet it's so life
changing and fulfilling and you know it
takes so much of the loneliness and it's
wholesome and you have like a little
baby to protect and you can basically
train it's basically training for having
a human baby sometime I mean it's better
than jumping from no human h no no baby
nothing to protect to suddenly having to
be a parent I it's not exactly a good
comparison like it's okay it's not
equivalent but it's
still better than going from Z to 100
instead in between you have a step of
zero to like 50 because 50 is taking
care of a pet although some pets are
more difficult to take care of and
therefore a higher level yeah you learn
some for sure like having to feed them
maybe sometimes having to wipe their
butt like especially if I have a dog you
have to pick up their poop all the time
and all that and then taking them to a
doctor and maybe if it's a dog you have
to train them you know like you you'll
have to teach a kid like all kinds of
things
too yeah like taking care of something
it's definitely
like I I feel like it teaches you
something you maybe you maybe you are
maybe then a little bit more prepared to
have a baby in the future I mean you'll
figure it out one way or another I guess
as people always figure it out but still
get a
pet yeah train the baby to use the
automatic
toilet
yeah speaking of I bought
um like uh I bought a new liner plastic
liner and I need to exchange it cuz like
chuny wonky when she goes to the toilet
I think I told you guys before but she
absolutely tears it
apart and it's been so
wrecked but the thing is they have an
extra part that you can buy additionally
which is like a plastic a solid plastic
um stick on like guard um that you put
on the
entrance so I think generally it's meant
to uh do something else than what I'm
going to use it for
it's hard to explain but like once she's
done with her business she like
scratches her uh or like her not
scratches but like she she you know
rubs tries to clean her paws in the in
the
front uh and yeah the hole the bottom of
the hole and then instead I'm going to
cover that area with solid plastic like
a piece of solid plastic from the same
company uh yeah and then she she can
still use it to do that but she won't be
able to destroy
[Music]
it train the pet to read superz that
would be great but you guys want it to
be read by
me yeah but I think I I think I know
what it's for because I saw some reviews
of like automatic cat toilets where this
dude I think I told you about this too
but like his cat one of his cats would
instead of peeing inside like the cat
would go inside but like my cats for
example they turn around once they're
inside so that they don't pee outside
but like some cats apparently they just
walk in through the hole but then their
bot is still facing the outside and then
they
pee out
there yeah so I think that's what that
guard is for like it makes the hole kind
of smaller and supposed to catch the
pee my cats don't have that issue but we
have different
issues but yeah it's time to exchange
the the the soft plastic liner because
it's just become really disgusting I'm
just just been kind of waiting on it
because I'm stalling because I I I don't
want to figure out how to how to take
the whole thing apart I should just
watch a YouTube tutorial that's probably
a YouTube tutorial on it taking it apart
and then replacing the liner and then
putting it back
[Music]
together instructions
unclear n they're probably relatively
clear just got to watch a
video but the thing is so huge I have
troubles carrying it around
[Music]
too one of my roommates cats trained
herself to p the toilet well that is
like
amazing that's
insane but I've I've seen cats do that
since like
centuries people have taught their cats
for
centuries you built furniture you can
totally handle it
honestly really my mindset has changed
quite a bit I feel capable of doing more
things now
[Music]
yeah my friend has one of those robot
toilets those things are enormous
there's smaller ones too call has a
relatively small one but then she also
says it doesn't work as well so I feel
like it's worth it to invest in a bigger
expensive one like the one that I
[Music]
have yeah but there's so many out there
right now so definitely worth looking
into it even if you just want a cheaper
option it's still helpful I think don't
have to scoop the
poop once you see how easy it is you can
just start putting stuff together yeah
it feels so powerful to to build
Furniture
[Music]
C than you vye connect ah yeah right cuz
it's a it's a sponsorship gift
sponsorship gift thank you melty claw
it's not back in order I'm just
streaming off of basically mobile
[Music]
data which is not
ideal but it works for
now a normal little box plus mat takes
up a lot of Flor yeah but I've noticed
that like the thing is
um
the the thing that I have the machine it
takes up a lot of height as well and the
circumference certainly didn't say that
correctly uh uh is also so wide so I've
been trying to put it like for example
under um a
shelf but to save space to have it like
you know be under a shelf but no I would
have to adjust the whole shelf and put
the the Shelf much
higher I'm not going to do
that I just it's just so tall you don't
just leave it in the bathroom
[Music]
no no
I've um I've changed its position a lot
of times recently because I noticed a
while
ago
[Music]
um oh a while
ago I
noticed uh that like in front of the mat
I noticed
some color changes in the
wood and and I'm like what the [\h__\h] and
then it it was just minor though and
like on the edges of the the wood
pieces it got
darker and then eventually I thought it
was only there but eventually just to
clean and everything I I I moved
everything I moved the whole toilet and
the mat and I
saw oh it was all under the toilet not
that something leaked but simply from
the humidity I think that came from the
wet uh
sand
some yeah some of the woods got like
yeah Darkly colored which I wonder if
I'm going to be scolded
for eventually by the the
landlord yeah it's not like anything
leaked though and the thing is I don't
even think this would happen normally I
think uh um at some point maybe for
example if I was on a if I was just gone
and
um I don't know when exactly it would
have really gotten to that point but at
some point
probably uh it just
like how to say I think I think just
like
it probably
stopped uh
being emptied out
properly uh maybe at some point and
then all the all the
wet somewhat wet moist sand in the
bottom drawer probably just um spread
too much humidity which is so weird
though because all of it is
like like within in like especially the
used sand is in a closed off solid
plastic container drawer basically solid
like it fascinates me that that can
still
affect the wood
[Music]
underneath you can definitely get the
staining out I I looked it up I looked
up these issues and I looked up like
ways to fix it and then there's there
were several suggestions on how to fix
it but all of them were like be careful
it might not work be careful it might
make it worse it might not but it might
fix it but it also might make it worse
like you can't be sure and all that and
especially depending on what kind of
stain it is uh BL blah blue I don't know
it's
like I couldn't find anything that's
like really
certainly the
solution even even if the example
picture looked kind of like what I
have so it's like a lot of them said be
careful it might not work so maybe get a
professional to do it I'm like H should
I really maybe the landlord also just
won't notice it I don't know if I want
to risk it but whatever just stay in the
whole floor and make it
even maybe I need to put a l box back in
there oh no that's like it's a drawer
it's a solid plastic drawer and then it
has like like a like
a trash
bag
lined in it which catches the sand and
then you take it out like every once in
a
while you'd need you'd need the floor
type yeah and I guess also I mean I
don't really know if that could be
considered urine because it says they
the advises said that like if it's urine
if it's a urine stain then it's very
different from how you would solve other
stain inste of just like by water or
something so I wonder if it came I I
would say it comes
from what do you say do you guys think
this is logical the humidity that is
like coming from the sand into the air
and and then into the ground does that
make sense yeah
condensation but then even through solid
plastic layers that's crazy but yeah I
don't think anything leaked like it
can't literally it can't
leak ammonia yeah it's just a moisture
but like so
weird it it couldn't have gone directly
through the plastic it must have gone
into the air and then into the
wood so if it's that if it goes for the
air and all that is that that just like
is that still urine or is that something
else just like moisture so water I don't
know uh that's too much science for my
[Music]
brain that would be just general
moisture
right cuz I have a little bit of that in
other spots as well like in front of the
kitchen sink for example I noticed it as
well not as bad and as big as and I said
I say bad but it's still not that bad
you don't walk into the room and then
see a big black spot no not at all it's
not that bad but like if you look there
you may notice it if you look into that
direction on the
floor for the air it should just be
clean water right yeah I think that's
just the condens yeah yeah yeah okay so
then
the way of com combating and trying to
fix the stain would be different so I
don't
[Music]
know I don't know how important it is to
fix
[Music]
that is it dark or is or black oh I can
probably take a picture for you guys and
show you guys and ask your
opinion
eventually one of these
[Music]
days is it black mold I don't think it's
mold or or is it I don't
[Music]
know is I guess is that considered mold
I don't know whatever whatever okay
let's go back to Super
Chat where was I yes beheim thank you
bansen starky Dan Captain meow thanks
for the
pinky welcome back waa and weisa looks
like you have a great great time in mold
today's my birthday it's an awesome gift
to have you two streaming on this lovely
day ah happy Bel birthday I'm so
sorry but I'm glad we could at least
stream on your birthday that's always
something you guys are happy about we
stream on your birthdays so that's
great so I guess I don't have to be
sorry thank you so much for your support
I hope you had a lovely
[Music]
birthday wow thank you sh for your
support and yeah hope you celebrated
yourself cuz you're great and you should
celebrate
yourself happy birthday captain meow
meow meow meow meow m is want
0193 T thank
[Music]
you can I ask why you scared to jump in
water I used
to be a able to jump at
least uh I mean I feel like I still
could like you know when you're in a in
a
swimming hall in indoor or outdo
whatever and they have like several
levels and then the first level is just
like a bouncy
boing uh platform which is like pretty
low okay that I could probably jump off
of but I can't do any any fancy jumps at
at all I can only try to become a
ball or jump in
straight and anything higher than that
I'm kind of scared of and even I feel
like I as a child I used to do more
things on the water like I was able to
like do a roll on the water and uh open
my eyes on the water and yeah dive
more efficiently have more more control
under water but recently I noticed I'm
like just too scared I really don't want
to open my eyes anymore under water I
would do it in pools and in oceans when
I was
younger my eyes would burn but then I
get used to it and then I didn't give a
[\h__\h] but nowadays I don't want to do it
anymore and and and I also can't do the
like roll the roll I can't do anymore I
can't do [\h__\h]
anymore
Cannonball wah came in like a cannonball
[Music]
but at least I can snorkle now which is
something I wasn't able to do as a
[Music]
child babies oh I wonder if they do it
just like
because they don't care cuz they're
babies they don't think that
far so they think water is the same as
air so they just open their eyes
automatically on the
water cuz it's just like a like a
human sense a natural desire to open
your eyes to see what you're what's in
front of you so they just
automatically open it cuz they don't
think too much about
[Music]
it
yeah a mental thing yeah probably but
yeah I don't know I feel like I lost
some some skills some water skills I'm
definitely not a jumper and I also don't
like slides that much like last time
when I went to the spa with my bestie
that had like a like a it's not it's
mostly it's less of a spa more of like
a water park somehow it's like a mix a
good mix and there's a slide there were
like I think two slides
and uh one yes both you're supposed to
use them with like
floaties and I don't know my friend
really had to force me even though it
wasn't even that crazy over a
ride I've become such a
[\h__\h] when it comes to slides such a
baby I used to do more slides I I was
always a [\h__\h] about it but I used to be
a bit more adventurous about it now I'm
like SC
me
yeah roller coaster I I I like even
less even less than water slides roller
coaster is not my thing
man I'm happy with the baby roller
coasters not baby but like the the low
key ones that don't don't go too crazy
maybe a little bit of excitement but
don't no not too crazy and and and the
thing I like the most
probably is like the rides where you're
in some kind of Cinema and the thing
moves the seat moves so much and maybe
there's even like some air blowing into
your face maybe even some uh water
drizzles and stuff like that but like I
feel like those are
intense if it's a good one yeah like the
minion R those are
intense
yo the drops they feel like drops and
when you go Zoom forward it feels like
you're zooming forward and when you stop
it feels like you're stopping and it's
amazing and then I still have the sense
of security I know that I am not outside
in like a wild roller coaster yeah I
like those I like them I clap yeah it
deserves
clapping you're just coming to realize
that you don't have to go on slides and
yeah I guess I mean I never felt like I
had to but it was just more it was more
fun as a child I care less as a teenager
and
child I just gave less shits about that
maybe I'm just trying to stay alive
right now maybe I'm holding hard onto my
life
maybe the more adult I become the more I
realize life is precious and I don't
want to risk it I don't want to
die maybe that's
why just want to stay safe survival
mindset
yeah thank
youan bro are you good yeah I'm good
because I try to stay away from those
things but gen
[Music]
genuinely roller coasters really don't
give me a good
feeling
like the
drops I literally
can't I lose I
lose like now I I I can't function
anymore like
[Music]
I I scream for the first like two
seconds I scream my [\h__\h] heart
out and I'm scared as
[\h__\h] and then I I get to a point where I
can't even scream anymore and I just
like
crumble and I become like baby fetus
position as much as I can while having
that bar in front of
me uh yeah I become fetus and I close my
eyes and I just wait for it to happen
while screaming inside and I think I
also kind of stopped
breathing
that's
how I'm with roller coasters it's not
good not
good I don't know how
people can lift their hands and look
straight the feeling cuz it literally
feels like my heart is
like like my body is going down but my
heart is like staying where the highest
point was you know what I mean
[Music]
that's how it
feels
[Music]
same
no no same
nice you like that feeling oh my God oh
my God you guys just feel like
everything shift yeah yeah GeForce I
hate hate
it I hate it I wish it was slower if it
was a bit
slower if it was a bit
slower like the the drops that are like
more kind those are
[Music]
okay I was new I wouldn't like them so I
never got I don't want
oh then you can't really know
though you should try it at least once
how come a friend has never like talked
you into it
ever that's why being on a rocket ship
wouldn't be great for
[Music]
you are you
saying being in a spaceship once it
takes off is like a constant feeling of
a drop in a roller
[Music]
coaster but it's going
up I guess it goes up so fast that
you're feeling like you're being left
behind like I just said in the opposite
[Music]
way
really
[Music]
oh
oh I guess I shouldn't go to the second
Earth or Pluto
even
ah once you're in zero
g oh no my Pluto trip
ruined once it stops why are you
accelerating it's different oh really I
thought it would be the other way around
okay
look up how astronauts trained yeah I
know they have crazy
trainings how long can you stay on the
water not long like as I said yeah I
lost all my skills my water
[Music]
skills one thing I just never seem to be
able to pick up is like the this way of
[Music]
swimming this way swimming oh now I got
dizzy oh
[\h__\h]
like way your face is on the water and
then out of water and then in the water
and then out the
water you just don't get the timing I
tried I tried like keeping my face in
the water for only one stroke I guess
and then I tried it like with like after
free Strokes or so like also uh not just
this one but the one where you just stay
straight straight and you swim like
butterfly but like still with the face
in the
water I I tried everything but like when
I go out of the water and
breathe that timing it just doesn't
match with my arm movements and all that
it's just so difficult what the [\h__\h]
yeah I need an actual swimming teacher
to teach me that again I wish I wouldn't
have always said I'm on a [\h__\h] period
when I was in in junior high school when
we would go to the pool for uh physical
education should never always skipped
out on it but I only skipped out on it
because at that point already I felt
like I was a worse swimmer than
everybody else and I was scared to be
embarrassed when they do would do like
stupid challenges in the water and and
then I would be so bad at it because I
can't swim so fast and all
[Music]
that K has the body coordin of a quop
character yeah in water may be similar
amazing you so lucky even had a pool we
didn't have a pool we just went to um
you know for PE we would in in the
summer we would go to
one I think all the schools in Austria
do
that
easy to practice the breathing by
holding on the I did that I did
that my my best friend she even tried to
teach me so hard a whole day we spent
there in the pool and the whole day we
tried that in different
ways I just couldn't pick it up it's
ridiculous anyway let me read Super Chat
though you're not in school anyone more
yeah well you can say I can swim however
I want but yeah that's true but I I
actually really want to learn that
because um for the sake of my back and
all that if you swim like that with your
head above the water all the time it's
not good for your neck and your
back you should keep your spine
straight so that's why I wanted to learn
that because if I can keep my head on
the water I can keep the spine
straight
you know if I had if I were to go
swimming like this with a
snorkel I could do it all the
time but it's kind of
embarrassing bringing a snorkel to a 1.5
M High pool or so where literally no one
else is using a fullon snork you know
what I mean this is [\h__\h]
embarrassing I see people with like
swimming goggles but nobody uses [\h__\h]
snorkel yeah of course you would make
fun of me quietly cuz I would make fun
of somebody like that I would be like
why the [\h__\h] did they bring a
snorkel there's no fish to see
either what's there to see and why do
you need to have a snorkel well for the
sake of
breathing super chats are an ad
[Music]
breaking app
training no no
no bring full on scuba gear aert
[Music]
D what are they looking
for if I had like a private pool where I
don't give a [\h__\h] about about because
like nobody else is there then I would
do it [\h__\h] yeah but as long as there's
other people I care too much about what
other people
think I just
can't not do
[Music]
that so many times people whatever it is
about whatever it may be about people
always are like oh you care too much
about people think you should not care
so much my be that's so easy for you to
say I don't even understand how you can
live your life not caring about is that
even really possible or are you just
like gaslighting yourself do you really
not care is that even possible you say
you don't care about what people think
is that even
really like possible for a human being I
don't know if it really is I kind of
doubt
it yeah you certainly can't consciously
change it especially like I always argue
that like while
I've been doing this my whole life being
in the public eye and being kind of like
a p a big [\h__\h] Target um that people
can throw darts at uh like always being
judged and like lit literally that being
like my part of my livelihood like you
know
yeah so I'm I'm just I don't know I
can't turn it off
it's just not
[Music]
possible I want to say I want to claim
that I care less about what people think
especially because I've been through it
like my whole
life but I don't know if I can really
confidently make that
[Music]
claim I think iel like care less
now in in some ways like for example I
used to
um I don't know until
when I
think this only really counts from when
I lived in Austria or so cuz in Japan I
could always put on a mask but um in
Austria for the longest time even into
my adult life I
even for going to like a
mall or definitely for going to work
even if I'm not like if even if I'm just
in the back office or so I always need
to wear
makeup and always have to
[Music]
have my hair
styled and wear cute cloes and all that
I just always wanted to look presentable
cuz I felt especially when it comes to
makeup I felt ugly without
makeup and nowadays I just don't give a
[\h__\h] I
walk I I go to the supermarket and
pajamas so
often I I don't like the amount of times
I do my makeup ever since I joined whole
life oh my God I'm saving so much money
that I would spend on makeup 50
memberships thank you holy
moly thank you Christ crazy that's so so
generous thank
you
thank very tuscaro but yeah so that's a
good change you would think but at the
same time I feel like I'm letting myself
go too much not in a sense as like I I'm
getting fat uh surprisingly my weight
never changes um I don't even have a
scale
but yeah I just um
I just don't care about looking good
anymore unless I meet like a whole life
member for the first time then I do my
makeup I probably also the second time
for for myth members I don't do my
makeup anymore especially for like
obviously for like
staying like for the 3D showcases like
for staying in the same building I'm not
going to do my makeup all the time I
felt
comfortable with them like that and that
was really nice
[Music]
cuz that was not possible for me before
home
life that's legit character development
yeah and I guess I stopped caring about
what people
think to a certain
extent
[Music]
yeah oh
so this
now it's really good though I hate
wasting time to do my M my makeup even
if it only I'm really fast actually I
can do my full makeup so many steps in
like 10
minutes really fast I can even do it
quicker if I want to I'm like really
fast other girls need like an hour
[Music]
crazy it's nice to relax around homies
for real for real
yeah I
mean it's also because they don't wear
makeup they
like Guna never does Amy never does Ena
never does Kelly Kelly wears a little
bit don't even think she wears
Foundation she wears like
like like some mascara I think although
now she got lash extensions so she
doesn't even wear mascara anymore cuz
she just has like constant mascara on
basically uh I think maybe her eyes are
a bit
like dark maybe a little bit of eye
shadow or something she's doing I
[Music]
think yeah Nissa doesn't wear makeup at
all
ever
even like for special occasions I think
the other girls maybe wear some makeup
for special occasions but yeah when we
were together nobody ever wears makeup
it's like so
chill I think it's also like a different
different feeling
because we get to know each other and we
get to introduce to each other and all
that like this I mean until we meet each
other IRL but like this is how we look
for work and all that and this is who we
are basically and so it's like no one
really expects anything from each other
in terms of looks I
think there's no pressure it's so
chill yeah
like it's very different from having a
normal
job
and
honestly it's been the best thing ever
to happen to me after so many
years
of doing stuff
where my looks are very important and
very
judged and always paid attention
to I always felt very pressured so
suddenly not having that kind of
pressure whether or not it's whether or
not I'm putting it on myself by myself
or not I think partially probably yeah
but
definitely for many many many
years I've been judged for my
looks uh yeah cuz people just love to be
judgmental to people on their looks it's
just how it is in our
nature and even more so if you can be
like somewhat
anous on the
internet yeah somewhat like you like
even here on YouTube you're like
somewhat Anonymous like I don't know
what your real name is and where you
live and all that it doesn't really have
an impact like you can say [\h__\h] to me
and you know it's what can I do what can
I do about
[Music]
it
yeah so that's been that's been one of
the biggest upsides of this job for me
such a
big uh weight off of my shoulders
mentally it's
crazy it's crazy how how healing that
is for my
[Music]
soul I know your first
name oh thank you for the membership
come I don't mind being found by Tel
thank
you well I still don't know who that kfb
from that genin concert
was
cool are you guys trying your best to
find
them have they reported themselves to me
yet
I have a screenshot you know but I'm not
going to show it obviously I'm not going
to expose their face on here but I have
screenshot no one self-reported God damn
it God damn it I guess they don't just
don't watch my
[Music]
streams
okay are you sure it was the K yes 100%
I saw it very
clearly
yes why do you doubt it so many people
so many kfp have that sweater and it's
[Music]
coffy yeah yeah if you wear that sweater
you don't watch my streams and what what
the
[Music]
[\h__\h] I'm legally obligated to watch your
streams in the K contract exactly
exactly that's how it
is I'm thinking of buying another one oh
I wonder if it's in stock right now I
feel like they restocked it a while ago
and probably it probably still isn't in
stock
cuz now there's not like a big wave of
people trying to buy it yeah love that
sweather yeah me too I just can't really
wear
it I think I still have it uh packaged
even in the plastic didn't open it cuz I
was like you know what I'm going to keep
this one packaged cuz I'm not going to
really be able to wear it
properly I just keep it safe and clean
there is
Stu
probably I might have to buy me a second
one they're really nice yeah do it do it
go for it I'm wearing it now a man cute
in your
uniform so
sweet I need to get it after the next
best oh you still don't have
it okay go go go go I've been thinking
of getting more of the omat stuff
recently yeah I think you
should all sizes in stock let's go can
you wear it at home oh yeah
normally normally I wear short sleeved
things or if it's really that cold um I
like to wear like long sleeved really
soft
pajama um
sweaters so I I feel like I don't know
I've never worn it but I feel like the
kfp sweater would be a little bit too
bulky I like it to be like I have this
one I have this one
sweater uh that I like to wear in the
winter time that's like oh it's so soft
it's like a blanket that kind of
softness and it has the fabric of a
blanket of a cozy blanket too I like to
wear that be comfy but then so often
when I start streaming I like start
sweating in my armpit
so I end up just wearing shirts whenever
I'm
[Music]
streaming but I feel like if I ever you
know I I will wear it I will unpack it
and wear it if I
ever you know anyway I'm not going to
end the
sentence for your sake
[Music]
that's why I keep it safe don't say
it yeah okay sweat
CH okay I should what's wrong with me
what's wrong with
me where was I oh yeah
here uh smash Rock 51
[Music]
Dan thank you you there for me a long
time I just have much text for this
amount
of thank you smash Rock I don't know if
you're here but that's
sweet Maple Lea thank
[Music]
you
okay yeah
[Music]
super M it's stable
Hallelujah pretty normal
yeah I guess so what a sweet gesture to
bring her to something she would love
taking narissa to the Elizabeth Museum
yeah hearing how happy it made narissa
was really beautiful that's our caring
tal yeah I I um kind of want to bring
her to the actual is Elizabeth musical
someday but like they rarely actually
play it like it's been years since
they've done it and it's probably still
going to be a couple years until they
bring it back and then I heard something
about it this year but turns out that's
like a concert and that's different from
the
musical um so I wouldn't even recommend
that to her we'll just have to wait
until the actual Musical ever happens
yeah and then I'll I'll I'll bring her
I'll tell her to come back to
Austria it's just really
rare because it's been I mean I think
it's normal it's been a musical that has
existed for a long time they don't like
play it every year for 20 30 40 years
[Music]
no considering there people who didn't
send Super Chat still want to listen to
your attention thing I guess so hm I
hope it's interesting for
everybody my tangents I would say it's
interesting I know I know I am a good
talker get the license to have hold live
performance nah it has to be the
OG or like not the OG but like at least
like you know German speaking people in
austr
but yeah the museum was interesting that
was the second time that I went to it
first time I brought Cali to it I think
uh and so yeah I think the first time
though um me and cie I mean we listened
cuz you get like an audio guide we
listen to it but we didn't listen to
every single thing but I kind of knew
that narissa would be very very
dedicated to listen listen to every
single thing so I thought okay I don't
think I've listened to all of it
so yeah there were like so many you know
there's like
numbers everywhere and then you put the
number into your audio guide and then
you listen she listened to everything
and I wanted to be like at first I was
like there's uh just so you know you
know I kind of I've V to you before so I
might just like you know follow you
around and but I ended up I ended up
also just listening to everything and
honestly I I it was like I heard it for
the first time again and yes the members
W paper I'm aware I'll upload it again
just keep an eye out on the community
board
please no no no how about that's uh the
concert it's not the
musical it's like a a musical concert
but it's not the
musical apparently so that's not really
what we want to see it's okay if we miss
out on that one was it interesting it's
definitely interesting like it's um kind
of dark Museum because they try to uh
bring the vibe of her
depression into the museum and yeah the
rooms are really interesting
[Music]
M really
artistic so the songs are about the
story that's what I think it is yeah but
like not even the exact same songs from
the musical probably like arranged and
like I don't know what it is really but
it's not really what what we want to see
so we just got to
wait there were no lights no I mean
there were lights but it was just
generally dark like yeah a really moody
Museum interesting in case you guys ever
come to Austria I want to go to an
interesting
Museum then I recommend the Elizabeth
Museum my hyper chat died
again
can explain
yourself oh it's back in
Action if R Ren if if she ever visits me
if but she honestly she should do a
Europe trip she should go to Paris and
whatever ever other I guess I don't know
Italy somewhere in Italy Rome maybe I
would go on a trip of
her check out all kinds of museums even
though museums are not my favorite
thing but yeah I would do it with
her look at all museums that are like
very very
[Music]
artistic that would be nice if they had
an yeah they do they do do all the
museums I went to in Europe so far like
they always had an English audio guide
the local language and English oh also
honestly they have in the ones I went to
in Austria they have everything they
have like Italian they have
Spanish they have I think they had
Japanese as
well they have a lot of audio guides
just the guided tours are usually only
local language and
English there's actually a place I want
to go to right now it's like um an
artistic dinner
experience but it's really expensive
like uh holy
[\h__\h] it's so expensive but so
interesting I want to go there and like
I I see it like advertised to me uh even
though I already follow their [\h__\h]
account I still get ads all the time I
hate when that happens like I'm already
following you stop giving me
[Music]
ads I really want to go there but like I
have no one to go there with unless I
invite them and I kind of don't want to
do that because it's so
expensive oh it's called they don't they
have it like not only in Austria they
have it
in uh also in some places in Germany and
even oh even one in
Dubai and it's like you eat dinner and
then they project like [\h__\h] onto your
onto the table and the plate and then
you also have to do some art with your
food and all that it looks so
cool but what was the price
[Music]
again look it up look it
up
[Music]
but the good thing is they have it like
I don't know for the whole
year so let's see what was the price oh
yeah
130 euro per person which is like 130
USD per person but you get seven courses
and this whole super cool experience it
would be like perfect for a
date but I mean I have no one and I I I
would love to go with my friends but I
don't think they want to spend 130 year
I mean honestly it's not too bad there's
worse for like a really fancy dinner I
guess 130 is not too crazy
right yeah it just looks so cool I want
to go
there yeah it's not too bad right you
would you would go with me
right H I need to find someone to go
there with me because I am certainly not
going there alone everybody goes there
and couples literally
everybody I'm not going to go there like
a [\h__\h] loner
alone if you're paying no I'm not that's
the
point not something you invite a random
friend to yeah I I I that's like
another now now it would be great to to
have a hollow member living somewhere in
Europe I could they would probably do it
they I could be like hey come over let's
go to expensive dinner they would
probably do
it it's super cheap to travel around
Europe
so hey if you're ever in
[Music]
Dubai I don't think so maybe I'll pass
on the airport but
[Music]
there's one
in I know maybe there was that I didn't
say that though not this one this one's
not anaka they probably have experiences
like this in Japan for
[Music]
sure now Arisa she just won't listen to
me I tell her all the time move to
Europe but she just won't listen to me
yeah I'm still the only
one I'm still the only
one which I I always like to think about
it in a positive way like I have a
monopoly over my time slots mostly so
it's good um yeah but it would also be
nice to have like you know off collabs
here more often and travel around Europe
maybe to together
bar it' be
fun and then stuff like Minecraft or P
world you know I have a buddy that I can
always count
on but
yeah now I'm the only one and I have a
monopoly I win monopoly by
default can't move her entire I know but
your rven craft Family
Channel yeah it's kind of crazy over
there I told her I told her why why
don't you just move out but yeah
so I don't know she's dedicated I guess
to her family I don't know or too used
to living with her family I don't know I
couldn't do it for that long like I I
love living
alone
H her family said they wanted
you yeah I think she told me I think I
think her her I think her dad said like
really nicely you know he would take me
to a shooting range or something
[Music]
like and I'm just like
oh that's so
nice I guess
um yeah yeah I don't I don't I i' prefer
to do something else I
really don't think I would want to
necessarily do
that not really my first choice of
activity but yeah
sure it's such a it's such an American
thing man it's such an American thing to
me like as a European
my coworker's dad being like Oh yeah she
seems so sweet I would love to take her
on a shooting range tell her to come
over she can sleep her anytime sleep
here
anytime such an
[Music]
American oh
man such a nice
pastime
[Music]
guns are
fun no no they're not
fun sorry but there's they're not fun
they're not a fun
thing don't lose loose track of what the
the main purpose of a gun is it's not to
have
fun maybe in a game a gun is for fun
because the game is for
[Music]
fun am didn't manage to convince you
then
uh I don't think she really
tried I mean I would do anything with am
if she says let's go to a gun shooting
range thingy I say yeah okay let's
go if that's what you want to do I'm
going with
you and then I'll have fun because I'm
just with
am water guns are fun yeah okay yeah
yeah
[Music]
yeah and I I I can see like activities
like
like laser tag and Airsoft thingies like
that that's that's really
fun but then people even misuse Airsoft
I saw a video the other day of an
injured cat that somebody found on the
street and it it seemed like somebody
shot the cat with an
airsoft and that's really [\h__\h] sad
don't hurt cats
please so
sad yeah it had a damaged um
leg y paintball yeah I want to try
paintball sometime that sounds fun but
I'm aware that that also kind of hurts
when you get uh hit a little
bit W I still live yay welcome back to
the gym oh my God you went to the gym
you used your gym
subscription I'm so [\h__\h] proud of you
for using your gym sub scription let's
go fre it work it lift it
bro I know you can do it lift it
yeah let's
go press press press it up run faster go
go
yeah okay why the [\h__\h] am I stalling
[Music]
again so hearing happy and M was really
beautiful that's so car T thank you so
much I'm glad uh I could bring her to
that yeah I I I'm I'm actually like it's
such a crazy thing that it can't even be
a coincidence that her favorite musical
is an Austrian one and I'm a can't be a
[\h__\h] coincidence but it just works so
well if I can make her happy with her
just being in Austria that's great I
don't even have to do anything I just
walk around and she looks at aan AR
arure and she's like wow so
good so
[Music]
easy h ah thank you for the
pinky than you no text so I don't know
what you're trying to tell me besides
that you love me I love you
too g d d d and Cru D
Sho y yo I have to say Super Chat
readings thanks to the break are
definitely less tedious right
now and then tedious I mean just kind of
like it feels less repetitive for once I
feel like I'm reading it very
consciously that's
great let's do the Sims
stream yeah monotone
yeah I mean after three and a half years
of
continue Super Chat reading I
mean we have to understand I mean you
guys even told me the same thing that
you don't even know what to write into
your super chats anymore although I said
for me it's like it doesn't really sound
repetitive to me I sound repetitive to
myself when I say thank
you but your messages don't seem
repetitive to
me break work I I in general I
definitely think it worked like not
having to work and think about work um I
feel like I still F thought about like
like V tubing as a whole every now and
then in some ways
small but I definitely felt like I was
able to detox from work
yeah for
sure so good and yeah I might
I might do it every year when you guys
are okay with that right if it means
that I'll be refreshed and you
know be able to be more productive again
[\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah I I think at at like a certain
point I just
after working for so many years in a job
like this you know burnout is always at
the
doorstep it's always a danger to be
burned out
so I'm just like trying to prevent it
you
know yeah yeah
yeah work
smart
not stupidly I don't
know
if it was just a little shorter yeah I
mean this time it was a bit longer than
I wanted to I got a little bit extended
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
yeah even if I missed you during the
break I'm even happier you took it and
it helped yeah I'm I wonder how you guys
felt like I know a lot of you guys
missed me but maybe you also felt like
kind of refreshed maybe but then at the
same time I wonder if some people
actually just felt like like when I was
starting to take the break maybe they
felt like they'll be back to watching me
afterwards but then now they ended up
just kind of being like Oh actually I
didn't watch your streams for a month
now I'm kind of like over it and now
they're not watching anymore I feel like
that there's certainly a few of those
cases because that's just a such a
natural thing to
happen but I hope that's not the
majority
h
[Music]
yeah you got an embarrassing level of
happy it was a bit of
both absence made the hard fer oh I hope
so no but I've only been Carey for a
couple months okay you're still fresh
all right but still
still my my fear applies I did miss my
afterwork routine which is me I guess
but it did allow me to catch up with
some of the other holos
[Music]
oh not for me a detox and now the waa
hits harder than
ever I missed you a lot and uh I kind of
took a break from beautiful content in
general but I'm so glad that's good
though that's good you know detoxing so
that you can work for kfp longer this is
going to renew our passion for Wawa the
break came in very welcoming moment oh
nice nice nice
nice felt like something was missing a
man
doubt there are that many so happy to be
here well that certainly isn't anyone in
this room yeah I guess
so realized that I wouldn't just shrivel
up and die of boredom without you so
that was
reassuring oh nice I think getting
burned out of content creator can happen
while you're actively streaming yeah of
course that's what I'm always worried
about I know I know but like my break
could have given someone a good
opportunity to realize they don't need
me in their
life that's
scary I watched your shorts but I felt
weird but I I'm got to say I I think I
did a good job at keeping you guys you
know some leaving you guys some
interesting content some cute little
tiny bite-sized
wahas every time somebody first saw the
chicken and P chat was
just of
course same thing in Minecraft
man I'm me everybody's brain rent
free we are in everybody's brain
rentree not just me you too guys
actually you just you actually cuz I'm
not a chicken it's just
you kind of like the Advent calendar but
just like w calendar yeah yeah yeah yeah
it wasn't every day though it was almost
every day and then at the end maybe you
noticed I I ran out of videos there at
the
end but yeah almost every day
for yeah it was like uh almost every day
at least for the first two
weeks sometimes I purposefully left out
a day and you you guys must have been
thinking like H did they forgot forget
to I thought it was daily did they
forget to upload a video today somehow
no video
why is that on purpose did I
[Music]
forget people named her chicky be
Jimmy nice I always F of you whenever my
DHL packages got lost in the
mail I don't think it's healthy to think
you need something rather you choose to
because you enjoy it yeah I mean
yeah that's f
what you mean I hate you what oh because
I didn't upload a video she hates
us I thought it was because we no it was
really random I just like I didn't have
a video for every day so like sometimes
I put a random Gap
[Music]
somewhere
did you like my snorkeling Members Only
[Music]
video the thing is like uh while we were
recording that cuz like uh Nissa was
like holding the the the case of the
camera and we were thinking that it
wasn't recording I didn't know until I
went back and checked on my phone
connected the whole thing and saw that
it was actually
[Music]
recording yeah so if I knew that it was
properly recording I would have recorded
more but now I know next
vacation yeah fish F maybe I want to try
snowking please do it's really easy I'm
not even a good swimmer and it's like so
chill and
interesting but the waves were really
strong so I was like just like like
looking at the F and suddenly I realized
oh my God I got swept away so
much audio and my Moda out of syn I
don't think so I mean to me it looks
fine the tea one was my favorite though
ah the girly tee thing oh my
God yeah uh Japan has a lot of these
like either all you can eat themed cute
ass buffets or cute ass afternoon
teas and a lot of the time they're like
Berry themed because that's the most
popular but sometimes if there's a
special season like for uh example like
uh what do they called uh
grapes then they do like sometimes they
do grape themed
stuff what
[Music]
else most mostly it's really berries
that's just the most popular it really
makes me wonder like Japan makes it seem
like strawberries are in season all
[\h__\h] year oh sometimes they do
like
Maroni
[Music]
Maron no no yeah I know it maybe seemed
ironic that um I was complaining about
the others taking so many pictures while
I was taking a vlog
but honestly if you were there I out of
like being there like an
hour literally I just took all these
like tiny short quick clips and then
immediately ate yum yum y yum yum but
the people around us oh my God I swear
they were not
eating we came in everybody was already
sat down and they were taking pictures
and then like uh 20 30 minutes later
they were still all taking pictures and
fixing their makeup and taking pictures
of each other and taking pictures of
themselves and oh my God it was like
sickening it made me cringe like eat the
[\h__\h] food I know it's like
purposefully so aesthetic to you know
bring all these girls in who want to
take cute pictures It's Like on purpose
it's like that that's literally like
their main audience but like okay do you
have to take pictures for one [\h__\h]
hour
it's like too much it felt like so
superficial like oh my God is that all
you care about the food is Yum eat
something don't take pictures the whole
time that's all I did like in comparison
to that I barely was using my phone and
me and uh jenma actually were having
some really deep
conversations I suddenly took it upon
myself to like ask jenma a lot of
personal questions and find out
everything about her that I didn't know
like a lot of her history cuz I felt
like she knows so much about me like I
tell her about a lot about myself but
then I realized I don't know it's kind
of one-sided I should ask her more about
herself and then she shared a lot it was
interesting we
[Music]
bonded they should be fake food yeah
yeah just put fake food there
[Music]
is Gemma single I think
so I don't think she has time for any
relationship kind of
[Music]
thing yeah all right let me read to
chats now you know the JT Secrets
yeah I'm glad you two got to get to know
each other for
real I think she likes me because like
you know she used to
manage uh GAA am
Ena like Ena not from the getg go first
it
was uh yeah good on
and then yeah I
was I was managed by J CH in the
beginning and then I switched to
JMA and then like she also like
partially had to manage Ena so then she
was managing four people at some
point and then new generations come in
and like she she she was like training
managers too so she's also like managing
the new ones partially as well like
helping the new managers and like you
know we have so many managers now though
so more and more managers come in and
like she lets go some of her
children guda and almond so on you know
right I'm a has been managed by uh the
name is known right HMA for a long
time and and so
on but the only one she never dropped is
me well I would probably
Riot if she attempted to drop
me I would
Riot favorite
kid I think she loves everybody you know
but I guess the others just didn't mind
being switched to someone else because
you know obviously she can't always
always take care of so
many
girls so workload had to be
distributed somewhat evenly to new
managers did you take on that assistant
manager yeah she's around uh but
apparently like she's ready to be a real
manager now so she became someone's
manager uh but yeah and Gemma kind of
seems more available now again so so far
far we've been just
doing uh handling things with us
too and if there's any like crazy time
coming up again surely someone can
help
yeah yeah eduma already ready to manage
someone that little
chicken did I tell you guys she she was
the chicken and the member's only uh
UNC I told you
right yeah I did is she was
so I don't know I think it was really
interesting experience for her too cuz
like on that day it was literally her
first time even seeing the studio and
her first time seeing like the M cap
stuff and all that how all that works
and immediately she gets like in
involved into it by me making her a
chicken
yeah she like she was constantly moving
in a like how to say Crouch yeah
crouched position and they got really
exhausted for
her exhausting U but yeah it was uh I
frw her into the ice cold water
basically
but it was so funny and she's so
[Music]
sweet
no same person same
persono I felt represented every real
nice cute yeah then she was doing the
knee
wadle she's a trooper yeah she's forever
going to be an honorary KY
[Music]
chicken I really liked being around her
too like she's
really fun and cute and
chill who's she working with now I don't
know by heart and I I don't want to
really be the one saying those things if
if the members don't feel like saying
something like that themselves I'm
really open about who manages me and all
that I don't really
care um but other people because they
don't really want
to be
[Music]
so wall breaking fourth wall breaking or
so I guess I don't
know I don't think it matters but I'm
not going to say it I don't even
remember and then honestly there's quite
often there's like because we kept on
getting new managers like they to even
the work Cloud out more managers are
being like shifted around you know and
if somebody says like oh my manager is
this person give them some funky name
and then later on it's not their manager
anymore and people are going to be like
uh making all kinds of
uh um theories up of like oh what must
have happened behind the scenes even if
nothing happened and even if it's none
of your business people are going to be
making up theories that are so
unnecessary so I understand that people
don't want to like you know say who's
with them so
clearly people are going to make a big
deal out of it if the manager changes at
some
[Music]
point s this now and I I want to prevent
that too see I don't need to uh really
be careful about that with Gemma because
Gemma literally has no choice but to
stay with me
forever we are forever
[Music]
together so I can talk about
it I'm not going to let her
go and she also she told
me she told me she's not going to
leave before I
leave so she's in
it for as long as I'm here
[Music]
I mean not saying that she leaves
immediately when I leave but she did say
like she wouldn't leave before I
[Music]
leave I should give her a promise
ring
imagine I'll go down on my knees and
I'll be like JMA do you want to be my
eternal
manager and she's going to say yes I do
got to ask her for her rings
size a Hol promise ring
yeah
yeah yes and then she managed me happily
ever
after
it's cute yeah better love story than
Twilight for real for real okay py check
47 J walk B Jim Tracy oh do you hit 5
million views let's go that's
amazing a I'm really happy with the
success of doyu and
Sparks um I'm kind of nervous about
putting out another
single to be honest but I hope it will
do
well I hope
so and but thank you Julian B thank you
for the red super chat
than what is that in your profile
picture anyway it looks like a key but
now now that I look at it closer it says
KD and then is that an L what does that
mean what is the meaning of this Julian
be explain
yourself dance is it did become the most
viewed
video
she that makes me want to
remind the H
[Music]
producer let's let's let's uh make some
money
[Music]
yo did you
know is it true really hor hor dance
became the most
viewed uh video on the Ian
[Music]
Channel
honestly it it would be hard to follow
up
though a second
[Music]
most damn
it almost second most God damn it
guys I just say second
most ult minino more views well ult
minino yeah has been around for a
while but yeah it's hard to follow
up it's like I don't even know like what
what genre would be good to follow it up
with or do you guys want to see the same
genre I feel like it's not good to
follow up with the same genre cuz then
we kind of get stuck in a box of always
doing the same
genre what do you want
guys heavy
metal oh baby metal style would be kind
of sick cuz we need something that's
as entertaining and
interesting as H
dance oh 13 million versus 5.5 but
that's hard
[Music]
to
yeah
yeah i' eat that up yeah [\h__\h]
yeah H I think that would be interesting
baby metal
[Music]
style you saw baby my life last
September
oo
damn you're a
beat oh yeah [\h__\h] yeah you're a beat
sometime
too just want to experiment with all
these like more interesting genres don't
like not like just you know the basic
ones it can't just be a basic song has
to be something
interesting
[Music]
okay and me K PE DC than the pinky W
here's how to get gay SS to have a
child didn't we get
them we did get no oh yeah but they
wen't gay in the end go to addressa
change Sim custom gender
settings um become pregnant oh really so
like in the past needed a like a like a
cheat for that or like a modded um item
Furniture so but now you can do it like
it's in the settings of the game nice
that makes it
[Music]
easier thank you though it's too late
but thank you though Brandon D smiling D
sky for the pinky a few days late but am
night I have a fun time watching W for
more than 3 years ready and I will keep
supporting my wonderful Kam oi oh my
God
guys you know what's
crazy aren't we wait
September October November December
January February we're almost like
almost again half a year
past
I already all all the time say 3.5 years
three and a half
[Music]
years yeah that's crazy didn't we just
have oh yeah we did just have the free
anniversary no that was my birthday
right we didn't have a free anniversary
birthday life uh Frey life but okay
yeah I I'm mixing up things I didn't get
a free the anniversary life
yeah true true
oh so perceptive K it's a key symbol
made of LK de for locked uh from my
steam profile
what lock you're you're locked from your
steam profile my good old high school is
oh okay I did I did see it correctly
nice nice
nice didn't you just deut it doesn't
really f like that to me but it's just
crazy how fast time passes
yeah like the half year went by so fast
what the
[\h__\h] now you can have a myth anniversary
life yeah yeah we'll have a birthday
life that will be on
time and a myth group anniversary life
and maybe some
more
[Music]
sasaa Advent has been like 6.5 months
time
6.5 you're counting it like
that but
[Music]
yeah
what a
deal right I'm going to be so hyp okay
let's go U Brandon wait I read that Skye
thanks for the pinky again and thank you
I'm so happy that you've been here for
so long you got your armor so I was just
going to say oh my God three and a half
years so I have to start thinking about
what the next next bat will be already
but I feel like we already kind of
decided but I'll I'll think about it
again when the time gets closer if
there's anything in
particular s do
[Music]
s maybe return to
egg maybe golden
egg let we just become egg again
Circle of
Life yeah you were going to be a rainbow
chicken though right yeah an egg
night yeah but we got plenty of time for
that
yeah turn to egg pile of
Ashes yeah well yeah the pile of Ashes
would have to
be like squeezed in between though
before the like Ki stage the hybrid
stage that would mean that some people
get taken away their badges that they
already have if you know I move it in
between and make the night one the
fourth year one I can't do that I can't
take away something I already gave you
that's like psychological
[Music]
torture anyway uh Cruz spank
pinky you were both cheating it's all
good I don't think we were cheating
either no well yeah for a moment I think
Nissa was doing something that she
shouldn't have been
doing uh but yeah it was fine like man
man I feel like that idea was so genius
too but but people were being so [\h__\h]
about
it telling me I'm cheating I wasn't
cheating it's but I I it was the first
time to you know try out the idea so I I
I wasn't sure if it was going to be well
balanced in hindsight I should have uh
definitely given myself more challenges
it was my side was uh easy to accomplish
but her side also like she could have um
done some things to make life harder for
me uh also if she knew the game better
she probably could
have uh made life harder for
me she could have made me um she could
have I feel like didn't I have a job and
she could have ended the job or
something like that or she could have
also ended my second marriage and all
that but yeah it really wasn't that
serious I agree I agree I agree it was
just supposed to be some uh
dorky
uh the Illuminati are getting
[Music]
me but yeah it was a new idea I came up
with
[Music]
so that was a test run if we ever do
another one maybe even with someone else
I think Gaa Gaa has a lot of Sims
knowledge so so she would be a difficult
opponent
honestly
go that would be
difficult they found
me
rejected they silen
[Music]
me no I still want to
man I really should uh get the like try
to get perms for the online mod for
Sims me and good I should just play
online
Sims I'm a t black Monkey D I am a beep
D and
[Music]
Zipp
why the [\h__\h] does the pal World stream
have so many super chats compared to the
others what the [\h__\h] what happened is it
because I was going to leave and you
guys said goodbye to me that was the
last stream before my
break what the
[\h__\h] maybe I'll read one of
[Music]
the yeah
um I don't know is that is that a lot
maybe it's not that much I don't know
maybe maybe it's
decent I'll try to read it and I'll for
once try to be a little bit more
efficient
okay just for this one time I'll try to
be a bit more efficient and you know how
that's going to hold
up oh oh that's a lot of a lot of colors
a lot of colors oh my God okay let's
see I love her art yeah okay let's go
Chris TR for I love one my oi
Phoenix I don't think I say it enough I
pray you Nest well and return rein egg
overrated after successfully detoxing uh
read some books get some masses schol
sign of Brea in the fresh austan air
enjoy your time off love always thank
you so much oh my god did you you have
to watch the new jibli movie did
you you should cuz there's so many birds
like birds are the main side
character so many different birds please
watch it you have to watch it it's made
for you and me and all of kfp but like
you with your bird puns you have to
watch it
you have a special obligation I think
you would like it unfortunately there
were no owls though I
think should have been
owls why were there no
owls I did actually just today I thought
about um ow ow they thought about uh me
having to ask unless they already made a
public St statement and I didn't see it
but I should ask
um if I can like fully play the T of
arise DLC yet and stream it like
fully t g where you at did you
[Music]
leave I'm tting because it it it's um
it's not so red super chat I have to
tangent a little bit about the super
chat but yeah I I should ask like what's
up with that even if they didn't make a
public statement yet maybe they they'll
be like oh yeah right oh yeah maybe we
should make a public statement now it's
been so long we forgot about it or
something like that
yeah it's not
[Music]
over yeah you've been holding back from
playing
oh oh man well now we'll kind of be busy
with Yakuza but I don't know I'm I'm I I
could have another game running on the
side I wouldn't mind
um but with the secret trip and the
Japan trip uh in the next yeah month
upcoming month um I might be a little
bit too busy anyway to start a second
game so for now I think we're good with
just
Yakuza but I have it on my radar
somewhere wouldn't that other game be
Dave the diver oh sure
yeah yeah yeah yeah of course of course
if that is going to be more if if I like
it enough to play it more than once I
don't know might just be a one time only
thing cuz it's a pixel game you know how
much I hate Pixel Games ew
[Music]
disgusting
JK
we good for Yakuza tomorrow I don't know
um I'll try I think we might be I I have
to buy the game though I'll I think I'll
buy it on my PS5 wait it is on the PS5
right wait is it is
it Anyway Trevor G you guys answer while
I read py d d for the pinky life has
been hectic so I haven't been watching
streams lately oh yes it is okay nice
but it looks like you had a great time
with Nisa and I hope you enjoy your
well-deserved break after the stream
I'll make sure to catch up thoughts I've
missed love you w thank you cute
Emoji my my break it was uh a nice detox
I will say that you know it wasn't
necessarily relaxing I've had some
stressful days and some chill
days uh but that relaxing never was
really the purpose so it was a good
break for what it needed to be it did
its job thank you so much for waiting
for me d means a lot to
me
J 47 D Tracy D thank you so much queen
queen Queen Wilder thank you for the
pinky as usual I'll be at work and
catching the VOD later but I hope you
have fun with p and I hope your break is
nice this chicken will patiently a wait
you return people like y thank you I had
a lot of fun with power
world and I got really addicted to
it and then I stopped myself I have so
much self-control
man I like I told you there was just
this one day where like pretty soon
after I think day after maybe even you
have enough data it's not limited it's
just
slow so
yeah I just have to download it in time
yeah but what was what was I saying yeah
I stopped myself I stopped my addiction
I just let it happen for one day and
then I was like this makes no sense why
am I playing the there's going to be a
wipe and like a
server I'm doing this for
nothing but I did like beat the first
boss uh during my little off stream
Adventures
and then I I focused a lot on like my
economy and
like getting all the recipes and all
that and then then I explored for like
three hours I went all over the map and
all that yeah and I got like this this
big
squiggly um thing that's marked on the
map it's like a
big and squiggle blue P that's really
cute I got that one and some other cool
ones yeah chillet yeah cute and I think
I used chillet to also fight the boss
boss is cute
yo first boss quite heart uh yeah um
wait did I die I don't
remember I think maybe I maybe I died
once or so that was quite challenging
but the the thing is uh right after that
after right immediately after I took my
break or started taking my
break my
faite
YouTuber gamer
dendo picked it up as a streaming game
uh and normally like when he does that
streaming games he like it's only like a
like a like a you know one time thing
where he looks into it for one or a few
hours but then people liked it so much
that I think he played it like twice or
so or or three times or so um but he
like he really got into it and then I
watched him uh beat the boss before I
even beat it
itat beat
it uh but yeah so yeah
yeah and I think because I watched him
play that
I
uh it kind of reignited my desire to
play it and that's why then I ended up
playing but yeah yeah I watched him play
and
um I on the Taki Ki YouTube account left
a few comments because his chat is
atrocious um let me tell you his chat is
full of
soakies it's so hard to find a useful
comment in his chat and so um he was
asking questions about the game he was
like kind of lost here and there with
several things and functions so I took
it upon myself to write one of the few
comments in the chat that would stand
out immediately because there were
proper
capitalizations like big letters where
they're supposed to be big and actual
information actual proper sentences so
it immediately stands out like you
immediately see oh wow there's one one
comment that's not written by an
11-year-old but
like literal children yeah like
literally I did I tell you I went to a
fan meeting of his uh before her life
long time
ago and I was like the only one that was
somewhat
adult everybody else was like like 11
year-old
boys I felt so
weird I told you right yeah that's how
his chat is too like
it's no no no wrong thing to have a
young fan base but like when the
streamer who's an adult asks questions
to his children chat it's like not very
helpful you know and so he kept on like
one the first time he saw my comment and
then it really helped him and then he
kept on asking questions and I I would
write answers into the spammy chat and
he would always pick up my
comments and I would actually
helpful with the knowledge I had from
the game already from streaming it
once
yeah yeah I was back seating but it was
like requested back
seating yeah I felt like how you guys
must feel when I pick up your comments
especially if it's a helpful one
yeah yeah but like I feel like you guys
like your com your comments are much
more
coherent and the your comments make more
sense and they don't look like an
11-year-old wrote them thank
God that I have a more mature audience
that I can have an actual conversation
with thank [\h__\h] God cuz I think I
would go
insane
otherwise yeah thank you
you so that was a little tangent I
admit and thank you so much for waiting
green Wilder or Wilder Wilder Wilder
right I usually say Wilder I hope I hope
that's correct I I forgot if you ever
told me but thank you so much for
waiting yay I'm back Flappy Boy Thanks
for the red super chat oh my God a
double even Al in for now you've been on
fire you said that so early it was the
pre- chat you've been on fire for
insanely long time but even the Phoenix
needs to chill down eventually so go out
there and leave no grass untouched not
going to lie though winter will feel
even colder and gloomier with the
without the Ardent Aura what the [\h__\h] is
Ardent of my Kam oi thank you I'm I'm
glad you feel like that you know I'm I'm
happy if you guys felt like a little bit
um
lonely you know
[Music]
you guys were allowed to miss me on my
break just saying you guys are missing
me and like being like she never streams
when I'm just gone for like two days of
the week that puts pressure on me I I'm
not not going to lie that that makes me
feel like [\h__\h] but like when I was gone
for like a whole month you guys were
more than welcome come to miss
[Music]
me thank you I miss you too so ENT means
strong okay okay wow I'm not really
strong though like I
literally injured myself from using a
spray can but I know what you
mean thank you so
much
I said it internally in my head
a I believe
you but we understand you need breaks
thank you I'm very respectful of you
thank you so yeah I I I agree you know
Phoenix needs to chill down eventually
you know just for a little bit to like
heat up for real for real
again thank you so much for
understanding that and supporting me
with all of that thank you thank you so
much Flappy boy and all of you
guys I miss you
T like I said I think YouTube got
worried about me it kept recommending me
your older video is like it was going
you okay you need WWA Nostalgia look
2020 ah but 2020 wa is so
cringe please don't 2021 Wawa is also
cringe in 2022 Wawa got more acceptable
I can't watch my thoughts oh my God
e
[Music]
thank you doll if you like my older
thoughts too my older
self you got Mario Sunshine BS yeah nice
thank you YouTube for once not trying to
sabotage
me lovey boy golden i d thank you so
much yeah I hope you really didn't burn
the kitchen no
the G cre thank you for the pinky after
working so incredibly hard entertaining
us all for so long you've more than
earned this long overd break I will
agree with that we'll miss you dearly
but we know we're getting you back fully
rested up and stronger than ever and
they'll make it also worth it thank
you it still feels a little bit weird
honestly to be like back like it's like
going from a 100 to Zer to
100 cuz it I was on 100 for too long
and suddenly I was on zero for
relatively long and suddenly I'm back
it's so weird it does feel so weird but
I'm getting back into the groove I think
this Super Chat reading certainly feels
like it's getting me back into the
[Music]
groove yeah we still aren't in the right
Rhythm we certainly are in the right
Super Chat reading rivm because it's the
one that we always
have thank you the game of green let's
go let's have a good time after this
break is finally over we're here now I
mean I'm really honestly I'm I can't
change it but I am so disappointed at
how the internet [\h__\h] went down um but
for now it seems like we can stream so
it should be fine
[Music]
is I think we're good now just don't
want to really do anything like online
like Minecraft or power
yeah
yeah so is now Rob
easy and the gamer
cre thank
you oh you had
a what your high
fever you had a high
fever or is it like a joke I hope you I
hope it wasn't too bad lily as Dan tror
go Dan oh you got the merch let's go
thank you so
much please enjoy the merch chicken is
so round and so
big yeah yeah yeah yeah I know I know I
should download it
early yeah I think it won't be too
bad pong thank
you the PE exploded into the
microphone P thank you for the r chat
Tak businesswoman of H life so to
convince everyone in the world can you
do infomercial style of telling people
that Carpenter is indeed person who does
carpet maybe you have to make carpets in
this game anyways have fun during the
break thank you so much for the Super
Chat why do I have to still convince you
guys it's the truth I don't know what
else I need to say like it's so obvious
it's literally in the word what do you
want me to say Carpenters make carpets
it's so obvious oh my
God so exhausting why don't you guys
believe
me
please because you're incorrect
no that is not
[Music]
possible yeah I mean yeah they either
make music or they make carpets but they
certainly don't make bridges like what
the
[Music]
[\h__\h]
Bridget make bridges such a shitty show
I hate it oh people love it though I
hate it though I need know how much I
love those kind of shows usually that
show is [\h__\h] I don't like
it sent dis thank you pong mAh
[Music]
yeah the pent c what does that
mean yeah Google it Carpenter makes
music Bob the bridge I makes Bridges
wasn't he Bob the Builder
though Jesus was a
carpenter
what Jesus Jesus
Christ
[Music]
P I never said I would do that what the
[\h__\h] things for the pinky really going
to miss you during your break but you
deserve it on the other hand I have a
chance of actually getting ahead of you
for infinite wealth is that
Yakuza have a great rest hope you get to
reading l Rings huh did I say I would do
that what the
[\h__\h] oh Jesus was a
carpenter man yeah he made carpets of
course he did
[Music]
yeah yeah he made so many carpets until
he didn't
anymore why is it so
hot
anyway did you Mon I feel like I gave
you enough time to even finish the game
so I hope you will be very
useful but I don't know how much I'll
get to play in the next coming month
like this weekend hopefully we can do
really long two streams um but I don't
think I can even play next
week uh unless I play it
like uh I don't know I won't say much
more but yeah I might not be able to
play it next week maybe next next
[Music]
week but that's fine I want to try to
keep it on the weekend you know cuz it's
going to be long streams certainly
thanks D thank you so much I hope you
did grow fonder of me Tassimo thank you
dun for the red J well I wish you
relaxing break yada you definitely
earned it I'll miss you but for now I'll
enjoy the stream and look forward to
your return Have Fun W thank you thank
you sh it was a good break I hope you
enjoyed somehow or profited or like I
don't know I hope the break from me was
good on you
too all also I hope it wasn't good on
you I hope you missed me and cried every
day just
kidding but I just hope you weren't
too too
happy I just hope you were slightly
sad thank you
taimo just
slightly depresso is
[Music]
brazle
Mary I only cried at
night oh [\h__\h] I guess it was better for
my wallet yeah it's like a tax break or
I don't know how that works
[Music]
five chickens in a trench cold oh my God
your profile picture what that's so cute
you're like
wobbly because you're balancing off of
the other ones we will miss you we we
sewing character we will miss you during
your break and patiently await your
return for now we will go undercover in
some other Holo girl streams to collect
information we will be here when you get
back with a full report put on spirit
Halloween skeleton mask oh no have a
good break oh my god did you already
send your report as a super chat when
will I get to read
it that's so interesting thank you oh my
God I'm excited to read the
followup I really am can't wait so cute
we used to have like way more like
larpers is that how you call
them in the super
chatos and it's kind of become a rarity
so it's exciting to
[Music]
me it's still being written ah you're
here okay okay okay okay then I don't
have to feel like I am there's something
out there that I needs to to hold in my
hands right
now
not quite the right term
[Music]
no why not what does it stand for what's
the LA is it Los Angeles based role
players is it laring if it's on the
internet oh is it like people who RP IRL
somehow then what life action a life
action wait it's life action
RP
yeah I got it before you guys told me I
got
it
oh yeah right like somewhere in my break
I don't know I heard about
larpers people who have laring as
they're
hobby I think it was maybe even in one
of those dating
[Music]
videos that's so interesting like I
guess that's is that is that different
from going to a
medieval or like Renaissance
Festival guess depends on how deep
you're into it if you actually have like
I don't know if they're the same in na
na as over here but like there will be
normal visitors and then of course
there'll be like you know people tents
who are like you know renting out the
place and then they're dressed like
really seriously and then maybe they
cook a little bit and then like a
fireplace and all that they just there
to I guess large so maybe is that laring
too probably right well I I wouldn't say
we were laring we were wearing the
outfits but that was more like just
cosplaying cuz we weren't talking like
them that's pretty much it I would say
yeah that's kind of laring but it's so
cool like I I kind of wanted to be part
of that I kind of wanted to be one of
those or like part of one of those
groups cuz there were so many of these
medieval festivals and we we will go to
them all the time especially in summer
cuz there were the most of them were in
summer and they were like scattered all
over like Germany and Austria and we
would go to the sou ones in um in
Germany like maybe a few of them and
then some in
Austria we would always go there and
then we would see some groups that would
be like everywhere like in all of these
some groups would be
there and then I think we kind of made
friends with one of those groups and
then got to chill in in their behind the
fence in their tent and in their like on
their benches and all
that that was that was pretty pretty
nice cuz we like got pretty close to
being part of
it
yeah we didn't have our own group but I
feel like we were I feel like I remember
we were considering either joining for
real for real or making our own official
group and you know get like one of those
big tents I feel like I can remember now
yeah I think we were discussing about
getting one of those huge ass medieval
looking
tents yeah like calculating a little bit
but we never ended up doing it for real
for
real
yeah but I really liked it and honestly
small Wawa really really really enjoyed
the medieval bands that were playing
there there was one in particular that I
really liked that I I have to try to
remember what they were called so I can
tell you guys but I had their CD I
remember I remember I I asked my mom for
like 5 or something and she gave me 5
and I ran over cuz like after their
concert at the at the
[Music]
place I I ran over there and I bought a
CD like an
album and I was so happy and
excited yeah then I would listen to it
sometimes like
oh whenever I could cuz back then PCS
still had CD cases and all
that
[Music]
like I wish I knew what they were called
maybe my mommy knows maybe she's
watching no maybe not
but they were so cute I want to find out
what they were called now they had some
bangers and I guess you call that
bore but they made their own songs they
didn't turn songs into bore no they just
made their own
songs m
[Music]
al were they Austrian or German maybe
Austrian God that would be hard to
find especially especially cuz I don't
think they're OCT
[Music]
anymore I have no idea I I don't know
what they're
called which instruments they
play I don't I don't remember that but
they it was just two people so it
couldn't have been many different
instruments but I think one
was
uh friend
shaped and one was uh I think not so
friend shaped I think but I could be
I feel like that's how I remember
[Music]
them just watch F the fans will find
them wait is that them is that them no
no that's just
no I'm kind of Googling I said I was
going to be efficiently reading super
chats and look at me
now anything
special
[Music]
no just that you know they weren't like
you know going like like the darker
Vibes they were going like more the
dorky bright Vibes it was fun and
cute
Papa let me mute
my wait Pap
P yeah that's them and it was a friend
shaped and he looks like a friend he has
a red
nose to wait which one was my favorite
one Pap wait I'll I want you guys to
listen to
one which one do I send you
that's but I think that
one V that's not even a Medieval
Festival
here I know this one oh yeah I know this
one they're so cute because
[Music]
there their interactions are so funny
too in this song the audience screams
like foas all the
time you were at that Festival not this
one though
[Music]
right they're so
fun fire
us
yeah nice thing about
alcohol
[Music]
noaps I remember the lyric
oh this is so crazy I was like I don't
know 12 or something when I you know
would go to these medieval vestival I
mean it was over the course of several
years but this is like wow my
childhood oh my God I would listen to
their album for
fun H now I have to find their album
again like I don't I definitely don't
have the CD
anymore but I have to
find if they have the album like
digitally
damn this crazy this
crazy you like
it if you understand the lyrics it's
even
better because they banter a lot and the
lyrics are really
funny he so
cute the cover collab
I don't think they're active
[Music]
anymore wait
B wait there's a One recording of 2023
of a Medieval Festival where they
performed man they must have aged so
much wait let me mute it though I'll
mute it and just look how much they
aged oh
sheesh wait they don't look damage just
the the friend shaped one is uh his
beard looks his hair looks really
rough
damn
a so nice I'll listen to this
afterwards yeah Spirit of Tavern
[Music]
music they were on so many of the med
festivals that uh we would go to and
whenever I saw that they would perform
there I was like so excited all the
time how do you spell their name p a m p
a t u t p a m p a t u t
Pampa I've heard of them before how how
the [\h__\h] did you hear about that how how
do how's there actually people who know
them guess he must have gone to Medieval
festivals
too
fall you going to pass out [\h__\h] I'm so
sorry I'm incapable of reading super
chance why am I so
stupid okay
okay where was I where was
I French shape but honestly like I'm
starting what at 400 p.m. tomorrow I
shouldn't go too
long but I still have to eat least I
don't have to cook cuz I cooked
yesterday
I simply do not have time to listen to
other albums medieval or otherwise my
car only has one CD player and is
reserved for the classical Masterpiece
album know's point of view I love you
but you know you can switch out CDs
right they're not stuck in there forever
once you put them
in that's so cute you are so
[Music]
cute just you just reject everything
that's not my
album
cute yeah tent
sto they welded the
cityan hot glue hot glue the the
opening PV has been in my car since I
got it thank
[Music]
you
a why massive affection a
[Music]
stop [\h__\h] where was
I I here oh yeah how the [\h__\h] did I get
to this
tangent lar ah because of laring cuz
five chickens in a TR coat thank you
chocolate Insomniac thank you for the
pinky hey kahua enjoy you break I wanted
to give you an update that I've been
working on my health more by exercising
and watching what I eat wish me luck
damn good job I've been eating way more
junk food I think on my break than I
normally would have like I ate more
sweets and uh I've been going
to McDonald's and Burger
King and
KFC uh a few times less
KFC KFC just once
actually and I was so disappointed
actually cuz I I I swear the the burger
that I chose on the like there's like
the screen that you can choose the stuff
that you're ordering the burger that I
chose I swear like it was like there's
like the same Burger twice but one of it
is like more special has a tomato in it
and it has like an extra addition to the
name like something like delix or
[Music]
something and then somehow I ended
up and honestly it was the same on the
receipt too um I ended up with the
downgraded version of the burger but I I
took it home so it was takeaway so so
I I I didn't want to go back to fix
it yeah yeah yeah you know what I'm
talking about oh my God I was so
disappointed because it was like a
chicken
burger uh like some of their classic
Burgers a classic chicken burger but it
didn't have anything in it it had just a
chicken patty and I think maybe one thin
slice of of
lettuce and that's it and it's like it
was so boring you can't do that you need
a tomato in
there
yeah whatever I'm not going to not going
to answer that question I can't ask any
questions um right now I I've been
advised by my lawyer to not answer any
chat questions I have to read my Super
Chat good luck chocolate insomnic you
you are doing things that I am not
capable of so amazing props to you you
can do it though you're doing
it s May Racer thank you for the pinky
you're just V I know you I got your
limited edition birthday celebration
merge as well and I'll keep it forever
as a memory about kfb and kiaha I hope
your BS still remain here when I come
back from the race a few years later
yeah right I yeah you said you were
going to be gone even if I'm definitely
forgotten from kfp see
you how long did you
say you say a few years now did you tell
me how long exactly because
damn I can't I don't
know I hope sooner rather than
later but didn't you say you you just
you still you still be kind of around
not completely like you like as if
you're going to the
military
I'm not sure anymore but I hope you'll
still get to check my streams out every
once in a
[Music]
while well have fun with whatever you do
and pleas yeah look at the merchandise
every now and then and be reminded of my
[Music]
existence yeah what's
a yeah
[Music]
Unity
CH what I wait what text says I once saw
a guy chasing another dude with an axe
on my way home from work they seem to
agree axes are
[Music]
dangerous
what
[Music]
a I'm so thanks for the pinky I won't be
able to stay the whole stream but I'm
glad I was able to make it before the
break you haven't even left yet and I
already meet you but I'm so glad you'll
have time to relax you're such a cool
bird hope you have a great break thank
you
yeah the Spy I went to was really nice
for relaxing I think I'll go there
again I really liked it
thank you so much for your sweet words I
feel reassured by
them come in US
D thank
you Game exceeded your expectations it
seems to have exceeded a lot of people's
expectations damn that that game sold
well huh
sheesh jro D nin Max the first chat
thanks for the pinky hey wa I wish you a
restful and good break I will miss you a
lot but I think that this can be really
beneficial for you so I will support it
but oh well absence makes the hard gra
funder does it also make it grow funu
maybe like chocolate funo meow meow meow
meow so K if you w't be so happy and
hyped when you get back
yeah I think you guys were
excited I'm just I just feel so bad that
I kind of ruined the excitement with no
I didn't do ruin it I didn't do it but
yeah with failed streams man I was so
ready I'm so
prepared I even brought out my heart
rate
monitor heart
[Music]
challeng guys what do you prefer
chocolate funu or cheese funu for me
it's like 100% chocolate funu although
maybe that would my my younger self
would say that and nowadays I I do
appreciate of cheese
funu no but I'm not that big of a cheese
person I've become less of a chocolate
person but then again it's a lie
recently I ate so much chocolate oh my
God but I think like I'm less U of A
Sweet Tooth now than I was a few years
years ago so many cheese
people oh my God you guys love cheese
what the [\h__\h] so
cheesy
ew I did really like um like when when I
say cheese Fun de I think of the
fountain but in in France in Paris I had
the kind of cheese fun you where it's
like on this like big chunk of cheese
and then you put it on on the bugget and
and all that like that I prefer over the
fountain although I never I don't think
I ever had a cheese
Fountain and also raclet it's not cheese
fun you but it uses a lot of cheese and
it's like the main component and I do
love
that and guys I
have due to circumstances I now have two
ret
grills two I didn't even tell you that
did I did I have two Reet
[Music]
girls before New Year's I had none now I
have
two so
[Music]
annoying yeah I was going to return it
but the return date was way earlier than
I thought I thought it was going to be
fine I was just going to return it
within a month I thought it must be a
month but then I eventually checked the
receipt and then it was like oh what
only like one or two weeks I'm like what
the [\h__\h] it's already too late but the
thing is did I tell you how I bought
that thing I I I I went to buy one I
think it was a day before New Year's or
so and kind of stressful everybody
everybody was buying ret grills so when
I went there they only had like big ones
left so I had to buy a big one but at
the same time I was communica with my
friend who was like oh I think in my
Clos to supermarket they still have one
a smaller one I can go there and I'm
like yeah okay go there but like the
supermarket is closing in like 20
minutes so if I don't buy this one now
and yours is actually sold out because
you're going on the way there now and
then and then it takes you that amount
of time and then say your sold out and I
didn't buy mine so you know I have to
buy mine and then in case you you bought
yours then I can give back mine later
but for now I'll buy this super
expensive one which is way too big for
us yeah so I bought it and then I ended
up with two but I was going to give back
one but then it was too late and now I
have one big one and one small one I
really don't need this much ret
grills give it as a gift oh yeah I think
that one is unopened I could give it as
a gift H not h
interesting you know what maybe I should
give it to cie I feel like she would
love
it that would be so great she also likes
to have so many like people over like
whole life members at her place all the
time she could do
Reet I don't know why the first person I
think of is Cali
but yeah the smaller one I think I would
give her
perhaps or sell yeah I can also just
sell it but
[Music]
yeah nice idea right yeah yeah had the
more sociable member exactly don't
snitch I wonder if she knows ret though
do they have the right kind of cheese
yeah that's the thing but even if they
don't have Reet cheese I think you can
just go with some kind of
strong cheese that's like
similar yeah any cheese will do any
strong like not spicy but like spicy
when I say spicy now I don't mean the
hot spicy I mean the there's spices in
it there's a nice flavor to it a
flavorful spicy that kind of spicy I got
my waa towel hanging in the bathroom oh
thank
you looking
good
all the fancy looking food is sending
me for once it's not my my
[Music]
Twitter so okay shut up my lawyer told
me to not read the chat
anymore um where was I I here
uh yeah Che monkey T sh blue thanon
thanks for the pinky hi T I didn't
really know what to say but I still
wanted to send a super
you hope you enjoy the start of your
year and your trip of Vis thank
you yeah yeah it's been going been going
nicely this year have a lot of things to
look forward to so yeah let's go thank
you so much Nathan for your random Super
Chat cuz you just felt like
it John mea than you soon hero lunar
heart
D oh yeah I'm still talking to her k i
Channel D Murphy
D and zipley thanks for the red oo you
zipley
[Music]
master xop phone thanks for the pinky
enjoy your break W it sounds like you
already have a book picked out yeah but
I want to recommend fourwing it's about
a young woman who becomes a dragon rider
Oh I thought it was something political
about the white h house
I don't know cuz aren't there like
several like
wings which is like parts of the White
House
oh I might have been really wrong a
young woman who becomes a dragon rider
wasn't able to put it down and seems
right up your alley
H I'm thinking of The West Wing
a I don't know before I read a book like
that I'll be honest I I I I really want
to take the time to read Lord of the
Rings and Game of Thrones and maybe um
the other one that I
watched and that is going to take a lot
of
time you're thinking of West Wing oh
okay okay okay
chill nobody ever talks about the East
Wing what happens in the East Wing does
it stay in the East
Wing hi m home thanks for the pinky have
a nice break and try not to think too
much about work harder than it seems
sometimes we'll patiently await your
return hoping you come back refresh and
reinvigorate it thank you yeah the first
few days it was really hard not to think
about
work I was really curious if if there
was something new going on but then
later yeah I didn't really care about
work but then yeah V
tubing as a whole I couldn't quite
Escape like being reminded of
it which is fine I I felt detoxed all is
good all is well Wheel of Time yeah
that's what I meant Wheel of Time you're
reading it right now my mom really loves
The Wheel of Time
Books and she said that one is really
easy to read I
think maybe start with The Hobbit yeah I
I know it's the shorter one I
know yeah
I still have
another uh Lord of the Rings
world
book that I didn't read yet didn't
finish it I started it sometime also on
a spa
[Music]
trip thank you motion thanks for the red
super chat don't read out loud or else
oh okay
[Music]
sheesh thank you did you think I would
read it before my break or
now in any case damn you guys are so
helpful thank
[Music]
you giant
Apple what the
[\h__\h] tell me
more giant Apple a stingray tried to eat
my hand 20 years
ago
angel I'm guessing you're not here but
like you're making me
[Music]
curious
they're in the same family as
sh
scary
ouchy
scary do they have teeth H good
[Music]
question yeah I heard about the bre
Stingray we got to check back guys check
back on it two days later and and tell
me about it and then it said you know it
said that either you know there were two
two possibilities why it could have
gotten prante and then one of it is that
it could have made it with like other
Sharkies in the tank but then okay how
does that work could it be like with
humans that like a mix
comes out or is it just evil or the
probably it's just if it's maybe if it's
in the body of the stingray then it
would be a Stingray or if it's the body
of the shark then it would be a
shark but like how can they even
M it could have made it with the shark
yeah but we're waiting to see what the
yeah that will be the
answer M Jesus
R genetically they should be close yeah
so maybe it's just either or like could
could there be if if it if that was a
possibility to have like hybrids and I
feel like Humanity would have already
tried to like create weird [\h__\h] with sea
animals or like we would have already
even seen it happen in nature maybe I
don't know sounds
crazy
feels like we would have already seen
like crosses between those
things yeah I know we we kind of have it
in maybe overground animals but what
about underground like water
[Music]
animals so I'm really curious what's
going to what's going to happen with
that keep me updated guys if I don't see
anything on my own h
[Music]
no of course I did not take a genetics
course where the [\h__\h] would I do that
certainly didn't have genetics courses
in my high
[Music]
school usually The Offspring is effed
up interesting interesting interesting
interesting what if it's a it's a like a
like a fish with a fish but not like the
same fish but still a fish so it's not
like as weird as a stingray with a shark
or a dolphin with a Stingray or whatever
the [\h__\h] just a normal fish with another
normal fish though that look really
different does that
happen surely that happens
[Music]
right are fish
racist that's a good thing to
Google
at half an hour past midnight are fish
[Music]
racist what do you mean that's not a
common question why is that
not why is that not a common
question do animals have the ability to
be racist to to other variations of
species they have to be really closely
related species are they otherwise not
sexually attracted I guess there is no
such thing as sexual attraction between
fishies is
there they
just nature is so
[Laughter]
complicated I know I mean I
mean I mean animals can be horny right
what whatever
whatever let me read this and the human
says no if you mean can they develop an
animosity towards others or aliens fish
can fight attack defend against other
species as a matter
of species are not racist yeah okay
what's what is it then species
species now with a species yeah they can
fight the this type of basss can have
beef with that one this breed of salmon
can defend the turf against another but
that boils down to competition over
shared resources both need to survive in
the environment in
question if
you yeah I guess you'd call that being
species all I can say for sure is that
some species of fish are more aggressive
BL blah BL blah
[Music]
blah this is such a I'm I'm I I'm so
[\h__\h]
weird dolphins are very horny yeah I've
heard about that I
think R you fish races and finish Super
Chat well well what do you mean Finnish
super chats my my super chats don't have
a nationality they're not
[Music]
finish this what are you talking
about very International Super chats
okay there not just
[Music]
finish I'm not going to finish them
anyway wait are you guys laughing about
what I just said yet
or there I think there it goes there
there is there it is dancing
[Music]
reaction
nice solid word like thanks I'm
[Music]
proud where was I oh yeah um maybe a
stop there giant Apple the stingray
Super
Chat I I'll end it there I need to eat
and then download uh or buy
Yakuza I'm happy that today worked out
even though the game was
well well thank you for watching today
and you remember
and I'm sorry
that I'm weird I'm
[Music]
sorry
and oh
man I'm so we I'm going to listen to uh
P
now and you should do the
[Music]
same byebye see you
tomorrow woo
[Music]
woo
for