assistant
[Music]
yes
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this is
foreign
[Music]
thank you
hello hello hello
hello
[Music]
everybody and welcome to Among Us with
whole life English and Indonesia
[Applause]
[Music]
today to present to you a new feature
that just was updated in Among Us the
whole life caught you
wow wow
okay let's go yeah wow
I have Cosmic Cube then you can like get
outfits from selected members from Whole
Life en ID and Japan this these streams
are not sponsored but we just really
want to show you so good look at
everything some of us are already
dressed up aren't we
yeah
wow look at those snazzy videos
introduce themselves and they can also
show off their sexy outfit while they're
introducing themselves
we might get kicked out of the room
eventually but let's just start uh let's
start with Ahmed
wearing anything uh number one detective
I'm naked
um
[Applause]
she will have some sick outfits some
sick trip right yeah yeah
okay below um we have Anya at least in
the Discord so Anya introduction
yourself please
hello everyone I'm shirakamian today
nice to meet you guys
second to the nation hello hello thanks
for having me
okay next we have pimari
[Music]
hi I can't really I'm having some
trouble with the choppy audio which is
yeah it's streaming but guess what also
my mommy hooked up my Wi-Fi which means
I'll be streaming in 480p which to be
honest why even why even [\h__\h] bother
why even bother yeah I'm here to get
some whole swag As a sheriff let's party
get this
[Music]
get the song clips of you guys every
once in a while next week
Amelia one of the selected people you
can get the outfits of hi Gouda
hello
yes we're officially in the Among Us
lore now
[Music]
you can have so many imposters of
yourself do you even know who who is you
anymore
please introduce yourself are you Gouda
who is you Google
um
[Music]
I don't know seems like an imposter
and then we have Muna who is also part
of the people's outfits you can get in
the game
hi everyone
nice to meet you you're wearing your own
hair oh yes
I feel like right now I'm wearing a
scientist outfit right now I feel like
I'm I'm doing a touring love in the
Among Us
yeah
okay okay and then we have Mommy hi
Mommy
this looks like Phillips Empires I'm
here I'm chocolate ice cream today yeah
chocolate ice cream we're working on it
right Mommy
oh
yeah
who are you going for what outfit do you
want
whatever is the closest on the street
yeah understandable all right and then
we have
yeah
whole life ID today I'm cosplaying as
sexy naked money in your area
that impression was so good what the
heck that was really good I felt like
she was here
[Music]
wow yeah okay and then we have Zetta
hello hello hello I am I will be the
second the shiraka museum today
[Music]
oh my God
okay
the organizer of today's events the
sponsor of today's event
[Music]
thank you
of course of course that happened one
second I will open a new room that
timing was amazing yeah the fact that
that happened on your turn yeah so sad
okay true a new code is in the Discord
chat please please go get it and don't
make it seem to the to your screen
um
one second
[Music]
let's let's re introduce
thank you thank you thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
and I will now change the world settings
we will have everything included we'll
have scientists uh just in case you
don't know the scientists can see the
vitals at any time no not any time well
there's a countdown but you can see if
someone's dead before finding the body
and then we have the engineer engineer
can is a crewmate who can jump into the
vents so you can maybe with that
tasks yeah or you can maybe find some
other imposters because of that might be
helpful meeting in the vents yeah
that's too spicy for you too you're very
spicy and now we have the guardian angel
which I thought was really useful
because the guardian angel is the ghost
of the first crewmate that dies who can
then go on to protect others from death
we have last but not least the shape
shifter this one is that that calls for
a lot of
fights I would say
Shape Shifter can be only an imposter
but that imposter can change the looks
of themselves even the name so if the
shapeshifter is me I can change to I
don't know Anya and even have her name
and her outfit and I can kill people as
her a people will think it was Anya oh
my God what if I was the one who found
you instead there will be two onions
but just so you know all of these roles
are not 100 so it's not guaranteed that
you that they will be in the coming game
but you know it might happen to you now
let's start off I guess yeah
[Music]
hello
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
she died before and she was just a
crewmate anyway I am I'm gonna go engine
room oh hello okay I'm a scientist
so far everybody's still doing well
sometimes you know there's some really
Speedy kills anyway hi everybody hi kfp
nice to see you here
uh how's it going guys I've been
practicing a lot today and yesterday to
get some points
um so that I can show you some sick drip
it's almost as if hi Mommy hi
oh what the [\h__\h] okay but now I'm
regarding Angel all good
Luna
oh there's a lot of people here maybe no
need for protection
know that she's about to be killed but I
don't want to waste it how do I not
waste it also I need an alibi there's so
many voices here I guess you wouldn't
have killed when there's so many
problems I'm
is on her that's I never I never
actually protected someone before
I think I saw an angel of myself on her
oh no it's gone
that was fast um
where was the body Armory yeah
[Music]
I think or was it Ollie
keep it
[Music]
come on
well she got killed fast
because I saw Guru also in uh nearby
there in the kitchen guys
inform you guys
[Music]
I have no idea
but can you guys like tell me um
um
news hello
good oh okay okay okay cargo bay oh um
can you hear me huh huh why would you
kill your mother I hear you chuckle
don't act as if you can't hear me ah you
know what they call it an English
mattress side is when you kill your
mother aren't you ashamed huh that is
unbelievable it would be in the news
tomorrow
tomorrow they will say
killed her own mother with no mercy and
she was just laughing about it
[Music]
was funny I will pay you back for that
revenge is coming I don't know oh hello
hello
[Music]
go away
thank God there's someone else here too
okay I gotta I gotta do tasks but in the
friend
there is a task there okay hopefully
hopefully she will give up
we'll have to do some tasks here
okay one
let's do one more and then we go back to
looking around
so they're still alive uh uh where's my
where am I yeah
I can protect people again soon
I really like this Guardian Angel thingy
um
I like this roll I think scientists is
like kind of lame which I actually had
before How Lucky I Am to get both
scientists and no wait garden angels
only because I died I guess Ollie can
you hear me myself
[Music]
oh
I wonder who the other imposter is
[Music]
where do I go
so this one
um
[Music]
maybe it's her too I can I say that last
time I saw zado they were in the main
hall
[Music]
you know I was listening about Google
because uh
she she telling me on the previous one
it was me well I definitely like far
away from the kitchen and now they are
seen her a little bit yeah
[Music]
do you have anything
yeah that's why any last words
I go up
don't you have some shoes
we have lived in a short time uh choose
uh who's you're gonna I don't know
[Music]
it's so chaotic oh my God
imposter she wouldn't be able to hide it
for too long
she's like
I think I think like Kobe is a typhoon
who's too you know you're just kinda
just kind of feel it oh let's make a
burger okay
[Music]
if only Elena could hear me wait I
forgot already
yeah a vegetarian burger
I want to protect Lena
let's try to stay close to Lena must
survive
we actually played so much off screen
today like for two hours at least with
like most of the girls like seven or so
and the more time would pass the more
would join us but in the beginning we've
even played a game of only four people
this is the Imposter this time oh
okay
oh security you can listen to their
conversations with their Channel
hello I'm doing electrical
um
who should I protect
oh
I have to do this task
I got imposter so many times uh off
screen
at least once today
that's insane Watson is dead uh I found
the body
I was in the front
um of the ship and I was doing the tasks
that were up there and then Watson came
in and we chased each other around for a
little bit and I was like don't don't do
this to me Watson she laughed she was
like I'm Gonna Get You he he and then I
was like haha very funny and so then we
did our tasks
right after while I was figuring out how
to do the mini game I was like how do
you do this then mume ran in and was
like he hates he and doing things and
then I walk out and watch some dead body
is there
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
Watson left and then you came in and I
walked past you and Watson's dead bodies
on the ground I just want to know what
that's about
why you remember so much Kelly I'm I'm
just surprised
here's the deal so the amount of time in
between me entering the room seeing
Watson leave and mume entering and me
going outside was so short
right so we win
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
are we getting it
yay
[Applause]
[Music]
the honest cream
good job everyone congratulations crew
yeah
um
[Music]
no that was the only time I've ever done
something legitimately in a month
I think I think Kelly you should go for
the Amelia Watson detective outfit
um
thanks are you guys ready for another
round yes
[Music]
come on
[Laughter]
always every time okay
as I said I was lucky with getting
imposter a million times off-screen
[Music]
yeah but I don't know what will happen
on stream we still have some time
I want to show my new imposter skills
because I I did pretty well off screen I
I did like like a full run basically
alone the other imposter did nothing
and I won the game
by killing literally everybody
was pretty skilled that was not even on
stream like I did some members only
among us last night but that that what I
just mentioned wasn't even on stream
unfortunately hello I
oh yeah I mean the toilet spicy and
close the door
maybe we can get like a nicer location
than a toilet hi I'm going to clean this
third spot
well why would you need an alibi
hello hi you're not gonna hurt me right
there are a lot of people in here I'm
just doing my tests as long as there's a
lot of people here we usually safe
okay why don't we just stick together
aggressive bonking
oh we're gonna go across did somebody
come on man we can't go across there we
can't go across
oh
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no if we combine your hats with my
your head with my body put your head on
my body
[Music]
found always dead
that was crazy so I don't know the map
super well but I left the shower so I
put away all of the washcloths from the
shower and then I walked up and I turned
right and I went down that long hallway
and found Ollie's body right in the
middle of there but I didn't see anyone
coming down
so like above the shower house above the
shower knives to the right yeah on the
way to the archives
and you'll remember well let's see um
Renee was busy doing things around the
shower
um also rained could have killed me and
she did pretty close I think girl was in
the shower as well but she like went
down to the left no I was up in the
meeting room with Cobo
do we have the like he said who's gonna
be the delay of the of the kill because
because if if it's really if it's
raining if she already killed only
probably she cannot kill you
right but I mean Renee could have killed
me several times and she didn't so I I
feel like
she was trying to tell me a joke and
then I ran away from her
[Laughter]
I have no idea because I didn't see
Ollie at all and I was like at the left
side
the whole time yeah it was mostly down
below
yeah no I'm just like saying uh so
probably saying that you are nearby the
the place I just like thinking oh true
I'm true
but I I don't remember I saw Muna Senpai
in the middle-ish or on the left side
by the way um
[Music]
let's meet on the left side
is Spider-Man
of course my date
where's your what my date I made a dates
an appointment and she's not here
oh she ditched me
maybe she didn't hear it I look he heard
her that's like
yeah yeah yeah
okay okay listen people you put your
head on my body and we can become one
[Laughter]
I mean it's not a joke
I see a statement
s
like literally
yeah I can't do this one I will do it
leave it to me
I fixed it you're welcome
um
[Music]
shall I be your alibi
well I just want you to know that I'm
yes I see you very clearly downloading
the secret files what are you
downloading
pictures pictures of me
that was funny because I I was
downloading pictures of you you were
downloading pictures of Me Maybe we can
share that in there where she does yes
how do we what is use the card like that
I didn't even have to go down there no
I'm going down I have one task here I
think
I know this because I haven't played
this game for a long time but I noticed
they added some new things like the
levels and uh
some other stuff they added streamer
mode so that the code doesn't get shown
on the screen which is really nice
because we always had to cover that up
in older collabs
always have to cover it up and then that
way always it was always someone who
would accidentally show it remember and
then randoms would join the lobby and
we're like let's make a new Lobby um
shape shift
you
oh my God
our children
or was she very bottom of the armory
what
um
anybody else Kiara I was whispering and
we confirmed each other as Alibi Yes
[Music]
actually I was on the way to the kitchen
so any any sooner I would have fallen
the body but I'm from the engine room
what the heck I saw you I saw you at the
right side of the map going up
because I was doing tests at the cargo
bay you know there's the top oh okay
cool
[Laughter]
[Music]
so um
so you from the cargo bay you need to go
you went up and then tried to go I'll
explain my route I went cargo bay uh for
the you know small thing and then I went
to the showers because you know that
those are a two-part tasks after the
shower I went towards the main hall
engine room Communications because I
have thoughts in the kitchen and viewing
deck and then I was about to turn to the
Armory and then bomb that body oh so you
were pretty close by yeah
it was my imagination but Dana went past
me and it was that that's voice we're
gonna be there
but it was like way back
inside
me and it was not famous voice it was
zetta's voice and I was like I went like
what
I didn't even spot
in time
it's that same
sorry
because I was thinking of like who I can
vouch for and who I've never really seen
around and who talks a lot or who
doesn't really talk in the meetings and
I have to say and
um Muna a little bit of sauce
some others too
but I can at least vouch for
um
Gouda
and Reina although they might just be
protecting me because she loves me
oh oh oh oh no no no no no no no no
don't go away go away please don't kill
me
[Music]
the thing is not here
you always have to walk around so far
well I like this map though
[Laughter]
[Music]
he's here right now
what you came from this side because
like for explaining yeah
[Music]
I'm so sure
right I'm so sure
yeah
we were we were met in here and you're
going that way I'm going down what
happened I don't know whatever I mean
maybe not but it was kind of weird you
came from somewhere right you normally I
wouldn't know
oh
I'm going here I want to go here and
then I saw you so I was just like going
around what's happening what's happening
what's happening
but just stay away from me and then
we're good okay
okay that's real Muna though yeah at
least you can confirm that oh I'm gonna
talk somewhere around I'm gonna say
something no okay that's right
I'm not you know what I mean guys
that was weird I feel like she shouldn't
have come from that side when I just saw
her somewhere else like you know going
in a different direction you know what I
mean
we'll see we'll see we'll see
we'll see eventually guys
also my intuition is usually right hi
lumay I have an intuition about you as
well
uh
uh I'll fix it on you know
who's that where's that thing
there you go hi
and then to the show hey
[Music]
the problem I have by the way is like
when I'm a crewmate I'm apparently very
sus
but when I'm not I'm apparently not very
stressed
because as a as a imposter
I usually always win and no one ever
stresses me at least in the practice
runs
wait why is team telling me that Elena
is playing Among Us now did she get
kicked out
she gets kicked out and join again
no she's still there uh
that's weird yeah I'm good I just now
got the pop-up
okay it's normal
wait send it back
where who's there
wait where
where I was I was just doing the stinky
electrical task with Anya and I ran into
Renee and mummy
that's uh technically that's true I I
keep thinking why I think these three a
two Row in the back is always you guys
always spots sounds about rainy why yeah
right
now it's raining nearby
it wasn't me it wasn't even me reporting
I don't know where the body is this time
yeah could be shape shifters don't
forget shape shifters where was the
vertical guys where was the bunny where
was it
wait I want to ask uh Arena where are
you at I'm at Medical I came from cargo
bay
um what with Muna Muna was like going
from bottom to up oh yeah
and and where was the body
how about Watson how about Watson was
with Muna Senpai for a little bit but
then I was down by electrical like down
the ladder that's where I was coming up
when it was reported
why is Mermaid so always so afraid of me
or is she just afraid of everybody in
general he's been pretty quiet yeah I
was thinking the same
I was gonna see
the body both the body is in the
bathroom
[Music]
I don't know what should I choose
that's okay I think that gets her kicked
out
no no
yeah Coco was trying to get the facts
so what happens
now we just need to eject one more one
more
who are we going to reject where are my
tasks
am I done I'm done
tax yeah my taxes no not quite yet
working on that
working on that in the next week
um
well yeah so I'm just chilling now
um what's up everybody
you like my outfit I combined these two
I also felt like my my quote on it and
the Amelia outfit worked really well
together I'll show you guys afterwards
Maybe
you let me be the hero of the day
beautiful lights back on baby
we like to do which
when there's light
so we see what's going on we can look at
this I never really look at this kind of
stuff because it doesn't really tell me
anything like I don't know who it is
hmm
I mean oh wait so someone just probably
vented there right oh
hi Cobble
talk to me
I'm sorry oh that's cool okay so I was
just checking your voice if that's
really you
I'll protect you I'll stay with me with
you so you don't get killed I'm safe
okay okay
you sound very terrified
no I'm fine you really
disappear
what the [\h__\h]
off
where'd you go
invent yeah
how many times
[Music]
it definitely wasn't rated then I
thought it was very lucky but uh I found
her body in the kitchen but I saw no one
else around
I I heard I heard rainy so double ganger
of me
so yeah
wait what I was I was in before that I
was in a cupcake with with Google with
gura and then and then rainy come and
say she got she's so double Ginger of me
so I didn't know so somebody was
pretending to be you I did see Randy
you're running from Luna but maybe it
wasn't Muna Muna
not this time but I was with her often
enough wait was that the previous run
I'm mixing things I can't remember yeah
was that last game
it might have been last game when I was
a lot with rain was it I ran into Kobo
Kobo was sounding very scared though so
we have to vote for someone hobo is
killing someone scary is that cool with
Como I was like for a while together she
could have killed me she didn't so I
think she's fine
I think we already went out so there
should only be one imposter yes there is
a couple of times a couple of times I go
with Ahmed but but she didn't kill me
neither
um have a feeling that
maybe but they're not but they might be
on there uh I got a doppelganger so I
don't know I don't know I just wanna
because last time Muna is with arena in
the weapons like it's me right wait so
why was Reyna's body in the weapon where
is that close the kitchen I haven't I
haven't go I have to go to the Armory
can anyone vouch for Ahmed and say like
she's safe I was with Gouda and I didn't
kill her mom and she did forever I was
fussing about Kobo though because
I don't know
no one isn't sure about anyone no you
know in this scene like uh when you
select which where you go I heard I'm
talking who also comes but she wasn't
like talking as if she
like was an imposter but I'm feeling
like maybe she she was like aware of
that that she's being heard and then
purposefully tried to create an image of
herself being you know
innocent
but I don't know
that would be like so big brain and I
want to copy that Strat I want to do
that too
like active oh no one hears me anyway so
yeah um so well I still have some tasks
to do say something like that you know
I think I still had some tasks there on
there hi Mona
e
[Music]
awesome
[Laughter]
contradiction
holy [\h__\h] that we're still there you
guys hear me yeah but very quiet
oh you wow
wow
[Music]
I wonder why people kept aggressively
trying to frame me yeah
it was really hard I was barely doing
nothing it was so easy to do
[Music]
it's not here
I have a question on there because I
heard you in the in the selection screen
where you choose where to go next I
heard you say something that sounded
like something
like you might have been acting
was that what you were doing
um
let's go okay so you were like aware
that we would hear you and you were on
purpose saying something that only a
crewmate would say yeah
let's go
oh my God are we waiting for Muna right
now
I'm back okay now
um
[Music]
let's go congratulations
[Applause]
okay I always got the boring [\h__\h] man oh
hello hey I
I'm the organizer and I only get the
boring [\h__\h] I'm crewmate with no roll
what the [\h__\h] you too
what the [\h__\h] man can I trust you yeah
always baby
even if I was staying poster although in
the in our practice runs I did kill you
as the Imposter
's so hard yeah I'm sorry Elena but you
know I love you today
I have to go now I have to fix this one
for a second I thought she vented
because she suddenly disappeared
you know the outfits look so cute in
game
[Music]
I wish they would add all of her life
but but to take you like a million years
to finish the the tree for everyone
who's curious it took me
um like two and a half hours to get a
hairstyle
because first you have like two and a
half half hours of proper games because
you just
can't yeah
[Applause]
I don't know the location of the map oh
you know
then you will know um
I'm so rainy uh yeah uh going to the
Armory and the kitchen when when I want
to go to engine room so I didn't I
thought you better see from cockpit or
main hall
[Music]
I think
she went to the left side so she was
yeah she went to the left side yeah she
was in the shower I saw her in the
shower Cali do you have an alibi maybe I
was going out to get service I did pass
you Watson I was worried you were gonna
follow me outside but you didn't
and he probably weren't that worried
since you're outside with us but yeah I
found that actually right by the body
because uh I was like coming up the
ladder yeah because it was really dark
and then
you went up I went up no I went I didn't
see you go up
okay
I'm skipping I'm skipping oh well
I'm gonna vote for Zeta because
that's very nice
[Music]
they were killed she said
I don't know like someone going up but
they didn't yeah I don't want anyone
dying here it's a lot of fingers but
that's just her play style another one
hurt me but that's like that's just her
like when she plays Among Us and I find
it really cool she's like really like
when she her comments back at others
excuses are so funny
yeah
um
yeah I'm as a detective of course she
points fingers
but she's also good at acting
you know how she acted as a crewmate but
yeah the thing is like my intuition is
good but I never have evidence the same
thing was with the members among amongus
I was like I think it's you I have
absolutely no reason to believe uh to
like you know proven oh but I think it's
you and then it was always right like at
the end
I always knew it like in the beginning
and then they're like yeah yeah you're
just pointing fingers I'm like no
I'm not just pointing fingers I know it
but my heart is telling me yep
go down
oh [\h__\h] the shapeshifter roll is so
scary it's actually so overpowered maybe
I should
lower the percentage is it possible that
there's like two shape shifters out of
two imposters okay
would be right here and you know
right or is it so that it can only be
one
oh wait the light is back on oh
[Music]
only be one okay
good to know uh here
[Music]
game seems fair I think so too
it's good
but I feel like I'm having a hard time
following
conversations which is no problem since
my intuition is right anyway
hmm
I'll look harrisoned by hello
I'm not here where am I going
this place is still confusing
happy birthday happy birthday whose
birthday
oh There She Goes who's birthday who's
birthday only it's my birthday what
don't kill me wait what
[Laughter]
I would know that right I would know oh
my God
Anya's dead
What the freaking I just found Anya's
body in the bathroom and I'm pretty sure
Zeta and somebody else serves us here
okay
did I miss something where's the where's
the body uh anybody where's the body
bathroom is in bath or showers oh no
wait what the [\h__\h] Lounge
Lounge Lounge which one yeah
though let's wear out that's a day where
um
the last time the last time I went near
the shower and main hall is I saw only
amen and I think I think did anybody see
Anya with anyone
um
no I know I didn't see I just did yeah
I think is she alone in the
huh right side then
I think it's uh probably Kiara and Zetta
what oh
everybody
[Applause]
[Music]
she's innocent yeah yeah listen to me
I'm always us when I'm a crewmate and
when I'm not a crewmate I'm uh nuts us
so keep that in mind now you're saucing
me which means I'm a crewmate it's
always like this and I didn't work I
didn't do it are you sure about that he
always
why aren't you providing an alibi
instead of Defending yourself I was
around but it's only um
twice I was with only this included room
where like she would have killed me I
would have killed her
[Music]
unbelievable I'm gonna skip
because I don't know that's unbelievable
wait what others College who's willing
for me that's cool
[Laughter]
[Music]
there's something
I know we're here
I'm scared about me I don't want to be
close it's them
and then we're gonna go to the viewing
there too yeah okay
yes yes oh thank you ollie thank you for
standing up for me
yeah because it is it um I don't know
remember being nice on my birthday
I'm confused it's not your birthday
right
wasn't it your birthday like a like
recently a month ago oh no my birthday
is actually uh next month only for a few
weeks
and you're like you know I oh yeah you
know
um yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
go away
all right
oh right okay it's Zetta for sure I'm
voting not really oh really why it was
it's okay
the one you you said you you found a
buddy three times in a row now yeah
because I just happened to be a
detective who's really good at spotting
bodies three times
but I don't know man Rayna could I have
killed you or would I have uh killed
that body if I was with you and in that
room for like over 30 seconds yeah I
don't know uh you want me to be honest
um yeah what you said was oh just
kidding I was just waiting for my cool
down too yeah but I was already in the
room doing the task before you got there
instrument
to make a snake I don't know
I'm gonna go for it
it's the next time
can anyone uh give an alibi to Jada
no
no but I mean I can give Alex outside of
running away from the body because Reina
and I were both up in the room like in
the meeting room and then as I went down
I was with Raina the whole time and then
we saw Zeta pass us
for now yeah yeah
when I take the elevator what's in like
near the fan if if I die if it's not me
then okay 30 seconds 30 seconds I feel
like inside
um
everybody
trying to be thirsty ten seconds who uh
I voted for Zeta but maybe it's wrong I
went for Jenna too but hmm
ah
a couple went for Emma instead of me
interesting
people want to stick together the three
of us
yeah a family meeting okay the mommy and
the two sisters we can go to main hall
records right
record oh records are okay oh [\h__\h] now I
landed in the middle
[Music]
[Laughter]
killer who you hear in the horror movie
you hear them coming because you you
don't hear footsteps or anything you
just hear distant Hicks
oh my God that's such a horror movie but
like this is so ridiculous
the Killer
I'm not funny I know but
I can like totally imagine this like you
know
in the horror movies you hear like
people
they have certain traits that they
always repeat
[Music]
one
and then I'm done what about you do you
have some left
yep I have two more okay I'll follow you
in one two three go
hey let's go flip it yeah yeah can
everyone open the door
okay well I'll do it let's see who's
faster
[Music]
oh no
um
I hope someone is going to the other
side
[Music]
you can go on this side
don't die over there
the 0713 thank God the thing the
platform was over here yeah
come back and check for a body
well only one person can go there Emma
was gonna kill me I swear also I'm done
with my tasks let's go let's go up to
the emergency meeting and talk about who
didn't finish their tasks
okay
Ollie are you done
oh I have I have uh this one and
another one okay
six five
one two three four what what are your
times
[Music]
or okay okay
this one okay
[Music]
got killed
probably
I know she's alive she's alive never
mind
[Music]
trust me bro trust me bro it's I'm in
trust me bro
okay it's Kiara
why are you calling a bow I was just
doing my electrical thing
you could kill anybody did you what what
with her
I'm telling you it's on the dress people
probably Kobo to be honest because she
was with rain and I were together and
Kobo was not doing any tasks and she was
just following us trying to wait until
one of us was like separated cool but
what were you what were you doing
recently
I was just following them why why are
you done with your task or no my last
stars is in electrical
um
then why did you go up to where we were
Ollie Ollie I'm just scared you're
usually something good with numbers but
why did you mess up why did you keep
messing up that number thing I had to do
the keypad thing for you oh true that
was such it took so long after Cobra
went over to that side but I can look on
that side too right I keep no I was on
the other side once I was just being
stupid [\h__\h]
oh
I'm sorry
okay so why do we call this emergency
meeting in the first place because all
right because we want to develop you off
yes let's go um
let's believe it's not me it's either
Chiara Kobo it's even amical bull I'm
gonna vote for Ollie because I kind of
feel bad for her because nobody ever
cusses her
boy
[Laughter]
but no is that enough that's enough
right
play the game
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm sorry
I'm sorry oh okay wait is it what's that
lane is just [\h__\h] around man
this is getting pretty
much why am I going away from her I
shouldn't go away from her I need to fix
the light down there of the the thingy
someone down there
[Music]
but we have to find the body or we go
ready for the Emergency meeting we go up
there again
[Music]
that's also only as long as I can count
on you
yeah I went over to go searching and are
cheering us on you're like ah
oh no the lights are off again ah do you
wanna
[Music]
do you want to call it
wait
what the [\h__\h] why did you ruin the boat
what
are you here
okay
I'm gonna go up back to the emergency
meeting okay
because I only have one emergency
meeting and I already used it so it has
to be someone else
I'm pushing hard on this oh there's
someone coming over someone's there
someone's there
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's go up let's go
explain it I have an idea I have an idea
I go with what I go with Kobo and if I
die that's probably her
but what the hell how does that sound
but no oh
make sure we're done we need to win we
need to win but like if you go then
you'll die and then if I find your body
and then there's ah
come on hello
[Laughter]
what about your what about the task huh
what about your task
I done all my tasks
what tasks do you have left
I already beat my electrical task okay
so you're dead but that would mean
because we're all done if we're really
all um uh normal and we're all done then
we should have won by now so it's Kobo
come come early no come on probably
come on
[Music]
we could actually rate me so so please
she's done with her tasks we we both of
us are done too but what about what
about
[Music]
[Applause]
nice Ali good job team thank you nice
hustle
for no reason
and that's right yeah
but to be honest was so spot-on
yeah
this was kind of funny not gonna lie
her personality it's not that she's the
Imposter that's just her personality but
then everybody was like cool I'm saying
that it's her and I was like doubting
myself
yeah I thought you would believe me
um
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
well you I think maybe you can just
leave the the game maybe somebody killed
me no you have to go to the Imposter
um
[Music]
well Mommy thank you for participating
no thank you thank you for participating
okay
that's if I would
do that there
one thing on that is the V word
together again I don't have no idea
where she like
what the light up is down here there's
several ones though there's more than
one oh
so there's more than one
I'm gonna go with you
and trust you too
running around
uh wait I need to do uh this one
actually
um all right Emma
Emma well we can separate it's fine
oh my God
whoa what
people does
you watched her die
where
you said that where ah maybe we should
vote out she really wants to die oh okay
okay
[Music]
I want to watch me get like you know
beheaded or whatever okay then I'll I'll
grab this in here but she have My Little
Pony all right we'll give you until the
next meeting movie and then okay all
right this combo wanna talk about it
because she reported so cool yeah
oh yeah yeah where was the body where
did you find the body Cobble I found the
body inferno's Communications between
Communications and Communications and I
was uh I was uh
[Music]
the last time I saw Cali was somewhere
we'll give you until the next meeting
[Music]
sounds nervous
fighter
bedtime
by the way everybody says everybody says
even you Mom
[Music]
I'll do this tasks
doesn't want to be my daughter anymore
ah
a
you're so lonely my daughter doesn't
want to be my daughter anymore you want
to be my daughter
I wanna die but I need a new daughter
she's my daughter scared of me I mean I
I'm your daughter I just be dead well
come here
she has been released
bye-bye
I'm like
I'm shaking I'm shaking like I feel my
heart is so Doki Doki
press inside
[Music]
okay so let me vouch I was with uh girls
and find electrical
pretty quick to get an alibi there huh
wait wait who found which body though
there's three bodies right I found
zeta's body in cargo bay and it wasn't
there a moment ago I think but the
lights were out
I'm currently well I'm currently on the
meteorite I'm at the very top
I have an alibi for for Oli and gura
because I saw them and we were we were
near the kitchen first and then go to
security and electrical we haven't go to
medical and cargo bay yet
for a while so
[Music]
I'll buy
um
I want to ask and also why Kiara is not
screaming at all what do you mean I'm
not screaming giggly usually when when
she was the crew man she always voted
somebody cut me off and did scream
are you sure about that yeah what the
[\h__\h]
I've been I've been I've been uh
watching all of you guys
um you know
Sound by on the previous uh previous
games
Kiera really loves to scream when I ever
met anyone that's because that's because
you're scared and now you didn't yeah
and now so far you didn't show that you
are scared no you have an alibi no it's
because I didn't see anyone probably
that's because you're myself
at one last minute I don't know we found
them last minute
hahaha
what the [\h__\h]
no I'm scared for my life I don't know
what to trust anymore
[Music]
she's just floating around
I'm learning you're still doing tasks
that's so nice of you to still do that I
guess we need that to win because I'm
totally a crew member since I passed by
Amelia Senpai she should know that I
shouldn't be such because who goes to
the meeting room
has to survive when she's what's she
doing Muna says do some tasks why are
you just standing around ah so says all
right
[Music]
Kelly you're calling Muna the murderer
oh you died no way now I've been calling
people murderer to see if they respond
so like I can figure out who it is oh
you don't know yet huh no I mean I know
that Coco is one of them killed you oh
man I will tell her to get you know
understand what her position is don't
kill her senpies oh of course I will
tell her
[Music]
sorry couple
I got too nervous
Cooper hears me right I think she hears
me okay finish this girl oh my God five
I'll do my best to support her but I am
hey Kobo you love being a murderer watch
out girl kobo's on the way
[Music]
we'll kill her she's down there Kobo
she's still down there
she's like all alone there I think it's
a good kill
oh
I believe
I will I will protect you with my spirit
mommy is here don't worry
try to find someone alone in the in a
dark area
come on get
don't be so shy
if she's up there she's up there
she's
um and she must have gone ah where did
she go
maybe up here
I'll go find her
ah she's here
[Music]
okay goodness over there alone on the
left side come on
if I hold like an emergency meeting oh
come on go get her and then go over now
she can't hear
but she can hear the the ones that she
killed right
uh
[Music]
she's seeing
it someone said I'll be very happy
[Music]
it wasn't me yeah I saw I saw him in a
senpai going towards where Ollie was and
that was the last time I saw her
[Music]
it really went to check if anyone's bed
or you're the last one left and you want
to try to vote people out
[Music]
I thought it was over well you know what
yeah I'm done with my task anyways so
like maybe I can just go chat with the
girls you guys can vote that's what you
guys want
to [\h__\h] with the ghosts
[Music]
[Applause]
the whole time
oh
[Music]
could win this she has to play it right
Ollie I'm sorry that that happened to
you
it's okay
it's just you know she's just trying to
be a detective you know
yeah really
I believe you you did the right thing
[Music]
where's where's cool
bye um
I'm the Imposter
you what yeah
and there's another one who's still
alive
oh okay
just clutches I see where is he
you're talking
[Music]
why
I wish I could jump in Among Us I'm so
happy I wanna jump
online
okay
oh my God
every time Kobo is the Imposter it's
incredibly difficult that should tell
you whenever people are dying really
fast it's definitely Kobo I just love
how all they listen she saw the crime
scene went goes to the emergency meeting
and then Ahmed Changes Everything by
saucing the innocent ones yeah yeah
[Music]
that's right with you Kiara salty hello
like one last round
yeah
okay
next time you'll be a crewmate and
you'll be in peace
[Music]
all right let's go
um
well well well
I hope at least I stay alive
for a while just can't make people angry
you know it can't be says
it's nice though that the one time I got
it was with Kobo hey
that's like something people were hoping
for but hi Mona
sometimes sometimes
sometimes miracles happen
I want to play like longer but I feel
like how long has it been
[Music]
as much as I like to play longer I think
this will be the last one oh I'm so
hungry too cool
[Applause]
[Music]
what was your body I thought it was oh
no raining is dead so here's what I
found I was picking up all of the towels
and [\h__\h] in the shower and I said I hope
gura doesn't kill me a girl is fine I
don't think that she did it but I went
to the left okay
um we were in the same room and
um the people I saw were you gura Senpai
and Zeta
from the left of the shower walked up
and in that photo room we're all like
it's like a dark room I guess that's
where I found the body I didn't see that
there was a dead body in there because
the lights were out until it said report
conflict report and I guess Renee was
killed in the dark room so that's all I
have to say about that I literally was
just cleaning up the shower was anybody
down there oh okay the life so I was
laughed at electrical
where where I was at electrical I have
my I was at the bottom right of
electricity I walked at the bottom
well I mean
yeah
did you finish the towel the towel Cask
no I didn't finish picking them up I
thought I did but it wouldn't let me put
them inside of the hamper thing so I
still have to grab a couple towels I I I
am something with only because I was in
the electrical I saw I was in the
electrical I was in the middle I was in
the middle bottom and see that he was in
the bottom but I didn't see anyone
fight fight I skipped I don't know who
to vote for
um
it's just begun it has only just begun
[Music]
um
too much I wonder if we also have a
shapeshifter still in this round
um
[Music]
cloudy you guys want to see it without
the sensor huh
ah you can't see it and I should maybe
go first to the showers
where hopefully it's been cleaned up
power on the wet floor hello
it's so aggressive holy [\h__\h] this shower
has been bonked too many times
gouda seems fine hi amen
wait where
I need to scrape I need to scream
oh this one I don't remember this one ah
okay I'm just screaming because people
said I I scream um when I'm a crewmate
oh so um
I I I pass uh on Ollie's I pass on
Ollie's uh in the in the electrical I
was doing my electrical and then and
then after that she's going up and then
I saw I saw
[Music]
the first time the first time only said
that she was an electrical but I didn't
see it and then the second time you know
we we had to teleport first right and
then after that he said you know I'm an
electrical I find you and after that
um I'm still fixing my electrical and
then uh Ollie pass by going up uh and
then I was on my my end task uh doing
the electricity uh and then I saw Carly
died
[Music]
I wish your partner good luck Ollie
whoever was with you
hopefully can do this alone
gotta be careful the next one might be
same gen
[Music]
buns
is it actually Ollie well I mean I think
it's only because sisters I think she
would defend yourself more of them she
would defend herself more if it wasn't
her
this just sounded like something
[Music]
did you vote for us everybody voted she
voted for herself that's you know what
keep styling her no no it's her
definitely
that that just shows she's not a not a
sore loser oh no wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait okay
I'm coming
although we don't need two people here
but I'm on my way oh okay I'll go next
side okay
okay there's someone here oh why are you
not fixing it uh oh took you a while I
fixed it
in the middle of fixing it oh hell I see
she was I'll give her the benefit of the
doubt
would be the other one I have no
evidence of anything as again but also I
have no particular
intuitive feeling at the moment
that I could share with you guys
oh that was bad oh no rare yeah
I just saw her like a second ago running
away from the alarm like as she finished
the alarm and then she walked to the
right side towards uh Records Lounge Etc
the body yeah
I was in Maine Hall going to showers and
then Zita passed by and then I checked I
checked like around the showers and then
I go up and there's Anya's body are you
saying it was so close so the last time
yeah yeah but I was I'm expecting me
again
uh-huh
come on come on
I wanna I wanna
shifter access here it could be we don't
know for sure but it could be we don't
know for sure I don't know I don't know
but me neither but but it's like it's
like a kind of when she tried to do her
alibiers
[Music]
convenient
because we know it's not ourselves I'm
is voting for me again isn't she
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
but I did speak there you go
go
[Music]
I told you oh man you know I was safe I
didn't even have like 10 seconds of
gameplay
[Laughter]
you guys figured it out
it was pretty good good job everyone
good morning
that was a great job
I hear music
sorry okay
it's anyone who didn't get imposters
single time yeah
[Music]
yeah you know this game is like never
end I feel like I want to play it until
I got a me too
yeah
I wouldn't mind playing more but I'm
just worried about the ID members
because it's like you know 2 A.M
for me it's fine because I usually sleep
at morning
I'm still I'm still fine if you want to
but yeah
okay okay
[Music]
do this
so cool
thank you so much
[Music]
they sound fake I sounded like one of
them was
actually imposter but I hope I hope for
gouda that she's getting her impulse and
roll because you know
it fits her
she does such good kills always every
time she gets it
at least this time it's not like
repeating history where she gets like
kicked out immediately voted out
immediately oh it seems like what gouda
is not it no
whatever Ramsay's gonna kick my ass I
can't make this burger tomato onion
onion
okay I'm
okay I
did it hello
oh
huh spicy
what's your been gone baby
turn them back on so that you guys are
not scared
wait who is this I'm opening the door
thank you
I'm the door opener
how long can Chihuahua survive how long
can she Dodge the danger
swear
are you sure it's not itself
oh come on give her a chance come on
I don't want to talk anymore
[Music]
it was in the hallways it wasn't a mean
Hall actually oh yeah okay hi yeah so uh
I was I was I actually uh saw her
through the showers I went to electrical
a little bit then I went back to the
main hall and guess this I actually met
another Ollie so if you guys said
anything like that I saw how to kill no
there was actually a doppelganger and I
actually remembered she was chasing me
down
no no
you know what even if you
no I don't mind
I believe you though okay
I think I think I'm gonna skip because I
don't know yeah
she's desperate whenever she's just like
this
and whenever she tries to defend herself
always just like very very desperate
yeah yeah
I need
I need only as a meat Shield
yeah
the last time we didn't have a shape
shifter so this time perhaps Dooku
awesome
[Music]
did you hear that guys
let me tell you chonkers is not it
[Applause]
mommy's almost done this is the last one
I swear
only I believe you
probably you're not going to kill me are
you no no no no see I'm leave I leave
I'll leave you alone
uh wait I need to go to the right side
I'll go up once all the lights are on
oh following me I'm not
oh six six five eight so why do we have
the same price
[Music]
and then you can go okay I did mine I
didn't need to go to a records next
okay have fun bye bye
bye bye I'm going to the engine room
okay
and I still don't really know where
everything is
oh
and this one this one I know very well
mm-hmm
uh-huh
[Music]
I think Emma just keeps on sessing me
because she wants to play with me I
thought that she likes me too much
fine we turn on the lights again
yeah
[Music]
oh Dolly gets a pretty name plate I want
it me I mean I have I have an alibi
uh-huh you do you know so I was I was on
the first I wasn't security we drain it
if if I was imposer I've been I've been
with Rene uh for like a couple of
seconds I'm not killing her at all so if
and then you're wearing cool time
like was heading towards the showers I
think or the main hall I don't really
remember to the right and then I think
Ollie was asking like have you seen gura
or something
and then there was also or something but
there was like a bunch of people there
show me a magic trick I feel like Yeah I
wanted to show a magic trick I'm not
accusing anybody I'm just telling what I
saw okay
I mean um yeah I mean uh
okay I don't know yeah
no Ollie's fine I was alone with only
four a long time it was around Muna a
lot but she never killed me but okay
it can't be the same for yourself and
vouching for Ollie I mean listen to me
if it's something
for like a long time you want to save
her yeah but the thing is I don't know
Anya Anya was also there but Anya's also
there but girls also dead I don't know
hmm
uh-huh
I want to go to the right cards to do
another
her task is killing people oh no no it's
a type [\h__\h]
innocent
[Music]
always quiet
perfect spawn
and we saw Kobo and we survived
but Kobe is like really
um what's the word hesitant to kill
people like when I was following her
when I was dead
she just she had so many opportunities
and just didn't go for it but she won
anyway so I guess winning stretch
sometimes being hesitant is good when
I'm imposter I'm like I get really
aggressive I I tried to stand by scenes
oh hi
hi hello
no no no no no I would not
instead of talking to herself like that
um makes me feel like she's safe
because I don't think she oh
is up there in preparation to kill
someone
I can't do my task there what you said
I'm scared can you guys come with me for
a second Raiders trying to kill me
okay see I guess I really do scream
that's a really simple task you
wait that takes literally one second
it's her
anger it's I know who it is I know who
it is I know who it is
I know who it is I know what it is I
know who it is like keep doing the
Cliffhanger what is it it's Kobo it's
Cobble it's called because she was in
front of task that takes like one second
and she just took a minute
sir I just need to go to get to the
lights where the [\h__\h] are the lights
uh where's the nearest one I know it's
down there oh god oh it's back on okay
ah
trust me bro trust me bro
but really don't you agree guys like
oh [\h__\h] I'm down here again I don't want
to be down here I don't wanna
see meaning Emma's just gonna be like oh
yeah
[Music]
I want to call it though
elevator is not here
not elevator yes
it me how many people died actually and
that's a good question [\h__\h] we need to
find bodies
together yeah so I'm actually an
engineer want to see a magic trick I
want to see a magic trick we're here
okay okay okay okay okay
you should use that ability to find the
goddamn imposter but they're not in it's
cold by the way
oh they're not there I need to I need to
call the emergency room
where are my tasks anyway
uh okay I need to go up anyway for a
task I'm gonna go there now I'm gonna
call it because also we haven't found a
dead body in a while so we should for
safety just for safety
let's go
Emma's probably dead yeah
rip
I can't I can't right now
can someone fix that who is that
don't kill me I I was gonna call an
emergency meeting I'm gonna call it now
but yeah hello what happened
I want to say
it's koboam
s
because I like previously when I was the
Imposter with Kobo
um and I died before her I was like
following her to try to cheer her on and
I saw her she would go to that you know
that place uh the Electrical uh where
there's like one task but it takes
literally one second to do it and when
she was the Imposter she would stand
there for ages thinking about what to do
next and I literally caught her doing
that thing now but like she was there I
said hi I ran away because I was
wondering you know she's always there
when she's planning something I know no
one died but that's because she's a very
hesitant killer she did that before too
I was watching her and she passed Guna
alone a million times and she just would
not kill gouda for whatever reason she's
very hesitant and she goes always always
to the electrical to
practice if she's doing a task but it
takes one second
there believe me trust me bro I will we
don't have any proof I will I will vow
because the only thing that's like for
me suspicious is that uh she's she's
being like awfully quiet yeah she hasn't
really said anything up until like in
the discussion at all do you have a
defense for yourself yeah do you have a
defense for yourself like why are you so
quiet or you know I'm always quiet from
the beginning
a lullaby
what if I really
do my task in electrical I mean why
mommy gonna be so that aggressive
I did it right after you too and I know
it takes one second to flip them
Ali and Watson are always together
yes
[Music]
thank you
fake if it's right then I think I
deserve a medal if that was correct
I deserve a medal
please please I want to be correct
because that was his big brain
hello yay sandwich
I'm so happy that was big brain it that
was right
wow
[Music]
yay
let's look for more people okay let's
look for dead bodies
and not what I had in mind but okay
aren't you used to dead bodies
when you look at yourself in the mirror
every morning
must be remind me
oh nothing here okay okay
why should we go where could be a dead
body like electrical yeah yeah won't be
there anymore
he's gone
so we have to fix the lights
where's the friend I don't think we
should get on at the same time hello
hello are you guys not fixing your life
huh
nice all right I fixed it okay okay you
guys are too late I'm gonna go first
wanna see it quick where are you going
where are you going she has a password
we can't go over there with her okay uh
you guys done the tasks too me too yeah
and then I think rain is the last one
okay uh only it was also telling me her
tasks are done okay
showers oh interesting
interesting
hold on don't leave me alone help me
with the I opened it
thank you
I just have lounges
door closed did you steal my outfit
because it's cute
oh gamer
hello I'll go to the other side yeah go
to the other side please thank you
I'm about to fix her a free nine okay
two seven eight okay other
s
are dead bodies but who who's
unaccounted for like who was not part of
that group Muna just joined now for a
second
I don't know oh my God hello oh my God
that was a legit scream
[Music]
it's like oh the view is like so narrow
hi I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm
gonna vent here okay bye oh my God
[Music]
what's that where was it okay okay I was
just trying okay right now in the cargo
bay and she was about to vent because
she's she thinks she's cool
um and then I saw a red bunny
okay I just saw Moonah it must be Muna
it's Muna definitely don't you see that
um I was from the Gap room and I passed
by when you are fixing the electricity
and I go to the shower and then I go to
record again okay I was in Shout earlier
why don't you see you I I saw I saw I
saw I think it was Kiara and then Zeta
is from the shower too and we passed
away right okay
where is where is the location of the
body uh you tell me it's
um in the cargo bay between the door of
medical to Cargo way Arena and Zeta
which way were you guys going through
the showers like to the left or towards
the right I was with you I was with you
oh sorry sorry
was with me we came from the top to the
bottom from like Lounge to we stopped
and going the other way or you saw her
going with you I don't saw her I didn't
see her at all which is the problem what
yeah
literally I saw I saw like um I was in a
break I wasn't breaking and I go to the
Gap room
I go down I saw Zeta and then Kiara and
then uh Zeta and Kiara I think there
goes some of them going to the up to go
into the records and then after so after
that I saw okay if it's not again okay
if it's that moment it's Zetta and she's
just faking being an engineer it's Kiara
you always say it's mean it's never
memory I don't know would you say your
brain cannot handle that kind of skill
we will see we'll see if the game ends
now
if it doesn't end up
no it's not me I think
we'll see I think you know Mona because
she wasn't part of this big group that
we are running around with
um but I do think it's a funny
strategy to just fake being the engineer
yay
wait was Cobalt oh did I was I right
with Cobble was I rap Cobble was that
right
oh my God
[Applause]
genius you guys you guys like playing
girls like you guys going to two two
groups yeah which one should I follow
yeah
[Music]
a great a great round
excellent I think now it's getting
really late so as much as I want to
continue playing I don't wanna you know
of course people yeah yeah maybe another
time I need to play on stream to be
honest just together yeah
I need 600 more points yo get those yeah
I know right now
and I'm wearing it
December 20th to get all the Halloween
stuff
[Music]
[Applause]
I want to hear a goodbye from everyone
if that's okay
um bye no no no no
this is a real goodbye yes
let's start from the top again how was
it today
oh yeah it was pretty fun I won an
imposter round and then won all the
crewmate rounds or pretty much all of
them so it's you know a pretty good day
pretty good game thank you for inviting
me Kiara thank you for setting it up uh
yeah thank you guys for playing thank
you for always sussing me even though
it's almost never was me
it's like your reflex now but okay I
just want to see your reaction that's
how I test you okay
yeah it was so much fun
um I didn't get impulsive but it's fine
it's cool next time
again together thank you
it was fun yeah thank you too and next
we have Queen cocky
oh yeah that's me let's see
um
I was born to be crewmate I don't like
playing imposter anyway so I had a good
round
um really only one super good play in
the beginning and then everyone gangs up
on your toys
and then everyone killed you early
thanks you had so much
whenever you like explained something it
was really easy to listen to you and
like we sounded so convincing and you
were not lying to you it was you were
never bullshitting us I just gotta work
on my longevity in the game
you didn't get imposter right
I didn't but I made sure to be the damn
this best teammate that I possibly could
oh yeah
honestly I'm a bit relieved I I was
scared to see what happens if it's like
especially like shapeshifter and
positive and all of you
oh my God that's terrifying thank God
she didn't get it I really want to be a
safe shifter I haven't got that yeah
it's fine pretty rare
well well if you guys want to look like
good on go get the Cosmic Cube
yeah take over the world
can you give us a statement about your
actions today how many times were you
imposter
three times
it's like sometimes I'm so rig and these
collabs there's always like one person
who gets it all the time
yeah I only got it quite a bit too right
like 20. yeah I want to say sorry for uh
those who are uh me imposter together
with me because I cannot
um I don't know why but I'm playing on
this room like a there's
maybe pressure pressure so yeah yeah
yeah I am pretty sure so I'm not that
like I felt that you you seemed very
pressure
if I if I silent for a long time because
uh first I I don't really uh can make a
good exercise or I will buy maybe in
Bahasa Indonesia
um it's a little easy but
um I don't know that's fine you can
always use that as the excuse like
literally you say I use that with the JP
no English please
[Laughter]
yeah
and then we have Ollie who gets sussed
so many times even when she died
it was actually pretty funny because I
thought the reverse psychology would
work it did not
like I thought if I actually reverse
psychology guys like twice which means
if I actually asked us and say oh I've
actually says
Ah Ali's just messing around but not but
that's what I was feeling like I think I
feel like
stay alive
[Music]
thank you for accommodating yourself so
sweet
hey Kiara thank you
[Music]
is not here anymore let's go to Lena
oh hello yeah I started the stream naked
in the end the stream naked even though
I unlocked the outfit
we're inviting me to the collab was
really fun playing with you guys was fun
or two to all the crewmates and also the
imposters yeah great shape and the
guardian angels
[Music]
to be the imposters yeah my link we have
one more time
[Music]
it was so much fun I got a few imposters
how many how many
two free
uh two or three I don't remember lucky
girl it was fun thank you for those who
teamed up with me and thank you thank
you for hosting it and I want to
apologize because my stream died six
times
I don't know I just told him oh God
[Music]
she can't talk well with that being said
I'm sure she had fun too
yeah and uh oh there she is
oh no voice
I'm Gonna Leave something in the chat oh
yeah you can say goodbye
hello
yeah okay okay let's go to Discord
everybody Discord all right all right
let's talk today yeah so I cannot hear
anyone we're here now
okay
okay so how was it
it's okay you got your full outfit now
Muna you did it
yay congrats thank you Nations you look
good so I hope you had fun yeah
[Music]
I have fun uh actually uh the first time
I'm doing uh the to become an imposter
with I mean it's really fun
is the one that I'm I'm usually afraid
of whenever I become an imposter
yeah I think I feel extra safe if I make
it a list it's probably a me Kiara and
then Kali is the one who can like talk a
lot that make me you know
so that's usually the person aggressive
protective Sheriff
[Music]
I think I got to hear from everybody I'm
glad that we all came together for
another big Enid collab I think the last
one was Mario Karts
like a year ago yeah it's a long time
well maybe since there's a lot of New
Roads we can try it again sometime soon
with the new rooms
[Music]
starting to watch our streams today
tonight
[Music]
I'm having so much fun and I really
don't have anything else to say besides
good job everybody hope you had fun and
yeah see you again soon sometime
yes everyone yeah see you soon
[Music]
[Applause]