[Music]
so
do
hi
whoa
yes it'll be working
[Music]
hello ladies and gentlemen
if you can hear us give us some carrots
in the chat please keep going
some carrots
good audio carrots
in the hair can i should i move closer
oh i see carrots okay they can hear us
yay your hearing works guys you know
your vegetables
carrots
lots of carrots
good for your eyes good friends your
audio sound besides me
because i was on the other side
hello audio does it sound okay
oh you can sit here it's like
yeah yeah
[Music]
you can't hide forever
look i care on the screen
i'm not a carrot
okay
should we get along one
yeah probably wondering what that was
well
i have a little bit of an announcement
as you guys know axe anime expo 2022 is
coming up and uh it will not be without
hollow live this year we are going to be
having our official hololive booth at
anime expo uh booth number being number
4606 in the exhibition hall
at the los angeles
convention center july 1st through july
4th
what can you find at the booth
i'm happy you asked
well then at the booth
uh uh-huh cue the slides
oh
look at all these merchandise we got
t-shirts and well uh we have home alive
uh
uh the chosen hollow live uh members for
this ambassadors
and myself
senpai's and myself
lots of merchandise that can be had with
really cute poses
with all of us which is really exciting
you can find us at the whole live booth
as well as uh
all of these
beautiful what do you think what are
they watching how are those look wow
wow
it looks like a pixel in my eyes
it looks great what does it look like
chad describe it to me
do you see your oshie's name chad i
don't see it clap your hands if you can
see her oh she's name
wow
[Music]
for other merchandise you have any more
slides in there oh
there are more oh
[Music]
it's on the screen it's it's me it's
your
shark
do you like the pose i chose it myself i
chose apples
that is really cute yeah jumping in
there
thank you you got a nice shape there too
is that your thumb
or is that like a one
acrylic
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's okay as long as
let's see the next slide
it's like slime
it's a button the button the button it
looks like
it looks like another tip anyway uh
something anyway it's a button with me
yeah
what you can literally put the button on
girl's face right now it'll be
exactly oh yeah
it's too much work but you know it's
it's not
that accurate
actually
i'm missing the impossible
oh my god
[Music]
okay
okay what else do we have uh
these are the close-up of the
keychains of various halloween
members
who can't
[Music]
a ring on your thumbs
some bling some eyes
you can get a t-shirt a t-shirt
wash it carefully now
yeah it looks like a manga or something
right yeah it's pretty cute isn't it but
everybody's faces
oh so cute
back i guess
right
it can work both ways you can do it
hard enough
i can work both
yeah so you can be like subtle or you
can be like really in your face
how anime would you like everybody to
know you are
i want people to walk up to you but like
what is halloween
[Laughter]
it could be a clear file that could be a
poster that could be anything anything
you want it to be all that matters is
that it's cute
[Music]
two more things verbally uh there's also
going to be merchandise from set ready
hololive comic market 99
as well as
our very own calliope maurice solo
concert merch
from new
underworld order
you'll be in time for her concert
essentials pack acrylic light t-shirt
towel with a pvc pouch and a sticker set
you have to pay for shipping if you're
going to ax in the first place yeah you
don't have to wait either you can get it
until you have a concert
yeah all right guys july 1st or 4th on
l8
[Music]
[Applause]
time for a regularly scheduled program
another one
we are playing
why am i michael moose hello but we're
playing last rows
we're gonna smash
[Music]
and we haven't set it up but we can get
no problems no problem you guys are pros
right
the only pro about me is my controller
that i don't have today
i'm incredibly good at this game last
person i beat the butter out of was
creamy
[Music]
can you guys hear the music their audio
okay carrots if you can hear
yes they say yes
we're good okay
very nice all right they're giving us
the carrot the carrot of okay
i don't know why i said carrots
mr yummy oreo
[Music]
for healthy chat also the tv is like
blinding me
it's very bright
[Music]
so
where is this girl
very good
what oh what happened okay
i mean let me switch over
sitting on her lap right now
santa i would like
a ah for christmas a pony a pillow and a
pony yeah two in one it's like buy one
or freeze it didn't change
they don't get lost
i i stopped moving because i was asking
for my christmas
on the screen right now animated so i
don't think i'm moving we will switch
off okay
no biggie but they have to move you girl
forcefully move you or move myself
together
do you want to go left oh there you go
here
okay this is fine
this is my shortest actually
for people who are wondering
uh where cali is
we will be with callie
soon soon
yeah it's a very busy
some people should know but we're
currently recording stuff for my
birthday concert
that's why we have grabbed here
[Music]
oh uh
i don't even remember them all the items
i think all items are fun
yeah yes all items is good yeah
oh man i can't wait to play against
yoshi
hey
but do we have all three colors
yeah they all connect i think oh that
one needs to be turned on yeah you need
to just press left right oh it might be
well it might be charging it might not
be charged why not says three
think that's fully charged right
wait oh you can't charge those
individually huh no all right we'll just
play till it dies
all right
because
[Music]
no
i see three fights here doesn't that
mean it's
it's the third controller connected so
it's just oh
yeah no you're right you're right what
is this
smash
i got the best seat in the house
oh my oh my god
[Music]
okay great it's huge i don't know where
to look it's literally like as big as my
bed yeah
the size of the bed
tv i like to watch movies it's bigger
than my bed because my bed is like a
single sized bed that's like half of
your tv
okay
wait i didn't choose a character
[Music]
yeah
yeah there you go
wait did it die steve i
i think i think you're
[Music]
but i have more characters
one two three
one two three one two three one two
three one two three there you go
dead
apparently according to i think buddha
said
she thinks i'm the fittest out of all of
us you are
i said that i think so rather than we
fit trainer for today how do we start
why are we being monkey man
oh why not we can be monkey
minecraft yeah
he's really hard to play clear the legs
so
all right just spam it
gotcha all right are we good what you're
[Music]
[Laughter]
wouldn't you be able to add one more
player
you
[Music]
plus
wait i think you have to like click
like clear three has to click but never
look oh it's fine on the obs i don't
think so
chad what do we have to play for you so
yeah don't you have to select yeah and
like go up the button
let go
select it and let go
there you go
why is he an underling
it's because they have to fit his skin
on like the minecraft steve's skin like
candy super chat playing against my
oshie oh my god what a dream come true
andy all right mine mine
minecraft minecraft
puppy i don't know what these are
all nice
[Music]
oh
my
[Music]
items i forgot oh what's this
wait where is the small oh
i think we swallowed one of them as much
oh wow
wrong way
oh
[Music]
nice
i think that was my pill
get inaudible
wow daddy wait happy
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
look at those look at the balance
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's not terrible it works that much
[Laughter]
oh
finally getting some more characters
can we have to fight him or something
yeah
really player one fighting one which is
i think yeah oh you're not gonna get any
characters
like
attack at the same time three versus one
maybe there's more chances oh i think
it's only one versus one oh no
what is it loadings for so long no smash
but we're ready approach us
[Applause]
you can do it get [\h__\h] fun oh no [\h__\h]
a bunch
oh no oh that's nice
okay
[Music]
maybe he'll get hit by a car
but you can lock him up at the right
time
[Music]
yeah
look at that okay i'll get rid of the
times
[Music]
go get the yellow one it's got a blue
it's just like you're good
[Music]
donkey kong looks like he could be
voiced by the guy that does scuba diving
oh yeah oh plan for you
place the light magne i'm playing
you seem to have bleached your hair or
duncan you like it
you look like that
don't stop don't stop
[Applause]
[Music]
no okay that was me okay all right i
think it's rolling out are you down
step into our domain and see what
happens
oh god
kirby
ah
this is a penalty look at that
oh
[Music]
i'm going left though
okay we're good we're good
[Music]
wait was that our first photos
okay
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
hello
it looks like a music teacher
[Music]
oh
is powerful
weak weak
okay
[Music]
get the big hit in
yes
oh
[Music]
if i'm frozen on the screen it's cause
i'm very comfortable
yeah they said my my couch is like a
venus flytrap it is it's like once you
swim you can't get out
oh it's still it's still going
still going yeah a little bit
[Music]
all right go next random
i don't even know what the button
so we uh
still go with the same character
have you guys saw
been feeling like it's it's my choice to
control one character with two
controllers uh
they're getting used to once they figure
it out they'll be unstoppable
if you want no i don't want to play
spammers alone
what are we doing wrong it's not
starting
just give it a second oh then somebody
has surprised
us
how do you play an ice climber
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
where's the other one
well do you guys think it has like two
oh there's something going on from the
right side i don't like it
oh [\h__\h] we're gonna wait this out all
right
[Music]
[Applause]
ice
[Music]
[Applause]
yoga so please leave me alone you have
to jump
there we go
hey i just don't remember your morning
yoga are you sure you want to be here it
looks like there's an ice storm in the
forecast
what
[Music]
well not me
oh it has one life left and tiara's at
95 percent health so
why are we in eggplant yeah
i think it's lore related
[Music]
that's our ocean mark oh it's our cutie
mark
i can't hit you anymore uh oh okay
looks like caramel might win this one
too
thank you thank you
i think it's so good i love the music
[Music]
i think i've heard a banjo cover but
that does sound really good i just said
to you it's really nice
oh
[Music]
you guys can smash each other
we're crying with
because at first we were like okay the
loser will play chiari
see that i'm just i'm smashing buttons
without knowing what's going on
i am bad i don't have much experience on
smash
house you guys are better
no okay
they must be for you
because you won
silhouette
[Music]
from nintendo 64. yeah but i think it's
like an update
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
try your balance
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
show them your strength inna it's your
channel show them your cool side come on
a big butt oh my god
but
stay awesome i'm so good at pizza
wait what really i just clicked all the
things
[Music]
um
those brains
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
yeah oh wait i had to jump up no time
[Music]
very very very attached and bonding with
the pets of amer
yeah always there
[Music]
so much love
they're like besties now so yeah
though you know was paying so much
attention to bubba
bubba kept looking to kiara and i'm like
now go away
you're too close don't lick me please
hold on
talk to blah
sorry he kept online
yeah henry does like you henry didn't
like it
[Music]
this is how the winner is
is
[Music]
oh doing her okay oh wait am i here oh
you're you're
oh oh no i'll take care of that no no no
no no no
no no ah
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm safe here right nobody wants to kill
me i'm the cutest thing on earth you
can't stop me
[Music]
that was like a paintball
oh what
oh there's like a pinball thing okay
that is a really high peel
yeah i'm so good really cute
[Music]
[Laughter]
the one who's actually playing guys i'm
not the one who was just npc
he's just a cpu level
what do i eat oh my god it's just dead
inside come here
i'm calling peta this is terrible
i know
i'm hungry
[Music]
shout chad do you guys remember when
these three girls played super smash
brothers in a collab alone
would you say they improved or they got
worse
i think they have clear answers
you're all mine
what i thought you were going to protect
pikachu
oh look it looks like they look like
right now i look great
yes they got worse worse worse
[Laughter]
[Music]
don't patronize me guys
but thank you
but where's the headphone
[Music]
oh damn there's spiders there okay what
oh i just thought i noticed okay i'll
fix it
always like this oh it might have been
when you adjusted something
and what's happening
there it is
oh it was a little off so it took me a
while chad to see that
it's fun it's aesthetically pleasing
wait were you in the whole time
oh no i'm sorry you guys oh no
you got myself there
i'm wearing ammo's t-shirt right now
that's why she's covering me
very comfy
i'm gonna took my my free size today
not actually free size actually all
kinds of sizes
oh yeah
[Music]
we could be like cowboys wait no
oh you're approaching yeah
um
become one
i don't know you could hold the charge
oh no oh no
i'm a strong she unleashed her power
took part
[Music]
wow just your presence made but uh
freeze in time to this impressive
[Music]
bad pro controller which is kind of
broken i actually have to get up sorry
so it's a gamecube controller versus pro
controller now let's see
oh don't let them know that i had to
keep controlled
[Music]
to my defense i've never really used you
can fill it before i don't oh this is
[Music]
and there will be the answerers wait
there's
that tpu oh he's the distributor
what did you eat
can i say that amen what can i say what
we ate yeah and we ate like
thai food curry it was really yummy
how was your food girls it was yummy
it's yummy hungry
oh you guys want to know one thing
um we went to amma's place today yeah
and uh
we were getting our goodies packing
things
uh in the morning to bring thomas dad
and i brought some
and the pop-tarts but then
oh my gosh
i was supposed to carry the bag but what
happened with the bag inaudible isn't
that yours no
ah
thank you yeah remember remember
yeah i wanted pop tarts
wow
[Music]
it's good they're like that won't be
good for you anyway i would have killed
you it's for my bunker
[Music]
austria
um i'll get it to you eventually yeah
yeah peace peace we will get that better
i'll hold him and you beat him ready
wait i got him here
yeah
do you mean
[Music]
soft strong strong
probably stronger than me it's a little
bit of an iron grip i'm not gonna lie i
think one thing that was consistent in
all of my hugs for these girls was that
i always felt like
[Music]
some breakfast for us yeah
she made like such good iced tea like oh
yeah
i like the powder at the bottom
it tastes good
like candy
can i have more iced tea tomorrow
[Music]
perfect
like something i would be served in a
hotel
with the lemons
oh okay
[Music]
wait are we fighting each other
oh i was just beating up mine
bryce
[Music]
i can do that too i can
tonight we'll get a good sleep and then
ah oh my god he pulled me up
good
what's diamond doing
[Applause]
[Music]
wow finally we see the kirby winning
screen for the first time yes
they're both kirby
well
congratulations i guess
[Music]
we actually are reaching the one hour
mark yeah
it was going to be a very short one
because we were pretty tired from
running around everywhere we've been i
mean we have a busy day tomorrow too but
i think we have something planned for
you guys
we have a funny idea for tomorrow
i think tomorrow will be on amma's
channel guys yeah keep an eye out for
that
maybe around roughly
yeah i don't think you can say exactly i
will we'll see how it goes because um
gotta record some stuff yeah so please
be patient guys but we'll try
as soon as possible yeah we're still
going to have fun stuff so just wait be
patient
we can chat for a little bit yeah also i
just want to see like if there's like no
numbers down the line too that like
can't make it to the off collapse don't
always like go and ask like why they're
not there and yeah
it's really hard to get us in one place
like even online like a lot of classes
have like our own schedule yeah it's you
guys we just stream and you know we
release cool stuff every now and again
but we have like a you know internal
stuff that we gotta do uh-huh and yeah
but we're all trying to make it work and
just believe
oh yeah
we said callie kelly will be with us
soon at another day that's just not
right which will be finally the first
full myth essential exactly yeah
[Music]
but i have already at this point met
every single miss member yeah
oh achievement online
[Music]
ask now or be silent forever
i was stuck in the couch
company looks like a little muffin
does he sank behind one of them
[Music]
actually the other day
after the karaoke that good and i did
yeah that's actually i think that is how
i ask them
should we should we smell each other
like really nice like if you guys have
ever smelled like a nice fancy hairspray
oh dang it let's pay for those ponytails
you got to keep them in place give them
spiky oh it smells kind of like my
strong tails yeah emma you gotta smell
me when i'm not sweaty please oh
i'm right behind you i could just uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
also waking up ina was not a problem i
basically i woke up early before my own
alarm and then i waited until the right
time and i went over over to ina and i
was like
and i started moving her like shaking
her
yeah yeah i hit her on the knee i was
like
she went
[Music]
honestly one snooze is not bad
yeah
i was i was uh
planning for 10 but
but i noticed after the first notice
when i gave you the second kiki i
noticed you were still not really
planning to wake up you seemed very
tired so i stopped talking to you and
asking your questions
i didn't remember what i answered
i just started a conversation so that i
could engage you and wake you up
mentally
yeah that's smart very smart
because inna is the type of person who
sets many alarms she knows this a
million times
so me and gouda said no
you're not doing this
i can't sleep so she turned out
we became the alarms yeah
sinking into the couch becoming as couch
and couch and pal
yeah
you got the color coordination no i'm
basically i
any any other uh stories girls
i'll tell you later
hello
it's like you can't remember right now
but then later as you're sitting alone
reminiscing you remember like all those
small details of smells you know it
smells again
maybe it smells just like made in the
memory the long and that's true yeah
these people isn't it like if you smell
something walk like a memory yeah some
mountain therapy
then they're all there one thing i must
say is what was really impressive is
terrariums
yeah
they're kind of smaller than i thought
they would be they're like actually the
taco is bigger than i thought
it's it's like i don't know
like a glue stick oh yeah yeah
okay yeah
so cool such a nice hobby
thank you
inspiring oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
was just staring at me and i could just
literally see like flowers and sparkles
and she's staring at me
i'm i'm an i'm
[Music]
in the flesh we're actually real flesh
tubers
what else we have
yes everybody is i mean there was one
time we just literally
sang it to the couch for like an hour
yeah but including dogs yeah all the
family and henry yeah
everybody was like really really tired
um
are there they snore
many noises
they make a sound like
bone vibrating yeah
thank you
yeah i was like if someone's blooming
henry is so cute
pretty fat
he's squishy
i've seen flower cats like
on the little rounder side big feet yeah
big tail big
[Music]
he's very like sometimes
i will like notice him somewhere in the
room standing in the corner or somewhere
between some friends herself like
standing there menacingly
and look at him and then like [\h__\h] yeah
doesn't he always he kind of always
looks pissed off or like yeah yeah yeah
well like well like when um
like like when we first came your place
just like ran away and like actually
literally just like dug
a face into the corner of the room and
hit it yeah
he's really shy
yeah the other one
i only saw for like a moment and then
escaped
never to be seen ever again
are there other cats named what was
wellington wellington wellington it's
like beef wellington yeah
name choice
[Music]
oh he's like
relaxing getting some pets right now
he's in heaven
i'm tired
all right yeah we should probably wrap
it up for tonight you know wrap it up
yeah thanks everybody for coming to
watch the champlain on the water
[Laughter]
um
a lot more things fun things in
the days to come so please look forward
to it yeah
and uh i guess we'll see you guys next
time
please take care
have a wonderful wrestlemania evening
okay
bye
[Applause]
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
p
do