[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
wow Wowie
the first English collaboration
[Music]
wonderful I hear a lot of motivated
crewmates only crewmates of course
we'll talk about that
um
it doesn't matter if you hide behind
that little block there
and I see a green root vegetables
I just want to mention what happened
before the stream we had a little
testing session and uh we just wanted to
play the game seriously for once and
then uh after a little while we had no
reports which was kind of does sofana
doing an emergency meeting uh just to
you know because she was obviously
scared and which I was too
um
okay she's in an emergency meeting and
then what do we see free deaths
she's not thus because she made the
meeting but turns out she was the
Imposter how Reckless is that
not to mention she killed so many people
so easily yeah
imposter was so short yeah
hasn't started yet
oh no are you serious
ly
oh my God I'm surprised you even noticed
oh mermaid there's a color that's better
suited to you this color
oh wait while mume is forgetting to
stream
um my stream's in 720 apparently so be
right back
doesn't count
it never has counted people
[Music]
I
guess
honestly was wearing pants that'd be
more important you know I knew it
definitely not us so next up Bay new
introduction please
representing
up everybody
stop talking because we have to follow
in order to hear you
baby I'm sorry okay I'm not obsessed
because
um I got a cute pet
for real human dollars
I saw the hamster thing and I was like I
got it
is that your child are you a hamster
yeah
wait no what huh
um
wow that's kind of kind of weird
interesting right
[Music]
all right
um so yeah
um death is real sus but guess what
everyone I'm not death I'm the sheriff
and because I'm the sheriff the sheriff
has never sus the sheriff obviously
didn't do it
um some people may say I I Shot the
Sheriff but I did not shoot the deputy
meaning uh I don't know what that means
it just has something to do with the
sheriff and I'm not sure I'm not suspect
so there you go how can you be the real
[\h__\h] whatever you can't even spell
sheriff right okay now that was because
you know that was because there wasn't
enough room for for me to spell it
correctly all right
now listen I'm definitely I'm the
sheriff
who's next
no my name is fauna and I am simply a
potted plant
cannot kill
me
poison ivy no no no
we have the non-poisonous variety
poisoning you've already killed enough
people for today so your deed is done
before
no no no a plant has never killed anyone
Little Shop of Horrors does it remember
I remember that Musical
foreign
[Music]
uh
I am very excited I am 100 say so I
would never lie which is why I've never
recess
Iris yes no trust that's not what
happened to my fox yesterday
she killed my fox
say yeah a very very
um
self-introduction about a lot of people
just yeah
[Applause]
please give us your introduction
oh yes
hello my name is crony Oro from the
council and I am blue
and Japanese
um your Senpai has filled in your color
but I'm a more Royal color royal blue so
okay okay
don't look at the color objectively look
at the color that's inside all of us
it's pretty deep I know
she's right she's right
blue blood
uh wait did crony say why she's not us
oh right I'm not sus because look at
this I'm wearing a mask I am doing my uh
part in this situation don't get close
to me
is
well I tried to social distance but I'm
not says because I'm doing my part in
this society and
I'm an upholding member of gosh darned
gosh darn it Yeehaw my dude
I was talking
um
opening Lobby Lobby's created code is uh
there no sorry
[Music]
I got rudely interrupted oh man yeah yes
everyone's everyone you can hear
everyone
um we should have done intros here to be
honest
you know we had a problem with the
servers last time right like during the
test
because of our inactivity it's not a
server problem don't worry it's all good
I was really interrupted
do it it says could not find a room is
what it says lies
oh wait I mistyped
there you go sorry
all right
is it possible to fix the strain quality
in the middle of the stream or is it too
late even if I stop streaming
uh pain okay
okay
[Music]
um
two people
okay let's see
mermaid please introduction and why
you're not says
that was my turn
it's your turn yeah yeah okay okay okay
I am moving actually I am the guardian
of civilization and I am an apex
predator of the sky and I could kill you
if I wanted to
introduction ever yeah
but I don't want to so I won't okay I
believe that because you are so peaceful
um those berry bushes
I take it back I take it back um
I I might not no taxi back seats
oh hello I am Nino my Ian is from Hall
of English
um
the uh Priestess of the ancient ones
I think
and uh I think yeah sometimes I forget
but um oh I am not soft because I'm
already dead look at the the Halo above
my head
[Music]
that chorus of O's
that makes a lot of sense all right then
thank you Ina so Santa next up Santa is
not streaming but she's here so please
let us know
it's on the big
[Music]
English Council
uh it's been a while
hello
[Music]
I have a big limiter on my head yeah
that's a flamingos
it's a flamingo limiter anybody thinks
I'm a sauce I'm going to take it off and
take all of you down with me
it's really reassuring back into back
into the space where you belong
you should be fine you should be fine if
you get kicked out yes I have no reason
to
oh well I'm very happy to have you here
Sana thank you for participating we're
really glad to have you as part of this
even if you're not streaming free
yeah
and of course
um
[Music]
and uh I am the one organizing this and
I'm really happy that we could all get
together 11 people is a lot but we're
gonna have a lot of fun today so let's
get right into it are you girls ready to
be not just at all yeah
the more the merrier
the more that there are woohoo
yeah everyone yeah
oh hello hello
[Music]
oh my goodness why are you wearing
clothes oh yeah because I'm civilized
hey
I'm sorry
a tank tank in the Box
okay let's see
all right there's free lemonade here
get out
there's nothing it's a fancy water it is
fancy water I'm gonna die
but I have to do my tasks
now if sana's done then that means
okay not yet
wait they're already done
wait how do you know if they're done
there's a screen over here yeah there's
vitals right here
oh my goodness that was quick the
sheriff's already done
two other people end like in the same
spot
um
you guys are safe than I bet because it
must have been two people who killed
them because there's a cool down on it
yeah so us three are pretty safe right
now
okay that was chaotic
[Music]
um
with the lights on with multiple people
around what was that about Wow
[Music]
it looked like either Iris or Bae
a girl
it could be both Iris no it was right in
front of my face
no wait hold on I am black screened
again
yeah
no not again wait we just got started
tripping to a new Lobby I don't know if
it's gonna be any better though
I'll try fixing it but maybe I don't
know maybe reinstall among us or
something like that because you had that
before you can only can you read that if
you try that I can restart it yeah we
can restart but who should we kill off
before that
I was Irish
let's go to the meeting
right in front of me bet you're what I
thought we were Kiara
where did you spawn
where where I spawned yeah
in the middle thingy there a record okay
uh where did you spawn I spawned in the
in the I was by myself it was the room
with the folder on the table oh records
okay Iris where did you spawn
uh where did I find let me look at the
map real quick um being a detective hmm
I do not have not really played this map
um I think somewhere like in the main
hall
okay well me Santa and crony all spawned
in the cargo bay and we were all by
ourselves and we checked the vital
screen down there and Cali and two
people were already yeah they were
already fauna and Cali were already dead
so whoever spawned with them there were
two killers with them and they know I
was at the same time
I was alone I did not wait hold on a
second so do we skip vote for now
yeah
like in the beginning right we're
talking about the beginning right all
right
uh I appreciate it Watson really is a
detective
[Music]
of the Rat but wait what what do we do
now
the brain
oh it's so wizard hat nice
oh hey hi how are you
I'm trying to figure out what to do with
Ina
first session uh if she can either a
reinstall or try to try to find the
problem
oh we're shiny are you are you polishing
the diamond yeah
Ruby Ruby a giant Ruby
nice
when you see it do be pretty like that
whoa those are some big hands
good for hugging and for killing
someone you heard that then I'd probably
be uh killed instantly huh
I'm gonna do this card oh it's not a
card suede
really good with card swipes though
[Music]
okay that was quick
behind
[Music]
what
I really like
[Music]
okay well I mean I did it so
uh will this ever come back
I think I think I have to ride it back
oh
okay well
just
don't destroy everything oh my goodness
yeah yeah I mean we were here together
we're the safest
yeah photo room
[Music]
okay
dirty stinky
poopy
I'm sorry
oh oh it's okay uh I'm not gonna deal
with that
[Music]
oh you just open it like this
like that
um it's a it's a card sway mission
uh how do you
uh you have to uh go near the door and
then just click on the use button uh I
don't know if I'm even talking to myself
are you even around
so nice
uh oh right Lounge
yeah this is the lounge for sure
laughs
okay okay
see flawless
pretty sure someone's dead right about
now
how do I uh
uh how do I get there right
oh my goodness of course Murphy's Law at
its finest
who's dead who's dead
I'm not gonna go near Bay biggest really
suspicious
he had to run away before she uh
laughs
she comes near I'm gonna
I ain't afraid to push this button
um yeah
but I have absolutely
running around a while here and I I met
no one close by there was so I guess
someone vented yeah you were saying
what do you have to say about that no no
no no I was seen last in Bay
so who's done with our tasks right now
because I'm done
I'm not oh
yeah and with your tasks huh I can say
though well it says total test completed
but I think that's something that an
imposter can do like show that shall we
the delay that it's I think they can
fake that I don't know I've heard it
yesterday anyway I think crony can vouch
for me that I'm not obsessed right crony
what do you think
well I I know that Watson and Sana were
definitely safe because the killings
took place when uh all of us were still
around and the only people who are
considered suspicious to me would be
or Kiara
why
yeah yeah good grass definitely uh in
the clear because she was really happy
with the toilet mission
[Music]
then we'll just check
um yeah
I'm gonna check uh Bae first and see if
the uh the taskbar goes up when she does
the mission
the whole way like how Amelia is trying
to control this whole room makes it just
mean no no no no Watson's definitely in
the clear because I was with her uh with
Sana well I can't undo my vote now
that's kind of suspicious What if I
because I got stuck in the bathroom for
the entirety of the last round because I
got I didn't know how to open the door I
don't know who to vote for yeah I I
think girls are safe with your guts I
feel like if it wasn't based you'd I was
cleaning my guts out of the toilet I
couldn't see anything I thought it was
babe but maybe it's Kiara yeah
I'm sorry
[Music]
hmm
oh yeah oh you choose where you loaded
yeah probably shouldn't saying this
screen yeah
yes I'm gonna check I'm gonna look for
Bae and see if she uh if her taskbar
goes up
I probably should do that okay I'll I'll
just follow you around so that you won't
get killed
yeah yeah
so you just have to open the map and
just keep going there
hey
you guys okay great yeah
good
are you done with your tasks
um
okay well and where are you going
here
um
like yesterday everything was fine hello
I'm not sass okay
okay
they always walking around alone
both are pretty so it's not gonna lie go
this way oh you didn't hear that
[Music]
I need to go to the viewing day
hey
okay
[Laughter]
we're waiting for the router
somewhere that'll take us far far away
I'm pretty sure it's Kiara
I don't know is there a cooldown like
when you spawn in
I don't know but yeah yeah so usually
they do
so I'm going to the showers if I die uh
let's uh look at the camera the base all
alone in the engine room
cargo bay
I'm getting cargo bay
let's see is she doing the mission or is
she just lost that's pretty suspicious
is bae really doing tasks
I don't know
oh no where did everyone go
hello is anyone around
wait I probably shouldn't say that loud
maybe it's not
by the way
okay
where'd they go
Sharky Sharky
do you guys teleport why are you guys
moving so fast
wait seriously we're dead oh
yeah yeah
I wouldn't be surprised
I left her and I ran around because I'm
done with my tasks and I found goodness
yeah
if you have been with me I couldn't find
anyone I was trying to find a bunny
where have you been where have you been
just now
yes hold on let me look at the map where
was I
um
it's quick though so that Ina can come
back yeah immediately
uh voting Begins the game vote PR
literally no no no no no no no no no no
no no no I mean I was I was checking um
Bay in the surveillance camera and she
wasn't really doing her tasks she was
just walking around around the
I mean were you doing tasks yes yes what
were you doing what was the last task
you did
[Music]
was the exact mission
emptying the trash in Maine Hall
haha
Kiara what's your Kiara what's your last
mission
Kiara what was your last mission Carol
was your last mission
with the the code where you have to
enter like
that is at the uh
[Music]
um
I think it's between storage and like
developing room the question question
room
I know for a fact I had just seen Kiara
like right next to me uh we were
together by the doors that open and
close and then an electric somebody but
yeah oh yeah Kiara was the one who
reported the body too right
this is my second body I'm reporting yes
self report
all right
you won't regret it no no no no no no
seriously
Bye Bye Baby
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh all right oh my God it happened in a
long time
under
[Laughter]
um
it's green though I don't know if it's I
don't know Iris did kill me [\h__\h] it's
just baby
because it was I I said bait in the room
and it looks like Iris
yeah
no but you were doing really good
I'm just like what
as we were a team I mean it is a
self-fulfilling prophecy I was so size
[Music]
and I'm gonna try to open one new Lobby
yeah okay okay
[Music]
oh
oh right I forgot that the chat is
connected man
pain
how do I
uh I can do this
hello hello
okay good good good good good
we are here in space
out here in space
okay yeah there's a code
it's a code Konami
okay now
let's keep on pressing your Senpai huh
why would you put the blame on me
say it first and I always think whoever
says it first is suspicious uh
understandable
quiet like we try
to smell before lost into the room all
right so who did it
hi hi everyone's just like uh you
you did it
oh I think it's you it's like oh no wait
I think it's you reverse side all right
which one of you suckers is the Imposter
um probably you Cali it's probably you
know
Ellie is Kelly looking under each other
already
[Music]
oh oh I'm just uh you're welcome vibing
in the corner okay
you come around here often
I do now
oh okay
uh nice egg
no this is Cool Kids Corner go away I'm
kidding
[Laughter]
so cool sorry about the fox by the way
yesterday yeah it's okay I mean
apologize to the fox oh wait you can't
yeah it was kind of Heartless she pushed
the fox down the hole
[Music]
yeah
what if it was your child that you
pushed down the hole huh oh the divorces
are duking it out it was an adoption and
you know it doesn't matter anymore right
because you know isn't getting in I'm
gonna we're gonna reopen the lobby one
more time
okay Kiara said no I'm not gonna deal
with this
she made it in last time though wait why
is everyone leaving what's happening I'm
scared
oh okay
man that's why I don't want to be
involved in love affairs seems like
so much drama
I adopted the I adopted the fox and how
dare you adopt that fox that fox
you know what you could have been blah
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
[Music]
oh okay
we're moving the chat to here
it doesn't work it looks full movie
we'll make that in wait let me try
but we can we can let in a try about
this no problem
this is the curse the en curse the en
law
yeah oh yeah the Ian law now can you try
making a Lobby
oh yeah okay yeah yeah you might get the
same
though because I got the same error uh
when I tried to creating the lobby
before the stream many times just try
again again again
I mean Angels do get nerfed in this game
the more evil you are the better
connection you have
oh wait my ping is fifth oh
that's why that's why my opinion is not
that not that good it's because I'm half
angel guys
the angel side of me is nerfing me in
this game
oh and the screen when typing code
that's right yes
[Music]
yeah maybe maybe we can try I I don't
really think it's closer but let's try
maybe an Asian server
we can we can try do you want to try it
you know or should maybe someone else
you guys can try someone else can try
making it okay I'll make one eight in
Asia everyone
[Music]
okay
cold is
[Music]
the code is code
the code is code the code is code okay o
d e and at the end is always an F okay I
got it okay
[Music]
it worked
did you get in first try yeah
um though yeah and the black screen
again just just go on without me it's
fine no no yeah
[Music]
doesn't work for me
what
Rihanna
yeah I was stretching sorry
I understand
yeah I've forgotten to change the region
yeah but this is a full Eon collab and
it would not be phone without you around
[Music]
oh yeah
it's fun
come on come on I'm leaving us
so how quick is the sheriff gonna die
though hey
this is [\h__\h] loud
thank you for letting me show you my
real powers
okay
oh burger then find the secret formula
uh it's a Patty that sounds disgusting
these fresh even
wow that's a disgusting Burger I mean I
guess we have some cheese maybe it's
fine I don't know where's the sauce
okay that's good
huh
I'll settle with good good is not bad
oh hello
hey don't don't kill me okay
can I do can I make lunch
[Music]
I just said
holy [\h__\h] oh no I can say about that the
only thing I can say about that is that
I heard Cali's voice close by for a
moment but that was like I didn't even
see her close by I only found the body
like a few moments later
bottom right it's uh because Cali was I
was going down to their bottom oh I was
bottom left
the bottom area but I wasn't I wasn't
doing anything I was like looking for a
pass to do well why were you not doing
tasks I don't think you're done with
tasks we just got started there's a lot
of tasks I doubt it it's a bit okay
[Music]
to me and I was in the Armory which was
on the bottom so it's the sheriff
and very funny
I see
[Music]
Charlie
well apparently
don't don't give her the benefit of the
doubt
that you did you weren't doing any tasks
you gotta play the [\h__\h] game
[Laughter]
if you really don't know how to play the
game I will give you a tip now a serious
tip a press tab to open the map so you
can run around while seeing the tasks
and that makes a very easy tap tab okay
I was like I was like looking back and
forth between the map get him get him
yeah let's go I don't
know
yourself that's right turn yourself in
Sheriff
this collaboration again
interesting oh you guys are too nice
enough to throw me out
no it's not
[Laughter]
what it says for now
ah yes the kitchen the place where I
died
okay so oh hi
friendly
no no
can't wait to see you die oh wow oh hey
oh well he's gonna find out she already
knows I missed the opportunity
[Music]
We Know What You Did you know yeah how
is it to kill the time Duo
you know this oh oh I see I see nice
nice
pretending to do your task and
sabotaging that's clever
are you like that angel where do I go
oh God
[Music]
okay I gotta do my tasks
okay
[Music]
and then refund is probably not gonna
die yet
very soon
okay who's gonna die
I haven't seen anything uh there will be
one soon there will be one soon
did you finish your tests no no
what
oh that's a weird task
a dead body
[Music]
the bathroom
just kill her
just do it already yeah oh there it is
yeah
oh my God yeah no that's what we all
thought
s
[Music]
which one of you just closed the toilet
door
why is she so into the toilet
paper
I was not anywhere can you hear that
because
um
because when I found Iris body right
here
the bathroom door closed
someone someone hid in the bathroom spot
you can do that
what a surprise I don't know I'm just
lost
acting like an innocence
objectively look there's meat and
there's no sheriff
and my ping is terrible so obviously I
would be in the clear you have to listen
to nothing
I bet that if you check their pings
right now it's probably low
which means they're imposters
crony's ping law but I didn't go up I
came from the other side
I don't know
and if my theory is right
the pings are low
consider me a genius which of course I
am
at one point lost
[Music]
they are going to win this they just
need uh one two three four five six
seven eight so they just need to kill
two more and
yeah
get get out get out get out get out
okay
Ira sounds mad
why are you mad just don't be mad
too late to get mad I mean that's a
that's a mortal thing to do you're dead
now
course
why is she panicking so much
oh because she's mortal
when you're dead
everything is okay it's calm and I
finish my tasks
now I'm just gonna have some popcorn she
goes hey you know hello
the Lost
Who you gonna kill who are you gonna
kill
me oh my mommy is gonna die
so what is Ina why did you just kill
mume invent come on nobody knows this
map
do we look at this thing
I thought something sus I see um
right area
before the wreck stop back seating how
do I backseat I'm dead
area I saw Cali so I wanted to say hi so
I followed her and next moment she's
completely disappeared I went I went
into all other like like
ways to look for her but she disappeared
and there was a vent right where she
disappeared so but until you walked out
of the room man you can vouch for me I
went down to the bottom and tried to go
through the bed and I couldn't
oh
yeah
stop stop stop it's so chaotic let me
talk let me talk let me talk let me
speak let me speak okay what I mean is
there was a vent down there and I
couldn't get through it because I'm not
the [\h__\h] imposter that's what I meant
oh man went down to the bottom I was
trying to go to the crying I was trying
to go right now
for me she just wants she just wants me
to get thrown out
right now
why else would you call this the [\h__\h]
suspicious emergency meeting Kiara
this is intense yeah
[Music]
and it's flawless
I mean she's a sheriff
I'm just saying you were sussing me last
time but it wasn't me either there's
somebody in the Box I am
I'm the boss
tank in the Box
tank in a box
thank God cheese
in the Box
oh you heard that please
in a box
no no nothing nothing that was all I
said something that you don't
[Laughter]
know yeah
what's I'm curious of the continuation
of this uh it was I was just saying
tenkodachis
was saying oh there's someone in the Box
looks like yeah tenkodachis and the
daddy right here
nice one no no no no no no no no no no
uh why why did you hear that
yeah okay yeah yeah I'm surprised people
are not voting her off she was stressed
from the beginning
she's a sheriff supposed to be the icon
I'll get the hang of it
you have a good hang of it
foreign
yeah it's so good that you should
probably give up that title of yours
[Music]
found her in the kitchen
which I normally what the [\h__\h]
me
I reported the body holy [\h__\h]
you're just you're just being like I
don't know clumsy I think in the kitchen
unintentional murder
yes I am the killer but I did not kill
that person
together
um yeah
yeah they're fine they're all fine
which kind of leaves them
trying to look like
we haven't
lost it yet because all of these are the
bodies that we found yeah just need to
kill three more okay right well I don't
like you pointing the finger at me babe
and I think that's suspicious so I'm
gonna point it right back at you
boy I'm just trying to be a good [\h__\h]
you're tearing this family apart
murderer Sheriff
I'm loving this
beautiful yes
what are you guys been doing yeah
right now yeah and I've been laughing at
Cali
for me when I when I like literally why
would I could have killed you if you
guys were alone if I did [\h__\h] nothing
anyone looks pretty convincing for
anyone peace
[Music]
I'm gonna regret this
the sheriff
but at this point everyone had something
about someone vouching for them except
Kelly it's really good
oh it's
red light green no that's not green
you know some people call Blue Green I
don't know why I'm scared
oh you're such a liar
how do you get there let's all walk
together
um
[Music]
I'm sorry I'm sorry you have a Halo but
I think I deserve it
um
social distancing but nobody's wearing a
mask
yes
[Music]
they're calling for social distancing
and no mask
absolutely disappointing
see I'm even wearing a mask when I'm
done
[Music]
I am
far from chaos
I know you can't say anything now
because others are around you but you
know I'm disappointed in you very
disappointed right now
we got it
we've been here awful everyone's
gathered
I shot my past
um
nothing wrong what button Nina what
buttons
[Music]
and I had one request and that was don't
kill me don't kill me okay
those are my last words
you even said okay
I might regret this
I might regret this yes you will regret
regret this yes you will everyone's
going here great just kidding hold on
those are guns
yeah oh Katana oh
yeah there's a lot of weapons oh Hammer
Hammer Time
oh
I forgot what this was called
hmm oh laser gun oh
I saw a Halo weapon somewhere
where was the Halo weapon oh wait
where'd everyone go
that sounds like mummy
oh hey
hey we're all in the shower nice
wow they didn't turn off this stall
properly that's a waste of water
oh true what do you have to say about
this fauna
engineer
's plumber
I didn't water my Sprouts
your spouts are in the washer
it wasn't me
real sauce I understand
kept saying that she was lost and I
thought that it was
suspicious
what was the last house that you did the
last one I did was the one where I had a
dress
[Music]
card fashion designer
doesn't get voted out I'm going with my
gut feeling I'm gonna go oh my God your
gut feeling used to gut someone I see
everyone votes for each other one's in
really quiet hasn't she you've been
really quiet too you know
I don't know
no oh no oh no
only has four fingers that's crazy
where we're going
well we're done
GG
no no it's too late it's too late
[Music]
are you freaking out you just need to
kill one more person why are you
freaking out just one more person Nina
just don't wait this is your first just
end it
be careful babe don't get close
foreign
[Music]
hey yeah so I have a question so when
you're imposter and you're like going
pretending to do tasks Etc can others
tell if there isn't really a task there
to do
uh no you know what but like if you're
doing a certain like if you're asking to
do tasks that should be probably longer
because there's really long time they
kind of can't stand out that you're oh
I've done so quickly
is someone
um
[Music]
okay
so we out here in space
oh that's the sheriff flying around
where's mine why am I not in space Oh
I'm here
I'm the host of course
what an unsurprising coincidence
of course I'm the main focus
you were able to hide your imposterness
for so long
um
I
waited for my chance
patient extremely believable
yeah I was asking Ina not to kill me
not I asked you not to kill me and you
said Okay that was those were my last
words
[Laughter]
are you sure okay okay
let's go let's do this all right let's
go
I'm recently no Victory Royale
yeah that's fine
oh I wish I was an imposter for once I
wish I was too I wish
you weren't imposter before oh boy I
wish I was an imposter oh boy oh boy
oh no no I didn't
what about you
I was when I kill you unless someone
cool down yeah
my cooldown's over
and you know for me
[Music]
good
excuse me I have a question was the
shark near the washroom no questions at
this time
then you were
suspic and then I saw Guru was also in
the room that Kiara went that was cool
right I don't know that doesn't mean it
wasn't Inna I watched it for me she was
right behind it no you was right behind
me you were by yourself in electrical
because I was humming no no no no I was
humming the berries and cream tune and I
was like I know where electrical it is
killed me last time
sure but did you ever stop by the
washroom
yeah
in place with the folder on the table
and I went right down to electrical I
don't remember how so you never stopped
by the washroom that's pretty sized
every time you were innocent you would
do something in the washer
[Music]
she's gone from meek and shy to very
suddenly very demanding of the room's
attention
[Music]
I have nothing to say about any of this
no no it's kind of suspicious
[Music]
yes please I would love to have fun so
she could kill them foreign
but
um
I remember I need a makeup Burger look
at those photographs
oh
yeah oh yeah oh I need to take a shower
oh my stinky I already said this
oh yeah yeah rub that soap oh yeah
hello
[Music]
everyone's too close to each other I
don't like that
I because I just didn't because
oh now she's iris is starting to get
obsessive with the
I don't know like a good relationship
well then I'm gonna have you
I'm doing my tests too
all
right oh oh it is gosh darn it yeah
unless she's on cooldown
I'm on cooldown because I took a shower
hi
don't kill me I'm trying to look for the
Wi-Fi signal
yeah
oh yeah at least if I die I have the
Wi-Fi signal that's something
nope nothing is happening
I feel like iris is in the clear because
don't kill me uh I won't don't worry I'm
just cleaning the vents
onion lettuce and make the perfect
Krabby Patty
there are no buns on this
what meat tomato lettuce
meat tomato lettuce
this is the worst Burger I've seen
that's not even a burger is that a
lettuce Burger I'm so confused oh hello
good I am not going to kill either of
you keep an eye out well yeah I mean
it's just two against one you can't kill
I'm using it uh we should probably turn
that off
[Music]
I feel like girls trying to kill me
you're lucky I'm here
what
[Music]
I don't know go away shark go away you
really don't want me to do that
[Music]
no trust me okay okay did someone
I don't trust either of you no no stop
following me stop following me
I don't trust you
I'll trust any of you
I'm gonna I can't click
foreign
not been inside for a while oh no why
are you following me stop it I told you
to stop following me
it's it's
great
girl has been trying to find the right
opportunity to she's been acting kind of
sucks
yeah I kept telling her not to follow me
and she just could say crony crony
no I was trying to I was trying to keep
an eye on you just in case you know I go
for that kill yeah she was saying she
was trying to frame Inna okay is it okay
that Ina keeps watching you for
protection but it's not okay if I do
that I don't know when on the very first
round when I reported when I reported
Ina absolutely flipped her story and
went from the super Meek I don't know
where I'm going to suddenly super loud I
don't know as if she's trying to protect
herself to be honest I don't trust
either of you so okay that's fair
what both y'all were a little suspicious
okay okay
is that you're suspicious of both of us
and not one versus the other day yeah
and I'll have to talk just now
I was waiting for my cool down yeah two
imposters
but the reason why I've been suspicious
about girl was because I kept bumping
into her every time uh it was just three
of us in total so if one person uh left
it would just be two of us and I kept
having that situation
because you were being left alone with
Ina and I don't even know and I wanted
somebody to be
my watch
okay we can try going together then
are we skipping for now there's still
enough people so I don't know
put my vote on gura I don't really have
a reason so I don't know both the Ina
and crony were like please be mindful of
Ena
[Music]
we're really trying to put it on her my
man
there's still enough people so
let's not be too hasty
hello
I'm innocent too I mean I know that you
were talking about the whole cool down
thing but I trust you
yeah I'm cool down right now actually
okay why are you saying
what if I'm on cooldown huh
yeah that's right
together showered together right oh yeah
that's true yeah you're good
[Laughter]
I mean we took a shower last time so
it's fine
they would have killed you know how do
you do this one again
seven
yeah
me if I wasn't with
if I wasn't
yeah I think she's safe
why what happened no she's right here
sorry
there's a lot of people right divert
electrical power
right I have two more tasks I have to do
if you'll excuse me I probably shouldn't
have said that around someone who could
be
hey
hey what's up please tell me yeah no I
trust you I think I'm one of the few
people who trusts you so don't kill me
I'm a good scapegoat you ah you didn't
trust me last time no no I trust no no I
I trusted you last round too this time I
trust you yeah uh why the side and try
and Trust all I mean okay because I've
been listening yeah thank you I
appreciate you listening to me
please don't kill me yeah yeah no don't
worry I got you
he's not killing me
[Music]
okay
unless you and Ian are working together
okay I couldn't really exactly gauge
that
that's okay uh what else do you need to
do I just need to do two more tasks and
that's about it
[Music]
oh no
sorry I cannot find report I cannot find
the report
I just want to say something quick that
girl is in the clear have been uh
following her around and yeah
[Music]
and I saw her doing the karting and
yeah it seems like she's in the clear so
does that means
so I'm pretty sure she's in the clear
too
yeah Sana is also in the clear we saw
each other and didn't kill each other so
okay as well so girl what makes you
think that it's Ina though
did you see her doing the killing I mean
I've ran into so many people I have so
many chances
no it's not let me answer the question
thank you the microphone is in my hand
uh because at the very beginning of the
match I was singing the berries and
cream song and I went into electrical
and right then and there Ena beheaded
that person
[Music]
yeah yeah Iris isn't in the clear if it
turns out that it's not Ina
I don't know I still I mean we can't
really tell who the Imposter is
following girl
he wasn't with like nearby Guru though
oh um so that was when the lights were
turned out and I saw Cali freaking out
when girl was nearby
I have no reason to make enemies found
the body yeah
where'd you find it yeah where the
mannequins are
oh Watson why would you there why was
she alive so easily I mean
you're pointing a lot of stickers
[Music]
says that she saw someone behind
that Tina didn't accuse her of killing
you just said she was more suspicious
is my mind cutting out yeah
pictures
I'll be quiet this time
[Music]
okay am I alone
Okay the reason why I don't think it's
Gara is because uh
if she was guilty she would not be she
would not sound so salty right now
so that's why I'm just going to give her
the benefit of the doubt because I know
how it feels to be accused constantly
foreign
ER hey Iris and Anna just went into a
room together and only Anna came out oh
okay we should okay uh is there a Vital
sign we can check
yeah there she is
already you just killed
I watched you oh oh how convenient wow
gosh every freaking time I'm about to do
a freaking task yeah so it is
I was watching the security cameras and
Ina and Iris Iris leading Ina behind
went into the room to the left of the
engine room and then only Ina came out
and then crony came in and I said hi
crony and then Nina came in and I said
oh crony I'm gonna go see that body that
Ina just left in there and lo and behold
there was the body of Iris oh well
that's a very convincing you know what
it was saying
taco
[Laughter]
wow girl I'm sorry I doubted you holy
[\h__\h] I feel bad I mean I never I never
voted against you
I'll be honest I thought I was going to
um
not last the very first trial but I
turned it around and I think that was
good enough for this round
I lost it this long the other imposter
huh and why is it Amelia Watson no it's
not farewell
[Music]
sarabada hmm why did somebody stay with
me next round you'll see
oh God
[Music]
four fingers
what last time I was in the kitchen I
died so
don't want to do that again
and then after I'm done I should
probably start checking the others
because I'm done
this one I can do this one oh hey
hey are you done with your tasks no I
was so busy trying to prove my innocence
oh
okay well I'm done with my tasks so I
can uh cover for you
oh okay
see you on the other side
body over here
hmm
interesting
oh wait I got sidetracked
one
clean swipe
you're welcome everyone
awfully quiet in here
where's the room where you can check the
vitals oh we're almost done with the
tasks anyway
uh I forgot where the vital oh Medical
[Music]
okay
dead
[Music]
nice
oh man
and GG
I'm not very good
it's okay we tried
I was moving I was in I got distracted
all the ghosts were singing along
[Laughter]
there's a time limits
good job
so it would have been difficult to find
out its movement unless we would have
done all the tasks so good job
I was really stuck for moving with good
adult because
[Laughter]
um
not gonna lie you were acting pretty
suspicious girl
oh you're not helping
it was like so
so strong against the very first round I
was like that's kind of stuff
you know right yeah we can't even
avena's crew I'm just like maybe we
should just vote for her
[Music]
toys
does everyone have imposters here Dead
uh checked because it didn't work last
round
I'm I'm more curious about the private
talk events is that working because I've
never like I mean oh that's disabled
yeah but only the host can change it
yeah
um
time flies
idle meeting idle meeting
[Music]
no
do do
it
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
we're done we're done seeing it what
happened
[Music]
Amazing Grace
[Applause]
[Music]
hello it's shadow
whoa what is happening
oh she's back okay
[Laughter]
it's definitely me all right cool cool
cool all right all right
where we land the next boys
nowhere I see have a nice day oh hello
Ina by association is now sus
I'm cleansing my sins
yeah once once okay it was my members
but now
um I never am the Imposter and collab
oh no I wish I was an imposter for once
and I'm definitely not on cooldown
oh no
boy
would be weird if someone died when
there's Delight out
and then oh boy I'd hate to kill someone
in the washroom right about now in five
seconds
five four three two one they're spared
[Music]
okay well I can't oh
okay I can't make that
[Music]
what I I did that
was weird okay
is that just the elevator thing back
oh yeah
my Yahoo
I love my job
until I get killed that would actually
suck
and that's the last of them
it's a really good spot to kill someone
right about now oh boy is anyone passing
oh
foreign
that's that's gotta count for something
thick what
even when you're dead you need a good
Wi-Fi signal
[Music]
oh you're singing too nice
vegetables the cards to open the door
I can't I can't oh this is the the card
does she look yeah I can't open the door
oh my goodness
Iris you're uh you're a good killer and
you can't even open doors
[Music]
you're right if the house doesn't have
good Wi-Fi I just won't be a haunted
house that's why you have data
no the cards
to point some fingers
[Music]
to the middle of a room
and they went together
why are we typing
forward
no I was still in ghost mode
[Music]
oh yeah I mean yeah I guess we can't
really have a conversation when it's
this chaotic huh nothing to base my
conjecture on yeah yeah typing is okay
[Music]
she's talking to you right now huh
no no oh yeah
[Music]
why would Watson out her own teammates
yeah I think I'm gonna skip it okay yeah
three out of five council members have
been killed
I feel like
because of that
it might be Iris away it is Iris
my my investigation skills are fired
today oh
[Music]
oh this is the worst one this has to be
oh yeah that was kind of the worst one
and if FaZe killed right at this moment
then yeah yep yep you see this you see
this there's something about
she has something against the council
[Music]
this is convenient and then now it'll be
the myth myth is next
my detective skills are off the charts
today
I found Ray in the shower
that's a nasty place for a rat to die oh
no yeah
we were alone and she could have killed
me but she just went off and did her
tests kindly howdy and I went on my way
couldn't have been Kiara but I think it
was the other imposter who might I
didn't even see here
[Music]
I was trying to get to the whatever it
was sabotaged I forgot what it was crash
course or whatever I was in records but
I didn't say anything it was records
you're right Council yeah it's only the
council that's oh my my ears that was so
loud
the rounder I don't know if those
records it might have been the room next
to it
is not a good answer
I mean I kind of sound like coming but
that's okay
I thought it was records it might not be
records if you didn't see me but I'm
pretty I thought it was records it's
like come on guys her name is Iris so
size she's been imposter how many times
now
this is her third time for a second
to self-fulfilling prophecy guys thanks
guys thanks
huh I don't even know where the showers
are late I don't know no it's the second
time you haven't heard a lot from mume
or Ina yeah isn't it well I was all the
way okay I spawned in kitchen with
roommate and then I went to do my task
in the uh the bottom left thing let's go
it's called Uh so our suspects are Iris
and Kiara got it
I don't know usually you should have
Carol would be like the ducting and like
doing stuff but
gooda can vote for me right but Iris I
mean you didn't kill me if I had a penny
for every time Iris was an imposter I
would have two cents but still and one
strength that's pretty sunny
I wasn't very convinced by Iris I was
not convinced
I don't know
Amy's giving me a funny vibe either I
mean
I love you so much
[Music]
and she's gonna kill you yeah
oh hey look at your hamster forever lost
without an owner some day last time I
didn't kill her last time that sun
didn't kill her this time
what's his name
pet
I see oh
you've been hanging out with me too much
that's sad
and you're gonna be next
why are you there
okay cargo
I really don't know who it could be ten
seconds before death
oh no no never mind hello
timeline has changed for now
the room if anyone
[Applause]
there we go
timeline has not changed it seems how
could she forget what room she was in
even I couldn't forget
oh boy
thank you Ina why are you thanking Ena
why were you thanking enough
how are you thank you
don't you think hey
[Music]
don't you think that sounds about right
it's interesting
it's all just canceled you need to hear
me out what what do you think this
entails right elbow deep in the toilet
um
[Music]
okay guys bye bye oh she's mentioning
toilet again she grows in the clear
um and Iris and Kiara and I left and I
saw Cali irises
it was literally me
I don't know I'm trying to think
[Music]
there's something both of them
I'm confused
I just voted for Ina though guys so if
you want to I think it's gonna make sure
yeah definitely both of them but we
gotta be strategic about who we voted
Universe brain
I'm not sure they both killed me
what cheese three times in a row wow
really nice
[Music]
right oh my God maybe her game is bugged
emergency meeting
I mean yes do it what did I say about
the law of ping
[Music]
I have a high paying right now so
obviously I'm in the clear
just the pink posters
[Music]
from happening so
and this Theory
this hypothesis
will be in the clear what's what's iris
is paying Right Now can anyone check
iris's ping
I think Eno's paying is relatively lower
[Music]
is the Ping law cronies ping law the
Ping posters are at it again
[Music]
you're dead you're dead you're dead
[Applause]
oh that was a clutch
[Music]
words
that was pretty funny though
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh God
well you know what
um regardless of where you fly after
this I hope you learned your lesson
you can get to not to not kill people
that's my job
he's like
such a good I'll be a good girl you
could be a good citizen the rest of the
games the game's almost gonna end
what you are worth a warnings
[Music]
Iris do you want to talk about it
wow
[Music]
see my theories have been really
accurate so far about the ping and the
and the washroom and gray
[Music]
is this
at least we won yay
[Music]
if only I didn't say that
oh my God Discord yeah
I couldn't okay
what
are going to Discord yeah we're gonna
use this this board
these cords
hello
[Music]
my theory throughout this game has been
so good
and cowboy cheating good fun
yeah
that was fun yeah
[Music]
yeah sorry you're the best
thank you because she was in foster
three times yeah you know it kind of
just like it kind of gets questionable
when you get it three times people don't
even want to trust me
as the game's going along yeah
yeah three times in a row wow
that's fine it keeps getting imposter to
like the same people yeah I was really
surprised that like you would assume
that you would assume that the reaper
would be like the number one killer of
everyone but I'm actually just the task
master
yeah exactly well see that's the thing
is death can't die so the prospect of
death dying becomes a thing it's quite
frightening
super scary
um I think we got a lot of really golden
moments out of this stream I'm looking
forward to all the clips to see the
other point of views
everyone's point of views yeah yeah
I'm sorry
I thought you couldn't hear me now yeah
I was like I was like okay if we get a
double kill like like this is good but I
couldn't say anything so I was just
chilling you around yeah
you were on cool down or not so no no
that's why like I I thought we were
going to do a double kill too that's why
I was like around and then I killed
someone and then I see you went
somewhere is like oh no no the double
kill and then I think yeah because all
right
so yeah
we would have won
wow
yeah do you want to talk about it Iris
that's something you want to talk about
coincidence but you know at the same
time like you know sometimes I I can't I
can't go and kill my senpas right away
I like that I like that way of life a
good good one well okay girls I'm gonna
go through everyone from top to bottom
again to give a good buy one by one and
maybe tell me your favorite moment from
today or your favorite kill or whatever
so let's start with Amelia Watson oh uh
wait what are we doing oh goodbye and
goodbye your favorite Kill from today
okay uh thank you guys for watching and
thank you Kiara for setting it up again
and organizing everything and my
favorite moment uh I really like messing
with Cali that was fun yeah that was
pretty funny I gotta admit
no she would just outright say things
like like I'd be like are you gonna kill
me she'd be like yeah you're lucky my
cooldown is off and like run away
that's another one for their archives
for me okay well thank you Amelia next
to bales
[Music]
um
welcome actually in game oh it was when
I went to the idol meeting and uh
chaos
we're adding music to your idol meeting
yeah
yeah without chaos to manage chaos it's
chaotic
it's even more chaotic when chaos is not
there that's that's the sad thing
what what
oh I'm not wait I I don't need to wait
right I mean you can well and yeah right
here okay everybody really guys
[Music]
now let's dial a bag just a little bit
give me your goodbye
me oh let's see my favorite moment has
to be um when I was trying to hold up
the the cell phone to get the cell
service on the deck where anyone could
have killed me and I saw Sana come up
behind me oh and I was like holy [\h__\h]
this is where I die
hey Callie and she just walked away and
she's like no I have to do my task here
and I was like okay so we just switched
spaces and be like washed out for each
other it was kind of cool it's a bonding
moment I was like oh yeah
oh really I thought that was so cute
all day today
I'm just excited to explore yeah yeah
yeah it was really fun well thank you
next up fauna
hello thank you everyone for watching
and thank you Kiara for organizing
everything it was a lot of work and I
really appreciate it
my favorite moment was not being the
Imposter oh
I don't know I think I prefer natural
Indian posture too yeah
um being imposter is just so much
pressure
and especially you can't really say
anything because
I said whatever I wanted
I wanted to get into that situation
unfortunately it didn't happen today so
yeah well thank you fun I'm glad you
enjoyed it next up
how salty are you I'm fine I'm saying
I'm talking to my Channel about like how
I don't usually I don't know have
conversations I don't talk like this
usually like accusatory whether it's in
a game or not so like it feels very
draining uh mentally I guess yeah
I don't like yelling at my friends
I don't know it's just a game I'm not
salty at all I had a lot of fun
um my favorite moments were uh and I I'm
asking clippers please uh the various
perfectly cut screams with the proximity
chat Valley specifically won that one
round where everybody was terrified of
me and every time somebody would walk by
me it would just be blood curdling
screen
but I'd like to see a perfectly cut
screens uh compilation of some sort if
there are enough
you had a good one too for putting us
together thank you
thank you my pleasure my pleasure I was
very terrified
oh okay yeah thank you so much for
organizing this wonderful Club here I
love among us to bits me too I'm so glad
I was able to do this and I I would go
for Among Us like off stream anytime if
we had enough people oh yeah I like it
yeah but that was a lot of fun and being
imposter was great pressure but great
and my favorite moments have to be yeah
killing a lot of people that was fun um
well personally for a moment that really
didn't have much to do with me
um I really liked how Cali you know when
she found Fonda's buddies like it was
pretty boys
thank you
she was totally you
[Music]
and I need to be careful with how I say
words sometimes
yeah that was my personal favorite plan
all the time all the time yeah
probably I'm probably gonna have to be
aggressive
and killing yeah
aggression is the way to go but I was
trying to clear my name and that was how
I got out trying too hard to clear my
name
and I was yelling in her ear the whole
time yeah Amelia just laughing a ghost
in my ear
oh
sorry
um
what was I was I gonna say oh yeah thank
you so much no no no thank you so much
for arranging this
[Music]
yeah we don't need it the free bgm
you're right
um thank you so much to Kiara uh for
arranging this I really love this game
and it's been fun I think my favorite
moment was
uh well every moment was pretty funny
but whatever the
the proximity trying to explode it
whenever a meeting happened
with bunch of streams
and the the first time when the meeting
happened everybody was screaming and I
didn't even know what was going on but
that was funny so thank you for that
I lost my phone thank you cronie
hello thank you Kiara for organizing
everything everyone says that well you
were doing
yeah
I'm blushing thank you please continue
uh I think one of my favorite parts that
I experienced was I spawned very Ina
we're with Ina and I turned and I said
wouldn't it be something if you're the
Imposter three times in a row and she's
like yeah that really would be she just
wants
laughs
funny I was like yeah they're really
funny wouldn't it
it's absolutely drenched in sweat
you know there's so much blood on her
hands today yeah
many in the last two games I
remember very good at innocent
who was your favorite kill Maybe
oh I felt the best putting a knife
through their stomach
well
um it's gonna be half
a lot of good kills but I have to go
with the
uh crony in the first game or something
where she was like please don't kill me
and I was like okay
you could just say sure you could have
just said sure but it's like okay easy
[Laughter]
she knows
it would be very scary and intimidating
though because Cali goes every time we
die when Cali like she was like so
intimidating to me I was so scared he
was yelling at me I'm sorry oh it's you
huh
no it's you no you're reverse
okay Santa give us your your goodbye and
your favorite moment please
okay thank you very much for organizing
the collab Kira
um I'm really happy to play a game with
you guys again it's been a while me too
I missed your voice
[Music]
we're so happy we're here today Santa
yes I didn't think about my favorite
moment as a
pretty much every time I heard Cali
scream but now
spending time with all of you guys
[Music]
I'm sorry I killed you I love you
[Laughter]
you should next time next time you
should uh leave me leave me alive
because I believe everything you guys
say again
[Music]
all right well
um uh for me my favorite moment when I
had so many but I guess the one that
stayed in my head now is
um I think it was in this in the round
before the last round where uh everyone
was assessing gura and she was just
trying to speak but then like good I was
really mad and then Uma was like well
I'm gonna follow you to see if you're
really innocent and I was like chilling
with Ina as ghosts and we were just
talking about the better curling uh just
we're standing there together as ghosts
and then Ahmed and Guna ran into the
room having a huge fight like discussion
[Music]
a kindergarten fights
that was good they were running in
circles yelling at each other it was so
funny
oh man um but yeah
um it was it was a I'm really glad this
all worked out fine in the end uh Ina
had some travels in the beginning but
I'm so released
[Music]
yeah it worked out for sure
three times that everyone had fun and
and no hold on here and scuff was that
present today and yeah
[Music]
thank you for appreciating I'm sure
there's some some Among Us who are a
little bit tired of this Among Us game
but I think with proximity voice chat
mod it made it a whole lot more
interesting and kind of refreshing so
yes
it's a blast I wish we could do this
sometime again in the future yeah
how about jackbox
jackpots
do many people in jackbox
one more thing I kind of want to do is
like because I organized the Enid Mario
Kart tournament now that we are 11 Em's
ends we could do a full en Mario Kart
tournament as well
11 people like not 12 by 11 is it just
one of the one of the people are going
to be bought is that what it is
you can just leave that one out I think
um
[Music]
is it time for another training Arc yeah
let's do it time to unlock all the cards
well is a past 5 a.m for me so I hope we
can end up yeah
announcement
do you want to announce something oh
yeah yeah yeah oh
um I have an announcement for next
weekend that we will be having another
uh we'll collab
um
[Music]
yeah
details are secret for now but uh yeah
now you guys mark it down
yes
yeah this one is organized but so you
know it's gonna be you're just gonna
forget it amazing amazing the organizing
amazing not even trying to do the pun
I'm just really saying it's genuinely
gonna be amazing yes
[Music]
okay ready
three two
one
oh it's Ian
[Music]
I love that thank you
foreign
[Music]