[Music]
n
hello
y
y hi
[Music]
I'm I'm I'm so sleepy I got coins why
not
sleepy yeah you get like 150 coins in
the beginning and one shirt costs 50
coins it's so expensive I have coins
no the 50 is nothing look at the other
prices those are way more crazy this is
the cheapest
shirt yeah or you can get like a little
fart so I'm going to click on okay well
uh is it everyone's first time playing
the game yes yes can we introduce
ourselves no
yes
oh
okay okay then starting
from the play
order yeah okay we can we can introduce
ourselves while doing the volume check
[Music]
then right
okay I'm not a I'm
hello hello
yeah s
good next one the one who says sounds
good oh
uh thanks for having
me you just wake up oh no I'm just sick
she's sick she sick she sounds a little
bit like
money
[Music]
oh my
God sounds like
okay next uh uh my lovely this running
bird
uh uh w w yeah why why did you need to
think so long about that cuz you both
are running I was
choosing
okay
um I'm the kiaha I uh love ID girls and
I love am so this is like the best party
ever let's go let's
go oh my God you girl are so [\h__\h]
loud let's
go let's
go
y next the one this yellow
birdow yellow bird
um how to how to
introdu
um my soul there you go introduction da
okay good good day man my name is
k from third generation D my
soul that's what we've all been waiting
for have you had bricky yet
bre Brey done bre nice
Brey Brey done okay next uh Amy let's go
hello Amia Watson
[Music]
detective we have a
detective we have a detective and we
have a secret agent very
nice I'm barely a secret
agent barely the misunderstanding of why
am is here oh oh oh should we should we
talk about
it wait can can we talk about it yeah
yeah yeah oh yeah I I I reacted with an
emoji to the the invite of this because
I was like oh shoot that sounds like a
cool game so I put a little POG a little
C POG reaction and uh I wasn't expecting
to join but I'm here and I'm happy to be
here anyway we're happy that you're here
we're happy that you're
[Music]
here sign up but she's still here even
though she didn't sign
up she didn't sign up for this it was
really
funnyer yeah it was really funny cuz I
was like uh uh react if you want join
and I was like I'm imp POG so I was like
let's
go
s okay uh
this
hell re I'm Ru
[Applause]
[Music]
yay next last but not least our sweepy
sleepy
bird oh did you just forget about
mea
wow oh
my even I thought you did introduction
[Music]
I'm
sorry attention please thank you for
your
[Laughter]
attention I miss
[Music]
you okay now the real last but not
least
Anya hello it's Ana from Hol Live ID
can
[Music]
second wait um how do you change your
color can you change it I think need to
change
it oh no yeah yeah yeah perfect you yeah
okay yeah it looks it looks good okay
yeah good
okay okay since we don't have much time
I'm thinking we can do um you don't have
much time maybe one uh one classic games
yeah one to two classic
games and then we can try other stuff
like um the hide and seek or The Killing
Spree one I think
ooh yeah there's many different modes
and stuff
da Sensei yes is this um is this game
like a certain impostor game this call
oh yeah yeah something similar but duck
okay and Goose quack yes wait which one
which one is the Imposter the duck or
the goose the duck I think the duck the
bab the goose is the crew
mate Baby I hav very mind I think I
haven't played either up in the
title I haven't played either so yeah I
haven't played either I couldn't up my
alarm oops also this is also going to be
my
[Music]
first sorry just in case I overslept
um yeah okay let's play I think it's
everyone's time first time playing
anyway so let's play Let's Play Let's
Play
what go
wrong three two
[Music]
one
huha hello hello hello hello hello oh
the lover
[Music]
please do not kill
me
Oho oh if you click on the
T kind of navigates you to the it gives
you like me
oh you're
[Music]
right let's
[Laughter]
[Music]
see want me to
leave finally it's
um finally it's time for us to play
Goose goose
duck and commence the be
D
jokes be is duck Mar is
hello hi wi I love
you know that you can walk using your
cursor wait
really your mouse cursor I know I know
oh you know you guys know I know am I
the only one who didn't know okay I
didn't know but I mean it's not nice
like yeah it's it's not really
nice just use W
ASD yeah I'm using W
ASD wait what's this there's a she's
good at
hello
STS how how how
how I understand yes I know we need to
double
yes
yeah okay
okay let's
[Laughter]
go
fre
[Music]
we were
lovers we were
lover no we l okay okay we need the wait
did no one kill yeah yeah I was just
trying to see what yeah it was me and
it's okay I think we can make the task
longer the task longer
I was looking for dead bodies cuz I was
the vulture I'm supposed to eat dead
bodies but there were no dead bodies oh
my
god um we do have um it's four vers
four and
no like two ducks and then two two other
people on the duck
side wait there four people I think the
roll for the um the duck side is only
two so oh wait wait wait wait wait but
then there's also other special only two
only
two a
B I think um I was I was a vulture which
is not the duck wait so who's the duck
you're not a duck but a duck is uh are
you guys supposed to help the Ducks no
no we're supposed to that means no the
vulture is kind of doing their own thing
they just they don't don't even have to
do tasks but they also don't kill just
eat corpses and if they get eat corpses
they yeah they're just in for the
they're just in for the win in for the
win just for food yeah I me Doo as well
it's like Jester if they get folded out
they they win I guess yeah I thought
that was supposed to be anybody know
what the um cuz when you're a duck you
get these like unlock this and that like
sabotage unlock blah blah blah d i but
yeah I've been trying to work that out
but I didn't get it yeah yeah I didn't
really understand you have to kill
someone if you want to sabotage oh so
it's like
oh okay this knowledge I will bring with
me Al senpie I was searching for you we
were
lovers you know you know what's crazy
the lovers role they didn't tell us who
the who the other partner is
yeah so we have to look by
ourselves if we just came out wor I love
her I love
her one more time um my task I I I set
the task list to be larger so I think it
should be fine can everyone okay let's
go press ready ready up please oh yeah
sorry ready okay again let's
[Music]
go who is it this is not fair also I
know then I die
to
lover you got another
poor So Silent what why
hello what's the where's the I need I
need the map to this
place royalty membership everybody
everybody join the royalty we have new
badges yummy I was pouring
tea I was pouring tea what hello no no
no we we were at the dinner table and we
didn't know that it means like emergency
okay
my yeah oh my
God
skip how do I skip I we can't skip we
can't yo this is literally a skip ad
moment okay oh now we can skip
ad the
DU the duck
loed
what what do that mean I don't know what
that means everyone is safe for
now yo I got literally skip at ah
where's my
tea my also I'm not going to be looking
at hi hello
hello where's the
because I lost it no I need
you I want to do my task Co sip some tea
where's the
door as long as we got the strength in
ourselves we could rise above the pain
hello guys where's the
entrance sa I don't know where did I
enter
from where am
I
[Music]
here I
know here why is it it's so hard to get
the
[Music]
dishes guys guys
guys the guys theut Olli
Olli no no no
noide
room you and Ollie went upstairs right I
went right and then I saw it upstairs
not upstairs the room beside
it
oh I was doing the dishes Ella was with
me where wait wait where were you can
you self report in this game yeah I
don't know I I think wait I it's I was
from I was from bottom both ol and
Kyla huh I was from the Bott K because
she just got into the room
okay I
don't you just pressed the name I think
I just what what yeah I think
I what oh my
God I think we don't know what we're
doing yeah say I think
I don't think
it's do the
knife the
knife where is
it who Super S Super S I only trust
rainy are you sure you only trust rainy
because I'm stting raining ooh hello a
lot of people we can stick together self
report but if you keep it's okay you can
just keep going with rainy so if you die
yeah you can yeah we can separate but no
don't
please only do you want to go with me oh
sure ah I'll protect you you look very
sus I don't like this we can go we can
go 3x3 or something how many people we
have yeah 3 by three sounds safe yeah or
five by four up to
you
where do you guys got to go I don't
know oh unclock the
toilet
wait
yeah how do you
unclock I had click just press click
click click click click click click
click click click click click cck click
click
click where
[Music]
are okay okay okay hello hello R do you
know that we we became enemies to lovers
wait what what is up we went from
enemies to lovers you can kill anyone
right if you're why are you guys always
together are you scaming that I can kill
anyone you can kill anyone right just
kill all of us is
so kill me kill me can kill anyone right
I no I'm a sheriff I I only I only kill
Ducks oh
I I think it's KY she keeps ssing
everyone then can I kill Kyla yeah just
kill me everybody Mi some room
room no no no no
so after witnessing yes
and yeah and then Zen going to be
responsible for
my my will die no that's so dramatic
[Laughter]
no no no one trust me I said trusted you
I said I said don't kill no one trust me
before why did no one trust her she's
selfreported
was staying ly the entire time wait yeah
wa did you actually report or because I
was Canadian so like no no I didn't
report uh it's Auto
report I had to lie as I breathe don't
kill the Canadian
I literally said that I saw wa and rainy
together before that happened and but no
one did
wear I I remember you saying it yeah I
thought remember you saying
it I mean I wasn't lying though we were
together you went up who was the who was
the who got the lover roll oh yeah who
is it I know not me
what theover was it was it you no I'm
I'm lovers with
you spicy so we got it correct spicy oh
my sorry my alarm keeps ringing up turn
it up girl I'm
try she's the one that on 10 layers of
alarmes uh I'll turn it off okay so are
we ready how about we switch it up with
different rules yeah okay
sure let's see rise and grind
Gamers I
think uh I think I think I think
I we can do assassin so basically uh you
can kill during meetings by correctly
guessing a roll or die trying that's
crazy die trying yeah during meetings
Okay mhm let's go let's go let's go
let's go meetings let's
go one
one you scare me woman you scare
meing a r I'm ready how that work
uh okay let's go safe safe
safe
we wisu and Wawa have matching outfit po
tea por te por te po tea oh my God you
have po tea too I'm also pouring tea
yeah it's over here
yes yeah guys it's the anniversary of
royalty so guys we're doing pour pouring
tea uh there's going to be a special
stream on Friday so be sure to join the
royalty when you
[Laughter]
can yo I swear to God the first time I
was really pouring te and then a meeting
was called and it wasn't even a real
meeting oh my god let's
go okay
yeah and then they just skip add
[Music]
moment we have to be quiet so we're not
suspicious
hello unclocked toilet
ow
I die in the toilet so
[Music]
undignified wow self reports
us no she's
not no no no can can can you explain was
the body where was the
body uh the body is in the
laboratory what
laboratory a labatory
okay Ella we
were I'm in the kitchen I trying to find
were we were in The West Wing yeah we
suspicious I think we
can don't skip it was me I self-reported
don't skip oh it was you actually it was
me that's very s that's
very what she's a doo bird she no she's
a doo isn't she she's probably a doo
bird very no so who
killed
yo you guys believe me so easily I was
like oh how do I make myself like if I
want to be kicked out as a doo bird then
I should just make people think that I'm
the sussy one so I
just I skip I voted
Watson so
trustworthy
um how many times did r s by got the
dock the go the do the do I'm voting you
next whatever happens we're voting her
out
first okay let's ready I'm ready I'm
ready again again
CL
H are we are
we are we are we yo yo yo yo are what
are
you me yes I am
Canadian oh a I see what are you oh are
are you lovers I'm looking for my
girlfriend
wifeu wifeu
wife bye she's not my wifeu are you my
wifeu wait ready yes oh my God oh my God
oh my God wait wait you're purple
survive Will
Survive
[Music]
are you guys did did
you wait why mirror where's the
mirror what clean water pump where is
it where is
it that's very
s h where is
it
and it's
outside no I need to you make it I need
to
survive I need to
survive yes
yes did you guys got it yes I got it oh
I got it I got it
oh to do it yeah I think everybody has
to do
it I got it I can do it already
wait wait wait I think
what blue with blue
[Music]
liquid
hello it's tea
time it's tea time for my
[Music]
LS
yeah
no
no oh do you hear me yeah
dead
dead oh no
no two people
gone two people
gone where is this in the piano room I'm
voting re Senpai no matter what piano
room why it's re
Senpai
recent because she's always
it nah this is my luck
previously are we V
I I vot I
voted I'm so
[Music]
sad
no what if she isn't
it taking a nap with the
fish oh so that's why you that's why you
should stay with your lover because if
one dies you die
oh but you know I thought actually cuz
you can also be lover uh if your lover
is like the other part like the Imposter
um so I thought you were impostor for
some reason but you're not impostor
you're just a lover yeah oh I didn't
know that you could actually do imposter
lover wait so did you die just because I
died yeah I did a the animation was I
was I was staying away from any
everybody and it's like suddenly oh you
saw the animation
see I'm
innocent I can't never
[Music]
trust Raina only died cuz she was a l
with me I was killed and way di with me
so
romantic
wait that's not true I murdered
you you did but R died with me because
you murdered
me so you at the same time I was I was
somewhere else and I
died okay let's do something
really
stupid let's
go stupid stupid stupid something stupid
St stupid something
something what about so what
about oh how about a detective round DET
what's the detective
do detective you can investigate players
to see if they have killed maybe too op
maybe too op okay never mind too op to
okay I can we we can go with stalker
basically you can track one
player
stalker again you scare me
woman I'm ready by the way
ready
okay
I'm
alone alone in the dark oh my
God hello
hello
what oh what's this oh
oh okay sorry I thought I thought that
was a task I think that's what they did
wait what am I what what I do
[Music]
oh is I
don't
[Music]
let's shift let me see if
people I I would like to deduct you
[Music]
things I thinkla might be a stalker so
she's not the duck what okay I'm I'm the
stalker Ollie and it's kind of
useless oh never mind calling her
useless calling it useless what no no
I'm saying the stalker roll is kind of
useless cuz I'm like I don't get much
from it I feel like does it like do you
win if you successfully stalk someone
what does it do Ollie Ollie why are you
blaming me I'm foring you no no
I was trying to call you no I was trying
to like no wa she she never even she
never even said what the stalker
did nice
[Music]
deduction wait everyone is safe
for
suspense the
suspense L
suspens
it's oh
god of you
follow you are not a
stalker
oh
oh oh my God I hope she sees it I hope
she sees
it oh my wait wait wait wait wait wait
what wait
whate I I was cleaning a picture and
Raina ran past me and I heard her and
then I was done cleaning the picture I
was going in the same direction Ollie
was going with me and we both saw the
body kind of at the same time I was like
what the what
what for sure it's not aelia
inp I was the whole time
is oh you guys are
lovers
Dam she's pretty good oh DN sheett good
we're not even lovers but that's pretty
good I was at the where were you you
tell me right nowson tell me where you
were I was
with yeah she was with me what the freak
that's pretty good no no before that I
was with her the whole
time what's happening oh [\h__\h]
no you messed up big
time up big time Ollie so
close ol was also close but she's
telling the
truth what I told you guys yo you were
so close you were so close but you were
telling the truth at the same
time I knew you were the doo you were so
fast sorry
what does doo do again she needs to
she's the jester basically she's the
jester needs to get voted off but but
Oli got the people right yeah she got
the
people yeah she
said yeah but I still wanted to win so I
voted for
myself yo that's
crazy that is so
sad and you didn't win I'm so mad for
you you self
voted okay so is kind of
unnecessary mm okay the stalker roll
useless um yeah this one instead of so
I'm exchanging the lover duck to um
Hitman duck and bodyguard Goose so The
Bodyguard gets a bonus for protecting a
player but the Hitman gets a bonus for
killing them oh I don't know what the
bonus entails though how to even the
same discussion time I feel like the
discussion time is a little bit too
short yeah to be honest okay okay
discussion time that was 30 seconds how
about um how about uh 45
45 yeah okay no I didn't know that from
30 to 45 with your mouse yeah and the
options are only 30 45
60 okay 60 okay let's go
60 okay okay I need to write this down
mhm let's go okay
so instead of mimic I'm using the
detective so detective can investigate
players to see if they have killed that
round M okay we can try that one okay
let's go okay let's go bye bye
[Music]
bye my God I swear every
single
hello D D D D D D
[Music]
T
that well wow that's so fast
that's so
fast is it self report self report is it
like automatically report where is it I
don't know I report it it was at West
Wing It was at West Wing to West Wing
can you actually see the map oh you can
actually okay okay yeah you can see the
map
oh I then it wasn't wa waa is safe thank
you why do that
pretty fast too so I'm SI too it was
last time the last time I saw someone
mhm and The West Wing is actually
reu I no
I yeah because
reaaa and then I left I don't I don't
think
it's from
hway you're from
hway library hallway yeah to It's a Long
Way from hallway to West Wing who are
you guys voting
for I'm skiing
again only kind
of oh you what
okay is
it oh she's still she's still safe okay
okay safe okay safe so number one is
always safe
so I think for the first one everybody
is always
safe in the thingy
[Music]
hello sweep sweep sweep sweep sweep
sweep sweep sweep sweep sweep sweep
sweep sweep
sweep I'm at e get away from me you
murder
yo
wait how do you deal with this
one do you
y huming the
pillow wait what you say he
one I mean it looks like one it looks
like one it looks like I'm Hing to
Bel where where's the
lights
I don't
know oh no see you people what the heck
we're trying to fix the light I think oh
oh oh it's fixed ni nice almost that
kill I
see
PL
[Music]
PL ooh what's
this what just happened hello
hello
get away get away no she's going to kill
me I was about to report that I'm the
medium I can see it oh I see W going
around and there is a corpse around
where wa
left I was with re Senai yeah the whole
time don't no don't stick it on
me I'm the medium I can see the dead
bodies I was about to go back to the
dining room to report because I just
looked at my medium what's medium medium
is it shows me it shows me uh like uh
there's a countdown every once in a
while I can press shift and then I see
how many ghosts there are and for the
longest time it was just one from the
last round and now I just after my task
refreshed and I saw two so I was in the
studio doing the the base or something
string connection and then just around
the corner is a dining room where you
can report right so I don't know where
the body is but I went to the dining
room to report you going back and forth
that was with I no I saw you going back
and forth as well so don't stick it on
me now you you two were together and you
were probably thinking oh we can stick
it on if I kill someone no I'm the
medium oh my God I God
wait I believe want to be killed
actually I wait wait how do
you how do you how did I just explain
how the medium Works no if you get the
wrong person it's going to be bad okay
okay I'm not sure yeah I'm hungry I
swear me too it was just around the cor
the dinner why would you do that why
would
you I just realized that i' I haven't
been voting or have I'm not sure we sa
okay nice nice good good
yay there's sticking it on me right I
swear they want to like kick me out they
they saw me and they were like oh she's
she's she looks like someone who we can
stick it on how do you vote actually I'm
not really
sure you like cuz I don't know have I
been voting because I tried to vote and
then I wonder too it doesn't really show
so well oh there's free free fre
[Music]
[Applause]
what these ducks are too
clever I don't I don't have the heart to
lay a finger on you like me me and simp
you finger on
me it was so funny seeing ol my run away
from
R didn't say
anything yeah we out a little bit too
late she was
silent oh wait you dead I'm
sorry
this oh
no okay uh I think uh
how about we try since it's been an our
help but we try different uh mode yes
yeah sure yes yes sure okay we can
try okay what about this hoot and seek
hoot and seek hoot and seek the owl must
blend in with NPC to complete task to
win the game spotters and snipers work
together to identify and kill the owl to
win I don't know how many owls that's so
much
anxiety a what about Goan might be
like yeah the
tag okay want to try
Goan good okay let's
try to reduce the timer or choose to
hide oh okay okay there's a similar mode
in um in uh Among Us I mean we can try
runs really fast can try the other
modes yeah I I think we can try the Goan
first and then we try a different one
after this okay should be a quick round
let's
go
[Laughter]
what h wait what am I supposed to
do what is this
[Music]
[Laughter]
huh
[Music]
so many dead
people wait where's the where's the
candles oh my
god oh
no
run
[Music]
hi oh my God why did she keep getting
the I don't know the task is too much
the task is too much too much the test
is too much okay for this game yeah also
I spawned where arisu spawned in the
beginning oh my God
like what are the odds of spawning with
the killer man oh we can't adjust the
task it's like set I know time K so the
moment risu immediately came to chase us
I was like oh no don't don't
come Z is like what what is this Z was
like me no I wasn't talking about I
thought he was I thought he was Zeta but
then Zeta
died why I did that thing okay um
there's this one called Trick and Treat
oh what's up so villagers complete task
to call meetings and then vot out the
monster to win so it's like we're wolf
right the monster wins when everyone's
been converted to a throw I don't know
what a thow like vampire I guess okay I
I this game you can okay basically we do
Tas call meeting vote out the SS one
okay
okay ready ready ready
ready oh sorry sorry oh yeah I'm ready
actually
[Music]
we got to be
silent wait how do
I
okay on this one hello this K me as R
ASMR content
good morning
everybody good morning what is up where
how do we adust for Prince how about we
dust for some Prince today and what's
this I don't even know
what what what is this what
what excuse me what the
freak restrings hello hello everybody we
restrain this
hello I've been diligently doing my
tasks
[Music]
what oh my God what the what
the what I don't know I was at the
studio restringing Theos I've been very
diligent with my
TKS I haven't seen anyone I haven't seen
anyone but wa wa but she was just I
don't think or Ru anywhere either I'm
going to vote
[Applause]
for
goodbye have an intervie convention
about bullying I
know she is no longer wanted that's
crazy and that means it's
them
hi that means they're
guilty
ah I'm so
scared I'm so
[Music]
scared it was so hard to figure out I
didn't know what I was doing but I guess
I
won yeah
thank you my little vampire babies
you're welcome I was the one who
converted all of them well not all of
them most of them oh
wow that was
funun wait so what can the th
do K
the vampires turn into like zombies so
they like yeah like zombies oh okay okay
but even when I clicked like the Turning
thingy it didn't happen immediately it
takes a while I guess until they
turn oh did it happen immediately for
for the others for the ones for the fs
who converted other normal
people you know what I
mean I don't know let's play let's let's
play one
more one last one I think whoever
becomes the vampire good luck just try
pushing everything
pushing push
push push push
push push push push push
push you can do it no no get away from
me
wait where is it
though I want to draw
bath draw bath oh my God that sounds
scary oh my
God no are you no no no it's not me it's
someone up
there oh oh oh oh
oh my God oh my
[Laughter]
God yo what the
[\h__\h] okay I don't think it's I don't
think it's Ana either yeah I don't think
it's rainu so it's either Ru or waa I
vote wa I had enough being
voted Le I understand it's okay I
wouldn't vote you either bullying is not
okay I'm going to I'm going to I'm going
to be a bully today enil
Ru you're going toet it right now cuz
you you were talking about spanking
something spanking that's that's my job
I see
what
again okay
okay oh I can
trim spicy he what was
spicy W
spicy I'm
spicy oh
spicy oh spicy
[Laughter]
see you got to trust me I'm always
honest I don't know why it gave me
vampire
again I told
you wa wa why spicy
time stop
you knew what was going on then what was
it's because I need to fluff the pillow
oh me too I had to do that too
earlier yeah it's cuz
you Out For Blood Out For Blood one more
please she's just out
for please do do we still want to do the
previous one or new one new new one
okay what about this taste like chicken
what do that
mean social deduction Battle Royale
protect your team's chicken and kill
everyone else what do you mean social
deduction
oh I don't dck the duck the duck
like Battle Royale I think yeah I think
it's like it's like Battle Royale I
think you're supposed to protect
yourself one one for their own for real
for real okay protect your chicken ready
up
prot so we
haveen ready ready protect the chicken
protect the chicken protect the
[Music]
chicken you're a chicken who's not ready
look
see everyone's ready ready why can't I
start the game again TR again are you
ready are you I'm ready I'm ready I'm
ready are you ready wait
maybe here okay up
[Music]
again maybe we need a minimum amount of
people
[Music]
to okay we can try the um we can try
this one this
one and seek maybe
okay okay let's try whatever this
is's go we have to take down even though
she's not
here someone will represent
her I can't start either I wonder why
that's so
weird wait
un ready and then ready yeah I I'm ready
and ready already um yeah me too I just
did it just now I'm ready now I also did
um
weird let me try again sorry let me try
again no
problem maybe if the room is restarted
worst case I think the only like you can
ready um if it's like plastic my button
lit up when it was classic but other Ms
I don't think I
[Music]
can what do you guys want to try
draft dra draft is like the like classic
but like you can pick your rules now
a that's so
nice let's go let's go let's go try it I
don't know how to okay so
let's
oh you get a gacha oh oh you get AA
oh what is this what what is
this to choose
first okay you need to win there a
vulture why would you choose V out of
all things look this I mean I'm I'm
picking I'm
picking whatever can we see what the
what the duck the goose the duck also
chooses the duck the DU duck can choose
we can choose everything like we can see
everyone's
oh but but I'm not a
OFA living the life of gacha show a fake
one maybe for the maybe show the fake
one it doesn't show people's names or
what play yeah so it's like doesn't
show I guess yeah I guess technically we
can just like guess which one is who
which one is it you can't tell a lot of
people picking random I didn't nice
Sheriff I was reading Sheriff
sherff damn it I wanted to be
Sheriff then K Sheri no
no
yo that's crazy that's crazy what the
heck has to do too interesting isn't
[Music]
it I want to I want to
try
oh my God the
[\h__\h] oh yo I can't see who this is
scary oh I got the spanking
task my God what is that
sound oh there
a
that's cool
though wait it's not
done
hi this car oh I didn't even see a body
so I don't know why it uh dining room it
says I I I actually don't know sorry
that was so silent where where was the
body where's the body yeah I I don't
know I didn't see it I think it's
self-reported I'm the sheriff so I can't
oh you're the sheriff the what role can
so um where were you I'm in I was in the
hallway by the laboratory by the sun
okay I think z z came from above from
the hallway and said hi was it
it yeah I it it though yeah Ollie you
the West you hurt
the two people did though what one of
them West wi no way you came to the
kitchen there's only there's only I was
in the
West in the loop I came in no you said
hi to us well one thing you for it's not
Ona because I was with her the whole
time yeah I was with
wait who wait who wait who who who tell
me tell me tell
me
hold
defend I'm so I'm like so out of the
loop who is it who is it
[Music]
myself
Z what did I
tell you should have not killed me I
actually don't remember saying
hi I don't remember saying
hi not kill me Zeta I am your
hel you like
help didn't you hear a hi didn't you
hear someone saying hi maybe it's no but
I did SAA I don't oh you didn't see I
heard hi I mean I said hi to
everybody she was singing weren't you
dead r i was dead zaeta killed me yeah
you were dead yeah I killed my
helper it wasn't you then if you were
dead cuz it was tried before before the
body was
found
ghost oh yeah we that was fun though the
was fun yeah can we do it
[Music]
again yeah let's do it let's do it again
okay I want to I swear to God someone
said hi Chad you Hur
no I didn't hear a hi
I was so close to killing she was in
front of my
eyes why would you why always a
vulture that's so freaked up who picked
vulture he's sick sick
being what those vure do again eat B eat
the B I like this
one then you're a party
you win then that's you
Z wow
Z what
do detective nice what is
that Batman
Batman will never
[Music]
know oh cute
they won't kill me
[Music]
because why are
[Laughter]
you
be
[Music]
what from where where do we get
this
[Music]
okay
bam I don't I don't want
[Laughter]
to
hold
together
together wait for me guys wait for me H
wait for
me okay
okay I need to dust my where's KY I
don't know KY was going to the upper
side I
think anything which I thought was sus
by the way even though I to her I said
hi to her but she didn't answer me with
hi back say hi
back okay thank you follow me uh armor I
need you guys here I need the two of you
wait are the there you go
kyank the P
sure
[Music]
okay spanking how do you spank the
pillow hold on you keep tapping I'm
going to
[Music]
do don't worry I'm watching I'm
watching my task was over here continue
your okay SC I need to reassemble
painting
hiy reassemble painting do oh wait I got
to do this one there's so many TS okay
I got to do this one the bath oh I hate
this one
theing I don't understand how it
works I've never gotten this one
before how does it
work oh no fire fire fire
fire fire fire
fire sorry guys I'm going to reassemble
the painting
first
hold on I'm
coming
coming it's R hey
what oh
god oh my God how how
do
[Music]
oh
okay where you guys did it you saved
saved everyone Ana's gone Ana's gone
wait no where's Ana is she
dead hopefully not h z and Ollie
where'sa okay eat
food foodoo foodoo foodoo foodoo are you
guys done with your
task not yet oh I actually need to like
handles B wait it's not here whatever
dust the chest the chest I mean
I none of us
yeah why the makan so
G where the
dishes
mamao mama where the
dishes salad turn on stu
stuff
CLE hell
[Applause]
yeah what the [\h__\h] you wear a
[Laughter]
vter she was following you just in case
you
di I was hoping I was hoping either of
you guys will
get it was hard cuz everyone was
together the whole
[Music]
time yeah I I think having only one
imposter is hard yeah it's difficult
it's difficult especially when people
just decide to be like yo let's be
together need to be yeah I'm not making
it better
though I'm going to any Al accompany me
the two of
you
yeah okay I actually you know what's
crazy I actually didn't know that party
was an imposter I thought party was just
like a like the just like just like a
just like a useless Ro I was like it's
it only says something like you can give
someone high pitch sound during meetings
I was like sounds
cool I didn't know either I assumed it
was some neutral role yeah Ian my uh my
role was guess it would be hard for
villagers to like discuss with each
other about sound guess yeah also
basically my R is like if I'm not alone
if I have like at least I guess if I
have at least two people with me I can't
get killed so that's why I keep asking
people to accompany
me I was waiting for someone to
get H was together the whole time it was
so difficult okay okay I think we could
possibly end it here
[Music]
maybe I want to play again
sometime yeah let's play again sometimes
sometimes yeah this is so fun thank you
for for making the time to play
together
for thank you for inviting so fun it was
a lot of
fun thank
you I'm so excited to see all of you in
Japan soon for
festival
y then we can party
y
[Music]
y take care Everybody Take Care
everybody
[Music]
byee