[Music]
I
bre h
[Music]
something I don't
to
[Music]
my something
B
[Music]
Ki
again
woo hello oh oh kind of sideway side on
the
side k
can you hear me it's Wawa from
Japan in the
studio the countdown is already counting
yeah you can hear me let me move this
here loud and clear woo I hope I hope
everything is set up and I didn't forget
anything
cuz uh had to set up everything from
scratch again m is a rare time yeah yeah
PSD like normally this is like in in my
time in in my usual time now it's like
early morning like what 6:00 a.m. 7
maybe 7:00 a.m. or no maybe even 8:00
a.m. 8:00 a.m. right yeah normally I
would not even be awake at this
time yeah I chose to do a
PST countdown stream I wasn't sure like
what countown down to do um I thought
like a jsd countdown would be difficult
because I'm in Japan and I can't I mean
I could maybe stream at that time but I
think the studio would appreciate me not
to uh try to be in here at 11:00 p.m.
and stream past midnight it's not ideal
400 P p.m. in Sydney the other Austria
hello to Sydney wait I want to like
chitchat a little bit um but I think
we'll also have time to chitchat in
between because I am not very confident
in getting many calls
today I did notify people and I we got a
few but maybe not an endless amount um
but remind me of Australia I want to say
something about Australia later remind
me of that um but yeah today is the
Birthday Countdown stream and uh the
reservation is not up yet but I am I'm
doing a
k birthday
Kar uh for the first time I'm doing this
in that style uh where you know there's
pre like a bunch of pre-recorded guests
uh singing uh green screen uh and I'll
sing along with them or they're singing
along with me however you want to see
that but it's mostly uh me singing along
to
them yeah there was a big crab game
collab yeah yeah yeah um I hope you guys
had fun watching that but now is wa time
birthday apparently it's my fourth
birthday should I leave this up maybe as
advertisement for
now maybe like down here and in that
stream there will also be the merch
announcement like right here right now
uh today there will be no merch
announcement uh my oh my B didn't thank
you of course it didn't of course it
didn't I thought I had everything on the
control oh there we go now we
will H although crab game in July is
kind of fitting I am I am Cancer sign wa
is cancer sign so crap game in July is
actually perfect yo I saw so many things
with GAA and the others at Dodgers game
yeah I saw like so many things in my
timeline was like he
wow this is bigger than I
thought so cool didn't you de after your
birthday what do you mean it's always an
after and a before there's always a like
before obviously no matter when I would
have debuted there would have always
been a birthday before unless I was not
alive
before maybe I wasn't alive was I not
alive I mean I'm a phoenix I was
probably alive and that's Chicken N it's
not even a chicken and egg situation
it's not like
it um
I have I have the Dodgers song uh in my
brain now because I saw videos of GAA
singing the Dodger
song but yeah blah blah blah blah blah
you like the apron it's like a a a
romper apron I think not really an apron
it's also not new I just didn't wear it
before so I was going for the cave props
tag to see if I can find anything cute
um stream is still vertical what do you
mean what is vertical what I want it to
be vertical is the lengthy one
right that's on purpose then
[Laughter]
yeah uh but yeah it it's by
elme elme an old an older one I dug it
out of the Treasure
Trove um yeah so have I have I done a
Birthday Countdown before I don't think
I do it every year
it's not a tradition at least oh it was
for
stue oh that makes
sense well this is uh fine no it was
made for my birthday it was made for
this purpose I'm not recycling at all
yes you did yeah I probably did it
before but I don't do it all the time so
wait there's someone waiting so let's
not make him wait too long uh oh my God
is that a oh wait there's one oh there's
there's five people waiting oh I didn't
I don't think there was so many people
waiting
already oh
wait uh wait wait uh okay uh how do I
they're all in the same room how do I
tell are they are they listening maybe
uh should
I girls if one of you is listening feel
free to send one of you to me ah oh ah
oh wait I was muted ah
hello
hello oh my God
[Music]
a double wait she's double wait how is
she double wait say something something
something oh she's double okay there we
go now she shouldn't be double anymore
okay listen I don't want to say happy
birthday to you yet because in Italy
it's like bad lck to say happy birthday
before your actual birthday so I'm going
to say happy birthday after your cown
it's not okay thank you that's okay
actually like uh apparently that's a
European thing oh yeah but I I don't
really I don't really care that much you
you can say happy birthday happy
birthday can you say it in
[Music]
Italiano
cute a wait I actually put I did prepare
a picture of you right here because I
saw you we're coming okay there it is
Raa a a new a new member of whole life
English yeah how how are you feeling
being a part of us I'm so
happy I'm I'm the happiest person in the
world right now I'm so happy and I'm so
happy to talk to you and it's so nice
I'm honored to be here oh thank you I'm
so happy that I have uh like that that
one of the new members was Itali because
I I can now like I'm a bit more
motivated to maybe polish my Italian
again for you for you yeah yeah but you
already talk pretty nicely though I
heard I I've seen some tweets
and yeah my my my breakfast tweets
recently so cute so nice I was like oh
finally then I have to translate this
actually I can I can understand I mean I
usually understand English too but yeah
yeah
and you know I'm actually in Japan right
now so there's a chance we could meet
but you yeah it's not like it's not
urgent but like no no no we can meet
anytime like literally if you tell me
hey I have five minutes free I come to
you I Lally run really okay what about
now what about now I can come now what
if I give youing what what if the
Birthday Countdown is also a countdown
for daa
arriving listen do not challenge me I
I'm actually going to do that if you
give me your
address my address was not my address
but when's your birthday is it May 11 oh
so next year next year oo it's already
my fourth birthday I'm four years old L
uh you 4 years old I'm a baby it's a
baby Babble Babble bubble
it's okay Mama's here Mom Mom you're
you're the new Mama you're the new mama
in the in the in the house I don't know
I I guess the meme is born because I
want to be one day I want to be mama in
whole life or I don't know that's my
dream right and then everybody started
to call me Mama and then I just embraced
it and that's fine your dream was to be
mama in whole life you you mean as an
artist or yeah art art mama
yeah that would be cool who knows who
knows maybe you know ra one day will
become someone's Mama maybe wait can I
you know I've been actually hiring like
different artists for my new outfits
each time what about you want to do that
you want to draw a new outfit for me a
live Tod outfit I can I can definitely
do that you you'll get paid oh yeah I
mean it's okay it's whole life money
it's whole life money it's not even out
of my pocket honestly me made me very
happy that' be so cool because then I
feel like if it's with you then I can
also make a lot of wishes like do this
do that oh
yeah I looked over to J and she's love
designing yeah yeah yeah let's do it JMA
is right behind me and she gave me a
like a look like it's okay I could them
I already made a MC for Cecilia too like
I love doing stuff for for my friends so
don't worry about it discussion with JMA
afterwards if that's even possible oh oh
she's giving a like a
maybe oh my God hey exciting okay cool
nice thank you so much La wait before
you go before you go since this is
actually the first time we're like
talking on stream yeah uh I want to ask
you what's your like image of Taki
Ki uh she is the idol the
[Music]
OG like whenever I think about the
actual perfect Idol I think about you
because you were the first yeah like you
were the first one in the end and I
don't know I think it's just I think
yeah I think that's thank you I do
aspire to be Idol like yeah yeah yeah
and also yeah I think I really
appreciate how how much you did into
this community and thank you yeah you
did a lot and I I I was watching you
since a very beginning so I'm very very
happy right now to talk to you like
immensely happy and you you're great
you're doing great and you're such an
inspiration for everyone here so thank
youa for being such a d Senpai thank you
so much yes yes Senpai so much thank you
thank you thank you you're so sweet okay
I hope we can collab soon because
apparently the band is
lifted anytime okay thank you for coming
[Music]
happy
bye oh that was our first interaction I
think there will be a few first
interactions this is not going to be the
only one I wonder who's coming in next
oh there's four people wa waiting that
would actually went back into the
waiting
room oh who's who's it going to be I got
to bring out the the Twitter profile
picture bring it on girls bring me any
one of
oh
Senai hi hi gy
g g
gy gy yes gy that's right happy birthday
thank you orange little new friend thank
you orange Senai I am your orange sta
yeah that's right gigg two oranges is it
okay I call you giggy yeah you can call
me anything good you had no choice
anyway you are so cute I love you so
much I feel like
I I I want to like OSI
you what but I I want to OSI you thanks
for coming to my channel talking to me
like pointing my fingers together and
I'm blushing I'm like oh my God K
streams are fun everybody you guys need
to check out gigy my new coire her
streams are fun she's cute she's orange
like we love orange here right we love
orange we love
orange yeah especially if you're here
right now spending time with Ki you
better love orange or get out of here
yes orange
Overlord
gy this is our uh our first time talking
and you know in your
generation there's um all kinds of like
multilangual people right uh uh well
maybe herb is Herb is actually not mult
multi Lang langual maybe but uh I mean
somehow H now can you sing me happy
birthday in in a a special language too
or
no
no I I knew that I just wanted to like
put you on the spot right here right now
I could try um uh okay um um what
language should I
Google um how about uh Finnish
okayish is Happy Birthday
lyrics Birthday Song Wait prounce it
no do your
best apparently
[Music]
it's wow you finished
I I Googled a YouTube video telling me
how to good J no don't just say you're
finished you're finished I finished I
finished now yeah you finished and you
finished singing your finished song wow
I finished singing and I'm
finished nice so Gigi I asked your gen
made now you can tell me too cuz you're
new what is your image of
takiar beautiful orange wonderful cute
wonderful Idol shining Idol beautiful
wonderful woman so beautiful and cute
and and the most shiny
Idol it's true it's true it's all true
wow and I just really look up to you and
everything that you've done and how you
have like a really like positive and
happy
attitude I don't know you like you know
I mean like you work really hard
for for the things that you really love
and like it's inspiring watching you
work so hard like I want to work as hard
as kiar Senpai 2o I think you will be
you already are the orange M it's the
orange orange jeans that we have the
orange jeans yeah I really love like
your whole design and everything and
your your Vibe and you're so cute I hope
we can collab at some point soon the
band is lifted yeah
when when you're not when you're not
busy yeah I'm a bit busy right now being
in Japan and all but that will I'll wait
for you yeah wait for me please I wait
what are we going to if you want to if
you were to collab with me what would
you want to do
H me thinking of a collab G I like but I
do like yapping I think you're a good
yapper what about freaking MMR PES
that's
one thing we have very big in common oh
my god let's play an MMO so we can Yap
together and grind so fun let's grind
let's
grind I love grinding in those like
anime freet to-play anime M more bgs Y
and then we can dress up and then buy
cute outfits and then we can oh together
cash up so cute mm I love how like you
were talking about this in the Stream I
think but I think I was in the chat
anyway but one thing that really um
resonated with me is when you said you
like to play these games when they come
out freshly so that you can grind from
the very beginning of like day one and
you know get up to the leaderboard uh of
your class or whatever because I did
that too like that's why I was so happy
that there were new anime MPGs coming
out all the time back in the day because
like you a new chance to like be number
one in your class but now they don't
release them anymore yeah what the [\h__\h]
man I know [\h__\h] that's was like a big
conversation a rant that we had uh once
once gigy and me started talking over
Discord when she joined before her debut
or I think no after right after I think
yeah we were like what the hell why
don't they release these anymore and I
don't want them on the freaking phone I
want them on the PC why is everything on
the phone
now yeah
man I'll get a su perms for some one of
those there there's some revived ones I
I'll get those perms okay yipp yipp you
want to play maple story how do you feel
a maple story okay so me saying that I
love anime mm RPGs uh now it may come as
a shock to you that I am like I think I
tried playing maple story for like one
day and I I didn't quite understand it
like it was
overwhelming yeah there's a lot going on
in maple story is it still going it's
still going it has a big event right now
but it is really overwhelming get us the
perms for it yo I start begging okay
okay but yeah we both played like Fly
for Fun right mhm oh my God that's like
it was so it was so fun like flying
around on the freaking snowboard or
whatever that
was all the other games it was like
really unique to that game and then the
grinding was fun too yeah it was so nice
and then and then and then oh my God I
could talk forever with you about this
stuff you play eatting Eternal right
yeah I loved eating Eternal it had
[\h__\h] alpacas you know I I actually
collect alpaka plushies I I'm a
collector IRL so it's like my favorite
animal besid oh my God me too during
that phase I was so obsessed with
alpacas and the the Vocaloid song with
Alpa and then eating the T came out like
oh my God I have to collect
alpaca they were so cute it's so good I
really like that one because I think
wasn't it eaten Eternal where you can
have like basically like you switch
between the classes or yeah yeah that
was really cool oh man oh
man God damn
it we'll y later yeah let's play
together soon soon soon soon yeah
whenever you're free let me know I'll
wait for you forever happy birthday
thank you so much bye bye
okay
bye I love
her yo the mmpg connection is so strong
I'm telling you it's too
strong yeah I scored I totally did ow
W who is
here hello
shei hello what's up W hi Shi oh my God
thank you for being here I'm so excited
because like this is uh shortly after we
have you know met for the first time oh
yeah yeah you pranked me with your waas
yeah do you want to uh explain the prank
what happened I don't know I like being
vague about it I was going to tweet that
too I was going to say like she pranked
me with her wobus but people would kind
of be like what no no tell okay okay for
contacts for contacts I was heading to
the the changing room after stuff right
and I didn't bother knocking cuz I
didn't expect anyone to be in my
changing room and then and then she
started yelling
like and I'm like oh sorry so I just
spun around and like I was like I'm
naked don't come in I'm naked I wasn't
naked
though no she was super naked I was like
w but no no kidding but I I just
remember like uh like doing a 360 like
okay see like oh I guess I'm almost
there whoops you you thought you really
intruded into someone being naked in
there I'll be honest I wasn't even
thinking like if someone says like
they're naked I'm just going to assume
they're naked okay yeah thank you for
taking me seriously it's totally totally
valid you know it's like if you if you
end up going oh man it's like it's like
when you go to the restroom but like you
accidentally go to the wrong one and
then you just you just assume like oh oh
crap I better turn around and leave and
that's it you know no questions asked
you hear someone scream you leave thank
you
sorry for intruding like I was actually
yeah waiting for you and and like it
took a while like I was hiding in there
for a
while and then you finally came oh and
then and then I came out and then I saw
I I came out of
the changing room and then I I have to
say Shi you really lived up to my
expectations as as as what asori I I
remember seeing her te like oh she's
very shy like like you are very shy yeah
also like remember that tweet you did
about like somebody asking you if what
you're wearing is cosplay oh yeah yeah
yeah some random person I was very
curious about that like what could she
have possibly worn and then what you
wore that day also made me feel like oh
yeah that gives me indeed cosplay Vibes
it does I just bought it cuz it's cute
yeah it was well I guess I cosplay all
the time then yeah just a 247 cosplayer
it's not even cospl me with my with my
plushies and everything yeah your
plushies yeah I I I feel
like like we we have this like Fire
Emblem connection but like you like the
guys and I like the girls it's a bit
difficult oh yeah we we're technically
enemies yeah a
it's okay I'll spare you I'll spare you
I'll be
nice thank you yeah cuz like she is it
okay to say that you oh yeah everyone
knows I'm pretty sure everyone knows how
obsessed I am oh she carries around uh a
Dimitri plushy
everywhere that's so cute and that
wasn't even the only plushy you had yeah
I had like the god and I freaked out
some people yeah so I I wanted to prank
people with so I brought it to the
studio to like I wanted to throw it at
people but I didn't just to nice but
when I first bought it I I went down
like an elevator and I had it like
hugging me from like um I guess from the
chest and this random random couple
showed up and they were about to enter
my elevator but when I came out they
they freaked out cuz they saw it
tery I thought it was fun I thought it
was cute and then they took the other
elevator it's like but my elevator Som
they could have gone in m M well maybe
they were like worried about you being
like strangled by Godzilla oh I know
they could have joined in you know they
could have helped they would have let me
die then join in okay oh spicy
spicy well I'm so happy that we could
meet and actually Shi uh I I can now
tell you because you didn't know I but
our collab is uh confirmed oh okay cool
cool yeah just let me know the the time
then shall next week next week everybody
Wednesday Shi and waa collab
confirmed our first one-on-one collab
and it's going to be an off collab yeah
y I'm going to bring uh wait did you
already tell them what kind of cab I
didn't tell them what it is yet okay I
shall I I shall refrain them it's very
interesting
though I'm very excited for it cuz like
you were suggesting it the idea as a
joke I think but I really liked it so I
said we should go for that all right
well it it will not be my fault if
something goes wrong it and everything
will go exactly according to
Kaku yeah translational Kaku means
exactly thank you for the translation
notes thank you so much sh for being
problem happy birthday thank you she Lov
me see you see you next week byebye
byebye
[Music]
byebye oh you guys I think uh the collab
that we're going to do it will be very
fitting like it it matches Shi I think
the idea so look forward to it oh oh
oh go go
ahead
t feel t feel for
[Music]
[Laughter]
um um
okay okay ask away ask away okay we're
okay guys we're switching we're
switching translate button yeah we're
feeling sorry for you guys you can't
understand
us okay so uh
Cecilia you are new to the group now I
asked your other gen mates the same
question so uh tell me what is your
impression your image of
Taki ooh okay let me think I have to
choose my words words wisely yeah
um
um don't anger
Senpai orange orange Idol
Senpai that is true orange idle Dyson
pie
yeah that is accurate 100% thank you
orange dancing dancing orange dancing
Idol dce Empire okay I can add that's
all the words I can add for good job
good job so yeah people have been you
know looking forward to us talking
because we both speak German obviously
what that's crazy that's
crazy I mean you've probably seen it too
that people are like oh it's true it's
true German another German speaking
people say that we sound similar which I
don't think is true because I don't
think so either at all we don't even
have the same accent it's insane not at
all yeah I mean neither in German nor in
English we have this I don't think we
have the same in both languages exactly
exactly one day though we have to try
like impersonating each other and then
like streaming for the other person and
seeing if the if your chat or my chat
notices I'm so bad at impersonating the
only impersonation I can do is like
P do it do it do it oh oh people have
heard it a million times already I want
to hear it again okay again again it's
your
birthday come come come wait it's not
working today it's not working today
come oh my voice is not ready today can
you do one can you do one uh I can do uh
uh I can do
Gigi
yipp
women she says women wait that's a she
loves women she goes like pretty
women yeah but not very bad Expressions
I try and I fail and I'm bad at accents
as well because obviously we don't have
any accents right so it's very hard for
us perfect English speakers so like like
you and me is that was a was that
sarcasm yeah
okay we should do oh I have an idea for
for a collab M we should do a challenge
um uh you versus me uh We like Let
managers or so pick out like difficult
to pronounce English words or like any
kind of word that they might think we we
don't really know the real pronunciation
and then we'll see how each of us will
try to pronounce that word and then the
one who gets closest we get a
point that's a good idea that's a very
good idea we need to judge a judge that
speaks English do you know well we speak
English Okay so there's one word that
I'll test you with now not iron no um do
you know did did you play Minecraft
before yeah okay so there's a word you
can type it if you want no I'll spell it
for you there's a word where I know how
to pronounce it but I still purposefully
pronounce it wrong because it's nicer
that way uh okay b i o m e say
it
biome biom me yeah biomi
biomi of course of course wait one more
one more um pH this is not Minecraft
related uh wa is it p h l e g m p h l e
g
m
FL get out of here get out of here R
away FL them FL get out of here cilia
you can't like come here and then wait
wait does this mean I won wait wait is
this no this was not the this was not it
yet this was just the test warm up a
warm up yeah of course the collab B is
over so I will soon challenge you and
and win I will win okay I believe in you
but I also believe in myself we'll see I
accept the challenge the one word I
struggle with a lot is like when there's
a th sound a soft one and sometimes I i'
say just s instead so like something
like South sometimes I just say
South when I speak
interesting yeah the one I struggle
because for me it's the other way like
when I when South for me it just turns
into a complete F South oh oh F you do
the F yeah remember I think it's very
German like to uh replace it with a s
yeah yeah it only happens if I talk fast
like I can say South but it's just it's
when there's a soft s and the T soft th
sound I struggle a little bit but it's
okay it's okay we can do it we can
challenge I mean beat the English
language okay one one one last thing one
last thing okay I can't understand how
about um okay uh t h i c k
uh t h i j h s thick yeah and thigh oh
thighs get out of here get out of here
get out of here okay thank you
bye happy
birthday che che
[Music]
yes
Nissa happy birthday my queen of fum and
bi
me grer is no it's your birthday in 20
minutes you can't cry I've been what you
call can you say I've been upstaged is
that what you say no is it upstaged or
betrayed bet definitely betrayed
mhm nurse I miss you I miss you too now
that we're in the same place I was
thinking when I heard you metant shiori
I was like what before me before me well
well you met shod before uh no I mean
she met you before I got to since he got
but you also met me before but yeah you
mean yeah yeah yeah but this is
different this is different I'm Miss but
we're meeting soon yeah I don't know
when after the heat is not so hard yeah
the heat is really bad I'm like I know
it I know it I've been going to like
Japanese summer for so many years now
but I still every time I I come here I'm
still always
like yeah it's bad but I'm excited to
see you soon I I think we have like
similar m skin types and all that
because like I I hear you like also
struggle the same way like with like
sweat and all that being immediately
soaked when you go out
mhm yeah I mean I don't know if I'm
immediately soaked but I'm immediately
stinky same same yeah I got really bad
heat rash actually and I'd never had it
before where do you get the heat rash
all over my like upper thighs it was
pretty bad should I should I rub some
lotion
on yeah you got some userin cream is
userin userin userin userin I Thinkin
okay I don't know what that is but I'll
go get it it's like e u c r i n c r okay
I'll get it and I'll rub it gently on
your
F thank
you how are you on this day of your your
birthday I'm I'm very really relieved
that so far I've had no awkward waiting
times between calls yeah you still have
two more people waiting for you right
now there yeah hopefully there's still
more coming though so good yeah
hopefully yes sing me sing me a Opera
birth happy birthday please okay
wait is this is this a Reverb that's
megaphone is this
Reverb probably but it gets a little bit
canceled out by
Discord wait okay yeah Discord shut up
wait let me let me quick let me quick is
it is it okay to sing you happy
birthday
okay we'll we'll have the the cut off
the cut off then you said Opera yes I
okay I I'll attempt I don't know how
this going to
sound happy birthday to
you happy birthday to you
happy
birthday happy
birthday happy birthday to
you thank you happy birthday k I love
you no I love you
too I miss you so much like this whole
time when you're like Japan
Ark you know I can't blame you because
you're you know you're obviously busy
and time zones are different so yeah I'm
dying yeah I know my jailbirds too are
like where are you and I'm like I'm
sorry I kind of hope that like even
though this is an exciting time that
will result in exciting results I hope
that soon for both of us things will go
back to normal and we can just like uh
have Discord calls again after I'm done
streaming or before your streamer so
like like we of did
before my cutie pie
Senai well soon we'll go get tea tea and
cakes really are we doing that I please
take me to a dessert Buffet I would be
so happy I'll try okay I'll try to
figure something out yeah yeah all right
all right all right not many not many
empty schedule days but somewhere
between we'll squeeze something in well
we'll find some time okay sure about it
I'll take you and I'll take you to the
that date and then I'll bring you to a
Japanese love hotel and Rob the userin
into
Oh yay I'll get to experience a love
Hotel hey y spicy spicy
spicy okay before it gets too hot in
here
yes better you want me to leave I see
all right I'll send in the next
participant
love you
goodbye I really miss her I'm not just
saying that I really
[Music]
do I'm a little bit
flustered
hello hello hello
hello happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you can you sing it in like
Skiby
SK cuz that's kind of like your
specialty
[Laughter]
yeah
please happy birthday to
youy
birthday nice nice you're really so good
at that for real
I'm going to have a skib
birthday happy
birthday so uh this is our first time
talking
publicly I know yeah even though like
I've been in your chat and requesting
songs that are 100% like perfect for
you yes yes I I did enjoy the Christmas
song I do love Christmas tunes Christmas
in the middle of the
summer look the in in where gigg is from
FIA they have Christmas in July so I I I
take that oh what what yeah I think I
like saw I love Christmas so I saw um
someone say the term Christmas in July
over there and stuff and that's I was
like o I'm going to steal this cuz I
love Christmas tunes so I was like o
I'll just make an excuse It's Christmas
in July just F that generally like
Mariah Carey has like like the belts and
all that that you seem to like and be so
good at so ex you're excelling in that
so I think you should sing more Mari
care oh I'll I'll I'll definitely take a
look into it Senai thank you so much you
seem are you
tired um a little bit but there's people
sleeping as well so I'm not being too
loud I see well you're still new so I
hope you're not like overworking
yourself or anything you know take it
easy and like enjoy your time Senpai
comes to collect my soul oh yeah yeah
did you have fun playing with everybody
in crab game yeah it was super fun yeah
it's very a very chaotic game but yeah
it was super fun hopefully we can play
next time
K yes yes I was a bit too busy with
other things so I couldn't participate
oh no it's understandable you have you
have your birthday going on it's my
birthday that's your excuse you just go
and you're like it's my birthday yeah
well uh BB um I I think I am like guilty
of coming up with that name uh I would
like your blessing to continue calling
you that no it's cute yeah really it's
cute yeah you have no issue with it no I
I I well one I I thought someone was
going to say that anyway just to make it
short and sweet but you okay no no I
think it's cute cuz like I I mean
especially as you came up with a senpai
yeah cuz I I brought it up like the
first time we had a conversation with
like
everybody when we first met you guys I
was like can I call you e RB
herb it's good it's like genius because
your name is so long girl what are you
expecting I'm intimidating it's my
intimidating name it do be intimidating
I'm the Scarlet Queen in it no but in it
but I can't be like uh intimidated by
like a kohai so you
know look fire gals fiery gals going to
stick together what did you think of my
accent just
now I thought it was great
fun I love like talking like you guys
but people say like sometimes what I'm
trying to do it sounds more Australian
or sometimes sounds more Scottish or I
don't know um I'm I'm trying I I can't
really like look if you don't do it how
you going to get better and also yeah so
it's fine thank you so much I don't mind
one last
question uh I asked your gen mates the
same question so please answer what is
your image of
takanashi my image beautiful hardworking
passion pass Idol passion mhm true yeah
you are you are incredibly hardworking
and it's it's it's I respect that a lot
K senpai thank you so much you work very
hard on screen and behind the scenes
that is true with your dancing your
singing your everything yes I hope you
can join me dancing and singing sometime
too that would be that would be a dream
come Che that would be absolutely
wonderful thank you so much her thank
you I hope one day you can teach me the
accents properly and we can have a full
on British or collaboration wait you say
collab I heard that I found that really
interesting the way you say collab is
collab yeah British collab let's do
it I I could teach you some BR well
great zardan slang
great exian yes
surely thank you so much ER thank you
have a great have a great rest your
birthday K thank you so much byebye take
care good night byebye team M bye it's I
think it's early morning though for her
I don't know if she's really going to go
back to
sleep we have 9 minutes left on the
Birthday Countdown oh my god oh oh my
God I think I'll get there if I listen
more to her streams you know I think I'm
going to pick up some words like car
carab I don't think I would have like
tried to pronounce it that way
otherwise uh I see
someone still there in the waiting room
but she's muted both ways don't know if
she's going to come over
here her C is unbelievable yeah her is
really strong Ana right where the [\h__\h]
is she she hates
me I don't know if she will show up
like I I totally did not ask her cuzz
why would I want her
there yeah I did have some more
uh seemingly interested people so maybe
we'll just have to wait a little bit for
them to oh wait actually she came in oh
oh oh
guua here here
Mor hi hello gu happy birthday I know
it's almost it's what 9 minutes left to
your vday yeah it's fine you can say it
okay cool 9 minutes left here's what all
right I'm going to say my happy birthday
here we
go Felix
natalis what language is that Latin oh
wait why did you go for that did you
notice a pattern no because I took AP
Latin wait was there a pattern I asked
some of the like justice members to like
tell me happy birthday in different
languages oh yeah actually chat spoiled
it for me I didn't know that it was uh
supposed to be something that you told
me so I looked something up ahead of
time Latin huh yeah Latin oh is that a
jerk because like you're GM beeper Latin
is dead and all that is that a joke yeah
Latin is a dead L true Latin is a dead
language also momento Mori it's a dead
language and a dad language huh Dad and
Dad yeah that's right all the dads know
Latin I'm terrible at Latin actually I
forget all of it but I thought that I
would speak it to I also learned it in
school but only yeah I was like in a
language school and the first language
that besides English that we would be
learning was Latin and it would have
been like the base for all the other
languages that we would have learned but
then I dropped out because uh it was
just nah not for me not a Latin fan no
not at all but vichi am I right yeah
that's right mhm yep uh uh um unter wel
no that's German I forget all that is
gerelt and I I'm the I'm the Zen and fra
Zen and yeah yeah I
remember oh good job German always works
I'm so proud of you than I did my best
keie how you doing right now oh I'm I'm
surviving I I'm surviving you had a fun
collab and yay yeah it was good it was a
good time it was a good way to wake up
in the morning I needed to wake up
morning it wasn't that early I mean yeah
but at the same time I can't sleep in
these it is early morning whenever we
say it is because we may have [\h__\h] up
sleep schedules just because we wake up
at sometimes maybe 2:00 p.m. that
doesn't mean that it's not morning for
for us it's morning in that moment
exactly that's how it is agree that is
how it is that's how it be I know that
you're busy are you are you like out
about traveling or I'm in the Glorious
nipon okay cool needed to confirm I
wanted I wanted to make sure that people
knew that you're yeah it's okay people
know I'm here I like I've been here this
is like my third like if you count the
day when I arrived then this is my third
day oh okay settling in no jet lag
hitting you right no jet lag but also
not settling in I'm I had to like
immediately do stuff like dance lessons
and stuff so oh busy yeah busy I'm I'm
here on the mission
after on a mission yeah good luck with
your mission I'm sure it'll go great
thank you so much Callie are you feeling
like like healed by now are you feeling
good yeah you know honestly I feel like
um my Rehabilitation has been going well
and um actually today today is my first
day that the doctor has allowed me to to
do a light exercising so I'm going to
the gym after this and I'm going to
exercise like really damn getting right
into it yes I need to I need to respect
my health you know I got to I got to get
moving moving and grooving can't be
solitary forever what kind of like
exercises do you normally do in the gym
well it depends I mean usually I like to
run SL walk up a really high hill on the
treadmill but these days I'm trying to
focus on my arms you know so I'm lifting
weights but like small weights not like
weight lifting but like you know arm
curls and stuff like that and trying to
tone up the arms you know gumy SC
swinging yeah like you know you hold the
dumbbell and then you curl it towards
yourself and then my favorite one that's
really hard to do is te- posing with the
dumbbells a not all I need don't you
don't you do
squat you got to do squats yeah I like
squats I hold the weight and then I do
the squat but it's a little hard to do
the squats right now with the knee
situation so kind of that makes sense
I'm kind of you know being careful with
the knees but the arms the arms though
yeah I want to get my arms super swo
and and gum but it with your quest as
well I know you've got quests so my side
quest and my main quest and all I'm sure
I'll see you at some time in the middle
of all of it though maybe hell yeah yeah
our paths will cross I know our our
paths will always cross there's no way
around it there there's always an
intersection yeah it's faded it's faded
to be all connected intertwined it's all
like it's a circle in the end it's a one
big circle yep can't be helped we will
always find other so poetic wow indeed
yeah did you talk to everybody today am
I the last one uh for now yeah but I I
think I have like
somebody that just dm'd me uh who might
join in a moment in a minute or so yeah
cool I hope that you have lots of fun
and have a happy birthday and um I'm
excited to to watch your bday f
festivities yeah thank you for always
like having my back and supporting and
being part of you know my projects like
Minecraft for example yeah fun you got
to do something like that again exactly
I hope we can like do many more exciting
projects together cie I feel like we we
always you know are very
very what's the
word uh what's the [\h__\h] what's the
word it's in there uh
the d d what's the I don't know whatever
but you know can you describe it in
other words uh it's not determined
diligent diligent maybe this determined
determined that's fine let's go with
that let's go with that yeah we like
doing a bunch of different stuff
together decentralized the [\h__\h] oh
decent decentralized no I meant
dedicated dedicated dedicated yeah yeah
we're doing all kinds of stuff all the
time let's keep doing all kinds of stuff
hell yeah hell yeah wow it's almost your
birthday so I'll I'll let you go now but
but yeah let's go enjoy your birthday
Kiara and I guess I'll catch you later
yeah catch you on the flip catch you on
the flip side why K you're doing great
and remember and remember Felix hold on
a second hang on a second hold on Felix
nalis
byee peace
peace who's
Felix she
talking about PewDiePie
[Music]
or no uh good Latin she got there
wo
[Music]
oh uh there's ah there's one callar that
I'm talking about who just uh dm'd me
she might not be able to call because
she's
like in a difficult situation ah okay
let's just uh focus on the countdown for
now ah can you guys count 20 19 18 17 16
15 14 13 12 11 10
9 7 6
wow it's my
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you happy birthday happy
birthday to you happy birthday to you
it's my
birthday
y I did it I did it
it's my birthday uh in PST thank you
thank you the green ocean
tasar a wa who I know a lot of you guys
already sent super chats thank you for
that too and it's already been my
birthday in other time zones for a while
now it's actually like 16 hours into my
birthday in Japan oh uh oh oh jenma who
is right behind me sent me a
notification that hold English just
tweeted out a birthday wish for me I
guess they were waiting for PST as well
huh did they just oh yeah they were I
was like wondering today cuz I saw so
many tweets uh from the whole life uh
accounts I'm like hm they have yet to
say a single thing about my birthday
have they
forgotten seems like they also waited
for the PST time zone did they always do
that or did they just do that because I
was counting down to PST
huh hold oh thank you also JMA sent me
um a website that kfp has created kiata
year in review like a birthday website
thingy I will not show it on stream now
uh it's uh uh too big for the screen
anyway but thank you for that
you're who the [\h__\h] said you urine
review yeah did I say it so
unclearly
yeah year in review I I me I can see how
it was something like that we're not
doing a year in revie oh my
God thank you thank you thank you thank
you so much for the Super Chat is that
the shield he could have no W my neck
really hurts actually [\h__\h] I need to get
a massage I had uh dance yesterday I I
don't think I use my neck that much and
yet and yet my neck is
really muscle
sore thank you birthday birthday
birthday
yay Moy Moy also sent me birthday
message with a twerking
G wonderful
beautiful thank you so much get a good
massage later yeah I was I was hoping to
get one
show you
aware
that Hol you is not necessarily Hol what
are you talking about Hol U doesn't
exist all it only exists in your mind
and your brain really happy for this
four years your amazing con cre and
really helped me during of rough times
thank you
for you you're getting autocorrected a
lot in that message
boing don't don't wish me Bo
don't wish the Boeing on to
me it's real to me it exists in our
hearts H is real to me oh my God okay
I'll I'll relay it to
Yago than you you Bo
Bo
yay thank you
[Music]
he had with this
so this year I don't have so much
special things planned because uh their
the birthday fry life that is happening
is being delayed to be like in later
later later later not not as late as uh
last year um is coming up I've been
working on it I've been very
very dedicated I've been dedicating my
time to it a lot of it and it's
happening but besides that as a little
little bit of um you know a taste for it
tomorrow tomorrow there is Kiana
birthday 2024 by the way use that
hashtag if you have anything to say
today today's stream hashtag is not kfp
it's this
and while we doing the K plus gu I
participated in several of these before
but I've never been
like uh the one hosting one so hasht
hash yeah take all the time to polish it
yeah I will make it po po po po wait no
I will not make it po polish no no just
because Poland Poland no wait it wasn't
Poland who beat us it was Turkey I was
gonna make a Poland joke doesn't work
can't make good good jokes like that
Poland mention no it's being polished
it's being
refined I'm excited for it
yeah had some last minute changes for it
recently but it's going to get better
and
better can't wait me neither
[Music]
many many
languages are present today
ohos oh
F oh thank you
thank you thank you thank you did Ena
call you today no not yet maybe she's
still calling who knows I'm going to I'm
going to wait a little bit I I wanted to
tangent about something right it was
about Australia yeah it's so random but
I've been watching this YouTube channel
who does like challenges I think it's
called like jet lag or something like
that and the most recent one that I was
watching was uh set in Australia and it
was it just ended I just watched the
last episode yesterday but it's so good
you guys need to watch it it's so fun
you know it you know it you know it yeah
the jet like J like the game yeah yeah
yeah and and it was really interesting
because like you can in the Australia
one I was able to like see a lot of
Australia and yeah they were traveling
like through the what do you call
it states no like the parts of Australia
and uh there's like two teams it's like
a yeah like a game of tag that once they
reach a new region uh like a province
yeah or state yeah they can like put
money down there but they also have to
use that money to book flights Etc I
guess they start with like a starting
capital and in each new region there's
also new challenges they get like four
challenges or so when they arrive they
can also steal money from the other team
and but then the other team can go to
that region to like steal their region
if they put put more money down and this
and that it was it was really cool yeah
it's complicated no not really though if
you watch it like it's very very in
intuitive and
fun yeah there's just I think there was
one only one state I
think that they never went to in the end
uh and feels kind of sad maybe like
maybe that's a state that's being
ignored in Australia constantly and
that's a joke or so uh the the left one
it's like on the very
left I don't know if that's Tasmania
it's on the very
left uh on West on the
west you knew it yeah is that Tasmania
Western Australia was just completely
ignored they even went to like some kind
of small island no that was Tasmania
maybe they went on some small island
that was like at the
bottom but they also went to the desert
at the top in the north too
yeah cool stuff I want to go to
Australia I want to go to Australia oh
the island is tesia
oh Australia has upside down world
map nah no
way kangaroos there were no
[Music]
kangaroos West Australia has nothing to
go there anyway that can't be true nah I
don't believe it
I don't believe it watch out for the
drop
bears when you're there if I ever will
get
there that's like so far and so
expensive please somebody get me to
Australia my my my it's like Australia
is you know basically my home country
just a little bit extended come to dream
hack next year make it happen the
Austrian and Australia make it happen
happen looks over shoulder to
jenma jenma looks
terrified my neck really hurts I need to
stop looking over to JMA my neck hurts
too much to look
over dream hack was awesome I saw man I
saw that sounds like a good name for a
TV show right Austria and Australia it
should be a
oh thank you thank you so much
[Music]
thank you thank you thank
you worldwide chat world wide
chat thank you thank
you
[Music]
yeah it's so hot in Japan it's so
hot I'm suffering but there's actually I
think after the stream I can eat some
ice cream
[Music]
I can eat some ice cream after this
because jenma uh brought me my ice cream
my my it's it's actually I think it's
illegal ice cream because it's Kang G
time limited but the limited time is
over and yet I have access to it so that
sounds kind of illegal doesn't it The
Quon the quason I have not consumed yet
I'm waiting for the right time for them
but it's illegal it's not within the
kikan it's not within the the time that
was limited it's illegal ice
[Music]
cream
ice don't let Justice see this oh we we
we we
FG
life you're under arrest what accent is
that so
so I'm
gonna I want
to let me mute myself for a second
[Music]
okay okay so um jenma was actually you
know keeping the ice cream no I wasn't
cussing at you no she was keeping the
ice cream uh in the freezer at uh the
office and
she uh was going to give it to me one of
these days you know it wasn't going to
be today or yesterday but yesterday
there was like like like me and Gemma
were somewhere else right and then
suddenly there's this like
notification that the fridges in the
office are going to be cleaned out it's
like cleaning day or something and
they're going to throw everything out
and the ice cream even had like a note
on it that said like it belongs to
jenma and that nobody should eat it but
we were like like you know somewhere
outside and we were like not able to
like you know save the ice cream in
reality we were supposed to go somewhere
it has a note yeah but then there was
like this big drama like oh what are you
going to do what are we going to do how
can we get there faster about to throw
it out how much time do we have oh no
only like 30 minutes until they throw it
out what do you mean oh no and then and
then uh yeah it was like big big clutch
black company how dare they they don't
even know they don't even know that this
ice cream isn't even really genma ice
cream it's it's it's ice cream from a
talent right from one of the one of the
talents of whole life English myth yeah
and they almost did a crime that I would
have never forgiven them and jenma
rushes over and saves the ice cream
rescues the ice cream she went on a side
quest she saved the ice cream and now
it's here with us and I can enjoy it
yeah she came in in
clutch hallelujah thank God man Yago
apologizing for the ice cream incident
yeah I'm expecting a like a apology
letter official one typed out nicely on
Twitter or even a YouTube
video no it's okay nothing happened it
only almost happened would have been a
really sad
day I think um another
another staff member who was with us in
the moment she also tried to save the
ice cream so she like tagged like all
kinds of like company people who might
be in the office she was like don't
throw out the ice
cream and they must be wondering what's
so important about this ice cream it's
just ice cream but even if it's not ice
cream from me don't throw it out don't
throw it out it's not like it was like
moldy or anything ice cream was good
forever going to eat it after this I may
have no birthday cake with me but I will
have birthday ice cream
yeah yeah should have put a note saying
it's yagos that would have made it safe
but then what if Yago eats
it that wouldn't be good either well
maybe he wouldn't eat it because he's
very healthy does he ever eat ice cream
he's he's today was like Dodgers game
right he's
there what what would this have happened
would they have attempted to throw out
the ice cream if yagu was in Japan at
the time
huh the world is not safe when Yago is
not
around he's here yeah I saw photos I saw
photos of him
there
what he ate a Dodger's dog what a hot
dog a dog just hot dog or what I didn't
know that's a
thing he's got a panel at ax ah then the
the the the what's it called good smile
uh panel I think that's what it
is it's not been
very uh attentive or like updated about
uh the ax stuff that's going on I saw
they have like one big uh like one side
of the boo is uh the like the the the
world
tour uh
standies you guys can take pictures
there if you were at
ax accept the Tweet about you being gray
W the gay one day she'll be
orange one
day those standies look so good thank
you Zetta had a panel to herself it was
nice what do you mean wasn't that
planned I did see like some footage of
her and some of the other panels if you
can call them panels I don't know waa
forever
gray don't say
that don't say that one the announcement
to G was so
funny yeah like that's that was like the
typical like baseball stadium voice
right the way he was talking sounds so
familiar and he introduced the whole
life
talents so
weird I wonder like I saw there was like
a lot of people waiting for the
merchandise like there was a long line
but I wonder like those are obviously
there because of the whole life thing
right but were there any any normal
people I'm sure there's a lot of
Hardcore Dodgers fans who go to any any
of the Dodgers games and then I
wonder what what they thought of
this I was one of them but you were one
of the merch people yeah not not one of
the normal
fans oh it was the longest
line apparently in Dodge's Stadium
history maybe the longest merch line
yeah
shees the merch line was massive they
should have put up more than one merch
stall is this only for one day or are
they doing it tomorrow too yeah I need
to watch Wiki's Vlog too I saw a preview
like one clip of it there was a single
merch boo see they needed just make more
merch boobs but they probably didn't
anticipate this
much that's always like the lesson after
every single thing it's like oh we yeah
we didn't anticipate this
much oh oopsy should have um prepared
more or so always always the
thing honestly I also didn't anticipate
this much I would have underestimated it
too yeah wait so is it just one
day or two days wait how long is
this you guys are powerful whole life
yeah powerful maybe we can make our own
baseball team maybe we can like sponsor
a team or or make one a team maybe we
can buy a
team baseball is very beloved in Japan
too so I feel like cover could consider
that let's buy a Japanese baseball team
I don't know like sports teams get
bought
right that's a thing you can buy
majority shares in the team Nintendo did
that what what team do they
own JMA are you hearing this she's
definitely hearing this
[Music]
collab with MLB bird team bird team what
oh com on for the red super chat thank
you why would knock it out of the park
oh no no I'm I'm I don't think
I I've never tried uh baseball before I
don't think I would be able to hit a
ball I would need a lot L of
training the MLB team is valid at 10
billion I don't know if cover can afford
that maybe if we sell our 3D uh Studio
maybe
then how much was the value of this 3D
Studio again it's a public value right
how much is it can we sell and then buy
a 2.7
billion really uh 20 million 30 million
which one is it 2ill 2 billion
yen two how much did you say it was team
two billion versus 10 billion or what
was
it 10 billion [\h__\h] maybe there a cheaper
team we don't have to get MLB how much
are they selling Dodgers
for is that an
option not in not in Yen oh
yeah uh a little league
team would be billions at the moment uh
I'll can we haggle I'll buy for two
billion thanks for 50 freaking
memberships
wa thank you so much thank you that's
going to take a lot of super chats who
says we're using my super chats we're
selling the Fredy Studio
decid after I record my 3D birthday live
after of
course
[Music]
hey nice gift nice thank you more more
members welcome to the
party we need to start the multi-billion
dollar fast food chain what do you mean
what do you mean don't destroy my my
rooll play my RP it's real it already
exists for a long time
eggs egg eggs egg yo is going to throw
out the first pitch and also every other
pitch wait why did why did he not get to
do that at the Dodger Stadium he should
have like they call like celebrities or
is that a Japan
thing is that an Asia thing
or I think I've seen that a lot of times
before don't they do that in America
too you do that too right and he did do
that before in Japan I think
they do that too e he's there it's whole
life day he didn't get to throw
one why why why was was he not like best
girl
enough God damn
it Riot Riot Riot Riot oh another 50
memberships thank you wow wow wow wow
wow wow scam
come for the red super chat thank you
it's only the first club or maybe maybe
there's a second time where he can throw
a
bowl throw it normally you always throw
it right is there not an option to hit
it I think I only ever see people
throwing it not hitting
it
oh h
[Music]
oh because it's supposed to be the first
pitch
a
hold happy birthday thank you I I
honestly this is just a countdown
tomorrow I'm so excited to show you my
merchandise but there's really not uh I
don't have that much like stuff prep
besides Okay so
so my sorry yo had a whole training AR
to throw the first pitch at a Japanese
baseball game yeah he was like already
ready
prepared doesn't it doesn't need to be
trained anymore looking forward to what
you
cooked I'm quite happy with
my merchandise lineups for this year
both birthday and anniversary
eh let me cook
you
m that sounds like a spoiler that maybe
it's cooking related but no it's
actually not what time does it go in
sale uh so the
stream I'm going to put up the
reservation after this is over the
stream starts at I think
7 7 p.m. yeah 7 p.m. jst and then the
merch uh will be like 1 hour in right
yeah okay okay
my
neck let's book a massage let's book a
massage I'm basically just like trying
to stall until this one person can call
man I
I
[Music]
I'm Salo my beloved
is it
Ana of course it is
ana
Anya hurry
up
please let me take off my
shoes actually Gemma can you get me the
ice cream let's let's do a taste test on
stream
okay she's on her way I'm alone now ji's
not listening anymore I can say all the
things I always wanted to say I had I
had her eyes staring at me from my from
my head this whole time I've been
feeling like I'm being
lasered she really does hate
you no no it's okay
[Music]
yeah no you will be
terminated okay I'll be careful I'll be
careful with what I say maybe you know
she can always watch the
[Music]
VOD T deserves some ice cream too maybe
maybe she bought some I think for the
quo she bought uh for herself too but
for the ice cream maybe not she could
have bought more she had the option to
but I think she only has one for me so
to
explain I love Baskin Robbins but
there's no Baskin Robbins in Europe
that's the oh that was fast that's the
first problem no basking Robins in
Europe
and
then in America American Baskin
Robins doesn't even have uh my favorite
flavor uh only for Valentine's I guess
what it is you already know if you watch
my streams a lot It's Love Potion
31 yeah and in in Japan Japanese people
are smart and so it's a it's a like
constant flavor not just temporary they
have Love Potion 31 throughout the whole
year
when I mess up
you yeah and they have this Kit Kat uh
collaboration while I was not in Japan
yet and there they had like several like
cups different cups like C face I guess
or
so and one of them has like Kit Kat on
top of it but the kit cat itself is I
guess for this like thing for this
collaboration that cab limited Only Love
Potion flavor
KitKat so let's see if my ice cream has
really withstood all trials all threats
wow so many that's like I got four
spoons and and a coupon to join
membership or whatever wow oh there's a
birthday
coupon wonder if I can go to 31 ice
cream and tell them it's my
birthday all right all right all
right let's
see I'm opening the package oh
[Music]
wait it's not what I expected I
think
what I mean this is uh this is one of
the collaboration things but that's not
what I expected what
the ah okay it's not what I thought you
were
getting
ah it's not it's not the it's not the
love
potion Kit Kat it's okay it's
literally it's not it's not Baskin
Robin's flavored kitat cat it's because
there was that too uh it's KitKat
flavored Baskin Robins like a huge cup
of
it uh well this would be good too I I I
was expecting something else that's okay
though it's good too thank you thank you
thank you thank
you oh wow it's like literally like Kit
Kat oh but it smells like normal
chocolate ice
cream let me take a picture of
this I take a
picture that's why there's so many
spoons it's like this huge
cup okay let's just pretend that this
was what I wanted all
along picture
time okay as always I send on this
[Music]
scch there w
Discord let me show you guys what it
is I
wonder I wonder if there there's been
Kit Kat flavors before
for this where did it
[Music]
say where is it
here save image ah
[Music]
here this
is my uh birthday
cake my birthday ice cream cake yeah
it's round it's pretty big you could you
could say it's a birthday ice cream
cake yeah and okay you can't see it but
the side it's basically the the opposite
side from what you see here on the side
it has like like tiny ball
kitkats
imagery it's
cute so let's see if it really just
tastes like chocolate ice cream or if it
actually tastes like KitKat but I also
feel like um the KitKat chocolate tastes
different in Japan a little bit not
completely but
it has like a swirly pattern inside of
uh dark brown and like milky
[Music]
Brown ta you can come in and call by by
way
hi okay it
tastes just like
normal chocolate ice cream it doesn't
really taste like Kit Kat I mean Kit Kat
is also just chocolate but wait what is
there no like waivers waiver bits inside
that would be like a smart way to do it
but I don't see any thing besides ice
cream here no no wave wavy thingies
it's a Ice Cream review stream
yeah
wait what was that that was Tiny was
that something have I struck
gold hello oh wait I see
something
oh there's
[Music]
something
something it's not it's it's too small
to I'm not gaslighting myself it's
something really small um that is so oh
wait no it's oh I found something I
found something I'm like digging for the
ice cream I found I
found
no okay okay
so let me take a picture
[Music]
all right I found it's like I found
gold that should be I think a whole
chunk of a ball KitKat like a
ball-shaped
[Music]
KitKat
wait what is it oil I'm becoming an oil
uh what's the word oil oil uh
oil was it
oil oil Baron
yes
T you see that so you can tell generally
it's just really smooth chocolate ice
cream but you see in the middle of the
spoon there I found something when I dug
deep what is this
stream let me try
[Music]
M um
oh
okay
huh oh
doesn't really taste like a Kit Kat it's
surely supposed to be a kit
cat there was
a um a hint of waivers in
that
but it wasn't
[Music]
crunchy after Taste of the
chocolate from the chocolate
[Music]
bit it's it's
certainly uh
differentiable from the rest of the
chocolate ice
cream H and besides that yeah there's
like the tiniest microscopial
bits of something I think chocolate more
[Music]
chocolate Gourmet
Wawa can youat a normal kit kat and tell
us what it tastes like of course it
would taste like Kit Kat not like
European Kit Kat but is it because I got
it
illegally no it was obtained in in a
legal way but now it's
illegal M no
huh oh oopsie
oh let me hide the cter cuz jenma sent
me something um yeah so what I let me
just show to JMA what I thought I was
getting
um this
cup this one where I think this this is
probably the same ice cream as this but
it just comes with the it's a kabande
with the love portion 31 kit
C they wouldn't maybe they wouldn't uh
you can't take away for sure you can do
take away it's okay though this is what
I have right now I guess
yeah um this but just in in a big
cup oh oh that's ice cream cake yeah I
got this okay happy break time share
pack made with KitKat
r no it's fine I I I I got the main ice
cream that is used in the collaboration
so share it yeah and if we have many
spoons JMA will be able to eat some too
yeah maybe we should put it back into
the freezer though for
now
M honestly
the ice cream the main ice cream is
really good it's a really good chocolate
ice
[Music]
cream yummy
okay okay let's return it to the freezer
for now and then later we can eat more
that was good it was good it was very
good just
uh the Kit Kat was the Kit Kat dominance
was uh a little bit too
weak that's my professional
opinion okay now Z was in the chat is
she not going to call me let me write to
her call me
[Music]
never going to get that uh basket Robin
sponsorship
now say that tweeted she left her phone
at
isus
what
[Music]
n wait let me just like maybe remind
some people I mean I don't mind like you
know generally I don't mind ending it
I'm mostly just staying here for one
specific
person giving them some buffer
[Music]
time there
okay I have sent out one last
call to uh Lou
just why didn't she give it to me in the
call there's
art art art art art art art art art art
art art what do you mean there's art art
art what do you mean there's art art
art what she like still finishing it or
what what no don't save it as a jff
don't save it as a
jff save it as a j pack please oh did it
work she was working on
this no way
o o hi are you still Al I'm still Al laa
oh my God hi laa what the
[\h__\h] La Laura just up uploaded a a super
cute fan art of
me I'm glad you like it
yeah okay wait chat is a little bit
confused uh uh gigy and narissa were
still together in the voice chat waiting
around I'm having I'm having cute time
with
myel I'm intruding just
chatting were you like still drawing
this why I'm surprised you didn't give
it to me in the
[Music]
call I was going shy you shy no W I was
waiting to countdown oh my God it's so
cute thank you w nice thank you oh I
gave you a good opportunity to draw some
shiny
FES
wow it's it's a little sketchy but I
hope you like it no it looks perfect it
looks so refined this is sketchy what
are you talking about the only sketchy
thing about it is that you didn't show
it to me during the call right away
I want to surprise you it's so good I I
was very surprised
indeed a thank you so good I love it so
much a new Kiara phone background done
by it has a really good
format happy birthday thank
you thank you to the other yeah yeah now
is my birthday indeed happy
birthday
you I actually just four years old yeah
four years I just ate like ice cream on
stream
I it was like a Time limited uh Baskin
Robins KitKat
flavor really good but it just tastes
like normal chocolate ice
cream it's K that's that's disappointing
no but it's it's it's a very good
chocolate ice
cream I bet you know I forgot to tell
you since I've come here I tried the
Love Potion 31 I've never had Baskin
Robins in the States but I think you're
right it's like the best flavor
yeah she gets it she gets it wait have
you do do you have you had basket Robins
before too yeah did you try love potion
31 no no it's the best one I need to try
yeah it's my favorite one I try yeah
I'll try for Kaba boost I'm going to
order in Love Potion 31 remember that
it's like a how would you describe it
narissa how would you describe it it's
like it's got like little chocolate
chunks but then it's got like strawberry
but like it's not like Japanese
strawberry flavoring usually is I don't
usually like strawberry flavoring
anywhere but like the one in Love Potion
31 is like really good I don't know how
to describe it would you would you
actually say it's strawberry cuz I'm
never really sure about it if it's
actually I don't think it's straberry
it's just some Berry mix it's it's some
Berry I presume it's strawberry but I
guess it might not it's raspberry
Rasberry yeah that's why it's so good
then it's like raspberry with like
regular vanilla and chocolate and it's
like mixed together it's really good I'm
ordering right
now I'm doing it now yeah actually there
was like um you know how how what I just
ate was a Kit Kat
flavored uh chocolate ice cream they
actually for the coll evation they also
had uh laugh portion 31 flavored Kit Kat
so the other way around yeah that sounds
so good I should have bought that what
yeah yeah you you got to keep your eyes
open on like time limited things while
you're in Japan because Japan is like
the country of time limited
Kang I wanted to have like a cheesecake
that was with banana and soda caramel
and I went like the first of July and it
was over because they they were doing
that just for June and it was so sad
yeah you got to you got to pay attention
to the time I was glad I didn't miss the
Family Mart choco mint party choco mint
party yeah I felt like it only lasted
like a week like they had like a ton of
like different choco mint stuff and like
one of them included like a Choco mint
drink now it's like all gone like it was
all gone like a week after it started
and I was like are you kidding me no I
don't even like choco mint so whatever I
I think mint is overrated and it's I
like Min I'm on your side GG wait but
speaking of chocolate I saw yesterday in
the convenience store I saw you guys did
you see the the Kuro uh like
collaboration I have there's like some I
don't know what it is but I've seen it
chocolate flakes oh like flakes covered
Corn Flakes covered in chocolate I think
I saw it with cor on the top of it so
cute oh yeah I saw it yeah yeah yeah I
remember flakes yeah crun what was it
yeah her flakes like from when she
doesn't shower for a long time and she
gets biky oh wow
okay
sense I was going to buy it cuz like I
feel like it's it's the perfect
breakfast like it's it's in this package
that looks like you're just supposed to
eat it like that as a snack but I feel
like you can just pour milk over it and
eat it like like normal corn
flakes actually that should that sounds
tasty o yeah yeah okay it seems like I
finally have gotten uh another caller so
I'm going to move out of the way have
fun girls here okay have
fun happy birthday thank you happy
birthday maybe I'll come back
later yeah they were just like chilling
there this whole time now someone not
Ana
someone someone is um someone told me
she can call me so I moved out this is
so good Mama Mia M literally Mama Mia
Mama
Mia she will be the new Mommy because
I'm going to say mama mia the whole time
I see her art so happy oh my
God like she's like you know she's a
blessing just like Ena like oh someone's
birthday let's draw them oh new outfit
let's draw them oh anniversary let's
draw them let's [\h__\h] go let's [\h__\h]
go
woohoo I love it it's so good I'm going
to cherish
that I'm going to use it for thumbnail
for
sure um our new uh kid in the
block P Drew this
guys oh oh she's calling here
okay hello
hello I'm calling from my phone yay y
That's okay ta hello yay happy
birthday did you just wake
up
yeah I woke up and then no cuz I woke up
and I was like oh my God it's W's
birthday and I just went to your just
like K birthday Kiara Channel a she's
already on I was like oh I missed it oh
my God I think Zed sleepy Zeda is so
cute I might fall in love
no wait that's a good thing
yes are you are you where where are you
right now I'm I'm on my
bed is are you at are you are you are
you in
Indonesia yeah okay uh for now for now
what
sure but then isn't it like what time is
it in indes right now oh it's like
almost 300 p.m. uhhuh Mama Mia well it
might for well in my in my defense I had
like a an event last night and then I
went home at like 4 or something cuz I
stayed over at do you mean
ax yeah the ax it was like it was
starting at 2: a.m. at my time and then
I went to resan place and then I went
home at like 4 or 5 and then I left my
phone there I heard someone in the chat
said that so which what with what phone
are you calling
me I'm using like personal phone I love
my work phone so like my manager can't
contact me oh no well this is a good
excuse to just not work
today or I can stream in VI a PNG tuber
I guess
really maybe what are you eating I saw
that you were eating ice cream I was
eating ice cream yeah from like Baskin
Robins there was like a kid Kat
collaboration wait is it true that they
call Baskin Robins like the 13 something
yeah sa1
sa1 no way it's not I know it's funny
that it's actually really confusing
indeed cuz like I I got I think I I
didn't know about Baskin Robbins before
I came to Japan so I got to know it as
31 oh wait really yeah because oh
because there is 31 Flavors
apparently wait there is it's also in
the logo like the number 31 is very oh
yeah I saw that it was in the logo but I
was like when I saw the logo the first
time I was like yeah well I didn't
really see the 13 at first maybe I'm
just color
blind well is I want to try is there Bas
Robins in Indonesia there is but I don't
think there's Kit Kat flavor or like the
gold stuff that you mentioned hey do you
know love potion
31 Love Potion wait there's a love
potion yeah it's like a a a flavor a
very popular flavor in Japanese Baskin
Robins they have it like all the time
but in America it's uh only Valentine's
time limited so maybe in Indonesia it's
also time limited I don't know wait love
potion what what kind of flavor is it
it's raspberry and it has chocolate
hearts in
it I'm talking too much about Baskin
Robins today like I'm constantly talking
about Baskin Robins we need to stop
talking about Baskin Robins I'm
promoting them too much you were eating
it yeah I'm talking to everybody about
it God damn it free advertisement ah not
sponsored not sponsored sponsored CLA
please s how you doing how have you been
doing are you stress I'm doing great
just busy cuz I think the ig's are busy
cuz we're leading up towards the what is
it called the August Independence Day so
we're just like doing homework and all
that stuff yeah yeah yeah yeah me too me
too for other reasons many concerts all
then concerts is
great yay worldwide concert can you sing
me Happy Birthday in
Indonesian yeah
uh
uh uh sorry I momentarily
forgot you
[Music]
the lyrics is basically like uh blow
your candles or like hope you have hope
you wait not die hope you have old age
wait that's that's not the right answer
hope you live for a long very long time
oh thank you thank you I mean I guess
you can say hope you die to a phoenix
because
uh can't get anyone but some there there
were two people somebody said that's not
it and another person said isn't that
the Christmas
song are you did you get the right
song wait that is the right song though
really some people are doubting you but
I like the melody no it's correct okay
somebody says it's correct it's the
right song
okay what
I like your first version more anyway
yeah it was more
interesting oh no I just noticed that
you have um my icon on the screen
yeah
it's that's your fault that's your fault
for having that your Twitter profile
picture wow I hope you have a good
birthday wow I hope to see you soon
hey appreciate it thank you for showing
up you're so sweet
also so D good and Morgan
goodg good and Morgan
can okay I was about to say that I was
about to say that your opinion was wrong
about chle Min chle Min is
[Music]
great that's all so so sorry so sorry
sorry to I mean I mean of course I mean
I I'm not saying it's not great I'm sure
a lot of people in the world are
enjoying it it's just not one I'm not
one of the enjoyers I suppose it's great
it tastes like
toothpaste wow sweet things should not
taste like toothpaste that is exactly
the problem you literally brought up the
issue with
it you got to embrace the
floss if you like toothpaste flavor that
much then instead of eating ice cream
you could just like constantly eat
toothpaste uh you know what I think you
know what we should do an off collab and
eat choco Min together maybe that will
change your mind I mean I I've had it
before but I it's a promise byebye no
way byebye happy
birthday I fight as she was about to
say we like just like uh Rea and Ollie
did it I was thinking she's going to say
we should do an off collab where we
brush each other's teeth like Oli and uh
it I thought that's where we were
going ah she made a very one-sided
promise yeah I mean I'm always happy if
she wants to do something like that I
would not say no to it but eating
chocolate mint uh ice cream should not
be the main part of it no no no
no flashbacks
[Music]
yeah but I think my argument is right if
that's the flavor you're looking for
then just eat
toothpaste I'll go back into the server
cuz she called me via
DM go back into the server and wait it's
been 2
hours I said I was going to do like 2
hours M do you think do you think she
will show up
guys I can't end this without our yearly
birthday
call
Ana my neck
hurts
Anya
maybe it's it's okay actually actually
it might be fine because uh
I'll I'll just say it she's part of this
tomorrow yeah
so she is part of this so maybe it's
okay she can also call in if she wants
to let me move myself
down so over no no this counts it counts
it counts there's a tomorrow yeah it's
not anony over no
[Music]
I've leaked the plan for
tomorrow that's
illegal what this is even better it's
even
[Music]
better it's okay we'll deal with this uh
tomorrow maybe I can get her to call
tomorrow as well we'll make it happen
yeah so now I will continue to eat ice
cream and uh do some more dancing U
thank you guys so much for watching my
birthday
[Music]
countdown tomorrow 7 p.m. or 10: a.m.
waa usual no not 10
a.m.
12 noon what usual time I don't freaking
know you'll see and yeah ah the the real
I don't know why this year I'm so
confused and I'm celebrating this a day
later uh let's just adjust to what's
happening I'll see you there tomorrow
and jman we thank you guys so much for
the super chats I love you guys I hope I
can find some time to uh read everything
soon yes it will be archived it's only
uh archivable songs don't worry about it
you can watch the VA if you can't be
there I got Hol plus notification for
your K stream what it's not even up yet
what thank you
Don Waba fourth
birthday hey I am
older yay will there be limited merch oh
uh yeah yeah yeah yes yes there will
be there will be but but I'm sure you
you can get it if you dare live then you
should be able to get it acrylic stand
no yeah sound those alarms limited
yeah I'm confused too I I I I somehow
somewhere last year when I was signing
all my things I was like kind of
committed to not doing limited uh that
much anymore but somehow I'm still doing
it it just happened so
four awesome years four awesome
birthdays you told us that there won't
be limited stuff this
time is it is it limited for anniversary
or for
birthday uh but then no no for
anniversary right or we don't know yet
okay I think no for anniversary there
they will be limited for
birthday okay uh you said there will be
limited for both did I really well at
least Le for now for birthday there will
be okay okay okay okay okay okay thank
you so much for uh watching see you
tomorrow for the birthday
K does did I say that already did I say
already I think I did byebye I'm going
to go dance going to go
dance will the the also be available on
gek Jack yes but probably a smaller
amount yeah
what to
[Music]
super
oh
[Music]