thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
hello
Kitty Keys
attention please
oh my gosh you're cut off
your hand was cut off sorry I fixed that
hi guys
attention please I'm raining from whole
life ID generation 2 and we have a very
very very special orange guest today
what's your name pretty lady
ah
um
[Music]
oh nice uh I also know uh
sorry my German still hasn't improved
yet I'm kind of stuck you know it's like
a pause pause game
oh my God it's always the same yes right
what how do you say I like you in German
again
I love you oh if you leave a dish like a
different smile yes
yes yes yes you are you are yeah S S
Type S Type S type
and between s m you're s because you
always want to hit people but it's a you
know it's a it's a punch of love you
know it's how I show my love you know
like so like uh
[Laughter]
yes yes what is it what is it
[Music]
[Applause]
do you know what that means do you know
what that means I love you yeah oh my
gosh I didn't teach her that I didn't
teach her that I heard it before uh
you've heard it before nice nice nice
nice nice nice
hi today we have gathered together to do
a very very uh spicy I don't know spicy
I guess spicy drawing session we are
sharing one canvas okay okay I was like
how did you nerve the booba and okay now
it's extended DLC DLC
yes so
um we were thinking before that we would
want to do like oh what if we do like a
Halloween themed thing you know and then
Kim was like yeah let's do it and so
and so what what
is that [\h__\h] stickers
oh
no I have to answer it's my kind of
sensor yeah okay
spicy yeah what was I saying yeah and
then I wanted to involve you guys in
this you know so I asked and you know in
my Twitter if we were to go
trick-or-treating together what kind of
outfit do you think you know we would
wear what's a good outfit combo and some
of you guys actually gave us uh you know
quite the hmm spicy answer I mean not
really spicy but you get what I mean but
I think we have settled on you know what
fits us the most right the one we
discussed before
yes wait wait what you were the one who
picked it I feel like there's two two
that could have fit us really well oh
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait okay
then
the one with the Dogo and the one with
the you know
um
yeah that one that one yeah because
before we played uh we put a fox right
yeah
mama
[Music]
I lost my cursor I I don't I don't know
where my cursor is anymore it's so
confusing I see it on my screen I see it
on my other monitor it's okay hello
[Laughter]
thank you for coming
yes
[Music]
okay okay should I get rid of the boobs
uh up to you do you want to Nerf it
forever how could you
and so yeah we'll be drawing something
new so let me get rid of this beautiful
yeah
I also Drew earlier to like test stuff
but I erased it and she didn't raise her
I shouldn't have erased mine I should
have erased it like I was like why don't
you keep it uh true but I didn't really
I didn't think of it
about drawing on live stream it makes me
so nervous and I feel like you know
because I don't draw regularly anymore
so when is it because I I don't like
properly draw for many many many years
I'm like so out of practice and I need
like to fix everything one by one so it
doesn't look like [\h__\h] but then if I if
I have to show the progress of when it
still looks like [\h__\h] to people publicly
on stream I feel so embarrassed
that's okay I mean that's kind of the
same for me too you know I haven't drawn
like in a while and these days when I
draw on stream it's normally just like
Doodles and stuff like that so don't
sweat too much about it you know we're
here to you know but even Doodles it's
better than nothing because you still
get a little bit of practice and you
know then you shouldn't you should
practice more I love
I will be drawing you
yeah yeah yeah oh yeah by the way yeah
yeah someone said that I was thinking
the same thing explain the thumbnail I'm
like oh you are barely visible on the
thumbnail and for me I have my whole
badonkadunks out there
be a nice summer picture because of
course Maldives is a lifestyle and I
think that's like one of the pictures
because like I think I want to find like
a really nice landscape picture yeah I
guess like my whole body they're okay
the reason why it's covered is because
if I don't cover it like the real thing
is pretty uh you know my clothing is not
very uh you know it doesn't really cover
my body that much for you it's uh it's
still a little bit you know it covers a
little bit for me it's even you know
it's even more open you know so that's
what I censored it with text
all right that's fine like we need the
world to see the beauty of kanashi
you were trying to get more people to
watch by showing the sexy body yeah the
sexy body of course everybody is here
for that sexy Phoenix body
okay should we announce what we're
drawing what costume we're drawing
yes we're drawing a trick-or-treat
costume a pair of
eggs and bacon costume
Kiara will be wearing the egg costume
and I will be wearing the bacon costume
that's not stupid it's cute
yeah yeah if we're doing it together
it's cute like oh my gosh
my eggs and bins so cute
right no breakfast together yes
breakfast I'm just gonna I think what
I'm gonna do is just like I'm gonna like
draw like like bust up or something yeah
yeah
I'm gonna make a small one I don't know
like do should I make more than bus stop
or not I feel like anything other than
the bus stop yeah anything other than
butter was too difficult for me spare me
please
oh I think that's Fallen I also can't do
[\h__\h] I don't remember how to draw
fingers either sometimes I have like a
like a lucky moment where the hand that
I want to draw it works it turns out
fine but sometimes it looks like Goblin
hands
censor the hands you know that's why you
know we have the you know hand holding
is yeah right so we censor it that's why
you should keep drawing people hand
holding so you sensory you don't have to
draw it
yeah
okay and the canvas though is it always
Square I feel like if it was like more
um Landscaping we would have better
space
true man but I don't know how to do it
is that even possible here I think it
might be possible but I don't know how
to do it okay that's okay yeah then then
maybe
um since since you're taller I'm gonna
like try to like you know make your head
here and you can have my head like
around here so sure somehow sure sure
okay okay okay
you're here but I want like a reference
that's not moving around
oh yeah yeah yeah
for this kind of collabs it's very
useful to use the life to do to like
look over and like cheat uh yes I
totally know by heart what she looks
like I don't I don't need to look up
photos though no I know totally I know
what's up you know like what she looks
like you know like every time I do a
drawing straight and I and then like I
draw myself I'm like I always go like
what does this what do I look like again
my ears oh this ears they look like this
I see
I'm kind of like checking myself out you
know
yeah because otherwise I don't remember
use references everybody don't be
ashamed references are your friend
[Music]
and I think by the way I threw a perfect
circle wow that's amazing how amazing
should I turn on pressure like this I
can't make up my mind
I I'm I am I I don't know I'll go with
pressure but you don't have to true I
think like because my my pen touch is
very very light so if I draw here like
some uh they they don't always pick up
my stroke so I think I'll turn oh yeah
then it has new tablets right yes yes
yes because of this collab you know my
tablet's been broken for a while so
I think it's like the cable issue but uh
I guess it's really hard to get the
cables here like I have to like buy it
somewhere else and like have it like
imported
yeah and then yeah so I don't know
rather than waiting for that I think
it's also time for me I want to sneeze
oh it's time for you to sneeze
so yeah it's time for me to change
anyways because my tablet was very very
old it's already very very old and if
you if you see the back part like some
of it is already like melting maybe like
due to exposure to heat and then you can
see like stuff it's like cracked you
know at the back like I don't want it to
accidentally like explode one day so I
was like maybe it's about time so I
bought like uh the same uh the same type
but like a different size oh yeah like I
used to use 13 inch and now mine is 16
which is I think just right for my desk
I don't know how big mine is but I think
it was a 21 or 24 or something like that
it's really big okay okay like my my I
have three monitors and they're like
overflowing the table oh
I wonder if I can like okay never mind
my gosh you're already drawing items so
slow that's always something I dropped
first I'm like taking my time because I
still can't decide like what do I want
to do
I still can't decide
like
I was like
cool yeah I was like is there a
selection tool so I can just like move
my stuff you know no I don't think there
is I don't think we have that
Monty yes mudgy this
wait I'm gonna see the reference
[Music]
eggs and bacon costume oh yeah don't you
know what an egg look like looks like
oh right no no but I just want to make
sure that it matches the reference you
know
yeah by the way like have you been Have
you ever been like you know
trick-or-treating in a costume or like
something like that
if I was then I was probably like
um
eight two
12 years old or so probably I think I
was before but yeah I think I stopped
pretty early do you do trick-or-treating
in Indonesia no it's not really like a
big thing in ID I don't think I think
like uh these days like people hold like
you know of course like parties or event
like themed like around Halloween but
the whole trick-or-treating itself I
don't think people really do that
[Music]
um
yeah yeah it's not here also it's not as
big as like in America but but
also I don't know but like when I was a
child when people were doing it but
maybe nowadays
maybe nowadays it's different children
do other things because
trick-or-treating is not cool anymore in
this generation maybe maybe maybe is it
still cool is it still cool I mean
do people still do trick-or-treating
because like I only know for movies you
know they always do it in the horror
movies
they do they go trick-or-treating in the
horror movies yes
that sounds like way too cute to be in a
horror movie yeah and usually things go
wrong
yeah by the way are you are you planning
to like color this properly or oh hell
no
keep it in sketch face or oh sure I'm
not really sure either I think it would
be nice if we could like at least like
make it a little bit nice but for
coloring now
what color is I started in the wrong
layer
I'm so stupid oh
and I moved the layer
it changed no yeah before we were before
we were like oh yeah how should we do
the layers flow like what I proposed was
like okay maybe you do layer one I do
Layer Two so you know that way we don't
erase each other's stuff by accident but
then um she was like uh maybe we should
do layer one for line and Layer Two For
Color in case you want to color and then
she gets it wrong
[Music]
I think like you know every time because
every time we enter this kind of magical
draw like we automatically like pick our
colors uh yeah yeah I was like oh well
that's okay I think that's okay it's to
show that you drew that and I drew this
okay well you know I made mistakes
already but I'll think about how to deal
with that later it's a problem for
future qawwa it's okay I don't even know
what I'm making right now yes yes future
future kiwawa future care now no problem
truly
when you go as bacon should you have
long or short hair I think short hair to
further emphasize the baconess of the
bacon
does Chad think at all good question add
empty yeah I don't know I I don't know
how your chat is but every time like my
viewers like I say something like that
they always reply with things like oocha
reflects the street or something so I
don't I have to use another you know
other things I can't really say that
they always go to the chat reflection a
streamer or something oh but they say
short indeed shorts no you know you
can't well then huh yes yes yes
of course
mmm
okay I will give short hair I think all
actually it might be even cute to give
you a new hairstyle oh but then maybe it
doesn't look like you anymore ah true
I only say some things like that like ah
true
okay I mixed I'm still thinking if I
should give you the braids like what
you're wearing now or should I like give
you you know your more regular like hair
down yourself I don't know wait okay
braid braid okay braid is kind of cute I
like it eggs and braids
eggs and braids actually normally I I
don't even like eggs and bacon like I
like eggs and bacon but normally for my
breakfast I always choose a sweet
breakfast yeah I can tell
you I mean I was literally
ourselves
uh
it's like a cultural thing right like
what you grew up with
yeah but for me I'm used to maybe like
for me honestly I'm used to more savory
breakfast because that's what everybody
at home does
mm-hmm
yummy as per the queen normally eat in
Indonesia
what I eat eggs
prepare it in a special way oh no not
really for breakfast honestly because I
think like a lot of Indonesian food like
Indonesian Indonesian food they require
a lot of preparation time you know like
because they use like all these like
spices and everything so they're not
really like breakfast food normally I
could be wrong but you know
and is there no like traditional
specific traditional Indonesian
breakfast
I think you know from you know like when
you go to a hotel for example like they
give you the oh Indonesian breakfast you
know and then like American breakfast or
something in the Indonesian breakfast
the food is normally like Nasi Goreng
which is the fried rice or like the meat
breakfast but that's not really what you
eat for breakfast right right exactly
I remember my mom used to make Nazi
golden oh really I think it was always
just um Frozen
[Laughter]
things we
um sell here as frozen food like quickly
you warm it up in the frying pan it's
really easy
I like that one
[Music]
huh have you seen froggy Walla
oh well I thought too I talked to her a
little bit so what's what's the deal
with froggy Wawa you're not dead you're
here yeah everybody revived I'm back but
uh I saw some notes that she left behind
yes and
so she was like I guess on her last
stream
she was like talking about insects and
so on insects yes yeah and one in some
of her notes is that like Indonesia
um has let me see can I find the note
Indonesia has like some some dish with
uh some insects
I think I know what you're talking about
because like in some areas
wait what was that called
it says uh that is with um it's B larvae
larva with rice
and coconut wrapped in banana leaves
one oh my God okay this is literally the
first time I'm hearing this but oh my
God this is crazy I was like thinking
like oh maybe you're talking about you
know one of those like dried uh
grasshopper snacks or something because
it's not common I didn't like you know I
don't eat it and I've never eaten it
before actually but there are people who
eat it you know so I thought you were
referring to that but this is like a
whole dish what
like I think that one is wasp instead of
bees but ah yeah
I wonder if it tastes good it doesn't
look good I don't know if I want to try
it I'm scared but is there anyone in the
chat from your Indonesian viewers who
had that before
oh
I wonder I wonder
I wonder if somebody
your wasp actually serve a purpose
apparently
but but no I don't think it has the WASP
itself it has like the babies of the
ones what
hmm that's what it's uh The larva Valley
larva yeah
yeah
[Music]
oh there's no
first time hearing it I probably pass it
I heard my grandma talk about it
yeah like I think most of the ID Bros
they know the food that's called like
the potok but like the buttock that's
like the the WASP no
um
[Music]
yeah so I think the inside is not wasps
oh I don't know what kind of face you
should be making
happy happy
I was like thinking if I should have
made you with this faces uh you know
with this happy face
you know you know when like people do
fan art of us of like the whole life
members in general some some Mama some
artists have like such a specific art
style
um that even in fan art people copy that
because it's such a feature that without
that it doesn't look much like the
character so I think you are one of
those cases where you know you have the
the white yeah in the middle of your eye
yes and I think a lot of fan artists um
copy that too like for me there's not no
such so specific thing in the art style
that people feel like copying but you're
one of those cases now I wonder if I
should do that too
and what about you like what what would
you have
um
as I said I don't think I'm one of those
people who like have
um such a like feature yeah Disney
feature like for me if my eyes look like
you know if they if they don't do that
to my eyes people will think it's
somebody else you really think it's that
that strong oh on it wait
that's it
some of you guys say the feathers but
that's not what I mean that's that's
that's that's not the art style that's
just my design but you know for for
Pochi mama she draws her characters
always with the white thing in the
middle of the eye that's that's the art
style yeah that's not a design you know
what I mean the difference yeah yeah
yeah
oh yeah
huh
slap a piece of bacon on it yeah naked
yeah me me I'm I'm just like drawing
this egg blob here
I wonder what I should do with the
eyebrows I don't know hmm
like this yeah but
hmm boba boba yeah your Boba now visible
because that's the limit of the
I'm gonna
put Elena's fingers on the shoulder of
Wawa ah nice nice
okay
so you're basically naked behind the
bacon
I guess so
I guess so because you know I think uh
you know the setting here is like uh
we're in the maybe we're in Indonesia or
maybe we're in uh some tropical country
because it would be it would be really
hot if you wear something like
underneath the you know I guess yeah oh
so maybe I should do the same for you
you will be wearing nothing
underneath this egg outfit oh my
[Music]
um you will be wearing your uh your I
don't know what's this called like
chokers thing
like your necklace looking thing
actually do we have a filling bucket in
this that's very nice because no there's
no filling bucket either you're kidding
me
I guess
I'm thinking what eyebrows foreign
[Music]
you should put uh you should make me
naked and then put on both of my Boba
one fried egg each
wait I don't have I don't have a
oh oh my God okay you mean you oh I see
I see what you mean okay that I'll erase
oh sorry I'm
make it better you can make it better
improve it
professional um
I can't it's not available
[Music]
I'll lift her shoulder
I'll lift your shoulder
and I think you said we were doing spicy
stuff yeah oh then I think we can only
see if as soon as I color this oh
censored by the hair censored by the
hair and then and then we draw like some
eggs here
ink you can't really see like here but
like
uh unless I color it but censored by egg
um
maybe maybe we get some colors later
yeah maybe when you get colors okay I
want to actually try uh going to oopsie
whoopsie sorry
I want to try uh getting some color
okay I need more more bacon reference
pictures
what's this color
um pink oh
whoa bacon so much bacon you guys love
bacon don't you guys
[Music]
what this looks more like raw bacon
no it's not spicy enough it's not hot
enough we need to cook them we need to
be grilled yeah need to grill
what about capacity
okay remember this uh three pixel
3 pixel I'm gonna write so I remember
three pixel and then I'm gonna try
coloring
I keep on moving the cameras because I
go to the edges oh man
oh man
why am I still on layer one I thought I
switched I feel like there's a ghost
that keeps on forcing me to switch to
layer one perhaps
there's a ghost
okay I'm like trying to color this I
don't know does this work is this if
this will work but I'm trying do you
believe in ghosts right now
um I don't know it depends do you
believe in I feel like you know it
depends on whether or not I believe in
ghosts no no no no no no I think it
depends on like whether it's whether the
story is Scary or not oh
yeah
I think it's like I don't really have an
opinion but I think like I I usually I
normally like stay out of trouble you
know for example like oh people like to
trespass uh to like say a haunted house
or whatever like I wouldn't do that
because say even if there's no ghost
there's probably gonna be like squatters
or like scary people you know you never
know something like that
oh yeah so I normally stay away from
stuff from from Ghosts no
no no
no no no no no like from Ghost I guess
like from like ghost stories and people
are like oh my gosh go to this haunted
side or so and so you know I usually
don't have a little challenge yeah
even if there's no ghosts there might be
something else
oh even more dangerous and you don't
know but if like for example someone
tells you
um oh this house that we're in right now
not necessarily a haunted house but just
generally normal house but this person
that you're going there with they're
like I don't know they believe in that
kind of stuff and they say oh I feel a
weird Aura in this house there must have
been a ghost spooking around here
because they can't let go of their soul
would you believe that no no not
necessarily I guess but
[Music]
I'm not not superficial
at all
okay I'm drawing the skin I don't know
if this will look good but I've been
trying
does my bacon look anything like bacon I
don't think yes it does don't worry
I tried to switch it up to to be a bit
more like cooked bacon
it needs more detail
more details I'm trying to get this the
correct shade of Orange
hmm
shade of orange Fifty Shades of orange
where is it uh is it this one maybe it
may have I don't know
not orange enough
maybe this
yes maybe this
oh
[\h__\h]
oh Dana tell me what have you been up to
recently me I have been I don't know
I've been like really busy with like a
project I think because uh I think uh oh
no can I talk about projects here but
you know I guess your deadlines and
stuff like that yeah and then you know
I've been uh busy doing PayPal business
as well I just uh yeah you know like
ever since I've moved to my studio it
took me like a long time like only today
I put up my base stations finally so
that I can stream VR again
yeah yeah before I I really really you
know held off to for a long time because
it's so
this is
MVR stuff
um I guess like nothing too big I guess
but I wanna I like because I like VR
it's so exhausting I want to keep it to
the minimum uh really
but I think it's like I don't know I
guess so I guess it could be tiring I
feel like I don't know even though
you're in like an air-conditioned room
or something it's still really really
hot what
does that change on your side ah I guess
not okay
when I was changing the opacity of the
layer it doesn't change on your side
that's good
okay okay I think the bacon um for now
I'll leave the bacon like this
okay
oh by the way what time do we start
drawing we ended up not timing
because we are going to draw for like
around an hour right I think and it
doesn't have to be extinct yeah
personally I don't think it matters that
much
I've tried to fix my mess by redrawing
the hair in Gray I don't think this
Orange Is Right but it's like you know
what it's fine
that's a good orange also like depending
on my outfit uh hookah Papa Drew me with
um a little bit different Orange
hair Shades sometimes oh really so a
little bit only slightly so it's okay
okay
I'm kind of thinking if I should
probably
turn
[Music]
I kind of don't I'm not really used to
cult doing like this kind of like soft
coloring so I'm thinking I just want to
like oh we're more of a cell Shader yeah
[Music]
so I think I might like redo this I mean
not redo like I like uh soft shading
more
um
I'm just really bad at like doing it and
especially because like the the
lines the the sketch is like super yeah
oh but maybe I don't know
[Music]
but it's okay we can continue we can
continue
struggling with drawing that's me all
the time
yeah me too I want to draw more but
I'm so self-conscious about it but I
totally get it yeah I'm also the same
honestly
um
he's just like especially because you
know it's because you think to yourself
that I used to be able to do better than
this yeah although not necessarily I was
looking back on my old art from like
10 years ago oh yeah
like yesterday I was looking at it I'm
like
what was I thinking
I don't know my I don't know it's just
creeped me out
wow that much
yeah
I was wondering how how did people ever
consider commissioning me for my art
when it was so [\h__\h] I'm I I'm so
grateful that anyone would ever consider
that
[Laughter]
wow but that means people like your art
they want it yeah surprisingly like I
don't know maybe they were higher I
don't know they were hired for once
commission you
didn't say clearly
yes yes yes yes
I like these these feathers
[Music]
I want to come up with a new art style I
don't want to draw completely
differently oh because I've been told
before that from my from my bands they
told me before that my art style reminds
them of
like
2010 or earlier old classic deviant art
is that bad but no even now you know
like some people are like purposely
trying to like recreate that like 90s
aesthetic art
that I understand that's actually
aesthetically pleasing but I would say
whatever I was doing was not so much
aesthetically pleasing really
that's that's interesting I don't know I
don't have to describe your own art
style
I don't know
I think like judging your own stuff is
always the most difficult
um yeah but a lot of people say a lot of
my viewers say I draw pretty fast but
then I'm just like that's because all I
do is doodle
it almost killed thank you
foreign
but yeah I'm just really really happy to
have someone that I can you know you
know we can chill and draw I actually
like drawing but I don't I don't like
the pressure that comes with it like of
course you're always the one who's like
giving pressure yada yada yada but you
can't help it sometimes right
I just like drawing for a leisure
oh
not for pleasure for a Leisure yes
pleasure and pleasure spicy and for sure
of course
pleasure not pressure yeah
yes no pressure please
yeah and then I I actually really like
drawing over my sketch like this
yeah oh
I don't I don't know I think it's
because I don't really like it when my
sketch is like the same color
yeah so I just like when I do like all
these like light drawing stuff I try to
draw over my sketch
um okay what do you look like you look
pretty nice
I need I need a Flip Flip horizontally
tool
that's how else will I know if
anything's off proportionally uh
you know one one question that I've done
before is pumpkin costume pumpkin wait
so how it's so cute I mean I wasn't in a
real pumpkin you know what you were in
the real pumpkin I was not in a real
pocket
I was like I'm interesting I was one of
my favorite costumes I think it's cute
pumpkin cute cute
I think like these days like because
people watch too much anime maybe if
they go Halloween or whatever maybe they
cosplay as anime what if oh yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
would anybody of you guys like go to see
a Halloween party and cosplay as a whole
Live member
I feel like if if you go like I don't
know as Elsa or something you know like
a Disney character yeah then you would
totally like still fit in I think yes
but like when it gets to like more
like anime characters then probably
maybe maybe it'll be a bit weird but but
if you have a really sick high quality
cosplay and you show up like that at the
party everybody's gonna be like damn
that's so cool they're gonna be like
sick
pigs please they would ask for your
pictures
cool you should try to be like that or
something you should cosplay you guys I
mean not you Kiara but you can so if you
want to
you you have to cosplay pavolian Wayne
and yeah spread the gospel of joinda
why me I don't go outside I can cosplay
you at home maybe but I don't go outside
me too how am I gonna spread the join
the
um on the street
foreign
make me a PNG of reina's hair let's go
yes
wait
wait we do that on the 31st like I give
you some pngs of my hair yeah
on top of herself
oh my God that would be such a great
idea oh yes please okay actually I was
planning on playing
um on the 31st I was planning on playing
Fatal Frame and I heard you played it
before right yep
uh I was hoping to like get perms in
time for the newest one but even if not
I still want to play it but maybe I
heard it's actually pretty scary do you
maybe want to give me if you have you
probably already have plans for the 41st
right uh depends on what time though
depends on what time I do have plans but
so yeah it depends on what time I
I'm so flexible let's figure it out and
then maybe if you want you can give me
like mental support yeah of course I
would love to do that and help me to
play the game yes yes yes yes
thank you
well wait so which one are you trying
I I'm I'm trying to get the Fatal Frame
black made water or something like that
yeah yeah that's the one I played on
stream yeah yeah but the there's like I
don't know is it a remake or something
the one that's really new the new new
new new one it's on Steam yeah there's a
new new one wait a new new one is the
what mask of the lunar eclipse or what
no it's just a port oh is it is that it
is that all the different seriously okay
uh maiden of the black water is the
ports
oh okay yeah
um well whatever we already have like I
think perms for two other fatal frames
so whatever happens I'll be playing one
Fatal Frame game I think yeah because
there's a good girl yeah true true let
that motivate you yeah at least
temporarily I think like I did I grew
immune after like a while I was like
I just want to live you know
foreign
that's not like you that's not like me
maybe maybe after a ghost kills you over
and over your teeth it's like you know
and then people would say if evil white
Hearts but they're evil they kill me I
hate horror games so much Lena I'm just
doing this to satisfy my viewers at
least on the 31st on Halloween but I
hate it so much yeah but I guess you
picked the right one the one that has uh
super cute girls if they're a mini game
you have you have to play then you know
play Fatal Frame because that's and it's
basically just like taking pictures of
ghosts right like how hard can and how
scary can it be
I heard it's actually scary I just can't
imagine it being that bad
mama mama I guess um if um if it's any
consolation I think like the newer it
gets the prettier the ghosts get and the
least scary it is
the prettier there's pretty ghosts
I guess so I mean if you you know if you
drop your standards into like the well
or something but uh
I guess the logic is that uh the newer
the game is the better the you know the
3D and everything and then they pay more
attention to like the people's face and
and then the not people's faces so even
though the ghosts are like
I'm gonna kill you sometimes you can see
maybe they're they don't look so bad
after all
on which uh uh console did you play It's
kind of frame oh uh on stream I played
on uh steam steam ah okay yeah there's
no because it's not like if you played
on Wii U and so on you have to like turn
turn The the Wii U to like turn the
camera and so on so it has like tilt
controls yeah I wonder how that works
since team is maybe I don't know if it's
easier to have it on Wii U or switch
there's no but I don't know I don't
think there's is their English version
in Wii because uh I personally only got
it because I mean played it on stream
because it's easy to just like Play
Steam right compared to yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah so what is this what is
this but
um there's like a problem I think with
uh I think like resolution and stuff so
um yeah
um I got some technical issues when I
first started playing
so maybe yeah I think you should play in
like 7 20 years I don't really remember
though but if you don't get the air then
it's whatever
I mean I always play in a really small
resolution because I like to have my
chat right next to it so it's nice yeah
that's no problem because mental support
yeah
or something like that
[Music]
I don't wanna hmm
this has taken forever for me
same here but it's okay we don't have to
speed we don't have to rush I don't
think we have to rush oh
yeah I don't think we have to rush it's
okay easy you just uh relax
and relax and relax I want to relax me
too on on the beach I mean me too let's
relax
[Music]
Beach yeah let's go
beaches
let's go I'm like I really wanna go on a
holiday you know me too you know now in
like December and so on Maldives would
be perfect but
I'm like so busy that's in in December
uh in November I'm going a little bit to
Rome in December I I'm having a visit a
special visit and then I go to Japan
after Christmas so yeah I don't think
maybe
the next time I can go to the beach is
maybe maybe in
February
sounds good I mean there's there's other
places as well right like any any place
you you know you want to go is it hot in
Bali in February I think it would be hot
in Bali like every time of the year
really I think so I don't know
okay that's good it's good that's good
yes yes would you join me would would if
I would would you join me of course
let's do another vacation
it will be probably a million times
cheaper than the Maldives I guess yeah
definitely definitely definitely
Hallelujah yes
I haven't even started like coloring the
egg or something I'm just like
drawing I don't even know what I'm doing
right now I'm just like anything I think
it's easy okay yeah
I don't know I'm I'm like getting too
worried about this this this hair which
I am like not doing a good job at
good job with the feathers oh thank you
[Music]
uh
yes yes but I just do
like you know what I won't have no hands
No Hands No Hands what about what about
our our spicy like shoulder ties you're
not gonna do it
[Laughter]
can you draw the hand here oh I mean I
guess this is okay something like that
sure yeah something like that or you can
yeah that's all right
[Music]
um
spicy
[Music]
does this look
this is proportionally
what that if I if you're right next to
me and I put my hand there ah then the
the thumb is here right
yeah the thumb is here
correct that's correct
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay fingers on your shoulder touch
we are next
go go go go go go go go go go
this hand looks ugly you have to draw it
I'm still trying to save this
um this this I don't know
[Music]
Halloween Sports Fest let's go everybody
right here also uh in the sports Fest
right yes I am wait are you but we're in
different teams oh I'm in white team
where are you
I'm in Savannah yellow team ah separated
from the homework yeah but we're only in
the relay so that's not a big deal yeah
it's all right
yeah this year uh this year's Sports
Festival uh I think Ian and ID were kind
of more like guests yeah yeah compared
to the last year
I know uh I saw like uh you know the
archive of like the practice stuff looks
interesting yeah like I also just saw
like a peak but they came up with some
new stuff I think yeah yeah yeah I saw
them fighting like dancing enemies
we're building oh I only saw the fencing
one
fencing oh
interesting it's always very nice that
they you know keep coming up with new
ideas yeah they're so creative oh and
they put so much work into it yeah yeah
and then like I don't know
yeah I think we are guests because I
mean I don't want to speculate but I
guess like you know there's been a lot
of members too right oh no
yeah so I think it's also really nice
and besides uh we already have the uh
what was it the Holo ID cop that's what
we had
were you in the hallway because
no oh okay yeah
maybe next time I wasn't the staff for
that so I didn't know much about the
people but honestly I think it's okay
that we only participate like a little
bit because
I if I when I try to remember last year
uh especially like I was mostly fine
because I was in Europe so the time was
not too bad for me I guess I was still
tired but for the N A members it was way
worse oh yeah they're suffering the
whole time and so tired they had no
energy and yeah and then it was so long
right yes very long
um they were suffering through it so I
think this way it might be a bit better
and I think you know
um
like if Ian if Ian wants to do something
like this and have a bigger role in it
then we should you know take the
initiative and do something on our own
instead of always like hoping that
Japanese members step up and invite
usually we can always take it for
granted in my opinion true I agree I
agree
yeah I think it would be really fun to
do something like it to like an Enid
stuff we've been doing stuff like that
right
I could finally no wait I haven't
unlocked everything I'm so close to
unlocking everything oh yeah didn't you
with ID didn't you have another uh
recently I was watching a little bit
Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah
I was so close let's go did Kobo get
imposter a million times again or uh
actually I think the it was actually
more balanced this time because even I
even I got impostered two times I didn't
do a good job
oh I did not do a good job sorry
practice
I don't wanna you know like games like
that always give me a heart attack you
know like I don't know I'm just not good
at games like that like uh you know the
mafia type games like what's your role
no it's different I like the objection
game but like if I have to lie if I'm
the pursuer of the truth that's why we
know we're innocent I you know most of
the time I didn't ask to be Not Innocent
you know hey you know what I just
noticed yeah
in in your stream my art is like
minutes like five minutes behind
yeah I think it's because
um the what you call it yeah latency
it's crazy yeah it happened I'm like
already coloring the eyes but since like
three minutes ago I'm coloring the eyes
wait what yeah I see yeah actually I see
you coloring the eyes right here my
mhm doesn't have so much delay
because I you know the way it's done
like I have like two windows open and
one is you know just in case you want to
zoom in or zoom out just in case I want
to zoom in or zoom up I mean I have a
separate window that like shows
everything so I'm using that oh my God
I'm disconnected from the server are you
freaking serious
which server
out of the room
come back yeah yeah yeah I'm coming back
I'm coming back I'm coming back I think
yeah your connection is probably pretty
bad here
yeah
oh my God
I was okay okay listen I'm like drawing
the I was coloring the egg
it has the perfect egg color
I was coloring the egg
and then on my viewers screen
I was the egg isn't even colored AKA My
Stream yeah yeah that's what I'm saying
same here like my my things are way too
late
oh my God
oh no what's going on are we losing it
like the one like ah
I think like it's loading but it's not
loading perfectly
oh no let me take a screenshot before
everything's launched yeah yeah take a
screenshot
disconnected
I'm gonna try to refresh
leave page
requested canvas downloading canvas why
the canvas smaller than before oh I'm
scared
thank you
did you enter for the same URL
yeah yeah yeah
unloading canvas
spooky that's like the real Halloween
spookiness huh
let me see let me see oh oh I'm sorry
guys please I just want to call it a
mouse I see your mouse moving
oh yeah this is on my uh this is on my
other screen that's like a viewer not a
drawing person oh
yeah this is the one that's like made
for drawing that's like a little bit of
[Music]
them he may be back
oh my God see like a Kiana Nvidia you're
free it's gonna turn your name to
participate I'm gonna enter as they need
okay okay on the room
the egg was saved
on the room the egg was saved like I
went back yeah I went back and then I
saw like the what the room looks like
and then the egg was there but anyways
you can see me trying to draw I guess
I think it might be because I'm making
like so many like Strokes at like the
same yeah yeah like overloading the ram
of the of the server yes yes
yeah I'm looking at like the difference
of my uh oh my God are you serious it's
not loading it's locking me out it's
locking me out
yeah it's locking me out
it's okay look at that beautiful egg
yes now it's coming now the colors I'm
still trying to get in
technical difficulties
who was mouse cursor it's me but this
one's like another window it's like a
window that I can't use to draw
yeah
this and this one's like delayed
because I'm watching it from see like I
was like drawing the egg oh my gosh very
nice they're nice soft
or maybe I'm not gone yet
no and then I'm gone it look at that on
the stream I'm just gone
I mean it looks already
pretty close to finishing finished but
what's the most important is the egg on
your boba
yeah
[Applause]
if I can't get it done uh please draw it
for me okay I'm I'm I I feel like I see
where one should be but I'm not sure
about uh the other one is I think the
the yolk part is covered by the uh hair
so you can't really see it yeah okay
it's okay but but I still have so much
to draw on mine too oh
maybe you have to come back what are we
gonna do
yeah maybe you can it says connected but
like the canvas is not perfect it's kind
of like
layer one and Layer Two
oh it's so weird because uh it shows
really weird like it doesn't show your
eyes
it doesn't show the eyes it doesn't show
a lot of things
[Music]
that's so scary
I'm gonna try and see if hmm
it's so weird
what if you know what if I try to draw
now will it like break everything
let me try to write something here like
something
see it
see me
uh-huh uh yes you see I just wrote hi
but on my end
it's not fully loaded yet the
illustration I see you moving about
coloring the skin and stuff like that
[Music]
um
how about I have finished my part then I
take a screenshot then I send it to you
you put the screenshot into Photoshop
and you finish your part in Photoshop
I wrote Hi and then you see it but like
okay okay okay now now rainy is drawing
now oh wait no rain is drawing hi see
rain is
okay fine I'm just gonna like try to
eyeball from my other screen oh
that's a challenge yeah
let's see let's see this next level
let's see let's see if if it if it
translates
oh my God yeah it's close
you are hitting the right spot
okay
um
yeah you guys you guys should see like
what it looks like because it I can't
see anything like so I'm eyeballing
right now just to see like oh maybe this
is the correct one maybe this is you
know
hmm yeah yeah that looks pretty pretty
good pretty accurate yeah it's like
you're giving yourself a challenge to
make it more difficult yeah yeah yeah
yeah
exactly except this is not on purpose
I'm like why why are we like this
oh my gosh the egg doesn't have any
shading
the yolk has but not the white not the
wide yeah okay I'm gonna do that now
okay I even did the hand I'm so proud of
myself nice oh my God this looks so I'm
gonna I'm gonna screenshot it if it
doesn't you know if it if it's still
like that even after we finish I'm gonna
take a screenshot and I'm gonna show you
what I was working with yeah
yes oh wait hey my my colors are coming
in pretty up to date now
nice nice nice nice yeah what I want to
do is like I want to erase these like
blue stuff but um
blue blue
ah yeah yeah that's why we should have
like
used more decent colors maybe I didn't
know that we were gonna color this of
course we have to wow
make it as pretty as possible to
commemorate this movie I guess so
Kiara egg and rainy bacon
what is this I'm looking I'm eyeballing
from like the the stream window
it's like maybe oops sorry perfect
[Music]
we're just gonna wear these costumes at
home right Elena not not outside uh you
know I don't think no no not outside I
don't think yeah
about it
is
like the you know the the blush oh my
gosh it would be such a challenge
because I wouldn't know but then I think
I would be able to erase so I'm not too
worried about it let's uh oh by the way
I'm aware that the face is way too wide
and if I had the tools to fix it I would
fix it but it is what it is also it
looks wider on your screen for some
reason than on mine really I don't know
why
maybe it's perception but I feel like it
looks wider on your side pressure is off
why does it look like this
okay is this correct let me see you let
me eyeball
oh
okay are you trying to make blush yes
yes yes yes
it's working it's working it's working
my gosh this is I I can't see anything
like on my drawing window guys I'm just
like so you you're basically drawing
blind you're just assuming where it
would be yeah and then like I'm looking
at like the stream window and like oh
yes okay so that's where it's supposed
to be that's nice yeah
I respect that so much Halloween magic
guys pink okay
okay
I think this looks yeah okay honestly
the blue looks so ugly
I can't deal with it
yeah I tried to draw on top of my Orange
Lines yeah that's what I was doing
before before this um okay you know what
I'm gonna close the window and then I'm
gonna
I'm gonna close the window I'm going to
try
to open a new window of the same thing
okay
and then you're trying to solve Tech
issues Tech issues this is the first
time I experienced this
magical draw please
oh my God
[Music]
yay oh my God
it's finally back okay red is much
better but uh still too it's not a
little bit too red for me
oh my God finally okay I gotta erase all
these like blue
blue goodbye everybody not everybody I
mean like just the blue oh
Goodbye Blue
okay maybe 100
two
you know just just to make sure we
absolutely get rid of it can we just
like have a you know like a color select
and be like destroy all the blue on
Minecraft that would be nice but that's
luxury that's luxury we have to learn to
draw without
luxury yeah
[Music]
Indonesia Indonesian class with me huh
you want to do it next month
yes okay well tell me tell me when
you're free usually held every Sunday so
any Sundays that you can do are you
doing Sundays uh normally but like uh if
uh if say like you're super busy or
something uh we can normally make
exceptions no we can do it Sunday that's
fine okay
[Music]
sorry I'm so sorry
the skin is too yellow why is it so
yellow I don't know it's the um it's the
style of the artist I respect it
you ate too many bananas yeah did you
know if you eat too many oranges uh they
say your skin turns orange
yes yes has that ever happened to you
before and carrots carrots too carrots
would be even stronger oh really it
never happened to me I don't eat that
many oranges okay okay I like oranges I
like oranges orange is really good yeah
have any of you guys in chat ever had
you know something like that you ate too
many oranges your skin turns uh I only
know that from Scrubs really like so
like somebody like straight up said it
to me and it's like oh you know I have
so many oranges in the fridge and
they're like are you eating that alone
I'm like yeah and I'm like did you know
that and I'm like no
but I guess now I know you know
also if you eat too many tomatoes you
get kind of red oh really I that I did
not know
do you like tomatoes
yeah do you like cherry tomato
yeah good I don't know like some people
don't like cherry tomato or is it just
yeah it makes me so mad
it's cherry tomato Raw
yeah these are people who who say they
only like tomatoes if they're like you
know cooked and like on pizza or so yeah
yeah but they're so good they're really
good like yeah I eat cherry tomato as it
is like they they sell it in the
supermarket as it is right and then you
can eat
yeah very very delicious and people are
like you were a psychopath and I'm like
what
[Music]
why why why must you be so picky cherry
tomatoes by the way I've been seeing
more and more of your cooking posts on
Twitter you're cooking so much what do
you think I think I think material waifu
material I was like can you cook for me
please thank you next time if
um what are you what do you what are you
gonna cook for me if if you know if if
if if
[Music]
well I should probably cook Austrian for
you ah yes yes
ah true true introduce me to the wonders
of Austrian Cuisine yeah
we have some good stuff especially in
terms of desserts if you like dessert
yes I would love to
is it the like the Sahara cake that you
uh gave me well that's just a cake cake
but like like real desserts you know
that actually need cooking to do yeah
yeah wait wait so like what like well
for example
what's that
[Music]
it's really simple but it tastes amazing
it's like it's kind of like
um scrambled pancakes
yes but like bigger and fluffier and
then you eat it together with either
um like an apple uh sauce kind of thing
or it's vegetable stuff which is um uh
Plum Plum some like some kind of plum
sauce
um that's really good it's not good oh I
want it I want to try because like
obviously I think even if we have like a
restaurant here in ID it wouldn't taste
as good as the OG you know
I've never made it before that that
dessert my mom used to make it for me
and sometimes when she wouldn't pay
attention
um like everything would like
burn oh yeah she would mess it up
so I have that in my memory so strong
and I'm like when my mom previously came
to visit me she was like oh should I
make you like something to eat I'm like
well I'm really gonna leave kaisersman
but you know isn't it really difficult
and she's like no that's not it I'm like
then why did you [\h__\h] it up
and she's like that's just because I
wasn't paying attention it's not
actually that difficult she said she was
just not paying attention okay
was doing it so often for us that
sometimes she would just do something on
the side and then she forgets about it
yes yes yes yes
like what about ID
guys help help me out here what's you
know she can't handle like spicy food so
no spicy food but if I were to cook her
something from ID what should I cook for
her not follow me yo what no like no
instant stuff the not instant stuff
please be larvae
from the shop
because it's pretty yummy yeah yeah it's
like a pretty yummy snack and it's
usually open even when it's like
midnight or whatever there's like two
variants the sweet and the uh the sweet
and the Savory one I feel like this is
like a pancake yeah yeah kind of sort of
sort of oh wait uh do you prefer pancake
or waffles
I love both
you can't you can't like this is this is
what uh what happened you know we've
been asking like a bunch of people
like this before
um the I don't know that maybe last time
I asked you it was out of genuine
curiosity but now I want you to say it
like right in front of chat so like we
we have it like clear like who likes
waffles and who likes it depends it
depends because like
um if it's just like pure pancake and
pure waffle it's hard to choose but like
if you say all the waffles will be
topped with a [\h__\h] ton of fruit and ice
cream and all that then Yum Yum Yum you
know waffle but but you know it depends
with the toppings the toppings are
important for me Nutella
yeah I'm Nutella but Nutella and maybe
some strawberries but then it doesn't
matter to be honest like both is fine
for me I just want to have some good top
things ah okay so also so for her I
guess the toppings it depends on the
toppings okay okay okay yeah yeah all
right yes yes yes yes yes yes yeah
yeah I'm good
okay I think what what's your answer
your own answer and I actually chose uh
waffles I like waffles I think it's also
because like waffles are kind of less
common so every time I I mean over here
at least like I think every store would
have pancakes but maybe some stores
wouldn't have waffles something like
that you know so every time I have
waffles like oh man I'm having a meal
you know
one thing every time when I go to
Harajuku one thing I would always do is
like the moment you enter takesha Dori
maybe you know it the moment you enter
Target on the right side I mean if
you're coming from Harajuku station you
enter and then on the right side where
it goes downhill there is this Cafe that
has waffles right you know I think um I
don't really remember like uh of course
like down the street they're all there's
always like stores that sells like
Crepes and stuff like that but I don't
think I've had waffles there okay so you
can see the place
um that you know there's a crap the
first if you enter takeshore Street the
first Crab Place on the right side where
you can also go to purikura it's
connected to a waffle place and I've
been there a million times they have so
many different kind of you know really
decorated crunchy waffles you know I
love them so much every time I eat them
every time it's my favorite place I
wonder if they still exist but but
they've been existing for many years so
I feel like they still probably exist
yeah probably probably yeah you know
even though they've been I heard they've
been like renewing a lot of stuff and oh
yeah in Tokyo and also in Harajuku as
well like making new buildings in the
takesha street yeah I want to go I want
to go and have delicious delicious
waffles yeah nice waffles
you know what would be nice if we go on
like some sort of like a cafe hopping
thing but like not for like coffee but
for like you know just like the little
tiny like desserts that they have I
think it would be like pretty nice ah I
went to like a lot of
um like all you can eat sweets buffets
before in in Tokyo uh yeah I tried so
many we should go to something like that
yeah of course definitely definitely uh
I don't know any do you have any like
favorite like place like aside from like
the waffles like if you if you go to
like Japan or something
clearly we really want to go on a
vacation
like uh do you have any like places to
recommend like maybe like a place to eat
what something I don't know
ah
favorite foods yes my favorite
restaurants like in particular
not so much that I remember I think like
I would always go to different places
also it really depended on where where I
was living at the time
I would just go to whatever is closest
missing everywhere like you can barely
do the brown choice
everyone always good in Japan always oh
oops okay
in the last place I lived in in Japan
like uh in 2021 or not yeah 2021 yeah
um there was uh uh a pasta Place yeah it
was focused on pasta and they had like
30 different types of pastas and I would
always like every week at least once or
twice I would go there to get some yummy
pasta and try me try to drive the whole
menu
that's so nice I think you know my
favorite was a lemon salmon pasta oh
that sounds so good oh nice oh yeah I
wanna eat good food you know what is
this with like food in Japan like
they're delicious but also they're like
healthyish I think you know to an extent
to an extent like for example compared
to like some I don't know maybe some ID
food they have like lots of maybe uh
what you call it like coconut milk which
you know if you eat too much it's like
not good or something really yeah yeah
like it adds like there's something
that's not good like you have to eat in
moderation I think or maybe it's
something else that's like a lot of ID
food
coconut coconut milk
I didn't know you could have too much
coconut milk
hmm I thought coconut is like healthy no
matter what
I don't know maybe the ID Bros can
further clarify please am I
hallucinating or what
oh and like I think like maybe some
other food like the snacks they have a
lot of MSG or something like that how
much coconut can kill you that's coconut
can kill you
it's a laxative yeah it's healthy but
like off to an amount because there's
like a lot of fat and everything so I
mean like everything in moderation I
think it's not like it's like bad bad
for you
I just want to eat food I mean to be
honest I don't really like coconut
anyway
you don't like Pokemon yeah I mean you
know when I make curry I I put in
coconut milk but you don't really taste
the coconut so that's fine yeah but
coconut milk on its own or like
chocolate with coconut on top or so I'm
I actually don't like it but don't you
use coconut a lot in Indonesia cooking
uh a little bit yes you know it adds
like to the flavor and everything you
know if it doesn't stand out too much
I'm I'm okay with it I guess yes yes yes
yes yes yes delicious
but you know what I can't stand um I
used to be a you know I used to hate
Ginger a lot
yeah because it's like you know the the
kind of spiciness that maybe baby Wayne
couldn't handle it's like weird it's not
chilly you know
um I was also pretty bad with Wasabi
until like probably like recently or
something oh yeah yeah yeah is there
like any food you were like bad with
like in the past that you're like oh
okay with it now
[Music]
um
maybe broken a broccoli I'm not sure did
I ever hate broccoli like most things
that I hated in my childhood I still
hate to this day oh really oh but yeah I
guess uh yeah I tried you guys remember
well what the [\h__\h] Susie yeah I I gave
Sushi a try like legit finally after a
million [\h__\h] years
huh yeah and it was okay I survived it
but I was just like I still don't like
say okay I wanna eat sushi today that's
not happening but but I tried and I
survived
that's good congratulations yeah I I was
like in Korea right with Navi mama and I
was trying really hard like there was so
much food that um I was recommended that
I felt like oh [\h__\h] if I ordered this in
a restaurant I feel like I'm probably
not gonna like it and then what if I
have a lot of leftovers I so I was
trying to be on the safe side and go
with things that look like I would
probably be fine with eating yeah
but I think nabioma had like a really
hard time finding places that have stuff
that I can eat
so for sometimes I I I I I held back and
I was like okay
it's okay I will I will try my best and
then we have something that was similar
to Sushi yeah and and I forgot what it
was called it was similar very similar
though similar looking and then it had
some some some stuff that I don't really
like like seaweed oh that's okay you
don't like seaweed
[Music]
yeah and actually it was a really really
really hot summer day so they came up
was really refreshing because it was
like a nice cool lunch a chill lunch
nice oh I'm so hungry now
my Hunger countdown you know yesterday
I wanted to go to Korea I want to go to
Korea but I still haven't had like a
good you know no time yet no good time
yet to go ah I just want a feeling
summer is deadly in any Asian country so
you should go in in fall or in Spring oh
yeah I guess so Korea again yeah like uh
I don't know
um I went once before but yeah I want to
just like go and have more you know
Leisure times just like stroll around
but why not what I don't like about fall
I think like this is why spring is my
favorite season like for fall the wind
is so strong it messes up my hair so
much it's just kind of annoying
I put so much uh hairspray on my mind
you have to do that oh my goodness yeah
so spring is number one season you know
like you think spring and fall paper not
much difference but I hate fall so much
but I love fall fashion ah true but it's
like you know it's like not like like
obviously not summer but not winter I
guess it's like the transition that you
know
the colors and like the you know the
outer layers but not too much it's like
hey nice I don't know yes yes
[Music]
our wardrobe is mostly like the same
because the weather is the same uh all
the time so I was like hey you girls
won't wear the same kind of clothes
ah no I mean it's just like a clothes
that are you know that fit the
temperature like for example if you live
in like a Four Season country like
probably your wardrobe is split within
like you know okay for this coats for
that and then summer clothes spring
clothes awesome clothes but we don't
really do that I want to know about ID
members who wears the sexiest clothes
I think like the ID members uh they all
like dress uh they dress well to a
certain degree but like sexy
it doesn't have to be like a lot of
exposure just like you know clothes that
shape your body like really nicely and
you know oh there can I be honest I
think um the other day you know like
Cobra was like staying over right and
then she was yeah she was actually
wearing clothes though we're like I
don't know like because cool Wears Like
shorts all the time I think oh yeah
she wasn't sexy
okay okay I think she's wearing clothes
that you would I mean it's stylish okay
this is very hard to explain
but like anything that's close to that
the person that I can think of is
recently too is probably her
yeah okay who is the cutest clothes ah
cutest clothes
who's the most booty girl
I don't know
I don't really know I think like a lot
of ID girls are more towards like the
cooler side type of clothing yeah yes
yes yes yes
two and yeah actually what about Zeta
Zeta I don't actually hang out with her
that much but ah actually yeah she wears
kind of cute stuff yeah I feel like
she's a child like from just like
listening to her I feel like she's kind
of she could be a little bit booty call
type oh yeah but take whatever I say
with a grain of salt like I I obviously
haven't seen her wardrobe I've only seen
her like okay we have to inspect her
yeah hello I think wardrobe inspection
wow interesting hey Justin of course and
and when you meet them in real life who
is the loudest
Ollie is so loud and if they would do
that okay okay listen it's kind of like
they would do a high five but they would
go like but with their boobas you know
they was like Hey girl Hello high five
but with their chest they do brofist
with their chest yes yes yes yes
I think it's all about passion
you know men do that before two day
collection and like jump like at each
other you know can you imagine yeah
something like this like the thing is I
don't know guys uh I feel like also ever
since I hang out with the Holo ID you
know if you're in Hollow ID it's
impossible not to become like you know a
little bit like touchy touchy or
something because like
everybody and all ideas like that you
know I heard I heard you guys are very
tense yeah yes yes yes so I was like Yay
when it's like sleepover you know yay we
tickle we I don't know but massage is
different yeah it's a different thing
bro diesel is really good at uh getting
massages oh I'll remember that thank you
for telling me down yes yes yes yes yes
yes
[Music]
just randomly start massaging someone uh
no I would need to be like
sorry out
sorry oh I made a mistake in Coloring uh
I would need to be like too bison I'm uh
you know my muscle hurting it's like
okay okay
my hand you know like massaging is like
a passive skill within Indonesian yeah
it's a passive skill everybody knows how
to not everybody I guess but it's not
uncommon to know like how to massage or
something how do they learn it
I don't know maybe like
from like family or something
or something yeah
you passively learn it it is what it is
oh that's very nice yeah I love massage
man you like massages right so if you go
to ID wow very nice
oh you can get the massage
dude I will test out Lisa's massage yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes yeah learn how
to touch learn how to massage from
childhood like even uh when usually when
the ID person is still very young like
but someone says because our parents
demand for massage
ah I don't know about that but it's like
you know it's also very common to like
maybe you have a grandma or something
and then you're like very little and
then you step on the Grandma's back you
know so you know that whole step on me
step on me joke like we've been doing
that since we were little or something
so it's Child's Play quite a cultural
difference yeah definitely definitely
what about do you guys seem to be not
not really like close but more like your
your parents try to get more out of
their children in terms of like being
taken care of right by your children
just like you know culture thing uh I
guess so uh but I think like when I'm
like
I don't know I think when like we're
little or something we don't really
think about it we just think like sweet
we get to step on our parents
haha this is so fun at least yeah
stepping on someone is not as exhausting
as like giving a proper massage with
your hands you just have to say yeah
yeah yeah
personally I've never actually been
asked to like yo massage my back for one
hour or something no but I like doing I
like massaging people and then if they
get like the relief it's great because I
know how it feels to like get back pain
so if I like massage someone's back just
for a little bit and they're like ah
thank you and then it's like oh I'm
happy
if you're happy I'm happy something like
that
I am always happy about massage yay
ah I just had a massage actually uh
early on this week because my back was
hurting very very much but now oh
I should go again but I took a really
nice bath yesterday oh I have like a
million bath bombs right now oh my gosh
very nice I had told myself I have to
start uh using them up because I got
even more recently sent to me from like
a sponsorship oh nice yeah from Valkyrie
connect because like the viewers could
choose gifts and then some of them said
she needs bath bombs and I'm like I like
bath bombs but I actually don't take
baths much so now I am starting to use
them up and and become more of a bathing
person for the meantime
I don't I'm not really the person I mean
I like bath bombs but what I use more is
the bath salts
I don't know
pretty similar I know Charlene I will
bring to you next time when I see you if
I don't forget I'll bring you some
Austrian bath salts especially maybe
from Scott's book because we are very
famous for our salt for some reason oh
really yeah especially South's book
literally has the word salt in German in
its name it's um salt castle and Scott's
book has like a big big salt history and
we produce a lot of like like like nice
bath salts like really magical ones
I'm so excited for that I wanna I wanna
I wanna take a warm like a hot bath
before I go to sleep tonight but I'm
also really hungry so I think I should
eat first or else I would like starve do
you know do you know you know I want
wait what's that um
thing let me look it up before I say it
okay
I'll delete the high that lady
[Music]
oh it doesn't say like where it's from
foreign
International thing or if it comes from
a specific country but it's pretty
popular here we have like
um you know in in in public pools
um where there's outdoor pools and
indoor pools like a mix and you know
they have like slides and everything
children so like like a big big like
public bath right yes yes uh pool
um and in those places what we have
often is something called a solar bad
which is salt salt water pool kind of
but it's warm so it's a relatively warm
not as warm as an Onsen but pretty warm
more like bearable and it's with salt
and it's really really healthy for you
like for your I don't know for like if
you're like sick or if you have
allergies or
um if you have problems with like you
know with your tummy yourself
and I remember like when I was younger I
would go uh with my family we would go
to like the public pool and then they
had one of those warm salt pools outside
and it was winter time so we would like
go outside of the pool and run around in
the snow and then jump into the hot salt
bath and this is so so nice that's so
nice it feels so cozy
warm bath now they're common in Central
Europe yeah that's what I thought I
wonder how it is like because I don't
think I've heard about it outside of
Europe but probably exists but
um you know I need to go on like a
Europe trip or something I think it
would be fun because it's uh very very
far you know so if I only go to like one
place and go home again it's very very
much you know like you already went
there and it takes you like 20 not 20 I
don't know I forgot how many hours it
takes and then you go home again it's
like ah no yeah it's always better to
maybe just visit multiple places but
when can I go I don't know
well you're still young
so lots of time to travel I guess the
rest of your life true true true no need
to stress about it now yeah but when you
come to Austria if you want I'll take
you to the salt bath yes please so
thanks I love it I love
yeah I want I actually have yeah I have
some more some bath salts that I haven't
used I'm gonna use it after the stream
but then I'm gonna no wait dinner first
is going after the stream yes
spicy bath for relaxing imagine
Imagination Running Wild wow it's just a
shower wait should I draw should I draw
the chicken yes
yes please I practice drawing again I
practice drawing the your your chicken
late earlier today
thank you more than like you have the
chicken bucket this is the chicken
bucket supposedly one more draw one more
draw one more okay
Let's Rock Cafe chicken dressed up as a
vampire
oh okay
chicken
I think I'm pretty much done with with
my Dana too I wish I could make your
face more narrow though because I [\h__\h]
up a little bit Yeah I think I'm also
done with mine I'll also draw uh my
mascot
maybe here because the chicken is on oh
yes uh what should they be doing uh what
cosplay zombie
or or Mommy Mommy oh Mommy toilet paper
wrapped all around it yeah
it's like such a cheap low-cost uh
Halloween cosplay
put on some toilet paper around your
body yeah shoe shoe shoe
that's mommy mommy
[Music]
sorry Mommy
apologizing to the uh
The Mummy
[Music]
yeah I think this is okay
why
we should write our name and date
because it's done right is it okay
done I think yeah I tried my best I
tried my best to
there's some space still up here on top
I guess
okay you can write first yeah
[Music]
um
oh your sign all right I can do that too
[Music]
and I'll write mine here
okay I think that was my signature if I
didn't do it wrong I'm doing so rarely
oh wait that's because the first time I
see your signature yeah
it's mine what's that what's that part
uh oh this one the one on the right is
like uh the feathers like the the people
tail feather thingy Yahoo
okay and the date
what's the date 27 7.
[Music]
thank you
oh oh should I okay okay
um color color
um pink
uh
at 20 oops undo oh you know what maybe I
have an idea
twenty seven I read it in European
Styles oh it's all right
20 22. yay
wait
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I want to make it pretty ah
do you know what are your plans until
Halloween what are you doing what are
you streaming me uh uh tomorrow
uh tomorrow I'll be just streaming at
night and there's I'm gonna be uploading
a cover premiere
interesting and then I won't be
streaming on Saturday but I will be
streaming on Sunday like I have no idea
what like probably you know uh free talk
the usual free talk thing in the morning
and maybe at night I want to stream
something I don't know what about you
what are you playing thanks for asking
because I kind of wanted to tell my
viewers anyway the check of the music
video is a little bit delayed so my new
song cover is coming probably on Sunday
after all oh you know what a lot of
people are uploading song covers
well they're uploading a cover they're
uploading the cover oh my God wait
everybody's doing stuff this weekend
like 10 different song coming I know oh
my God like can I can I know oh oh oh oh
oh oh are you are you doing I don't know
how to pronounce four blood
from this is my birthday concert
everybody liked it so much and I really
loved it
too so I decided to make it an official
song cover and with professional proper
mixing and so on dude it sounds amazing
oh that will be I think like Sunday
evening my time oh I'm excited to see it
and for me guys did you know that
tomorrow 8pm GMT plus seven so that's
like 10 p.m GST I'm gonna be having a
uploading what it's already uploaded but
it's gonna be a premiere of a duel cover
with me and a princess Kobo kanairu
we're gonna be singing aikoto before
yeah
share the news to your friends and
family your extended family
because the more the merrier right we
want everybody to discover
YouTuber and you know what we should do
yeah is it too late what like this
already almost looks like
Halloweenish sticker like in some
Corners ah sure sure sure we can then I
wish we could add a layer zero on top
okay I think I
I might I'm I will put like a pumpkin
here sure maybe you can put like a bat
or something somewhere oh a bat okay
sure something something Halloweeny okay
okay okay you will put the pumpkin where
at the bottom yeah in the corner into
the bags so where should I put it
because I feel like the chicken is
already like but okay I'm gonna do it
yeah
sorry I've we were already finished
finishing up but I was looking at it and
I'm like this looks like this
you know what I can add like borders
like just like a simple border like that
but I think like it helps you know what
should the Border color be hmm just Gray
um
either purple or orange yeah orange like
Halloween colors sure
you're not do you're doing everything on
layer one or what yeah
okay I'm gonna make it
you hear him like my uh you hear my
fingers like this
Dragon I'm not wearing my gloves you
know
the thing about drawing gloves do you
use it because I don't
no but that's so professional wow
drawing gloves as well yeah there's like
uh my yeah when I buy a tablet they
always come with it
oh my God it's so not straight the lines
whatever it looks pretty straight to me
cool
thank you
okay I want to do one more one more what
other sticker like a I'm sorry for
drawing over your drawing
that's a bad luck
uh color it may be like a little bit
gray so it's not like a overwhelming all
right let me let me look up Halloween oh
it's such a cute sticker
or the pumpkin
or what what's a cute sticker
oh no no I was talking about the pumpkin
thank you oh oh oh good I have a good
one maybe in a darker space can I draw
on top of your hair or my hair oh of
course I'm already doing that with your
your hair
decoration time
oh no there's your signature oh well I'm
not I'm not gonna draw over your
signature
oh oh okay
are you drawing a ghost what are you
drawing yes
good guess yay
the ghost is eating the egg oh yes
yummy oh spooky so spooky oh this is so
spooky scary wow
okay
spooky
[Music]
haha
and
[Music]
um I want to draw I want to draw oh I
have more ideas and
we do know candy corn
uh yes I think uh the triangle looking
thing right yeah with the orange like I
I've never eaten it before but it's
quite the Halloweeny American
candy thing right yeah so typical oh my
God that reminds me do you want a Kiara
tangent a short one yeah sure of course
I went to the supermarket and I cannot
believe what I saw what
candy corn no
apparently we are starting to sell in
Austria and Germany [\h__\h] Pop-Tarts
what oh Pop Tarts
I'm wait what is this doing here this
people gonna maybe like buy it once for
curiosity and then they're gonna realize
this is this is not yummy this is
disgusting and then they won't buy
anything I want to try to like okay I
bought Pop-Tarts right because I don't
know why is it such a you know famous
snack or something because it's so cheap
I don't know
so I heated it up and I was like eating
it I'm like why is it why does it taste
so
I don't know it didn't taste like what I
would imagine it would taste like and
did I not you know prepare this
correctly
[Music]
ugly disgusting by default it's not you
wow I don't think they will be very
successful but
um
the packaging it looks so yummy so it's
very to see this deceiving I'm adding
like a little Shadow to the ghost oh
yeah it might pop up a little bit more
yes spooky wow
that's so scary
I'm making a bat that looks really
shitty it's okay I think my border looks
really bad whatever it's fine
you can add uh
I wish we had Sparkles you can add maybe
Sparkle brush that's a luxury
yeah
we're now you know living you know
simply simple living
laughs
oh wait it's missing I was wondering
like what's missing is the ears
we have some ears I'm gonna maybe we're
gonna make it like pop up a little bit
too thank you
there's so many
um
what else what else what else do we add
can you draw like a black hat somewhere
a black hat what a black cat oh yeah
sure sure yeah I can do that I'll use
the same color as the bats
um let's see
you know some of my fans have been like
um starting this project where they
commission artists to draw me with like
collab partners that I collab with
before but in like a purikura style
it's like a project they have going on
because I talked so much about purikoda
before and it's like this whole thing so
this reminds me of that they can add
this to the project
by yours truly
do you think like adding this here is
fine
the black cap yes yes yes
I have one more idea
what what's one more
spider web oh yeah like they can be in
the corners
like in the corner oh yeah I can try I
can probably drawing it like in this
corner because spider webs they don't
really take up that much space
okay okay a new drawers by the web and
then
I draw one more one more candy corn
one more
yeah you know it's it's getting so
nicely decorated it feels it feels so
Lively yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
are you not gonna give the cat a face
um I don't know you think I should give
it a face yes A Derpy face
[Music]
I can do that
hmm what kind of a Derpy face though I'm
thinking thinking thinking it's getting
a little bit cluttered now but that's
okay that's what purikura is it should
be cluttered
[Music]
suit okay I think I can zoom in how do I
zoom in again oh there we go
oh
my gosh if I have zoomed in while
drawing this would have been so much
easier but yeah uh you know I made a
I made these two windows just in case I
want to zoom in
so that you guys can see like everything
anyways but at the end of the day at the
end of the day I never once even zoomed
in until now
what
yes happy Halloween
yeah I think this face is okay what's
your favorite Halloween movie my
favorite Halloween movie I don't
actually watch that much I remember you
know I remember like Nightmare Before
Christmas or something like that yeah my
mom loved that we watched that one uh
did we watch it on Christmas
is The Nightmare Before Christmas a
Christmas movie or Halloween movie way
that's a good question it could be both
but I think we considered it more as a
Christmas movie because of the title
yeah I guess so
yeah I don't actually watch Halloween
movies have you ever watched
um Halloween
is that a movie wait am I hallucinating
have I ever watched Halloween
Ride the movie yeah yeah yeah
what's that um it's a it's a it's a
classic movie it's basically like a
slasher you know uh
yeah yeah yeah Michael Myers
yeah it has it has he has his whole
theme song and all yeah it's an old
movie I think it did it get remade or
something
but it's okay if you haven't because I
recently tried watching it and I
couldn't finish it why because it was
too scary oh not really I think uh you
need a little bit of patience I think I
was expecting some fast-paced action and
it was like a little bit slow so you
have to like watch it like Patiently I
haven't I haven't watched it
yes yes yes
yeah that's what I always uh that's what
I'm always curious about because like I
found out about Halloween actually like
pretty recently like not recent recent
but like I guess recently compared to
like other Halloween movies like uh you
know like Friday is it the guy in the
hockey mask that's Friday the 13th right
and then there's also
uh for for Freddy who was it the
nightmare on what Elm Street I don't
know man like don't ask me like those
movies I know like since the beginning
but like Halloween I never actually
found out until like a little bit like
more recent
[Music]
I only know
um Scary Movie
that's the only kind of scary Halloween
movie that I know it's just it's so
stupid
yeah well it's fun to watch it's fun to
watch I agree I think I only watched the
first one I think there's like several I
did watch the first one I'm pretty sure
multiple times but yeah I think like
they stopped around like scary movie how
many yeah I kind of lost track I never
watched it it's a scary movie the one
where they
um there's like a a uh this crazy girl
that's being
um
uh
oh God oh God oh no wasn't there
something with like um what do you call
it again when you try to get the the
evil ghosts out of people
ah
yeah the evil gold exorcism
wait was that was that in the scary
movie or was that in a different movie
no it might yeah yeah there was like I
think there was like a reference about
like something like that The Exorcist or
am I wrong am I hallucinating there was
probably a reference to that
then I watched scary movie too and not
one
yeah yeah yeah
oh yeah could be oh I don't know yeah
the the girl yeah yeah she reverse drank
no that was such a [\h__\h] movie
I watched it like oh my God
15 18 years ago
yeah there was like just a lot
did you know about uh say uh what was it
I Know What You Did Last Summer did you
ever watch that
it's about the dude and like the I think
the raincoat or whatever I think uh I
think she did let me look up the poster
the movie picture ah
I've definitely heard of it but I don't
think I watched it
um
is that one more serious or is it also
just oh the hell that's serious that's
serious that's serious
yeah it's serious it's not like scary
movie
yeah and I think one of the scary movies
also made a parody of that
yes yes
there's a scene that's a parody of like
based on that movie it's about some
teens who did something really bad and
then somebody starts like uh terrorizing
them and then like giving them nothing I
Know What You Did Last Summer and then
people get killed and stuff
look yeah and then uh there's also like
the new Scream movie which I haven't
watched yet which I need to watch
yeah I will not watch it with you why
I don't wanna you must find someone else
for that yeah
[Laughter]
but what what what should I do to make
you want to watch the scary movie maybe
with me if you're scared of watching it
yourself
but but we can play Fatal Frame together
so at least that's something
I guess so I guess so
yes of course I'll tell you
um what time then later okay yes I
didn't figure it out yet when I'm gonna
stream it but all right then I think we
finished uh the pretty good yeah
all right happy Halloween wait how do
you save this how do you save this
before before we ask before we forget
I think
download all layers
send the canvas to Twitter now I'm just
gonna
is it download all layers
so oh yeah
yeah but with
um background color white
that works for me download all layers
oh oh for me background color display
wait what I did I didn't buy it oh okay
okay
yeah I don't okay let's try one more
time let's download all layers download
all layers okay
thank God we didn't lose it even though
it was somewhere in the middle it seemed
like we yeah oh my goodness it was just
like me drawing over like a blob of skin
color
yeah you guys didn't get to see it
because it all went back to normal which
is good
okay thank you so much
[Music]
I had a lot of fun drawing with you and
I'm gonna post this on Twitter thank you
for forcing me to um draw because
um normally I don't make myself draw
anything oh yeah me too if you ever if
you ever want to draw with me or
something I think this is fun you know
just like a little exercise with a theme
or something just hit me up I would love
to drop
what do you mean teach me
drawing ah let's let's be stronger
together let's be stronger together yeah
I mean you get what I mean all right
guys
um okay we did say our announcements uh
before but since we're ending the stream
do you want to announce you know what's
coming soon
on your side
uh well hello live English has something
coming out uh in the next like couple
days so yeah some people are speculating
oh what is what is it I wonder oh
I think a lot of people are very
confused
if you go on the whole live English
Twitter they changed their their image
to their profile picture to like a noise
noise picture and they uploaded a video
with noise and I think it was bails
Hawkings
what is this okay yeah anyway so that's
something we're following and then for
blood but that besides that nothing okay
okay tomorrow at 8pm GMT plus 7 or 10 pm
jst I will be uh you know there will be
a cover premiere of eye color before uh
vocals by Pavilion radio and cobokanaidu
so share with your friends share with
your family share with your extended
family in your WhatsApp you know just
like copy and paste the link to your
group your college friends or whatever
because the more the merrier ride and
then uh I'm also gonna be participating
in a project that
um hasn't really been fully revealed yet
it's been teased on Twitter at least so
if you guys saw one of my retweets then
yeah
project yeah what is it I wonder
share with your pets truth let's go and
then
yeah and then there's still more but you
know
um it's still uh in Hush Hush but look
forward to rainy projects uh next month
as well yay
keep your eyes peeled okay
okay today and we'll talk about the
Fatal Frame thing later okay
thank you yeah okay and now we're ending
the stream we're gonna be saying
[Music]
let's go
I lost my cursor no I won't hit you
[Music]
come on
foreign
[Music]