e
[Music]
[Applause]
n no
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
I was B to tears like 9,000 years every
back and forth and compo cl me like a
knif but then I saw it in your eyes and
it took me by surprise 10,000 Vol both
to my heart
life and I want you here right now you
know cuz I'm ready to let go get me
through the night somehow show me all
you
know my r mystery one kiss and you'll
agree if you're down to get familiarize
and baby say it right e r i s s a k play
with fire take me
high
never play with fire take me
high Bur up the floor you got a Vibe I
can't ignore and a sea of Embers dancing
way into the
night The Best Is Yet To Come cuz you're
not like anyone get a B so One Shining
so
bright there's a scent that's filling up
the air and you're still unaware but
you're falling fast under my spell oh
baby it is a fair when a mix up this
solution I am anyone and everyone
logic Fades away tonight you got to say
it right e r i s s
AAR fire take me
[Music]
high play with fire take me
high take me higher
it's a
game play with
fire say my
name play with
name say
my glorify your
take me take me play with fire take
me play with fire take me
[Music]
high fire take me
high oh
[Music]
hi you Darlings this is hollow life
English Advent Devol Diva and today I'm
here hosting a cooking show in my very
own kitchen delicious devilish dishes
and as you can see it's basically my
kitchen however I must tell you this is
actually a replica if you'd like to look
on the other side yes you can see the
jail Birds hard at work making sure that
this show goes on without a hitch but
today is also about me as you can see
it's my 3D debut how do I look how is it
am I beautiful am I am I met
sexy uh I you could you could look me up
and down I suppose starting with my uh
lovely shoes going all the way up to my
skirt and you might realize something's
missing since we're cooking today I've
decided to remove my jacket so say
goodbye to my wings but without further
Ado I suppose we ought to get cooking
right get right onto things so uh first
I suppose I have two lovely guests I'd
like you to meet if they'd like to come
on
out congratulations 3
[Music]
debut would you like to give an
introduction real quick oh oh
you
okay GP Hol takou
and then hii everybody K I am takas from
Whole Life English myth and you notice
something we are birds birds birds
birds H toi and H Tori
in so will you like prove yourself to us
today mhm so they're going to be cooking
and I'm going to be cooking but shall we
start with the first dish yes I am
hungry I'm hungry too do that oh is
going to be making us something called
nikua okay Nika Japanese traditional I
love Nika it's my first time so I'm very
excited shall we get
started let's go let's go let's
[Music]
go all right let's start make
ni I'm hungry hungry hungry
please make I will make Nika for
n sorry Sor you too you too don't worry
you too you
toai too yesai so all right here what we
we need Nik Jaga is here the
ingredients take a look wow I'm down
this is
personal okay let's start will cutting
vegetable
cutting and put them in in the
pan
yes fry yes sir it's already in there
o to good you made them appear out of
nowhere and please for
uh meat meat first meat first yeah meat
first and then add veget change change
the color change color and put vegetable
okay so not like we did it where we
threw the potato in first yeah cook the
meat then add the vegetables and cook
them down a it looks so
good smell
good and change the
color oh it's okay uh-huh good lady
already so yeah put water and seasoning
oh she
standa the
okay
hey thank you what did you thr in there
yes there we
go good I just threw everything oh
everything okay okay so please wait 10
minutes 10 minutes 10 minutes will C
cover and get a lid for it
okay hi question hi why why is it like a
lid like inside and not like on the top
oh I see I see
[Music]
uh it will be like easier to soak in the
flavor yes yes yes yes oh more delicious
W 10 minutes wait wait I'm waiting
patiently it takes too long I can't wait
10 minutes yeah I don't want to wait 10
minutes either can we hry up yeah can we
use some magic maybe to speed up the
process is that some magic all right so
please put love oh okay yeah it's
[Music]
[Applause]
magic after 10 minutes okay
easy will check check yeah take off oh
looks good Che soft or hard oh oh a
little bit hard hard still so if hard
please wait more 10 minutes okay all
right but M
[Music]
magic okay s the finger yes okay soft
soft yes soft good so complete complete
[Music]
finished okay
my I'm so excited as you can see it
smells
great and it looks good too as you guys
can see this is the real the real it's
real but uh I'm hungry okay me too is
probably hungry shall we try
[Music]
[Applause]
first IO for
[Music]
carrot
actually eat rice together is very good
we have no rice now but yeah today is no
rice without rice is also
[Music]
okay it's like impression m makes me
think it's a very homey flavor like um
it feels like this is something I would
eat as a kid and want to eat like want
to come home and eat you know after like
a long
day very
good please listen
[Music]
yeah oh my L Lou um
can you make every day for me every day
yeah but easy to cooking yeah she taught
you so now you can make it yourself okay
yes but it's so
good I'm like really hungry I feel like
if you weren I will cook it you yes okay
every day but I want to eat like fried
fried chicken or
I want to eat we do happen to have the
queen of fried chicken with us today mhm
you have to make your signature dish for
us I want to
eat let's go showy let's go
[Music]
go y it is time to bring kfp to your
kitchen I'm going to make the best fried
chicken I've ever made in my whole life
I want to try
I wen't you e Fried Chicken we're
missing thank you for the beautiful
intro we're missing some livestock what
are we going to use oh well I actually
have the perfect thing right here JY
Jimmy take me instead take me no sorry
Jimmy if anyone's qualified to do this
it's me as a past
kfp not anymore well I I mean this used
to be my form right I guess so so but
now I look like this so anyways Jimmy
come
[Applause]
maybe I can't even look do you think
he's too big I think maybe he needs to
be a bit smaller don't
you extreme
Violet thank you Jimmy for your
contribution my God this is so sad it's
okay he'd be happy are we is this going
to be enough for all of us there will
yeah some we'll use magic all right then
here we have the the batter and the
flour so I'll I'll do this for you okay
I'll do my best g m o I will do my best
let me take it up so you can see clearly
secret spicy yeah it's got secret spices
we're getting deep in there
Jimmy looking shiny wow okay and then we
go into the flower the
[Music]
flower it's nice and coated as you can
see some spices were mixed onto that too
but they're secret secret nice okay and
with that it's time we have a 160°
Celsius celius heated up oil thingy
what's it called so dangerous H Deep
Fryer deep fryer I knew that that was
also a test question so
we
go to get
in it's dangerous oh already oh it's
already finished that was oh my God yeah
want one those
those on the
floor yay you've got you've got crazy
hands to be able to handle that
Phoenix I guess so it doesn't feel like
anything at all yeah nothing at all
[Music]
phoen thank you
Jimmy and now finally the food of dreams
for any kfp
fan the proper or the biggest
fear Kiara fried Phoenix your final form
final form kfp you're looking at it but
without further Ado I really want to
taste it don't you yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
wait we're really eating chicken
right yeah I did a good job you did
that's like a lemony taste in it I think
where's the lemon come from did I put
lemon in there you must have maybe put Z
it wasn't a batter already probably mhm
oh she you know you're the
CEO spice is good like my my jimmies
work for
[Music]
me no it's really really good M maybe a
little
bit
dry mine's nice and juicy after after
one bite yeah I want to more Bri yeah
more bright more bright I want sace yeah
want some sauce I want sweet sour sauce
M I understand oh yeah it's good party
food we're having a party should we do
sleepover too I would like
[Music]
that good job thank you thank
you thank you Jimmy your sacrifice is
letting us eat the best food ever kfp
you're the best thank you for your
dedication thank you Jimmy thank you
thank you
KP you know you guys have both cooked
but I haven't cooked anything yet
actually so I think I have something
special it's not technically my dish
however it's using things from uh Hol
life English so to make
something so if you'd like without
further Ado I would like to cook for you
so let's
go cooking be good looking for
[Music]
us here we are ready to make the last
dish of the day oh dessert uh
well behind us we have all of the
ingredients if you'll take a look I call
this dish Hollow live soup Hol n soup
W no no no see these were donated by my
Senai to me to make a soup with I asked
them I said ah I want to make a
delicious soup so what will you give me
and this sorry I important job okay see
see you see you see you see give her a
chance maybe we'll try it could be good
you don't know yet all right well uh I
guess I guess I'll get started oh okay
right into it uh we're going to be
making it in this
big magical mystical and we're starting
out with some chicken Salt donated by by
she gave me up before as a
present I'm so sorry you can't do that I
didn't to out no I you know I think it's
fine I think it's fine that
way what's next H this is donated by
Shi it's an eggplant and it looks like
yoro her little a mascot
guy yeah he's so cute isn't he so just
right in there
not you know if we cook it long enough
it'll like disintegrate right so yeah it
doesn't really make sense to cut it out
cuz it's going to cut itself like what
do you have the kitchen for right and a
knife you don't need that no cutting and
this one can you predict who it could be
from uh it
says it's beu feet salt salt be
flake so stink it's just a little oh my
God I can Lally smell salt it's it's
okay now we have that yeah it's okay
it's okay it's okay this is from M Senai
don't drop the whole thing try try to be
more careful maybe this time okay okay
my God it's okay
over
horrible still we still have the saing
still have a sapling which I'm sure this
will absorb all the salt right veggies
yes so but first I want to cut off
this I know it's sad sorry about your
haircut yeah well I guess that's fine
could have cut it a bit more and then we
just have a little bit of garnish to put
on top no how about you eat it
separately no no no they're GRE Donuts
donated by uh fuaa and Moco respectively
they each gave me one so let's go
ahead however it doesn't stop there now
we have to stir the soup so we have to
give it a really good stir with all
those ingredients
look it's coming together you see the
color green yeah it's the it's fine it's
fine look it's not even there yet no
that looks like meon soda or something
just a little
more
go not perfect
Murasaki
Murasaki my God it's perfect it it looks
like something from hollow life right
and no don't you think I'm sure it's
delicious I I don't want to eat yeah
really good Nik is there more
Nika to finish so let's try it oh my
God finish let's eat it let's eat it
let's eat let's eat it it's fine you
guys have to taste it oh my God you
don't have a choice get back
here this
is I'm you're my oi so you have to 3D
debut anniversary okay okay okay 3D
debut all right let's go let's
go and we're finally ready here is the
final Dish as we've served it up uh
don't you think it looks delicious I
don't even want to look why it looks
good come on it's purple it's got donuts
in it it's going to be delicious looks
like grape juice it shouldn't like no
it's okay let's try it without further
Ado Abomination how do it smell how's
the
a good point smell is okay smells okay
smell is okay
[Music]
see okay don't knock it before you try
it's like burning my nostrils it'll be
okay all right
eat same
timing no what did you do to us I didn't
do anything she wants to poison oh my
God she wants to take control of h
no it's not it's really not that bad
what have you eaten all your life it's
not that bad it's fine you dous yeah
yeah yeah I'll try again see maybe hers
tastes different oh oh my God is this
the same yeah
same same same same cannot no sorry n
it's Hardy and it'sing enough enough
enough thank you this is not how you you
you can treat your Senpai no no
congratulations
congratulations see where you going
thank
byebye
unbelievable I can't believe this well
of course jailbirds I'm sure you don't
think such a thing about my cooking
right surely you see it and you thought
ah the brilliant purple color is
wonderful so uh won't you tell tell me
won't you praise me come on jail bir
don't you like
it wasn't it
delicious well I guess that's it for my
cooking show this is probably the pilot
episode and the only episode so I guess
if you enjoyed we won't be back so time
to distract you with this s performance
it
[Music]
let's go
Dynamite
[Music]
for yeah yeah yeah
wo wo wo wo dance dance all of the
[Music]
night e
everybody
mystery mystery
[Music]
wo w w dance dancing all of the
night breakdown
[Music]
love love love
machine love love
love love is so Wonder
[Music]
dance dancing all of the
night
Dance all of the night
[Music]
love machine
oh hi Darlings I didn't quite see you
there it's it's not that kind of thing
though uh welcome to my studio this is
where I do all of my recording of course
you've heard of it but this is your
first time being here but more
importantly uh my my little guy here
here quoting it hi look it Shadow my
baby my baby bird isn't he cute I know
you guys are always begging to see him
so there you go and now that we're done
cooking I've gone ahead and put my my
jacket back on very nice right it really
adds to the appeal but today is not only
all about me I have some wonderful
special guests if you'd like to come on
out and introduce yourselves hi
Daddy Daddy what's up Darlings it's your
boy Darlings yeah I don't know I'm just
trying to you know get with the match
the vibe that you have going here n this
place is awesome yeah you like it
yeah open
this I'm so happy to have these two
wonderful ladies here with me today
thanks for inviting us
congratul looks so good you look lovely
yeah well I'm so excited cuz we have a
song we're going to be performing for
all of you I know Trio between Ki Marin
and narissa who would have it but the
team is not quite ready yet so first I
thought we could uh l practice a script
that we are performing because you know
we are profession actors hi this thing
this thing that script that script for
that thing yeah do you know do you
remember what our show is called I sure
do but can you go ahead and and I guess
recite it for the audience who doesn't
know going to be
um good question yeah done done look
it's it's on here you see oh oh check it
can you read uh yeah totally can you
read it's I think a brush with death a
pirates tail a pirates tail so please
look forward to it coming out on Hollow
tv.com totally real site right
eventually it'll be out at some point oh
oh my god oh my god let's go everyone
let's go let's go you're ready it's a
good one
okay
okay my godess of love I
have i h please my present please a
wonderful job finding my lost we's
Captain but you must realize this was
not the treasure I spoke of what of
course not it never was it was always
about what you had not what I lost all
of these things were stolen from my
idiot siblings thousands of years ago I
planted these here for safekeeping and
they were safe at least until the waves
took this place you Ro
Thea what no what I'm saying is I knew
where it was the whole time I Cuts what
did she see in you a beautiful young
woman like her with an old hag like you
oh I'm young
beautiful yeah and I'm the goddess of
death look at you you're creeping slowly
towards your
grave I'm a sexy Captain P
Captain yes well moving on I brought you
here to exact my revenge on you captain
for the untimely death of your lover you
I know that you are the one to take her
life and I will not stand for it you
will suffer by my hands
huh you know this Quest was just a
distraction it was meant to keep you
from watching over your beautiful and
sexy
lover and leave room for me to take your
place but now your lover is dead and I
am left with a hole in my heart you will
pay for what you've done here and now
that's enough of that
death what are you doing here don't you
usually work the graveyard shift unless
you're planning planning on bringing
back my beautiful little bird to me you
can turn right around and poof yourself
back to wherever it is you came
from well maybe you don't know me as
well as you pretend to or the pirate
Captain as well as you think either I
that's look you can go ahead and smite
that human if you like I'm not going to
try and stop you but I really think you
might regret doing that you would take
the side of someone so cruel that they
would take the life of their own lover I
expected better of
you besides how am I supposed to take
their place and make that beautiful
cream puff my wife if this fool here has
killed her wait what you want
the no where did you even get that from
why would you even think that I would
want someone as old and badly dressed as
you but
you no it has always been that treasure
box of wonder that twintail talent that
sweet girl who can do no sin that you
kept back on land that is the one I have
wanted you no not at
all yeah but you just called that
treasure box of Wonder a hag not 2
minutes ago what are you even talking
about I called this wrinkly old wreck
here in front of me a hang not my
beautiful bride to be oh man this is
Rich you really have no idea do you
narissa why are you laughing I not a I'm
17 let me see if I can help you here
maybe all the beauty is being hidden by
this I have
not no she is actually his much more be
lover who you claim to love that's right
here is the modding you thought was lost
that's not possible I would have known
or or I never would have I have a lot to
say but my most pressing question is how
on Earth did you not know you know
that's fair because they look nothing
alike but how was I supposed to know how
did such a simple mustache make her look
so decidedly unattractive it's just a
mustache I'm a still cute of course you
are dear she's just an imbe w why am I
so mean can me change that um anyway uh
but my dear her stupidity can't protect
you now that you've broken our deal a
broken deal with death means that your
soul is mine this is all your fault
drama queen you claimed to love mum but
you had no idea that she was hiding
behind a mustach because of your idiocy
idiocy that's kind of mean too her soul
is mine now
me how was I supposed to know she was
never supposed to be on this quest in
the first place wait if she's here then
that must mean the real pirate Captain
is dead and that's your domain Miss
Reaper if the captain is gone it means
you have had some responsibility in all
of this you could have stopped all of
this at any
time oh so you want to blame me for all
of this it wasn't me who killed the
captain I only protected mine after she
begged for me to help hide her identity
from you she just wanted to complete
your stupid quest in honor of her lover
yes but you shouldn't have agreed to
hide her I would have known if you
hadn't meddled and I would have given
her my favor without this
Quest my soul you're lucky she's here to
keep me from hurting you I'd like to see
you try besides this one wasn't me
so I
his tee but wasn't the captain deadly
allergic to
bananas wow should have seen that one
coming I wanted an
adventure but he said that no so forness
uh that's huh wasn't expecting that
unfortunately that means that you a
human meddled in matters of life and
death however after that night you uh
helped me catch that escape Soul a few
weeks back I haven't been able to stop
thinking about you it looks like you've
already won the heart of the Grim Reaper
so consider yourself lucky what night
don't you dare I will protect this woman
from her own crimes even in death no one
else has to know that she was the one
who took the life of her lover it can
all just be an unfortunate accident
banana peels are known to be
slippery no she'll never be able to
escape the Reaper clutches and I can't
allow that to happen after all this is
your fault myy for even letting her take
this deal in the first place
but Mor's doing that's her fault her
fault uh if you come with me I can
protect you from even death itself she
can't get you in the realm of the
Immortals oh you absolute but
no you'll be known as the goddess who
protected the banana Bandit the others
won't be very happy with you and you
think that matters to me
why van they'll blame it on her of
course no the best course of action is
for me to take her to protect her and up
talk think fast
[Music]
Nissa thank you thank you thank you and
good news girls it's seems like the
music team is all ready for us so why
don't we head over and show them our
super cool song performance let's do it
let's
go wow cool place you got thank
you
[Applause]
[Music]
for
for what I
[Music]
got for
another more
[Music]
for
fore fore
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
thank you guys for
coming so fun thank
you oh my God
oh my
god wow it's getting H thank you for
coming too yeah no problem I'm happy to
be here congrats on PRD thank you made
it's so special to have you two as guest
and to get to sing with you too that's
crazy but we still have one more song
after this one not all of us just me
sadly we have to say goodbye to these
lovely ladies but the jailbird Tech have
to set it up so we're going to say
goodbye for a few seconds and I'll be
right back let's go okay see you byebye
byebye
byebye so this last song for today is
actually going to be the titular track
of my new EP in my feelings song is the
same name uh I really worked hard on
this song I think it came out great so I
hope you guys will enjoy listening to my
first live performance of it
[Music]
can't believe the words that came out of
your mouth your mouth never thought that
what we had would go this round this can
see the clock is ticking but I just
can't stop thinking every little memy is
tormenting
[Music]
Mees want to sleep but it won't happen
for the I'm wake we live in the past and
still haunted by the ghost of you
everywhere look it's like you're always
there despite the fact that I'm on my
own I'm in my
feelings like braful on the ground
they're soaking through the sheets of
drench and every single inch of me I'm
in my
feelings it's falling all around inside
there's never ending down for it's a no
you to look you in the eyes the
up night you left and
you that morning I awoken my heart bred
and broken feeling I could drown in the
tears I cried
s like I'm submerged in
water struggling to Brea just thinking
about it stilled by the ghost of you
everywhere I look it's like you're
always there despite the fact you left
me alone I'm in my
feeling like r on the ground they
soaking through the sheets of drench and
every single inch of me I'm in my
feelings it's falling all around inside
this never ending down for it's a no
escap
to
do where going oh I don't want to
[Music]
know don't need you to call me don't
need you to love me don't want your weak
explanations know that I never met your
expectations now I just want you up my
head want to move along carry on hold my
head high but I'm in my
feelings like Greatful on the ground
they're soaking through the sheets of
drench and every single inch of me I'm
in my
feelings it's falling all around but at
the end and another this down for it's a
hope I waited
for yeah I'm in my feelings
feelings yeah I'm in my feelings
feelings ooh yeah I'm in my feelings
feelings at the end of another this down
for is a rainel I have prayed for
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm
no it's a w been cled that wasn't enough
for us needy jail Birds please jail
birds do you know what time it is
[Music]
say
un
un un
got I
got oh
jailbird you guys wanted one more
song I see come come here come
here well I suppose if it's you guys
asking then how can I resist uh but uh
you know I am going to perform one more
song for you I think it's going to be
super hype but before that I have uh
some important things to tell you about
but first reminiscing already today was
so much fun I had such a good time
cooking Lou and Takashi kiaha Senpai the
Niko was so
delicious like honestly of everything I
think that was the most delicious thing
and I really did fulfill my my title as
the demon of soup because I made a
really weird mind you soup but it was
good and then getting to read that
really silly script in mine and cie it
was so much fun the banana banana oh my
God mine is a natural comedian obviously
because she's in hollow life we're all
comedians uh and I've had so much fun
performing for you guys if you enjoyed
that last song uh in my feelings I hope
you did um I I was so happy to finally
get to share that with you guys so I
hope you've enjoyed everything that I've
given you so far but without further
further Ado I do have some goods for you
or a good for you so let's go ahead and
take a
look ah here it is so this is based off
of my tuning fork which some of you may
know some of you may not know is also
actually a microphone but as you can see
this is a paper knife or a paper cutter
do you have mail that has been you know
really annoying you as you try to open
it you're like ah I can't get it well
this will solve that do you have a
problem and you just like cutting paper
this will help you too any of your paper
cutting needs this will help you again
it's pretty much a replica of my weapon
so if you think that's cool if you want
it it also comes in a cool box so please
do consider picking it up H my paper
knif so also as I already mentioned
before my EP just came out it's already
been out for a little bit now but if you
haven't heard it there's three new songs
it Al includes a fourth say my name
which of course already a fan favorite
but if you haven't already it's
available on streaming services it's
available on YouTube please go give it a
listen I work so hard on it and I'm so
proud of all the songs uh of course you
heard the titular track in my feelings I
I you know that one I poured a lot of
myself into I think it's just so
fantastic but there's two other songs
that you have yet to hear today so if
you haven't already please go ahead and
check it out again so proud of it and
I'm hoping all of them can get to a
million listens on Spotify so please
listen to them lots and lots and lots
but without further Ado you guys did
call me on here for an encore so I guess
I'll stop Shilling and I'll start
singing so without further Ado Please
Listen to Swedish Scarlet
[Applause]
my swear
[Music]
myar my sweetest Scarlet my sweetest
Scarlet looking to find the words to
tell you this feeling's brand new trying
to make do still I can feel my heart is
traveling
inside the group wishing you would make
a move cuz I can't even look away your
eyes are shine and still there's
something that you're hiding won't you
tell me with the warmth of your
lips how you found me was lonely then
you filled my heart up holy let me know
let me know let me know it keeps you
smiling by my side if a b below me baby
you're my one and only let me show let
me show let me show you I can love love
you through the night yeah
my my
sest baby you're on my mind all of the
time yeah you plus me I can get behind
my truly you got my heart right from the
start you fil Me With Your
Love stand with you beneath the
Moonlight it's
midnight shine is so bright
longing to have you through the gold
night stay close warm m into each
other's arms don't need permission my
decisions already made clear you can
feel it from the moment we kiss how you
found me was only then you filled my
heart up holy let me know let me know
let me know it keeps you smiling by my
side if a b below me baby you're my one
and only let me show let me show let me
show you I can love you through the
night yeah my
sweetest
Oar just want you to hold me
darling cuz how you found me was Sly
then you filled my heart up holy let me
know let me know let me know it keeps
you smiling by my side fall below me
baby you're my one and only let me show
let me show let me show you I can love
you through the night
yeah baby you're on my mind all of the
time yeah you plus me I can get behind
my my
sarl truly you got my heart right from
the start you fill me with your love
my sweetest Scarlet my sweetest
[Music]
Scarlet my sweetest Scarlet my sweetest
Scarlet
jailbirds thank you so much for coming
to my 3D debut
I hope I was able to put on a wonderful
performance for you seeing all these
flowers it seems that was the case so
thank you so much I hope you enjoyed my
new music uh I hope you enjoyed my
performances and seriously thank you
thank you so much for coming I love you
jail
Birds
bye-bye bye-bye bye-bye bye bye bye bye
bye bye-bye thank you you bye-bye
[Music]
e