[Music]
Nh,
good, good
hoop same
[Music]
Nm
me
can you do
[Music]
N
yeah
[Music]
le
N
me
ha ha [Music] Nh, yeah yeah
[Music]
Nn
Nm
me
can you do
[Music]
Nm, yeah, yeah, ugh,
uni-nee-ha
, that's a lie. Good evening,
my cute Yukimura and others.
So,
good evening, everyone. Today, it's
been a long time since I've identified Horai Mushin. Yes, the color of this live show is a bit cute, cute, and weird. Now that I know about it, let's read on.
Tiara-sama,
Ti!
Guard me
From Suita to Sekihara sonar wings Good evening everyone & Hodo diving interest Takanashi
Chiara overview
Hosomaki cake haha
goo
nao
Hmm, please listen a little more and say you want your own Chuo Road. I'm nervous,
nervous, nervous.
It's about me today. I'm worried that people will find out that I'm an idiot.
Thank you. It's okay. It's a loss.
Director.  But I'm looking forward to being interviewed, and I'm
looking forward to it, and I'm looking forward to it, and I'm looking forward to it, and I'm looking forward to it, and I'm looking forward to it, and I'm going to take off my mackerel, so I'm thinking about it,
and Choco has already accepted it properly, so
let's take it here.
[Music]  Come
in and put it on
haroo
Oh, I'm so cold when it comes to that kind of thing, so the result
is Saganti, why is
Adrapura unemployed?
From Morse, that's a natural natural appearance.
Well, if you do everything, let's go home.
So,
before I start streaming today, I thought I'd first decide if there would be two people.Yes, yes, I think it's
probably the
air tag bridge.  I
wonder if everyone will do it for 5 minutes with a hashtag on the broadcast that starts from now on
DF is a bridge type 4 Tomorrow I
asked the leg type of the person's meeting O 72  I
said good Bizlill Yeah Yeah,
Disney is good as soon as Ana is born, huhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhha
Genuine
chocolate and 5 little birds are ski
enthusiasts.The
diameter of the judge's circle is chicken, right?
But now, when it comes to foreign gods,
my brother and I are not pony, so I bought it knowing the difference.Because it's
already the fastest.  The only thing I'm trying to do is to go back to school
and cook chicken for the Air Flo Perth Food restaurant.I
guess it's because I'm a phoenix.
Newly, everyone understands that the car used at Choco is a
betel obscene 6. Ok Well, there was Urawa, I understand, the food looks delicious.
Hey, ha,
there's a lot of Choco-chan himself. He's noticeably cute. He's the neighborhood winner.
If you'd like, everyone, I'd be happy if you could tweet a lot with #ChocolateFund as the tag for today's broadcast.Eeee
tale.It's not
something I want to endure.Chocolate this summer.
Well, when he took off Tiara-sama's clothes, I got blamed for looking at him.
But,
yes, Tiara-sama was a little naughty on the line. Hey, I
got a little photo of him. He's a naughty
guy.  Yes, naughty guys
are naughty, but please show me aaa
hey meow
3 f Photos of that h Can I show you the raw material of this book?
Oh this or
this?  Ah,
oh, not, I'm going to wear a hat at the time of limiter and look at the counter expansion. I'm
sorry.  Let's
just say it from the feet, like the cat was a deer.
Yeah, the feet were good, too. The sneakers were really good, but I looked at them and thought, Miyata, this is
cool.
Good, good.  I do
n't like the cap or the thin Ronnie.It's
in my absolute realm, and I'm
thankful for the part with the meat on it.Often
, these socks aren't a normal shape, and the poop part looks a bit like a feather.No
Katase  It's cute, is
n't it? It's really cute, but I think it's a little more narrow-minded than the absolute price, so I like it.
Yes, it's true that it's already a little bit too much for a normal document addressed to Absolute Possession.That
skirt is way too short.Ah, that skirt is too short.Futuro
Girly Week is great.If it's
this long between cars, I'll close it already.
Moscato is said to be a bed and rides in 3 forms. It's
light asv. It's like sending it off when it lands. I don't want it to go any longer. I do
n't want it to go any faster.
Perfect for the role of Runha, Perfect Wings of Sky Ichigokan
Donbaek Kihoskar To
sum up, I
thought their Sakko belts were quite impressive.Can you
see what it says?
Zoom in.  Let's wait a minute!
10 points during the operation
[Music]
Okay, okay,
wait a minute, I
can see you
[Music]
TG Rank
Golden Lion
What's the point, come on, daddy, he
gave me this belt, but the
magic part is to pass through the long root phoenix's nest, so when I
use that, Sakuragumo, well, actually, my appearance has changed, but I can transform.  I
said that, and the
Meiji government is in trouble, it seems like it's an opposition party.I was really saying that, I'm no good anymore, and this tape was pasted
on my face.
Well, the reason why Kanna is really bad is because of Kido, who begged him many times, and Colt
told him to be a little quieter in his current form.Andy
also laughed when he took her home, complaining that she wasn't old enough.  I'm a dog person, I'm a rap
guy.
Oh, I guess I should wear a belt. I
don't like it, but I tend to make loud noises. I'm a refugee. When I look at this, there's something black on my waist.  I
can see it, is this the boss? Well, hahaha,
Aso no
Sunny, it would
be better. I
don't think there was a sea town attached to it, but it's called a room, kid. It
's a cart. Wiki.  Well, I'm
sure what's inside will be revealed someday on the daily broadcast.  That's
probably not true.The 3rd brother at the recent Otohoro live show was wearing that chanter's body paint,
so oh, Ninoya, I
have to eat something, I'm not hiding it, I'm getting painted.
Moore,
there's a
sound coming from my dad. It's okay to hear the sound coming from the os. He's a
good guy at home. When I heard this, I stood up and thought, ``It's leaking.''  That
strap that connects the skirt to the top of Yokoi is
good, but
I'm sorry, but I think the wrap is really good too.You
can see a glimpse of the part of the foot underneath the strap.  It's really the best, whatever it is,
ran, it's
ferocious, but I think this slap match is Tae-woong 102 for
a while Hotatomipoo,
yeah, when you say he's exposing his belly button, yeah, it's a little bit more from above.  I'm going
to take my belly button out It
seems like it's a long way, but I'm
putting it out at the very last minute But it's already JD, but it's Meteor, and it's in Lily's place.The
absolute score is 1.This
is a big help.Ah,
this is away.  Hmm, I'm
going to do it inside.I
think their moe sleeves are super cute.Ah, yeah, they were
cute before too, but the balance between the waist and hips is really bad.  It's
really packed in. I'm going to praise you, but I'm already
praising you, but you're already showing off your waist. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
This is really a feast for the eyes. Oh, I'm so
full of plump girls.
[Music]
A
tease.
What's that on this chest?
Um, which one is that?  I
had a sword, a sword, and a shield, but even when I don't use it, I put it on this badge.It's so
compact that it's so young.If you look at the picture in the middle, it's
Asuka's pressure-welding type, and the border is early.  Even if it's from the sky, it's getting smaller every day.I
can't see it because it's barely scattered, but I
see.The one
with the chest is hard, and it
's really quite dark.It's dark brown.Jiro is ready soon.Yes
?  I'm really
attached to that scenery, and it's the one that Papa Ran made for me.
No, Happer is the one who made the moose and azaleas do a little
fire day.
I also liked their sound, and I bought it.  At home, when I look at the city, it's
a little bit from Kadashi. I like how you can see a little bit of her armpit pie, too.
Idiot fall, everyone, party hair man princess. There's a
little part of her arm where you can see a glimpse of her armpit pie. Pitch.  Hita lol
Wow, look at this blue
. You're watching this while you're nagging. Yes, the
teacher is lewd. He's helping you more than me.
Oh yeah, chocolate is sold at Steve's. Please understand. It's not a
problem,
no, it's theirs.  Is it an eco ribbon or something like the neck that someone gave you? I
don't know. I
especially like collars that look like rooms.
7 I see. Hmmm.
Their ring piercas Cases, I'm good for the throat, I do
n't grow up from behind that ears, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh,
and it's
so cute and cute
rice
that's really cute.  That said, it's delicious today Hime. I'm
often told that I want something like a normal rough hat as Okutsu, but the
Great Prevention Star is true. Chapter 4 might be a mess. I love Space Pointed Star.  I'm
wearing that mark, but I thought it was a text official, so I
see. Yes, it
's a sub, but that hearing is really said a lot, so the armor is really
serious, and it's a big deal, but I
wish it wouldn't be done.  Well, it
's all growing. The
white ones were originally on. It wasn't just those two, there were a lot of them,
but the
long roots were bald.  I've
become a bit of a fan of Teshikata.I
don't have any leftover earrings, so I want them to recognize them as feathers.I see,
even at home,
this god also looks like a feather and has a gradation.  I thought it was so beautiful,
and the
God of love is so beautiful.I
wash my face with gravy, which is also used for cooking chicken and other dishes, every day.
Well then, there's a
saying that it smells like a fault outside the Tiaratia.I'll give you a jam, Gori Garry Kabbalah Day.If
I
say that, I'll make the water bloom already.I thought it was the third time.It's
Taiko Shampoo.  People often say that
I'm poly. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah  The
characters look delicious, but I can't eat them every time I go to the bathroom.I
can come back to life as many times as I want, but that's because
if Mogi is entertained, I won't be able to change my clothes anymore.  That's
why I fell down, and that's why I brought food with me all the time. I
see.
So, please excuse me for a moment.
Eh, no, there's a regular event going on at the shipping nurse's office for that child's chocolate. Yes, please
excuse me for a moment. I
'm going to go to childcare time, Mr. Misawa. I'm going to go ahead and choose the
savoy.
I'm a mapper, and I'm the Minister of Winter.
Hey, he's super cute!
re
me,
this is good, kanden
aname
he said, oh
yes,
ahhhhh
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
, this is a devil's creature, so it's a proper measurement of leg retirement.Yes, it's a shame.It
was such a wonderful thing that I could touch this point.Yes, it
was a puppet.  I felt that strange
feeling when I became a radio operator.It's a feeling that I can't really explain.Well,
well, now that I know what Chiara-sama looks like, it's a little strange.
Baba, I washed the marquee and said we
broke up, and that's when it came out.It sounded like it was made of key-wrapped pottery, with fur attached.I see, if you say it's nice, it's pretty much
Ladas Calidad.  Good color
Wata ah,
no, I do
n't like it. I'm washing something.  I
thought it was good, but I was wrong. Haha, I can't let go of that nice sprint.
Okay, from now on, I'll call you Ki-sama.
[Laughs]
Rain
Miyabe: You've broken a new word.
Now, let's move on to the next area. There's a
cherry tree marker here.
If you want to finish that line,
how can we support Phoenix's psychology?
[Music]
ana
scene
By the way, have you ever done a psychological test, Chara-sama?  I
wonder why he didn't have that kind of loan when he was little. I see, but probably in what era. I see that it's different from the argument that you put it out. Hmm, this time, chocolate will be tested on this line.  I've prepared it...
Oooh Tone
That's what I think.One
day, you were walking in a dream in a world where no one was around.After a
while, a little girl was standing in front of you, cooking a stuffed animal.
Now, what kind of stuffed animal was that?
1 I'm
a bear with rabbit ears.
Rabbit. There's
no rabbit in there. I'm so excited. I
like rabbit ears.-6 I
like them.
For a girl, the one that would probably cost 10,000 yen
is the rabbit.  I see.
Then I chose those rabbit ears.
Achiarosa is bent.
What a husband.
With this Senri jet, I can understand the healing you are looking for.
If you chose rabbit ears, the healing you seek is the healing of being
cared for.High
In other words,
rabbits are a symbol of weakness and passivity, and you would rather take care of someone than be
subordinated to others.  It
seems that there are many
people who like animals and children who feel good about themselves by taking care of others and doing things that are good for them.  Well, in that analogy, I have a cat.  I
have a cat, and for my cat, I love it, I love it, I love it, but I'm a human being.If it
's related to Noh, I'd like humans to see me,
but if I push a little harder, I
think it's a good fit.  I thought it was something like that because I'm doing things quite close to each other.Oh, I don't know.Well, I
guess I should do something that's not that far.I see, I often end up in that position
.  If
someone else doesn't take that kind of position in the middle of the day,
Mercer will take the picture,
and if I remember correctly, that's what Otoya calls ``Anegohada.''  AaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaA
I'm doing my best to dance to
Wow
antutu
I want to take Hiyoshikara Torida Atsuji's psychological test Dai Let's go
Charger
One day you go to a concert and suddenly you are brought up on stage and you
decide to jump in and play an instrument.  You
think you can't do that, but he hands you an instrument,
music starts, and to
your surprise, you use it to perform brilliantly.
Well, what exactly was that victory?
1 guitar, 3 saxophones, 3 basses a
Is that really that good? I suddenly pulled it out and was able to play it. That's right, that's right. I
thought you didn't need me, but it seems like you were able to do it unexpectedly.  Probably,
if I had to choose, I would choose another guitar because I love it to that extent. Hmm, I feel like I
play an 8 guitar,
but I don't think I can do that. It's kind of empty, but the instruments inside stand out and it's a little long day in Oa.  I
was taught by a family member of a certain person who plays the guitar, but it's only for one day, and I do
n't want to do it tomorrow.Chara-sama, I don't think it's the opposite.The liveliness, the vocals, the ideals, etc., are the ones who
chose that guitar.
This melody pressure will tell you which job is suitable for you.
Your suitable job is a. Pop.
Pop. You chose the guitar, which is the star of the 5-minute bounce vocal. You have a firm opinion
and are strong-willed.  A
hard-working type of
person: When people get mad at you or when you have a dolma, you have the upper-level timidity, but with your natural hard work, you'll
be able to do a lot of work.You'll also be surprisingly good at promoting your products and making sales pitches, so you'll
get good results.  That's
right.Hmm, I
see.This is one of the interviews I've been doing recently.Although it
's not a great product, I'm also promoting materials such as Nekojimen.Oh,
that makes sense.Oh, I see.
But, you know, I've changed my clothes over and over again after the Fuji theft,
and I've worked in many, many different jobs,
so
of course I've also worked in sales.Well, as expected, I can do anything in the world.  Looks
like it's going to break
Yuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu's
amazing That's
why
Chain
Cindy So let's stop at this point with the test Ah, I
want to go on and on even if I ride, but that's enough~
No, isn't it cute?  I
want to play eco with my nephew. There's
a sky there. I have a pen. Go Hmm, there's a boo-boo. It's good after all. Wow, what's this? When I come to your plaza, I see something high in the sky.
Well, what was it all about? 1
Written by Tako Mitori
Eh, that's the point, hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha funny
By the way, this psychological test is a psychological test that is similar to
yours.  I
know this year's fortune, ah, it's not yet
time for next year to open.I can't get through the new year, so there's only 3 days left.  It seems like
you will have a new encounter this year.It seems
like a good encounter that will be a plus for your future life.A
very good person will be there, and if you don't have a lover, your lover will be gone.
If you're in a Passat, you might meet the person who will marry you in the future.The
cherry blossoms are along the side of the road.We met this year.The
sweetness
of the
sky.
Hey,
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  It
seems like the two of them are thinking that the spirit witch is really good because they can do the hood raise.That
's right, that's right, that's right, on the first day, I
can't get hit.I
went and did the house finesse 4s as well.  It's
noisy because it's noisy because it's noisy
, oh, oh
, oh, oh, so I'm living, so I don't have a regular race.
Yahiko no Oka Ri-chan, please choose your country here too. Show your true feelings as well.
By trying to do that, you are a
hunter. Let your child take off their clothes. Well, that's a
tone that can be played honestly. It's a little bad.
That bus in this tab.  Ohno, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, Ohno.
Tiara-sama can't help the club. Let's let the house arazar go. I think the
future will be good, but are you going to watch 3 or the first move? I
can't see Yao chocolate, so I'm watching Curia Play properly this time. Nya campaign.
Daddy Is that okay, so it's okay to leave a cage other than the person himself.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Well, if you're saying you're going to get married already, then a
futon would be better, right?
pet Hmm, that's good.
So, I'd like to move on to the next project.
This is the best place near Ichizen.
Yeah, the one where I
have to answer all the questions. SSO is terrible. Oh, that's not it
at all. I'll do my best. Please
let the hippopotamus come out. Mountains c
Daaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaiaaaaaa
Well, my favorite food is Ishii 0 and Hirekatsuju.
Ah yes, the food I don't like is Porin-san.
Quartet. Hmm, I see. How old are you? Umm, why
don't you have an age?
Yes mhd. I have a habit of
turning my neck.  It makes me tremble, tremble, tremble,
haha The
happiest thing about the rock was
[Music]
Oh, this is what I wanted.
Is there a dark history? The audience's life before Oda Hanomoto live is a dark history. I
see. My
current goal is too much of a lure. I want to make that single, and all I have to do is work with the Japanese members of that digging live.  I
want to go south with Choco-sensei. Ah, I
want to go shopping.
Words like ``happy'' are ``
hmm, chimi-
moryou, uh,'' and
Drer, especially, ``hmm,'' and ``apaka.''
Then,
I tried to demoted it to the river and I would
like to look back
a little, so I would like to look back a little, but the
chat is confused.
Since then, my dad has started eating my
favorite foods. Yes, I
love Hirutsuki.
Except for the messed up things, I'm finally sticking to lunch around noon. Asoka, I'm sorry
about my wife, but we're going during the fried season.
[Laughs] That's
good.
[Music]
Hey, Harvard. The
moon in the hole of life is also water, right?
I guess Ada-chan was a dandy on the moon, but it was true. Um, it's
big, isn't it? Everyone, yes. I
like the meat of funds the most, though.  After all, I really like Hidaka Hirekatsu.
I see. Or rather, it
was a confession. I guess I couldn't hear you because it was canceled. That
voice.
Oh no, I'm sorry for Takasugi and everyone on the top, let's try again later. Hello,
that's a law for people who don't like it.
Hmm, I've been pretty bad at vegetables since I was little, but I
can eat most of them when they're warm.  Even though I've become like this, I won't eat spinach until the day I die. Yes,
Ryder. Even on Yu-Tele, spinach is a
must. It
depends on the cooking, but that's a shame. There's a dish called that in my hometown.  There
's a dish made with local spinach that's made with spinach.It's a lucky 6 side.It's a bit strange today.There
's a dish that uses elf spinach, and it's topped with cheese sauce.
But I think it's delicious, and it
smells like the grass of the law, so I'm
going to fall in peace.Chinese cabbage still makes me cry today.  A
door that can be
mixed up Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  I'm going to
go there.A I
want to go.Well, I'm wearing
dark uniforms, shoes, and all sorts of things when I walk up the stairs.  I
wonder if Chiharu-sama is a fashionable woman.But the sound of selecting chocolates sounds fashionable.I just think she'll take me to a good store.Oh, well, I think she'll give me advice.Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa to to everyone
Hey
everyone  We want to coordinate something with each other.Then,
Hayashi Nen's difficult song new song looks like it'll be
fun,
and his
favorite thing to do is to go to Team All Hus, so the cat was worried, but maybe they should
come out with something called Maji Kanben.  I was thinking about
whether or not to release Chimi Moryou, but in the end, I decided to release Jido 3 as well in order to show off that feeling. I
see. At the station and at the end, he confessed his love in a cute way.
Well, I
screamed for a long time, but it didn't seem to go in.
Well, I thought so.
No, the knife I made was a result of my efforts.
[Music]
Amo Tess, then that's it.
Until Tial-sama's love, machine 3221 Kanto It's
cool. There's only one who's in.
Well then, it wasn't bent. There's a lot of this. Isn't that what Noise-chan is saying? Ward: Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa's
Discord and God's God's words to me to
quietly confess my feelings to Kitani.  That's what I'm saying, so
I guess that means I'll be able to find out my luck in the morning.Maybe I'll try again.
[Laughs]
Then, Tiara-sama.  The
country has been assembled and will fight against Sasanian.No matter
what happens, no matter how many times I die, I will always love you the most.There
may be times when I miss you,
but I'm sure I'll remember everything over and over again.  Find at the store as many times as you like at the store, and
Ainny Ku
Endo
This is the hearing party yawan,
thank you
RAN
Ahhhhhh
Yes, it
is.  That
's right, it'll take a little while to get back, but it'll
be okay. It'll be okay because my memory will come back. I see. You remember how many times you played Line. That's
great, Spoon 5 nights.
You're good, but this
is what I've said over and over again.
Oni I've been to school
many times, but ameme
media I wish I had a future. I asked Rody this center, eh, so pounding.
I see. I see.
Ah, Asia, so please use your voice. Thank you. It
will cost money. That's
all about you.
800 Type Okkimandon
Okay, then. [Music] Well.  I'd like to go to a little water project here. It's a
5-chat turn near the top. It's
so bad. Congratulations
. It's endless, yeah.
By the way, have you ever done anything with that kindergartener or something?
Eh,
well, of course, and the governor's meeting also featured Hollywood actresses in the tower.  I've
done everything before. I'm a dream person, so I've never been to a voice live show
before. I'm a celebrity. It's a
different world, but I've done a lot of things like being in Caliwood soy sauce.
Why did the phoenix survive so long as a pin shop?
Well,
that's because life is a mess.
This roulette, this effect is the character where the roulette money stops,
Chiara-sama becomes the character, and I go with Mr. Choco and make it elaborate.  It's a corner called
Spiy Yabai Hai Choco Sensei's Chocolate
Bar.
Alright, let's get started right away.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.
Yang Perry:
Well then, if you're that sick,
then you'll have to act like Choco-sensei.  Is
it actually a job? Is it okay to think that Choco-sensei is someone else? It's
finally time to get permission and meet up.
What's going to happen?
That's what
Tiara Village is doing.  What do you
like about 1 year? Eh, no, that's not true. I like Tiara-sama the most.
But I heard that someone confessed to her on the air behind the scenes and said that they wanted to get married. There's no
need to hide it.
No, it's not like that.  Who said that?  I'm
glad I'm staying because there's no Gator in the red, and I'm thinking
that's a good thing, so I take a closer look at Zac.Yes, it's
actually not there, it's always facing me.Parton
and everyone facing me
don't give me a flash.Hehehehe
Ephefefefefe
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa I
won't get married if I'm Banya I'll
fight as many times
as I want Bach Tokoro cane
Everyone's Bukkurasgaan
No, no, wait a minute, wait a minute, it's okay.
People who really like you can't say things like Karugara 6t like that.
That's just how they look at you.  I don't like
chocolate.I only look at Tiara-sama, but even that
doesn't work.Well, I guess that's what you promise, too.I
can promise chocolate.I love Tiara-sama.I
understand.  It's true, it's
only Kiara.
Absolutely. I'm
only watching the big character sours
right now. Hmm. When
I say right now, I'm only looking at Tiara-sama who's right in front of me. Hmmm, Zuttori-san, it's a
lie.  Teyohedo is Hideyuki Arasawa's words disappeared. I've been
watching it for a long time, but what do you do when you're not in front of me?
Haa, I'm not sure if the conscious layer playing in Tower's brain is a big deal.
Well then, it's okay if other people don't have to be black. Well,
even if I get killed, I'll endure it.
OK OK
[Applause]
Ana
This little guy hahahahahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa It was If you're a
[ __ ] outside of the tournament, it's Tiara Sour.
Me.  I wonder
if there isn't.
Yes, there were a few places where the level score was recorded.  I
was listening to it with a grin on my face as I thought the sick character was cute and funny.Is that a
story about Kinami that actually happened?
Then what is the story itself?  I
won't say that either, but I'm
already 9 years old.
Well, I'm
just 9 days old. Ah, I'm
happy, but yes, mother.
Right?  I
think you're going to come to me, I
guess. It's
okay, I don't care about most things, but Lotte
's bones are connected properly, so it's okay. I
know, you're
cute.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
No, this is  She's really cute.By
the way, she's not playing a crying child.Hahahahahaha,
Goddess Endo dl
I haven't gone to the next land, so why don't you go to the next one?
Let's meet up. ee The sentence is tatatatatatatatataboosa. I wonder
what will come out at the end. I wonder what will come out of him.  Man, what's going on?
[Laughs] There
are all kinds of things, but cancer rank is different, and my instincts
are telling me to act like a yandere.
Eh, haa, the
spoiled brat won,
huh?  Can you
be sweet as if there were a day?
Oh, I caught it for a while -After this, I would like to go a little bit of the angle a little,
ah, ah, ah, ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah,
Ah, will go
to SBTM eco -car 2 Let's go to SBTM eco -car
2.
act
Notch-sama said it was okay to move chocolate, but today he wasn't with Sanchokon Reitei.
It's okay if I go to stay at their house. Of
course it's okay.
Hey, before that, it's okay to go to a state where you can praise the dead and eat 2.5 cups of Namibetsu, but it's okay to have a
home-cooked meal that was made for everyone.  I've made some, but you can't cook for me. I'll make some food for you. She'll
put strawberries on pancakes and make ice cream sauce.  I'm
going to make some chocolate too.I feel
like my older brother is going to make me eat some general-purpose food.No, I'm going to make him
eat
soba noodles.I'm going to make him a house in front of the pancakes.And then Marin will definitely let me live with him.  I'm going to make sure I get a proper bed
so that I can vote for Bocchi and leave with Tiara-sama 7 lol So, hmm,
can I go in and buy a cat now?
There's a cat in the chocolate too, so wait a minute and that's okay, please.
Hey, it's like a sun.
He's also next to the tree. Meow,
good, nice arm.  Yeah, I've
been loving pancakes for the past two years,
so I'm
really going crazy about eating musky pancakes
yes yes yes yes
yes s Can you make them? I can make them too, but oh, I
can make chocolate panties or something boa
Ah, dea, I thought I'd
put some wild strawberries on there too.I just happened to have a meeting, and the strawberry chocolate curtain is in the fridge.Oops
, it's John Mibee, it's perfect.I see, if you want to kidnap that hotness, you'll have to
make pancakes.  When Tiara-sama comes by, it turns out
that there is a cat in Choco Sensei's house, so just having a cat makes me
want to go on with 4. I'm going to give this guy joy and money.
[Music]  I
love it, I love it, I love it, hmm, but there's nothing like a cat in a cat cafe.Hmm, that
scene where it doesn't come to me is a relief.I
think cats in other people's homes are a little more attached to them because they were born, so even humans are fine.  Well, I
thought they'd get along pretty well, and
Sone told me to play with my mother's Aso 24 hours a day, and the
cat thought I was strong, so it's okay,
noream Uuuuuuuu
Inner
Sorry for the top 3, Mr. Soko, but that's because my family loves cats so much that it feels like I'm going to see them just for the moment.
[Laughs]
5 liar
Ah, this is effective.  This is
Bach winding up and reading
me
I see, hmm
Wakitani is a tiara
Ahaha Wow, well, I'll do my best, okay? Next time, let's make some bread together
ad Hey, nice
[Music]  Let's
make it together to be strong.Let's go through the hardships together.The
word prefecture should be ths
ah
and the cat who lives in the back.
Okay, let's get to the
last project. Hey, this is the last project. I
'll respond to your request for rice. d Prefecture and corn
yeah
ana  That's
good or bad. From now on, please let us know what you'd like us to do by commenting. We'd
like to choose what we'd like to do from the comments you've given us.
Revision to Windify
ananan Capa Uda  Don't live, Sakura.
There are a lot of dwarfs after English. Ah,
I'm certainly happy. I do
n't know what to do, but I'll let you take a test on Ai Kiu, and it'll be called Nine.
There's someone who seems like a home.
Suzana is okay with the red power test and the fact that it's not true. I'm fine without it. I'll
end up getting a 0 point anal. Ah, on
the other hand, I'm glad I did. Oh
no.  Well, the national aptitude test is so boring after all,
so I felt a bit sorry for the academic ability test, so I took it and
went to Chuo University, Osodo.  I don't know what it's like, math or
anything, but it's like a test of Japanese general knowledge, and it's a well-connected bread.  Well, I
guess I'll give it a try, but it's true. Well, everyone should complain if I don't do it. It seems like a good wife, so I'm
going to do it. I see. It's been a
long time since I've had a little more time.
3 minutes  I'm
going to give you more and more questions.If you don't understand, you can pass as many questions as you like.Alright, you can
pass all the questions for 3 minutes.If you do
n't understand the questions, you can just pass all the questions.
Umino is arrogant and says it on the screen.
[Music]
Yes
. So, if you don't understand after listening to it, you can say "pass" right away. If you give me a pass, it
will be an exhibition. Please help me with hot chat.
I'm going to do my best to manage my mother and my friends.  Choco-sensei, I wonder if you
can't just use it as a ``sometimes'' or ``anno'' pass.But it's
always written on the border, right?There's a video that goes beyond consent.What's
wrong with Racer
?It's 3 minutes long.Ai.  I
think I can probably answer the sound, so I'll get
rid of it if it goes well.Now that I think about it, I'll
take the customer's academic ability test for a while at 32.The
sum of the arc and the interior angles of a triangle.What, the
sum of the interior angles of a triangle is
Perspective
5000 Yen bill.  Who is the person written on the page? Ah,
what solidifies dry ice? What
are the three major nutrients? Ah,
who is the person with four eggs?
Who was
the one who sent the baku?
What do you mean? What do you mean?
What do you mean by that thunder? It's a lie in German.
Bach is good.
What is the name of Miyazaki's tassel part?
How do you say a basket that doesn't blow a lot of carbon
? Ah, with
puzzles. What is the campion made of? Tappy
Kanpyo Pampi Wow!
What's the name of the paid run
? Big, what a divine day. It's like a
guitar. The tip's pass, ah,
ah, ah.  What
's inside the garden lighter? What's its name?
Wave of 100 yen lighters
What's the name of the gas inside the 100 yen lighter?
[Music]
Puff!  The
reason why the entrance to the jam room was made small
is the reason why the entrance to the room was made small.
Hmmmm, write
What is Japan's national bird? What is the
country of Japan and how did it steal the country?
Phoenix Zaninon  It's not Fujinari
Atte a It
starts from the time
211 Ki g Se d e
That's it. What food did Momotaro give to his servants?
Momo
Boom Ah
Well, here's the
last question.
What does www in the Internet stand for
web?  Wide
momo mon atta
ana
[applause]
[music]
Who are you talking about? Seriously, that Japanese
Umazon girl. Is this a big problem?
Hmm, it's a little boring
. That's why I'm typing this because it's a question for Japan's general entrance exam.  It would be nice
if I could do that. Even if it's embarrassing, there's nothing else to it.
Who is that? Aqua-sama is restarting. See, what's going on? I'm going to
train Sakura-yo. It's
because I was alive. It
was a chain.
No, that's what Soi and I are. Ussos is
not at the bottom of the list who will soon take revenge.
None
ana
Thank you very much, thank you very much, you're a genius.
Thank you very much, Packer. Thank you, Grandma.
Please count me, because I've been praying for something like that.
Congratulations! But I'm honored. No
one can say I'm an idiot. I
can't say this is the average of Moon Live.  It
's 5 or 6 points, so I'm
doing my best.
No, I can't say I'm confused. Actually, I don't have that much money. If it's in Mahoro Reeve, it
's someone who knows. They're not Japanese.
Because I want to go further, the main Peter,
Hardunholive,
ah, for everyone's sake, why don't you hold a lesson about your stomach and your head, like that school, ah?  I'd
like to see everyone wear uniforms and the teacher teaches Japanese common sense.I'm
not doing a project.I'd like to join in.I think I'll vote for the main character.Well, it's a
picture book live filler.The child who can't get up in the morning quite often.  I don't think the attendance rate is very good because there are a lot of students who sleep around in town and there are a lot of problems with students being left behind,
but that's why there are other schools with that hot water.I see, Yagi is amazing.That
and this.  There's
something wrong with the shape of this.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhh this is how close to Yabe this is yeah I did my best .Motivation is a starting point and it's
already the end of the day but I wonder if the new measures this time have decreased.
Thank you for using that question.I feel like I've learned a little bit more about myself.Hmm,
well, that's it.I'll continue to
take my clothes off from time to time, so please bear with me.Thank you in advance.Yeah
When you call me, please read that Chiara too.No,
of course
Hambach, we're both lucky.Are you
going to break it right in front of me?
Okay, so I guess I should just take my clothes off.
Haha, I want you to give me a marker. Yeah, it's okay
. I don't think she's going to be too worried about love.
Emon, I'm a very employee, so if that male teacher were to do something naughty to me, I'd probably cry.Catch Oh, I'm the
Grim Reaper, but you see, it's the
most war-like part of English.In
Win 8, the tag that matches the governor is Hinako, so it's probably okay.  I do
n't know if that's the case, but I'm
pretty sure it's true.Dad, I
see, it's better to use glass than that.Make sure you stick that breakables warning sign on.
[Music]
Ah, yes.  If you
like, Chiara-sama's YouTube channel and Twitter,
please subscribe to the channel and follow us on Twitter, which is posted in the summary section.What's the
tone now?
Well then, in the end,
let's get chased by the relationship rate.I Well,
then.  Everyone,
I'm an elite who has built a friendship with you.Ahaha, thank you very much.By
the way, Chiara Summer,
yeah,
Ana, well, I've already finished paving.  It's
about time for Kira to let me touch that girl, Usuka. I don't know if it's a good fit. Well, now and then, Ra can't stand it either. The
reason is that Arthur touched it from overseas.
None. I
don't see it as a dare.
lol Aaaaaaaaaaaa  Chi rar
[music]