foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
no no no no no
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
two three
[Music]
oh
oh God why is it so hot
you can again
oh
wow
um
oh God I think I need to switch from
sweater to shirt
it's too hot I'm suddenly feeling
so hot
one second
[Music]
I never dreamed I'd grow up to be a
super sexy chicken lady but here I am
killing it is what my t-shirt says
I think I got that one from
a fan before maybe
I never thought I would grow up to be a
super sexy chicken lady
but here I am killing it
huh
motion mentioned what
what did I say
where's the motion mentioned in here
what what did you manage to catch the
Stream
that was his gift what
home ah
it's too bad that like generally we
can't accept
uh
I can't accept gifts but that may have
been you know from dokomi or something
like that
[Music]
yeah yeah good shirt it's light so I
will not sweat to death
um
[Music]
it's been a while since we last played
slay the Spire
but I really likes latest buyer and I
remembered
we still have yet to slay the spire
does somebody remember what we played
last time
which which out of the four classes
we sure
does anyone at all remember
what what's with a frog frog
the fourth silence
aha the lady you mean
purple lady
okay I'm thinking
I've I've watched yeah I played uh a
little bit before the stream well I died
because I didn't think too much through
uh every move I just was like whatever
comfortably playing in bed
so I died
after the first boss though
um yeah just a refresher and then I
watched the video on Ironclad Builds on
um
on
uh silent builds ah yeah silent is the
green one and on defect builds
and I mean I played to the fact when I
was
um warming up so I'm thinking
I might wanna try the defect even though
apparently generally
the iron clad is the easiest
to just build a deck because you know
whatever works yeah the fact may be hard
but it's fun
the fact was my first heart kill
Ironclad was second oh iron Chad has a
lot of options well the effect has two I
think
but no I don't I think I did well with
the Watcher but I just don't really
remember it
but
I'm saying the last time I tried silent
because we fought all poison strong
poison easy
and we failed but not really my fault I
just didn't get good cards
that were harmonizing with each other I
suppose
ah for me the fact is the hardest yeah I
didn't get poison cards but then I guess
maybe I also made the mistake I'm not
sure I don't remember but maybe I made
the mistake of like settling for a
certain card uh deck that
I didn't end up getting so usually you
don't settle you don't decide what to
get
before starting you have to deal with
what you get but even then even then we
got like cards mixed cards
well
I don't know I I I we will try what's
the defect first I will say because it's
fun
and then
oh look I also have the least unlocks
remaining with this one hmm
yeah Tony is um
sounds like a plan you got this gaming
easy thank you
gotta play the hand you're dealt exactly
oftentimes the best choice to choose
what's most fun yeah isn't that
wonderful
as I had a good somewhat healthy
breakfast so hopefully that gave me
energy I had a little bit of a lunch
before the stream like two minutes
before the Stream
now to the fact we can either go for a
frost build
which is not what I did before I think
last time I played the effect was just
like a mix uh with powers and lightning
and when I got some Frost I guess I got
some Frost as well
but it was more of a like big mix but it
worked really well I think I was trying
to
um
no I didn't do claws really but I know
another deck you can build is the is a
claws deck which is
you keep it as a small deck there's like
three claws cards and you want to keep
uh the whole deck like low cost and keep
on cycling in the cards that cost zero
including the claws cards um
it's a meme build
in your opinion
yeah and then and then there's like a
the power is built which
apparently is a little bit difficult but
that's kind of what we did last time I
think kind of more or less
yeah but but Frost thick seems easy
enough to build and
very very
defensive and and
yeah you do a lot of passive damage
because you focus on getting blocked
with your cards
and then you do passive damage with your
with like one lightning orb or so
whatever
um
is what I have picked up on
[Music]
gotta ask Nino for tips you're
watching this help me she should coach
me if we if we still don't get the Slate
Aspire this time maybe next time she can
coach me for real like she could just
yeah that's actually a fun idea
okay so actually last time I I lost so
this is not so exciting here
because
maybe I shouldn't have even played
before the stream because then we could
have gotten a random nice Relic and now
now this
ah I don't want a curse
I don't want to lose my starting Relic
um
relic of course
that's really not a green start
I'm just gonna go for HP whatever
[Music]
and then we'll see what's this
brings us
I don't remember what this is but it'll
be fine whatever whatever it costs
um I think I'll go
here hi oopsie I go
to the right side so often
come again now
all right also I was playing on my steam
deck before the streamer was fun in bed
cozy with my steam that is so heavy
though
seems like it's so heavy man
all right
yeah it seems like my brother used it
while I was gone but I mean he had
permission too so no problem
um
because his account was logged in
sister has all the cool consoles huh PS5
and switch and a PS4
the steam deck well gaming laptop gaming
PC oh man my sister has got all the cool
damn
yeah yeah
uh-huh
who's the gamer now
wow wow
a tech potion attack potion mm-hmm
Okay so
whoa
[Music]
I saw this card in some
build I don't know which one it was
and
what was this one for
this will often end up in killing an
enemy I think
[Music]
well yeah this one is like a safe card
what was this a Vulcan next to our
channel the orb that was just evoked oh
oh I think I used this before
okay I'll go for lightning but does that
mean we are now
already kind of going for powers
um filled
more or less okay I guess I mean we
could still go for Frozen uh Frozen
frost deck we'll see we'll see we'll see
just just uh
Justin it's a little bit too early okay
12 damage from learning math again here
I don't want to lose
too much
um
HP in the beginning right away because
we want to focus on going to shops
rather than resting
I sound like I really know what I'm
doing so far don't I
talking about builds and all that what a
pro
and and two
perhaps I'm too
oh yeah I should have defended
perhaps I'm too too loose
game looks a bit different
doesn't look different to me why do I
get the same potion again
okay
[Music]
I will get capacitor for now capacitor
very good capacitor useful in every
build I would say
like
um
oh no what is this 11 HP
you fall into a puddle it's made of
slime group ew frantically you claw
yourself out over several minutes as you
feel the goop starting to burn you can
feel in your ears in your nose
everywhere climbing out you notice that
some of your gold is missing looking
back to the puddle you see your missing
coins combined with gold from
unfortunate adventurers mixed together
in the puddle yeah I'll take the gold
11 is not too much Indian icono
money
ouch
oh
and we might lose even more nah but
upgrading now I only have two new cards
so far I would upgrade I guess capacitor
and ball light thing or or dual cast
is this no
because 16 plus the HP we previously
lost
I wait it's random oh well then never
mind
okay
nice
yeah before the stream I called into
muna's anniversary stream
did you guys see
probably not I I posted the link in the
creature though when I ever write one
second before it was happening
eight times six is 69 according to Mona
childish childish and foolish
we had to call in oh okay
Oh see now we could go for a claw deck
Maybe
or
[Music]
melts are damn that's that's good for
certain enemies who just have endless
block even for some bosses I think
some bosses have like so much luck
this is just like a basic
good card again
I don't know what's eight times six uh
84 right
I'd pick one of these well me too
um if we go for this one we're
automatically going for a claw deck we
must
but then we get unlucky if we don't get
many more claw cards
eh
let's say 84.
I wanted to say 48 guys obviously
I'm thinking in German
because in German you say the other
number first
what
no of course like for sake come
on anyway
um I don't know melter is interesting I
never had that card before
but it only really
it only really
helps you sometimes not always while
this card
[Music]
okay powers powers build it is
rad yeah just just choose everything
that looks
like
like it's Dippity zappy
uh seven damage okay
um
perfect because I will receive unblocked
damage
and channeling wonderful yeah so Muna
was doing something interesting
she was doing like a call in but it was
planned so she asked me to have like a
job interview with her
I was like oh sounds fun
hell yeah
so she was applying to several members
jobs
called in and she applied for job at the
police station I guess
oh damn oh wow wow I may have been able
to kill in this round
can I still yeah okay
and then uh elfi I think for some
designing job Kyla for like
blacksmithing job
oh Thunder again
fun
um double your energy
bam one second let me look up
I want to look up
defect Powers build
so I have
something to look out for
what's it called lightning build frost
build or Bliss build hybrid build I
guess it's more of a a lightning build
um electrodynamics from the strike ball
lighting static discharge
storm biased cognition
and there's so much text give me
pictures
ah
nah
a zipped up you're very lightning at the
moment okay
but then I don't know about these cards
one is best
one or two
okay
you guys help me with choosing cards
okay and I do the thing
uh let's go upgrades
upgrades
free slots what's the maximum of slots
to lightning
oh free free
holy
oh my God
what's up maximum 10. wow
wow wow okay
hello hello oh
I love that card already wow
I have no defense card that's okay I'm
gonna kill him right away
yeah
okay 13 damage I think
um
[Music]
I need to use my potions
and next time we have like a little bit
of a more difficult battle oh okay we
have compile driver
s or heat sinks won't even play a power
card draw one card
none of these are on my list
so I skip
my in my warm-up uh Rana used his heat
sinks though it was kind of fun it was
kind of good should we go left or right
because here we have a little boss where
we could get a nice Relic and I think we
need a relic
right but like not right away right I
don't have to do it right away
I think I want an Uma Morty
yeah no rush okay
I also had that in my warm-up run today
okay little boss time uh-huh
okay
[Music]
good morning
cookie sorry that I woke you
hmm
[Music]
ah mate I'll drink this
because I have so much energy still deal
11 damage gain an artifacts
still seven damage and lightning or go
for the eyes
I'll go for this one
what's an artifact again negates one
debuff oh why not drink another one
oh
she didn't even cost anything oh remove
a vlog 10 damage deal seven damage to a
random enemy for each lightning Channel
this combat
um
does he have block on right now I don't
see it no probably not no
[Music]
I only channeled one though
and I still have so much because it
didn't use up anything I guess I'll
block
wait I can do a swift potion as well
see
all right
uh
Go full block them
[Music]
damn it I can barely block it
oh damn it
ah damn it yeah that's gonna hurt a
little bit
[Music]
now he's thinking okay
yeah okay no problem I'll kill him this
turn
three six
nine twelve
[Music]
T
oh happy flower every free turn skin
energy Yay good flower
all right
um encouraging if okay next up and
channeled again
so this card would be great for a claw
deck
uh we don't need it because we're not
going for claw deck
gain free black put a card from a
discard pile into your hand oh Graham
very good okay I guess when you upgrade
it it probably goes to zero
I assume
wait I need to I kind of need to heal
my God
breath ruff ruff
oh
yeah unfortunately
we have to heal also eventually we have
to get the Ruby key
um
okay
[Music]
foreign
little slimy monsters
this one gonna hurt you mean this round
surely we'll be fine
[Music]
damn it I changed my mind ah
ah
kill him yeah at least one okay
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no need for
help with Zippity tap
[Music]
um
and then we just hope that it hits the
right ones go go go go yay
a power potion and
draw two cards at a burning now
another double and no we don't need two
of those do we
also already have a ball lightning
we should get better cards later next
time
I believe
I believe in getting better cards
[Music]
all right
zoom in
hello hello hello thank you for coming
to the Stream
what's this again
random power
I might do that first actually
uh at the start of your turn draw one
additional card
in one Focus whenever you play a power
card Channel
one lightning
okay
hi
that makes my thingies stronger my
little text
okay I'm I'm barely blocking it though
but wait wait
maybe I'll get him down to half right
and then he'll split right and then he
won't attack
yo let's go let's go
okay okay that was
that was a close call
if I I can't split those anymore so
gotta be careful here
yeah
I want the car that
um
makes my lightning strike all the
enemies
on the field
but at this rate I might have to rest in
the next
um
in the next
resting field again it's not so good
yeah electrodynamics I need that one
anyway
[Music]
um
okay good
uh oh is this skin 14 block retain your
hand this turn
game block equal to the number of cards
in your discard pile
um
man
hell no I don't like these cards right
now
we need vlog
I never have so much in my discard piled
alive
but just in case when we really
urgently need block maybe a Libra
equilibrium would be nice to have
because so far whenever I need a block
I was like always relying on the defend
cards
yeah let's let's get this one
nicer was this at the first time you
lose HP each combat draw three cards ooh
or the sapphire key
what do you think guys
[Music]
free free cards team
it is kind of a free chance to get the
key because this question mark could
have been anything
[Music]
okay let's take the key
okay
but now we have to rest again
[Music]
we have to it's boss time
ah this one what does this one do again
what's the special thing about this one
oh
don't heal it's the hexagon eh
you shouldn't rest versus hexagon why
shouldn't have healed what
scales off your current HP for its first
attack
[Music]
he deals 50 one yeah there's no bgm
wow there you go oh five times six
that's how he is how much damage to do
five times six is thirty
well
attack scales of them okay whatever it
is what it is
what it is
[Music]
now I know
it's pretty damaged fruity damage
[Music]
oh
I could get a equilibrium with hologram
[Music]
would possibly be the most
um block I could get
[Music]
but holy what I want to redo
already like what the what
no no
no okay now he does six
oh
okay
[Music]
oh
was there anything else special about
this one that I should be careful about
he does that only on turn one okay
okay okay see I got one damage but
that's okay because that made me Channel
One
I think or did that not activate that
no yeah okay
it adds Burns in your deck oh
five times to ten
ten
I can't block more
yeah I have to kill it fast
[Music]
six and I think I'm not gonna go for
equilibrium because it's just six
[Music]
I'll burn well
he's gonna he's not doing anything now
I don't have the best
hey can I block burn I can right
[Music]
[Laughter]
seven times two fourteen
perfect perfect
[Music]
oh
he's gonna lose the block afterwards
right
I want one damage yeah
so
it's funny how that works out isn't it
in it
okay not so bad now we can survive this
afterwards we got healed
[Music]
oh should have no it's okay no need
to defend go get him go get him
out
okay well now I really need to kill him
though uh
birdie
29 we need to do 29.
three six nine twelve fifteen
um
21.
uh 20
seven
no that's not enough
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
what's four times six uh
24.
okay
that looks painful
oh meteor strike
[Music]
oh
it tells me to look for thunder strike
not for me to strike
[Music]
two is great for your build too
uh yeah multicast thanks for Ghana thank
you
because double energy
yo yo
yo yo that's a good combination
all right
hi oh we have a nuclear battery at the
start of each combat Channel One plasma
um
a tiny house upon pickup obtain one
potion gain 50 gold it's a sling
Monopoly raise your max HP by five
obtain one card and upgrade one random
card
nice
or S
astrolabe upon pickup transform free
cards then upgrade them ooh
everybody says battery okay
[Music]
now
we need to see
[Music]
thank you
okay well I mean
I mean I think we can go right again we
could go to the question mark then to
the fireplace
well then we missed the shop
and we could instead of the question
mark and the fight now yeah wait no
what if we
go question mark question mark fireplace
treasure
oh no shop what the
[Music]
okay then we kind of gotta go left
question mark
question mark boss Fireplace shop
treasure fireplace
question mark Fireplace shop oh that
isn't is that good it's almost a little
bit too many fireplaces but we need to
upgrade
ah right I have to go for this one huh
ah why is it there
what's my question mark
he
question mark
treasure
and then fireplace little boss
no shop either way yeah I will I would
only get the shop if I end up going left
here
don't act two little really hard to save
his loosen ad free I can free okay
nutcase I'll go left we can take all the
all the fireplaces I can
it helped the game stream better it's
streaming fine though isn't it
thank you for the Super Chat though
anyway okay start of act two six times
two twelve
t
[Music]
I rarely work with plasma so
interesting
I hope animals is fun for boss and her
daughter oh yeah yeah at Boston I was
like pretty nervous about it because it
was an overall stressful day
but
I had a good time
definitely
um I had a panel of Cobra and
holy but wait that doesn't really
help me wait does it stay it doesn't
stay right
oh multicast
[Music]
yeah
um
the panel was about you know DNA whether
or not Cobo and me are really related
but I feel like even those questions
like even related people are not
necessarily or even often not similar at
all in terms of like what they do for
breakfast and all that or
what if they prefer comedy or horror or
stuff like that
um
[Music]
so
um
[Music]
evil one
I think maybe
charge battery maybe it's safer
yeah but it was like those kind of
questions
and I kind of took off the rollers stuff
MC more or less because Kobo didn't talk
much
so I took the lead
Sasuke Mommy I guess
but that made me really nervous and you
know we did it over Zoom again so we
would
we would hear the audience reaction
often but sometimes it was weirdly quiet
and that made me feel so awkward like
this is not funny is it oh no
I'm not funny what do I do
ah
I was getting
pretty worried about it holy
um
it was Sunday everyone was tired Kiana
oh so where are you guys actually quiet
you're very funny am I
am I
don't like everybody had a good time
I think the during the songs
I think it was pretty hype when because
both me and Kobo sang two songs and Kobo
sang very Mimi songs that are not her
own songs and I sang my own songs and I
think both for both we were really hyped
there were so many kfb in the audience
and they knew how to chant to high
Challenger and Sparks which are the two
songs that I performed and they went
they went so off oh my God I was so
happy yeah
towels yeah I wanted to see the towels
again so I I performed hard Challenger
and it seems like somebody organized
self-made
um
like kfp towels
orange towels with white kfp logo print
on it and gave it to like all the kfps
that was beets ah Sasuke thank you
I thought you know I saw it like in the
beginning
somewhere in the hashtags I think and I
thought maybe you only made it for
yourself but then I saw I saw so many
kfps using it
and yo it looked like it was official
merch
yeah and it was perfect it was perfect
for the occasion yeah I saw you guys
practicing beforehand on Twitter so cute
like before entering the panel room you
guys were out there playing my music and
then somebody was you know leading
guiding people on when to do the chance
and when to do the towel and all that
ah
so sweet Gotta Love kfp
need the block don't I
retain your hand and says there's
nothing to retain unfortunately
but at least I can block a lot
done done
[Music]
yeah can't be based in cool as hell I
agree and they also like chanted really
hard for Kobo as well
but she chose
this is a crazy frog
I can't believe it man I know that she
would
um
yeah I know that she would
sing the Numa Numa a song but I didn't
know about the frog one because in the
rehearsal she they asked us okay to test
our audio and I tested my two songs the
audio the instrumental
uh and she
she for her second song she brought out
her guitar
I don't know if she like last minute
changed her mind which normally you
wouldn't be allowed to because we have
to check with the staff beforehand if
we're allowed to use this instrumental
and so on and rights and whatever
and and she
she went on
this would be good for a frost build
this would be good for a claw build this
would also be good for claw build we're
not doing any of that
um
she in a rehearsal brought out her
guitar and was starting to sing her
first original song so I was like oh
she's doing that one okay okay and then
she ended up
that girl
yeah I was Bamboozled yeah
and crazy frog see she
just went all out for jokes
which is absolutely chaotic it was so
funny though
the crowd was going crazy for those
songs
yeah she wanted to have fun rather than
Flex her songs or her singing
oh man
[Music]
um
aren't those songs even older than her
probably yeah
anyway you come across an ordinary
building which appears abandoned a
plague a plaque plaque that has been
torn free from moana's on the floor it
reads the library inside you find
countless rows of Scrolls manuscripts
and books you pick one and close
yourself into a chair for some quiet
time hmm
foreign
[Music]
definitely read
okay
we have
[Music]
um
nothing I'm looking for I think I'm
looking for electrodynamics
thunderstrike ball lightning static
discharge storm biased biased cognition
oh
[Music]
those are in here
there's a ball lining
ah no okay never mind because I already
have that one
white noise
oh I guess
all right I had that one as well in my
in my practice one so I know how to use
it thank you cigarettes oh I got your
I got this fire
hey I even bought it on your switch as
well it's perfect for that yeah
you're welcome thanks for the pinky
let's hope I can slay the spire
this time finally
um
okay let's focus again
should I retain
[Music]
let's don't switch Yeah it's like
everywhere
[Music]
um
I can still do all costume
you know
okay oh
foreign
[Music]
no wait I can kill him probably
no wait no wait
no wait wait
sword isn't even lightning
[Music]
what do I have in my described pile
huh
no
[Music]
no lightning
think
wait
hmm
[Music]
oh drop potion if I only have one energy
yeah whatever I'll
oh I guess I'll block it
what could evoke
whatever
come at me bro now I have my lightning
[Music]
uh at the start of your turn trigger the
passive ability of your next orb sure
why not he keeps on daising me but
whatever this fight will not be much
longer
[Music]
so much
so much power
um
I'm hoping that the lightning will
strike this one down I don't know if
it's foolish
yeah
come on yeah okay
okay we're good we're good we're good
we're good
27. you little bastard
[Music]
huh
that's so mean I can't do anything
even with all that energy
now 27.
I hate him what
[Music]
fear ah
no I do have some Block cards I don't
know where the hell they are now 12.
7 27 wait wait can I kill him three six
nine twelve
uh 15.
I can okay
[Music]
okay in four plated armor
great
force field plus
game 16 block cost one less energy for
each power card played this combat
um Doom and Gloom
like Bloom and Gloom
uh deal 10 damage to All Enemies channel
one dark
force field
one is good for on your power build yeah
maybe
okay and one more block card because we
just noticed we really need it
and I shall go right and then left again
maybe
but with this little HP
I mean I kind of have to if I want to go
to the shop otherwise I won't be
reaching uh no I could still reach a
shop up here
I'll go to the question mark though for
now
oh what
refuse
this will kill me whatever
yeah I will go
get the heel again
[Music]
oh it only lows my Maxis but it was
still like still that's crazy
that's crazy
okay
cultists wonderful I feel like I'm among
equals
nice
we all
[Music]
should I get my ball lightning again
I've got the balls I'm so ballsy
so ballsy oh by the way my breakfast
that was not an egg in a glass so many
people thought that's an egg in a glass
it was just apple juice people thought
it was egg in a glass of oil maybe no it
was just apple juice in a round glass
that was hit by Reflections in a way
that it maybe looks a little bit like
that
picture on my Twitter by the way if
you're confused
I was not having
an egg in a glass of oil no
didn't look like an egg to me I mean
after people told me I was like yeah I
can see it
[Music]
wait can I if I already use static
discharge before does it stack somehow
[Music]
does it stack they stack so I get too
lightning
I don't need to
definitely block a lot
[Music]
I'll use the armor that works right
in four block
um
[Music]
yeah I was thinking about the plasma but
it's okay
dun dun
okay
stable the energy
[Music]
they're gonna attack with 18 27.
27 well I definitely want this then
maybe even this one
[Music]
okay
easy easy easy see I got my block up so
high did I exactly only took one HP yo
[Music]
big brain
and now they need to die though because
look look at their damage
[Music]
I don't know if I can though
I only killed one
poof
six I'm only getting six out of my orbs
we might die rich here yeah I have a lot
of money
[Music]
and I just rested and I'm already down
to so much and so little HP again what
is going on
what is going on foreign
wait can we do I have another power card
no okay
[Music]
um
uh
[Music]
I mean I can't I can surely kill him
okay
all right all right all right
tell the oh streamline
plasma streamline I would say streamline
I love me as streamline
okay I need I need to spend my money
maybe maybe the next question mark I can
get something uh
money related
where I can use my money but damn
[Music]
this one also hurts quite a lot often
foreign
who do you normally go for first I think
last time I just like in my practice run
I just got them down both more or less
on the same time pretty fast actually
went first
[Music]
I'll try
doesn't the Mystic heal him though
or buff him he Buffs him doesn't he
no hell
oh
okay
[Music]
night gets more aggressive if you kill
the Healer hmm
okay no problem no problem
[Music]
foreign
I would like to evoke a lightning x
times but I have the plasma
[Music]
and I
um yeah
[Applause]
that is not fair
oh yeah
and now I get my block cards thank you
now I get all the
way
[Music]
yeah my run is so dead
my HP and then
[Music]
we actually don't have to fight until
the next rest resting place but
if we do that we don't get to the shop
what a run
terrible
no I will I will not give up until they
kill me though
like they they might not even kill me
we'll see we'll see we'll soon but even
then afterwards I just already took so
much
damage from this
[Music]
instead of your turn at a random common
card into your hand okay
um
[Music]
at least I'm blocking the whole damage
yo
[Music]
there's always the next time we've only
played for an hour
easy we'll make a new new build we'll
trim my deck better next time
[Music]
huh
GT
you are slain
Mamma Mia
too bad
that is sad
I was just getting started I was trying
to get started man
[Music]
should we go for the defect again
or should we go
something more simple
[Music]
Ironclad or silence
sure
effects to practice
I'm glad
all right let's do iron glad classic
should be easy right it's a very simple
character
what did I get starting to come combat
with an additional energy
okay
[Music]
um
I'm gonna go here
didn't even look at the bus let's see
what bus do we have
this one it's not the same as before no
no that was a hexagon this one's
different
it's a good relent gown
all right
here we go
hey
I haven't played Ironclad that much
though
until now
so
I don't know what I'm doing I know that
there's like a strength build
and a rampage
build I think
I think
but the strength feel is like the
easiest
[Music]
is this the winning run now we're just
restarted well hopefully it is yeah
the Rampage is not a build oh it's
something I picked up in a video
[Music]
for Africa to kind of traditional cars
this turn okay if I block up and get a
card in the head I remember these cards
you know
let's go I'll go for this one
strange blue humanoid with a golden helm
approaches you with a huge smile
and I'm with cleric are you interested
in my services the creature shouts
loudly oh
hello friend
uh here 20 I am full health
I guess we'll remove a card oh
I don't know remove a strike for now
and
um I think there was a card that is like
strike but gives you something
additionally
and you want to replace all your strikes
of that one
I forgot what's it called
yeah
drop kick
almost strike
or maybe I'm thinking of the uh poison
boy
when I said that I might be thinking
about that
yeah
because there's a there's a poison
strike that does
or am I I'm confused ignore me
ignore me
is she going for act for this run I'm
always going for act four
I always am
trying my best
I always I'm trying
the sound is a lady oh
I thought so
hey good for now isn't it good good run
I'm still full HP I'm still fully and I
had two battles already okay this this
is maybe this is the Run
um I just need to oh
I just need to build a good deck and we
have to know what are we going for
flying Aspire
ironclads builds
uh strength build
spot weakness that's exactly what I have
okay we're going for spot weakness guys
all my Chat is dead Let me refresh
it says spot weakness in flame demon
form limit break
would be good cards
maybe even Rapture but hey we have one
if the enemy intends to attack game free
strength okay
I also like pommel strike though
strength build most basic thing we can
do
should we already go to the shop we have
no money I think we should go to
question mark
thank you
come upon a Dapper look at the wheel the
wheel
[Music]
last time I got a curse don't you always
get a Christmas
it's pretty bad chances fifty percent is
bad
come on
for my full health
wonderful
unbelievable
oh ah the card removal would have been
good
thank you thank you thank you
at least it's nothing bad yeah at least
no curse or something like that
yeah
wait that's a lot of them
I'll go full block this turn no risks
will be taken
okay
that's how does this work
the animate intends to attack in free
strength
gain free strength
okay
oh I'm only vlogging
eh I had energy left oh oh no
really
little needle
[Music]
God damn it
ah
[Music]
I was greedy I didn't want to waste the
big damage on this small boy
all right
ah ah
we get a weak potion and
nothing on my list but
welcome
freeze
five block deal five damage deal six
damage deals to the additional damage
for all your cards continues to ride
okay I'll skip
and left or right thank you
ah I want to talk a little bit about the
Easter stream I guess as well
it's okay
yeah it's the Stream
I'm sorry it ended up being kind of
scuffed oopsie
um
I was hoping
it would be already in time
but unfortunately it wasn't there was
like I
have
um
you know I think I I gave them enough
time oh God oh God oh God
but yeah
it just so happened
all my potions
[Music]
and unfortunately also because of that
one of the games I wanted to do
we weren't able to do in the end
I was gonna do like an egg balancing
game that originally the idea was if
everybody would play in VR
that you know through your movement
it would determine whether or not you
dropped the egg on like a spoon
that was the idea behind it
um
it would have been fun I think so but
then we ended up like planning for it to
be usable even without actual VR anyway
yeah I was like wondering could we even
make that is that possible and it seemed
to be possible somehow even for people
who don't use VR
but
yeah
Yum Yum Yum Yum oops
[Music]
should I apply this too
it's okay though
seems very ambitious yeah maybe next
year I don't know I don't know I I I
don't know if I even wanna organize
something like this again I was also not
planning on having AMA help uh at all or
ideally as little as possible but
because of things not being finished
before the stream
um it was very chaotic and me and AMA
were like trying to test everything
really quickly and troubleshoot and all
that and figuring things out
but yeah
yeah
it just wasn't ideal
strength I I lose strength do I after
[Music]
I don't I keep it okay
it's always great fun when you all get
together yeah I I think even with the
scuff of like scoreboard not working and
so on like the remaining bugs even with
that it was probably as a viewer kind of
fun but I just feel so bad for having a
one hour delay because that's just too
much and I swear I swear I wasn't
supposed to be like that
ah but like we found a bug and then it
took like 15 minutes or 10 minutes to
fix it like because it has to be like
big fixed and then the it has to be
exported again and then we go in again
and we find a different bug and then we
fix that too and then it takes again 10
minutes and then it Stacks up it Stacks
up it Stacks up and it turns out to be a
full hour
ah
I felt
so bad and stressed out I didn't because
I know I was I wasn't
the only POV ever I was hoping for the
other girls to do a POV they were
welcome to do so I told them they can
please if they want please have your own
POV I'll just have my camera appeal be
the general camera system one and others
can have their own POV up and then
nobody did so now all the viewers were
waiting for it on my channel and I felt
like I was
you know in charge for everybody's
enjoyment but but I couldn't I I
couldn't deliver
[Music]
ah pressure yeah the pressure man
was very big I really felt it I was so
stressed out
I was so worried but at least the girls
were
um very understanding very kind
okay now I need to focus
because I barely have any block that I
can do uh can I kill
do I have lethal
Maybe
with bash spot and strike
seemed like you all had fun even with
Cronus motion sickness yay
no
next turn
but that's so much damage
and I have to walk as much as I can
run into damage again
[Music]
it was a rough day and because of it
being so late
um
because of all the all the the whole
delay for all the bug fixes it ended up
being so late for me
and then over at the end I really had
like no energy left during the quiz
fashion strike okay okay
at the
it was so late it was supposed to start
at 1am but then we had a one-hour DeLay
So it started at like to 2 A.M
for every five cards in a deck heal free
HP oh okay a little bit over here
how late was it for you by the time it
ended I think oh
how long was it three and a half
half as three a.m or 4 a.m or so
no I guess 4am and then I still had to
eat some pizza
um one deal eight damage to All Enemies
all right
so late
I up my sleep schedule and I had
like no energy for the whole day on the
following day
I was so dead
I wrote on Twitter I was half asleep the
whole day I didn't didn't mean that I
was like napping all day no I didn't
take a single nap but that was always
like on the hinge of falling asleep
constantly
yeah
so ugh
dead
yeah
it do be like that
not much yeah
feel better today though yeah today I
definitely feel better
um
and I had a good breakfast and a little
bit of a lunch
and after the stream I will cook
let me cook but I can't cook here
because I only have Block cards
ah what's this fire breathing whenever
you draw a status or cursed card deal
six damage to all enemies
that's good if you get this card offered
late game and your whole deck is filled
with like shitty cards
no you know 12 damage apply to a week
um skip
curse bill down
um
left if we go
to this one
all right wait is there is there no
shops in act no there are
oh are we in act one
getting confused yeah act one
he's a little fire lead in act one we
missed the shop they were so early only
are they always this early in act one
I guess we'll go this way
Maybe
I'll go for the elite I think
[Music]
no HP though oh yeah
oh
wow wow wow wow wow wow maybe one of the
question marks is something that heals
me
oh
I don't know if I'll be fine I'll be
and my deck is still kind of as
well
[Music]
we just gotta
roll over everything
try berserk headbutt Blood for Blood
getting too vulnerable no fuel line
damage put a card from your discard pile
on top of your draw pile plus one less
energy for each time you lose HP this
damage deal 18 damage
now
I refuse guys sorry
um
oh this might Save Our Ass
this might Save Our Ass
oh
a good bug good insect thank you
um
yeah
uh 10 15 18. are you kidding me
are you kidding me
18.
6 12.
12 kill
this one
yeah
ouch okay
I will not
have them play with me like this
wait I will first build up strength
if I want to waste Dutch
[Music]
laughs
less than one with one HP can you
believe it
okay
rapture
Rapture you can also utilize Rapture
which gives one
or two upgraded strength every time you
take damage from a card bloodletting
offering on hebokinesis can all practice
us as can brutality and nah nah nah nah
I'm going for the promo strike
one
[Laughter]
I don't know
but we
we got them down to 25 percent less HP
am I safe if not we will die you die if
you were killed so
okay okay this one
is I think
he hits hard doesn't he
[Music]
um
if I use skill to block I alright yeah
yeah yeah yeah
and then however defending is a skill
but now he's still doing pretty little
damage
it's okay
next turn he might do much more damage
oh mine that's okay
ah one HP really
ah
what's the matter this is like Fire
Emblem now always leaving the enemies
with one HP but
look at this wait I get the oh yeah I
get the emerald key just for free okay
nip every temp attack you play deals
double damage
Emerald key
and this nickel oil drop five cards
randomize the cost of cards in your hand
what ah it's a it's a potion I thought
it was a relic do you have a Snicker
potion oh
foreign
[Music]
can only be played if every card in your
hand is an attack deal 14 damage
my uppercut uppercut is good I think
for my build
um
22 HP ah okay this one's all right if I
get them down to
30.
4.5 HP
right
which I can't I don't think I can
six twelve
20.
potion
ah okay
[Music]
um
should I Strength gain the strength
first is kind of expensive though
we have bash is free I see that I don't
know which one to go for first because
50 vulnerable is nice but strength was
also nice
but what do you go for first
[Music]
strike cleave
most of them cost two
I'll do
[Music]
yeah
strength
and then 11.
I suppose
from there
when they come back in my hands Dave
will not be randomized anymore right no
this will be this will stay randomized
what
those cards stay randomized
hey I didn't interrupt yeah
[Music]
I did I did
okay
foreign
I don't think I would have been able to
do that
so
ah that was all I could do okay
okay it's okay it's okay I didn't lose
any HP yet and I'm gonna take them him
down now
free free
okay carnage oh
20 damage
gain five block upgrade a card
Rapture again Rapture oh it really wants
me to get rapture but I don't wanna
um
okay I'll take ottomans
Our Deck is still pretty small it
doesn't need to be trimmed yet however
this
could be your downfall thank God we have
cliff
um
pretty sick move kiwala pretty sick wolf
pretty insane what you did there kiwawa
oh my God
yeah
oh another cleave
[Music]
but it only really makes sense when I
have many enemies against me
should I get another cleave
there's also feel no pain whenever a
card is exhausted again free block
whenever exhausted draw one card dark
embrace
[Music]
we are hot water
yeah only people who were at the panel
know what that means
more Clips better than the strike yeah I
can get rid of the strikes then if I
ever reach a shop again
good guys
it
43 HP for the boss risk it or heal
risk it for the biscuit 43 is not so bad
it's not so bad but I don't know what
the boss is like
yeah hug mom everyday
he'll heal upgrade you're fine upgrade
um
we're gonna risk it
love it
Ah that's that's right
I remember that that's pretty Epic
okay
I mean if we can't make it with 44 HP
then that's a skill issue
honestly and then I wouldn't make it
anyway
ah after for any damage
changes to defensive mode
uh-huh
[Music]
uh okay
so
do we want to do 40 damage
[Music]
I don't think we can but this is one of
my free cars
[Music]
can I use a sweat potion now
I don't think so
um
[Music]
42 okay uh if we do any damage then he
will not do the 32 damage to me right
but he has some blocks so we have to do
almost a double
okay
oh
[Music]
uppercut plus uh promo Strike should do
the trick right
[Music]
whenever you play an attack take free
damage
wait so how long does he stay like this
just for one turn or so
Iron Man's
[Music]
better to just
block on my turn as well right I can
turn big attack
foot turns oh oh
I wanna be safe
look for now okay
I can upgrade again damn
take free damage from one attack eight
times to 16 after block 16.
I literally can't block
unless I get my Swift potion
then maybe armament
all of it
good Armament right
[Music]
wait I'm already at 16 blocks so uh I
could cleave I could spot
okay
more strength more power
five times four is twenty
could be worse I can do 21 damage holy
wait and I have to do 40 damage all
right all right all right
okay
[Music]
done
where Danny with the funny easy easy I
figured this one out completely
I've got him wrapped around my finger
so now we block nicely again
it looks so much damage in exchange for
free
for free
t-h-r-e maybe a one can I do like one
yeah I I will block the free damage
anyway right so
foreign
that's so worth it
yeah okay
well now
like this
that was worth it
okay
now he does 16 again
I can upgrade again
is there any way I can get another card
no
no no
[Music]
no no no
I know I had one energy left but I
didn't want to take the damage
okay 50 50
damage
50.
[Music]
21-21
I didn't do 50 damage guys
it was a little bit too much
but it's okay five times four is twenty
that's okay I will live
that's okay
that's okay after we saving any damage
uh he would block anyway easy I went he
won't he won't attack okay
foreign
okay
I'm doing the whole thing over again
um
I have no I have a little bit of a block
card
should I wear skirt for the brisket
foreign
[Music]
if I do an attack but
I'll just
defend first
[Music]
and then I'll do
I'll pull more strikes and he is dead
yeah
wait was that the boss
[Music]
I need this card apparently according to
my guide
[Laughter]
apparently it doesn't even seem so
convincing to me but okay
um
double demon form did
form oh
demon form no not quite
um
burning blood oh
at the end of combat oh healed what do I
have I see oh it's a bigger Hill
all right the Ironclad heals after each
fight I forgot about that
we might need that
black side of insect is kind of massive
let's die at least drop an additional
Relic when defeated
[Music]
here we go act two
this must be the run but which way do we
go we don't need to um do that special
boss anymore the special leads
this one which one was this
I met as many Elites Pap with mostly
I'm scared
mostly it's there's one here one here
wait was there one at the bottom no
uh maybe left
I mean it's yeah unless I don't as long
as I don't go right side
I'll go I'll go left for now
okay okay let's do this guys we're gonna
slay the Spire five times two
dude
[Music]
I have a potion by the way there's still
chaos
does it play those cards for free or
does it use your energy plays them for
free right it must
because who has
who has the energy
play them all
yeah keeping them for now though
uh he's thinking
foreign
[Music]
I'm actually going to use that because I
don't have good other choices anyway and
I don't need to block anything
um
okay little kidney
21 damage
[Music]
um I think spots and then promo and then
a strike or whatever I get from the pomu
oh okay
[Music]
a little bit defending is good blocking
kills you against this
none you'll be fine but you won my God
uh 29.
12 uh 24
I can kill I have lethal
a fair portion and
Twin Strike plus isn't that a fire
emblem engage attack
Twin Strike in flame in flame is one
that I need which gives you two uh
upgraded is good
inflame
I need I need I'm we're going for
strength build after all remember
yeah scaling the city you notice a wall
covered in writing of ancients as you
try to wrap your head around what the
puzzling symbols uh and clips could mean
the writing begins to Glow suddenly the
message becomes clear remove a card or
upgrade all strikes and defense
now we need to get rid of them even
though that sounds kind of tempting when
you still in add to have so many
so many of those cards
but we gotta remove them
yeah trim the deck
I know buff is good though I think in
this situation hmm
um
[Music]
you asking who am I kiddies are those
are the famous chunky wonky and smoothie
how can you not know
my babies
and the blanket is my merchandise
blanket
that's Ross
twins
strength feels good so Twin Strike would
have been a good pick
and see it again I'll choose it okay
[Music]
hey should I use team on the farm and
you just about my energy in this turn
but I can't defend anyway even if I
wanted to
[Music]
he has so much block
Chase I don't like this ones
what the
um
foreign
okay
what did we do an uppercut and the rest
of what happened too fast
okay
[Music]
okay now he's down to 13 block no
problemo
[Music]
there's so many I have so many strength
cards now
but my chat died again
these draws
Emma I don't feel that unlucky but if
you guys say so I I
even have hypochet on
what's going on
I have to keep on refreshing you guys
it's weird
[Music]
what
I mean I have Leaf oh wait 63
I didn't see the number
I didn't look at the number oh we have
Flex
which is a good card
um I heard that there is a relic
that kind of makes this one much better
because
there's a relic that that has the effect
of you not losing things like that and
then you keep the strength so you have
free
free flex
um yeah
but the chance of us finding that one
oh maybe I don't even have it unlocked
okay okay
skip this scoop
but I know of its existence maybe one
day we can do that
uh I guess I'll go right side
you'll spot a loose brick with a pillar
that catches your eye oh I've never seen
this one before I think a note for
myself
passed by here before you find a folded
note of a card inside it erase the heart
awaits this is your handwriting receive
iron wave
and store a card store a card
whoa
[Music]
that's my other me replace a strike or a
block
I already okay right okay what is going
on I don't know
[Laughter]
yeah thank you wow
she was thinking ahead
five steps or 10 or 20 steps ahead
[Music]
from do you looking out yeah yeah
there's there's a navigable
ah
[Music]
where are my blocks question mark
maybe behind promo strike
[Music]
kill the mushroom if you can block
I can't
well I want to draw a card with pumos
okay
[Music]
I want to wave why do I have knock
Ed
I'll wait
I should should have done this one first
then I'll do this
not ideal
killing would have been less damaged
well past kiwawa didn't tell me that she
only gave me the iron wave and didn't
warn me about anything else she could
have written so much on that note to
warn me from the future and she didn't
wait what
she's isn't she future
isn't she ahead of me
isn't she future wow and I am past Wawa
yeah she's future me
you guys were wrong
[Laughter]
14 12.
[Music]
I'm vodkaing from the future no you're
not you're watching live right now don't
lie to me
it's not good for me
[Music]
I'm getting wrecked right now
uh
Focus
I'm getting wrecked
yeah
um
okay block I should probably block but I
also need to attack
do this
[Music]
okay okay I'm just losing one HP it's
okay
it's okay just one
19.
23.
ah okay
oh happy birthday to Sag right no
somebody said happy birthday to Super
Chat wasn't it this one
this one doesn't say anything about
birthday
but you got accepted the study abroad in
Japan oh good luck and congratulations I
wish I wish that would have happened to
me when I was younger
I applied and I never got
accepted for something like that damn it
I wish I would have taken this Flex this
plus Flex instead of the other one oh
but look at all these Block cards double
your block deal damage equal to your
block wow
[Music]
what do you say guys
hey I didn't take Flex
yeah I think I did
ah I didn't
why did I not did you guys
you guys uh manipulate me
did I accidentally skip it or what what
happened
[Music]
huh yeah
I don't want to go for the elite now I
need to rest and then I'll go for the
elite okay
I have to rest
I mean
now I'm now I'm at 34.
but then there's another Elite
at least on that route
if I go right there's free campfires if
I go left there's only two more
campfires
and what do we want more
more Elites or more campfires one two
one two and
okay two Elites
and two campfires on the left
left
rest recall
more leads means more relics so
rest and then double Elite here I mean
oh
okay
[Music]
scared my focus from the beginning of
the stream is gone and my confidence too
laughs
what
an IP what's nip
oh
what do you mean the nib
you have nip up now
interesting pajamas nip
what what the is ninjas and pajamas
really confusing me
what nuggets and production
[Music]
sport organization what the
I will never understand
what that what you were trying to tell
me okay uh oh hey yeah they started
all three of them wonderful
12 13 7 we need to go all in with the
block man
I don't have that much block though but
I can do a Pomo strike
wait maybe I'll do the Pullman Strike
first because maybe I get the armaments
and then I get bigger
um
okay I didn't
no
one
why
we've killed one by getting strength
first
oh
[Music]
should restart I can't restart just oh
wait no eh when I eh how was that
I can't uh if I crash the game I redo
this one fight right
okay
oops just as I was speaking of it it
happened what that's weird
it's as if the game is listening to me
because
that's such a coincidence
man
they're watching me they're listening to
me
even though I don't want it
ah stop listening to me
okay what did you want me to do actually
the spot first
and then a pumo and then a defend
ah
thickness potion plus spot
with inflames
spot strength pommel maybe use fear plot
uh foreign
spot
and Flame spot fear
uh
in flame
[Music]
oh
oh okay
ah
I couldn't have killed the last one I
was only gonna kill the first one
it's fine that's fine
yeah
[Music]
attack potion next potion artifact
potion
[Music]
um
18 lap 18 damage 18 damage I can kill
this one
oh
all right
that wasn't easy Relic more or less easy
oh look I also have so much money
the merchants card removal service now
always costs 50 gold as opposed to what
it does go up pretty high I think I
remember but
this is good
whenever you lose HP gain free Block
next turn
47 HP in pretty good shape 50 75 125. oh
okay
can I get two relics both of them
in free Block next turn
yo okay
um cards
[Music]
inline speed equal to the unblocked
damage
[Music]
Reaper Reaper Reaper Reaper Reaper all
right all right all right calm down
calm down please be a shop
[Music]
wait but hey aren't these Elites and
they didn't even start with -25
because this is I guess different but no
ah
their leads in act one oh here they're
not considered Elites
still Elites I haven't changed much
either so you could say oh you but
you're so much stronger no I'm not no no
no no no no no
what is that
maybe I'll drink a
Shake It Off
who should I go for first
which one is more dangerous
[Music]
I want to use it too I was thinking
about it the whole time ah do you like
dancing Christmas cards damaged by five
just combat feels like damage deals two
additional damage of all your cards
containing strike deal 12 damage can be
upgraded any number of times
[Music]
yeah I
um
searing blue
okay
hmm you're feeling lonely without your
friend huh understandable
maybe you should join kfp it's so easy
to make friends in kfb
it's crazy I think at uh Anime Boston
some kfps who came there made a lot of
new friends I think
which I'm so happy about
y'all were looking so friendly
and so sweet and so kind and so
welcoming
um I made a lot of friends yeah oh this
was weak
I was like dkfi experience exactly
and I was so can I just talk a little
bit about the mean and green
I was so
so
happy
about you know almost almost everyone
mentioned to me like oh
you I was I've been watching you since
the beginning and you've helped me for a
really really hard time yeah
almost everybody told me that and it
doesn't make it any less special to me
um
I'm glad I can help people for a hard
time
by streaming is my existing that's
really nice
yeah and
I don't know I don't know if it's okay
to say this but like one one person told
me oh they
uh
uh they had cancer
and they're like one year cancer free
now and and I was the one that helped
them go through all of that can you
believe it
can you believe it I was like so moved
like what the
um
they beat cancer
and they they gave me the credit for
like getting through it like being able
to
to get through that time easier
um
oh and another one told me like they
found me uh through I think it was one
of the girls told me they found me
through
uh that video
the comparison I think
it may have been the comparison video of
like how streamers deal differently with
you know certain comments and and she
found me for that and was like oh she's
she's so nice and then started watching
me ever since
yeah damn that video
still following me to this day
yeah
very nostalgic
yeah there were quite a few girls
it was cute and there were so many like
um kfps that I also like saw for the
first time some who are lurkers there
were a lot of lurkers they told me you
know they told me their name and I was
like oh I don't that doesn't seem so
familiar to me are you like a lurker and
they say yeah and I'm like why you're
welcome to learn class
comment some of them are VOD Watchers
which is okay too
yeah and then there were some
non-lurkers who I however haven't seen
ever before until this day and I was
like really surprised
like like eat an exile who makes all my
backgrounds and Kanto who made hyper
chat and helped me with the with the
um
with the Advent calendar for example
advent calendar
yeah
so many
interesting meet and greet sessions I
wish I had more time like I would have
given everybody way more time if I
didn't have
um something to do after that but
yeah it's kind of standard that we do
like three four minutes per person
and those are over so quickly
unfortunately yeah Luca Bros thanks for
being here
but feel free to learn less
It's never enough time I wish I could
talk more to you guys about it but it
was fun I really enjoyed doing the meet
and greet and also like
um apparently I had like 21 people for
my meet and greet
and I was like
uh
like for at the end it was like four
more people and they tell me oh four
more people and I'm like what are you
sure didn't you say there were 21 people
for me but it felt like at that point
but like I only did six or seven people
they're like yeah yeah
was so fast
[Music]
ah one funny thing was that
um there was like one guy who signed up
for the meet and greet but also his
girlfriend signed up for the meet and
greet and he was like actually and I'm a
fan and his girlfriend was a Kiana fan
and his girlfriend didn't make it in but
he made it in and I was like scolding
him why don't you give your girlfriend
the chance instead he said yeah he's not
allowed to do that and I'm like
well maybe rules are meant to be bent
and broken but
it was so cute because he was dressed as
a Mondo cosplay you know Amelia's alter
ego
it was so cute and then he told me about
his girlfriend and I was so so moved
like it's so cute
this is unrelated to me kind of but I I
I isn't it so cute like they're they're
dating for eight years
and and they are both big whole life
fans and watch it together isn't that so
titty
what the hell
that's salted and then I legit asked oh
oh eight years when are you gonna marry
her and he said ah our uh Grandma also
also always says the same thing
just not my business of course but hey
eight years perfect couple yeah but no
pressure no pressure anyway yeah meet
and greets are really fun
they were really fun
um I hope we can do more this year maybe
again for my birthday so that people who
can't go to the conventions can sign up
for them too because last year I did
um
last year I did meet and greets for uh
some of the people who purchased my
birthday merchandise and then I gave you
guys like an option for two different
dates and we had more time I gave you
guys more time yeah yeah so I think
we should we shall do this again
okay back to
back to gaming I have no block right now
so I want to block
maybe I should have taken dexterity
potion
[Music]
um
that would be great for everyone yeah
would be nice I know I want to meet even
more from you guys
more more
Irish
[Music]
there's still so many who would love to
say hi to you of course I know I know I
know I know
I know
the explosion seems like a good idea now
yeah do I have a
free Block uh
deal seven damage to All Enemies Hill HP
equal to unblocked
your free Block
I need this one too
in in my opinion Flex first ah okay
nice
at least we got rid of the block
uh
uh 19 okay easy
oh no flex plus and a clean Plus
don't I already have two Cleaves
yeah I already have two clips I know I
know I know they're not upgraded but
we don't want to get our deck too
crowded
yeah
okay
every time you play free attacks in a
single turn and gain one dexterity or
the sapphire key
oh
I don't know
are you alone block anyway
it's insanely strong kunai isn't very
good
night is bad with your deck yeah I think
I saw it in a different build
not with Ironclad but
um
could help against heart
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's the last delete though
what are you again book of stabbing
whenever you receive attack damage from
this enemy add a wound into your discard
pile
[Music]
hate this dude
six times two
twelve
[Music]
what's the skin perfect
so now he does eight so now I can block
it we're good
foreign
he looks so funny though
[Music]
four times free is 12 again
I have one defense card that is not
enough
I could do promo strike and get a card
[Music]
I could
now just heal and strike I guess
he like damage to all enemies
an HP equal to unblock damage I wish I
could combine them but now I don't have
enough
oh wait what no wait I'm understanding
it wrong
yeah it's all right
it's all right
I I
hmm
and 21. it's not a book of stabbing
anymore it's a book of chopping
[Music]
one
eight block
five block
five o'clock
okay okay
should I inflame an iron
okay
um
it's times for 24.
24 24.
I have a lot of Block cards now
still spots
foreign
it will hurt a little bit
six times five thirty okay it's time to
kill him
or
we can track
first I would say
I'm kind of wound okay
yeah then we can only do damage
[Music]
good
shine it
next turn Maybe
ah it hurts
I dream catch up
whenever you rest you may add a card
into your dick I know Grandma horn
whenever an enemy dies gain energy and
draw one card
so many relics
[Music]
yo grandma horn is good yeah
I think especially with the dream
catcher
we don't need any of these cards but
what do you say
let me play it of every card yeah
um cards
um
offering
the best car in the game in the game
okay
oh let me take a look we have one more
resting place ahead of us
and I would say
yeah
two question marks shall we rest
or Charlie Smith or shall we recall
upgrade you have feather for HP
wait
yeah we should upgrade what do we
upgrade
let's just do three string
deal five damage
three strings
five cards yeah
[Music]
demon form or offering
okay
demon from but I would have hoped for it
to go down in cost
free cost makes me
kind of struggle to use it a lot of the
time
yeah I rarely use it okay
[Music]
offering
if I die if I die guys
I will take you with me
no strength card
foreign
[Music]
wait why did I do that I didn't need
that much block sorry I thought
I thought I was gonna get more well
[Music]
so this is the day I've been marinating
for
hmm you smell so good
meow meow
um
[Music]
I think today is Tuesday right so my
next hello beep order is arriving
[Music]
later
but I think for this week I missed out
on choosing what I wanted so there's
like one or two dishes where I'm like
but I still have one left over from last
week as well so I will cook something I
just don't know what
[Music]
thinking guys
oh wait I'll lose the strength huh
no
he is absolutely insane
um
[Music]
seven block and 11 damage versus
a block
[Music]
um
uppercut
for the weakness I mean
blocks more what no
I'm
um seven
huh
[Music]
well okay
next turn then
discard any number of cards then draw
that many oh okay
oh
autonomous
perfect at strike Plus
no no no no
Our Deck is 20 at 20 now what
oh
exchanging relics no no no
we like our relics don't we
okay
hello
and the cultists no you look almost like
a cultist the chosen one again okay uh
one times five five and ten fifteen
foreign
you're being accompanied by a chozo nah
can't be it can be
[Music]
foreign
for sure
[Music]
and Reaper
offering
always
ah
wait
oh wait they're not planning to attack
never mind
[Music]
ah how is he still alive what the hell
foreign
block
all right
next turn this turn you're going down I
think I hope
19.
yeah but I don't have enough Attack
cards I need to shrug
[Music]
oh there we go
oh wait wait was that enough already
Gonna Save my butt
oh
let's go oh
Puma
she came because I was using all those
promo strikes
as a reward oh look there's a Twin
Strike hmm
[Music]
battle trans no
no
do you all want me to take that one
I said next time I see a Twin Strike I
take it but this one isn't even Plus
yeah I need to draw Power what does that
mean
okay
okay now 44 HP against the boss
is not the worst
rest I'd slap risk it rest
I think yeah I'll I'll sleep I'll sleep
this time
oh yeah right it gets it lets me choose
something but I don't need this thank
you
[Music]
so let's go
uh who's this guy what does he do he
Gates three debuffs but so far that's
like vulnerable and and all that and
weak right
[Music]
summons ads that steal cards what
and he fires a Hyper Beam
trunk
[Music]
oh that was that was worth it
okay if he calls minions then the
Cleaves are gonna be very useful
[Music]
okay well done I have four more
foreign
[Music]
there are the minions yeah
I think
May trance now
because I want the good
[Music]
seven times to 14 and 8 is like 22 I
think
the human form but
then I'll take
find some damage
wait so the negative effect is that a
debuff basically should I negated
I'll use it I'll use it
even if that's not a debuff the next
debuff I will just negate oh it's the
steel oh you little
you little how
go not the reaper
no I need that card could have just
taken a strike what the hell
what the matter with you
[Music]
okay but most of them are not attacking
so that's pretty good should you go for
the minions first or for the big guy
if you kill the minion you get the card
back oh
they always go for the rarest card no
way for real
minions minions first
okay but then won't you just continue
endlessly spawning minions though
I need my AOE cards
[Music]
uh it's only Atlanta oh okay one time
summon that's all right then
[Music]
oh that's a lot of damage
it's okay it's okay it's okay
um
I have weekend
big boy
oh Trans as well
okay
[Music]
I don't know if I want to use armaments
now because I need the points
the energy points for other things
oh yeah the weekend won't work on him
the Wake won't work on him
it could it will work on the other ones
though
please free what
[Music]
oh I got my rainbow back
should I do this now I'll get i'll get
healed
or should I defend
what's better
use it okay
yo
[Music]
big hill
now they don't want to attack so I can't
use my spot weakness
[Music]
26. I can kill the minion that's for
sure
even just by using
um the cleave
[Music]
and now
oh wait do I have I can wait I can
inflame and then I can uppercut I should
have insulined first but maybe was that
even there
I think so okay
[Music]
ah from the Mania
he wants to rip my ass
I am scared
[Music]
um
yeah is that the Hyper Beam
uh yeah I have Poma and I guess I should
use both blocks
I will use both blocks because I'm
scared
[Music]
he will AFK next turn
oh okay holy okay
[Music]
really even though I only have two cards
no need right
mommy mommy mommy mommy mommy mommy
mommy mommy
[Music]
I well I mean really the only thing I
can do is block some more
which still will result in me using a
fairy in a bottle huh
[Music]
yeah
I wanted to keep the pomu pods oh no I
want to keep it for the next ACT
oh so sad
I'm still alive oh no I'm not okay oh
my health though
[Music]
and I hope I get another one I really
want another one
ah
blood potion oh a healing potion
at least something like that
limit break
I'll be taking this one thank you
that is on my list
choose a relic social
gain energy at the start of your turn
you can no longer obtain potions no
no gain energy at the start of your turn
Future Card Rewards have two less maybe
that one
on this one
um no I think I'll take the first Crown
yeah
we don't need that many more cards maybe
none at all
free and I still need uh one uh thingy
puzzle piece by sleeping right so
ideally
I want one with many resting places
oh
our right side seems the way to go right
so that's one extra
like from middle to oh we have two shops
here
through the shops and then either left
or right but eventually here is where I
would go
[Music]
okay okay sounds good
hello chest yeah many chests
can I it up Chihuahua we've come so
far
I might use demon form now
and block a little bit I suppose or
battle trans you know
just a little bit of block
[Music]
s
yeah I got my demon form on oh look we
already have the limit break but I don't
know
I don't have to
no they're not attacking nice
[Music]
wait spiky spiky boy oh wait that's the
one that detects me back
[Music]
ow
that little
[Music]
um
I'm purposefully not going for the left
one
it'll be fine it'll be fine
it's just it's just so easy
strike
[Music]
Twin Strike again
I will take a Twin Strike Plus
if I get one
this one I don't know
[Music]
what's this
comment reward screens now contain
colors cards oh one of my hands whenever
you play a power card a random card in
your hand causes zero that turn
toxic egg whenever you add a skill into
your deck upgrade it
of course we're removing a card of
course of course
which one
kind of
I guess we'll remove our defend
and get a the mummified hand
what about the cards
um
no
no need
deal 20 damage
[Music]
duplication portion portion
save the rest
I mean we have so much money but
look at least the duplication portion
could be nice
duping demon form is gross you say that
as if it was a bad thing
do you first reap oh yeah that as well
and listen did you really just say that
is that a reference reference to Diablo
2 oh is that a representative
cross is good
thank you
you guys say always always do offering
first
[Music]
thank you
wait uh-huh
[Music]
I got it I got it uh now yeah we just
used a Reaper and Cleveland strike
but uh yeah just not Reaper
it's here that's six damage okay homo
first
[Music]
I'm not a defend
I know
[Music]
holy
holy sh
holy moly
[Music]
and I can even block the little damages
oh right don't they revive if I don't
kill the others fast oh yeah yeah yeah
okay okay no problem no problem no
problem
[Music]
shouldn't be too difficult
um I would like the cleave exactly none
should be that should be like it
[Music]
yeah nice
went out there with full HP
what was this
[Music]
I'm getting powerful guys what do you
think can I can I say this fire today
what do you think
[Music]
Maybe
I might
is this the Run
maybe it maybe maybe
y'all are so not confident
no I've never beaten the heart before
never
or or
what we do uh I need some sunblock I
think because
this is danger Ross
safe Reaper and limit break oh
oh wow
mm-hmm
[Music]
I have nothing to upgrade them so
yeah that's all right
[Music]
only 13.
damage
[Music]
all right
no wait I should have Shrugged It Off
to get a card as well
oh well
[Music]
oh baby
why
[Music]
it's okay
it's so cool and the result is
acceptable
1713 okay we'll kill the left one at
least I'm pretty sure
we can do it should I I could even play
uh the duplication proportion if I
wanted to
[Music]
no
it's a good hand
unlimited options
[Music]
okay do I go for the damage now or do I
limit break
[Music]
ow yeah
ah weak potion
yeah I'll just keep the ones I have
don't need enough elements
my Armament shows up often enough in my
opinion and we're still getting rid of
cards
I don't think we need it next shop
what is this upgrade to random attacks
at the start of the bus combat heal 25
HP
when viewing your draw pile the cards
are now showing ah no don't care about
the first name I kind of want the
pantograph
and the Whetstone too after removing
a normal strike
can I afford both
but this costs 50.
nah I don't think I can afford both
[Music]
I can't
okay
okay now we're out of money
this is important too then resting
before the boss will not be that uh
important
[Music]
um
let's go what is you
are you supposed to be a normal enemy
you look a little bit Elite but I guess
you're not even though you have 300 HP I
guess okay I guess weak
[Music]
thank you
good
[Music]
pretty decent first turn
so then this one just that he has a lot
of HP
she said it
[Music]
was floating in the background this
thing it's kind of weird it's moving at
[Music]
literally one FPS it's like a clock
oh oh he gets the hitting harder quickly
oh okay
[Music]
okay we want to end it quickly all right
all right
[Music]
maybe in that case
I don't have that much strength now
[Music]
I was wondering if I should duplicate
one of the Cleaves
[Music]
but I guess we're okay
mm-hmm
[Applause]
he's not attacking
[Music]
ah
pretty free
[Music]
couldn't I have done more damage with
Pomo and Cliff together
hmm
[Music]
yeah but the tip of soap all right all
right I'll run
all right all right all right
um
eight times two sixteen
he is like halfway dead
we want to block a little bit
a little bit
and maybe a little bit more
maybe a little bit more
okay now he's cooking again
I will cook as well why do I get spot
weakness only when he's not attacking
and now I get so many defense cards as
well
[Music]
should I
am blue gamble gamble
[Music]
because I still have free energy
replace the place replace
[Music]
wonderful
yes let's go
funnel clap
deal seven damage and apply one
vulnerable to all the enemies
[Music]
it sounds fun but no
fireplace
we are full so we can recall or we can
Smith but we kind of have to recall
because we're in act free
unless
that was a good moment I remember
and now we are RGB
[Music]
RGB RGB RGB RGB
wait oh
foreign
[Music]
twenty seven all right I'll add one more
yeah the order was a little bit but it's
okay
[Music]
I'm aware but sometimes you just want to
throw out these cards quickly
sometimes there's just no chill
I have
right now
and I want a card
limit break
I want a specific card I want one of the
cliffs
[Music]
nice
am I not so big brain because I used the
attack
that would block the damage the spikes
would do to me
I was thinking
maybe you know often when I'm at the
last moment of the game of the combat
and I know oh I just have to throw any
attack card at him now
because he'll die anyway
normally I'll just use whatever but yeah
this time
eh you took the wrong path you skip the
elite you want to farm with the star
no I want I wanted to to rest more and
upgrade more
[Music]
yeah anyway I think that was a good move
from me
[Music]
needed to keep yes
left or right can't be left or right
[Music]
a bag of preparation at the start of
each combat drops
let's go
[Music]
let's
see
W strength not exhaust
Mamma Mia
here I go again my my how could I resist
you
yeah I've been Brokenhearted
yeah since the day and we party
by my God I ever let you go
um another upgrade guys which is exactly
what we need offering
draw five cards
all right
I'm leaving all right
I was so close
what is this what the 999 is this
[Music]
it's not even Elite
that wait it dies in fact you just have
to block for this one I don't have that
many blocking cards that's my problem
but wait he shifts right loses that much
strength until the end of the turn
uh
[Music]
uh okay
thank you
[Music]
how much damage do we wanna do what
because I don't see any strength on him
now can he go from zero strength to
minus strength for what
all of it
oh okay I'll just no okay
um okay
and
[Music]
uh in flame first
and this one's I don't think we should
use demon because then I can only do so
little damage
I try yeah
that's a little bit
[Music]
huh
hmm
[Music]
he dies in free turns
what a depressing
states of life that is
[Music]
um
Mamma Mia Mamma Mia Mamma Mia Mamma Mia
[Music]
if I if I do battle trans now I feel
like I won't get all the four cards I
might not already like so
uh you know full-handed
[Music]
foreign
doesn't matter right actually
[Music]
being cheeky
being extra cheeky
[Music]
and the rest
like whatever
whatever
[Music]
ah
sixty sixty
[Music]
let's limit repo thanks
thank you
[Music]
this is manageable it's manageable
okay
411 damage I like to see that that's
what I like to see
uh he did he did yeah no oh
I don't think it looks
headbutt plus still 12 damage put a card
for me in this card no no
oh
eh take it
take it
[Music]
yes well I'm a break
okay
no more cards though no more no more
shall we go for the elite or the
question mark
do we need more relics
[Music]
I didn't take it
[Laughter]
for me sometimes I want to take a card
and then I don't take it maybe it's my
subconscious
okay
[Music]
this you you will be your own nemesis
ah
[Music]
what he's not even gonna use his first
turn
[Music]
weak and foolish you are
weekend foolish
[Music]
I'm speaking like Yoda no we're just
speaking like kiwawa that's just how
kiwan would speak
[Music]
just defense
uh reduce all damage taken and HP loss
to one this turn
yeah yeah but
block not much has
heck can do Reaper anyway question mark
waitsu
[Music]
onion
no it's the West no it will oh ah I'll
only heal one
hmm
[Music]
I can't
block more
[Music]
should I attack for one HP for free
I mean
[Music]
no downside to it so
okay Flex
[Music]
how much 78
that was an easy one
um
bracelet normal enemy combats are no
longer encountered in oh
at the end of the game
that doesn't really help me
uh
strike it off plus
I thought skipped it I wanted to check
what my shrug it up is
just normal right
um
take it
but there's like no this is X3 right
there's no more shock to get rid of the
other one
it's always good
okay
[Music]
I already forgot after you beat the boss
of act free was it like you move on into
a room I think I remembered I was like
not immediately the last bus there was
like two more fights so one more fight
or like one fight and a restaurant or
something like that right but the the
fight before the big boss was also like
an elite or so
ah Fireplace shop Elite then final blows
oh okay five plus at fireplace and the
shop okay
okay I got some uh uh
eyelash in my eye I think
okay Spire Grove uh
I have to slay you
[Music]
um
should I draw a card
should I draw another card
[Music]
not
but in the end I didn't lose anything
because the other cards would have not
helped me either
[Music]
okay
I'm kind of a wasted first turn I guess
because we could have done much more
damage
[Music]
Township games oh you
got I think I saw like 500 gifted
memberships
what the
first I didn't even stand like you know
all the gifting no gifting more than
usual huh I guess because there's so
many um
unusual viewers but then I realized
it's Easter and my gift memberships
on the first stage their eggs
and it makes so much sense
Cali was writing people up I don't think
it was only that but yeah yeah holy
you guys we're so
so crazy with the memberships what the
hell
yeah
500 man
members I I wonder if there will be some
who will watch the membership streams
the upcoming ones or the previous ones
who knows
um
oh I hope they don't watch the Star Wars
movie watching okay
one out of the 500 maybe would do it but
but generally
damn
[Music]
I shall do an uppercut
and I shall wow
44 damage
should I not block at all what do you
think
defend
okay
[Music]
my hand is full
do I really need to upgrade it wait a
second
[Music]
that is six strength
oh he is going down
oh he's going down
oh goodbye
I forgot this is the famous buyer
are we there almost oh it's almost right
before him right in front of him
or him his or what what name them
uh
uh no
[Music]
I think we should heal
or rely on our potion but I think we
should rest yeah Our Deck is pretty good
now we have armaments so upgrading is
not that important I would say
I know I have relative but I mean we
have Armament whatever better safe than
sorry
all right the donuts and the other one
Deca Donuts it's been a while
been a while
who to kill first did it really matter
Donuts okay
[Music]
I'm scared do we get healed after this
or can I
can I can I go all out
you do okay they're not that mean that
they don't heal you okay
[Music]
um
it's a donut first
[Music]
I don't know if I should defend or focus
on the damage
if I get healed anyway
um
it's just five blocks
[Music]
do I have something to get cards yeah I
could shrug it off a little bit
and 10 armaments or armaments first but
I kind of want to Armament on the new
card maybe as well
okay
shrug
yeah and Flame
uh two more energy we can inflame and
limit break or we can reap
[Music]
ah
okay
[Music]
Oh Mamma Mia
I'm back to full health this card is
Gonna Save my ass
It's Gonna Save my ass
oh
don't forget your potions yeah I want to
use them but I also want to keep them
for the final final Final Boss you know
or we shouldn't use at least one potion
[Music]
I got something good
out yeah save potions for art at least
the healing potion I want to save
and maybe the duplicate tool could be
very very helpful
[Music]
I can't get it out but oh well it's
better now it's somewhere else now
oh they got so much blocks this time
oh what I'm gonna do I guess we shrug it
off
[Music]
shut it off
draw those cards
and armaments would be nice additionally
before spotting them but I guess
[Music]
um
did not get the armaments that is said
[Music]
should I trans
guess
or Flex
free flex
okay okay okay
I
I want to weaken but he'll negate it
anyway right so
what ifs
[Music]
that's okay I only lost one HP
good
it's premium
safe stable choice huh
mmm
Maybe shruggage
um
it would only upgrade Bash
I'd rather limit break and then Bash
[Music]
I got an achievement jaxed why because I
have more strength than ever or what
[Music]
50 strands oh
okay come on come on
[Music]
shrug
shrug again
should we limit
okay 114 to all enemies
who are enemies
[Music]
oh
I didn't even use a single potion
look at my strength
wow
[Music]
ducky ducky ducky
a deep posing dreads can be felt
throughout the room is this the heart of
the spider the source of this game
you ready your blade
attack
you deal 7 out of 12 damage your hot
squirms and bleeds but it is ultimately
still pounding
that hard not my heart are your
mightiest attacks not enough
you ask yourself have I been here before
the heart pulse is louder and louder as
your Consciousness begins to fade a
sudden burst of energy emanates from
inside you jolting you awake
the heart Retreats upwards the large
door is revealed in its place
porch
hi TV
oh
it's only our second time
that we've gotten so far and I have a
good feeling but I will I will leave a
lot to you guys and I don't want to
it up
so we Smith
we Smith my daughter's movies
um
nah
come on
brought two cards
can a cut
two two
four
eleven
frame
um
okay
I just woke up cute thumbnail and thank
you is good as well today
are you surprised just kidding
we're a good morning we're on a way to
slay the Spire yo
hi
I will spend all my money on you what do
you have it let's buy a nice right like
a happy flower
uh instead of each comment apply
vulnerable to all
uh what unplayable sense cards can now
be played whenever you play a status
card exhausted
um
[Music]
it's good for the heart
oh my wrong Boomerang what Boomerang oh
feel free damage to a random enemy three
times
eh
mad kid Mad kid Mad kid
[Music]
and we have Justin
open of a card should we remove
the block card
or strike
strike
okay
because I feel like
the fans are already
not often there often I'm in a position
where I need to defend and I don't have
anything to defend with
[Music]
and then we shouldn't lower the chance
anymore than we already
now
pouring
[Music]
huh
right now it's just random enemy three
times I I guess with
with a bit lot of strength it would be
good but
[Music]
we can't even upgrade it though
I guess
ah higher Raiders oh you came at the
right time okay let's go let's give them
let's show them
something exciting
let's give them a good show shallowing
we won't we won't
all right all right
uh ah yeah right here now you're like
surrounded by them
um and thankfully they start with
25 less should I go for one of them
specifically first I know what it was
something with back attack deals 50 more
damage as it is attacking you from
behind
um
can I turn them around well I turn
around when I attack them right
so I wanna
I wanna face away from the one who does
the least damage I guess
right
um
[Music]
most take the spare out first usually
you can kill Shield really fast
okay okay
um
yo
[Music]
I'm so scared
nothing wrong
[Music]
they shouldn't be too much of an issue
though with my
damaged output
you can always crash the game if things
look bad that's right that's right
that's right that's right that's right
uh where's spot oh here
um yeah whatever
now
I have two more
I could do a free cleave do I have some
more strength strength card no
no no
okay but I can apply weak and vulnerable
first
[Music]
ah
boomerang
[Music]
should I not make them vulnerable first
though
[Music]
I got pen buff
I spent all on the same one
is that good or bad
oh it's good okay
foreign
block a little bit
more strike
[Music]
drugs
yeah but the damage
it's still quite a lot of damage
because I don't get healed anymore after
but we have we have our our healing card
we have our healing card right so
um let's maybe shrug first
yeah Reaper can heal me
struck first
Flex
and then maybe limit break and then
bash or well maybe Pomo strike because
we get another car
[Music]
yo
oh my limit and then Pomeranian
perhaps on the spear which is now dead
wait what
25 28
all right
all right easy easy
[Music]
yo
no mistake please
[Music]
should I uh
rip already I'll spot first right and
then shall I reap
[Music]
hey what
ah mommy
no I saw people say rain
he blocked it all that little
[Music]
Mommy
and one guy no I think it was more than
one guy
should I heal myself while I'm here
though
and what what oh my God I was by
accident
cute
uh and a
[Music]
and it was the phone will take 75 more
damage rather than 50. y'all
and whenever you play a park at Hill 2
Hp which is really not much but okay
oh I would not take this
you know froggy Wawa is coming
kind
skip take pass take pass
I will not take it
if we could ah
I go we're gonna slay the Spire I hope
we have to
what's the catch like what do I need to
be careful of can always bring them
orange pieces ah okay there's like a cap
to how much
HP it can lose
and whatever I play a card I take one
damage okay
drink potions uh text
okay
[Music]
offering right
try the dupe demon form
um
I have demon form now
should I do demon form
okay
[Music]
I will literally check for every move
guys
[Music]
in flame and flaming flame and Flame and
flaming flaming flip in flame
we have no no Armando
no I'm on
[Music]
come on shall we
shall we block
yes
Amanda Watson
shall we battle trance
truck first okay
I'll
Flex
battle trans
[Music]
oh still no Armando
limit break
[Music]
and now and now and now and now and now
best
[Music]
not even that much
favorite before later okay
and then maybe a clean
oh actually
homo does more
[Music]
okay
how much damage is he gonna do
[Music]
I think I have a shit's hand
what the
shut up did I get the thing where I can
play them are they free to play
what
exhaust potion ladies can I play them
oh but I should I hmm
use the potion now really
[Music]
oh
well
okay
[Music]
my hand though I can't even I can't only
have my blood potion in left
[Music]
sword swordfish
Boomerang hey baby
[Music]
is there like a second phase
was there a second place
it's been too long I don't remember
[Music]
just as one oh now we can do it we can
do it
well my energy is so wasted
ah yeah only free on the damage Pro okay
I only did like half of that
holy
no
am I drinking now
he just clapped me
okay at least we have some Block cards
um I guess I'll drag it first
ow
okay we can weaken him
[Music]
do I Armament as well first or do I
cut away
that was all my energy Oh No 2 times 12.
that's 24. okay
okay
should I play in the board
always
[Music]
I need my Reaper what the is my
Reaper oh Cali
[Music]
no I didn't get one guy there was like
10 people saying that
Bell trans
okay he's cooking he's cooking we have
some
time to play around
do I shrug
and then Armament Maybe
almond first
I think it doesn't really matter right
does it
I'm A bash arm first
oh wait I guess I don't really need the
blue you know okay arm
mustache
36 37.
don't draw this thing okay
[Music]
just clean
okay ah
[Music]
foreign
that's so sad
we have to we we can win right no
we can win
we can win this is beatable
it could be beatable
won't be beatable
Ryan
definitely beatable no copium no
okay start again we'll do this until we
win
ah demon form I can do right I cannot
even form
no wait we doubled even for him I
remember also uh during this
and find duplicate fashion and then
doubled in my phone yeah all right all
right so far so good oh
um
can we take what block first before
doing all the other stupid things
I feel like last time
no why
because every time I do something I get
damaged
[Music]
that's what I'm saying that's exactly
what I'm saying but then still people
say no don't blow don't blow what what
what what what
I am bread right
keep making me question myself some of
you
all right all right I'm right
foreign
[Music]
yeah of course the block goes away but
for every of the other cards that I
would play I get a damage and I want to
block that because every damage counts
[Music]
your clay thingy gives you free armor
next turn for every envelope damage you
take
[Music]
hmm
it's more worth you also heal a lot
okay I see you
okay well um
[Music]
fresh rock again
Donald Trump
[Music]
no more draw oh yeah right
guess I could limit break
all over 20.
[Music]
I'm Gonna Leave oh wait 45 well
wait didn't we do like promo last time
[Music]
um
the l25 damage will run should we boom
around
face wound
[Music]
they won't not days to play won't end
this remove the wound
[Music]
play play it wounds play wounds
foreign
and let's not play Reaper
but wait holy he's gonna do 60
damage I'll heal afterwards right we did
that before
am I blocking as much as I did last time
I wonder
26.
[Music]
51 damage
but this time what we did differently is
we didn't use the exhausting potion
right away
cool user now I will definitely drink
[Music]
I have a worse hand than before well
extra time exhaust all of them
or do I want the damage for blocking
[Music]
I wanna win this
there's like but just like sincerely not
that much more than I could do different
than like you know
that would make significant difference
[Music]
I think last time we like Shrugged
pretty early
because maybe I was hoping for an
armaments but I don't know if I did get
it
oh
[Music]
just like this maybe the more the
merrier hey hey hey hey we got him we
did 250 damage
[Music]
I think we're further than before
referred it on the floor
it's the turn oh oh I am in Kill range
[Music]
yeah because he takes he can take
maximum 300 and he's at 280 now so in
theory we can kill him next turn and we
never got to this far before so we don't
even know what that will get in my hands
let's go
foreign
[Music]
could be worse but I can't defend a
is this bad
because I can't I don't have that much
damage output and I also don't have
let me in
this is not it either
[Music]
wait
I I I I
[Music]
I no
how am I gonna win this
my cards oranges
all right
don't play offering on turn one
[Music]
exhaust potion early yeah we need to
change the iron no wait it's not even
about RNG I'm just gonna keep on getting
the same cards aren't I because they are
on they're in that order
unless I play them in different orders
[Music]
I will get there we have to it's a
pretty decent deck
[Music]
don't block eat clay
doesn't sound so healthy but you know
all right no block turn one okay what
about the offering though should we do
the offering
[Music]
safety potion for second limit break
okay
no offering offering yes offering okay
offering
what should we not should we do that
though
yeah because we never did one break we
took things
don't always do
[Music]
with the potion
the two decks is for the whole fight
right
[Music]
try exhausting strike and other useless
card yeah I mean I guess we can try why
not but they don't look that useless to
me Mr only strike Maybe
and cleave
[Music]
thank you
clean
[Music]
too basic you're basic
yeah well I mean we can try we're gonna
try and see if that like helps us
we might just get like more of the
shitty wound cards and all that instead
all the time
well that's okay I will drink this I
know
[Music]
okay where do we go from here
Lucy
[Music]
this will lead to the same thing we have
to change it we have to get out of this
Loop
[Music]
no
[Applause]
[Music]
I can't spot because he doesn't attack
me spot only gives me strength when he
attacks
[Music]
that's
huh
you want even more iron
you just want me to play it for the sake
of playing it
um
[Music]
yeah anyway I defend 30. that's uh I
guess already more than before right
foreign
[Music]
this is what I'm getting from the chat
link
yeah
37 may have more HP done before
but still shitty hand
[Laughter]
uh heal
drunk
y'all okay yeah I've seen this hand
before
[Music]
okay
do I play this
[Music]
huh
okay
[Music]
39 and 21 block
that which will which will not matter
just her
name
[Music]
okay
frog and trend
[Music]
see
yep lemon break wow I don't have the
tubing anymore limit upper
I meant
[Music]
okay
you're good now am I am I
hold my hand please
this is the run really
promises
[Music]
we can heal oh yeah oh hi Reaper Armin
and reap I'm gonna reap and I'm
Boomerang I'm reap I'm
okay first of all armaments
I'm gonna reap now guys
I'm gonna do it
okay
now I'm gonna Boomerang him
looks damage
okay
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
it doesn't it doesn't matter it doesn't
matter it doesn't matter that much it
doesn't matter that much but uh
the limit break
and there we go there we go this is it
this is the moment we've all been
waiting for
[Applause]
it was a bit ridiculous
surely there could have been a little
bit of a smoother run with that last
boss oh my God thank you guys
what yeah
it was all right that fight I guess all
right I mean I wanted just to make sure
to make no mistakes
so I asked for a lot of help but but but
oh well
it was light
what happens now
oh what's that
is that just one one like one piece of
the puzzle or what no I'm walking up the
stairs yeah I slayed the heart I'm
walking up and then
while I'm walking I'm burning
[Music]
um
I set it on fire is that good or bad
thanks for the super Jazz oh and then
what do I do all there on the Flaming
spire
gonna jump down
oh
for the first time wow
Heartbreaker I defeated the heart
Overkill yo
Tony and some new cards yay
oh
finally is it no more lore
where's the lore
I thought I would get more lore
I do not get it until you slayed a
spider with every single character
emulate good card
there is some more lore
after credits I am the Lord
[Music]
now what has it been done
yeah good question that's what I'm
asking
the Spire sleeps
and so shall I
ah
what's that voice
who was that voice
that
nice touch right
I don't understand
I guess it was good right I won I won so
I take it as a win
[Music]
ah the ship from Legend of Zelda Wind
Waker
you mean that the big
the big
fish
I unlocked Ascension did I
better art oh
Is this different
is this is this the front
[Music]
ah
are they different
[Music]
for the cards what
thank you
[Music]
on pendium what
ah
card Library
they look the same
is there like a
H wait there is
ah
wait
wow
wow with a glow up
oh my God anger
oh
what's this the poor the poor fish
uh I kind of like this one it changed
quite a lot maybe they should have kept
it with the animals
ah
what if I check them this is how they
will appear in the game as well
[Music]
this one was all right yeah
oh my God
oh
oh funky wait what
thing uh mid-life crisis the right one
public strike oh oh is that is that
blood streaming out of his face
shrug
the boomerang Circle meringue oh
this is Wi-Fi coming out of my body I am
Wi-Fi
what
what it's a cowboy
spinning in a little buckets
laughs
well yeah okay what are they on the
strike ah they're twins on the strike
that's so funny
oh my God these cards
these cards
oh cute
oh my God
oh my God what was the what will this be
that looks terrifying
very bloody
oh
I like this one
how cute
drop cake
Apple becomes shiny Apple what why
[Music]
it's right like this and give it to the
artist like hey can you draw this but
better or or was that not even the
attention because some of them are so
different that doesn't really look like
um
they were supposed to be
like this
come on the fire breathing is a hot
sauce
I have placeholders until the artwork
was finished it was so funny then man
how long were it is used
oh
I want to see all of them but there's so
many because this is only the Ironclad
cards wait have I only unlocked the
Ironclad ones I suppose probably yeah
right
um
yeah just power through GO train go you
can do it
head butts the wall
did I see them all now
oh so angry so angry
and kfp calls her chicken I will keep
this one
Rampage
come on when ah
it's wrapping a page oh come on
Reckless charge why because they're
charging him recklessly or
although he's being charged because he
does reckless purchases
oh no oh no he's gonna buy
what is going on here I don't even know
searing blow
you know there should be like a card
pack with cards drawn by Hollow members
and then most of them will be shitty
like these ones
except when you know draws a card
but I want
yeah a whole no or Hollow card set with
these shitty coins
that's funny
uh
it looks so funny
oh we're seeing red
uh severe severe Soul oh he goes for a
ghost this one's pretty good though
[Music]
oh spot weakness let's let's see because
this one's out I feel like this one's
also kind of derpy with the with the
like minus HP or so
haha
okay it's basically the same
but more Derpy it's good I'll keep that
one uppercut oh
a dragon does uppercut on small human
Stickman
wow they put some effort into this one
that's a legit Whirlwind y'all
barricade
or Cirque uh
smash bludgeon yeah yeah
brutality oh my God I'm gonna get age
restricted
[Laughter]
ah
why is
the deform like I guess a human in a
bear costume no no wait yeah oh now I
see it he's like
oh
it's a bear form not a demon form
they took it from Japanese
they're doing a Japanese joke jerk
akuba is demon and a Kuma enough
enough
double tap
oh come on
oh
you little shits
feet Yes feet feet the burger turkey
please now I'm hungry
being fire
hmm maybe I'm not getting some of these
jokes maybe they're going over my head
but I feel like I'm getting plenty
[Music]
it's fine
impervious
I don't know what that means but that
looks like one of those candies I love
that one it's really yummy
juggernaut
mm-hmm
limit break
[Music]
that's how he's going offering
oh I offer you the heart looks like a
turkey for Thanksgiving
Reaper
hmm
oh locked oh no
oh only two more cards that I didn't
free three more cards that I need to
unblock
oh
see all the other ones damn they're
worth seeing
it
they're so funny yeah well that took me
four and a half hours and it's kind of
late so we'll keep it at that I just
wanted to slay the spiral ones but I
suppose we should space inspired
maybe we can spay this bar as well well
maybe that would help less less spiring
um
less spiraling all over
the space fire
yeah with Nina helping me with the more
difficult ones I wonder is she really
that good that she can coach me she has
like hundreds of hours on there I only
have like 30 40 hours damn what only 40.
damn
father will be more by now
um
don't want any baby spiders running
around no no no more no more no more
little spiers no no we must kill them
all
ah by the root we rip him out hmm
that would be amazing yeah then you guys
don't always have to help me so much you
can I almost have to wait for the chat
to answer
but I think
team two aren't chat
me me and you we're a good team I think
yeah pretty good pretty decent oh
we did good thank you for helping me ah
I mean I think I played quite well on my
own today as well a little bit a little
bit oh Chihuahua
um doing her own decisions here and then
every now and then but then later I was
nervous so I just wanted to not it
up
ah thank you
yeah that was fun it feels good to
finally slay the spire
let's go to my office
oh my God
as long as I
um caught up we shall try our best to
keep it that way right
[Music]
here in this double
oh this is probably double
here we go
there we go
I feel like I kind of cheated by
crashing the game
so often
would be good if I could do it without
crashing it eventually right
we'll get there
hopefully
no I reset all the time the game
mechanic
if it was really then wouldn't they give
you like a setting retry
you can crash it yeah but
I feel like if that was really like
supported by them wouldn't they give you
a like like in five of them retry this
fight
option huh
they really didn't mind but I guess they
could change it if they did mine but
um
I feel bad when I went by using that too
yeah
it really means it's a skill issue
caused by you
player
I have so many DMs
wow wow wow wow wow wow wow
have you guys heard of this this game
coming out called the Mage Seeker from
riot games
is that gonna be good because I'm
getting a free code very nice from
Bright games
they don't they said we don't have to
play it
but you know if I get a code might as
well do it for one one stream
the Mage Seeker never heard of it it
looks alright
the Mage Seeker
looks a lot honestly from the trailer
that I saw
let's go
let's go guys we have to do karaoke
stream
I think
um
somebody coyote
uh used it already but so we have like
this new thing
uh you know how in Japan there's
two big karaoke systems
I didn't say Senpai there's two big
karaoke systems joy sound and dumb d-a-m
and when you go to karaoke place they
will often ask you which system do you
prefer joystand or Dam and then
depending on that they will assign you
to a certain room because they have
different songs I mean they both have
like like everything you could desire
some systems have more like Vocaloid
songs for example than others
and some systems have maybe more
original music videos than others
because often they just come with a
really generic videos that fit the
the feeling the vibe of the song I guess
it's been months since my last public
honor cup really
so last one was archived Maybe
ah true
well yeah so anyway
seems like Korea you already used it but
we're getting
access to an application from joy sound
where they just for our streams not for
song covers but just for streams cargo
streams we can use it
and
basically we have access to a lot more
songs and I think it should be even
uh non-japanese ones because Joy sound
and damn they both have a ton of
non-japanese songs as well
so that's really helpful because I've
been struggling to find
um some instrumentals especially for
Kpop but also for J-pop like for hello
project songs
because I um
especially for like Betty's Google and
cute and smilage there weren't so many
that I can use
most of them were like morning musuman
which isn't my favorite group so you
know and bull on some ah there's there's
so many more songs that I can use them
yeah no no they're not gonna be archived
necessarily
um so if there's like an English song in
in the joy sound application
we still have to go by the other thing
um Jazz rack and check if
that is okay to be archived or not
but still it will give me much more
choice of instrumentals
yeah I can do hello project cut I'll get
that should be able to be archived
because uh those are Japanese songs and
usually they're fine with jazz rack
yay this is good yeah other song is
public
they might have a public Choice sound
oh list maybe uh probably I'm not sure I
feel like they might
oh
oh always it seems like that not
immediately the whole Library will be
available for us
um
but I can request
I will I'll have to check um and test it
out I don't know everything yet I just
see the big big
announcement
you can use this now please
don't worry next time next time somebody
gets together
I'll get that done I'll check it off my
bucket list
I will I will
ah looking forward to it
subscribe
yeah you've never done karaoke no
I mean we've done you know the myth
karaoke on archived one in LA
where we were all together
but I didn't really sing with Google I
think I'm just saying like you know
roughly a few songs together but I was
mostly like half asleep on the side
um
no
oh yeah yeah
we did a song cover but no no karaoke
yeah cuddling with India
in a blanket
yeah oh
I'm looking forward to meeting Guna
again eventually
and
using this hair
I think she knows a lot of Vocaloid
songs I was so shocked when she chose
last night
as her song in the forecast
I was shook it
oh
didn't think she would know it
it's pretty old school that song
um
back then they were look after Luca Luca
Night Fever
you know
fever after that somehow there was like
this this boom Going On
when they kept on releasing songs like
that Legos
fire endless night or whatever
a night of Desire
there were so many of those they were
all like kind of
you know
similarly themed on purpose there was
some pattern going on
and Meg Omegle is one of those
ah
right I guess because she plays project
diesel yeah that's why she knows a lot
of uh vocalypse songs ah
oh wait my hand
just realized you couldn't see it I
thought it wouldn't be able to see it
okay
that makes sense
but I could no it makes no sense when my
hands are supposed to be around my
costume
blanket as a whole no no
they were like I think maybe two people
who brought their blanket to uh Anime
Boston as well
I saw it on the picture
somebody used it to put it on the ground
to maybe sit on it yeah it was just fine
it was just fine but um you know I'm
just worried that you know people will
just walk over it huh be careful with
their dirty dirty shoes people will just
step on it
it's kind of risky huh
but in general it's like a good
um like area marker when you put it
there you're kind of asserting dominance
to say hey this is kfp area
and at the same time you're advertising
me and at the same time
it's just cute
and you're maybe giving other kfb a sign
hey hey this is where we are
yeah kiwawa territory
and it's also nice decoration just you
know
well it's like a picnic bracket but not
really
don't use it as a picnic blanket outside
on the grass not recommended
but on on normal carpet ground and so on
yeah fine okay okay I will I will let it
go through
I think the bright orange makes the
obvious that is true but I saw a lot of
staff
at Anime Boston we're wearing orange too
not only the you know the shiny
reflective
um
reflectory reflective
jackets wet vests but also some others
were wearing orange too
um
and the MC was also wearing orange
it worked out though they often join in
without parting really deal
uh I think you guys left the impression
that kfp is a lot of fun to be around
um
you guys went all out
staff loved us
you know that was funny to see in the
zoom call while I was saying while Kobo
was saying I saw a staff like walking
through the aisles
uh
but while walking
[Music]
the whole time they were like cheering
themselves they would
I think they even had a pen light
possibly
they were like
showing how to cheer as well
yeah they were enjoying the concert as
well
also by the way our time slot normally
would have been 45 minutes I think
but since I think I was told nobody
would come in afterwards and we were
welcome to just
go up to one hour if we wanted to but we
could also just end it at 45 minutes
turns out
well we took the full hour anyway
not including
the time they played our two music
videos in the beginning
not even including that including that
it would have been over an hour
also not including the pre-show where we
were
only talking to you guys via voice
not even shown on screen but we're just
like saying hello to the people that
were seated
um
yeah
so that was hopefully yeah your money is
worth
um
very important
but what I didn't expect for some reason
I thought it would be hotter over there
didn't expect it to be so cold in Boston
I thought you guys were just like not
able to communicate properly because
even though I said Celsius please you
guys were maybe saying in Fahrenheit or
so
and some people because I didn't hear it
so clearly some people were showing it
with their fingers and I'm like he's
showing nine fingers what does he mean
there's no way it's just what does he
mean 54 because one hand is five and one
is four 54 Fahrenheit Maybe
which is I guess kind of realistic right
you say it was 40f that weekend well it
could have been something like that
Boston be cold surprisingly
yeah and couple told me well not Coco
told me Google told me over there in
Indonesia right now it's really warm
damn
probably never that cold in Indonesia is
it
tropical
although
is it always warm
um
makes sense
lowest I've heard English you go is 21
000. whoa
whoa
I think I'm glad I live in a country
with four seasons
especially now I went outside today just
to buy
you know groceries and stuff but holy
the air is so refreshing right now
I was like damn I gotta go outside more
I'm like suffocating at home
um
somewhere where the only season is
Autumn yeah why not spring then
just wonderful oh also by the way I
think what comes pretty close to that is
maybe England
foreign
ing
always cloudy isn't it in it
um
yeah yeah
okay let's read some chats guys and then
I'll go cook myself some food and then
tomorrow we're playing uh passport two
two the second one came out finally guys
and I played it a little bit because I
suddenly felt like it when I downloaded
it and I tried it out a little bit I did
so much better now because there's like
you can walk around the city
or this little village and by helping
others with drawing specific things that
they're asking for you're opening up new
areas and so on and it's like really
cute it's really cute
the graphic is better too and I don't
know it became really detailed I feel
like
yeah there's quests now they want you to
draw like specific things and and I
don't know if you really if they if
there's any AI or sort of like
recognizes what your if you're actually
drawing what they're asking for like
roughly by the colors or by the letters
or so
I'm guessing no and it's just like you
depending on how how committed you are
to the bit maybe
can you still go broke oh you are broke
in the beginning and then you have to
like you know get money to buy
little little studio and so on
did that fix the pink issue now I would
assume
that they are not so biased anymore but
we'll test it out I only play it for
like 25 minutes or 30 minutes
I didn't get really far I just wanted to
play a little bit and it was really nice
it was really relaxing I played the
whole thing on my Wacom so I was just
moving around with the pen as well
because it's like click somewhere and
then they walk there
um it was really comfortable to play on
my Wacom
on my cintiq because I have the screen
you know
as the painting
surface
it's really comfy
um
closer to Scribblenauts now maybe maybe
yeah
oh my God
all right
reading super chattan
from now on
oh wait okay for the holy and Easter
thingy too oh
not so many it was mostly memberships
wait there's so many what the
there's so many cat stickers for Judds
huh
a banana and a million cats
what what why
except ah didn't they do this before
girls talk
I feel like yeah that happened before
I'm not gonna read all of those
I'm not gonna read them you know what
I'm gonna be really really mean and I'm
not gonna read them I appreciate them
but I am not going to read them they're
basically flush Jets
and the saplings are probably not gonna
come by to listen to my Super Chat
reading anyway are they
so mean
fair I think so too
I normally often don't read plus Jets
anyway
I'm establishing I would like to hear
well did you send a cat
or some saplings there yeah maybe like
some cave
of peelings
but now
so okay let me skip those uh all the all
those stickers I'm skipping them this
could be scoop
Boondock thank you soon thank you Cruz
thank you oh my god a rainbow
thank you thank you for the meeting
great as well as the panel sorry for
being nervous and not asking you any
actual questions yeah some of you guys
did it again I always tell you guys
think ahead of time what you want to ask
me and then write it down
because then
it happened again people not knowing
what to ask or forgetting what to ask
because they didn't write it down
happen again
hmm
oh well saplings riot
it's just nature
um I kind of wanted to thank you in
person and there's so much I left out
like how amazing your music is how good
your art is and how funny you are I also
forgot to mention that tomorrow is my
second anniversary as a member oh as a
member but not as a viewer right
being at kfb has been nothing but
positives showed shootouts no shout outs
please to all the kfp and Anime Boston
who will help me throughout the weekend
you build the best community I've ever
been in oh
yeah
I also forgot to mention that wait I
already read it again thanks for being
you you're giving us so much and I'll be
a loyal Champion till the end of time
love you on kfp finishing the rainbow
with a request for more Alto kiwawa or
another my hug
great
talking to you don't worry about it
it's really nice
to put faces to the
to the names and so I saw your results
of your of you working out because you
always report on my hashtag about
working out while watching me which is
so a die so respectable
I think you said you started because of
me doing my workout and then I stopped
but you continued so respect
please please keep on doing that don't
give up
yeah because there are results and I
think once you actually see results
that's more
um motivating when you start something
and you don't right away see the results
then it's easy to give up because you're
like it's not working it's not worth the
efforts though
hmm
but damn good job on that and thank you
for coming thank you for the support
thank you soon and thank you soon for
the support a little little close kiss
in your ear
you you
thank you
thank you I hope you had fun
no
I think you're good
check out 47 Alexander
soon
it's a red one chickens who's a chicken
did I
talk about frequent
they're in the Stream
in what context
what context is that
but I want to show you the eggs that I
drew like especially one because there's
one that I think turned out really good
let me show you
where did I save them
because they were special eggs
that would give you even more points
remember
run by me
maybe they are in here
you and Emma Bieber so cute together
right
right oh okay so I don't know this one's
just nothing special the nice real
one with clouds I didn't even see that
one anywhere Juana must have collected
it immediately
and one with a bow and some polka dots I
was like rushing these
and one with a logo of whole life I saw
this one on a cup
and then this one I thought would be
nice I I just made Emoji stickers on an
egg
I said you can add even more if you want
and then this one is my pride
look at this burger egg
I even put in like shading and
highlighting I have to be fast with
these you know
I think I did them I threw them while I
was waiting
to call into Cali's stream actually it's
a couple
days ago a week or so
because the eggs I was told they can be
just last minute because they're really
can be implemented really fast
um they said no worries about that like
could even be one day before but you
know I wanted them to be done a little
bit earlier
um
fun is a little try hard in these games
really I feel like she was maybe just
lucky being in the right position
running in the right direction but holy
they were just gone instantly what
the if we could have tested that
out properly if there would have been
time I would have added like a million
more eggs
or another area
to collect them in my God she's so
she was vacuuming them yeah
we had no chance
and she especially got all these
Chihuahua eggs that give five points
instead of all the random one point eggs
I I would have probably had them add
more in the in the private rooms because
I think the private rooms legit didn't
have so many eggs
the individual eggs in there
I don't think fauna took them all
oh yeah
Spice in there right there was plenty of
space to put in more
hmm
oh thank you yeah I was
if I already had it as a VR model
so and I was really happy that we got to
confine combine froggy Wawa with iMovie
I just put I'm a B on the funnel because
I thought it was cute I was looking for
like pngs or pictures easy easy to use
Easy to crop pictures for the thumbnail
and then I remembered oh yeah Emma has a
b model oh my God that would be so cute
on this thumbnail because hers was the
last one I put on the thumbnail I
thought it would be perfect if she was
flying around there so I looked for a
good full body shot but there weren't
really any
but she did one stream with a black
background
where he was just messing around in full
body
I took a screenshot from that
um
and I looked like she's flying around
and then you know I may saw the funnel
and she said I don't know if I can
really use Imma Be unfortunately because
you know size difference and all that so
I thought oh that's okay I guess she
won't use it that's fine I mean you know
no problem but
[Music]
so tiny
but it's so small wow you're so small I
could eat her I wish I wish I had them
the tongue out option in VR as well
because I did have that um
during my normal streams
yeah but she was flying around and then
she was sitting down in all these little
spots like in the cup and then the
Easter basket and all that oh it was so
cute it was so cute
she flew up I don't know how she did
that I don't know how because I couldn't
get up there but she flew up into the
tree and I couldn't reach her there what
the she was legit flying how does
she do that
huh
how does she do that you're so cute she
was so cute
unfortunately somehow like right before
the stream started
um you know I had her
stream uh free obs
to my channel because
um you know there's this whole camera
system that we have
and I wanted I wanted to play in desktop
mode because it takes quite a bit of
stress off of me
so
um the problem is if I use desktop mode
and I activate our camera system
the thing is like if you have VR goggles
on then any of the young girls you still
see normally what you look at but on the
desktop it would render the camera
system to the desktop view the window on
the desktop
so you can capture it with obs
um if I don't know if you understand
what I'm trying to say
but basically if I were to play on
desktop mode you know if the camera
shows AME that's also what I see and
like I can't play like that right
because often I would want to run around
collecting eggs but it would show other
people
so I was like
and then yeah I asked if anybody anybody
who wasn't planning on streaming turns
out that was everybody
uh could help me out and stream
um it's to me but it would have to be
someone who would be okay with using VR
so yeah amen was okay with doing that
for me
and I think she was gonna do VR anyway
even even if it wasn't for that
yeah yeah thank you I'm a problem was
somehow right before uh the stream her
internet suddenly got really shitty
that's why another reason why we started
a little bit late because she had to
like restart and everything
um and and then somehow even after that
uh her Discord was still kind of weird I
told her in the beginning
I told her that she she hears us she
hears me
like five seconds later because she's
been like replying later to us
but you know maybe you we thought it
would fix itself later but it was
throughout the whole stream and then at
the end I told her again and she was
like yeah really what what
because she didn't even realize
awkward for her because it was like
there was some awkward moments because
silence there after we asked her okay so
what about ilama and then silence
silence and then zoom into her and then
she answers it always gave
ah oh yeah right I was thinking that for
us it was really delayed but probably
because she was streaming and she was
just answering whenever she would hear
it for you guys it was probably on time
huh
wait what how did it
how did it come across on stream
actually I need to check that
wait but then I wonder does it result in
us talking over AMA a lot because like
you know by the time am I would answer
we would like react on time again right
like she would say something and then we
would answer like
that's stupid or whatever but then
wouldn't that be
no way that would also be delayed
on her side okay I just hope it didn't
seem like
too weird on her on her side on the
stream sign
you guys were the ones delayed
you guys responded to her like she was
on time
oh
yeah but I think that was Abby's
internet because for all of us we heard
her too late but then between the rest
of us it was fine
um
it was like a comedic pause every time
she spoke
she would answer and then you guys would
just be silent
than a second later love oh that's so
awkward that's so awkward
ah
another time where Discord me
over they replied I was like uh quote
retweeting that tweet somebody clipped
on Twitter of me saying s-e-ggs but I
actually said eggs eggs
but this chord was cutting me up so I
said disco what the and they
answered to me on on Twitter official
Discord
little shits
no man
bad what must the members and the
viewers have followed me in that moment
I must have thought oh she's bottom left
after all she just randomly says s e g g
s but no no no
that's what I was saying like really
elongated I was saying eggs
and then I guess it cut off the first
egg and then it rejoined on the S
ah
yeah
why I wasn't even screaming like I
understand Discord cutting off when
someone gets like loud that happens a
lot I wasn't even screaming what the
hell
yeah
they were like oh my God what
okay and I'm like what
what I said nothing weird
man what did I do this time is what I
was thinking
why
[Music]
oh man
I hope they believed me afterwards why
would I random
random like to say it like with context
or so like now
I don't even like to say it when it's
like you know the other word for gender
not even then because I know you guys
will clip it
and be like whoa
she said the words
I'd even like to say the German number
exactly because of that because the
German number six
is stat
[Laughter]
oh man
anyway respect and I thank you for the
red super chat I went on a big tangent
there
um
oh that slipped in here interestingly
random person happy
25th birthday congratulations
good for you 25. what a nice age
thank you
for froggy Walla okay I'll give it to
her Patsy donkey
sure
look thank you
I know how to say that
oh I know it Charlie age Plantation I am
a tea
stance
no text
why why thanks for the support though
I
um after all
I paid for this adventure I don't even
know how much I'm paying
I just said hello can I commission this
and this and this and that and then I
didn't even ask for the price because it
feels awkward to ask for it
I I should ask
should ask
um by the way
which am I
being charged for the extra stuff
I don't even know I normally don't like
um commissioning things without knowing
how much I'm paying I normally don't do
that but uh
often times these things are being
you are like oh what the but like I
normally check this you know when it
comes to like music videos and and my my
yeah whatever when it when it's like
music stuff I always check like uh other
commissions
but yeah okay for this one maybe I
didn't ask because I was scared to ask
want to not think about it
but but you know what am I told me like
sometimes I ask your Hammer how much did
you pay for this just you know it's a
reference and she's like oh I don't know
I just I just say you know henna I need
to Commissioners and I just let it let
it happen you know I never I never asked
I never know
she's more irresponsible than me when it
comes to that she never knows how much
she pays for these things
oh another I've already answered
because no reps is watching the stream
it seems hello thank you
I'm so sorry for the stressful situation
I really don't want the people I work
with to be stressed out about these
things either so that they don't feel
like negative about the experience you
know
I'm feeling really bad about it for for
the viewers and for the people involved
um
when it doesn't go so well
but I mean I think for the viewers it
wasn't so bad it was really just a
waiting time and the scoreboard was like
whatever right I mean it would have been
nice if it worked but in the end you
guys see us playing the game so as long
as we got that to work it's all right
um
okay
doesn't know either
well
oh you know when I saw Cali
Cali got two signed cards out of eight
boxes I just wanted to mention that
unbelievable and Cali got assigned okay
and I'm like so close to asking her if
she feels like she needs the card or if
she would like to donate it to twenty
because chenma really wants it I think
and I couldn't get it for her and then
Kelly got that yes yeah I wrote to jenma
when I saw that I'm like Hey general did
you see
did you see Kelly got assigned oh Kyle
and the Sun Moon
I'm so sorry I couldn't make that happen
for you
maybe I'll write to Cali now
hello Miss Calliope
Mori I come to you with an inquiry
I saw you got
two signed cards out of eight boxes you
lucky
bastard
um
the question is do you really need
them both
I think there is one person who wants it
more than any of us
and she really deserves it
so if you feel
kind-hearted
and wants to do a good thing for a good
Soul who always
Works her butt off
for us
which you would you maybe
that's just gonna play it she's not the
Ambassador
she doesn't need it
I'm sure she got a normal okay too which
he made me wanna give it to gentla
give mine to her if I would have gotten
one
I gave her my other
cards
but I didn't get a sign for him
anyway if you wanna
keep it that's fine of course
but you know
Cali is really nice I think she would do
it yeah
what does she get in return the feeling
that she did something good and I think
that's enough for her she likes to be
nice to people okay
I think if she knows that she can do
um
Gemma a big favor then she is
more than happy to do it
um
don't worry guys don't make a big deal
out of it it's not guilt-tripping or
pressuring I wrote it in a way that is
noticeable that is a joke as well
no you're not serious about that are you
guys
she knows she doesn't have to but you
know
chenma is working so hard for us you
know Gemma might not be careless manager
but she you know she works for everybody
basically
she always helps us so
Cali is super nice like why would she
need to hold on to this one card you
know
oh okay
okay
um
yeah I think Cali will be more than
happy to do I know Kelly you're welcome
Kelly would be
over the moon if she could do something
nice to Jenna
yeah
that will be worth more to her than
keeping the card
yeah
you should offer her to sign her a key
wild card and she doesn't need a pillow
card
yeah yeah I am asking for Gemma because
there's no way Gemma would feel
confident enough to ask
don't worry don't worry let's move on
um
oh again a pinky following up the
wordless red super chat thank you so
much thank you and hope you enjoyed the
Stream
cheers
[Music]
okay now
now now now
uh from today
[Music]
it's so weird
this artist drew me quite a few times
it's always so nice
and hey we
die for real for real finally I'm true
to my word
[Music]
thank you for
how many super chats and a pinky
weird story incoming recently had to
design and build a trap to catch feral
cats we needed surgery you did that
situation seemed impossible for thinking
about the way you fight for hopeless
seeming situations and make the
impossible happen for share willpower
gave me strength the Trap worked and he
got the surgery needs a home now but he
lives
just want to say thanks for the assist
you didn't even know you gave me oh also
yesterday was my birthday so I'm
treating myself for treating you oh
oh wait first I want to ask
are you working for some like I don't
know
um animal rescue whatever thing
Pro tip tuna
yeah but they
um yeah I guess they're very they can be
extremely careful though
they recognize traps sometimes
cry all cats
yeah but like I'm thinking like if you
don't have a job like that could you
have asked like some animal rescue place
to help you with that I just did it on
my own got some connections and then I'm
in my rescue place though
why'd you do it on your own if you were
struggling with it it's so sweet but
you could have asked maybe there was a
service like that
a lot of places will just give you a
trap and nothing really
so nice that you have because the cat
needle now
thank you for doing that and hopefully
it will find a good home
oh I needed to build a custom Trap by no
trap in existence would have work why
how did you build a custom trap like
what did you make
explain
this contraption
build it out of planks of wood
man you must be really handy man I don't
know how I would build that
but I actually I actually also once had
to catch a cat
today I would tell you about this
this is like maybe um five years ago or
so
yeah I saw
I think so what happened I think was uh
or so long ago so I don't know if I
remember the order correctly but I think
I I came out of this old apartment that
I lived in and it had like it has this
inside
um
quartz kind of relatively small with
lots of green or some bushes
and
I think that's when I noticed there was
a rag doll cat
there and I knew that ragdolls uh people
normally don't keep ragdolls as any
other than like in-house cat because
they're too precious and people will
steal them yeah I think I told the story
before but I'll tell it again
and and then and then I was like that's
weird but I had to go to work
so I think
what I did
I think I right away
try no no maybe first I just left some
food there
yeah I think I went back up and I I took
some I took a
I took something to give it to give food
to it I think and then I came back after
work maybe
and I saw it was eaten
the cat was still there maybe maybe that
was the order and then I took it in
and
um I I already had cats at this point oh
so it can't be five years ago maybe it
was like four years ago all of my class
you know something like five or four
years ago
just got my cats I think so I had to
like close uh the other cat in the other
room and I was gonna go to the uh vet
oh yeah because I think it had a
microchip now first before I did that
before I did that I think I went around
the neighborhood
and I asked everybody if they had lost a
rectal
I asked a lot of people
I ran a lot of doors I I went pretty far
away from my place as well
um
I think it was a lot of nose
uh-huh that was weird asking for so many
people but I really wanted you know
somebody to get their cat back
and then and then I guess then I went to
the vet
yeah and then it had a microchip
and I got the address
and it was pretty far away
I went with a taxi I think
I put the cat in the transporter I
brought it over there and they were
really happy well
well but you know I paid attention
because I knew that cat was too first of
all it was too pretty to be an outside
cat
was too well kept and
yeah I knew the race was the type of
race that you keep inside
um
why not just leave it at the vet
or I don't know I think I just brought
it because I was you know already
you know
on it oh breed yeah
yeah so I did a good thing and but that
one wasn't so hard to catch I think how
did I do it did I just pick it up
normally
so easy see that means this should
be extremely easy to just steal it as
well if you wanted to
hmm
ironically at that time I was thinking
you know I want ragdolls by myself
and hmm
they were like oh if this cat wasn't
taken
when I if I hadn't just gotten my own
cats recently
I could have kept it
yeah but obviously it was someone else's
cat
they can be pretty expensive
depends on the country and city and so
on I guess but
yeah they're like they range from 600 to
900 per cat
maybe I think in Japan they're way more
expensive actually in Japan generally at
Pet Shops my God
pets
so overpriced like babies puppies and
kittens so overpriced
crazy
you're my baby now
it wasn't the baby anymore though it was
a grown cat
um
I really want my own ragdolls one day
yeah ragdolls are just so irresistible
aren't they but
um I
I mean I'm I'm not in the in the
position to judge because I didn't do it
either but
at least not in this case for my own
cats but should always go to a shelter
to save
um
an older cat or like a
lost kitten or so
yeah Berman rattle 1400 500 oh that's
not your place Danielle
um here they are a bit cheaper they
don't go so overpriced
yeah if I ever get an extra pet I want
to
get it from a shelter hmm
I hope I can
oh
yeah older shelter cats they're often
just so sweet and they just want to
cuddle all the time
you know
I wish I wish I could take them all in
I need to get a house for many many cats
my house or space for many many times
and save all the cash I will save all
the guns
and we'll get
um
a house with five rooms
four of the rooms will be four cats
okay now yeah now but honestly I really
should make like a cat cafe
hmm
like a rescue cat place with the
a side option of being a cat cafe by by
doing that it will like run its own
itself like it will pay for being you
know a rescue animal shelter basically
it's just so genius
it's so genius
it works in Japan too they have
um cat cafes which are just if you guys
go to a cat cafe in Japan I know it's
really like like hard to not go because
oh it's a thing that many other
countries just don't have and and you
want to check it out right but maybe if
you plan on doing that at some point try
to find one that um is like you know a
rescue type
there are a couple just gotta look it up
because a lot of the ones which are not
like that which are in like the popular
spaces like on takesha Dori and Shinjuku
the places you see everywhere especially
I mean you can kind of put one-on-one
together but if like the lower floor
floor is a pet shop and the floor above
is a cat cafe
this is often the case then you know
please do not go in there
don't go there
go to a place which has
rescued cats which maybe they're not at
all as cute as the ones in the other
ones
why
I don't want to go into it but there's
like many many
band
stories
about
those places
it's just all for profit
mm-hmm
I don't know if it like really applies
to every single one of them probably not
maybe there are some better places but
in general I think it's just better to
support a place that is trying to bet
their best to help out cats who
otherwise would be
you know taken down in an animal shelter
because no more space you know
cats who really need help
yeah
my first week
okay where was I anyway Happy Belated
Birthday no actually nothing like this
yeah Anna yesterday yeah close but not
so so related as sometimes others are
congratulations
[Music]
I feel like you doing that for that cat
is kind of a present to yourself
because you did a good thing
you made a cat out there very happy yeah
congratulations for your birthday
you're a great person
I can tell and I think you just have to
stay the Way You Are
happy birthday
Justin thanks for the pinky sorry for
sending a red super last year
sorry
was speechless
Oh you mean an empty one can you sing a
happy birthday in a whispering tone for
all the KFC who are silently celebrating
their birthday
they'll try to stay awake as much as I
can don't want to be vodka in this night
just to never say but you're still here
I'm probably sleeping right now now
[Music]
I don't see him
happy birthday to you
yeah it's gonna be a jam I don't care I
don't care
[Laughter]
damn it
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy
everybody
happy birthday to you
chat
[Music]
in your shoe too
I might be late to work thank you as I
got robbed on the way there
they took my bucket and now I have no
means of friends
tell me right this is a joke right the
bucket makes no sense
also I'm hopeless now how the wings work
am I supposed to eat them you didn't get
Rob's did you
you didn't get robbed right he's just
joking about what maybe membership uh
you're out of your bucket is that what
you're saying
you okay
you stole my bucket ah
you didn't steal it you trashed it you
don't need it anymore Revival
you're a little confused but you got the
spirit
don't eat your wings
just fly try you can
you got way better than before
it only means of Transport how is a
bucket a better way of transportation
than your wings think about it you can
think
how were you ever able to move in a
bucket in the first place where you
cannot use your your wings unless you
fall over and then just roll
think about it
but who's gonna push you you will need
someone to kind of push you
no wings are better understand just try
give it a try don't be so skeptical
thank you for the long long long term
membership
just trust me bro
let's do it
don't let your wings be wings
rolling is fun rolling is easy I
wouldn't say it's easy
it'll be easier once you know how to fly
trust me trust me flat flap flap flap
panicly
yeah you get dizzy when you get rolled
don't you throw up all the time when you
do that
foreign
young gals are just so awesome and
amazing thank you very much
thank you for the support
even though you lurk now you made your
uh you're lurking known to me I'm very
happy to know you around thank you so
much
very glad that you guys enjoy watching
us get joy from us thank you
foreign
I bought it a second time to play on
switch for my flights to Japan and
really helped me get for the 11 plus
hour flight starring home also was
surprised by the lack of Ian merch in
Japan
Oh you mean like in those little shops
like in Akihabara and so on or
or where do you mean
because generally they don't really sell
them in shops it's all just online right
most of the time
well those are well that's kind of you
know different but uh
they probably have Cali's relaxed time
or whatever that is figure in the arcade
now because they had Subarus before they
probably have calories now right
purse looks so good
I was so surprised man
oh yeah by the way I'm so sorry
um
so sorry that the uh concert merch is
not available in Europe at all
I I can't I wouldn't even be able to buy
it think about it
um
but I think this as well can be solved
by using a proxy right
probably
which you would maybe want to do anyway
because it's cheaper in terms of
shipping probably
so yeah Australia as well
I don't think it's not I don't think
guys it's like oh we don't exist uh for
cover I don't think that's it like I
think they would like offer it if it
would be possible same with like the
Amazon things where some countries it's
just not possible
it must be like the shipping provided
that they use
not being able to ship there for some
reason which is weird I mean I think
it's weird too I don't understand either
um
I don't I don't I don't get it either
but you know if you really want it and
you're in Europe I think using a proxy
would be smart anyway
um
I know I know it's not intentional
though but yeah I I know I know if I was
a fan I would be kind of mad too
because you know I'm in Europe I'll be
like hey I want to buy this but I guess
I guess you're saving me money by not
making me able to buy this so I guess
thanks thank you now I make better life
decisions by saving my money because I
would be broke if it was for whole life
so thank you
and I keep on telling them though guys I
was like eh
I'm gonna promote this even though I
can't even buy it myself
really
hey I get it guys
but you know
I've been really um
making them look into
the whole weird shipping crisis issues
though and
you know in the end
yeah it is what it is
it's not that's it don't I don't want
people to always assume it's cover's
fault I know it's frustrating but it's
not always yeah it's out of that control
often
so please understand
online friends with you project I don't
know what that is
what is that
all our friends of you what is that
but is that anything like whole on live
meat related
the plushie project
I haven't seen it so I guess no
I guess that's a no
oh
let's meet anyway
um
hopefully hopefully you didn't have as
much trouble slaying this spiral as I
did but it was fun
it was a lot of fun I want to play it
again
Dusty thank you for the rest of the chat
my cute
I'm so glad I had the honor to meet you
I remember you my mind did blank out
though when it was my turn
Ah that's okay it wasn't so bad I think
we had a normal conversation I love your
singing voice your dance moves are
amazing and your quattle is the most
adorable sound in the world
are amongst the things that I forgot
love you see yeah I think you are one of
the people who didn't you know
I think I scolded you
about thinking about it you know
I ate a croissant today yeah today I
attempted on having a better and
different breakfast
I bought so many fruit so today I made
it looks like berries and banana and
tomorrow I make it with banana and kiwi
probably
and oh also I bought also canned um
uh orange slices thingies
not oranges Mandarin and
I have many different ones and I want to
do it like with vanilla yogurt and maybe
eventually maybe I'll add some
um Corn Flakes or so as well because
I used to have breakfast like this like
corn flakes with yogurt
grab and bananas rather than milk
sometimes milk as well but I think the
Corn Flakes of yogurt combination works
really well
mmm it's really yummy
I love Mandarin oranges yeah they're so
good
yeah I bought everything fresh except
the Mandarin slices
I thought
it would be too annoying to always you
know open them because ah I hate how you
know there's all this like these white
strings on it and I I always I just
can't stop myself I always feel like I
have to you know
rip them all off and it takes so much
time so annoying and when they're canned
they're gone
what how you can't you can't boohoo you
cannot say that my croissant is the
reason you're not going to the gym
anymore
you are making excuses
unbelievable
my fault mental gymnastics yeah see you
don't I guess you don't need to go to
the gym because you're doing mental
gymnastics by claiming it's my fault
I read the Super Chat wrong I said the
opposite he said the opposite
oh
well okay but I don't even think
croissant makes you gain that much
weight I mean
but okay if that's a
his Island's the one doing mental
gymnastics
ah whatever you know it was just like
passing by quickly I was just trying to
read it quickly
they're bad for you no how can a
croissant be bad for you like listen how
is that bad
oh
okay see how is that good for you how's
that bad for you
can't be
no no it's good butter is healthy
[Music]
um
thank you Dusty I'm so happy you came to
the meet and greet and that we could
talk like this
yeah even though it was very short thank
you for coming I'm glad that you made a
good experience as well thank you for
thank you foreign
that's what I could get behind
uh billion thanks for the Easter stream
it was so much fun
oh but aren't you
European
if you watch the ball or did you
suffer like me
in the middle of the night
yes I stayed up oh mental gen you stayed
up too
yes we suffer that's up for the whole
thing oh my God I'm so sorry if you have
a like weird question but do we have a
job
I hope I didn't like up your sleep
schedule for a job or so
especially yeah for EU
H this is not ref from the EU or that
area as well
sorry
I thought you know 1am not so bad but
then
I started at 2 am
that's pretty bad yeah UK
um
oh okay this man
it's fine thank you
you know I thought you know because it's
like a bigger collab and I'm the only
European so I should sacrifice
you guys two hours behind ahead of fun
what
who else
but it was just one I didn't even like
really think about that that's true
fine
um
so it really ended for them at 3am
that's
that's fine
it's fine
that's nothing
I stood up with had to rewatch the quiz
that definitely drifted in and out of
sleep
um at least you had something else to
watch later and falling asleep for
something like that is really comfy I
think
I like falling asleep too like Netflix
sensor one but then I wake up and
sometimes it's still running and I'm
like where's my where's my remote
control where is it
and I can't find it
and then the more I look for it the more
my mind wakes up
I want to announce that I officially
dropped one of my remote controls
between like like my bed like my bed is
like weird it has like
the the head part is like kind of
separate
I'm gonna drop that today
like in there and I don't know how to
get it out but I have another remote
control so it's okay
yeah I won't get it out until I move
yeah the headboard my bed is so heavy
and I can't move it
rip
it's served me well
as a string to it well now it's too late
isn't it
hahaha
bro Tony job
my nose is
[Music]
did I get my finger yet my box
my mom wrote To Me
if you are looking for
a really genius game look at pentiment
it's absolutely amazing trust me
also your Slater's buyer is also great
we should play Magic against each other
and then one and a half hours later she
writes to me and says after checking it
again I'm sorry actually I don't think
it is something for you or your
community sad
huh
why not
she changed her mind one and a half
hours later she never goes back on what
she says
laughs
why
she changed her mind
I never heard of the game
never
very text Heavy
maybe that's the problem
maybe for a stream it's not really good
but as a game it's good
she's trying to reverse psychology
Maybe
anyway did I get my
um
I probably got my
my hello beatbox
boom boom boom boom no
I'm gonna get spit on my microphone if I
do that
I can't I don't know how to beatbox
how do you how do you even do it
[Music]
there you go how is that
[Laughter]
Google
no bgm is a nice addition
me
wow
[Music]
sounds pretty good I think
[Laughter]
I have a talent for this
Calvin real quiet
okay okay
what where was I
didn't even finish the reading a super
chat I get all emotional thinking of how
hard you work pursuing your dreams and
still finding time to arrange of
wonderful collab whilst also being live
at Boston you're an absolute treasure
thank you I I was like oh my God I was a
I was I was feeling so stressed
to hold it I don't know why like in
hindsight or like if you think about the
calmly calmly
it's not
that bad of a schedule but
[Music]
um
stressed me out especially because
I didn't have time to test it
that stressed me out more
um
but yeah I thought it wouldn't be so bad
because I'm not streaming on the day and
the panel is just one hour the meet and
greets they ended up taking like two or
one and a half hours it's not so bad
it's not so bad
somehow
I'm so stressed out by it
yeah
I was so nervous I was mostly just
nervous about the stream more more than
I was nervous about the panel I was
nervous about the stream not going well
because it was the first time I'm
organizing something bigger and I didn't
want to rely too much on Amen at any end
I did rely on Ahmed
um because I needed her help I mean she
kind of did it on her own without me
even asking her
kind of just was there when it was time
to test it out she was just there
already doing the thing I'm like oh oh
no oh no oh no I don't wanna
[Music]
yeah but she really helped me because
you know I would have been kind of lost
um
but I tried my best to take care of
everything else
like planning it out you know
explaining things to the girls
yeah anyway I hope I really hope it was
fun for people but I definitely cannot
do this regularly as much as Emma did it
before uh maybe I'll do it once or twice
per year like a little VR thing
organized by me
um
not more
take it
it's like I don't know why I don't know
why
how why
hmm
I don't know why
am I probably has like no
stressful feelings for this kind of
stuff because she's just so used to it
I stress myself out so much over that
um
yeah stuff like unbelievably believable
I was worried about too but I had more
confidence in that because I feel like I
had more control over it
um
and it was just easier as long as it's
not in VR things can't go that wrong
I was determined to make that one go
well
to make up for
and the other stream that didn't go so
well like audio wise and delay and all
that so I was like okay okay the fans
want to hear everyone clearly everyone
loud the same volume and all that they
want to hear everyone talk okay okay
okay I wanna I Wanna Give something like
that to them so
I booked the studio
you have everyone you know being a
professional environment and have
everything going well no no big problems
no delay but I mean the delay could have
been fear still happened if I wouldn't
have prepared well but I did
um
yeah unbelievably believable
I feel like you could create that in VR
too but
um
and it would look fun it would look good
would be cool but
I feel like it adds an unnecessary layer
of stress
yeah would be funny but yeah hmm
I'm so hungry now guys I need to finish
super chats otherwise I'm going to die
right before your eyes on stream do you
want that
chocolate insomnia thank you for the
pinky thank you all thank you for all of
your hard work this past weekend you
definitely support us we are hot water
hme yay hot water no I don't really
agree with that
couple name at all
that makes no sense to me
Kobo came up with that
I don't like it
I don't know I don't know I don't think
it's good don't tell her though
thank you any math
um
writer child
thank you for the pinky I don't know if
you're allowed to play with Steam
Workshop mods but did you know there is
a mod called the iron clock that turns
the iron clad into a chicken
thanks for streaming this game so much
no way
one of my faves and really fun to watch
thank you but wow
why
does he keep the same attacks and so on
is the only thing that the visuals
change
should be making chicken sounds at least
iron Club this is a visual mod it's so
funny
yeah
I mean for mods it really depends on
what the publisher says
and I don't know I don't know that's not
the information that we normally get
like we have to ask and then they have
to go to the publisher and ask and then
it will take a while until they get back
to me so um it's kind of too annoying to
inquire hmm
but good to know maybe in my private
time
I don't want to ask though about mods
for slight Aspire because I want to play
the online two player mod thingy
I have to slightly inquire inquire the
Spire yeah
they have Steam Workshop integration and
they're probably okay with it then
I have to ask
okay we're done thank you
oh that sounds like fun damn
it'll be on a roll of too much happiness
thank you for the pinky I want to tell
you that you've been a huge inspiration
for me you're talking about learning
Japanese on your own made me want to and
I passed the M5 after a year of studying
I also got excited to study abroad in
Kyoto so thanks love you cute Vala thank
you oh my God congratulations I'm so
jealous
how long are you gonna be there Zack
how long
you know this will make it more
difficult to watch my streams four
months ah okay that's not so long
but that will be fun
excited for you August of December oh
enjoy actually you're like I mean August
and September still gonna be hot but
you're you're experiencing like summer
autumn and low-key winter but not really
I mean yeah yeah Loki maybe even like a
low-key winter
not really high key winter but you're
gonna experience kind of three seasons
more or less in Japan
let's go and join I wish you best of
luck
hope you can travel around a little bit
too while you're there
um
oh that's so sweet what
I saw a picture of you guys in the
waiting room I was like oh that's so
cute they have their own room
tables sitting in groups I'm like are
there like oh interesting group
constellations formations
thank you unwrittenberg thank you soon
please
let's go both thank you two for
celebrating my win thank you thank you
thank you
we did it we have a lot of help from you
guys but we did it animal dance
thanks for letting us back say thank you
no thank you for helping me although
there were a lot of like mixed
um mixed signals today and I didn't know
even one guying it's just very mixed
signals today
but it's okay like I'm not I'm not
criticizing you like I don't I don't
know what to do how could I criticize
the chat about you know them not knowing
what to do hmm
it's like hop hop all the time
do this no do that do this no do that um
I was guessing you little you're
confusing me
we're just guessing
but nah it's okay it's okay
we had we had fun and I mean there were
it was always the option to just crash
whenever something wasn't going well so
the most important part was building a
deck really
yeah and I think we did that relatively
well
I am
thank you foreign
um
[Music]
thank you
ah
you're the one you're the one
beautiful I mean you guys saw the super
chat too probably though
you're the one
talked to me about your Journey with the
cancer
wow
I feel like it's so random that I made
you learn dances but I don't even know
how we got there ah because you told me
that you like my dancing so I said oh
you should take dance dancing classes
wow good luck with that yeah yeah enjoy
life every day
um
so so happy for you
foreign
about that really oh
well I slated but she should still help
me I would appreciate it the Jolly
Ranchers
thank you
the one you met my boyfriend in Boston
we both were so happy you were able to
come your pound was amazing and I hope
you can come back sometime soon I met
many amazing kfp I'm so thankful to you
for bringing us all together
thank you
it's so sweet that you guys you know can
end your whole life together I think
that's like so adorable that must be so
good
you know because otherwise maybe there
would be like hey when you're watching
this
um girl online call Amelia what the
don't you love me you know like
that we don't need that we don't need
that just enjoy a whole life together
right awesome awesome
um
you know you know you know it's like oh
you need if you're in a relationship you
need to like appreciate and understand
each other's Hobbies because like
sometimes I see these videos
I'm sure there's like the other way
around there's similar things too but
sometimes I see these videos that maybe
I think they're they're just doing it
for the sake of making a funny uh oh so
funny video
but you know how like sometimes there's
like like girls women
they film themselves going up to their
boyfriend who's like gaming and they're
like why did nothing attention to me and
then they take their Xbox or Playstation
or whatever order a TV screen like Smash
It and destroy it and then they're like
what the
what
the is wrong with you
yeah and then for one of them that I saw
it seemed really legit like it was just
a joke to her
and he didn't even do anything
and it's like Soul toxic it's so bad
um
and even if you know that's like pretty
expensive things you need to understand
like a PlayStation 5 is
expensive
don't destroy it for the sake of a funny
video those have to be fake I don't know
sometimes
people can do really crazy things for
the sake of views on tiktok or whatever
and yeah don't understand where the
boundaries are also in a relationship I
think I don't know I know
um yeah it's not funny it's really not
funny it just seems so disrespectful to
destroy the the property of your
significant other
it's because you're a little bit pissed
you're not getting attention or so
like that that's why I think it's
really nice to see a couple that shares
the same hobby therefore you will like
understand each other and enjoy it
together and that's just like goals
isn't that so ideal
nice crane
so happy
you know what you should you too since
your boyfriend did Armando before you
know what you guys should do
although I guess hmm
it would be so cute if somebody could
cosplay I'm a b and froggy Wawa
maybe you couldn't do who Amanda B and
frog
cosplay together
cosplay your horses
[Music]
right
um
I want to see that
oh my God froggy wow yes yeah it is so
easy to laugh and you could you could
easily find like a froggy Wawa kigurumi
jumper thingy
I mean ideally froggy wow should be
small and and chubby
but maybe you can fill out the jumper
nah don't need no need even but froggy
loud cosplay in theory is really simple
really simple
yeah let's go
fill it with padding if you want to go
all in you know
look onesie so cute
riveting
celebrities
hope you can afford those commissions I
don't know how much the Super Chat costs
me I might look it up later or you know
it might forever remain in mystery you
should know how do you not know
he was just like closing your eyes and
randomly clicking on a price
and then just random without without
even looking then you type in the
message you don't know how much you're
actually sending
nah you know you know you must know
thank you though thank you for the
support
[Music]
I now know how much I'm being charged
while I was discussing it on stream I
have been
I have been uh
informed
yeah
thank God
yeah Jen my nose too now
uh
Eric
thanks for the pinky thank you so much
for the mng mng M meet and greet
and panel at anime boss and this weekend
was my first time visiting the USA
and meeting you wait are you the one
who came from what was it I think it was
Belgium
are you the one
yeah yeah yeah oh my God I was like what
the yeah but you said that you're
not there just for the convention yeah
yeah
thank God I would put like I would I
would feel so pressured to make it like
most enjoyable
for you the panel um
well it was a big coincidence that uh
overlapped with your trip yeah
I made it into my favorite vacation trip
ever fingers crossed for another eel
can't appearance soon I I gotta be
honest I have absolutely nothing lined
up for this year and normally they're
like kind of planned ahead
um five months roughly
soul
now I said it before but maybe at the
end of the year there's still something
possible
[Music]
um
like you know
November December conventions
I mean I'm open you know
European conventions yeah I mean the
either don't have the interest or they
don't have the budget and all that you
know
to be like that
but anyway thank you so much for
Africa I don't know if you're back
already home but if not then safe trip
and I hope you enjoyed everything maybe
you made some great friends in kfb
I yeah I'm glad you got to go especially
uh still in your hotel room oh
especially because there are barely any
appearances in Europe so you got really
lucky there to just happen to go to the
city where that convention is happening
at the right time
you are at the right place at the right
time perfect
hey so sweet uh ow thank you for the
pinky boss I forgot to tell you I love
your animal outfit has cute ear and
fairy tale plus your hair is very
beautiful so cute is this outfit
represent type of puppy
you mean you mean my casual outfit with
with my cat ears and my cat's tail
right
now
say it say what
is he recommending a game no
from my cover of Animals
ah
oh
let's go though
I love cat I love cats too
Maybe
you mean the ones I'm holding right now
I'm confused but thank you thank you
soon
and that was supposed to be a cat at
least like for my casual outfit that's
supposed to be a cat no
but it's a very like Foxy Cat and I like
that
Black Version
[Music]
stay in here you gotta get me to a
Brazilian convention yo
goes Brazilian conventions invite
takanasikiwawa huh
how about that I
yes
I want the Brazilian
s watch us
we didn't watch YouTubers I wonder if
we're like popular there
we virtually transmitted to Brazil
that's all I want to do
unless they pay for my flight
then I go to Brazil
I have some some Brazilian fans no yeah
I'm happy
thank you Celia
let's hope I can be a Brazilian
convention sometime
21 months thank you and for me
to freedanka soon rise of free Danke
Schoen mental Journey Danka soon
and hopefully
boots and cats boots and cats
nah doesn't work
and back to Turkey
I'm done I'm gonna go cook now it's
already passed me that what the
[Music]
man
tomorrow I'll finish before midnight
[Music]
now I'm almost also kind of I'm a little
tired
I will contemplate I got contemplates
don't think about it
and
German we say oh
fingers
[Music]
I forgot the rest
bye
[Music]
foreign