n
[Music]
w
a [\h__\h]
[Music]
w
oh
[Music]
B
h
[Music]
Kitt
hello uh hello to one
four 1,440 P kiaha but I don't know if
it's actually wait it's actually like
this not fitting the screen size is not
[Music]
fitting it sound
weird I I played around a little bit
with the audio settings well how weird
when you how weird do I sound like a
robot
or yeah I have noise cancel
on I do have noise cancel on because um
I have it's we have a [\h__\h] heat
wve and I bought uh like a like a vent
fan and I will probably turn it on soon
and I listen to
the audio with the fan and it
sounds uh noisy so I figured okay I
might need to use a noise because listen
now I'll turn it
[Music]
on well so I in my headphones I don't
have the noise reduction on but you guys
should have it on so you guys shouldn't
hear it yeah in German it's like 30
I don't know how much we have here but
it's very
hot yeah you don't hear a thing right I
mean I don't think it's very let me it's
on four now let me set it to to 10 and I
want to see if you can hear
[Music]
it wow it's so
noisy do you hear it it's 10 now my
voice cuts off occasionally is it really
bad though cuz
I think I need the I think I need the
fan for a while I don't have proper air
conditioning okay okay now this is too
loud anyway I want it to be want it to
be less us
okay
uh I would I get caught up oh God damn
it really really really do like I tested
it and it seemed fine
[Music]
why I mean I'm using because the goo art
uh software doesn't have noise
suppression or reduction I'm using the
one from OBS and but it should be
good cutting midw
sometimes I mean I can turn it off but
yeah you'll hear
the let me show you how it sounds
without uh
oh okay so this now I think every time I
speak you hear a little bit of noise do
you prefer this
one do you prefer
this this way I thought it might worry
worry um bother you guys it's better
it's not so bad yeah I have it pretty
low I can turn it even a little bit
lower maybe barely noticed
okay yeah well we'll have some gaming
sound too
so uh with the gaming I mean I don't
know it seems like a relatively quiet
game so maybe not too
[Music]
much we'll be playing the game straight
that has just been
released uh the yeah just now yeah
sometime I'm around
now I could probably turn it up oh no
it's pretty pretty nice right now I
think pretended City sounds all right
yeah this is totally it's cars it's cars
driving around I I could imagine
that sorry guys it's been it feels like
it's been a while but it's only been 2
days but it feels like I haven't
streamed in weak I feel like a noob
right now H It Feels So
unusual like who am I what I'm a cat
right I'm a cat tuber I
think
[Music]
me it feels does it feel long for you
guys too cuz inor it's only been 2 days
so it shouldn't be
do You Hear the bgm right now by the way
it's not the game bgm but just just
wondering do you hear the the current
bgm yeah okay and by the way for the,
440p
uh I think I got some YouTube settings
wrong I mean it does show give you guys
the option
right but wait no I'm actually I don't
know is that really 1, 1440p cuz I I set
OBS to an output of
3,840 X
2,160 but YouTube is telling me in
YouTube studio right now that I need to
change that because they don't support
that
size they I I guess because you know
when you stream there's different
settings um is that 4K yeah if you
stream 4K or so then you have to like
lower a different setting like there
will be more delay also I
think I wanted to try though and see how
it goes but it seems fine so far no
buffering whatsoever right
[Music]
yeah I think it it sized it down
right it sized it down from 4K to
2K YouTube come on you're you're trying
to limit my true
power it smoth right on my ears that has
nothing to do with the 4K
[Music]
ah okay well then you know what next
time if it sizes it down anyway then
next time I'm just going to use not 4K
but 2K which is still an improvement
which is what you see now apparently 2K
is
1,440 I thought that's
um I thought 2K means at least
2,000 my cat ears are distracting
well then you're going to be very
distracted throughout the whole stream
all right we're going to play stray
which I've heard about quite quite a
while ago and um I'm not sure if I'll
play the whole game today I heard it's
like around five five uh huh around 5
hours Alo I'm waiting for an Amazon
package but I'm I'm not sure if I can
hear it with my headphones on
if you guys hear something if you guys
hear something that I don't hear that
would be scary but let me
know um sure otherwise I guess I guess
I'll just uh not receive it um what was
I
saying oh yeah yeah so I mean um what we
could do is either split it into two
streams and chill like play for free
hours and then read super chats or try
to go through the whole thing today but
then we probably don't have the energy
or time to read super chats what should
we
do ghost in the room I don't believe in
ghost so
uhuh D but don't worry about it two
streams better two stream
really I'm not sure if like you know
everybody's going to come to the second
part of the stream I feel like usually
when you split something into two then
less people are going to come to the
second
part just because they lose the
attention H play until 3 hours and then
aside you know what we can do that that
makes sense let's do
that close apartment is hunted yeah yeah
I've
heard to me I listen to it but it just
sounds to me like she's breathing in
between talking but I don't know I mean
if she doesn't have any recollection of
that of breathing between talking
then I guess I don't
know I mean she's actually taking a
break so she must really believe it was
a
ghost since she she's take she she's so
scared she's taking a
break maybe she needs like uh what do
you call those people who get rid of the
ghosts in your house
maybe she needs a ghost
extinguisher not extinguisher
exting Terminator ghost terminat
Ghostbuster okay ex Exorcist that's the
word I was looking for but I guess I
could have said
Ghostbuster who you going to call
Ghostbuster you saw you saw both voices
no there's no such thing as seeing
voices usually unless you looking at the
volume on the PC or something but you
cannot see voices okay now I'm just
roasting you
sorry you mean if I saw both clips of or
you know instances uh I'm not sure I
think I did I'm not sure
anymore
[Music]
anyway no but but I've I've uh when I
lived in Japan with the people I've
talked to I've noticed a lot of them are
very um what's the word when you believe
in super lemono not Super H
super super
super uh magical
stuff ah okay yes I guess yeah a lot of
Japanese people from the ones I met are
pretty
superstitious believe in supernal not
not Supernatural stuff but you know
yeah yeah
yeah surprisingly I don't believe in
that at
all I think at all at
[Music]
all okay maybe we should start
playing so I let's get into it I was
wondering also should I play full screen
or should I stay like this I usually
always stay like this but I don't know
maybe the immersion will be stronger if
we if we play full screen you
think oh wait sound is
crackling sound capture fix this [\h__\h]
for
me now I lost my
hearing oh you guys now hear it don't
you I kind of [\h__\h] something up I
think did
I trying to fix the audio now I [\h__\h]
it
up God damn
[Music]
it a
[\h__\h]
sound sound sound
sound I would like to
[Music]
hear
Hello you guys hear it
[Music]
I broke my sound I don't hear it
anymore I know you guys hear it it
doesn't it doesn't go for the same
before I heard it now it goes
away standard
system not
there let me do this
or let me do this
[Music]
hello no
confused okay not a good
start it's a ghost
o o go done no it's it's it's it's uh in
my capture card in my sound capture card
is trying to control it and take
over oh no O It's haunting me It's
haunting
me oh I restarted the game
capture but now the screen is empty
oh my God what is going what was
that no I feel like I heard a ghost but
that was was that my
throat oh now I'm
getting no now I'm getting
paranoid you're hearing voices too oh no
[Music]
ooo I'm turning into a cat I'm already a
cat
oo oo
[Music]
ah
no why is it doing that guys remember
that probably happened did it happen
before during
Zelda I'm not sure but if it happened
before then I told you guys the solution
probably
do you remember do you guys hear
something I save you B hang in
there n my cats are ghostbusters don't
worry they'll take care of it just like
they did not take care of
Casper
uh game why is it not working it just
worked a second ago it was just
[Music]
cracking wait that I'm going to I know
you guys don't hear it anymore because I
want you guys to hear it for desktop
audio not for that other
[Music]
thing come on let me play this game now
I restart it
again game capture [\h__\h]
Elgato what did I do what did I do
[Laughter]
what did I
do what did I
do second voice shut
up everything was working fine a second
ago [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h] I was
system
system it won't
work hello or is it just it's just so
quiet that I can't hear it
no no sound yeah mhm a [\h__\h] helmate
bloody helmate I know you hear it now
but I don't I still don't hear it I
still don't hear
it have that no I'm tapped in but even
it doesn't make a
difference I even don't I don't even see
the screen anymore like my elato is
black now I saw it
before elato sound capture what the [\h__\h]
is this
[Music]
[\h__\h]
ah now what about now
[Music]
what about now what not why why can I
still not hear
[Music]
it what about now what about what about
now what about now oh that was that was
Windows see I heard
Windows like I hear
Windows uh you didn't hear did you you
hear
windows that was just
Windows what
if
um you hard Windows okay well that was
not a ghost don't worry guys oh [\h__\h]
hell can we like restart the whole
stream from zero from
scratch
scratch like a cat scr scr scratch
M I can't
think elato no I am in the Elgato sound
capture board thingy
but is not doing
[\h__\h] task
manager help me help me Desk Manager
elato closeth
iato
close I feel like I've did that like
I've done that a few times during Zelda
as
well thank you for the red super chat I
thought that might have been advised but
I guess it's just a nice Super Chat
thank
you damn
it is there any more
elato no okay
open
elato you hear it I know you hear it but
I don't hear
it now I hear it thank you task manager
oh s now you hear it double probably
guys
right all
right okay okay sorry for the win ah was
it the the PS5 controller again maybe
because we had that before oh well
whatever it Go
all
St become cat M
cat wonder what kind of game it is oh
it's pretty loud
actually my game besides being a game
being a I wonder what game it is besides
being a game no besides being a
cat I'm playing on PS5 by the
way cats
oh
cute free
cats one black cat and the rest is kind
of orange and
white I see a purple pink cat oh
[Music]
wa it's it's kind of dark is it too dark
guys should I change it full screen
should I full
screen okay I can do
that and we can get rid of this and the
chant will go we might change this later
but
um wa too bright too
bright I guess maybe
is
it is it I don't
know let's
see do we want to change
anything
Graphics motion
blur controls master volume G there's
not so many
settings cats can see darker yeah but
you guys are chickens so I'm trying to
make you
R was there no nothing for like
subtitles maybe maybe there's no need
for subtitles cuz all they says meow
meow meow can I talk to the cats like
NPCs it's playing with a
tail such a cat
move yes yes more yes slur SL
CH when chunkers tries that on smoovie
smoy nickel punches cat punches chunkers
cuz smoy doesn't like to be licked by
her sister and smovie also does not like
chunkers either like clean a so
cute by the way both of my cats are in
the room too but they're not really
watching I I felt it like in my
controller oh my God lag
no more what do you mean lag the
stream mean what when you say lag do you
mean low FPS
[Music]
or
huh but it's uh H that's weird
lower to
1080 doing that Midstream is kind of
risky looks low FPS even at 60 FPS turn
off motion it but it's a PS5 like
huh they turn it off completely what
does that that exactly
do oh more than gaed
together curled up together so cute is
it better now I can't wake them up
though so cute
though it's
smoother it's better much
better still dropping frames but that I
feel like that wouldn't be the fault of
the game
because it's a game capture from a
console so if it was a PC game I would
understand yeah okay then let me you
know one second we might have
to go down a
bit from 4K to
2K
ah okay I changed one thing I don't know
if that changes it Midstream though let
me see that's was the bit rate let me
change okay the
the I turn off any outputs to change
yeah okay I have to stop the stream once
if I want to change
the uh is
rain yeah no it's not the PS5 guys to
the one second we'll be back in a second
hello am I back
yet oh am I
back hello I made it small I mean on
YouTube it probably didn't change
because um it didn't take my 4K
originally anyway but now I'm I'm on 2K
now so
maybe maybe that's better you know I'm
just experimenting a little
bit see what's
possible possible like the cat's paw get
it get it move around
okay it's Smo on my
side how's it now looking
better yes I'm a cat I'm a kitty cat and
I'm meow meow meow and I'm meow meow
I was watching you play the your truck
simulator a little
bit driving in the dark scary much
better okay let's go we need to talk to
this cat
too oh my god did you guys hear the
purse and I feel it even oh my God okay
do we just jump down
n do we maybe parkour
can't I can't jump
down maybe it's that way for the
door can a cat open this kind of door I
kind of doubt it
no can I jump do I have some sick
skills I can
[Music]
me a couple of them oh I was I was
supposed to bring them all together oh
cute I'm one of them I'm one of
them
cute sleep all day cat life
wonderful cat
life
hello hello
Cat I make myself a bit smaller
maybe
butterfly wow
twitting
twitting what the [\h__\h] was that who just
woke me up Who Dares touches my ear you
shall
suffer that's uh Jonathan he's very very
very sentimental and chial and edgy and
he thinks about life all day that's why
he's sitting there and they're like oh
not this [\h__\h]
again Jonathan just stop thinking don't
think so much you're a [\h__\h] cat like
dude there's no need to worry so much
about life you know you have nine of
them just go go do whatever the hell you
[Music]
want inside the wall
uhhuh it's like neata this
place it's a Side Story of
neata he eight now no no no he didn't
look lose one just now they don't lose
them so
easily drinking chalky milk right now
chalky
milk yeah he should go his own
way oh are you playing Mario cat now
Mario
Kart race let's go
v
answer I'm cat oh you have a funny
pattern on your
tail and you eat your head too I like
the pattern on your head you look like
wait it looks like a like a a red panda
from the back but like it looks like the
the front of a maybe a front but like
its back looks like a red panda you know
what I mean
right how do I get up is there a jump
button how do you do that bro teach me
oh you're so sweet you wait for me ah X
yeah I'm not strong enough yet I need to
go this
way are you scratching the Tre oh my God
wait let me look at you oh it's so cute
can I scratch a tree too I need to
scratch get my get my nails my nail game
going L2
L yeah yeah L is that the right button
faster or oh yeah oh the tree the tree
I'm going to destroy the tree look at
that is the game going to let me like
poop
too can I like Mark my
scent somewhere also I'm going to look
up here maybe there's a
secret a who's going to go here first
why are you following me I guess we're a
gang game of the
year wow yeah very
pretty
venue very nice like a lost place I
wonder what was it a factory or so can I
just okay I cannot just like jump off
there and die okay that's
good H and for like
every like jumping up and down I have to
press
X oh do you want to talk again oh my God
my trash Pand of friend
oh sweet oh my
[Music]
God totally bro it's so true I know what
you mean it's such a struggle being a
cat it's just so exhausting like oh man
but honestly L like these are straight
cats so it's definitely more of a tough
life than
for pet cats house
cats right I I I kind of have to give
them some respect because yo this is
like their hood and they they go find
food and [\h__\h] and they have to survive
and not get sick you know can I go on
the
rail
dangerous ooh what a b
arena hold X to chain
jumps a hold X oh over
there can I jump from here
no okay wait wait for me guys no not
here doesn't give me the prompt I just
have to okay there we go
[Music]
nice I'm better at this than playing
Mario look look at my
jumps yeah bario was just
too it was just not on my level you know
Super
Mario I wonder if we're going to be
doing a lot of Parkour I really don't
know much about the game I just saw some
Aesthetics but I don't really oh I like
how it shows me like two options like
you can go here you can go there this is
a failure bad at jumping but that's not
really catlike so so pretty
magical
wow
wow oh it just had its tail up high not
anymore it was happy but now it's
[Music]
not that's googly
eyes that face look
at look at those eyes yes okay it's
telling me to go okay all right I'll go
was oh they're following me so sweet am
I the
leader am I oh Ducks automatically
a oh cute that's that's like you know
how cats walk when they're also really
terrified and scared of
something they duck like this it's
cute oh more parkour holy [\h__\h] hold L2
to
observe wow oh that's how the gang does
it wait observing observing
o yeah no I already knew that I'm the
leader after
all thank God I can't fall
down wow
and they actually left quite the
exciting life no it's one of them are
they going to fall
down no no
musal no oh I SC I'm scared you can do
it how about no
no no this like
Titanic no give me your [\h__\h] paw
[\h__\h] come on no why that's so
sad no
I'm alone no oh my God baby that must
have hurt so much I can't play this game
this [\h__\h] sad I'm out of here I want
cats to be happy oh I'm out of here I
don't want to see this any of this
no no sounds so
sad oh
[Music]
oh my God look at its posture it's like
something's broken looks like it broke
its neck and it's
leg
No
[Music]
[Applause]
Cry this makes me really
sad there's so much compassion and
empathy for cats okay no
no no I'm going to
cry no
baby no no no
no
no no
[Music]
have tears in my
eyes it's eating trash no somebody to
give it some good
food what the [\h__\h] wait it's not a
cat I thought it was me
AKA heroine
cat baby
baby
baby I need a
doctor call 911
somebody am I feeling a bit better oh it
looks a bit
better it
doesn't it moves perfect hi chunky wony
chunky wonky is feeling for the cat to
CH chuny gave one of her lives for this
cat
thank you for your sacrifice
junkers oh baby oh okay wa which is the
right way I think the trash bag's over
there that's the right way can I can I
Dash but I mean we just recovered maybe
we
shouldn't that's it's my real cat
sorry I think it's uh I think she's mad
cuz I'm cheating on
her am I supposed to eat this stuff too
oh it's not even
open okay guess we're going through
here missed jump what do you mean missed
jump did I miss something it's closed
what the
[\h__\h] Dam
City it is so scary I want this cat to
go to a happy
place [\h__\h] those things what are what
are
those that was my real cat excuse me
I'll meow
[Music]
back doesn't say
demic
protocol so realistic holy [\h__\h] oh
jum I'm the king of the
world so is that what oh it and
endemic where are we
going maybe uh on top of this and then
over there whoa nice jump
hello I am a beautiful cat I need to be
filmed yes yes I'm a streamer now I'm a
cat tuber look at me look at me
camera take a cute angle of me
please I mean every angle of me is cute
even even the cat's butthole so I mean
[Music]
I heard something weird oh
oh I need to you know look around a bit
more not go completely straight maybe
but it's like is there something here
something secret no I can't go
okay where are the other
cat I thought it was a human BL is a
robot oh we're that far in the future
huh okay so my guess was cyber cat was
not that far off the humans died the cat
survived well that's that's actually oh
no wait human personal only which
implies there was still
humans but I mean now there's definitely
no
more sorry not my fault
not my fault at all it's never my
fault
help
hop I mean originally was supposed to
say something else a chapel chapel Loop
Chapel
Loop but now now it only says
help very meaningful ew that looks
poisonous be careful kitty cat
careful be
careful hyper
letal oh we're going that
way
huh what and now went in the circle am
we not supposed to go over there to the
help ah wait this this
box that's the one and then
this and then this there we
go okay
is that a cafe here or follow me okay
okay okay but can I look
around oh wait I dashed yo I recovered
so fast
[Music]
what oh [\h__\h] follow me where where where
where where where
to why it react when I meow
[Applause]
it it's trying to answer
me over
there no it just goes down okay all
it was that a real cat no that was that
was my real cat oh
hello
what what I can't that that that was
still my real cat there's a hole in the
wall
huh what's up drunks oh right here
n
window oh
[\h__\h] um maybe not
necessary up we go up we go
o what's up you want to be a cat to
you're already a cat did you know
chunkers you want to play the game when
you already playing the game in real
life you don't need to play the game Jun
G wait actually she might be lagging
some some Kibbles I don't think they had
that many left give me a moment
junkers wait I don't want
to I don't want to no I'm not going for
dare I need to save some lives yo I mean
my own lives that's what I mean I can't
go up there
what can I go for the door
no I can't go I didn't but I Came From
Below I guess I went the wrong
way well where was I supposed to
go oh maybe I can turn it off
or what was
that I'm have a
bucket now I can I can go in the street
and beg and maybe some people will give
me some KES yeah oh wait water can I
collect
water no I don't think
so can I
[Music]
I have to place it like
properly
nah the bucket is B
yeah I think that would be too yeah I
think I have to drop it in on in the fan
and that will stop it I feel like uh it
would be too finicky
if I had to collect the water and like
what for what
for yeah okay
okay
paint oh [\h__\h] Paint Bucket
bye-bye yeah let's make some
art some sophisticated or
beautiful cat art
B more yeah yeah good job good job good
job that's beautiful M I'm not even
looking at what I'm doing but that's
just true art true passion I'm just
feeling it I'm not seeing it I just need
to feel it that's all I need to do all
of it yes go down go
down how do I get over there there it
go it it spoke to me the cat spoke to
me oh it's answering me again that thing
down there was answering me again I'm
not hallucinating or
anything chunky wonky
bye-bye chunky wonky has left the chat
one more that's the last one I
think oh oh and it opens the
ah I'm here yo nice room but shouldn't
my paws be all blue now let me see no
they're not H would have been a nice
detail can I scratch
the yes
yes scratch
the rug yeah beautiful M that feels good
that feels
good I wonder if I'm not going to be
like fighting anybody cuz I feel like
strengthening my my nails my
claws would should make me stronger
then then it would like the game would
would want you to do it more often you
know yeah it's like a cat Simulator
game what oh my God that's fun oh my God
oh we used to have that uh I think like
even in the kitchen or in the in the uh
hallway of our old old family apartment
that's so fun I mean as a human I used
to hate it but as a cat I love
it as a human it just kind of bangs into
your face all the time and it's like
annoying the cat doesn't give a [\h__\h]
love it love it blue paw prints no I
don't like blue paw prints
do I no I don't see any wait do you see
any from like a previous
cat that's so fun that's so
satisfying and I'm you know I mean I'm a
phoenix
push
push it's not breaking what the [\h__\h]
break
it is it out of plastic or what
that was very
aggressive
okay whoa like
elevator
[Music]
cute [\h__\h] cute
mate I see them I think I see them
feasting over there what you bleeding
I'm comeing hungry too what the [\h__\h] are
those okay those are aliens has this
world been like taken over by aliens oh
my God what the
[\h__\h] the [\h__\h] are
[Music]
you I'm I'm a cat what are you give me
pets
please what did I turn it off come back
to left come on
[Laughter]
hello the last robot has died also I
know one of those went this
[Music]
way I kill it no I wanted to help well I
don't know what the [\h__\h] that
was can't help something that I don't
know that F [\h__\h] it's fatter than
chunkers let's check it out let's fight
fight fight fight
fight so many oh no they're all waking
up e yeah I would be scared
[Applause]
to run run
run hold r two to run okay I'm running
am I running is that part to wait what
am I what what button okay circle circle
run yeah let's go you can't get me I'm
out of here see you later suers
byee I'm a car I'm a car I can go on the
cat
Highway this is the cat Highway ooh o oh
I like the Aesthetics the lights and Ne
lights should I have gone up there get
out of me I'm not the cat bus from gibl
gibly no I'm
not no no no you don't even have a
[\h__\h] ticket oh my God there's too
many what the
[\h__\h] run run run run run run up up up up
I'm just going wherever feels right
right
now no
no no no oh wait sorry the the music is
super loud right I'm sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry
I turned it down a little bit on OBS let
me turn it down
here it's fine
really
[Laughter]
okay safe oh this place looks nice
pretty intact
ramen wait wait follow me yeah wait let
me check out the place ooh Foton are we
in Japan
that's kind of creepy
though the apartment doesn't look like
Japan although wait yeah no the ceiling
is way too high can't be
Japan couldn't be although maybe it's
like in h it could be inspired by it
maybe like a a mix
wait I mean the the writings are made up
right that's not no real
like existing
language I would say
so where we
going m
oh nice ambient music I maybe this
way oh [\h__\h]
oh I too shall become cat
yay cat life is best life I'm going to
go this
way a but that just leads me to the same
place must be a down down down it's not
always up
ooh oh my got
chunkers H are you requesting Kibbles is
that is that what you're
doing
meow she's so loud holy [\h__\h] yeah okay
okay okay okay sorry let me give her
some
kbl I think that's what she needs
[Music]
for
game sounds uh
realistic well that was my real
cat my cats are jealous maybe but I gave
her some kbl so hopefully she's happy
now thank you
yeah thank you for the Super
Chat I hope I get to the super chats
soon I think worst case I'm going to do
a super chat
reading uh oh
ball
ball h on the day after
tomorrow
perhaps and also I don't know if you saw
on
Twitter
sorry uh but I'll be I came from there
right
or did
I I'm not sure anymore maybe I didn't no
I didn't H I'll be uploading that
director's cut of my birthday
concert no that's where I came
from wait follow of sign oh yeah yeah
okay okay
okay uh of my of my birthday concert
I'll be uploading it on either Saturday
or
Sunday it will have some improvements
uh and missing things and
changes just for my own
satisfaction yeah yeah
yeah oh oh that's a nice workout why are
you going so slow you need to go faster
oh it's really heavy you need to go spin
it uh faster like a
hamster yeah I do have very high
standards
so
wa that's high teack they made lights at
react to kitty cats
voice it's the world is about to be
ruled by
cats are it I think it's telling me to
go up
but don't I need to bring it
to somewhere specific wait that looks so
Japanese that literally looks
like
j po
looks a very
Japanese it's a
puzzle no way sometimes it looks Korean
sometimes it looks Japanese it's like a
mix I guess we'll do ah wait that's
where I jump up yeah okay it had to be
like super close probably and then up
here okay okay okay have a
camera maybe they're filming a document
documentary of me
I like the the Paw tap tap tap sounds
cute thinkink like a cat okay I'll do my
best should I go there wait is there a
sign somewhere that I'm an obvious sign
that I'm
missing I
hear I hear some and that's just the
light okay it left or right I'm going to
go down if I can
that feels that feels correct there's a
camera here
too
Zoom oh
[\h__\h] was that supposed to happen were
there like two choices and I I chose the
wrong path
or y b that was
dramatic dramatic
magic go here go
here go
next
what oh I want to go over there I hear
like a
heartbeat uh maybe I'm not supposed to
go there maybe I'm supposed to jump
oh have to keep your eyes open
at all times guys it's a cat cat Venture
yeah actually my cats have been like
incredibly clingy for a while and it
gets they get clingier and
clingier every day they they like are
not only clinging to me but also to like
visitors I don't know what's going on
probably I feel like first of all when I
came back from America they were
really nice really
clingy and like happy that I was back
but
then like recently they
[Music]
became even cling here yo they keep on
revving themselves up against strangers
legs or friends legs strangers to
them and uh now last night and the night
before they've been like sleeping they
always sleep with me in the bed but
they've been sleeping like even closer
than usual like normally like smoothie
would sleep around my legs but now she's
sleeping around my head like in the
middle of the night I woke up and she
was like above my head literally
touching my head while we were
sleeping and I'm like oh my God this is
so cute what's going
on why why why why I guess it's the age
maybe I don't know or because I have
been so busy so I have been out a lot
but I know I give them plenty of
attention I give them so many cuddles
and so much attention like for real like
way more than other people give their
cats and pets I would
say all right we going up or we're not
going this
way feels like it should be there though
it feels like it should be here
H what is it not down
there is it not
up oh meow
first now the lights turned
on I came from there no it didn't no
it oh wait maybe I did
what okay it's confusing a little bit
oh boxes boxes let's
go and actually speaking of boxes for
chunkers you know she's always sleeping
sleeping in a cardboard box like like
that like the white
one and she like I put it on next to my
pillow on my
bed do I need to put something between
the fan again first I need to get there
oh wait sh the m
that that's
sus oh it's a button
mhm yeah so anyway since like the the
box that I gave her was kind of falling
apart I don't need it anymore do I I
looks looks special though I'll take it
hoing how do
I um I guess I can just go like
this cats can jump so high oh no oh
place the flat
oh to
it it's like super futuristic with
robots and aliens and all that but the
PCS are super old what the [\h__\h] and the
what's that cow
[Laughter]
poster Quantum
tunneling that's English a boring book
it says a boring book that's actually
the the first time I see
English oh I hear
[Music]
music oh I could have gone from the left
side but here we
go I turned up the music I'm like nope
no music allow nope not
here it's nice just chill
I like it actually it's a very honest
title yeah it
is I was saying though that I got my um
cat a new cardboard box that was about
the same size but even like a little
tiny tiny tiny minimal bit bigger
because I felt like looking at her that
she was like barely fitting into uh the
box and it was falling apart so I got
her a new fancy box still a cardboard
box but like very very stable and she
stopped using the box like she tried it
out once and now she just sleeps outside
of the box which makes me think like she
didn't like it she liked the
the yeah let's go
communication um yeah she liked the
older box that was falling apart yeah
I'll send you some some information body
required enter the door turn on find a
body I don't know what you're saying I'm
a
cat speak to me in cat language
oh look at that the golden
[Music]
can the box was closing yeah now I
already threw it away I can't get it
back maybe I just need to like like
destroy it on my own that looks like the
mes where I went with rea
that looks like the moldes the the the
sand is so white I mean it could be
other places too I guess but for me it
looks like the
mes nice
Beach cast simulator
literally oh radio station
[Music]
the camera nods at me is it my friend or
my
enemy there was a oh a little
T I took it
out oh I see what we're doing we're
going to put those in
there yeah we need all of them okay so
we go for the room to try to find all of
them oh I saw
that take it hey fast already
to instincts cat instincts
guys oh NY
NY cam oh this one ah there we go I
thought you weren't nodding at me I
thought that was kind of sus ew spider
webs maybe up here oh I see
it made in France
oh wait that's
a
frog I thought it said guen which is um
German a problem no sorry sorry sorry
frog sorry [\h__\h] oops I let
go okay one more one more one more there
must be
like up here I must be able to like go
further up no
I did it
again ah I see I can go up from there
there's another one up there let me let
me let me let me pull it
again I thought you know cuz we already
moved it and it gave us something
already here the that thing itself I
thought that in that area judging by
usual game logic there should be no more
left over
but there was
something big jump
or it C me out right now cuz I've got
something in my mouth oh wait it was
this one there you go talk to
me wo Secret
Door what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what is that thing
there's a dead robot and a container
thing like a is that where you put dead
robots in
done what is this right now I'm feeling
cold what the [\h__\h] turn that turn that
thing off
now actually cold
now thank God I'm not hot
anymore where are we doing over there
spooky drone
companion is that going to read my
backpack
no I saw the scene where the Cat puts on
the
backpack it doesn't like it doesn't like
it at all what's in
here
oh well where did I put this
thing on its head
head no
no what is this thing I have on here M
go is there something else
underneath that that's all there was in
here I think I feel like I should put it
on this robot's head but it doesn't give
me the
option I want to open the capsule I mean
do I really want to open the capsule
it's kind of scary oh wait maybe what
what about
this
no I'll find maybe
outside maybe in like
here oh
STS all rows are all showing in One
Direction what about this you like these
o what is
[Music]
this it floats it can fly it tries to
fly let's play with it play it's a toy
it's a
toy B12
oh it's kind of cute I like the
design
friend do you have a
soul you're cute but do I have feelings
pke he
ping is so catlike
they really got those movements
down mhm I'll get you
interesting ah oh uh
H sorry sh sorry that's that's
loud okay turn it
down couldn't believe the camera is a c
in the dead
city um I can't remember my name it
seems my memory is
corrupted I've been TR in the electronic
Network for so long you know I work for
a scientist who liveed here for now you
can call me B12 that's what it says on
my
Experia dangerous in the dead City but
you seem like you know how to handle
yourself let's get out of here follow me
[Music]
what what I have a friend is it going to
where is it oh wait
again the key the key unlocks the door I
remember that huh let me get that for
you
huh yeah are you getting it
though you said you'll get it but
I don't see you getting
it oh I have to take it in the end
myself
anyway battery low already come over
here keep going have to change
this Lu just L just Manion old man oh my
God I see what you're talking about and
I I I kind of agree
[Music]
yeah I don't want to put it
on no no you can't make
me yeah
Dad no I'm just going to lie here until
I'm dead [\h__\h]
it I'm I'm good at just lying here like
I'm dead I'm cat after all I'm just
going to just going to sleep sleep for
forever I love sleeping meow
[Music]
meow comfy um actually not so bad it
kind of feels like I'm being
hugged but I want it to be on my
own what's the word on my own I wanted
to be my to get hugged what the
[\h__\h] I love
that I love that so much I saw that on
Twitter they posted the the the account
of this game on Twitter they posted
this yeah I feel it I feel you
consensual hugging only
yeah this backpack was designed for
small qu rers like you
is this uncomfortable for
you don't worry you get used to it I
digitize the key and store it in the
back oh open inventory open an
inventory oh and memories switch
category oh oh n it's like a vacation
thingy salmon
[Music]
okay got it okay what exactly we doing
if you're ever curious about an object
you can show it to me or two others if
we come across any two others like you
you
mean n what was that oh yeah I can
scratch somewhere let me just just get
myself ready for some fights outside
let's go now after that chase I really
feel like we might have to really fight
some people
actually some some
aliens
perhaps torch I have a torch light
oh it it's not a scary game is it is it
going to be
[Music]
scary but there's a Code 37
48 I still don't quite like
[Music]
it I still don't quite like the feeling
of this backpack but I got to get used
to it I guess I guess it can could be
helpful I can play the
piano nice okay well let's remember 3748
that might be NE ah
I got you I thought you were going to
ask me much
later oops [\h__\h] damn it you know cat
paws it's hard to put the code
[Music]
in I got it oh cute
oo o oh
wow look at this place that elevator in
the distance that's important I think I
know we need to go
up
up I guess it's always up
okay but what about this bucket elevator
I guess we're going kind of down first
Zoom fun oh look
at what the [\h__\h] are didn't realize it
was that
bad
it like an alien
infestation poor
cat you
know it makes me really sad to feel
think about the fact that you know maybe
in how many years could it be 5,000
2,000 years already humans may not be
around anymore but I'm sure some animals
will survive longer than humans and then
they'll be alone do you think dogs and
cats are going to make going to be
around longer
than
humans you think you they can take
it but then they'll be
alone
probably oh
man cats definitely yeah I mean they I
guess they'll just go back to being wild
cats but I want them to get proper pets
you know who will be there to pet them
on their belly give them belly scratches
belly rubs huh and scratch their ears
and and poke their noses boops boops
their noses
and all that kind of
stuff petting robots oh I hope they live
in a world with petting robots
yeah good reason for us to survive yeah
I'm on
survive I'm on survive
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait I remember the
outside it feel what I've been here
before is this where you came from
someone that would go there promise
to the almost painted from it let's take
it let's go why do I have these memories
how did they get here let's keep
going
H the robot thing has memories I thought
it was my memories but I guess we're
collecting the robot
is that robot my my my previous owner I
don't know maybe maybe but kind of weird
that we collecting robots memories I
thought we were collecting cats
memories I see all right
okay next we
go yeah it's this way it's this way
down that's
a I was going to say like from far away
I was like that looks like a human sign
but something's off and then when you
look closer it does look like
robots translate safe Zone translation
not hold safe
Zone oh that doesn't look safe at all
well you mean this is the safe
Zone let's go to maybe this leads me to
the safe Zone oh oh my God we need to
set it all on
fire he like for real though if we set
all of this [\h__\h] on fire I'm sure oh
[\h__\h] that would
help I
think yeah
it there's a RIT alive
there the
slums hey yo what's up you're not going
to fight me right you're scared of me
I'm a
cat huh don't you know that like what
was that what was
that n
why but Roberts Liv normally with cats
no why is that one scared of me
wonder is it my back
what is this it's like a clo it was a
clothing shop and that was a
mannequin oh
no how could you be scared of a
cat nice music
though oh there's a bar
I hear like in the bgm like a lowkey
alarm I like it it's like
implemented that dude has a
weapon you hear that alarm it's like
part of the music it's
cool I'm not the bad guy what the [\h__\h]
what are you saying cats killed humans
and now are about to kill the robots
too why are you you want to fight okay
mate I I am I got my nails done I went
to the pedicure AKA I went to the
rug okay okay I'm just a c
meow did you see my eyes they turned
white we're going to
f
[Music]
meat it seem to have her own
language you're no
jerk we're not familiar with your
kind you're welcome in our village as
long as you don't eat
anyone I'm like you I want some tuna I
want some [\h__\h] tuna not your
disgusting metal
Parts ew would never eat that not even
good for scratching
unless you put some tuna oil on it maybe
I can I can lick it off of
you no not wor I'm a [\h__\h] cat man I'm
not one of those aliens you should know
that aren just programmed to be smart or
so scary
[Laughter]
[Music]
cat you start it you know the [\h__\h] did I
do to you guys oh are these
oh my God what a weird
world nice black K you got there
though you gave us such a PR we thought
you were a
jerk
Jes no no I'm I'm fine with
Jes no why do I keep on I want to talk
to one next to you can I not I guess
not really thought you take the elevator
i' never seen that thing work and I'll
be 374 for usual
tomorrow
374 why go up there there's nothing
[Music]
there I mean there's a story line
lure oh
meditating can I scratch out sofa
please please sorry it's just what I do
I can't hold back
I can scatch will they get mad at
me I'm sorry I just it's it's my
instinct I can't stop
myself okay that's
enough wait they
really they really did get mad I like
that thanks for the reaction
mate this fellow seems to know a lot
about the area uh should we show should
we show him the postcard yeah
sure oh you don't mean this dude you
mean the
one you mean this
one oh I guess I mean this one show
item show item there you
go oh oh oh oh a picture of the outside
ridiculous
uh this elevator isn't operational
everyone knows that it is impossible to
leave this place well except the out but
they're all gone now except M he try to
talk to him if you want but he gave up
and try to leave it's for the best he
lives high up in the building with the
orange
NE I got you okay ask 12 for
okay don't to call me any I'm
here building of the orange he's the
only we got for getting out of
here getting out of here but like where
are we
going Rob boys hard to
understand you know it's the immersion
it's for imers you have to read the text
along
okay what you doing nice fashion you got
there what is that
Balenciaga you do look a little like a
zerk from far away
ah uhhuh but I'm a cute cat Now give me
some R belly
rubs they look and sound cute but don't
they don't they don't look cute but
don't be fool those things true for
metal oh wow
okay well don't worry about it I'm one
of the good
peeps hell yeah and I don't want to go I
don't want to no I want to explore I I
I'm wondering if this is the path to
to not explore I want to look inside
here
ooh a
jukebox but it looks like a modern but
still old jukebox like a different kind
of what I would usually see
oh
fun
meat you want something yo one of those
cakes I want the
cakes I don't really have anything in
particular to show you but maybe in the
future we come back here and show them
some stuff wait oh no they have the same
picture do they sell that at Ikea or so
because people always get the same [\h__\h]
the same paintings and all that from aea
right
but not paintings but like photos of
like the city Al your fridge door is
open close that
[\h__\h] oh oh chill music you knew around
here what can I do for you nothing
nothing right now I guess I'll come back
here
[Music]
later I smell balls let's go
oh I I'm sure I get an achievement if I
get them all in
right wait a
second get in there no not that
[Music]
[Laughter]
way yeah that way okay okay got it got
it yeah go go in there nice oh my God
I'm better at this game as a cat then I
am as a human wait there's nothing left
and I got no
achievement where's my achievement
you know what I want to scratch your
couch for not giving me an achievement
cuz that's [\h__\h]
rude
hi this is the newsp paper from the
people living above on level two it's a
few years old but it's something to
read I'll show you
this good luck it's not going to happen
anytime soon H so negative positive
thinking friend it's important o sheet
of music five oh it's a
collectible five out of
eight
hold some of the balls are down
here oh I I put too many in there
huh
okay W I like the music but I guess we
got to go we got to move on that's like
a punching
bag not quite
okay need to orientate
myself he said uh I think up
there what is
that what are those
Stars okay I mean that's definitely
we're even not on
Earth
or this is some kind of barrier that the
aliens put
up it's a circle guys what the [\h__\h]
something's wrong
here I don't know this feels like this
is like our headquarters for later like
we'll we'll get back here I feel
like all right where do we go what was
that I feel like I saw something yeah I
saw
this I can scratch on the door let me in
let me in
NY are you one of the troublemakers
playing with a paint
fers
no no no no no no you got the wrong guy
no no
no I'm a sophisticated cat I don't do
stuff like that no no no no I'm a good
kitty I'm a good kitty little oh you're
chilling on the roof what's
up swano
the circles of light oh yes I'm
wondering about those tell me about them
are pleasing to watch but I want to see
the real Sky one
day yeah another hotel so tell me more
about that
please are this dude is that the dude uh
I which one I
wonder we need to talk to what qu
hey hey
H me please don't bother vapora she's so
clumsy I wanted to push them down God
damn
it wait is that Vapor VAP
vapur wait should I help
you
ah wait am I going to meow right when
she froze it and then she let it fall
down
it didn't
work is it like it like the Untitled
Duck game you know
no am I too
late no I feel like I got the timing
down pretty well oh maybe I need
to when they're supposed to catch it
then I meow
H untal cat
game the prompt lights
ah it did light up okay it looks like
milk is that milk is that
milk wait so that was really not me that
the the person that they asked about cuz
like it dropped down there it seems like
that happens more often
meat
oops oops you did it again don't worry
was I I'll take the blame this time I'll
take the fall I'm I'm a hero
cat okay now ah are we supposed to take
that bucket or is that where we came
from no
no we're supposed to take that
bucket I think
so in cat language taking the bucket
means
taking the
elevator
oops I think we have to take it big
[Music]
to
D it must have really been the Kibbles
huh cuz my cats are gone now am I not
just going
back you're so well versed in cat
language of course I am I've been living
with cats my whole life man oh
nice I don't know where the hell we're
going oh what is what's happening here
remember oh
[Music]
memories it looks like this poor guy
also wanted to go to the upper level yes
I remember m is up there away from all
the garbage and sickness of the Suns
even in dire human could not help but
divide themselves by
soci then a lot of people from the slums
were prepared to do anything to move up
there apparently her also copied this
Behavior we got to keep an eye out for
those memories those are humans no no no
no no those are robots humans already
dead but as I just said um robots like
try to like copy their behavior do the
same kind of stuff
so I don't think this was like the main
route but it was a route to a memory I'm
not sure if I need to get all of them I
feel like it's more like of a
collectible kind of thing
probably oh where am I going now I'm
lost H I've seen that smiling before
though okay let's go down I guess
again where are we going didn't we
already GL go to the orange sign now and
wasn't that who I was supposed to talk
to
anyway
basketall
[Music]
yay let me talk to these people there's
a there's a cowboy yo what's up oh you
selling some stuff let's go music sheet
they have money though I'm The Merchant
of the market give me something I'll
give you something tochange just as
simple as
that what and our specific things energy
drink
can is something close
by energy drink no that's pretty that
sounds pretty cheap but I didn't see one
that I could pick up like that before
you're sorting for the trash look at all
the hidden gems in this trash Pennies
from Heaven or from somewhere
anyway
oh it's very important there must be a
lot
trash but think that like re-evaluate
what's valuable or not because humans
are gone and and robots need different
kind of things I suspect they don't even
need food and yet yet they have a pizza
box over
there H we're fortunate to have these
items to to help us defend against the
jerks the slums has its threats and
preparation is key ah the slums has its
threats and preparation is
key something dangerous dangerous oh my
God
[\h__\h] those alien
thingies
Pizza some pizza left
no any energy drink
cans God damn
it I want the music sheet it's a
collectible secret
path we're going now a
[\h__\h] I jumped down I think I was able to
jump up higher
though I could also jump up
here no go I'll go
here ah it doesn't really it doesn't
really bring me anywhere I thought I
could go higher with that all right all
right orange
sign okay
okay orange sign do I have to go like
pretty much far around it or I wonder if
there's like a best way of
going how about
here oh this dude is new
too can I sit on your lap that would be
so cute a the weird stuff always happens
to you
mate I don't dare to leave our village
it's too dangerous besides the gardian
is the only one who can open it's crazy
right they can eat everything does it
mean they can eat cats too they tried
already they
did a
stream oh we back okay sorry what the
[\h__\h] I don't know what that was I didn't
notice it besides you know seeing the
chat
you guys know which way I should
go oh hi
dude I made a trip oh sh Elite
programing knock on the door and wait
for us to open what Elite
programming Elliot if I was Elite
programming stream keeps dying every 30
minutes
really it really that was the first time
I know
show knock knock how do I knock I can
only
scratch stable in Europe okay they
opened hi can I become a hacker
too meet meet I can't meet
him no
open do I am I not ready yet to become a
hacker
[Music]
I know what I mean oh I can just go
in I can just make my way in here make
myself comfy maybe there's some
something special in here eventually
we'll
just we'll just eventually reach where
we want to go by just exploring
everything and now I can meet
him here for Elliot he's just over there
uhuh
translate we were programmed to be
slaves but since days we have a soul oh
they do have a soul hope one day The
Outsiders will find the exit of this
hell
M so wait uh I guess humans made you
slaves yeah oh there we go I found
another sheet of music let's
go o that's like a nice nice bed oh I
can move those things yeah let's go
love it
nice oh I hear nice
music I found a memory a toilet
plant I guess the toilet is not needed
anymore so it's used as a pot for plants
the tree is a scientific Marvel it's
remarkable that human iny found a way to
create plants that thrive about sunlight
oh I need those plants
YouTube hiccup stream
lag is it like so
frequent if it's affecting signals but
may maybe it really is I don't
know
weird Susan's in the
mood which
[Music]
no it just did it twice but other is
okay okay organic life requires trees to
purify the city's air rits are needed
but they take care of them anyway sweet
I mean it's aesthetic
so stream is fine in Europe oh like
overall didn't have any
hiccups is it
orinal seems to be Regional cuz for
other people didn't have a
hiccup it's what the humans would have
wanted oh wait are they like trying to
like are they not how to say if they're
trying to do like continue what humans
did does that mean that they separated
separated I mean I guess humans just
died but did they do it in like a good
way like they're not mad at them or
anything there was not like a big fight
between humans and and robots maybe but
just like it just happened and now
they're trying to live live on and then
do what they would have wanted to do do
I
wonder yes can I help you I don't know
probably not right now maybe I need to
go back here in the story later am I
just can I scratch ah I can
turn it's like a shortcut all right I'm
out of
here where am I where is the orange sign
no I
there oh let's see if we can get
closer can you go up there yeah of
course you can oh wait I was here
before yeah yeah yeah yeah I was so
close but then I kind of I thought you
know that was it
ah I talked to this dude before right
swano oh what's that place over
there
what nice BG if I fits I
sits yeah John
hi maybe I find a Rob Rob but yeah she
would still be alive
probably okay wait I lost track of the
sign
again it's over there isn't it how do I
get there there was
a what it why am I so [\h__\h]
stupid I want to go up
there let me look ah ah I see a path no
no
cat I want to
[Music]
go over there and then
here
yeah jump one more one more you can do
it come on
what yes yes yes yes ooh ooh ooh ooh
don't hurt anyone with
that no no no
well I sent the bucket there in case I
need to come here again
hi
W if I have a nice rainbow
[Music]
face can I help you
sir that's a big screen oh he has a
family oh cute wait let me see he also
has one of those Ikea pictures I guess
yeah they all shop there he made a light
out of the traffic on that's fun I like
that that's fun it's got a lot of
plants cool music is playing I like the
soundtrack of this game
already new
socks hold on hold on why everybody
leaves their fridges
open you need to save energy guys he
also has the moldes picture everybody
wants to go to the moldes I guess they
probably watched our streams about it oh
yeah looks
amazing time for me to go again
too oh you got the fun thing the fun
curtain
yeah what's that oh remember oh back
home too is that a actual game probably
from the same publisher or developer
y oh back home too I remember this video
game I don't remember
it it was made just after or is it like
a game that only exists in the lore of
the game ah it is their first game
okay uhhuh it was made just after I was
created I think I can't remember it well
the scientist and I spent a lot of time
playing it it was fun I miss him oh why
I canot remember his
name
why
ooh already got quite a few memories do
you guys know if I need all of them or
is it like a collectible
thing let's never going to work why did
I let them go I'm all alone now hey what
do you want I'll show you I guess my
postcard it's a picture of outside oh do
you want to go there yeah
I don't bother it's a waste of time it
will bring you only loneliness and
despair my friends had this dream too
but now they gone and I'm all alone it's
a collectible not a h okay I don't know
where they ended up I tried to Cate them
but that [\h__\h] [\h__\h] turn doesn't work
my friends and I took notes of for
research about the outside here take
mine if you really want to go out there
the
outside it's a book M's notebook I like
the design
I'm done with the outside good
luck I wonder if the the whole outside
is covered in all of that [\h__\h] that we
saw between the
streets woman seems very sad he misses
his friend let me check the notebook he
gave us the outside is Manifesto we must
go outside at any cost we must protect
our brothers and sisters we must stay
away from
jerks we must go outside it says we must
go
outside sign by Clementine's B our duck
and Mama it looks like mama's name was
added later I think we should find the
other notebooks oh
okay okay I'm good at um looking around
leave it to me
oh oh
fun oh what's
this it's a cat toy what the
[\h__\h] is a sid squ is it going to be
mad now he didn't
[Music]
notice cuity killed the cat don't know
wait I think my controls are
inverted I'm so bad at this yeah good
that I lost it I don't want that I'm so
bad at that kind of
stuff I'll through here excuse me
oh see the music I'm really good at
looking around in this game finding
stuff we could get all of
them yeah nice touch I agree do some
scratch scratch sratch scratch oh yeah
oh that feels good M we name we're my
nails have been so [\h__\h] like um like
you know when like on the side of your
nail like my nails in general always
like [\h__\h] I feel it but you know when
on the side of your nails you have like
these little I don't know pokey pokey
things and it hurts and then I try to
cut them off but like it's not it still
hurts hang nails I've never heard of
that before is that what you call
it I hate it
I hate
it oh I can scratch this one too I
thought I could open
it there a called H
[Music]
Nails
translate
Outsiders okay how do I go outside by
the way how did I get out for this
window okay byebye I guess I'm done
here oh what that Earth Earth is the
third planet from the Sun and the fifth
largest in solar system by m and
diameter they're talking about it as if
they're not on it to dat is the only
celestial object known okay no we're
still on it okay okay according to the
radiometric dating the Earth is 4 54
billion years old it has a single nature
satellite the moon which formed soon
after gravitational gravitational inter
with
the who me at me that was in game oh
sorry
whatever okay so where are we going next
the symbol in the wall me the one on the
notebook which
symbol ah we're going there next
okay this seems like a lead okay
speaking of my nail oh see the bucket is
back another thing remember when I told
you guys like a few streams ago that I
burned myself in the on the
oven when I put the frozen pizza in
in now normally like when I burn my
stuff I normally never get like
a like like it doesn't get too bad you
know like it doesn't like have anything
following after that but this time holy
[\h__\h] oh is that a music
sheet
yeah let's go at this time I want to go
for that door
first did you properly cool it I I
didn't cool it that much I guess a
little bit but not too much yeah but I I
I yeah I got a blister and like a bubble
with like liquid inside it's it has
actually today and yesterday it kind of
like actually mostly today it emptied
itself so now it's now it's flat but
it's like a really dark dark triangle on
my
hand and yeah that was this bubble it
didn't hurt uh but I I was I wasn't sure
if like I'm supposed
to like just let it go naturally or pop
it myself but in the end I just waited
and it emptied itself pretty
fast but it was weird I don't normally
get that like
yeah medical natural that's kind of what
I did yeah but I was like using my hands
so much the past two days that it kind
of emptied Itself by accident popped by
accident but it didn't hurt and now it's
fine
[Music]
that's fine W what is
this oh these are the NPCs a lot of them
we know them nice
music nice
place I love the whole atmosphere
generally the the music helps a lot with
the atmosphere
too and I like these uh
these blankets on the ceiling
hello Moy
Moy I'm a
cat I pop blists but you shouldn't yeah
no I wouldn't do that that sounds like
ew
ew wouldn't pop it on purpose on my own
noise keyboard ARA approves oh there and
no one's here am I really okay to take
the
notebook and outside a notebook it's the
same logo as the one Momo gave us this
one seems to belong to someone named
Clementine is she gone is she dead
everything is going according to plan we
managed to contact the upper level
before the transceiver went down they
are in a place called Midtown and
apparently is controlled by some kind of
oppressive Force I told him M earlier
his eyes I know this look he will not
come with
us then she went and she died or she
never came back
back Clementine Clementine Clementine
are you okay let's find the other
notebooks
okay they all she also has a mes picture
and the cow picture is that a cult a cow
[Music]
cult wait I have so many already holy
[\h__\h] I hope I didn't miss any so
far in the places I went to
and I need to push some things over
really quick for my own satisfaction
okay where are we going next you're not
going to tell
me I it's not going to tell me
[Music]
really I already went to the orange side
what do you mean
I already went there
right ask B12 for help how do you how do
you ask for help
again temple building blue son press
down
Ah that's turn ups only two well uhhuh
we have to look in the abandoned Flats
of the area you should be able to see
them all from the rooftops look for an
outside a logo
wait what does the outside logo look
like that the blue one for example over
there I don't
know
that is that is that really the same
thing I
know the oh the the that face the old
face I don't see that there either
though
where do you see those faces guys I
don't see any
faces smaller blue sign
up ah that one ah
okay okay okay
okay I got to get a high get some
altitude uh I was there before I feel
like I was kind of close oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] how do I get
there it's over
there yeah I was here before
if I was a cat I would constantly be
distracted by everything and never reach
my goal which is basically what I'm
doing so I guess I am a
cat maybe I should go down once and then
find a different way to get up I should
be able to get there though there maybe
from that roof to that
roof so new
Yak
n 5 hours
ago it's is
back first images reveal returning
characters
n first images of Yakuza appeared online
[Music]
will be reportedly beset in a new town
and we also learned that asak himself
would be appearing as a character in the
game kasuga has also had somewhat of a
makeover simly now appearing with his
hair tied back instead of a iconic Wild
Hair
D it's not like a
trailer wait when how was it
revealed was there a YouTube trailer
oh am I not supposed to see
it pictures at F like is that like an
accidental accidental thing HOH oh there
was an interview okay okay is there a
release
date was tweeted okay okay thank God cuz
I don't think I'm supposed to like talk
about things are like leaked inofficial
okay seems fine then uh
[\h__\h] it God damn
it no
done catapult is it because I jumped so
often wait was I in there
before doesn't look like I've been there
before I want to go
I think out seem to live in the Upp we
won't find yeah yeah yeah yeah but I'm
curious about that
place you're telling me we won't find oh
wait I've been here
before ah it's the bar place I
think yeah okay okay okay but
like sorry I'm having some trouble
getting to the blue [\h__\h] sign where
is
it let me get up
here not
that's just where I came from I want to
go
there I
know where the [\h__\h] are the
Kibbles there we go oh is that those
threee pink
dots is that also the
local uh
oh there we go getting
closer okay okay okay uh
uh what there bucket are we going
no ah it takes me down does it take me
up
too can I can I go back
up [\h__\h]
no I thought it would take me
there okay then I'll go without the
bucket how did I go there
first don't use the bucket apparently
buckets are not always my friends where
am I now no up here again why do I keep
on coming up
here where's a blue Sun just going away
from
it
[Music]
ow somewhere
over the
rooftops this cat will
go and
save all of the
robots in just one
go who are
you an
elder oh hey it's you you don't look
weird and small but there's something
about you I feel B the pet what I want
because I don't understand why no please
pet
[Music]
me P please I'm in desperate need of
pettings
please
please where's the blue
Sun ah there ah there's a bucket but
don't take the bucket this time we're
not taking the bucket come here you
dying
again
oh I love when cats do that when they
like curl their tail like
that controller is vibrating with the
purse P me hi chunky wony
hi
a a if I lay
here if I just lay
here would you lie with me and just
forget the
world forget what we're
told the we grow too
old I forgot the rest of the lyrics
that's
okay nice ah the logo's right there wake
up wake
up I wonder how far it would zoom out
like endlessly or does it stop somewhere
oh yes yes good stretch good stretch
good
baby you want to go there
money I have no money
though what it doesn't need
money oh it's energy drink can that I
can use to buy something
maybe oh music Let Go let's
go what is this turn on the
TV n YY
look is that is the robot in the back
looking at
me I don't think anything's happening
here oh the music
okay
hello oh my God
this I don't like this place you know
why can you read my
mind you know what I'm thinking of
yes little
nightmares yeah little
nightmares this place in little
Nightmares of the library holy [\h__\h] it
triggered me so
hard remember how I struggled in there
hiding from the big
[\h__\h] whatever that was the
monster is he de there's spider webs on
him
books collapsed on
him I hated it yeah how to develop your
artificial intelligence in order to be
as creative as a real human volume
42 is this like one of those people in
the
book okay maybe we can wake him up oh
sheet of
music I feel like we almost got all of
them maybe one more or so that's at
least I feel like like I would got so
many platforming of
books I can I go though no no can't
can't really go that high can I read
some
books oh no there's an arm there and the
M picture wait is it does it have any
meaning or did I just not didn't have
the the budget to buy more stock photos
[Music]
oh it almost looks like a lava lamp it's
like a budget lava
lamp oh translate there's keys I found
the keys to your safe you need to be
more careful of these can I take them oh
yeah it's not enough to bury your safe
behind a bunch of books just the
librarian so in
there what the [\h__\h] we'll probably find
um
um the next book in the safe wherever
the safe
is there's nothing else in
here oh there's a music thingy up there
is a safe in here there's a open fridge
of course but it's filled with
books it's those kind of books that you
need to keep chill because they're too
hot and I think there's only one type of
book that can get too
hot erotic novels I've never read one
before no no no
no that must be it I cannot get up there
like anywhere no really I want to like
throw all the books
down spicy books M
spicy where's the
safe is the safe in here
[Music]
even am I missing
something I like that
book it's like it really stands out and
it has like a catpaw on it it's
golden do I just
[Music]
leave I don't see a safe I think there's
nothing here
[Music]
oh
m
[Music]
we back really
really
really really
[Music]
m
ah I don't believe
it I say A you say
B I don't think that I don't believe it
it's a
bamboozle it's a
bamboozle oh you said be oh my God
what did really
do you see me or do you only hear
me
mus
hello you see me
too oh look I did that several times for
a second but now it's probably back
maybe really I was about to give up and
just say
[Music]
say looks
like oh my God I wonder if the 10
minutes of me just chilling and making
some noises every once in a while be the
B oh oh hry back let me tweet that
way're back cuz some people might have
also given up too we
back really really I don't want to jinx
it I don't want to jinx
it okay Twitter let it be
known Let It Be know
hello hello I never give up for you
thank you never give
up oh okay okay before it this appears
let's continue playing so does anyone
know where the safe is also this number
11 October 11th does anyone know where
to save us I want to make some progress
now yo I've been waiting for you guys
for so long I'm bored I'm
bored I need I need to find the stupid
safe it's probably not here I think cuz
I looked at every
corner where could it be is it
outside let's cat some more read the
note for safe location
what behind some book
really it is in the
library behind some
books behind some books I would assume
that like there would be like a popup
that tells me oh there's something here
like a button to pop up like I can move
something or at least jump up to
something something that looks
suspicious you have to keep dropping oh
okay I mean I've already dropped quite a
few let me see what else can I jump
oh you see that that there's a there's a
sign there that I can get on
something but that's just the back
yeah is that is not just uh this stuff
again maybe from here I can jump on
there no oh wait oh oh I can
go I can go there
oh okay this is not what to save us but
that's hella cute so I'm blessed #
blessed
oh yeah oh just take a cute nap why
couldn't I have done that during the 10
minutes okay that was not it good
morning Wy Wy come
on can I jump up there no I want to jump
up there what
[Music]
about
no can't push this over
[Music]
why am I so blind I was so good at
finding stuff in this game so far and
now I'm just [\h__\h]
blind is it really that hard to see I
what about this this path I this
path I never went for that path that's
the only path I didn't go
for it's went in circles a million times
okay what is this another notebook can I
take the rest too this one seems to
belong to someone called do after weeks
of research I've combined the
spectrometer with a powerful UV L with
this we should be capable of warding up
zerks on our way out the initial attemp
was explosive I might have to test it on
the real conditions let's find the other
notebooks yeah there's some moniki
nickel every every now and then we can
find them it's nice nice little
detail the moniki Nickles the golden
cats in case you don't know what my Niki
nickel are okay okay now we can
exit uh what's
here okay okay where do we go
next go
next where are these noises down
there where did I not go
uh other bilding which one the another
blue sign the I guess the what so
brightly blue behind
there
okay I probably could have jumped there
from where I just came from
maybe
maybe oh
oh like I want to go
there is that the right
way but wait I
can't this way
jump and
then
H H you know we need an upgrade AKA we
need
Wings become the the ultimate cat
bird okay I think I think we'll go down
here go down here H I don't want to go
completely down I
[Music]
just wait you weren't here
before I do love knitting it's a crab my
grandma so far I've dided 478 miles of
scars it's something to do if bring me
some electric cable I can make you a
poncho you're inspiring me but it's not
easy to find the r materials electric
cable wait we do have something to trade
so far where was the
shop we have the the
can it's not the right way this feels
spooky I feel like that's the way to get
back to the
monsters which we don't
want where about here oh there's a
memory oh Ponto that's
me I used to really like ponchos when I
was younger and I wanted to wear them
but I feel like [\h__\h] is that message but
I feel like it's really hard to pull off
a
poncho and combine it with other clothes
rip humans love humans are the first
residents around here it seems that
they're all dead now what do you think
it feels like being dead
but the music changing is makes it so
creepy I know it's silly coming from me
eh but are they actually at
peace will I be at peace when I die I
don't know what death feels like for an
AI that rhymed like a poem I'm sorry I
didn't want to break the mood let's move
on yeah it it's it's okay uh yeah the
vibe kind of changed but yeah
existential crisis oh wait we can get
something here another energy drink can
or something
else oh we got another one which means
we can buy like two of those things
whatever that
was if we find the shop
again oh oh the music is so mellow right
now wait I want to go up there I want to
go up there
when you get too close it won't let
you but even if I go up here it won't
let me go anywhere okay okay okay
okay
suor where's the shop I'm a business cat
I need to spend some money make some
Investments what does this say B men
super Spirit laundry Grandma clothing
alien prog programming
a he's he's cleaning up the mess that I
kind of made what what what it's
complaining I cleaned on por of my shop
again stop playing over my shop you
clumsy Rascal see I like that the you
know before the grandma wasn't here and
now this dude is cleaning stuff like I
like that there's like some stuff
changing while we Pro progress in the
story
oh well at least kma is making use of
all the detergent and now he's reacting
to
it to her doing
that
nice yeah it feels like I can make a
change wow oh man life changing
Cat hello so I got some stuff I want
electric cable but I guess um wait what
do you want from the electric cable
super Spirit
detergent I can probably get it from the
hacker cuz he's using it right
now and then I can use that to get to
the the wound lady but I guess let me
buy it's wait is that actually maybe the
last piece of sheet that I need the
music
sheet I have that I have that wa we have
is eight we have 1 2 three no three four
five
six wait is it repeating yeah six we
have six and there's eight so this is
the seventh
oo take this can I buy two
actually four out of eight okay now it's
gone I wonder if we at different items
what is this thing
inspect this an ancient Relic a
testament to the talent of our ancestors
he says ancient Relic but I'm sure it's
like something that's not very ancient
and not very reliy like some kind of
meme or some reference or something but
he just won't show me now right free
drink can I get more than one energy
drink can from
those vending machines cuz I got one now
left still
H but I want the electric
cable for the
lady the mem is kind of a relic that's a
fancy name for
it let me try
this is this the same one I used
before can I spam them wait no I think
there's a cool down or I haven't used
that one
yet wait is spooky music this I think
it's the first time wa the music is so
spooky can I sleep
here oh my god there must be an
achievement for sleeping in all of the
possible
places comfy 10 out of 10 love these
pillows if you can give me one
I'll let you pet
me I'm aan but I don't
have any songs do you
want the sheets and you can play them
for
me tomorrow
tomorrow sounds cool here what that
what's the Tomorrow song like
[Music]
normally very
Cal but on that one day there was
something
B and she said if I shook her face
tomorrow
tomorrow and then she went on to become
a
meme now she is done perfect m Queen
tomorrow
tomorrow they all say together
[Music]
tomorrow holy [\h__\h] I made a Tomorrow
song hi
Clippers let's go that actually wasn't
too bad was it I feel like my lyrics my
my my random lyrics were pretty good of
a song Thank you thank you applause
applause 10 of 10 more I have more I
have so many so many songs for you that
was the perfect song I I feel like I
don't want to hear anything else but
also at the same time I do was that was
that three out of eight or does he take
them away from me the ones I already
listened to let's try one out of eight
petite V what does that mean
V sounds cool here watch that
okay petite
VES oh oh I love
that
yoube you little [\h__\h] why do you [\h__\h]
with
[Music]
me you
[\h__\h] you very much I just want to stream
YouTube this melody is confusing I can't
Jam to that on the first lesson but that
was nice I like
it I like it I like it I'm very excited
about
that you think you can find of
course oh he'll give me something if
once
I wait he is taking them away indeed
right cuz I can't see one of eight
anymore more I can see one of the four
of the notebooks he does inde need take
them away okay okay okay that's good
that clears out my
inventory can we make it play Fever
Knight that would be nice Untitled okay
how about fever Knight that's a nice
title isn't
it this tune contains exactly 44 notes
[Music]
okay sounds like [\h__\h]
what happened who made this who composed
this
[\h__\h]
sucks and the sound is crackly is that
you or is that
me that sound like [\h__\h]
dude I thought they would all be bangers
and we were lucky we started with with
tomorrow okay what about this one B
Ballad of the Lonely robot
a I think I can play this look
[Music]
okay every day I'm sitting here
alone every day my mama's
gone every day I don't know what to eat
the pizza box is
empti every day the cat passes by
and I say to her
meow she looks back at me and says me
out too but
still I'm a lonely
[Music]
dude holy [\h__\h] I'm
jamming let's go moris let's
go I'm on fire I'm on fire I'm even
trying to rhyme a little bit but it's
hard to come up with words when my first
language is not English but that was a
banger so emotional so Jazzy wasn't it I
felt that was kind of
Jazzy
yeah let's go let's go thank you put the
music I will practice well I have more
yeah I have more I got like almost all
of them dude okay I'm feeling inspired
cool
down help
oh yeah oh yeah oh wow that sounds
familiar world is on fire Europe is
burning trees burning down ashes on the
ground it's like someone played Sparks
on the radi all do we do w w all do we
do w w
must be around she stop burning down the
world oh song is
over no it's not
[Music]
over cables are melting YouTube can't
handle it at all YouTube can't handle it
at all SP first
y woo
[Music]
global warming every day let's go global
warming every day let's go forest fires
are the norm
now you done that was [\h__\h] amazing D
I love
that oh holy [\h__\h] those Tunes let's go
seven out of eight
mly
important this one was composed by a
renowned algorithm with
voo
oh
[Music]
oh audio
Stu audio Stu
audio
stock audio stock
[Laughter]
yeah that that that did sound to me like
something I would find on audio stock
you
know ah I think oh we only have one more
oh no the way you compute tonight sung
by something like a computer
[Music]
oh the way you comp tonight makes me
crazy and makes me blind the way you
compute tonight is so bright I love
you way you compute tonight makes me
crazy makes me blind the way you compute
tonight I love you yeah
[Music]
let's play computer games I like the
computer games I'm a gamer girl after
all don't you believe me hey I love the
computer games oh that's
it oh I love the I love the rhythm of
that that's fun oh my God thank you for
entertaining this cat I wish I could tip
you I wish I could tip you you're my
favorite dude dude yo we should like
make a band or something amazing what's
a paper paper back again oh no oh no
impro yeah Jam CH Jam CH where did I go
where did I
go I can't see I can't [\h__\h] see oh
there we go okay [\h__\h] oh my God it's so
confusing welcome back baby where are we
going uh I'm going to try to continue in
story while also finding hopefully um
more vending machines and
[Music]
stuff ow I love that that was fun J
session I'm missing one sheet yeah I
think so
too that's so sad we got so many so
early on though so we got like kind of a
concert there isn't that
nice
oh I don't know where I'm going I'm just
trying to get up higher
again cuz that's the
key the last one's stuck in my head now
I don't know if about you guys
[Music]
but where the [\h__\h] do I go I can't go
anywhere I'm so bad at being a cat right
now I guess that's not
[Music]
it
[\h__\h] cool I talked with them before yeah
[Music]
oh cat I'm K cat and a me me me and a me
me me ooh oh
okay uh are we going that way I guess we
are let's see let's see if I can get
there that's that feels like the right
way if I yeah I think last time I had
the problem I couldn't quite go from the
right side or the left side no where are
you going
cat
unless maybe I
can
no no I would prefer to stay up higher I
think I dance dance dance and I
definitely can dance dance dance and I
dance dance dance C okay [\h__\h] that make
me stuck here wait can I go up
here come on I know you can do it
oh come on that jump is nothing to
[Music]
you okay I guess we'll try we'll try
this way or do I have to go right no
that's why I had trouble so I don't
think that's
it don't want to go too far down and I
can't go
there if I go there and then
there and then I'm stuck here again it
must be a different way jump from the
table which table there's a table there
but you probably mean a different
one
w at that
table a smart
wait uh
no doesn't give me a prompt
There Was You in the upright what that's
the wrong sign anyway oh you guys where
am going where am going we found for one
we're good uhhuh we have to look in the
abandon Flats I know look for an outside
logo oh wait was that one over there
already there before we checked that one
out right that one that's not
new
it that's a library right
that's just a library on my
right no wait ah what about that one
behind the behind the fence or is that
the
library I was there a vending machine
just now cuz someone in the chat just
said vending
machine it's important I feel like
there's a limited amount of vending
machines very
limited and only with that
n oh [\h__\h] I'm like turning into a
collector in this game are you guys
still doing the same stuff now they're
just looking down worried about what
they did this game looks interesting
so I only use running machine here okay
but have I been in there how do
I looks closed off by fences from the
side and up so I think have to go from
the
top okay I think I have to go up to that
dude
again
there perhaps this way
perhaps I want a banjo that sounded like
I guess it was a guitar but it sound of
kind of
banoy you know what I'm me
[Music]
sound like a banjo to
me I was listening a little bit to Kobo
stream too and in the end she just
casually pulled out her guitar and
started singing Mantra hu Jan jamming to
it it was so nice
oh do I have to take that out in order
to get in oh hell
yeah without even trying no no I don't
want to put it back in I just want to
drop it drop a like
[Music]
guar what does it say ventilation power
supply okay
hold yeah cool boy is really talented
and I was just listening to the Super
Chat reading and I I was like is that
really Indonesian does she speak like it
sounded like Chinese to me like Mandarin
does she speak Mandarin cuz in between I
felt like I heard non Indonesian words
but you guys probably didn't listen to
was fascinating though water I can drink
some water here she does speak a little
bit of oh because it sounded pretty good
to me I mean I I don't know really but I
want to look at me drinking I can't see
it properly can I zoom
out can't no no drinking animation for
us
today okay I think we're in the right
place
[Music]
squish squ
s wow that looks like a shortcut now
washing
machine there must be a book
[Music]
somewhere cute oh God damn it what's up
with these
boxes sorry
where's the tuna where are they hiding
the tuna there something on the roof
maybe I do have to go for that window I
thought it was just you know to come
back here
easier but
[Music]
maybe do I have to push over some boxes
what was
that where there it is I I guess it
wasn't one of the boxes I I just knocked
over finally a last notebook this one
seems to belong to someone named zal
old traes of organic life has
disappeared except for what we call the
jerks they seem to eat almost anything
that moves and breed at an inconceivable
rate as if being locked in the city
wasn't hard enough oh there's also a
note in this book oh it says I found the
assign flaw in the transceiver but I
think I figured out how to fix it
transceiver here's the equation with
this we should be able to help M repair
the transceiver transceiver
if it can't communicate with the upper
levels that could be our way
up let's show him what we found uh is
this the transceiver what I have with me
this thing without knowing
it yo there's a memory down
there but can I get back up cuz I also
want to check back up
there let me get the
memory memory memory
Thanks for the Memories even they so
great there we go ooh wonder what it is
randor think think think
think remarkable companions have evolved
so
much in the early days there simply AI
merely imitated Human
Art imitated now this is all their own
oh humans often say that making art is
important in Desperate
situations H what kind of situation
situation would that be there are
certainly desperate times and these are
certainly desperate times oh I wonder if
it's recent
[Music]
then
art
wow that song is kind of heavy what
which song What Was I singing
was that
[Music]
singing a kitty cat kitty cat oh thanks
for okay next up what about the
top have I been there before
is there a special way of getting up
there wait no that's where yeah that's
that's where I went to to open it but I
guess maybe I missed something up
here because somebody said they saw
something
interesting what's interesting
here what's so
interesting tap tap tap tap tap
tap can I get
there what so interesting I see nothing
[Music]
interesting oh okay ah you mean oh okay
okay because of the button prompt okay
then I think I'm done here where are we
going
next we all got we got all of the
notebooks let me
ask found on the note how to fix the
transceiver let's bring it back to Momo
up in the building with the or neon okay
orange neon that one right over there
Momo what did Momo look like
[Music]
again
Momo oh nice jump that's not Momo right
that's
Meo I need to go inside I guess how do I
enter this place
again parkour that's always a
solution hello what's up I got some
interesting stuff
guys I'm literally the hero in this
storyline also do you have any more
music sheets I want to jam one last time
with my buddy
found the ball that's good
too
hi hey little cat are you still looking
for those useless notebooks they're not
useless I got all of them but I'll show
you the note probably wait I can't I
can't show the note
only just that's my
note uhhuh should I show you the
others you find Clementine's notes she
was really Brave you know the most
Fearless person I've ever met
I'm just giving them all to him
now
B notbook right I never quite understood
what he was talking about most of the
time but he was very
wise okay yeah he's taking
them wait you actually found all my
friends hell yeah I did yeah I'm amazing
I
know what's that note the transceiver
can be repaired this is a
incredible that means we should be able
to communicate outside of
the you mean a phone are we talking
about a phone Clementine about a do I'm
sorry I dabbled our C I promise you I
will find a way to reach your
surface I want to I want to see you too
maybe there's more cats there wait yeah
my cat friend should be there wait
that's what they mean with the surface I
remember now I I've already forgot what
the outside world looked like I mean
that place also looked like like the the
aftermath of an apocalypse but there
were no
monsters so I guess the goal is to go
back to my cat
friends and show them that I'm not dead
you know you know I hit my head when I
fell down there so I forgot
understandable right the near looking
place okay okay that definitely even
though there's no humans to pet me that
definitely looks like a better place
although this place is really
interesting too but without the moment
moners it would be better if we could
just kill the monsters then we could
live in peace and harmony with the
robots and they could pet me and give me
ear Squatch and clean my [\h__\h] litter
box
yeah I feel like that would be like more
interesting even than just going back
you
know at least that's my opinion well I
don't know where the game wants me to
go the place is
sunlight maybe we can like bring the
sunlight here too am I am I not the
sunlight you know people say I'm the
sunshine you know
so let's fix this piece of junk
transceiver
okay how did I help you can I help you
wait do we go to the hacker man maybe he
can help us Oh no you're doing it okay
nice I like the cut
scenes hea it works oh are you French
come with me okay
momo
yeah cool dude I you're opening it up
for me thanks dude is that A New Path up
there see that building high above the
others not when I'm down here I'm really
small you know if you install the
transceiver at the very top of the tower
you mean the orange the orange glowing
one we should be able to communicate
with the whole city my friends might
still be out there if there's a way out
they'll know
it exciting oh my God I have a I have a
mission guys you're the only one small
and quick enough to evate the Zer we
need you little Outsider bring us to the
city to the sky okay hi hi hi to
die space taxi to the sky that's a meme
song from a German movie guys the one I
showed you guys before but I I think
it's really hard to watch it if you're
English speaking cuz there's no English
version sadly am I just going to take
this looks like the best
[Music]
solution no trumpet is
allowed that's not a world I want to
live in I'm going to return to the near
Overworld after all
rooftops
okay we need to go out there I guess
tallest building it is it does seem like
the tallest build oh no wait that what
about that place up there do I have to
put it up
there or
here detergent Quest yeah wait am I like
soft locking myself if I do this stuff
now can I not do the detergent Quest the
side quest follow the lights
lights okay I'll try
[Music]
me I don't want to why would I want to
attract
enemies
no I sof look already I can come back to
them later
really the movie looks horrible no it's
great B
[Music]
A it uh uh so much for that y y oh I
need to I could walk like can i
[Music]
y ah they can't go ah
it
it do I have like HP can I go down if
I okay yes I can go I can probably go
okay [\h__\h] what happens
[Laughter]
oh man good that was for science okay oh
was for science I'm a scientist cat
now robot I'm holy [\h__\h] he got eaten up
while he was while he was climbing to
escape okay I know what to do now I
think
I think I didn't no okay come over
[Music]
here I was too fast can I go here please
say I can yes yes yes okay okay okay I
can't climb right that's a real Merit
Merit de Merit for them not being able
to climb kind of sucks I got nothing on
this kitty cat
[Music]
turn on my and say what you
do I see
nothing I'm singing Pussycat Dolls
because I'm a
cat
oh what
[Music]
the why are they able to oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
ah no no no I saw it I saw it I saw the
prompt oh God give me give Meen to
recover hold on on I saw it I saw it
where was it where was it oh
[\h__\h] okay
run okay I think I'm safe wait they
followed me up there a little bit when I
jumped on that one [\h__\h] I thought they
couldn't do that was just two or so
though maybe it was an
exception maybe it was like
timing where am I
going
here oh
memory
remember the C is full of neon it wasn't
always this way they used to be strict
Energy caps especially in the slums but
people couldn't handle the constant
Darkness all a understandable yeah one
day someone lit up a rain lit up rainbow
lamps neon signs all over their house
that person was taken away and never
seen again holy [\h__\h] but people saw hope
and not to not long after everyone
started putting lots of lights in their
homes there was nothing the oppressors
could do light oppressors what the [\h__\h]
like who are they what what's their
problem is that are we talking about the
robot times or the human
times was for people to see colors again
like on the outside I think it
helped people well it sounds like it was
still during human
times before they all
died so they were stuck in the slums too
it was like they were already stuck back
then I wonder or if they or did they
have a choice you know asking so many
questions questions of questions will
they ever be answered oh
[Music]
wait am I supposed to reach that
place that
place maybe one more jump we yeah we'll
give me the
momentum no I think they could see color
it's just that everything was so dark
that there was no color really to see ah
okay I have to move this one again
probably like
before now I'm thinking with
momentum yeah baby oh that didn't help
me wait maybe the other
way maybe the other way Maybe not maybe
it's just useless hold on no wait I
think I'm rolling
it it's all infested I'm so scared I
just want
cables wait I feel like I'm
stuck I know now I see it
aha I like it
[Music]
ooh rooftop
parkour does anyone of you guys do that
like I feel like it's a really dangerous
but really cool
hobby I would I could never do it
though way too
scared I mean I not afraid of heights
but oh
[\h__\h] okay they're getting
stuck um right I need a moment to see
where I want to go probably up there
okay
um okay we're good we're
good wait wait wait wait wa wa wa wa wa
wa wa wa wa wa wa wa I need to I need to
get up somewhere I need no h door what
do you mean hack
door [\h__\h] H what what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] where do I go
where do I go let me escape
mother oh I can get them
stuck wait can I close the other
door I wanted to run like jump over
there but it wouldn't let me at least
not that fast maybe from here
[Music]
jump scare jump
scare mommy
mommy f f f [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] where the
[\h__\h] do I
go I need to Barrel about they make me
[\h__\h]
busy so I feel like in order to use a
barrel I need to get rid of them first
so I need to make them stuck in the room
but I hacked one door how do I close it
before they come no
way I l i open this door and I lured
them over in this area and then I try to
close it without them coming over again
maybe
[Music]
maybe okay okay they're over there but
there's some stuck here God damn it can
I just smash
them what the [\h__\h]
God damn it they are in the
door can I like [\h__\h]
hell that that's really not cool that
that
happened can
I help wait I'm going to die want to
hack the door
again I guess I got to open it again so
I can get everyone in
are they all in
now so I closed it
again but now they're leaving
[Music]
ah why did it not just go well the first
time did I oh [\h__\h] fing
[Applause]
out you have to give it to me though if
it wasn't for the few ones that were
struck on in the
barrel I would have done it just fine
the first
[Music]
try do a barrel roll wait where the [\h__\h]
am
I ah okay
[Music]
okay
what where are they oh there they are
there they are should I hack this one
first maybe ahead of time cuz it will
close it
already ah wait it switches it one opens
one
closes
[Music]
[Applause]
so I I open this one now and then run
away right
[Music]
okay okay okay yeah okay that makes
that's okay okay okay now
now I thought that both doors close and
I have to get them stuck
inside never mind not quite like that ew
this is so
disgusting sick jump
wow ni
C it say ni cation with a c which is
obviously obviously a reference to
Japanese word for cat
Niel look at the scenery a
bit a looks like a horror movie
huh I'm paying
attention it's just [\h__\h] stressful
sometimes okay
chill having to retry one time doesn't I
don't think it gives you the right yet
to claim that I'm not paying attention
I'm try paying attention quite much in
this game
okay also not everyone can always like
see the same things the same way we
proceive things in different ways you
know that's where I came
from I need to
go that was just me sometimes the cat
says something un
prompted Oh e I don't want to go in
there e
e it's like I'm inside someone's
body cuz it's also flesh
[Music]
colored do you guys understand why I'm
trying to sing this song because I feel
like the bjm right now sounds like the
beginning of that ever LaVine song
[Music]
like I'm
not used to love me
you
[Music]
[Laughter]
was that's I decid
I like care what's the plan
here oh I don't care I was so alone I
love that Arrow song I Love
It I got to work on an arrow concert
what like as it security or something
like that
cool e they're [\h__\h]
disgusting also fat box look how they go
crazy with the boxes maybe they maybe we
should see it as something cute they're
playing with the boxes it's I guess it
could be perceived as cute see once
again we perceive things differently
right depending on your point of view
they forgot about
me where do I want to go can I get them
stuck too it's like a kind of because of
like the how the path is made it's kind
of like a
Lain like
lowy let's
try I'm just going to
[Music]
run okay okay okay okay oh [\h__\h] someone
followed me I think oh there's more of
them a no no
no F [\h__\h] F just want to zoom through
there come
on okay I have to run around a little
bit to make them like walk more cuz I
feel like I'm a bit faster than
them and lead lead them
away
bucket a bucket I feel like we're going
to finish this game today after all cuz
I'm I don't know how far I am but I'm
feeling
I'm feeling it right now oh [\h__\h] ah why
did I run right into
[Music]
death where are they hello
meow hi yeah yeah come here can I jump
so high no come here I know I guess it's
fine yeah go
here yeah are we good
go
[\h__\h] it's okay it's okay h no not down
not down not down I didn't want to go
down I wanted to go to the next
one go
here I don't think it's short enough to
finish him are you
sure am I still not
far memory percentage says it might be
longer than I think
much maybe then maybe I not stop in half
an hour or so am I like 50% through at
least
it feels like I'm pretty deep in it but
it's probably like get the transceiver
and then
memory and then the whole there will be
a whole plot twist a lot of other
[\h__\h] okay Nel Corp they were responsible
for Waste
Management as trash from the upper
levels overloaded the slums they try to
develop the bacteria to oh is that where
these things came
from after the humans disappeared that
bacteria mutated growing eating way more
ah and now we have
jks I'm surprised they don't eat the
buildings though cuz like but if they
eat everything and they eat metal then
why don't they go for the buildings why
are their buildings still so like intact
I don't
know let's go okay are are they saying
that cats are
bad cuz I don't like that way of
thinking I no I don't like
it they it's like they're blaming the
cats okay I think I need to Larn them
over to this side and then run to the
other cuz I guess there's something
there that I can jump on this these
things
there
okay hacking to again let's see what
happens are you guys coming okay
[\h__\h] maybe I waited too long oh well ah
now I'm here and do
I do I hack it
again Barrel
Barrel a barrel that way oh god oh
they're coming oh they coming where are
you
coming why you call
me I'm hiding to think reink the
situation why are they coming back they
gone
now they're over on that side okay
not sure I
understand should I have closed
it okay okay okay it doesn't open
another door it just
Fu did they just die in there why what
made them die I was just rolling around
I'm
actually I want to know what killed them
cuz that's the
solution
maybe it would kill them
nindo okay that's not where I need to
roll
it how did you
survive there just one one baby is
left a
okay I see it now I see it now
probably hi hi hi
[\h__\h]
hi no not down up
up there you
[Music]
go blind CH Strikes Back Again
maybe that's not
a that's how I got in roll P to Gage
should I open it
again can I I guess it looks like it's
could fit through but really ah to jump
on that
thing
o
ahuh okay oh I hate her sound crackling
I'm scared of fixing it though cuz last
time I did that it [\h__\h] things
up oh
no oh no oh no
run
run okay okay okay okay
okay terrifying terrifying absolutely
terrifying I I don't want to be eaten
just a cute cat what does this do
probably drops a [\h__\h] ton of them no o
we're almost the top of the tower
though please don't say it drops the
[\h__\h] there a ton of them no but maybe
they're all at the top one no okay
n where you
go okay um am I just going to wait until
the [\h__\h] elevator drops down just
going to run in circles for
real that boy coming
what what the [\h__\h] what actual
[\h__\h] wait wait [\h__\h]
you it was like
there it's [\h__\h] arrived
already I tried to jump in I'm not sure
how you were supposed to enter the
elevator from the front the door was
closed I so from stop right cuz I was
trying to jump in jump up and then jump
in but oh man okay Panic
continues idle cat no touching okay uh
come get
me baby please don't please don't come
get
me
[\h__\h] sick
jums no what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h]
now I died earlier than before the
camera uh is a bit slow for my taste I
know it was like an auto camera setting
but now I'm used to this somewhat so I
feel like I want to change
it used a maze on the left what maze on
the
left I'm trying to use this whole jumpy
thingy is that not what you mean
um I can't push both of those at the
same
time just run far far
far okay yeah running
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
squares oh it should be there now any
second now open the [\h__\h] up I'm going to
go another one another Circle another
one I feel like I wasn't ready for
that oh God how do
I there we go go
up you're not going to enter
right they look
disgusting help
me help
me nice okay okay okay
okay oh yeah you're all welcome to jump
out now so that if I inspect this Tower
you're not
there this going to
open
huh I guess I have to enter another way
okay no mobs here I think we're
safe here it is put the transceiver on
this antenna okay thank
God
here who it's pretty big how did I carry
that
here how ooh the
lights we're turning on the
lights also transceiver thing and then
we'll have a
signal yo that area on the left that's
really high is that are those the
rooftops have been
there cuz there's quite a a difference
in
height or is that coming
up calling all cats yeah cat party let's
go oh we're taking a bucket
look The View it's beautiful from
here yeah I guess
so up a part of the city I remember now
the city it was meant to be a
shelter
oh
really those look like stars but they're
only lights marking the Hermetic roof
ceiling of the
city yeah I thought so that didn't look
like normal Sky humankind built this
shell to protect themselves from the
outside but it came in a Coss nobody can
go out
mhm the outside was a disaster
completely Barren unlivable and
dangerous well now it's [\h__\h]
dangerous here
too but if you come from there it must
be safe again
oh oh I guess the danger that made the
apocalypse is gone yeah
so I guess it's safe to go back up again
I guess
yeah and my promise wasn't just to go to
the outside it was to open the
city yeah those things can't jump very
high so if we go up then they'll just
rot down here and eat all the trash and
just what one point at one point there
won't be any more trash and they'll
die yeah and then looking maybe unless
they don't have a system like a hunger
system in their body I still understand
why some memories are coming right
others aren't but I'm certain now this
is my purpose I have to open the
city come on let's go back and find Momo
now that we've connected the transmitter
we should be able to get help oh
Momo it was in the the orange place
right wow I want to get up there can I
jump
there no
okay ah oh oh oh no the lights are
turning
off oh oh they're giving me a shortcut
am I already there be nice where am
I slums part too I know I think I'm
somewhere else what was this place again
ah that one one of the first H oh wait
M's not oh no that is M's
place outside if you're raring this that
means you're still alive excellent I
took some equipment to the bar to take
advantage of their antenna come meet me
there ah the bar I've locked the window
but the code to open it is quite simple
it
[Music]
is no no I'm not writing this down and
I'm not remembering this be care is case
sensitive see you're [\h__\h] kidding me
right no there must be like some AO
enter that no
no no no no no no no there's no way that
I need to type that in no [\h__\h] way
that the game would make such an
obnoxious
[Music]
Choice sound crackling
cat I don't know how good the memory of
a cat
is okay uh to the bar to the bar to the
bar heuse B too oh can you open the
door that it was o or wasn't
o wait did you do the Long Key m is at
the bar okay well at least the the B12
was entering a code for me so let's hope
they do it
again uh bar was like somewhere around
the bottom right or was it that place no
that's a
library o I'm actually surprised I
remember some things cuz like it's quite
a quite a um intricate environment which
is good they put a lot of work wait is
it the dude is gone
once again something happened in the
world I wonder
why where did he
go oh you don't hear it
oh that's surprising what about no now
you should hear it
[Music]
ah was that the
bar is that Momo Momo catch me m catch
me if I jump will you catch
me m that's the bar he can I jump on
your head that would have been funny hey
little F yeah what's
up come here man you going to see no
it's [\h__\h] noise what do they say yo
I'm such a hero that's funny he bumped
into him can I sit on the to I can't see
from so
[Music]
low God I'm coming all right oh my God
what a precious
game let me see if I can get this thing
working it was literally asking me to
sit up there that's so
cute they're watching o hacker
skills Hing to the gate are those eyes
I've almost got
it
w hello can anyone hear
[Music]
me guys we in area where are from the
slums we're looking for a way out and
wait is that you about oh
M can't believe it I'm so happy to hear
your voice where are you are you this
okay yes we are safe we found a way
up oh they're safe they are up they're
so hear me if they made it then we
should be able to make it you have to go
for the sewers to reach us very
dangerous berserks everywhere O Holy
oof sewers how hello darn we lost a
signal oh
no can't believe it's a basar is alive
he and the other outside has managed to
go up for the
sewers sewers are the most dangerous
place in the slums but if Zas are made
it there must be a y I'm small and fast
honey oh you going to say something the
mysterious guy the bar turns
around you'll never get past the soon as
it's infested with Zer they'll make a
quick meal out of you especially you
little one no especially you guys not me
man R to Lu in the best it doesn't end
well anyway I warned you your business
is not a m business
[Music]
see his father dog used to be a great
scientist he was working on some new
weapon to fight the STS a few years ago
he went off to test the device never
came back seem as has never been the
same
since I look so cute
don't listen to se he's just scared like
I was if DC build a weapon that's our
ticket to join The Outsiders wait and I
going to be carrying the
weapon in his notebook doc mentioned the
secret lamp a few times that must be
where he was working on it there might
be a clue in se's apartment come on
follow me
huh is it
upstairs no
man coming
thank you for leading me there cuz I it
would take me ages to get
[Music]
there the Drone probably ah yeah
probably that makes sense are he still
cleaning on yall wait can I do I have to
follow him will he stop if I we stop
walking oh yeah okay uh how do I get the
the from you by the
way I saying the same stuff maybe it's
inside maybe me pushing that down was
necessary to get him out so that I can
take what I need here oh wouldn't that
be like smart super
yes I probably wouldn't have been able
to do that if I wouldn't already have
done the ground
workor ah cat balls rubot oil
yo who are we supposed to give that to
again the shop right the shop wanted
it and for that I get the electric
cables no hey
buddy wait I I'm going to go do
that yeah I was doing it all according
to
kle
here he we're back to the side quest
no
work I have what you need buddy and I
also got two energy drinks I need one
more here you
go yeah so that's for the grandma which
I think and I think I know the way
roughly this way
straight that's where my buddy playing
music is we're at the shop where's the
clothing
shop oh wasn't here but there's a note
take save some St is
password
what
wait what did I just
find show to
B12 it's written follow the numbers but
it looks like a binary language a
succession of zeros and ones you must be
able to decifer decipher the code
decifer decipher in one way or another
it's probably related to the safe wait
we can't do it
immediately I want to look at it like
how do
I how I examine
it maybe maybe I I can't do it
now show it to the
coder do you
mean coder mean that
like hacker
H tip for the last dring oh I suppose so
I don't know if I'm going to go there
immediately
do
uh
hacker
okay maybe next time for this code but
nice that we found that but I was
looking for
the Grandma's
shop the where is
it here
maybe no no I don't want I slipped don't
want to go that
way get that
Ponch why looks so adorable in
it oh there we are are these new
ladies are you guys the cat was here
alone last time and these ones they came
from the the other
Camp Cory grandma made me made me these
clothes pretty styish no
uhhuh wait do I get something like this
you want something oh
no wait this are not the same people but
oh well okay what happens if I do this
oh oh she loves that Grandma I know
that's like the best
feeling my smoothie does that all the
time like holy [\h__\h] strangers too all
the time she does that and she makes
everyone so happy when she does that
[Music]
yeah yo I got the electric cables for
y'all take it I got to work right away
oh right meow meow
meow is it going to be orange
colored o it's kind of like pink yellow
green all kinds of
colors can I wear
it how I wear
it oh my
God how I wear
it this looks really wrong Prett for a
cold rot no I don't want to
wear can I not wear it I have to give it
to someone else is this like part of a
side quest
too I was looking forward to wearing
some
[Music]
fast I don't know where I'm going right
now
um where where's the dude where' he
go let me find the dude again we
continue to a cold I don't remember
anyone
freezing is this one cold cuz he doesn't
have a p no wait can I say
hello it looks like I can do that with
everybody who's
sitting so cute
anyone cold here oh what are you
doing Joy look at all the great stuff
that falls into a trash so many
Treasures you should go visit the bar
man there's something for everyone over
there oh you mean where already went
there yeah yeah yeah been there been
there done
that what are you guys doing Guardian is
doing some workout
meditating oh what are you doing I
thought you were peeing in the bus for a
second oh
a he's taking care of the plants how
nice of
him dude are you are you
cold no not you just want the sheets of
music okay I think it was not this way
it was
[Music]
this
way and then I think it was that way are
you
cold dude Sly I never talked to you did
I or did I I
did he gives you a hint for the there
you
are gives you a hint for the cleaning
detergent translate I'm looking for
anything of music to play the guit
yeah already you brought you almost
every single one of
them come on see open the door you know
your father would have wanted to help
us open up you doesn't want
[Music]
to that was expected this situation is
pretty tough on seus he doesn't want to
hear about Outsiders anymore he won't
help me but you I think I have an idea
H we just enter from the top how about
that but I'll wait for your idea
oh
okay I'm going in here take dog's
notebook and show it to seus
okay got
it contains a lot of information that
will hopefully act as an electr truck
oh wait can I use that info for my for
my game show I want an electroshock too
guess we're talking about kind of
electroshocks find the secret lab little
Outsider I'm going back to the bar to
try toab reestablish communication okay
sounds good to
me look at that cat butt
cute oh cute this looks so
fluffy I'm sorry to disturb
[Music]
um I'm cute just accept me why you doing
I told you get through the SE is a
suicide mission leave me be
M this for you what is this wait this my
papa wait was this my Pap oh wow I never
knew there's a secret room here now flat
but where I bet it's like really
obvious that would be
[Music]
funny okay I guess I have to look for it
is it like behind here
no
no you good mate I wanted to actually
take this one guess there's nothing
behind this
one okay I found the right one in first
try what do I know I not a cold
never noticed that di code before how
did I miss it uh there was a picture in
front of it I have no idea what the
password could
be um let me take a
look is that the
password oh damn it I knocked it over is
it like behind here
maybe it's not the
password time will
tell that doesn't really seem like a
password
a I'm destroying this
place is but it's not
the it's not the the long thingy that we
got before
right I W tell crony will
tell if I Could Turn Back Time
if I could turn back to what is this one
that also looks like something I can
translate what
clocks
clocks I
tell I don't
know l oh what what if I try
some
uh give me the
code give me the code
chat one two three
four oh wait my chat died
no it was I not using hyper
chat not that I need to refresh the
wanted to
refresher I didn't have hyper chat on
I'm so sorry after all this time of [\h__\h]
yeah let me open that chat after all
that time of hyper chat advertising
me okay turn enable hyper
chat you guys should be using hyper chat
too
okay okay I got
it
[Music]
oh H yeah that was um very obvious
everything here is pretty obvious how
did Semus never
notice dear
God but you know it's a cat point of
view you know
you can't you see what's on the height
of people's
feet ooh there's a nice emotional music
they captured some of those
monsters I've never seen his room before
I can't believe he managed to hide it
from me all this
time These Blueprints they asked before
his JK weapon Papa was always so
secretive with his
work he told me the weapon was working
in theory but it needed a real life test
he went outside to slums and he never
came back that's probably because he's
safe up there no I mean let's be
[Music]
positive are there's some plans for how
to make the weapon though this
one the flux are blue BL print
con okay do I need to remember
that
appear 20 jerk destroyed per second is
the objective that would be
nice what about
here no
can't wow the music so
moody oh wait what's
here cute sounds but never friendly of
human time eat all kinds of materials
Soul vision and dark react to intense
light in a bad way in a good
way that's a really important hint
probably because it wasn't yellow
yellow what are we looking at next
dude I already looked at that
dude we already already looked at it
what are we thinking
find anything interesting oh you want me
to find an
item I'll get you something
noise wait does my light always uh light
up when I'm like close to
someone never noticed that
before Oh what about here translate that
up the top
I'm getting a
headlamp rabbit rabits news headlin C
are officially no longer on the control
they now eat metal oh
[\h__\h] pick
up here he wants an item
what what does he
want n n n n n boxes on the
shelves I do I want him to show that
show him that thing there no I
can't oh I I won't look at that ah wait
this
one oopsie must be something nice in
there
no come
on no it was just a [\h__\h] normal box
wait but something
underneath
no I thought that was it
h hey yo what's
up thanks for the
pinky uh okay um
lost this one this one that one looks
like I can knock it
over there we
go take broken
tracker hi must see I got it
you are so useless that's why your dad
never shared that stuff of
you need a cat to help you whatever
remember that that's his
tracker Pap always used that tracker to
keep an eye on where I was well that's
kind of creepy but I guess okay maybe
you you always get lost cuz you're
stupid maybe we can R to find where he
went I can't believe my papa might still
be alive I've missed him so much you
need a weapon for the jerks right my
papa definitely took with him we just
need to repair the track so we can find
him someone in the slum should be able
to help come with me I'll open the door
for you what a gentlem all
right
H helicopter parent
yeah my bad B even though this robot is
like full size by his dialogue he still
seems kind of like
childish thanks dude oh my friend is
gone he went back to the bar I guess
we're going back to the bar too
right what is this interesting
[Music]
details
wait cute this one actually does give me
like paw step the PA colored Paws in
white did you
see that's
cute not the paper bag again no no no
PTSD
where's the
bar yeah the P tracks
K Bar Bar
here hello ah friend
M did you find anything interesting oh
yeah this thing
here you ask this is the bar you ask
this
guy Jacob
now you can't fix this right there
someone else like the dude above
probably yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh wait was that always there how
did I not say that I was up here
before that wasn't here
before did I really consume this the
original design didn't have a digestive
system what is that oil no it's like
those um PC cards that cards you put in
the
PC but they're like in
a some kind of
water maybe they somehow evolved by
mimicking humans oh do you think I
should try some of it I don't not I do
not want to be disrespectful of their
ways I mean yeah I gu just
try where for try oh a squish Squatch
squish Squatch board let's go
oh you nice that felt good refreshing oh
he's mad how did you see
that well I can't I can't wrap myself
around your leg I'm sure you would like
it if you'd only let
me
Carl no Carl
no so can you fix
this Elliot where where the hell was
Elliot
[Music]
again
Elliot
Billy never talked to Billy though let's
talk to Billy one something
oh is see the guy you would show this
safe C second floor of his
shop door I knocked
on
Ted a there's I already met so many NPCs
now I'm getting
confused this
place Elliot Elli
I've got two things for him don't I
didn't I want to give him something else
the the password
thingy show me my
son open
up he did open
hiting I think it's so cute how I just
walk in yo you can close the door now
I'm in I'm
in just letting myself
in can I can I cuddle with you
no
okay he falls asleep
immediately if you want oh wait that's
Nestor what what the [\h__\h] where's Elliot
a second floor right well nice to meet
you
Nestor nice Nest you got
here hi I'm back sorry I forgot about
you okay we'll start off with with this
thing want me to read this binary call
just a second I need to calibrate my
lenses here it means doofer bar strange
it gives a Rand the be a binary code
okay the doofa bar probably has the code
thenal okay let's remember that he needs
a puncho this guy cuz he's
shaking
oh this guy or the one
below
try when you find this it's amazing let
me try it
on is shaking
indeed I mean please come see me if you
ever need anything fixed all right at
the moment uh the weapon in the future
but that's a side the p is a side
quest weapon is a a main thing so I
guess probably not
that why is the music so scary
what the
[\h__\h]
wait the broken tracker is
also wait was the Poncho something I
needed to
do that's a great what he have not done
that if I didn't give him the pon this
model is a TOA BR 2000 you can track
anyone with this little Gadget may I
take a look just got to give it an
update and one more thing
why would you assume it's a side cuz it
felt like a side
quest okay so all that was
necessary
okay oh good then very good there you go
little one good luck finding what you
looking for oh thanks
dude thank you I'm not going to scratch
your carpet this time cuz I'm
nice just this
once is there anything else I'm like
maybe a music
note last music note last one's hard to
find isn't
it I already read that one I
guess can I scratch the car for go ahead
let's just open the door
again he will
open yo dude thans I have no fubs and
and [\h__\h] I don't know I'm fast but I'm
not particularly
strong hi hi I'm a better cat than that
monik nickel oh where are we going again
I forgot
uh back
to back to the bar I think yeah the
bar tap tap tap tap tap tap tap I fixed
it
stying to get the connection but did you
find anything
yeah guys are we do you know how far we
are like 50% or so cuz maybe I'll stop
after giving him the tracker and then
we'll continue another time and now I
can read like maybe in super chats for
an
hour
halfway basically okay good good good
good good good good okay wow it took me
three and a half hours I mean we waited
m we we we maybe actively actively
played for 3 hours we waited because of
YouTube and the beginning was
slow and the game says like five okay so
average 5 hours but I'm probably taking
6 hours that's all
right I don't know how wait
what what who am I giving it to bucket
wait this bucket wasn't here
before did something did a pipe break up
there or what
is where's it coming
from where is that even coming from
there's nothing up
here the bucket wasn't here there
right some pipe in between I love that
detail h
y I can go in here
M let me
explore what do we have
here something interesting come on give
me
something give me something
no
nothing okay
Jacob no someone said in the chat to
show him the
this only a realy doesn't take me who's
a realy I already got somebody to read
it
uh
Billy
ah hey they already went to
Elliot we already read the code and it
just told me to go to uh
doof
whatever I'll just show it to you just
in
case to Elliot huh didn't I already show
it to
Elliot now you're making me question my
memory I gu the PCH oh yeah I gave him
the
tracker but it I also showed him the
note cuz he told me oh Rand deu haha who
who does that
no just you code in the bar oh okay
that's what he meant with the bar code
in the bar there's a lot of numbers here
maybe back
here that looks like
[Music]
to City run
oh one 28 three oh
love one
free that's probably the Cod wait what
do I do with it
again do I tell
you wait no the code was that was for
that was for the safe I'm getting all
things mixed up is a safe also in the
end main quest thing not a side quest
like I thought it
was let me run around and try to find
that safe
again don't that
[Music]
[Applause]
scary
[Music]
uh where was that
again are there cyos and maybe they
aren't but I feel like at least the
music notes the music sheets are but
maybe they
aren't we will
see uh [\h__\h] I forgot
uh one something
284 1284 was it maybe 1 28 three okay
close enough one two eight
three yeah what ins that
NY take is that the last sheet what what
did that say that was too
bright it's the last
one that's perfect I think that's a
perfect way to end
it the final music
[Music]
sheet let's go let's listen everybody
sit down and listen I hope you guys have
popcorn last music sheet have this badge
as a token of my
gratitude well meic B let's gool I'm
such a musician
ah
meow let's see what is this last piece
un readable she you can't read it not
very readable but can still
try sounds nice so much for not being
[Music]
readable will he just play forever
now I don't think I was able to move
[Music]
before thank you everybody for watching
to now let's me
CH oh that's it oh okay it would have
been funny if like now until the rest of
the game he would just endlessly play it
because that was the last song no that
was nice though thank you for all that
I'm a great musician now yeah you have
like a big repertoire to choose from
that's important for a musician yeah
yeah yeah okay that's it then we have
such a great time I want to talk more I
feel like we're besties now but okay
does this game do auto
save one minute it seems to be doing
auto save but one minute one second go
[Music]
okay we'll
continue um maybe tomorrow I'm not
sure uh but in any case I have to do a
super chat reading the day after
tomorrow I think cuz like holy [\h__\h]
we're back we're far back but I'm going
to read some
now I'm so glad this came out today
originally I wanted to read chats today
cuz I felt like I I have to I shouldn't
wait for too long but yeah it came out
today so I was like okay we got to play
it
huh
tomorrow yeah we'll see
um I'm not sure about what to do
tomorrow
yet some things are kind of like up in
the air um so it will be probably pretty
spontaneous um I'm taking a fruit candy
now so now we'll switch over to the
chatting screen and I'll read some super
chats if that's all right with you thank
you for watching so far
[Music]
everybody it's 11:00 p.m. now so an hour
or so I think I want to read for an
hour okay so uh now the thing is because
I changed the
size I think the office will look really
[\h__\h] up let me go somewhere else where
it's easier to fix maybe
um maybe we can go
but yeah maybe this place doesn't need
too much
[Music]
fixing God do you guys hear the
purring so nice oh my God I love cat
purring and the controller keeps on
vibrating okay I think we're good to go
let's go to this not so messy room
probably
hopefully okay okay this this decent
decent
enough should I dress up should I change
I'll change
where is my dress
oh this
one all right ooh feeling so
fancy how about
these okay oh my God the purring oopsy
[Music]
hello I don't wear this so often
nowadays
do all right fancy fancy you make me
fail no wa that was enough
[Music]
fancy yum
yum so do you guys know where we where
we left
off what did I
where until where did I read last
time going close the game now I
think oopsie what how did I close the
game
home there you go I finished the concert
okay that's exactly where I left off
okay okay
[Music]
uh let me find BL came after
that game is fun I like this
game and it's relatively short so that's
nice too not going to be too much of a
commitment but I really like the story
so far
and being a cat obviously is the best
thing
ever the graphics are
fine so
yeah so far I'm really liking it
uh is it
this oh do I have to read um I guess I
turned it off pretty early but there
seems to be super chats in the recap and
super chats I
stream
right it feels so pure M yeah but like
it also has like the danger and the
excitement and the
[Music]
adventure ah I would probably buy it if
I didn't get it from PlayStation Plus
for free already H originally I I forgot
that it was on PS5 and then I got it on
Steam but then people were like telling
me Oh like oh there's a new game for PS5
so I was like assuming that you guys
would want me to play it on PS5 is it
like prettier on
PS5 cuz I could have just played it on
Steam as well but
I I I got a refund I think
[Music]
oh it's never pretty on Console no
vibrational yeah I wouldn't have had
that either I guess I probably would
have played with keyboard and mouse if
that was
possible but yeah I think I like it on
the PS5 right now PC game always have an
edge graphic yeah and then why did you
guys want to play have me play it on PS5
cuz like people pointed it out to me on
Twitter like oh this game for PS5 is
coming out tomorrow
so I was like okay I guess I should play
it on
PS5 cuz my computer my computer doesn't
have issues you have issues mommy
issues just
kidding yeah let's stress on the PC cuz
at least you know when I mean my PC
would have been fine but this way no
Holo cure did you not watch the second
stream of Holo cure because the second
one was totally fine there was just
something wrong in the first one but my
PC was just
[Music]
fine reading a few ons from here not so
many
though H looking for the to for the wa I
should move it to the
middle than for
the
uh almost
rainbow thank
[Music]
you wait oh is that a continuation cuz
it starts off
like is that where you got like cut off
uh in the previous stream I remember
something like
that what is a
rainbow I don't remember what it said
the last one let me pull it up
um should be at the very bottom of the
actual concert super chats there we go
okay let me start from the top
again happy birthday kiala thanks for
the concert I'm amazed how you didn't
lose your smile for a single second to
kept to being energetic and cute girl
everyone knows you're such a strong girl
at least at least on the outside I kept
my smile you're such a strong girl your
expressions are so adorable and Frey way
more than I imagined listening now
continue in in the other stream to you
singing your heart out while dancing and
smiling knowing how many hours it took
to record the whole thing makes me feel
tremendous respect for idols and
entertainers and you in particular and
for all the effort you put in the only
thing you're asking return is to have a
stage to perform in an audience that is
happy to listen it really brings a tear
to the eye wait what's this my legs are
giving up my knees I'm
kneeling I was going to divorce Gloria
last stream but then he closed the post
chat and Super Chat off guess I'm keep
oh [\h__\h] you guess I'm keeping my GF now
huh making this a rainbow because why
the heck not you've more than deserved a
good head pad for this massive
accomplishment else somebody's got wait
wait what hey just because you're so
slow you can't blame me for that just
because you didn't send your your Super
Chat early enough because I kept that
ending screen for quite a while I was
like oh they're still sing super chats
oh maybe I should leave it open so that
I don't cut off anyone and I kept it
open for quite a while
okay this is entirely your
fault yeah so you know what to
do you know exactly what to
do thanks for the rainbow though thank
you very much thanks for the kind words
and yeah all I really want is a stage
and an audience
yeah to show off like my passion you got
that right
so thank you for being part of the
audience
thank hopefully one day we can have
another concert yeah
[Music]
Cruz thank you for the pinky don't want
to add uh to the Super Chat pile but I
forgot to say happy birthday and my
rainbow T you all so here's a please
forgive pink and happy birthday R
Redemption might also want to turn Super
Chat off for this one yeah I did for
this soon
after
than and happy birthday to me right not
to
you yay thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
um guys I have a happy message you can
stop the
petition um my butt is being worked
on I repeat
[Music]
my bot is being worked on it's probably
going to take a while quite a while I
don't know jenma it's probably going to
take a while but um they're working on
it now I'm obviously not going to
somehow suddenly end up with a Kim
Kardashian butt um but a more realistic
and and not anatomically correct one
because like the way it currently is it
really stood out a lot after seeing it
uh move in frd for a whole hour and the
arm wrestling one like I wasn't sure if
it was because of like the glitching but
certain poses just looked like what the
[\h__\h] so uh they're working on it yeah
maybe uh by the
next concert or by a Fredy deut or
so I don't know how long it takes but
but maybe that's when I get to show it
off yeah
Hallelujah World have physics no come on
no no butt in the whole life has
physics yeah I don't I that would be a
first and would be kind of weird cuz
like o I even feel like you know anime
boobas are already kind of
unrealistically wobbling bubling
wobbling I don't want to say the same on
my butt it would be like bubble bubble
bubble butt
bubble it could be the first one
um I I I don't quite trust that on the
first try that we get it
right I don't know no no no we can do it
maybe an after fact like after editing
post
production we can like make that part
wobble wobble
wobble yeah anyway so
[Music]
thank you I'm glad you liked my set list
yeah what's AIM thanks for the pinky hey
I heard that employee number what is
employee number can I get
one uh sure what you want you are here
again you want an employee
number uh
okay what should it
be what should it
[Music]
be uh
6810 because that's the Super Chat am in
Yen that's being shown to
me it's a nice
number wait it's a wait that's a four
four digigit number we usually don't
give out four digigit numbers how about
681 we get rid of the zero I hope nobody
else has it should be fine
yeah thank you one hope you like the
number unknown thanks for the thinking
sorry for adding more Super Chat but the
concert was seriously so incredible that
I want to send more thank
you I we watch it more than 10 times now
and I still can't get enough of it
everything about it was amazing it
really is the best birthday content ever
you already watched it 10 times even
though I said there would be a
director's cut you should have waited un
known but you got to watch the new one
10 times too right also congrats on 1
million followers on Twitter T you
really deserve this and much much more
you're the best love you always and
forever thank you and for everyone who's
not following me on Twitter yet you're
really missing out on something I
communicate the most out of whole life
English on Twitter I would say so go
check it out make an account communicate
with me and then I might I might notice
you yeah
they're just preparing themselves to
spot the
differences yeah I'm not sure how much
differences you guys are expecting
but um there's just some major things
that I personally really wanted to have
fixed so uh there's even there might be
one or two songs that don't have any
change at all and there might be one
song that only has one tiny tiny tiny
change and then there might be some
songs that look way different um so I
guess yeah keep an eye open uh it it
won't be like crazily differently edited
like yeah I
think it won't be like a completely
different uh
experience but like
certain two songs probably two songs
will be pretty different due to
circumstances like the some some big
things being fixed but yeah will it be a
Premiere um I guess
probably yes I think I'll make a
Premiere out of it
yeah Saturday or Sunday so look forward
to it and Nathan conton thanks for the
red super chat happy birth lady birthday
T Bo kept me from watching a concert
live and I and will keep me from
watching the stream as well oh no but I
hope you know well also proud of you and
amazed at all the hard work you girls
put in here so another year K yay thank
you oh man you're you're donating in Us
doll I wonder if you're here
now na are you
there it's sad if you can't watch it
live but you're still around and that
makes me happy thank you for being
around trying your best to be
there yeah thank you
and see you again soon I hope all right
you're here
hello did you watched the concert by now
I assume it would be crazy to wait for
so long I don't know if I could wait for
so long but yeah yeah got to watch the
no one has it okay nice you got to watch
the director's cut
too thanks for being
here I'm glad you made it hope you had a
lovely day so far yeah
patience is a virtue I do not have it's
all right I
mean I feel like it's totally fine to
watch it beforehand too like I I will
say
that um it's been quite some time now so
I I definitely calmed down about a lot
of
things but they still need to be fixed
but I'm not as
um embarrassed about it anymore as I was
the first time I watched
it so yeah four blood was pretty good
yeah especially for the fact that I kind
of improvised my own choreo even though
I'm not a choreographer but gave me some
confidence to maybe come up with chos in
the future on my own I actually like
when I listen to songs what goes on in
your guys' brains when you listen to
songs because when I listen to songs in
my brain bra the whole time I'm making
up movements and imagining imagining
that I'm dancing do you guys do that
too like I imagine a
[Music]
Coro story but certainly not
dancing not not at all no no I air
drum oh you imagine like a fighting
scene and Beast yeah that's fun too I I
I like to imagine it sometimes too you
imagine
stories that's interesting when you say
you imagine stories you mean you imagine
something like an a music video like a
movie like something when they sing
about kissing someone you imagine two
people
kissing I guess
so that's interesting see I don't do
that because I focus on something
completely different I focus on Dance
mod I just can't stop myself I can't
stop myself and then like I I noticed
myself like when I sit in Uber for
example and they're playing the radio
and I listen to it like I sometimes my
eyes even move like with the the the
moves that I make up in my
brain okay that sounds kind of creepy
it's not that like they grow like wo w w
like that crazy no not at all but like I
feel like they're slightly
slightly oh and my my I will I will move
my I will close my eyes according to the
[Laughter]
Rhythm but then you see uh when I like a
few years ago or so when I would try to
come up with my own
chorio you know in my brain I have so
many cool moves but then when I try to
act it out
spontaneously my
brain
doesn't it's not able to catch up so
fast while I'm actually moving
so I need to really like take it step by
step I can't do it all at once like I
guess it's kind of like improvising a
rap to a song as well cuz like then it's
just too fast when you actually have to
do two things at once like actually
dancing and thinking about the next
move but I think I could I could do it
when I like um take some time to split a
song into parts and
then and go go like like by by 10
seconds maximum more than that nah 10
seconds fix a move and then record it
immediately immediately because I will
forget I did that with with four blood
too I was like okay I have to I have to
record something because I I can't
remember it if I don't record
it and then I like I was in my bedroom
playing the music and just like
recording something with my
phone like in a dark pretty dark room
like I think my head and my legs were
partially cut off I just needed like
some kind of like something to roughly
remember the next
day yeah but this is also the thing with
like writing things down once you write
something down in order to remember it
you never read it again because just the
act of you writing it down will help you
remember it and the same thing was with
me taking a video I never looked at the
video ever again just the act of me
taking the video made me remember
it it's all
[Music]
connected dancing in a d
with that sounds kind of
hot anyway continuing that was a tangent
thank you Nathan here's case
M fresh out of the oven Dragon Days
thanks for the Super Chat than I need
help I can't stop watching your concert
what should I do it was seriously
amazing though great job you should wait
until the new
one which will be soon yeah well then
you can you have a good reason for
watching it again and you can like
compare it with the old
one and then then I think you'll
understand a bit better what my problem
was with the original
one maybe some of you guys will be able
to relate a little bit better but I
think a lot of my my first reaction came
because of all the stress and all the
time invested and this yeah mostly the
the stress and the pressure pressure and
you know it was a big big thing so I had
a much bigger audience than usually and
I wanted it to be right because I wanted
to leave a good question for all those
people who probably also watch me even
for the first time or for the or for the
first time in a long time and don't
usually watch my streams I wanted those
people to see the best possible thing to
you know I I was like those people are
not going to give me a second chance
even if I upload a director's cut
that's and I think that's true like you
guys are going to come to watch it but
and and just for my personal
satisfaction in the end because I know
there's not going to be what 40K people
watching again I know that and that's
why I I was so I felt so pressured the
first
time and then I I teared myself up when
I was watching and I was like oh
[\h__\h] I was I was really not feeling good
on that day that's that's why I couldn't
be so excited about it as you guys were
and not I'm sorry everyone tried their
best everyone involved really um in a
short time we all worked hard on it so I
don't want to blame anyone and I don't
want to be too negative cuz I don't want
to like make them feel
bad but you know there's this one
chance don't get this chance so often in
a year it's like birthday stream
anniversary
stream
maybe maybe like a
maybe a end of the year stream or
something like that those are like the
special
occasions ah freedy debut Frey
reveal I just I just need those times to
be right
because you know last the year when we
debuted 20 20 2020 holy [\h__\h] you know
back then you know we all had like a
great growth because that's when home
life English started out and you know
things calmed down obviously and the the
sea thing calmed down too so less people
would watch life and all kinds of things
but this this is why I feel so serious
about now having to take advantage of
every chance I get um to get like
momentum and growth you know I'm I'm a
businesswoman after all and this is my
job I have to take it seriously and I do
it's my my my work and my passion it's
not only my work if it was just my work
like when I worked a normal job before H
I would just be like whatever I I'm just
do it half asked and it's fine and I go
home at the end of the day and I don't
think about it anymore because what what
the [\h__\h] I don't give any [\h__\h] but this
is more than just my work it's my dream
and it's my passion and it's my chance
in a lifetime and I don't want to waste
this chance in my lifetime by doing
things half asked
[Music]
yeah maybe you can understand the way I
feel
sometimes you know I talked about how I
felt before joining Hollow
how how I was at a low
[Music]
point so this right now feels like the
last big chance I get and I need to do
it right
need to make need to make every every
day and every opportunity every stream
something
special as much as I
can
yeah yeah
so but I'm fine now as I said like you
know sleep a night over it or sleep two
nights over it feel less stressed move
on and
now it's all right I'm looking forward
to to the director's cut but it's all
right oh I'm proud of
[Music]
myself thanks guys thank
you thank you thank you thank you for
being so real with us a whole time yeah
probably too real quite often but yeah
we're proud of you too thank
you thank you
thank
you how you feel makes 100% sense I
think so too because it's how I
feel that's a mindset to mindset to
create great things I
agree so Dragon Days here's the kisse
there you go
man thanks for the pinky happy birthday
T congrats on the Fredy live proud of
everyone involved especially knowing
what you all had to overcome to get the
show on the road very happy and amazing
with the concert and where you see scuff
I see Soul always here to support your
future projects
[Music]
Soul well yeah I mean I don't mind like
for normal streams I don't mind scess I
think it's funny too but that was you
know really important to me but anyway
I'm glad you enjoyed
it yeah thank you for watching D for the
support yeah I'm proud of everyone
involved as well we learned a lot of
things too I think learned a
lot that will help us for the future
ma d a Col D for the pinky I love your
concert but it made me think of
something that's been bugging
me why does your live singing always
sound better than your recordings for
the same original it's like the mixes
you choose are always doing weird stuff
to your
voice uh I don't really agree with that
[Music]
but one thing I could come up with as a
reason would probably be be although
that is a weird thing to send in a Super
Chat uh would probably be that you know
you get more used to singing the song
over and over and over again after the
recording and then yeah it just comes
more natural like hoton have sang a
million times you know at this point so
the way I change thing the way I sing
something will be more natural and more
uh less less tense and more stressfree
and then I might come up with my with
some with a new way of singing a certain
line or so or you know just try
harmonizing and all that no and I think
you know sounding better alive that's
also
like I think just perception
no
no m
[Music]
yeah so thank you I I know it's actually
kind of a compliment uh but
also I think it's just a matter of
opinion and taste
and how much dirt you have in your ears
just kidding clean clean your ears but
don't go too deep because uh you just
push it further inside your ear and then
you have the problem like me
a while ago where um I couldn't hear in
my ear anymore I never thought that
would happen to me ever but it happened
to me once fairly recently and my ear
was um blocked
completely and it was so [\h__\h] weird
and I tried to without making it worse
just really carefully I tried to like uh
you know shower and then have the water
go from my ear or so but it didn't help
so I actually had to go to a doctor and
um it was
crazy never had that before did you guys
ever have your ear washed out
professionally
before like oh my God like on on first
she like I had to have it done on both
ears actually but he first started out
by I think he first vacuumed and then
washed or did he first wash and then
vacuum but he did both things he would
like put a little tiny really loud
vacuum sucker cleaner into my ear it was
so loud he was like be care just so you
know it's going to be loud or so and
then I was like okay all right but then
when he turned it on it was actually
surprisingly [\h__\h] loud and the
loudness kind
of felt lowkey like pain it was
weird yeah it freaked me out I was like
I was like really
tense every day I live in fear on no
yeah that was crazy and then he washed
it and that was really [\h__\h] weird too
having the water go through your ears so
weird ew felt so weird
[Music]
what's vacuum cleaner again what the
[\h__\h]
like oh go in with an endoscope and a
metal scoop she did that too he did like
a scooping and then a vacuuming and then
a washing or I don't know if that was
the actual order
[Music]
but I felt like I had Dolby sound after
amazing for the first few minutes I
still feel felt weird cuz it was that
weird clean feeling that almost felt
wrong but it was all
[Music]
right crazy crazy crazy it was funny it
was an an
experience
yeah and now now I just um I mean even
the doctor's tell
you that using cotton buds is not really
recommended just use your finger because
you're not supposed to go any deeper
than your finger can
[Music]
go so take that to heart don't go so
deep dude yeah you can harm yourself
we're looking forward to the
collaboration Cafe in Korea and me too
that would be great it's happening this
week oh in 2 days it's
opening h okay I need to read more Super
chats let me get somewhere uh Aker thank
you for the red super chat the concert
was amazing so proud of you thank you K
I'm guessing the typle there was on
purpose
amazing thank you for being proud of me
I feel like
um man it's nice to hear that it's like
you're my parent or so but not in a
weird way it's just nice to have you
guys be proud of me cuz like you know we
joke around we have fun we play games
you call me stupid when I can't do [\h__\h]
right but at these moments you guys are
honest and you say I'm proud of you
kiaha you're amazing that's when you
become d d you leave the tun tun behind
and you become d d and sweet thank
you Ricky do down thank you for the r of
chat I love the frey concert I already
watched four times o what so four hours
thank you for the hard work Tel your
effort has given us a lot of extra
happiness I've been smiling all week
very rare for an English man really you
know I've been watching this this
British uh game show right Taskmaster
and I see them laughing so much so I
mean but I do understand like the the
hosts they try to look serious and not
laugh too much but but the the other
comedians they they love quite a lot I'm
in season eight now I think
yeah so there's still quite a few more
thank God there's so many seasons I'm so
happy but I I really like the British
comedy British humor so I'm having a
good time yeah trying to not watch too
much all at once though but
yeah it's a job to
love no it's a job to make people laugh
they don't have to laugh there's so many
comedians who like put on this whole
character of being grumpy or tired or
sad and make that into a thing to make
people laugh it's not necessarily that
they are
laughing
a you don't know [\h__\h] about comedy
you're trying to tell a comedian aka me
what comedy is and how it works like get
back into the frying machine
dude anyway thank you Ricky
DOA thank you very much Englishman
British
friend have a nice cup of tea when you
watch the uh the director's cut
[Music]
okay for
Pinky coner was absolutely amazing I'm
so proud of you you're so talented the
corio your superb movements you're
singing the stage everything was so per
perfect but girl you need to do
everything in your power to get the
trash compactor fixed yeah well as I as
I've mentioned uh I'm happily announcing
that we're getting it done so please
wait thei D Dragon birdie D miniature PR
J thank you for the R thank
you I think I saw you in the chat as
well are you still awake crazy thank you
so much for loving me so much you love
me too much staying awake all night it's
already what almost uh almost 700 a.m.
over
there thank you dear T we saw your
tanaku it's the day after tan but we
pray for oh wait tanaku tan is that what
you call the thing you hang on the T
butter
tree never
realized but we pray for you we wish
attention will always be filled with
happy while you're alive eternally oh
yeah you guys may have seen if you
watched the Tana's and ena's T butter
stream no I sent them one thingy one
strip of paper with my wish on it maybe
if for the people who didn't see it
maybe I should show it I was thinking so
hard about this like to be honest like I
it took me like 10 minutes to come up
with something not because I don't have
anything I wish for but because I have a
lot of things to wish for but they're
all too serious and I was like I can't
put this on there like
yeah I shouldn't be too serious
and yeah so I fought so long about it
man where is it where is it a here it is
this was mine in the end I wrote I want
K to live on eternally just like me and
for myself to wish I wish to get better
at living life and be loved by all
cats yeah so it was not too serious but
yeah you know I considered the fact that
it's a stream where they read out the
the yeah the wishes and it shouldn't be
too dep
depressing and there were so many like
MiMi ones some of the other members sent
some basically joke ones so I'm glad I
didn't make mine too
[Music]
serious yeah yeah no I love this it's a
piece of
bread I like it well that was that thank
you for mentioning it I didn't talk
about it on stream yet thank you good
opportunity nice smart Miniature Pin
Jang good good tangent you threw at me
there thank you so much I wonder what
your wish was for Tan you guys celebrate
Tan in
Korea I would think it's like a Japanese
thing but maybe I'm wrong
kak thank you Lily for the red super
chat thank
you not in Korea that's what I thought
yeah but I guess you guys know about it
yeah happy belated birthday kiaha it was
such a joy seeing you up on stage your
dancing was Next Level incredible and
I'm already looking forward to your next
Fred appearance here's R to add to the
mountain siiz POS thank you I'm I'm over
the mountain I'm just over walking um
for some Hills and Valleys now thank you
very much H I'm looking forward to it
too I I wish I had like aess any time
but I don't which at least I guess keeps
me from overusing it but I want more you
know it's almost been 2 years since I
joined and I feel like I need to make up
for all this time where I didn't use my
Fredy you know
you
know but I need to hold back a little
bit I mean you know it takes time too to
plan these things and organize it so and
and put it into something
watchable thank you
Lily
sky thank you for the pink Super Chat
happy birthday T the conent was amazing
hard to believe that it wasn't made by
by a professional studio
mhm but but I think um after seeing what
we
made uh and like you know what AM
has uh to work with now I think um that
they will help us next time they they
told me that uh they are open to you
know work on the footage that we sent
them because you know the original plan
was to record with that suit that we
used used for the arm wrestling and you
saw how that [\h__\h] glitches
out and uh I recorded with that suit the
N MC so even there I feel like you could
notice a difference even though I was
just standing around um but yeah that
was the original plan and then suddenly
Amma decided to get like much better
equipment to work with and it arrived so
last minute but you know the whole
decision was last minute and unexpected
so it wasn't really what I was um
expecting anyway so that's totally fine
it's actually much better than I thought
it would be so it was a pleasant
surprise but you know the original plan
was the that other suit so it was kind
of like hard to work with that's why it
ended up being kanuru who um helped us
with it but then surprise surprise we
got something way better than what was
expected so
now I think we can count
on uh our inhouse team as well to uh
help us
yeah although canu you know he has like
a very a personal style which um you
know compared to the concerts that cover
create you see quite the difference in
style like cover is professional and
clean and perfect and nice to look at
you know of course but then kodo has all
these little ity bitty details that are
fun and he has his own personal style
that's really cool to look at and I feel
like I could probably um put give more
personal input I get more creative with
someone like
kanu um but actually I can't say cuz I
haven't worked like on a concert with
with the company yet so where I could
like my own concert where I could put my
input in so we'll see about that but you
know just from looking from the outside
it's just you know a difference and I
think it's nice to have both every now
and
then sometimes like a more cover style
concert what do you guys prefer
actually what do you guys
prefer now I'm curious
[Music]
I think if I were to do like a proper
concert at a venue I would probably
wanted to have more of a serious
look but I understand why you guys
prefer kanuru style I'm sure kanuru
could like tune down everything and make
it look way more professional too
without all the you know Meme artworks
and stuff in
there like everything besides those meme
artworks looked very professional anyway
because I told him actually I told him
that I don't want too much of that stuff
in it cuz I wanted to look actually
serious and
professional but there still was you
know a little bit here and
there I was almost going to make him
delete that um hook Papa artwork of me
uh you know what I mean I think it was
during favor night when when I saw that
I was
like
No And then I was like oh I guess it
will make people laugh so I guess let's
let's keep it I
guess this one
[Music]
time yeah but I see you
guys I see a lot of you guys wanted to
see more from kanuru but you know he's
just one person and he's like producing
like every single whole live English
thing at this
point
Y like music videos and concerts like
the and the the small small myth of
video in the
space holy
[\h__\h] yeah not only not even not only ho
yeah and his own stuff too anyway um
slime thanks for the r of chat happy
birthday T here's my first ever Super
Chat to show support to my oi cuz you're
just this amazing seeing all these hard
work you put in finally paid off really
fills my heart with joy and I hope the
world is ready to withstand those off
liit off liit idle power cuz it hit hard
thank you so much slime for your free
Super Chat than soon for being so
generous and
[Music]
supportive thank you very sweet to hear
those words and yeah finally I could
show up my power at least part of my
power was
Unleashed I'm really really glad it
finally was uh able to
happen thank you so much I want to mon
monopolizes time either that's what I'm
thinking too like I don't want to put
too much work you know workload onto him
but then again I also usually just don't
know who else to ask when it comes to
Fredy stuff you
know um yeah like someone at that level
it's just like I mean maybe someone
outside of the fandom but I wouldn't
know who either and then even someone
outside of of the fandom would be
probably like I don't know Hollywood
level and then they probably charge like
Millions I don't know
I don't know
but I feel like he's he wants to do it
but then we put so much work on him that
he's also suffering from it and I feel
like he's the type of person who can't
say no who can't say who can't turn
these things down he just keeps on
taking more and more and more
work
uh it's not not uh good but uh suffering
from From Success basically
yeah and I'm guilty of it too cuz I
already have him working on the next
thing
so oh well
F yeah thank you thank you slime a kiss
for you oh that was already the second
kiss I hope you like those two kisses
two for one M special uh special special
only for the first Super
Chat Kate thank you for the
pinky thank you you for the amazing
concert thank you too you're one of the
people I mean everyone but that means
you're one of them who made it possible
so thank you so much for being part of
kfp and supporting and watching lau lau
sigus thanks for the pinky I just saw
saw that I was so excited about the
concert that I actually forgot the most
important part in my last Super Chat
happy birthday K much happiness for you
in the coming year and may everything
you plan be successful thank you so much
I want that same thing for you of course
wish you all the best as well thank you
understandable to forget that also uh
just so you know I guess this is
important for everybody in case you guys
were waiting for the meet and greet
information of the birthday merchandise
purchase and the raffle um
tomorrow tomorrow there should be some
info coming out from the
official uh whole life account I think
it should be tweeted and then I will let
you know on stream of
course uh for the people who are not on
Twitter I'm going to post it on the
community board
too look at my eyes PE for it all
righty noise yeah sorry for the waight
um some details needed to be ironed
out
iron H yeah look forward to it for the
pinky four blood cover FS love the
concert K thank you actually yeah for
blood was already I've been planning to
a mention to JMA I want to cover it like
already ages ago when it first came out
so I'm planning on it but I'm
I still need to First focus on my next
original song so yeah I'll try to be
fast which reminds me of
something
yes okay hope don't forget
that thank you
na D beon thanks for the pinky too thank
you and no 429 thanks for the pinky I
can out your birthday concert was
awesome hope there are more in the
future I hope so too and I hope you will
be there to experience them yeah we need
people to experience them all of it the
kiaha experience freaking love your
version of the song Thank you very much
it's a great song it's really
cool well k k never misses mhm
[Music]
my throat actually you know even during
the two days where I didn't do anything
my throat was hurting when I like um
tried to yawn and so on it hurted a
little bit like I felt like there was
something hurting in the very back and
it blocked me from doing a big de beond
even though I didn't talk so much yeah I
don't
know don't know why because I didn't
stream and now it's it's it's not too
bad because of the fro candy it's pretty
good but I still feel
[Music]
it but I'm all right it's not like crazy
painful for the chat happy birthday your
concert was the best the most
interesting am them was Kentucky FR
Phenix I wish you all the best in the
future than thank you how could cie make
that mistake dear Al this woman makes me
[Music]
crazy the immediate Panic though after
she said that I thought it was funny too
I was like uhhuh I hope we don't have to
beep that out n yeah I was always
worried that you know kfp would be too
close to a certain competition
competitor don't make it worse don't
make it more obvious Callie please don't
want a lawsuit on my table
tomorrow thank
youbody you very much thank you thank
you thank you I'm glad you enjoyed it
[Music]
[Applause]
to
[Music]
Moonlight for theet happy bled birthday
lady Ki this is my first ever aaspa and
I'll take this opportunity to thank you
for all your hard work since we shared a
b birthday oh thank you for two amazing
gifts in a row first you s you and I my
favorite song and now 3y concert I love
you ah you yeah I've been digging up
some some Kon songs these days right uh
you were probably also happy about me
sing uh no thank you the other
day yeah you're
[Music]
welcome thank you very much and also
happy belated birthday to you
too that's nice that we share our
birthday
yeah and now I'm done with
those I mean it it wasn't that many but
you know the problem was that there were
again a lot of pinkies and reds and
that's why it takes so much time even
though the as a number itself they're
not that
many now it's already midnight God damn
it I'm not getting very far am
i holy [\h__\h] I think I really need to do
that Super Chat raing stream oh
[Music]
man Minecraft almost nothing ah I turned
it off didn't I and what one of those
streams I must have turned it off
right I must have been that
[Music]
smart let me
see oh yeah oh yeah okay let me finish
that one
fast it looks like I did turn it off
[Music]
my
frog my frog baby ah what a precious
Adventure that
was
uh stun
D ghost d d Mar p d Big D Jones D ultr
thank you for the red super chat with a
just a DOT
what trying
to tell me
something are you trying
to trying to challenge
me you think that's better than not
writing anything at
all it's just a thought in there ah this
was one the super chats open on own oh
yeah a you just wanted to be fast got to
be fast Ultra Noob okay I'll give you
that that was a fast reaction holy [\h__\h]
thank you for the red
chat g d stri d for the pinky Freedom we
can't be contained take my money
dangel okay I'll take
it I hope it was worth it
mysterious
k r fre Dan Gabriel FW D and Del 184 fre
d that's
[Music]
it thanks guys for being
so supportive and wanting to give me
money so badly even in like 2 minutes
crazy crazy you guys are
crazy and now you have me reading these
super chats endlessly never
ending did I have them on during this
the snack box oh yeah I did it's not
that many though
and not like you know compared to the
birthday super chats not so many like
pinks and
reds I'm not going to read them now
though but I just want to take a look at
like how crazy it's looking and then the
Rea collab has only a couple that's good
Holo
cure yeah Holo cure is a a tad bit more
[Music]
portal I think I had yeah portal I had
turned
off Smash
[Music]
Brothers Super Smash Brothers doesn't
look too bad cuz like it's mostly like
non pinks non Reds
okay and then Mario party I think I yeah
had that one turned off
[Music]
too okay it's not too bad if we do a
super chat raing stream uh Mario party
here if we do a super chat reading
stream I think we can catch up or at
least get very close to the
[Music]
end all
right Super Mario
whatever you know what I mean you know
what I
mean yeah should be fine next time then
but sorry guys you know it just piles up
so much with these kind of streams yeah
well thank you for watching today um
tomorrow o
i I really don't know what to do
tomorrow I want to stream but I don't
want to set it in stone right
now oh it's
midnight ah it's the 20th of July which
is the release date of Callie's
album yay congratulations Callie for
releasing your
[Music]
album let's
go
nice
[Music]
um yeah
I'm going to make lasagna now frozen
lasagna and I'm going to eat
it thank you may Le thank you KY loves
me I love
KY it's not Monday it's
okay yesterday I ate leftover
pizza but it was not frozen pizza it was
actually good pizza from a Italian place
so it was really good and today I had a
great breakfast I had like a lot of
strawberries and and
uh not blueberries but the the other
ones and I had a nice breakfast sandwich
which is not what you guys imagine like
the you know with the sausage and all
that no no not what you guys imagine
Austrian
Style Salon M wish
V
uh Sal mhm that was
yummy yum yum yum and chalky
milk and then before the stream I had a
now this may sound weird but I had a
sausage
salad when I say sausage salad it's
called W salad is like a very thin
slices of uh like a pinkish
sausage very thin
slices uh with like uh some vegetables
and like um vinegar uh
dressing it's really nice in the summer
I really like it also for
picnics really like it for picnics my
mom used to make like that salad and and
and similar salads for uh like going to
going to like a lake or so
yeah I know it sounds weird but it's
really
yummy doesn't look super good on Google
but I guess it's h it's a nice you know
um make yourself some salads and bring
it to the lake or to the ocean or to the
pool kind of for your family kind of
snack okay now I'm going to
go
[Music]
for water there might be a chance I'm
not going to stream tomorrow I'm not
sure I I don't know we might finish uh
stray we might
[Music]
not oh
no
uh we'll
see I'll sleep on first yeah I want that
Las
now thanks guys for watching have a nice
day or evening and good night and thank
you for watching today sorry for the
hiccups uh but I hope it was still fun
it was fun for me so yeah have a great
one byebye and enjoy when we say
of
V
yay
yeah is there any music
playing I don't think there's any music
playing is there
oh this oh it's just see it's too small
too oh [\h__\h] that's the wrong
one [\h__\h] people going to know I have
things layered
[Music]
here there you go there's no be gem okay
I thought
so where is that one back here because
it's nice to then I don't have to look
for it when I want it again
exposed in AK no no exposed in
2K yeah I'm done being a cat mommy is
done being a cat now Mommy will attend
to you
[Music]
now gosh I love you oh my gosh she wants
the belly ropes she flopped
[Music]
over okay I ripped out my headphones