​​​ ​Oh, wouldn't it be ironic​ ​​
​​ ​if IRyS sabotages the tree?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wake up, IRyS!​ ​​
​​​ ​Time to ruin Christmas!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's gooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​How, how is that sabotaged?​ ​​
​​​ ​I guess it looks, like, kinda messy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, IRyS shall light the tree.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aargh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nooo! Not like that!​ ​​
​​​ ​Not like...​ ​​
​​​ ​What what what?​ ​​
​​​ ​I... I thought...​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​IRyS, what do you have to say?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, did I misunderstand?​ ​​
​​​ ​Or...​ ​​
​​​ ​Eh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Nooo! Nooooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​IRyS, what the f*ck?!​ ​​
​​​ ​IRyS!​ ​​
​​​ ​What the f*ck?!​ ​​
​​​ ​You ruined Christmas!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's not time!​ ​​
​​​ ​What the?​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, so what're we gonna do?​ ​​
​​​ ​We're just gonna let it happen?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's gone, it's gone, its f*cking...​ ​​
​​​ ​Am I the only one misunderstanding?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not sure...​ ​​
​​​ ​Does this ac...​ ​​
​​​ ​Does this happen because​ ​​
​​ ​we sabotaged the tree?​ ​​
​​​ ​Which is also what IRyS did...​ ​​