KY ke hello everybody first of all let
me say before you click away this is not
the final Advent calendar video and
that's what this video is about to let
you know that the final Advent calendar
video will be delayed um you may already
know but there have been some issues in
the process of it that maybe let's just
not get into the detail of it because
it's I don't even get me
started but please check back next week
I think around Wednesday or first day by
the latest the video will be going up
I'll be notifying you guys on Twitter as
well and the other girls probably will
do the same um please check it out
because it will be great it will be fun
and I worked hard on the script and the
sock puppets yes the sock puppets are
coming back which is the whole issue um
but yeah please wait for it it might
take a little bit longer than expected
but we're working on it thank you and
Merry
Christmas see you
soon