[Music]
n
a
[Music]
e
n
[Music]
oh
n
[Music]
sorry it's a little bit of mess I was
cooking uh the last 40 minutes before
the stream so that I don't have to cook
afterwards but in Japanese we
say that is very of me very what's in
English for in German though I don't
know in English
what did you make um actually I'm still
ignoring my hellofresh recipes cuz I'm
stupid I just wanted for some reason I
really wanted to eat what's this cable I
really wanted to eat Austrian versal
goulash oh wait that reminds me of
something I think um I have to I have to
CH choose sorry guys I have to choose my
hellofresh recipes cuz it's Thursday
right yeah have to choose my hellofresh
recipe
where
where um are they there it is there's
the
email goulash yeah it's it's gou but
there's like different variations of
gash and uh this one's not like the the
beef the beef gash is amazing too but uh
this one's more simple it's the sausage
with potato goulash just normal s Venus
sausages to be
exact it's easy it's easy and I bought
some bread to eat it with later and I
also I made also a sandwich and I ate
half of it as fast as I could but if I
get a bit more hungry for now I'm fine
if I get a bit more hungry then I'll
I'll num nom on that so recipes do I
even want to
like cuz like I can't even keep up with
the recipes of have night I feel like
partially they'll they'll suffice for
half of next week anyway feel like I
feel like I just want to say no and cook
my own things cuz like at the moment me
getting motivation to cook in the first
place is like
really you
know rare me wanting to cook today and
not even the things that I got from
hella fresh is kind of weird wasteful
but at the same time also
fascinating okay I paused it for the
next week cuz I don't know if I want to
cook something I'll I'll cook something
easy from my
own ingredients and recipes okay sorry
sorry I just have been having some
issues with motivation to do daily life
tasks uh oh before I turn on the super
chats that's right I was keeping the
super chats off before we play the game
and before we turn on the super chats
let me explain why I had the super chats
off
um so I had this
actually I had this in the works or like
ready to go since I don't know long time
ago but I waited for the right
timing uh so now that I am caught up
with my super chat so I thought it's now
the right timing so let me
uh no no alerts um a long time ago when
I saw n doing something with like
signing uh for her super chats I thought
hm I don't want to copy that thing that
she does but I want to do my own version
how can I make it different and so I
decided something
fun um as a warning this because I'm not
going to sign every freaking Super Chat
you know uh uh that would be too much it
will only be for red super chats and
only for the streams where I announce or
pin a comment beforehand that this
stream applies to this event whatever uh
so this stream this very stream will
apply to it I will do this for this
stream
so kfp Polaroid menu sheet we'll be
doing kfp
Polaroids I prepared with Duma long time
ago 20 different patterns and when you
send your super chat you can say number
one number three number 17 or whatever
whatever you feel like suits you the
most then I'll choose that and I'll take
you know I'll put it into Photoshop and
then I'll um layer it over my own
picture and then uh you know I can sign
it afterwards so here are your
choices we have number one sailor
chicken number two frog chicken number
three Elvis chicken number four kiaha
fan merchandise ocat chicken and number
five
a cute girl chicken in a dress number
six vacation chicken or whatever I don't
know Dad chicken maybe too number seven
cool young teenager Chad or whatever
chicken number eight chicken in a
suit number nine nerd chicken which one
are you guys which one is
you I what's which one speaks to you
guys uh number 10 uh
outside Harvest autumn chicken I don't
know uh maybe British chicken uh number
11 cooking chicken oh I know who that's
one that one's going to be number 12
smaller smaller
chicken number 13 H
chicken I don't know chicken wearing uh
Mario chicken and number
14 chicken and number 15 otaku chicken
number 16 cute pose chicken number 17
presenting chicken number 18 wizard
chicken number 19 made chicken and
number 20 hippie
chicken now you can choose one in the
future you can like you know choose
another one and you can collect them all
or you can choose the same one each time
but basically what I'm going to do when
you choose one I'm gonna like you know
I'm going to do this in Photoshop but
just so you can imagine I would like
down oh that was big i' put this like
like this or wait maybe want bigger like
this and I'll put myself behind
you
yay and then I'll sign it yeah you can
get a signature okay understand there's
so many yeah the kfp P I'll upload this
in the community uh board later and on
Twitter there's really a lot yeah I just
had so many ideas and uh so that
everybody finds something that speaks to
them you know big
variety and this was also just to you
know make my Super Chat ratings maybe
even more interesting especially for the
uh kfp who uh really really want a
signature but can't usually get one or
for the kfb who just want to support me
even more and want a good reason to do
so had me at
wizard I wanted this will be my dream
awesome idea
right yes yes so everybody gets like an
individual one but no it will not build
up because I will only like do it at
certain times when I know okay I have
time to do this like today uh because
I'm caught up on super chats and when I
you know just feel like it you know just
every once in a while can you explain
again sorry I just kid okay really short
explanation I thought I want to make my
super chats a little bit more special do
something like n is doing um but kind of
different so uh we designed 20 different
chickens that you can choose from if you
send a red super chat but only in the
super only in the streams where I say it
applies to like this one for example um
and then you write up please number
seven thank you and maybe a little
comment too and then I'll uh on the side
in Photoshop I'll put it over myself and
I'll sign it and then uh you can have it
I'm thinking of like I mean of course
you can take a screenshot from the
stream but I'm thinking to give you like
the cleanest and biggest version I might
just um after each signing uh put it up
on a giga file drive folder thingy and
then I'll post it in the community board
for everybody to download and and find
their own you know you know [\h__\h] you
now I need it to work cuz I'm explaining
things okay so with that I hope
explaining it two times filled all the
gaps for everybody who's been paused by
YouTube uh are you okay rootar yeah I
saw like it was like lagging for a
moment I didn't move anything it was
just like oh my was just
heavy are you okay YouTu are you okay
OBS is everybody okay are we fine now
like what's going on how bad is the
lag in the meantime let me turn on the
super
chats so every red super chat okay that
actually says a number if you don't give
me a number I'm not going to sign
anything okay I'm not going to run after
you and be like hey hey hey hey which
one did you
want
[Music]
okay okay okay okay good explanation
wow amazing kfp best place best fan
service kfp forever kfp have it the the
best or the worst no the
best Okay okay then let me write um
I I know people who will come in later
will not understand it but uh let me
write a pined comment for now
um 18 here we go KF KF
Polaroid
session number
[Music]
one applies to this
stream choose a number and send a red
Super Chat
yet if you want one
K now remember this now cuz I'm going to
put it away from for the rest of the
stream but I'll upload it later on the
community board okay V faction made
history cuz it's the first ever
yeah so
true a cool guy like me will take them a
free if if like later on if you guys
really like this we can make even more
you know I make thousands if I have more
ideas you guys got to give me some
suggestions but for now this is a good
selection I think did you screenshot it
good good good you see I I prepared this
for you aren't you aren't you
happy two number nine a number nine
latge wait wait wait does that mean no
okay number two okay and only one one
checky per stream okay one Polaroid per
stream don't go overboard and even if
you um donate 300 in one go it only
applies to one polar R I'll write down
the lyric the the rules as well
separately thank you red Super Chat
[Laughter]
is red W holy [\h__\h] I'm a [\h__\h]
businesswoman 11 that's not how it works
it has to be a red super Chad sorry I
thought I made it clear cuzz I can't
sign it for everybody if everybody just
donates $1 I'm going to have to sign 500
thingies no it has to be special to uh
to some
extent
okay makes sense right that would take
too long also that would be not a good
business model for
me not a good business model
stons I've had this actually lying
around for a year or so but I never
caught up with super chat so I was like
uh can't really do it now uh I can't
really do it now uh uh
[\h__\h] I I was
waiting it's been a while right
Duma Duma was probably wondering when is
she gonna when is she gonna do this
uh when can I talk about
this know okay so let's get to real
business yeah all super chats are
appreciated but if you want to you know
if you want something like this then
it's got to be a red okay
okay oh if it's an ARS or so super chat
by the way please be from the actual
country you know I can't really check
but I know certain suspect who are not
from there so that if I know it then
I'll say no no no no no no no that's not
how it works
okay it's difficult but please
understand yeah U I wanted to show you
my practice Victory
oopsie I played off
stream play it off stream ah [\h__\h] I'm
too bad I'm stupid stupid I'm stupid I'm
stupid
uh so I was I was I was playing random
map random uh
civilization and um I wasn't really
happy with how I started out uh but I
was trying to practice some shortcuts
that I wrote down
um yeah yeah and got me Vikings by
random but no water at all okay that's
fine for me I didn't really want to play
with water
[Music]
and
oh and and then yeah I started doing my
thing it's not ideal like certain things
like I was like brain broken when I put
a house next to the town center where
there's supposed to be a farm uh yeah
but because I got Vikings by random I
took the opportunity to watch some
guides about Vikings like what what's
good about them and this and that so I
learned about the the berserks ETC but I
started building and I thought got to be
extra careful because Henry was like
Henry the Britton he was like uh
advancing so fast and like getting so
many resources I was like [\h__\h] he's
doing good I thought like last time I
played moderate it wasn't that y so I
was like uh like Walling up myself here
but it wasn't necessary at all you can
see like they weren't Walling up but at
some point I noticed they more and more
kept sending like small groups of
enemies over here and I was like
okay sort of sort of I have to I have to
hurry up a little bit
so I uh like spammed my birer added a
few uh something this and that some Rams
a few Tres and this and that they all
like most of them died but uh I kept on
since the distance is so short I kept on
producing more and more but I went with
already a pretty big group I would say
and then I noticed holy [\h__\h] they're
actually like building so close to me
I feel like there was even
like no it felt even closer than this
and then I was like okay what the hell I
I kept on going deeper and deeper and
like this like pretty spacious but he
didn't wall himself up at all so I was
surprised I guess I didn't need to wall
myself up that
much photo security guys thank you guys
I'm so happy you likeed the idea yeah
yeah yeah I do it like maybe once a
month for so you know so that I don't
have to like do it too often and that it
still stays kind of special
probably the the war
tutorials I tried a couple of them uh or
all of them but I failed at some of them
uh but anyway yeah this wasn't ideal I
was just
practicing I was kind of annoyed by the
placement of wood and how far away all
the stone camps were and this and that
but that's just nature I guess but yeah
I I won even though he was always like
faster than me with advancing and all
that I won I won yeah the water Tor is
really
hard did you set up your hot casys I
changed a few so that I remember
them thank you
guys thank you thank you
ah I'm glad I won I was kind of scared
well uh one question when you're just
one versus one and the other one is
obviously your
enemy can I I forgot can I still send uh
a market a card to their Market a trade
like you know even though we're about to
have a war can you still do that yeah no
yes no no no okay I'll believe the no I
can still trade I saw that like I can
still sell gold in this n but there's
like no trade card option then okay okay
wait now there's yeses some yes some no
what does that
mean yes but if they destroy your card
it's a huge loss
ah they can break it well do they
usually break
it oh thank you oh which number is
popular is it I see I think I saw a lot
of
17s wait blank you forgot the number
blank I told you y I told you guys you
have to add a number blank you can add a
number in a in a separate small smaller
Super Chat okay don't waste your
money you can uh theoretically you can
but why would you if they destroy it I
think you can't try they don't notice
it's good if they do it's
bad
[Music]
okay the gu
you just want to trade in team games
anyways no point in okay okay okay but
so then if I really run out of
something like really a buy my my only
option is to sell like normally but even
if when when even that's not enough I
guess that's a rare case like I had that
because our matches were way too
long oh well
well
[Laughter]
number five question question you don't
know what you're
choosing
know how many villages do you have at
the end uh you can see at the top I
think
48 um yeah I was like spamming uh
military units at the end so okay that
was moderate difficulty one versus
one uh so
ooh oh I got a I got a achievement for
that I finished an hour ago by the way I
just wanted to show you guys oh it was
exactly 1 hour and 1 minute
long it it was kind of long like I could
have probably attacked earlier but I was
so worried and I was like Walling myself
up I just want to be careful you know I
know Vikings would have been a good uh
Sith to like raid with but I don't
know gold would constantly run out to
due to how laidback most games are oh
the thing that I had troubles with was
wood all of the time
technology Society was same but yeah
okay I won by far military winning oh he
I was hearing the the the magic all the
time I knew he converted
something oh gold waa 10,000
gold well I collected so much wood but
it still wasn't
enough
and you see here 5 minutes later around
the same time 7 minutes
later
yeah oh he researched 30 things
[Music]
wow total cast is
one I was wondering I was like in the
beginning when my Scout went around I
saw like the the the white Relic dots on
the map right and eventually
I I I took one but then when I looked
again later all the white Relic dots
were gone and I was like eh do they just
disappear after a while and I have to
send my Scout again or Nah that can't be
I was like no way did he take them all
what the [\h__\h] crazy wait oh my god wow
AI loves snagging them AI likes taking
them I've I have noticed I thought I
must have I don't know must have not
known that they the dots disappear after
a while and I have to find them again or
so damn he really took them so fast must
have made more than one monk though
because like they're so
slow o pretty much like on par until a
certain point and then I
[Music]
win hold
okay that was fun for me uh hi Raiders I
want to challenge myself to be a bit
more aggressive but I'm just so [\h__\h]
scared um by the way today's goal is not
necessary really to get already into an
online the thing is like I know um I
know ranked matches are hard but you got
to get started uh and like get yourself
ranked like you will lose the first
couple of matches for sure but then it
will understand at some point that
you're like really weak and then it will
put you like where you belong to I have
to get through that eventually but we
don't have to do it today we don't have
to do it
today um I want to feel comfortable with
at least a couple of uh hot
Keys yeah and high
AI yeah a little bit just a little bit
but already scares the [\h__\h] out of me no
maybe maybe one more time moderate and
I'll just try to attack earlier okay can
we do that
and the rest can stay the same random
random I don't uh or or should I
practice Vikings a bit more the thing is
like if I if I get something new I want
to understand first properly what it is
I'll just maybe I'll just practice a bit
more with Vikings cuz the the free
um uh stats that help the economy are
actually quite nice where are the
Vikings here like uh uh wheel B hand
card free is like pretty
awesome I'll just I'll just try Vikings
again I think it's nice to focus you
know that was my first Vikings match but
I should learn one by one I learned
Toons now I'm learning Vikings and then
we can learn something
else yeah they have some of the best
economy I know I know and I I like the
berserks cuz they're not as [\h__\h] slow
as the tuttons but they're still very
strong and they heal themselves a little
bit so it's pretty nice guys oh my God
wait how
much nice
businesswoman trying to get all the
money that I spent for the motion
capture suit back thank you
guys STS let me take one bite from my
from my
sandwich
a
so
small say two player but it did feel
pretty small should I make it
bigger
[Music]
okay two
two ignore this oh
[\h__\h] two two two two
two two two
two so should I do small tin
no I just want one versus one I want to
practice one versus one cuz we practice
bigger matches recently
anyway Vikings are good for SE Maps I
know that but like if I play online and
everything's like random I'm going to
guess like like maps are mostly
random then I don't want to be like you
know like oh my God I I can only play on
the ocean ah
I want to be surprised oh bgm
oopsie okay there you go it's really
quiet right
now is this
nft is
it I don't think so cuz I'm
it's it's made to order and it's like
unique
and is it
nft not really really
right technically not technically yes
the duality of
kfp
um let's let's just say no
okay it
no yeah I'm not killing the
environment H let's start Mongols oh ahe
okay okay okay I'm also trying to
practice um the beginning m but I I
think I already forgot um I just know I
just know
um wait
[Music]
yeah
uh see this is what I'm trying to
practice and
then no not don't kill it but
wait wait oh
[\h__\h] okay and now oh uh ah uh then what
wait wait wait uh then all of them both
on the sheep right matter after the
houses are done all of them on the
ship no I have to pause little bit I
have to think I have to think I'm trying
to I don't even have this written down
I'm trying to
remember
yeah trying I I'll I'll I'll have to
yeah once we find the boar yeah but I
need I need first I need I think once I
have seven I'm going on the boore with
the SE the seventh brings the boore to
the town
center
right and then once wait let me let me
look it up
again I have to see it
uh where is the
guide here written down here shortly uh
two houses right away queue villagers
first six on the
Sheep next four on the so once we have
six we stand the next four on the on the
wood wherever the biggest wood is also
there's water o and
then wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait hot keys I don't know I'm
practicing
whatever uh yeah okay
okay uh to until 6 we go on
sheep and my idle villager hotkey is I
changed it
to matter Mouse
wheel thanks for playing this game it's
fun it's nostalgic to me to wait we have
fishes and I have I have I weak wait so
this is actually
hm even though I'm a viking and there's
water right next to me should I still
follow this basic
15 15
villager um menu because the the fishies
are right
there I
could I should
[Music]
um where do I start with the Ducks I
wonder maybe wait are there berries yeah
there are berries maybe we still go for
the
berries uh until 15 and after 15 we go
to the water instead of building too
many farms right away don't worry about
dogs dogs C that's
true maybe only once I'm set with lots
of wood I don't
[Music]
know
oh there's a Bo by the way okay well
okay let's just go classic for
now that's oh wait H seven we
already is that already seven I only see
six ah the Scout is the
seventh the Scout is the seventh
okay sometimes it's hard to see I see
the top left I see it next person come
on okay bring me the
boar I now also know that I I knew this
a while ago already but that you can
control the Sheep some I I also know
that some people like send it
to uh look around a little
bited bring it
here yeah sheep control sheep Scout but
you have to control yourself so yeah Bo
don't die don't die run
[Music]
run
everybody [\h__\h] he died he died that's
not good that's [\h__\h] also I wasn't
creating
oh oh wait it oh wait I was
confused I thought the boar was my
sheep rip restart
no no no no restart yet but yeah wasn't
ideal
uh what was it berries no wood
[Music]
okay next four on wood I know it's a
huge loss I'm just practicing okay
chill
oh we keep it six here or should I add
one more to the
[Music]
meat yeah should I it's over no it's
not chill oh there's like a looking at
the map there's a
huge uh yeah huge body of water in the
middle
free that's free we need a fourth one on
wood oh [\h__\h] I didn't okay I'm so bad
it's age over
Empires come
on oh you guys are done [\h__\h] these sheep
are [\h__\h] I should have sent someone wild
they're okay
restart we want to be efficient okay
uh wait what was my what was my shortcut
for villager new is plus but I can't
find the [\h__\h] Plus on my keyboard
because like I have a Japanese keyboard
and in order to write a plus it's like
with shift I have to write it with with
up uppercase you know so somehow it
doesn't work the plus doesn't work I
should change it to something that I can
actually
press where was it where's
uh Town
Center villager is this make a new
villager but then it wouldn't be
Q oh maybe I oh did I already change it
oh this is make one oh let me test so uh
h q I love not not enough food but okay
that seems to be
it um gag
matter uh okay which one are we working
on okay so sending the ship sheep a
little bit away
too come on you're not finding anything
of value right now and I already know
what there
is old nice he found the Sheep though
this
time good
good sheep sheep go
[Music]
man oh uh hi uh hi sorry what are you
doing uh oh wait uh how many is this uh
wait we seven so the next one next one
the next one where's the boore the boore
should be here I'm meta gaming now cuz
my Scout is useless Scout go go like
here and then go here and then go here
oh go go go
hunting when sheep go
here thank you guys oh my God stons
hugest stons on Earth actually could
have taken the the right board
too
Ali
Ali stks stks
uprising
what are you
doing anyway B
Master
[\h__\h] I [\h__\h]
[Music]
up [\h__\h] up hoay okay that's pretty
thick uh forest all
right can my f my ship find my sheep
find the
other uh what was I supposed to do wait
this is uh eight now so this one can go
make
wood [\h__\h] ship
sheep sheep can't convert sheep okay
damn
it oh dude be efficient do
something uh
oh one joined the
party Shep Shep I'm I'm a shepherd
shepherd okay this set for next uh 11 uh
11th goes boar
hunting we on the
[Music]
yeah how many is this seven that's one
one can go get the bo
right and then what does the next person
do
again cuz like isn't there a Gap I guess
not 11th goes B that's that's that's
what I was supposed to do anyway okay
okay 11 goes Bo
hunting go go and um build house and
then
Mill and Mill and then
Mill wait girl girl what did the boy
forget me [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah then she shall build the mill if
she only could um Let me let me add her
we'll adjust we'll adjust the situation
actually no she's waiting so she can do
this tree I heard about that than you I
learned
this
bye no she didn't die okay uh uh
efficiency efficiency wait but then
that's probably isn't this too many
people eight people okay
one
uh [\h__\h] she was supposed
to build a mill uh
here and they all go
there okay
okay yeah it's fine we don't need Loom
now uh wait you can also join the
berries now that was just a isn't that
smart that I did that this is a only a
task for shortterm uh how many people on
the berries not that
many um not that many necessary wait so
13 to 15 help berries we're we're over
15 now so we can just do whatever we
want now
right
maybe you also
help and then the next one's a few more
on the wood and then we can make Stones
as well I guess and although we really
need more food holy
[\h__\h] okay also house no house house is
okay
uh
[Music]
matter what is
this what that
sound
[Music]
uh yeah the goat the goat doesn't come
on its
[Music]
own let me send
one Queen yeah okay I sent one uh
red I don't
know I don't know she's just she's just
going to get
the sheep and
then don't follow me right ah [\h__\h]
that's that's not I don't like this like
what do you do if you kill a goat then
you're bound to get the meat from
here so far
away build a midd as a house that was a
house [\h__\h] I'm so
stupid I was confused I was
confused no it's a mining camp that was
on purpose guys what do you mean it's a
house it's a it's a it's a mining camp
you guys are
confus [\h__\h] it's
fast how some berries oh
Dad
h what what
happened
uh
my
God
sheep okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay both
nice nice nice nice nice the game Crash
no no no this is legit I'm just trying
to practice you know the important
things to get them
down is there nothing left up there ah
there is see okay see I'm doing that
good I think I'm doing
[Music]
good okay okay okay okay
sheepies what is he doing
uh yeah I couldn't really see
the okay couldn't really see which one
is the right
sheep so now it's time for
boar start is important now so you have
to practice to
start yes yes look at all these
sheep
get him get him get him get him come
on
[Laughter]
faster what is this what is this
efficiency
non-existent uh wait so
uh what was next I uh wood
[\h__\h] I
think this is the this is the
ninth so that's already isn't that
already too
many you sure what is off the
board ah what is before boore n damn
it damn it wood was before
b s this
there
man ranked is point five speed faster
that's okay I'm not ready for it okay
I'm not ready I know I can also not
pause this much I know I know I
know where is this dude
[Applause]
going timber timber h
it's good practice yeah good practice
this I have to do this 1 2 3 4 five
that's way too many
people also one should help the the boy
guy going to help him out a little bit
before the boar meat is like dead and
useless
do this sheep we're running out of sheep
soon
but oh this
dude oh no go like go like
here uh uh I think one
more sometimes it's kind of hard to
tell then after that next one builds
another house in the mill another house
in the Mill House in the mill
one two
three what are they doing why are they
all splitting these
[Music]
idiots SMI
SMI who sh me and then the mill and then
the mill and then uh I can do it can I
do it with like this with shift then
it's uh her next task right no no no
finish this one man
is this a new
girl do this I
guess it's already it's already getting
better Queen okay house is
built yeah she can go straight to the
berries I
guess at one point should I send someone
to the goats or should I ignore the
goats for now I don't know
what is
he no don't go this way just go this way
you [\h__\h] idiot
here uh ignore them for now okay but I
think I'm out
of I'm out of yeah yeah
yeah so let's add them to the berries
are you finished with that too okay
that's actually a lot of people
so I
will make one mining
camp I'll build I don't know from now on
it's freyle
so one more to
Wood and one
here yeah
yeah
I'm learning what language is
this like the even the tuttons were
speaking like some old Germans so is
this like some old nor where Vikings
from Swedish nor Nordic old nor
oh okay what's more
[Music]
important
M wait I can't keep I can't make up my
mind ah let's make a
farm what's the shortcut for
Farm shortcut for Farm
a ag up first yeah I need I need more I
need more food but I I can't I have to
always make
villagers so
until until it keeps up yeah the food
with my Village creation then uh you
know uh maybe make a house I don't
know what was
it sheep found not my sheep
right a h a h a q
q enough wood for dogs I don't know
uh no he huh what wait why it's not
working can I take them for real I think
they're gone now can't take them
anymore oh we're just like on the
outside we
need we need muchos muchos
[Music]
Timber no
no what are you saying I don't need gold
right now I need wood
Timber much
Timber maybe a second
one over
here but what I'm also assuming now is
that we don't need to really do any
walls on this map
either this is
good we have uh I don't know about the
Mongols but we have a an advantage over
the
ocean I've scouted the en base more or
less not really sa
satisfyingly can he go here or is it
just wood yeah
yeah what lber camp build
F it's okay I was behind in the last one
too
q a Ah that's why it's q q and then q
a oh they're done with the berries uh
okay uh q
a uh QA I can make one here too right
and then QA wait what uh
QA q a q
a q a q
well
yeah
okay almost 500
food I'm trying my best here okay I know
it's not ideal yet but we're getting
better and better I'm going to be the
best AOE player in whole
life you got to get you know it it's got
to be in your blood it's difficult B
matter you know what she can do that do
you need two people on a goat I wonder
probably
right leave it and
then
B
matter
what yeah okay uh what do I need gold
okay it's time time to time to do
gold K
age it's Bonker seeing this game play
the whole life I see like this game
brings me a lot of non-usual uh viewers
I'm happy to see that hi guys everybody
welcome to the show I'm going to play
AOE next week too that's my
plan maybe you guys should uh do over
here not here just saying just
saying yeah
yeah wait actually yeah okay it's fine
after this
villager yeah I love I love this these
kind of nostalgic games I play a lot of
games that are just nostalgic to me even
even if other people don't care much
about it q
[Music]
a over here so that there's
space we are going
to feudal
age the Starship Titanic stre yeah that
is that is one of the most
n nostalgic games that I've done so far
also they went back to that okay
is this is wait what do you think guys
is there uh there's surely information
surely some people who are smart enough
who know this how many people do you
need on a goat for it not to be
wasted is true enough or do I need three
four
four at least two two to four four as
many as you can okay
um
probably yeah I could probably get this
dude to drop off and then
help it's it's ni it's already gone
anyway oh they have to go so
far uh
okay okay now that it's advancing we can
think
about what to do
next chat's median age also go you mean
the uh average age of my chat
oh what just that what was that sound a
weird ass oh they continue with that
okay well then let me
help I like how they're doing that
automatically that's nice that's
helpful don't get housed what does that
mean running out of house oh is that
what you
mean yeah the next the next villager can
make a
Housey
okay
Advanced that is
good I have the situation under
control oh he's so stupid this a most
stupid Scout like he always goes where I
don't want him to go but there's a relic
oh you at least found a relic in the
middle of the wood ocean H what
Forest uh house kill
kill
here h four that's also good but I would
need seven people again or like
six is that is it worth it at that
point
like getting people off of work for
that
yeah thank okay then we'll bait him
bring him over to the town center and
then all the farmers will help for a
moment with that
actually these people can help too but n
they're on the goat B matter uh what do
you do what what do we need
gold actually I need to build stuff wait
ah run run run run run
run girl the board is
confused nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice nice nice okay okay okay okay okay
1 2 3 4 5 six I think it's six okay
H meanwhile the new ones can work on the
farms that have been
abandoned
okay that was that was good that was
beautiful that was ideal
yeah okay
uh Barracks Barracks Barracks maybe
close to the ocean so I can load them in
fast upgrade ah yeah upgrade wood
ah yeah I forget about that upgrade all
the
time
um was the
Toons oh are they are they done okay
then
QA
QA what was that advanced
cast how far am I from Castle Age Two
feudal buildings okay yeah uh what are
we building next there's a feudal
building M
stable
work harder everybody Chop
Chop faster
[Music]
faster efficiency is of the utmost
importance uh
wait
yeah
um
[Music]
okay okay
houses housing
crisis who wants to live here in the
woods no
nobody n
I don't want to like take like block too
many things to get
through but we're going over the ocean
anyway and I'm building all these
buildings close to the
ocean so that's fine what that man at
Arch arms res I can't read my my brain
is too focused on being
efficient let's build one one one more
right the
way
and okay my
speak this isn't Sim City throw them
anywhere some cheap housing for families
yes yes I'm trying my best mayor mayor
kiaha is trying her best for you just
for
you okay um these
two let's
see an archery
right
a I don't know but like generally
genuinely wonder if the military units
are able to walk around
properly like this also I should make a
dock let's make a [\h__\h] dock let's go
hey dog we where's the dog's
here
fish
uh then we'll make a few fishing
boats do
[Music]
uh do we even need watchtowers at
this a
blacksmith can't build here other
materials or
what no can't just can't build it let's
go there uh fishing
ship maybe
two oh Castle H Castle H Castle H too
steep
oh yeah
uh
house
um
what okay is there any upgrades here
that we
want no but
uh wait so the the the um the uh the the
shippies that only Vikings have they're
only after Castle AG I assume so I don't
know if I really want to build like G
and stuff right
[Music]
now actually are we going to use the
ocean like even if we R although
there we would need Transportation ships
too I
guess is this a town center no
where's the Town Center oh wait blind
this is the Town Center could we could
we reach it from here in the
water Mongols are hold see use that to
your advantage okay
[Music]
okay East Asian Barracks long boats yeah
yeah long boats that's what I meant the
long
[Music]
boats yeah I guess like I don't know if
that will be like our main battle thing
like for the big battle cuz like I'm I
usually like to build up for for one big
attack rather than like a lot of small
[Music]
ones build more than one dog e why I
mean okay can
do should it be like close to each other
or build castle near sea okay
wait am I in Castle H yet
no oh wait cancel do Castle [\h__\h] okay I
should have I should have not canceled
it when it was so close to making uh the
Villager anyway
okay enemy Scout yeah just ignore him
just ignore him wait uh we go
here I guess I'll make one two transport
ships I have so many Idol
[Music]
Villages where are they okay a couple of
you oh no join join those stones oh the
stones are almost done
to Idol it sounds the same the
unemployment they're going to hate me
they're going to move over to the
enemy transport ship cre
it I'll make one more fishing ship and
uh ah we might just well build another
house
right okay almost Castle I'm
so slow right now with
that almost there though go away Scout
we don't need
you house built
um I'm I'm having trouble finding things
to do for
them
Mark I
guess
oh there we
go uh okay when you guys are free
uh actually you drop that off and start
the castle building uh Pleasant peasant
build 1,000 farms in total let's
go this will block my whole
view I hate that placement I hate that
you can't change change angles at least
like a little
bit okay we should be fine on food
now actually for real for real like do I
even need so many people in food now I
guess I'll I guess they can
stay ah prepare the long boats long
boats long boats long boats uh
uh Long Boat
G trade where are the long boats an next
tab demolition
w m how
many actually make
a no they cost a lot of gold right
that's the the
thing I wonder how many I should
make two Castle AG buildings on or a
castle wait I'm almost done with the
castle don't worry don't worry don't
worry don't worry we can get
there
oh not a h i mean I know this is more
efficient but I I don't
even I'm I'm not even you know capable
of be of using all that efficiency for
what it's
worth
on uh
okay oh what was that was it a fishing
boat from
them
okay first
time as many as
possible was it just a normal enemy
boat okay
well
[Music]
uh gosh this is
so we need stones I'm really low on
Stones
this oh should I do one of these
upgrades um but this is this is not from
long boats ship armor that's for sure
fishing ships oh oh they're attacking
the Scout don't waste your time on
him no don't chill
chill okay he's dead okay you did
it oh God
uh
uh okay ah wait uh now I make I make a
few nights couple nights upgrades oh
yeah upgrades upgrades upgrades where
was my where's my blacksmith where's my
blacksmith house house didn't I build it
here learning how buildings look is also
important did I not build the
blacksmith want to build a blacksmith
North that's
okay
uh all of this yes yes G longboats yes
yes okay Imperial age okay we might be
late but I feel like we we're still
still going to
[Music]
win okay we have no idle
villagers we're building stuff Chie
ttain is important I I learned that uh
after Chiefs not like the next upgrade
is not that worth it cuz it costs too
much might as well just make more bks
over
that yeah my my economy is pretty
good uh let's make we we could we could
make a
monastery I'm being attacked like for
real for real no it doesn't look like
I'm being is it my Scout oh goodbye
Scout that's
okay yeah yeah I got to learn to have an
eye for um you know just
everything gold though gold wasn't there
another
gold
mine I'm
blind here's one did I already clean all
the gold
up I'm blind I thought there was one
more gold Farm like in like in this area
[\h__\h] we have to attack soon cuz like
there's no nothing for
me Relic that's true yeah so that's why
I'm hoping that the monk will show up
soon
um guess we can make a
house Monk and monk
speed
oh guess I could I could always trade
some wood for more gold for example
H it looks like this building is
burning do this is my where are my
fishing
boats yeah bye yeah bye yeah wait wait
wait let me make a few I my first C
first make a crossbow
man
one more house Q hey I wanted to no qill
Q I wanted to
learn no not all of you uh I guess
they're all out of job
[\h__\h] what can I do what can I do maybe
build another dock ha no seat
workshop and then some people
[Music]
Bo
stuck upgrade to no ship speed transport
capacity yeah okay okay sounds
good more uh
also wait this is finished so let's make
a few ramps
oh the gold the
gold yeah they probably already have
like all the other relics like how many
relics could there
be in this
map I
wonder ah what do we do enemy above oh
oh
what is that a castle no how
what the
absolute audacity they have to build a
town center
here what the actual
[Music]
[\h__\h]
what I didn't
see
what I actually can't believe
that is
fascinating wait
[Music]
um unbelievable at least they can't
really do much about me destroying
it
wow it's
here okay okay I don't have much more
patience we have to do something now
um you can't really can you put Tri
ships in
the in the transportation
ship where are my where are my
Transportation
ships here I might need more right maybe
one more two
more yeah
okay make one
here
[Music]
how many
people get in the
ship who can make it into the
ship uh
what happened did I not get another
where where's my other Transportation
ship I'm so confused I'm so confused
where did my trans didn't I make another
Transportation
ship oh I may be I may be running out of
like
materials I have just two population
limit
yeah who
[Music]
I hear scary
sounds there we
go if I double click these now are they
only the ones that are outside yeah
okay get the Ram
in h [\h__\h] this is not ideal I know it's
not ideal I don't know where where
everybody is either
[Music]
uh should I
go how do
you
how does the fish net thing work anyway
why do I why do you want me to do
that I don't
know could sent will surely do some
damage what's that t pack okay H get the
T into the
ship get these people to the
ship this one's this this one's fully
packed
right this
one's oh okay it's
[Music]
starting I'm not fishing ship
[\h__\h] die die die die die they came for
trouble but I'll make it
[Music]
double
off uh blacksmith
[Music]
uh what what what is this doing
here is this a scout why is he attacking
me why is he trolling
me somebody's building here again
too uh do I have like any more units
outside right
now who
uh do not panic do not panic do not
under any circumstances Panic do not
panic uh do do do do not
[Music]
panic
uh no
no okay good job good
job
ah
uh okay fight me fight
me no wait this is not a I thought it
was a tri or something no they're just
building
well oh my
God I want a couple of
these
okay man how
annoying
let's
make another should we make another
castle like
here but I don't know I just want to go
there now I want to attack from the
ocean
[Music]
they don't they're probably not going to
give me space to attack from the ocean
though at this
rate uh yeah yeah
uh
[Music]
um attack from both
sides I I'm not I it's like a it's so
messy
so
messy Castle there will stop them I
think
so so stupid stop sending me your
people ah I can't can't I can't I can't
I
can't just T this
just uh ah I can't multitask like this
how do I know how
many there's some people in this one
should I send them over I don't know how
many people are in there now but [\h__\h]
it
ah my
monk oh did my monk convert the this
night wasn't it like the other way
around
yeah nice Wu nice
W oh okay good
stuff Stu good
stuff they
done okay
uh I guess we're doing this I guess
we're doing
[Music]
it ah I'm so
stressed
[Music]
uh
two arms I guess we're
fighting
ah I don't know I don't know if this is
enough
[Music]
people maybe it
is taking down the town the Town
Center's already down does he have a
second one that I don't know about I
think I'm
winning cuz like there's like no people
here m
let's kill the
docks what's going on here oh they sent
some people
[Music]
okay wow wow wow wow best matter
uh
wait just just give up
already I'm killing everything you
[Music]
have just give
up why are you fighting what are you
fighting
[Music]
for
nice nice
okay what are they trying to
accomplish there's nothing left to like
how long how long does it take for them
to understand it's
over maybe I'm missing another town
center oh there's still people I thought
they already unloaded
everything is
[Music]
this what's going on what's going
on we're fine we're
fine uh what did I just
select
okay where if if they're not giving up
now it must
mean there's still a town center
oh
no right pausing will hinder you yeah
there is this is it this is
it this must be it or is it is it even a
castle that's a castle probably but
maybe they feel like as long as they
have that they're not going
to uh give
up
yeah okay
okay you need your tries I have like two
here
[Music]
yeah
okay definitely still not very
ideal
um
but this is like one they should resign
now when no T no Castle yeah yeah yeah
we're getting them we're getting
them
maybe send these people
over these ships whatever they can shoot
try it
oh
ah I found
them this is the Town
Center what what is this Longboat doing
here all alone you're making huge
improvements thank you I don't know did
did did that sound just now does it mean
they have
uh will Lo
someone or have I probably they did cuz
I my my one single monk is probably
dead Okay
a my my buildup of the economy is fine
but like once I go into battle I'm like
oh what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
especially if I'm not the first to initi
appreciate
it but that this was wait I lied oh no
did I no it still it was still moderate
right okay it's right cuz I changed to
heart and then I changed back to
moderate okay next maybe we can do heart
I don't
know but
yeah that was the Town Center they were
hiding little town centers here and
there they they were not as greedy about
the relics this time cuz like there was
a great A Relic here and a [\h__\h] ton of
gold
wow and look at
these what are
these Le
[Music]
leopard oh they're so AI monks
automatically try to convert what
attacks them but I have to micromanage
them that's not
fair that's not
fair
okay
so they were once again uh further ahead
in technology but once again we're the
same at Society just like my previous
one but wait being ahead in technology
does that just mean like being faster in
wait was it 20% of the resource value of
every technology each player has
research ah just researching okay plus
10% 10 point for every 1% of the map
explored uh oh I lost no
buildings I converted a unit and they
converted a
unit I oh what their army was 23 people
at
most what
oh what what are you doing what are you
doing
[Music]
oh well gold wasn't even a big
difference this time the rest I'm
winning by far yeah oh look at the food
collected 18,000 versus 9,000 I'm like
doubling that same with the
stones and yeah I'm pretty late with
advancing but in the end like same thing
in my last match and I still
[Music]
won
I don't want to play extreme AI yet
no oh they did capture free
relics so every every Relic probably
accept the one that I took and except
the one on the island my villager high
was 69
nice
o not a well it was never never
seemingly an issue for me I was really
late on the third
one now I don't
now play game at standard play at
standard game velocity what does that
mean I should try to
not pause as
often that is one
thing oh game speed is a standard game
speed but you mean normal standard asn't
what they gave me but default but okay
game speed
normal less pausing I can't do no
pausing yet especially cuz my finger is
now like used to going on every
fre
um we can do something
else should I do something else or
should I stay with
[Music]
Vikings AI sucks of water
water sucks for them sucks to be them
random yeah but the problem is if I get
something new I would want to pause to
watch a
video from uh spirit of the law to tell
me about
them like take my
time I can't really play it unless I
like mute it and then it's
[Music]
awkward uh try Britain for Archers is I
want to I want to I want to take my time
with learning about them I think I'll
just go for
Vikings
again cuz I know what I'm doing more or
less what what guys uh besides like
pausing less and other obvious things
you have some advice in like uh watching
what I just did like what can I improve
uh that's not not like too too advanced
and like think about my small smarter
brain small small small small brain and
and then think about what I could
actually pick up right
now uh rally
points yeah I do use them
sometimes what do you mean with attack
move you mean like choosing like little
groups and then oh do you mean like like
pointing at one point and then you know
when they're like shooting at me with
archers then moving away from it quickly
and then attack and then move and then
attack that's what you mean right do do
I look like I'm ready for
that does it look like I'm ready for
that's not what you
mean
what attack here
command
what you send your units to a place and
they attack everything ah
I know I know that a scouting does
that is there an
[Music]
attack ah instead of right click to move
hit a then left click so after I have
all my units selected a and then left
click units will attack anything in the
water
okay build more Barracks I don't know
about that when I'm not even making use
of my one
Barrack at this
point Mak some attack any okay okay okay
get gold on the first tutorial it's very
good
maybe is very important focus on what
they're targeting yeah yeah yeah I I I
try I try when when there's not too much
Panic it's it's
r a used in another games okay R uh okay
R and then click I'm going try
okay start it
Chinese yeah
uh
uh can I go like
oh
uh I'm like the
Sheep
gagn bore
cited
uh hi sorry
uh let's go ah you chose the wrong ship
No 1 2 three
six next one is B no next one wood next
one wood but where is my big wood Source
I can't even see
it uh
here maybe I see the is
now q and
then yeah okay that's where it is let's
put it
here two BS very close to each other and
The Relic okay all right all right all
right more sheep
seies oh [\h__\h] it wasn't creating I
thought it was creating
yeah nice resources yeah yeah they all
right Lumber Camp build next one also
[Music]
on
the why are they so spread out these
idiots oh my
God what is care of Po oh my God I'm so
sorry I should really explain it again
but there's no
time
um yeah I'll I'll explain again after
the after I'm done with like the gaming
portion
okay yeah I know how long I'll be going
but I already cooked before the stream
so there's not really anything I got to
do it's a
thing
maybe if you're in the kfb Discord they
probably can give you the info there
oh oh you're stuck aren't
you oh two relics right at my
side a not efficient
enough I cooked let her
cook wait 1 2 3 4 that's already four
that's already four right on the wood
one two yeah I think so so next one is
the four oh perfect timing actually cuz
they just got
[Music]
done not
optimal wait uh let's make
a [\h__\h] okay did somebody die I don't
think anybody died at least
why is she on the
tree nobody died that
is a decent accomplishment ah wait I was
supposed to build a
Mill and then those other people join on
the
berries
okay oh
sheeps
oh
who okay is that Autos Scot yeah yeah
yeah he's terrible right like in other
games that I did he was way better like
I was never unhappy with the auto
scouting like I don't know what's going
on I don't know
yeah you're
terrible
yeah it always starts from the right
corner really he's doing his best yeah
let's give him a
break just
one just one just one so that we can do
it close
by
[Music]
sry I was
confused
cute oops I Did It
Again have yet to find the enemy but if
I'm down here I I guess he's like
here but I like this map like there's a
lot of stuff
here let me build a house here and then
how do I do
like is is line queuing up things [\h__\h]
I'm sometimes
unsure no okay that worked
okay holding ship okay
[Music]
okay wait you
lady uh no water though barely any water
so I don't know if we can if it's even
worth
making
any uh dock especially cuz it's not
close by why still early I don't know I
don't know I'm confused
okay actually no sheep we still have
some
sheep yeah
[Music]
uh
should I make a
house at least I'm pausing not so often
for
[Music]
now
uh
yeah get someone go yeah was that was a
plan but somebody was already making me
uncertain of my ideas
yeah what's mining
come damn so many
resources oh but I think I see now it's
like a woody map cuz like we have to go
for all these paths it seems
these paths through the
forest foresty map
um a bit more food a bit more food
[Music]
Black Forest wi I love black forest cake
matter let me send them on the goats cuz
they're so close is it forgivable to go
for the goats when they're so
close yeah matter I'll send another free
on the second
go wait those are only
too I'll send one to help with the
goat and then the other
one oh the other one wait I can
advance the other one [\h__\h] make
decisions wa make
decisions
Q mhm okay okay it's not so bad a
b they don't get faster they don't get
faster with
Bloom but what I do want to research
soon is uh double bit
axe house built yeah I find it
interesting that I only ever hear about
um sorry one time pause so I can ask
this about um the upgrading the the
lumber but nobody ever talks about
upgrading like this kind of stuff is it
not worth it I mean 15% is quite a lot
we C is speed uh I am Viking so I uh
don't I already have
it I mean I'm thinking it's gr out cuz I
already what don't I already have it by
by
default it is but W is more important
okay cuz I never hear anybody say hey
upgrade
this
m
are you done with that
one
okay
nice is just HP yeah that I
know q
a we have Advan y
c people still ordering the the
Polaroids wow oh my
God got I'm going to get in trouble for
having a second business on my side a
side
hustle uh wait so I'm supposed to build
some stuff now build build build some
[Music]
Barracks I know it's really far but I'm
just considering the fact that we'll
have to walk really far how how have you
not found the enemy yet maybe they're
here they're not straight across of us
then they must be
there okay upgrade
[Music]
ax maybe not
necessary
yeah actually do this one
[Music]
first yeah
okay oopsy
[\h__\h] quick
question is Outpost this early worth
it enemy Scout I ignore the enemy Scout
he's just scouting he's not attacking
me
no no need for Outpost I never buildt
Outpost okay Bo boing
boing okay our next goal is 800 food two
feudal buildings okay we have the
barracks uh we'll build
archery oh wait so many people no no no
no uh
what don't think we're being actually
attacked they're attacking my Scout holy
[\h__\h] look at them go we're building uh
we're against the Chinese right now
right I I I think I heard something
about
their um Specialties but
M wasn't it like
they have like
more yeah some some some extra
villagers so they build more
faster honestly sasuga I feel like that
that is really
fitting
oh God not efficient
enough lure accurate or an Archer unit
merciless oh [\h__\h] then I should maybe
think about what's what's strong against
archers advaning let's go let's go oh my
God should we make a few cheap men at
Arms just a
couple because I can put them in Rams
later if they're still alive at that
point oh wait we don't
[Music]
really where's my where's my mil
here I don't really need that
much Stone right now we need more
food you can attack their villagers with
your manat arms I could if I if I were
ready for that kind of micromanaging
across the map yet
but
[Music]
not 14 or Babble
Babble Babble Babble chimkin oh wait Q
cute wall the gaps should I be walling
in this
case yeah yeah they say
yeah okay
que with a gate or without a
gate with with a gate
Maybe
thank you thank you thank you for saving
my life oh my God holy [\h__\h] can we get
the meat of that
no God my brain my brain finish uh this
G me surprise was that a
wolf
maybe should I go across
here I I'll
[Music]
try and then a
gate can it be like
this and
then stone
wall wa
this
okay seven people oh my
God h
Castle two Castle AG wait wait I'm in
Castle age I'm in Castle AG I didn't
realize where are these people that are
currently not doing
anything I don't see
them okay I'm housed indeed I am I just
noticed Sor I was focusing on the walls
because I want them to have no Gap but I
think they have a gap
here TN or oh do they they're building
something here wait they're right over
here wait wait wait wait
what
Castle well then the castle shall go
here [\h__\h] but I have no
space but if they're going to come from
that side so yeah bye that's just a
blacksmith yeah yeah but like
still wait I shouldn't have built it
like this should I build a castle in
their
face the Scout can't get out oh no ah
close the
gate
um uh God brain is so slow brain is so
slow
Siege it's so
mountainous can you make elephants I
don't think so make monk for real yeah
that's what I'm going to do right
now
um wait why didn't I make two why did I
make two just one is enough
uh they're monk they're monk they're
shitty monk [\h__\h] off die die
can I really will they will they really
be forgiven for doing this for doing a
castle right there I don't know man it's
kind of scaring
me they're not attacking me what
oh get the Relic get the
Relic
yeah Timber
on
them oh [\h__\h] they're doing it they're
absolutely doing
it Imperial
H we have another Relic down
here
uh okay then now I have two castles So
Close
by and
anyway I guess I'll
Garrison
wait o they're now they're going to
attack
it well I I made myself the Public Enemy
Number
One no I angered
dii no that wasn't a good
[Music]
idea e what do I
do d can like I don't have murder holes
and stuff so like the castle can't even
attack the ram if it's like right there
let them waste their resources but I'm
also wasting mine I I
not all right my my birker is going to
do this oh yeah they took down
the don't go too far no stay in the
protection of the
castle stay in the protection of the
castle make a couple more of these
Advance Imperial a well me too
[Music]
uh oh wait I have like 12 people not
doing anything uh [\h__\h]
uh sorry I need a I need a
[Music]
moment ch ch ch ch chill chill chill
chill
oh my economy is so useless I'm so
useless
[Music]
uh
H my Mele armor at the blacksmith so is
it do I remember which one was the
blacksmith this was hores where by the
way I want to build some night
blacksmith who's the
[Music]
blacksmith
oh ah Relic picked
up the Scout is like forever
lost how what should I what should I
like make their formation be so that
they maybe
guarding
okay okay just attack it if you want I
guess uh we can we can make him GA
here
uh
q
q k k k k kill make more forward Castle
what do you mean you mean like even
closer to them
[Music]
yeah now I really need some more Farms
because I just noticed how little food I
have holy [\h__\h] they're just letting me
do it they don't care what's what's the
what's the reason do they have a secret
or am I just too
powerful
little monk for
healing AI is dumb they sure seem to be
this time even oh wait the mother I have
to change here my little note about what
the difficulty is it's currently at hard
I
think see I'm already is so good at this
game I can play this game at
hard yeah Didn't I go one rank
[Music]
up okay uh I made I think I made a
couple archers where are they oh no wait
I was waiting for the upgrade
let me put them here but I know I could
put some into the castle I only change
speed it's still moderate really oh I
just changed the speed oh okay never
mind
then I
lied but that's already making it more
difficult changing the speed to
something I'm not used
to so I shall have your respect for that
let's make a couple of this and then
we'll add uh we'll put some mened arms
inside oh is that a castle that I see I
want I don't know I I don't think so I
actually don't think so no don't attack
don't attack don't attack yet keep it
there for a little bit until I have my
Rams once I have my Rams no
[Applause]
stay no you're going to die you idiot
okay The Archers though The Archers I I
I I made them
go wait Garrison in oh did I UNG
Garrison
[\h__\h] Garrison here
okay they faster uh when when there's
people in the ram right but are they
also stronger
I don't have the wood
for okay I really need wood did I make a
market no I don't think so Yoo I didn't
make a
market smart oh so
smart
mhm
mhm we need more villagers oh but we're
at almost at 100 nice nice nice nice
nice
oh I need to Market dou wish sh our
phone from behind walls or against walls
yeah what I keep on getting baited
somehow uh okay but I'm like almost
ready to attack
them I would
say this one stays here cuz otherwise
I'll forget to put someone inside this
one also they don't have but I don't
want to put my burer in there you know
what I mean I want to put the cheap
units in
there my Rally Point
true oh was it the
archers oh there you
[Music]
are I know I can put even more people in
but
me oh you guys can you build me a market
really
fast thank
you okay then I think I'm going to soon
be ready to
go I could make a few more cool
units wait they have archers what was
good against archers once again I'm
asking you
I am once again asking you to tell me
for the 500 time what's good against
archers
skirmishes squir me little skirmishes
skir which
wait which ones were
skirmishes these ones should I upgrade
them is it
worth is it worth upgrading the scrimmy
scrimmy
mans
wor
okay and when I stupid question but when
I'm like when I make them before
upgrading them do they uh the existing
ones get upgraded too
right yes
okay
house
okay what was I doing here
skirmishes get a couple of
those well I guess they're queued up
after the upgrade anyway so that's
that we have so many Rams let's [\h__\h]
go okay is not looking
good is this L this thing already too
far away what do you
think actually build one more house one
more for good measure
oh what was
that
what chill chill chill
chill okay okay
it's time it's
time
[Music]
[\h__\h] not good not very good
Stay Stay Stay Stay Stay keep keep
distance I guess
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] no no Stay Stay Stay Stay Stay Stay
Stay thank you
monkey oh
okay the they're doing their
thing okay not too bad actually not too
shabby might as well go for
it or should I I probably shouldn't I
probably
shouldn't oh
should well I guess I
am
H is that their
[Music]
Siege I can actually afford just doing
this right now
so okay I barely have any units but they
are not sending much
either mhm push push push push
push
go for it go for
it kill them all they must all be
eliminated and be taught that I am
number
one oh that might be actually a pretty
good match cuz it's going pretty
fast more more
more Town Center down unless they have a
second one this is easy easy oh is that
a town center it
is go for the Town
Center Ramy mamy go for the Town
[Music]
Center all
right nice building recognition oh thank
you so
much yeah like if it's like in this
shape it's very Town centery even in in
a different kind of look aesthetic oh no
oh no no no no no a he he got one he got
one he got one he got one that [\h__\h]
got he got one he did get one he did get
one oh that little [\h__\h] oh you little
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] you is the monk dead he's dead
right this time at least I saw it so I
have the situation under
[Music]
control yeah yeah yeah yeah let's go to
down you have no chance against my
Vikings
yeah kill the kill the archers
[\h__\h] ghost g go go skies go skies go
skies what's good oh he has
[Music]
applicated oh I really wasn't sure if it
was a good timing to go cuz I especially
killing those two castles they also
killed a lot of my units there but kept
on pushing actually the the short
distance was really
useful yeah
woohoo these are the voice LS we wanted
in World of Warships what what what do
you mean the the the the the dialogues
weren't good enough or my emotion behind
it yeah we can do heart I think I'm
ready for heart this wasn't so bad this
really wasn't so
bad now play the same Ai and difficulty
again but this time be better optimize
to kill him
sooner oh this is soon
enough I can do hard or explain Polaroid
again please okay are you guys okay if I
explain it one more time um really
quickly because some people missed it um
I explained at the beginning of the
stream that I prepared something for you
guys and for only in streams where I say
it applies in the PIN comment or
whatever um if you guys send a red Super
Chat and a number which uh you can take
from this C polar word menu sheet um
then I shall write you a
signature it's going to be like you know
like I it's going to be like I I'll take
it you know like like with me like this
you know properly sized though and I'll
put a sign over it and then you can have
basically your own signed waa waa signed
Polo
with the chicken of your choice here
take a good look I'll upload it later I
just don't have the time right now cuz I
want to upload it with a proper
explanation and then after the stream is
done all the signed Polaroids will be
uploaded for everybody to download and
have it in the original size here they
are good
nft if you don't want the same name uh
wait I didn't even decide if I want to
sign a
name I guess I could sign the name your
guys's names
too yeah I probably could I don't know
if there's enough space I'll have to
test it out today if there's enough
space
cuz
yeah yeah it might get a little bit too
cozy I I want to and then in that case
if you don't want the same name as your
username write something else otherwise
I'm just going to go with your YouTube
username and also only one per stream
you can't send two super
chats two red super chats and and get
another
one oh you still working my streams are
helping you my I'm super stressed out is
that making you feel better about your
own stress I'm happy to hear that I hope
that was a good enough explanation I'm
sorry my brain is really fried right now
yo it always looks the same here I'm
always behind on technology damn I'm
typically AI I would I would
assume units lost 72 yeah that's not so
good buildings lost
zero one one again 26
hey yeah I think moderate is no match
for me
anymore I still feel
nervous but I'm
fine yeah they don't Idol villagers they
they try to minmax everything I
guess try hard AI with
treaty I don't really think we need that
treaty cuz they're not that aggressive
[Music]
anyway two two two
two oh they actually got more Relic gold
yeah probably cuz they had the monastery
earlier survival to finish yes all
right oh their beginning was way more
efficient than
mine the very first like whatever 5
minutes or so yeah not not not even
under five minutes if you look
here like the first two minutes honestly
they probably have the first 15
villagers
down like nothing else ah ah it's cuz
Chinese level uh villager bonus ah right
right right that that's it
probably all right I'm feeling good
about this feeling very
good okay okay okay
okay all right hard for real now let me
change it in OBS AI difficulty
hard speed mm H
normal let me add
that all right all right random for for
me I'm I'm fine with them being random
but
me
me yeah let's stick with Vikings for now
maybe next AOE stream we can focus on a
different Sith and we keep on going like
that eh
should I change the map size even though
we're two
players it does seem quite tiny like I
wouldn't mind going a bit bigger but I
don't know if that's normal for when you
only play One Versus One do you really
go for a bigger
map what the hell two
players you can try small but tiny is
normal tiny is
normal like would in online matches
would people also go
just for the like the one that matches
the
best there's a ludicrous size map and
giant and
ludicrous
ludicrous Giga
[Music]
Mega something wild all right one versus
one tiny Arabia or Arena are the most
common rank
Maps ar oh and we
should are people like actually choosing
the maps or are they randomizing them or
does like each person choose one and
then it randomizes between those
Maps
Arabia this one
huh we can can we can choose
Arabia random but ban pick oh yeah map
pools I know I know there's map pools I
just wonder what what the usual way of
doing it is all right then if that's the
case it's the most played by far I don't
think I ever played before it has no
water
though no water so Vikings again
although I really don't mind playing my
Vikings on on on land
only oh more orders holy [\h__\h]
where holy [\h__\h] my ah yeah I didn't
expect it to go that stons holy [\h__\h] uh
you know in exchange for signing these I
might not do as much tangents and
chitchat on the red super chats as I
usually do cuz it's already going to
take time anyway to sign
them oh my God I just yeah I just
checked the
stalks through the roof you guys really
want your wa signature thank
you that's fair right okay
I got more Super Chat than during my
third
anniversary for real for real what the
[\h__\h] don't tell don't tell everybody
about this Strat holy
[\h__\h] I figured it out I cracked the
system I cracked the
code ultimate
stons okay ah let's
go Vikings all the way cumans [\h__\h] cumans
[Music]
cumans
butter
it's not German no no it's like no nor
right what what was it Old Norse
language yeah matter some of the words
are similar though cuz they all um in
the end come from Latin and I have
learned Latin in school
before but I gave up I was in a language
Focus school before going to the art
school yeah and if it wasn't for Latin I
think I would have been
fine if the if like the first language
you have to learn besides English and
German wouldn't be Latin I think I think
it would have gone better cuz Latin is
so
difficult I feel like other languages I
would have picked up better but the fact
is they do that um
because it's like the base for so so
many other
languages you know Bo
boing Lumber cam it's so far away is
there nothing closer it's so
far I don't see anything else I guess up
here [\h__\h] they're both pretty
far both pretty
far and yeah so I was doing Latin for
how long was it a year and a half or so
and then I switched school I think
something like that why are they
spreading out so much again Mama
[Music]
Mama I think Arabic is more difficult
than that it could be probably yeah but
like from the choices like here in
Europe it it's quite common to go for
Latin in schools like that
here but you
know
wait 1 2 3 4 uh wait wait wait wait wait
uh
and so shouldn't there be more there
there don't go for the board yet or
should I ah
[\h__\h] terrible terrible terrible terrible
[Music]
Terri not efficient enough triming
efficiency must be
better
[\h__\h]
don't
no yeah yeah yeah the beginning is so
important it's so important it's just so
important can't get it wrong I see the
boar go on go on this sheep please this
this very specific
sheep screaming how to play better I
feel it I feel it oh another Bo oh gold
okay where are the berries where the
[\h__\h] are the berries oh where are the
Berries gagn Mother gagn
Mother they're oing wait these are not
sheep these are
pigs uh seven seven 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 Uh
Wood uh what it R oh my God I remembered
I remember she
remember
uh
okay oh more piggies go over here before
I lose
them okay okay okay we're getting there
my chat broke it's not moving I see it
moving in OBS though
timii the berries must be here I no we
there
they
um that is the fourth one so the next
one gets the
boore the Next Room brings the board
before we're done with the chore of the
PE I'm actually doing The Scouting
myself this time holy moly holy moly
wait let me refresh the chat for one
second this this pausing does not
count okay here we
go all right I see you guys again thank
you for Super Chat oh my god what have I
done what have I
done
what no no
no I clicked into the
window I made him go somewhere
else
okay run run run run run run run
run R run run run you better
[Music]
run yeah get him get
him Bard down Bard down I repeat Bard
down Relic
found
okay okay okay uh ah ah q q ah ah house
next one house next one make house next
one make
house my my my thoughts are so oaba like
make house chop wood
Q who
me I'm just trying my best
here any more BS a there
[Music]
okayi what's
next you want to get them the boore I
don't know man C how about no that's the
wrong thing uh what I what am I supposed
to
do
mail the mail I forgot about the mail
it's okay though we still have like so
many
animals
parore K well the problem with K is I I
even for unarchived ones I actually need
permission for the instrumentals and if
they're not on K of fun K of fun saving
our butts by the way then it's kind of
difficult
cuz we would have to directly contact
creator of the instrumental or make our
oh which cost money
money
money in a rich man's
world I know I know gold not necessary
but it's right there I'm going to put
the next one on the
stones great Age of Empires hell yeah I
love Age of Empires I also want to try
civilization
[Music]
though never play C Age of Empires I
played when I was younger is that the
right thing no [\h__\h] what is the
E what was I saying ah I played Age of
Empires when I was Babu Babu
child before we're done with the Sheep
now perfect perfect lineup
WWA get the board so that you know
everybody can help out with
[Music]
that yeah and
shoot
okay H an know an know I I also know
that from my childhood but I uh
oops I didn't
ever you're going to go up there aren't
you okay do whatever you want I never
played
it
okay
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] it's not ideal that's okay
wait they're
already is this still not enough just
going to love that Super Chat whoa whoa
whoa whoa
why that'll attack soon
oh that's wood
too the bushes are also wood oh are
[Music]
they
uh wa don't forget the ship oh it's all
gone okay okay okay
okay we have to get rid of this
otherwise we can't build on it but I
know I know that unlik with this wood
the ones that are standing like alone
once you have them chop down you can
already build something on top of them
haa wow Sugo is superior knowledge
very wholesome oh really and now I'm so
curious can't believe you're attacking
her you little
[\h__\h] what why would you do that are you
going to do that they're really
attacking what that's not you're not
supposed to do that you're supposed to
be scouting you're just a scout
uh
what they're going to [\h__\h] ruin
me all right keep them busy there at
least they're raiding
me no I think we don't have to bring
everybody inside at this point but help
them help
them holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
holy I see okay that's already the
difficulty uh difference cuz I've never
experienced that before
at least they like mostly occupy
themselves with one
thing oh are they
leaving are they
leaving okay then I oh no they're here
they're definitely here ooh
where did they
go
oh
[Music]
oh I can't even survive that at
all stay here for
now wait oh my God my ftil
[Music]
age help
help I feel like I have to redo yeah
yeah I had no other choice yeah making
something else that was my only
choice oh gag
M do you like my
pattern
I like it gag
matter I can
redo what I just did yeah gag
matter fix my
oopsy early Outpost yeah maybe Outpost
this
time I I I feel an immediate difference
in difficulty that's for
sure 1 2 3 4
six
gagag for the next
one got to try to get to FAL as early as
possible but the I also I mean I still
need the people on the
wood
I don't
[Music]
know I mean there definitely some things
that where I wasn't like fast enough so
maybe we can fix
that wait you didn't discover them
is is a mill now too
early but I'm building a house that's
okay that's okay that's
okay
[Music]
[\h__\h]
but I can't afford the mill I need more
wood I need more
wood okay that's okay like I was
supposed to put four people in Wood
anyway so
fine let me get this one close
by damn that was so scary what do I do I
need to build the barracks earlier or I
I need to do
watchtowers oh there's a
bear
um barracks and feudal fast yeah 500
food yeah why that's so stressful oopsie
a
oh sorry I'm so sorry it's not working
it's not doing the thing that I wanted
to do
what cuz I
can't matter shouldn't have built the
farm yet anyway cuz I still have
berries go to the
berries wait before I go to the Bears
shouldn't I have sent one to the
boar also I guess now we could get Loom
cuz we might need it in this case
yeah okay let's get the
bo get the
bo bring him over
here matter
and I think there's one too much
here
B oh
buty that's why people do Scout rashes a
lot yeah I I
know it's good this way I'm learning how
to protect myself against that I
guess [\h__\h] that really [\h__\h] me up that
really messed my my whole everything up
cuz the things that I could create were
too weak
who gag matter 56 the things I could
create were too weak and I I I I I
wasn't able
to you
know be fast enough with that [\h__\h]
but
[Music]
let's make
one soon they're all going to be farming
after the board they're all going to be
farming red Scout yeah well he's he's
Scout now he's really just scouting
alone I can tell the difference when
they're alone they're just here for fun
just to
report actually
build
[Music]
Min always keep them queued up also I
need another house
soon don't go for stone
Que
let's build my
Barracks I need lots of lots and lots ah
ah no wood lots of wood and lots of food
that's what I
need
[Music]
the lack of wood
hurts
okay oh
man at Dark Age priority is food
villagers wood
houses I'm reporting so many on the wood
[Music]
ah okay
well these milia are really [\h__\h] weak
but it's all all I can do but they also
take 20 gold what the [\h__\h] N I can't
really invest in
[Music]
that feudal first right okay
well I'm almost there I'm almost there
they have advanced when they Advance
man okay let me stop creating for a
moment there we
go one of
[Music]
you and now that we're advancing maybe
now we can go for gold
oh okay I didn't see I had so many cute
up oopsie all right now we're going for
feudal
age I don't know if I'm faster than last
time
but I feel generally it might be a
little bit better should I make a tower
a watchtower what do you think
yeah
[Music]
uh wait wait wait wait wait
who's
who
Spar
stop spares spars Tower really useless
we not help against
okay
done
this is really efficient you can't tell
me this is not efficient what I'm doing
here woo wo wo wo fast
fast who else
um whoever else is left you can go work
on that actually no you're so close
let's make another
house did we Scout enemy my Scout is
doing something here at the corner of
the map you little [\h__\h] I have advanced
okay
uh
sparman we have to be ready to
defend also we could Advance the axe the
lumber help on the
gold on the
wood make one ooh no
space uh
okay who no no no wood again not too
many might want to scout them I I am
relying on my Scout but maybe I
shouldn't
[Music]
be oh he found some cool stuff
though
ah I tapped
out okay how's it going how's it going
how's it
going we got we got some people now all
right I'm I'm ready I can defend myself
woohoo let's
go just a few okay just like five or so
then I can probably defend myself also
my chat is gone there you
go upgrade farms at the Mill
oh plus o okay I never did that I never
knew about that upgrade thank you build
stable oh yeah oh
yeah stable maybe
here we need the buildings we need the
buildings right I forgot about the
buildings ah no wood for real there we
go archery
range
uh more holy [\h__\h] my my
wood usage is so high like I'm barely
keeping
up is this one exhausted have to build
over it
okay should I make some archers or
skirmishes we're playing against what is
it I already
forgot cast H archers few archers just
just a couple I can't even make that
many just a few just a
few move the lumber Camp up okay um wood
is almost gone up here anyway though
maybe I'll make one down
here houses
ah okay going immediately down into c i
I see I see I see what was going on
there holy [\h__\h] ah we have not fallen
behind
yet
honey they always spread out so much
holy [\h__\h] their their stuff looks so
cool what's their specialty in like
units I
wonder let's make one
more okay but my I'm catching up with
wood looking good I need gold now
actually M where Sith I I don't
know I don't know I forgot humans oh
yeah cumans that was
it humans dis
man strong
Cavalry so what do I
want are my are my Burks enough once I
get
there Advan the castle age me too me too
almost wait for
me spaman
Pikeman okay for now just for
security we we'll we'll make a few more
cuz I'm [\h__\h]
scared wait
skirmishes spaman and
infantry W with the fast Castle Strat
not so much right now this is not really
fast come on come on come on and then I
make
castle I need I need a castle for my B
so but I have
nobody nobody available right now
there okay
Castle
uh should haveed more St attack oh
that's okay I can handle
that I can handle this little baby
raid it's over it's over it's so it's
over it's so
over
yeah [\h__\h] this it's so
over I don't have enough materials to
build the
castle they are currently killing
me the only I think what I got to do in
that case is raid him earlier raid him
before he can raid me I don't
know
ah
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] scouting could help you know what
they're going to use
well well even no matter what I wouldn't
have been prepared I
think
Walling I don't think I would have had
enough resources for Walling either
there's so much open space I couldn't
have walled up that much I
[Music]
think damn I have no problem against
moderate but but hard is pretty
hard Walling with my
houses h on this map though maybe I
should try a different
map oh this isn't even Arabia I just
noticed right this is not
Arabia
[\h__\h]
M I'm drinking the fancy five euro water
from
Voss damn maybe I should go hard but
speed back too
casual but I mean it will that change
that much I want to get the nice in
between you know of
difficulty ring the no no I'm not
ringing it cuz it's like I I can't I
can't defend myself against this and
hiding everybody like they're just going
to destroy buildings and N this is like
over keep the
speed add one bot as allies well no I
have to be able to deal one versus one I
have to deal with that I have to be able
to to handle
it hard will push but won't follow
well need to get to feudal faster
wait let me
see you have too many unspent resources
need more
production unspent I was I was
struggling hard to get the wood up and
now we're just getting the gold up and
the stone was kind of
uh close a close call there as
well until
[Music]
now
yeah food is good food is
good early aggression on mother oh
man
skirmishers maybe it's just because it's
the cumans maybe against nonhumans I
could do
it you do the early SC that's what I'm
saying yeah maybe I should
just but wait the
scouts for more Scouts I need to be
already in in feudal right and then I
need to make
my my Scouts here 80 meat okay they just
need
meat is this just a thing that humans do
or would any civilization do this to
me practice your build orders
M yes I I shall practice
more handicap is a good way to cover the
difficulty Gap now I would like
something in
between
crossbow that's exactly why feudal is
vital you all the axes mhm
mhm cumans is also Rush
focused your economy is great with more
production buildings and walls to stop
them for a while I could counter
attack got to spend your
resources okay okay
um should I restart again we should
restart as many times it takes us to win
this I'm not ready maybe a bit more
pausing in between then so that I can
get the most efficiency from you guys
don't restart no yes restart it's not
good we must make it
better well the problem now is I can't
see it yet so I can't make a house wall
properly
yet
G
okay no no it must be two and
one I have learned that on YouTube which
one are you taking
okay two house one
house
food oh yeah I could Scout with this the
these are not cheap these are pigs but I
get what you
mean you better find me those yeah yeah
yeah thank
you oink oink oink
oink gag matter 1 2 3 4 six okay next
one goes on the
wood Yeah by food
doco oh was it the house first I think
it's I think it's Lumber Camp
first found the
boar ah create those just what what are
you doing what are you
doing I can't see I have something in my
eye no no no no no bore yet it's too
early I can't see wait my
[Music]
ey yeah Scott was taking a break that
little
[\h__\h] there's no breaks for you I don't
understand why you were you thought you
could take a break right now okay I
think I think I got the the rid of the
cat
hair come
on I'm not losing my pigs right they're
this one's this one's
chilling
wait come on come on come on come on
come on what's our strategy this time
again uh better more buildings using my
resources
and P Pik spare what was it
uh faster feudal age to get more units
but um or attacking with my own
Scouts both fudal K close to 21
I'll try my
best
[Music]
yeah gag matter I need there we go
there's the
mill oh maybe it's time for a [\h__\h] I
missed timing I Wish I Could Turn Back
Time If I Could Turn Back Time well
there's a pig
here come on piggy come on
piggy it wasn't quite time for the board
anyway if you ask me because my my pig
was just too late to come
back
okay
um
berries four un peig rest no it's free
wait there we go guess the boar is
bigger so it needs more people on
him Barracks next to your houses
okay uh
Barracks okay
glad to see you playing this again did
you see last week I was playing it too
that was last week right time passes so
fast it almost feels
like matter it almost feels like wait
should I keep them actually for the next
Bo I'll get the boore I'll get the
boore last week we had the tournament
right and me practicing um like bigger
skirmishes like two versus two versus
two
okay could make one my
house kind of trying to
wall don't die don't
[Music]
die I was trying to get it away from
it w why would you have to die why did
she have to die oh man okay
uh should I make a
farm I'll make a
farm
here should I make some miltia now I
feel like it's a
waste I guess I could have hid her in
the
TC right I yeah I think it's a waste
okay okay
okay okay maybe I should close the PO
submission no it's okay guys if I can't
finish them today then that's that's
what that's how it
is uh can we advance 5 I'm so far from
advancing yeah bye okay then we got to I
got to step up my game I got to step up
my food
game
wait are they ignoring the other Bo
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
up
yeah make a wooden gate next to gold
mines here I don't know I would have to
wall up so much
anyway like I don't know if that really
makes
sense
[Music]
a oh [\h__\h] Queen I was already right you
guys have like such a good overview over
this damn what do I do with
you another
Farm may cause no
harm we're going
feudal and then when I'm
feudal I built the the buildings fast
right uh what's the first thing I want
to build cuz we already have
Barracks that's not not a feudal
building anyway huh I never built the
barracks before feudal age before until
today archers archers stable archers
okay okay okay okay okay we can do this
can we
I want to win this time I want to lose
again if I get like through the rating
then I feel like I'll be
fine come
on come
on
down yeah
yeah
okay I'm doing
it 800 200 okay we need gold now
to
uh mining
camp I'm being attacked
they're already
raining how are they already
raining okay ignore them ignore them for
now just got to build
fast what the
[Music]
[\h__\h]
man
uh skirmishes or
archers well
[Music]
archers don't sent
them span just spare Min
okay
oh they're doing it they're killing them
I love you guys ah go away get out of
here you want
some yeah okay there's
[Music]
more okay we scare them away they come
back okay okay
okay they're done here ah
ah ah wood
ah go
here what's going on no no no
no [\h__\h] [\h__\h] come back [\h__\h] Pik
p p
p yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah good stuff good
stuff okay God they're so slow on the
Pikes um it it was because uh no
houses okay we're fine now we're fine
now righted
uh uh H H wood wood uh okay next time I
have wood I'll make a I'll
make I'll make uh another Lumber Lumber
Farm okay we we're we're fine let me
Place one of these over here for
protection okay Lumber Camp
over I
guess maybe should have had it up there
okay okay okay we're kind of over over
the panicky rating period I got to fix
my unemployment I got to advance two
feudal age buildings wait wait wait what
am I what do I
need what can I build um uh nothing
[\h__\h] Fe feudal
AG no no what are you attacking it's
just here
[Music]
okay blacksmith blacksmith blacksmith
can I build it actually no no no no no
no [\h__\h] the the lack of wood
is ruining
[Music]
everything
sorry a
[\h__\h] we got we got a bit better
[Music]
though okay can we build it
now come on a bit more where is this
there you are okay come on come on give
me my blacksmith [\h__\h] A
houses
oh but house also takes wood no yeah I
was trying to save for the
[Music]
blacksmith
oh yeah yeah
ah
okay
okay once I have that we can
advance okay finally man
[Music]
man should I do loom it's kind of late
for it but might as well okay ah
yeah I'm so late on Stone but it's okay
we don't even need it
yet now it's
fine
okay oh
wait sorry
sorry
going to try to build a wall of houses
here hey my Scout is still alive
hooray I know I can cute him up but
I'm I'm
fine
okay MH
mhm advance to Castle age we're being
attacked no we're not being
attacked well my Scout at least found
like the whole map pretty
much and I have no one on no one idle we
have enough food
everything should I should I make some
more units or should I wait for my
castle and then make my B
ax I would say my personal choice would
be wait for the
castle can I get through here more units
more
units okay I'm going to make a few
more Castle Castle come on come on come
on
oh
uh uh uh
uh uh
uh no how could they have so
many
ah
[Music]
yeah it's
over what you're supposed to produce
units all the time know I mean there
were also some people say no no need for
anymore so you
know guess there was need for more but
they also they're also using they're
using skirmishers is Pikeman really the
most effective against uh skirmishers at
least at the at this point when that's
all I can
produce without any Knights
yet no that's what I thought they don't
look like they would be a good match I
watched by the way I watched the counter
video before and I played the counter
tutorial but I do not
remember time to go back to
modate
maybe damn it's such a huge difference
modate was no
problem they want to scout their units
to counted them wait they don't change
it each time right it's always the same
so far no I mean now they definitely
seem to have a bit more like before they
attacked mostly with horses but when I
was able to counter the horses I guess
that's when they decided to make
skirmishes no no not last time was
crossbows well and mostly like horses
cuz they already got me in the stage of
their horse
raing this is like this is like
already
War by
my uh judge judgment look at the amount
of people This Is War This Is War we're
in Castle age we didn't even get to
Castle age before I
think this is an army we got through the
rating so we already
improved
je
okay oh God I don't know it's so
difficult what do I do
I
think I'll give it one one more try but
I feel like I can't at my current skin
level I can't do it just I just feel
like I can't I hit a wall
again maybe I'll change to Tans I don't
know will that be better at least I know
how to play totin more or
less is it my Vikings are my Vikings not
good
enough
I I could do some
handicap no it's not the
SI I improve they're just so fast and
they're
smart like how can I compete with a
computer
brain do I resign or do I quit there a
difference right in this case
[\h__\h] this is
rough okay we're going to do one more
match but I'm going to do a little
handicap
maybe
oh should I do a handicap or should I
change something
else maybe is there something
else I changing game speed down huh that
that could
help you could give yourself an allet
that's not fair though two versus one
that's not fair that's just too
easy okay let's try let's try this maybe
we get lucky maybe we get a better map
too better map for
me
Koreans what's
this
Goose cute okay
wait
H see how fast I am oh my God she is
speed she is
lightning what kind of map is
this
okay I already faster did you notice is
this AR Rabia now oh
okay find me some more goose Mr
Scout no no not that one this one yes
yes yes yes yes yes six seven there's a
boar
okay where the geese where the goose Gee
Gee right
geese seven wait seven
seven wood
right I could the wood close by too if I
wanted to but wood wood
wood yeah okay uh uh Lumber camp this
looks to me currently like the closest
Big
Forest oh there might have been one here
oh there is a there is that
uh another
boar where are the key still why are you
hiding them from me I need them not for
H ooh berries fruit Bush but these are
yellow what kind of berries are those
supposed to
be
honk
honk one more to
food
yeah is is a
[\h__\h] it's enough people
no
Three
Bananas I know maybe mangoes how do how
do M mangoes
grow
do mangoes grow in
bushes six and is it not six maybe it's
five
two six okay now it's six
[\h__\h] thought it
was six okay now it's
six where is he going he didn't find my
other GE I should have scouted with one
Goose big regretti
spaghetti
yeah wait what now ah there [\h__\h] I
missed the
timing I missed the timing I I missed
other timings too so I'm redoing it
okay
I
cute okay hopefully nobody shoots down
my
Goose W with the micro moves shall I
micromanage your life too H well I first
need to learn how to micromanage my own
life
honestly honestly so true now this is
four now we have five
just like a real mom I'm not I'm not I'm
not anything close to a mom though oh
look at all the colors of the trees wow
I thought Arabia map was a
desert I was
[Music]
wrong well maybe I'll make it here I
don't know how ah maybe I shouldn't have
it's closer
but although no that's fine I thought I
thought the map was uh kind of like in a
different
direction might be fine cuz like the map
ends here it's a small Forest
[Music]
but how's how's the goose doing maybe
Goose maybe Goose come over here now cuz
it's about
time it's about
time
still haven't found the
others fly you could be faster
N
Fly Fly you
fools people said houses and it's not
really part of the order right now just
want you to know okay but I'm doing it
because you guys said houses but like if
you actually follow the right order the
most ideal one you're not supposed to do
that just
saying I want to build a mill but it's
not time
anyway boy oh we're lucky that the bo
what's your
problem no no come on bring me
this what's going
on
okay okay uh now we can make a
mill
okay oh this is fine okay B
matter b matter go
okay it worked nobody
died I get the second one going to go
get the second
one up
see I'm doing two things at once
wow
no was close he's alive H
H stay alive stay alive I got no food
Mama
M okay I forced them to drop off quickly
Quicky four
strats okay so what do we uh what are we
going to do what are we going to do what
are we going to
[Music]
do join on the wood Maybe
so far so
good gag
matter definitely need a lot of a lot
more food hi
Scout
don't don't do anything
funny I want
to Darkness
matter I want to build farms but it's
not
really time for that yet is it
well never found those Goose
GE they're probably
like close by
but no
idea falling
behind
well yeah my Scout is on
auto can you peek the enemy can't see
much my Scout is
[\h__\h] not doing the best job here gag
matter oh
okay they wouldn't be
J if it wasn't for my shitty Scout and
they could do even more geese but that's
not the case
unfortunately there's a boar under the
TC
b b what how did it what how when
what
what Mama
Mia what is the first one oh I guess
they gave up on him when I when we were
protecting the dude from the second
boar
TN
okay so this
now what's
that
what are these animal
sounds is there another board that's
alive
even oh it's the male ah okay I I
welcome
that I don't mind that
one FAL
age I'm I'm I'm I'm there soon too I'm
going to be there
[Music]
soon
[\h__\h] join the wood for now wait wait
okay let's go let's go let's go cancel
cancel cancel go straight to feudal
age
and then make some
more
[\h__\h] Barracks build
okay they're running out of ber
soon who are we fighting oh yeah Koreans
they have like some special what was it
the uh Rams or what they had some super
strong something or was it a
boat I the bar wagons yeah yeah yeah
yeah something on Wheels I remember the
wheels and what did I counter that with
I had experience with that cuz I I
fought with my totons against the
Koreans
ones oh back in the old days in the in
the
war versus Tans versus Koreans yes yes
yes those were some tough times for me
and my
family we struggled so hard and we
fought so
hard you have no idea these kids
nowadays I have just no
idea what we had to deal with back in
the day hey
skirmishers are you
sure skirmishers are archery right
Archer
range
yeah
who I'm I'm I'm
Kaba in the end it it did indeed
matter cuz we won the
war
I CAU them right as it
happened oh God okay quick break think
thinking
break
waragon is a castle unit ah so they
can't build it until quite a bit later
[Music]
okay more on wood and
gold more on wood true I'll make
um Bo H I can't build another Camp right
[Music]
now uh go here while when you reach it
maybe you'll be able to build an y yeah
yeah they they have arriv
arrived it's
skirmishers they rash for skirmishers
H can you do something about this
dude that's all I
have
oh there's another
[Music]
one oh by the
way uh are we still on hard but casual
speed
right [\h__\h] fre
and there's more I feel like I failed
again do you think my Scout alone can
handle it I don't even know where he is
right now where did he go a there he is
should I do the the lower ones
first come on come on come on come on be
fast he can handle it but he's slow
oh and I don't have materials to build a
new
thing can't make more don't have a don't
have the the H horsey place
yet they can take them B you think
so
oh can try they can they can kind of
scared them at
least
ma
ma I hate that they run away like how
dare you beat me like that you little
shits [\h__\h]
you I can't go back to go back
to we scared them a little bit but we
scared them [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
you stop that
now can I can I build it now I still
175 175 Scout you're my best friend
right now thank you for being so close
instead of
scouting wait girl if you go after
him he's going to run away
kill him kill him kill him fast kill him
fast so ridiculous this is so
ridiculous
okay I
think I've protected
myself po
properly yeah good job you guys are the
best hey MVP goes to my to my villagers
Scout you you will stay here for
protection cuz I'm scared
shitless I survived the rain I survived
the rain
oh
H uh
ah uh uh scout scout scout scout maybe
I'll attack with them even maybe I will
oh they only cost food oh I can make so
many with them actually why they only
cost food that's right Scouts are
op at least for rating at least for
rating okay let's get those villagers
back
um let's work on the
wood and maybe one Stone Farm wouldn't
hurt soon or will would it no
would more units how many do we want do
we want to raid
them should I raid them is that our
goal I do I do need them on the goal for
advancing
should we go
rating I need five Scouts for ra but I
also need to be able to look at
it I don't know if I I have the
multitasking skills for
that I give it a
goal
okay here we go wait how was it what was
it R uh
okay attack attack attack
everything just for
fun we need we need to win
this I don't want to
stop I want to I don't want to stop
today on a on a loss oh [\h__\h] oh
[Music]
oh maybe maybe that wasn't actually so
effective oh wait kill him kill him
first I'm actually glitching them they
can't run
away big
cusa okay should I send these to
actually or not oh wait don't send
them ah never mind that's just a normal
Scout he won't attack I
think check their Woodland it's to see
careful to
see no
okay okay let's stop that for now then
then they're just for protection for now
uh make a
house some food enough enough of being
inefficient but they make me inefficient
cuz they make me like focus on other
things that I don't even want to focus
on why are you chopping wood over there
what the [\h__\h]
yeah
huh what is that lady
doing I don't recall giving you that
permission okay okay it's good that I
still had some people left
over don't worry guys I will protect
you
[Music]
no no no no it's okay it's okay don't
worry about it don't worry about it
don't worry about it don't worry about
it I'll I'll replace you you're very
replaceable oh my
God barely ha they coming with reps you
kidding
me that's ridiculous
us a [\h__\h] Ram
really I killed my
hores the
audacity what do I do what do I do what
do I do yeah the Rams are not even that
bulky it's okay it's okay um um what do
I do bring the Bell Garrison for real
but I will stop all my
Productions I don't want
to not everyone is in danger either oh
there's some dude here
[Music]
actually
okay I'll survive it but it would cost
oh does the Town Center only shoot when
I'm ringing the
bell oh no they ruined it they ruined it
all why is this worker so close
did they build so close to me
n [\h__\h] they must they must have
something here wait they must have some
Barracks or something
there my
[Music]
Villers [\h__\h] I hate
this why are they doing this to
me why am want St do this where's my
horse then my horse die
what all right it's over it's
[Music]
over there never mind never mind
that I can't I Can't Fight Hard oh hey
hooray we're Castle AG let's
go um Town Center is burning [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h] this it's so over and I can't I
can't fix
this I can't fix this un ring the bell
why oh because otherwise they all die in
there or
what it's over anyway it's
over he fix it try fixing
it it's so
over it's so
over oh
man I'll practice more off
stream and next week we're going to play
again we got to have her signing session
now why did I what have I
done thank you guys for helping me thank
you guys for the support thank you uh to
the Koreans for blasting my
ass I know a few words in Korean maybe
maybe if I would have tried to
communicate in Korean I could have told
them be friend take down sword
and then we could have had peace I
forgot all my Korean
[Music]
[Laughter]
so oh
man you would think my Korean lessons
would have paid off
here my poor ass yeah it was fun though
like what I don't understand why there's
so many like diffic diffic difficulty
modes but they're still so far apart
seemingly oh my God I think I need to
turn off the super chats it's like
enough oh let me turn it
off
uh H thank you guys for jumping on this
new thing that's so shiny AKA my polar
RS they're so
shiny no let them no I I'll open them
again when I catch up like holy [\h__\h]
what have I
done yeah I feel like people don't if
people just come into the stream like my
usual kfps are just a little bit late
they'll be like what what what happened
why is there like five million ride
super chats what happen did she cry were
people trying to cheer her
up what's going on I like your AOE two
strs thank
you can you show them again I will I
will I will cuz I'm going to be signing
them now anyway um okay let me I will I
guess maybe just stay here cuz I have to
show
Photoshop rates for improving so much in
A2
obviously remember to see what units
your opponent is using in build
counter okay okay that is definitely
self I didn't do prior to
today I shall I shall work on that
sure
now okay this will
be how do I do this this is the first
time I'm doing this so maybe these super
chats are not on Hol lier yet right cuz
if they were on H lier I could sort them
by Reds
only
let's see maybe in the future if it's
really always this much I'll even do a
separate signing stream cuz Mama
Mia they are okay but they're not like
in the usual place they might be on the
I go on the start website and then I go
to my current stream oh my
God in if if if I was Japanese I uh this
stream made me millionaire haha
okay then I'll sort them by the Reds and
only do the Reds until the or should I
do it the other way around actually that
might be faster so the non- Reds at
least get their thank
yous no never mind cuz sometimes people
followed up their Reds with the numbers
in smaller super chats and most of them
just want a polar red anyway all right
all right all right so I'll go from the
top so for example somebody says number
18 so I bring out the 18
[Music]
but I'll show you the screen just one
second uh trying to figure this
out
uh window window maybe I can just
capture
[Music]
and I felt so strong when I was playing
moderate and then and then they hit me
in the
face of that difficulty now I feel I
don't feel so skilled anymore but I will
not let
this ruin my
experience with a
okay got to go step by
step make improvements one after another
all right this
is uh the first one so what I'm going to
do is actually I should add a little
background too
probably
[Music]
let me see what I
have in my resources cuz I'm not going
to cover up all of
it let's
[Music]
do
oh bgm too sorry I'm like I'm like all
over the place right now here how about
how about this make it big oh
[\h__\h] make it
bigger this okay this can be our
background for
today is this idea based on a cheis yes
exactly and a music music
is let's do some
chill chill Cafe music jazz not quite
Jazz okay and I need my pan good that I
actually really recently bought new pen
nibs for my welcome tablet pen because I
think chunky wonky may have like bit
bitten the uh
nib out of my pen not she hasn't bitten
it off I feel like she she bit on it and
then like ripped it
out cuz like at some point it was gone
and I couldn't find it
anymore had to buy new ones she nibbled
the nib hi Raiders oh you have arrived
just when I finished AOE I hope you
don't mind but I'm doing a new thing now
going to
sign um some checkes for you guys that
have been ordered
one second the cable my microphone cable
cuz I hung it up is like in the way of
my tablet also I can't really move my
tablet closer to me anymore so my setup
is not really ideal I have to change
this okay this is number 18 for V
faction let me get like a the right pen
signing pen for now we'll just do
black maybe like in other times I can
try to find like a cool golden color as
if I had signed it with a golden
pen
uh how
big like
[Music]
this yeah that looks like I sign I'm
signing it with a sharpie
right
[\h__\h] my my setup is really bad oh like
this
maybe checky for the chickens ah but no
I like that the the P the Polaroid P
fits into the K of P so well so it's
called K of Polaroids okay so I think I
would do my signature at the bottom on
your name here or the other way around
maybe
here kind of
messy oh it's too fat
actually I wanted a little bit little
bit
[Music]
finner
uh oh God
it's easier to sign with real
pens this is
fine okay n then
four
B AC there you go did I write it
correctly yeah so this is how it will
turn oh wait F I forgot
myself I forgot
myself I will not like take a new
picture uh for each checky per day but
uh
um just
one per stream oh don't look ah don't
look I want to take a
[Music]
picture
and cheese okay and
then I'll place myself
[Music]
here ah it's still
there there you
go
that's a little bit of preparation work
but is this the small one or the big one
oh it's fine I go behind I signed over
myself ooh I didn't consider that
okay sign can
go there's not much space maybe like
here or
here
smaller also you know the heart is
actually just an extra that's not part
of my official signature I shouldn't do
it better the without actually how about
like this that's good it really looks
like I'm looking at
[Music]
you now I actually I don't know what
happens if I if I save this do you guys
see the window where I save it I would
hope
not
oh game is still
[Music]
open let me let me do this let me sound
and save it as a
PNG make a
folder V faction V be faction and then
you guys can find it later I'll upload
it
separately okay
nice next next see this will take plenty
of time so I'm not going to like react
to anything you're saying in the super
chats you're not saying much
anyway
um can I you guys you guys don't mind if
I only write the
name each time or do I feel like that's
plenty personalized this
it if I just write the name and keep the
sign
here that's fine that's okay that's
fine okay okay cuz that would be a lot
more time
necessary okay then what do we have a
number
threee you would like to have a number
[Music]
threee oh where is the number threee
here number threee is would I like to
call an Elvis
chicken uh okay you know what in this
case I'll have a very iation where I
look to the other
side I do have one
actually here oh too
big cuz this one's on the opposite side
we want it to look well
balanced ooh is Elvis chicken singing
something for
[Music]
me give me some dance moves too while
you're at it so this is for Jacob 47 out
should I write Jacob or this the whole
name Jacob what did you say whole
name or just
[Music]
Jacob
ah is he here to answer I don't see
him don't please don't write my fullone
name on mine okay okay yeah that will be
good for you guys to add next time if
you order
one I'll just
try as much as I
can at least I have enough
space please write full name on my I
will only write ja it monkey that's
where I
ended okay and I can save
[Music]
that
nice I think the signature
can although yeah I can stay it doesn't
take too much Jacob 47
out maybe I'll get more practice in this
later on for now I'm like
scrambling
who knows maybe this is actually faster
than reading and and reacting to normal
red super
chats n oh Nexus FL flight to
fancy
four wait I'll I'll write this first and
I'll change the picture of
Nano
lights it doesn't
fit maybe I'll do two rows
four
Glo
flights off
fancy name to Long help and you have a
number 19 as a ma enjoyer
[Music]
ooh cute we got our first kfp chicken m
cool idea for redas
right I won't do it all the time just on
on certain
streams I don't like the the
why
[Music]
okay oh she's blushing is she going to
clean my room please clean my room while
you're
[Music]
here
did I write it correctly flannel Flights
of Fancy flannel flight of
fancy all right that's already free
super chats taken care
of you're welcome what are you going to
do with the saved images I'm going to
upload them for you guys to
download now we have Brandon with a
number three oh another
Elvis all
right
[Music]
of
Brandon maybe in the future cuz this is
the first time I'm doing it so everybody
went all in on it but maybe in the
future there won't be so many then I can
try to change things a little bit more
and have
like different pngs of myself in the
back or or change my signature like
position and like rewrite it and all
that make it a little bit more
individually but for today this will do
these are first editions
yeah for Brandon honestly I think I'm
really faster than when I would normally
react to a r Super
Chat
shocking zipley with a number two ah
frog chcken frog
chcken frog
chicken all right wait I'll make a bit
more in side
[Music]
okay I love frog chicken look how
sparkling the eyes are they're like
[Music]
P they're going much quicker than
expected yeah after the initial setup so
this is
for
ziping must be
here you get a heart must be cuz there's
so much space must be a froggy wa
enjoyer if your name is so short you
might get a heart or something else a
star or
something okay next one is
unknown with the number one ooh our cute
sailor
chicken
cute basic
basically upcoming Viking
chicken very on theme
today I hope this way everyone who
didn't get a signature from me yet cuz
they were too slow for like let lied
Edition gets one through this wouldn't
that be
lovely nice handwriting no I can write
prettier but like usually signatures are
like pretty messy
anyway okay saved I don't know if I
really have to like do this each time
like clear the window
but for now we're doing like this next
is Sky with number
[Music]
12 ah it's this
one
[Music]
M you should I make two hours no I I
maybe I'll make another pose I'll do
another pose I'll strike a pose really
[Music]
quickly
wait I'll strike a post just for
[Music]
you okay I hope that looks
good whoop whoop who just for this one
cuz this is this one's in the middle if
anyone else also chose this one you'll
get the
[Music]
same taada
actually using that weird hand pose hey
but it works it's like a like you fell
on my lap and I'm like surprised like oh
hi are you're photo bombing actually
that's so
cute
and the signature though is kind of
difficult I guess it can also stay there
cuz like I can't really put it in the
middle maybe I could
this is for sky
right it's good there to be honest
yeah
here you get a
sky cute
hope you like it thank
you Sky okay
safe beautiful I wonder if there's
others who chose that one now we
have as much as I would like a nine or
18 I'll follow myelf given title and
choose 11 11 for Nathan
[Music]
coton 11 11 ooh 11 a you cuz you're the
home
Baker
oh you get one of
these
[Music]
M
cute that one is so cute you look like
you're working in in the in an open
Buffet at a res at a a
hotel okay now we switch to this one
again what will you cook for me can you
can you make me some
pancakes it's like he's stopping me from
cooking why would he do
that maybe I should teach you for a
naan can I get the full
name yeah
yes there we
go
okay beautiful so cute
[Music]
in theory I could even do this off
stream but I feel like doing it on
stream like like a real signing session
is nicer cuz then you also see how it
happened you see the proof that I did it
you
know you
know but if I have a run out of time I
could do it off stream if I'm like super
super busy but but then if I was super
super busy I would probably not open up
this kind
of
session okay
uh oh yeah yeah yeah yeah chicken sent a
super chat but it wasn't no red one so I
don't know if you followed up L later
with a red one but for now no no checky
no Polaroid sorry and GD with a number
two ah another frog gang
member froggy Wy
I support froggy
polar for
[Music]
GD should I do the
spacing so small name small small
[Music]
namea who W where's my
mouse
TD okay smaller smaller name spacing not
necessary
well well I had so much space might as
well thank you thank you all right next
is Digga witz number
18 it a fan game of whole life Fire
Emblem
what what the [\h__\h] for real wait 18
you're also a
ma wow
surprising surprising amount of maids wa
did I delete the made one already no
wait that's not made that ah wizard
wizard uses a
wizard almost gave you the
ma close
enough saw that earlier oh my God is it
made by Japanese fans or like
English-speaking
fans cuz if it's Japanese fans they
probably make it in Japanese first but
if it's english- speaking fans they they
usually make it in English
first yeah 18 yes Wizard
what's it
called also is it like in pixel like old
Fire Emblem
games I guess that would be like simple
enough as a fan game maybe pixel
art English it was English
ooh
FR ah [\h__\h] oh sorry brain H good I
didn't save it yet thank you thank you
thank you that actually I would have
actually saved it like
that somebody else in our
picture hey get out of
here take
out rare
misprint am is the MC in that game n
Amelia
Watson the
MC did they give her a new like more
Fire Emblem outfit thank you you're
welcome I wish I could give you guys
handshakes too but unfortunately we're
not that far with our Tech
yet Dragon days one to number seven oh
actually now that I look at it again
gives me like hip-hop vibes so you're
like a hip-hop
[Music]
chicken yes the the the paddon's
announcer Amilia Watson that's right
well let me take a bite from my I forgot
about my sandwich existence and now I'm
kind of
hungry
ah feel like this should be dedicated
stream well it's the first time so we're
doing it now and I have time I don't
need to go to sleep or anything
yet I got
time maybe next time I'll do
separately
but I'm not that
slow
honestly there you
go no no
no wait that what wasn't your
[Music]
name sorry sorry I'm so sorry thank God
this is virtual so I can fix it it's not
set in
stone damn that was a close
[Music]
one Dragon Days
Dragon you know you guys you guys are at
fault for turning me into this kind of
person who would do these kind of
jokes
[Music]
beautiful thank you next is
Kur as a UK
FP ah UK FP ah I was like what's that I
clearly need to request number 10 cuz
that's Paddington ah yeah yeah see
that's that's why it gave me British
Vibes
British Paddington chicken
m
M
[Music]
mhm this might be the go-to for the
British
chickens maybe I
can make like chickens in like all kinds
of countries traditional
clothing
like Yukata and dandle and hambur
[Music]
Etc
M
someo I feel like I've seen a sombrero
kfp chicken
before but I don't have it
here well Americans have all of these to
choose
from oh yeah so L
[Music]
beats okay
n switching to this side
[Music]
now
H I'm adding that for
fun got to make sure everybody
knows don't we look great
together you
thank you
woo
wo okay I only have like two bites left
excuse
[Music]
me
m nice Extra
Touch
[Music]
next
is
J
X should I ride it with the
XD oh without quick quick answer
fast be
fast
why just pull the right thing about I'll
explain one more time wait
[Music]
wait is he
here I can't see an
answer it's
okay in the future everybody will know
what it's about
[Music]
so oh what should I really R sodin jodin
ger
ger well
today today it will be
oopsie
this oh you are here oh oh that's what
you wanted anyway okay good good good
good good
good I read your
mind I already I already did like uh 4
9 10 11 12
13 let's
go honestly po like anniversary
streams this would be the faster way to
get through them
to through the super chats I
mean 13 out of 82 that's not so bad
that's not so bad I expected it to take
long but after the setup it's fine it's
fine I'm even snacking on the side yeah
and it saves my throat too and we can do
like
anniversary anniversary uh special polar
roads wasn't really the plan
originally but we can have like we can
have special
frames that are just for the you know
how with polar cameras um you can have
special like Polaroid
thingies that have like patterns and
poka dots and stuff we can have like an
anniversary frame with the logo on it of
whatever occasion it is oh that makes it
special again we commemorating that
particular
day ooh now
[Music]
so wait we did D around next one is aor
who is also a wizard oh so many Wizards
ooh wizard quite
[Music]
popular I don't like
that
wizard you get a
star okay Wizards are pretty
cool they
are I need a shortcut for exporting it
as a
[Music]
PNG I wish I knew how to do
it uh okay what is this Daisy you sent a
couple of oranges is this supposed to be
in total a red I think it is and then
you
want does it count like this 18 if it
does don't worry if it doesn't of course
it does I'm not that weird and
like exact about it number 18 wait the
wizard you also want to be a wizard
Daisy oh I didn't think you would you
you would see yourself as a wizard
you didn't strike me as the wizard kind
of
person you know what I need a I need I
need so many more but I already have
20 I already have 20 and I there's so
many ideas
man
[Music]
Daisy you're a wizard
Daisy if you want to be a wizard I
believe you can be a wizard
[Music]
let's
go
da then we have Merit
Pippin retroactive funds oh yeah thank
you number
16 what was number 16 did I have that
yet oh I think I didn't have that one
yet for today it's say like shy ah so
cute shy
chimkin
oh so cute
oh hi I'm
Daisy wait you don't want to cuddle with
Daisy
right we could have we could have
partner uh
triple triple um polar wordss if
somebody's like really really into
getting one partnered up with
someone H what am I doing here switching
the side
[Music]
group group polar
word I'm not sure if you can get five
people for
$100 polar though like that's I have to
think about
that if you can use my
system like
that wait Mary Pippin do you want your
full name probably
right let me make some more
space
Mary
Pippin right that was from mared pons
number 16
yes
oh yeah yeah you guys could design your
own chickens but then I'll have to like
save I don't know where to get them for
like how do you send them to me and then
I have to save them like separately
um well who knows who knows who knows oh
yeah I wanted to explain for
poto
for eh also no I would like them all to
be designed by dma so that they kind of
have like this like M you know this
look how how to
[Music]
say consistency yeah
oopsie so to explain again what I'm
doing
here um I already had this prepared like
ages ago but I didn't get to do it until
now cuz I was always like behind on
super
[Music]
chats and I wanted to do it as like a
good timing but
basically uh well you can see what I'm
doing
right at special times where I feel like
I got I have time for it I'll be
signing uh these polo rids for you guys
with your name and you can choose from a
menu which picture you want me to choose
and you write it in your Super Chat the
number um the menu will be uploaded
later on Twitter and uh the the
community board so you can always look
back on it and then you choose it you
send a red Super Chat has to be minimum
a red one sorry and only one per stream
I will not do like five polar wordss for
one person in One
stream and then I'll sign it like this
with your name especially for people who
can't get who couldn't get a signature
until now and still don't get into like
The Limited
merch uh thingies to get a signature
from
me I think I explained it a little bit
in Japanese I can do it
again
[Music]
for
my production
R what was next
um wait we had Mar Pippin we had da now
C
ER C uh C did not understand the
assignment but do you did you did you
send me a number later when you
understood what what was going
on I think you wrote there's enough
super chat but with the 11 is that
supposed to mean you want the number 11
cuz it
says doesn't say number 11 please or so
it just says nobody in AOE MP likes to
play water Maps
11 does that mean you want oh it's
laughing in
AOE wait do you um do you want do you
want one
C you sent one red Super Chat maybe I'll
just give you number
11 is C still here I might as well give
him 11 cuz like he sent several super
chats ending it with number
[Music]
11 let's give him 11 what's 11 ah 11 is
the chef though do you feel like the
chef represents you if not then well you
didn't even ask for Polar word as far as
I can
tell
so normally normally I said like if you
don't like tell me the number I'm not
going to bother with it
well I'm going to make it for you
anyway this is for you you shall be in
the kitchen now well aren't we all in
the kitchen anyway at
kfp at some
point all
right syy doesn't seem to be here so uh
he cannot change what's happening this
is this is what's
happening
cra
next wa I have to scroll back up is
Slavic fellow with number
four number
four
oh now I'm surprised nobody chose this
one
yet this one with the cat merch let's
[Music]
go
my own laugh just reminded me of the
[Laughter]
song Imagine Peter Griffin's
laugh but then autot tuned to match that
Melody I want to hear
it
[Music]
why
not the fandoms are not clashing so
nobody did it until now I would imagine
so
[Music]
sad
pet you have imagined that in the past
no
way no I'm sure it's been
done find it for me then find it for
me okay that was Slavic fellow now I
have long time no see or wait you're not
actually requesting it's a red super
chat but you're not actually requesting
anything are you here a long time no see
would you like to fix this mistake I had
to send lat ah you did send number three
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
number three did I have number three yet
I had ah Elvis
chicken where is it
there there we
go good good good I'll try to write your
whole name long time no
see
[Music]
four long
time see
hey oh yeah it seems like I I gave up on
the
kisses for okay if we're writing signs
you guys you guys already got enough
kisses until now it's not special
anymore right this way I'm making my red
Super Chat special
[Music]
again yeah that I have withdrawal nah so
special
really stop okay number seven for uh for
red number seven oh wait I have that one
already there it
is zomer chicken you call yourself a
zomer really
wow you bought the game you bought AOE
okay since you're a noob maybe maybe
someday we can
match
sure
cuz your name is so short I added
something hella red looking hella
Red O I'm afraid you'd beat me that
that's that's good that's exactly what I
want to
happen that's
red okay next
uh Ohio
[Music]
enjoyer what's what's TBS
gamer tactical what to to be what oh
enjoyer wants number
17 do I have number 17 in here
no oh number 17 is a first cute cute
cute cute cute cute cute cute cute cute
sometimes you just want a
classic just turn B just a classic
chicken that's
enough good old OG kfp
chicken I still hear High
enjoyer a you
are getting all those lurkers back too
[Music]
woo
can't go wrong with the classics that's
what I'm saying
yeah giving me a pet no he's like look
at this this is my Oshi I love my Oshi
she is the best proudly presenting
me kfp proudly presents takanasi
kiaha okay next is
blank blank blank number 18 okay okay
blank was blank didn't write a number
first but fixed it later should I leave
it
blank should just should just
write
[Music]
four n we're going to write your
name of
[Music]
course would be funny
though what a comedian but
by the way subu Senai messaged me and
asked me if I can be the like leader for
my for the English speaking people for
my uh Minecraft
[Music]
group I said yeah no problem of course
cuz I'm like I think I'm the only one I
I checked who can speak English and
Japanese
fluently I said of course I already
expected that to be the case anyway like
not that I would be the leader but that
I would take the lead in
translating and then she asked me for
advice who to assign that job for the
what was it red team yeah I think it's
red
team thank you blank na with
17 and so I I gave her like an overview
cuz in in red team there's actually
plenty of people who speak Japanese like
fua Moko Ena and Cali and then I told
her these people can speak Japanese and
this the these are their uh Minecraft
skills as far as I know
them so Japanese skills and Minecraft
skills and she was like oh my God thank
you so much you're the
best
uh-oh close
[Music]
one yeah I don't know how the A and B
thing is going to work honestly but she
only asked for like
generally the overall like red white uh
and the other one what was the color
blue green blue
team blank used to be your game attack
oh I mean I I took that kind of a yellow
I took that kind of lead before anyway
it's no
problem I didn't save it
ah ah wait did you see me ride it did I
forget to show you I'm so
[Music]
confused yeah you you saw you didn't see
oh [\h__\h] I swear Nai I wrote it I swear I
didn't let someone else WR it but wait
was that even the right one 17 yeah it
was okay okay I got a bit confused cuz I
was talking about something
else
oops
oopsie uh multitasking
do oh next one is also
17 so I can stay
here M
Rainer rainy here I hope this will cheer
you up on Rainier days
[Music]
h
yeah I was tanging and writing I'm doing
my
[Music]
best thank you guys for all the
participation for the stalks investing
in my NF yix wants a number 16 all right
that
cute the chickens are so
cute
adorable
but change my name into hardest to write
characters M why would you do
that why would you do
that no no no no I will ban
you
no
cost German German
thing let me
yeah these are the the best nfts on the
world no they're not actually nfts
though okay okay just joking just
joking thank you
you shy little
chicken and then we have space waterfall
with a number
[Music]
eight do I have number eight oh that
might be a
first oh we have a soup
chicken not not to be confused with soup
chicken it's a
soup sou chicken yeah
suit not a soup chicken how do you
do we're going on a
date how
fancy a that was for space
water
[Music]
T the the the the the
date how you dress for all my streams
oh and yet you never showed me before
what the
hell you're welcome thank you than you
soon now chck
[Music]
monkey ticket monkey ticket monkey wants
uh a number 27 a number seven and 19 and
eight and seven no an
eight oh wait also suit what a
coincidence
ooh okay for the
monkey
H oh it's not caps oopsy j k
[Music]
h
monkey monkey
Wawa you have dressed for the occasion
for this like as if you
knew as if you knew this was going to
[Music]
happen okay thank you very
much it does sound like a takeaway order
it basically is you're taking a polar
right away you know you guys can you can
even print it if you
want print it out on some nice um photo
paper fancy th shiny photo
paper right next is another the C who's
like I just got here what's going on
number
five did you actually understand what's
going on at that
point number five is new cute cute wait
every another cult are you okay with a
girly
one were you were you
girly I don't
recall is this
fine
sure I don't care that's
that's you don't you don't care about
this do you
not do you want to see the menu again I
sound like a
waitress would you like to see the menu
again I like to I strive to make my my
fans my my cutest little chickens very
[Music]
happy I can show you the menu again
look at the
[Music]
specials wait am I missing an answer oh
there what I wear doesn't matter only
being with wa oh wait that's so
Charming I mean okay if you don't want
to change it all right all right you'll
be cute cutely
dressed wait wait oopsie wa what the
[\h__\h] no number five here this
[Music]
one there you
go there we go there we
go do I write your name with all the
underscore
thingies or should I write them
[Music]
without just heavy
oh oh then there's so much
space big
heart too much
[Music]
space maybe not a
cult always make sure to save them not
that I forget to save
one next is eiy with a number six oh
that's a new one let's go ah
cute ah freaking cute cute c c cute cute
cute
cute I can stay on the same side
[Music]
too see if is also coming out of the
lurking
Shadows vacation y we're on the
vation if
e or iy
if
whoa next we have Ultimo
[Music]
MK with the number two Oh frogy waah ah
you got it right you were trying to get
the froggy waah one good job good job
you got it right you guessed correct
clue there it is I have to switch
[Music]
sign
four should I also just write the full
name with the number or I'll write with
I would write it without the
number but let me know fast if you want
to change
[Music]
it Ultimo
MK oh ultima's fun well now it's Ultima
okay I just woke up what are you doing
ah checky sign k no Polaroid signing uh
for red super chats starting from today
oh I already closed it cuz I got so
many M let's see how fast I can finish
maybe I'll open it up for another like 2
seconds or so um but basically I'm made
a menu of Polaroids that you can choose
from like um little little templates
template and with little chicken
characters and then if you send a red
Super Chat you get a chance to get um a
a a wa Takashi kiaha signature like
this show the option again well okay you
see the options here but there's 20
options
20 maybe more
soon
H give more work to
Duma James Bond I would say the the
chicken and the suit number eight gets
the closest to that
mhm I wait rat rat changed their
name yay d yay let's get the bear P
paid okay okay okay wait
wait uh ultim okay I saved it right I
did I did I
did and then next is motion with number
18 where is
wizard I
guess trying to be kind of fitting for
aelier games I don't know the mage of my
party time to sell some co-workers on
the black market to make some money hey
hey hey hey hey you'll have to sell a
lot to make enough money I don't I don't
think chicken sell so well on the black
market motion for
motion oh I didn't see it must have been
fake no I'll Rite it
again I'll actually write it
again cuz you want to see the motion of
me writing your name right
oh I faked it hi
Nissa do you want a
[Music]
sign
maybe
maybe I might make you
one
perhaps oh and you guys can upload them
on Twitter by the way if you want let's
make a let's make a little um a little
hashtag for
this but only don't upload the
screenshots now don't just upload the
the data that I send you later data that
I sent you
later okay Nissa look at look at the
menu wait uh let me show you the
menu let me show you where's the menu
where did I have the menu where's my
menu
where did I save the
[Music]
menu Polaroid menu there it is look
there's 20 choices you probably want a
feminine one there are a few feminine
ones so number
five oh 16 is cute 1 is cute the ma one
is number
19 what do you think
but narissa hates chicken
well she'll have to get her [\h__\h]
together two more 19 what was two ah
frogy
wa I'll give you
19 I think that suits you
[Music]
better think 19 looks good on here I
think so too but let's make her one
quickly here number
19 and I switch sides
oh wa there you go no need for double
[Music]
w she gets one for
free
narissa o I'll save it for you I'll send
it to you
later me
saving
there's always need for double w if only
I could split or like double myself I
wish I could I'm
[Music]
winning
okay uh back to the the ones who
actually paid the paying
customers fried
screw fried screw yes number 1 just came
back from a long work trip ooh wel
welcome back let's go number 13 is ah
this is a new one
too
[Music]
M I'm sure she'll make up for it
later
okay uh uh she doesn't have to
ride
[Music]
screw
I think I heard
Kito well I'm so confused
my I'm confused I'm
confused okay Fred's what's going on I
just woke up you missed all
this you missed this all of
this even the beginning with the
explanation oh M hi
M what what are you doing
here I'm doing a
a sign signing polar word signing right
now I'm starting it from
[Music]
today I have like a menu I just showed
it to narissa but let me show you
too uh where is
it I have this
menu with 20 different chickens I
actually prepared this ages ago until
when and then like every once in a while
like not every stream but every once in
a while and people can choose which one
they want and then they sign it for
them right cute right oh M really likes
this
idea do you want do do you I mean you
probably just saying it's cute because
you know it's cute but you don't really
feel like you need one right right
right uh you could I think number five
would suit you very much you know oh
almost looks like you
almost just just a little bit but
you really you want one
really okay okay where's my number five
here
cute
cute this is
M almost an
owl
four M
Moon
yay I'll send it to you oh wait you
didn't see it no I covered it up but I
wrote it I'll send it to you in Discord
when I'm done I got to save
it normally everybody's supposed to see
it when I sign it oh
well okay here we go back to uh our list
next is Dominic K you're
welcome you're welcome yeah I already
signed for two BBS one Raven one one owl
they're all flying in here with their
wings flying flippy sounds like can I
have one
please movie is smovie is crying Dominic
wants and a number four number four
let's see where that is there it is oh I
love this one I love Theo I think I want
more chickens that are wearing the
merchandise
it's just
genius maybe the first myth
shirt could be
one that's Rissa oh yeah don't you have
that t-shirt
[Music]
Nissa you
do
yeah okay
I'm still jealous of not getting one oh
don't worry there will be plenty of
chances to get one
TB do Oh you mean the T-shirt not the
sign right sorry I thought you meant the
sign I wonder if you got one I wonder if
you made it I don't see you so
far why is this smovie
crying worries me it concerns
me yeah the ring raring a shirt is like
really soft uh and good to wear in
summer cuz it's like thin but it's a bit
seethrough that's why it's kind of tough
as as a girl maybe because you're going
to see the bra unless you have another
shirt underneath and then it's
hotter not so
good
okay what does the rest of
say thanks to all the chims helping me
out all the time why you why are you
being so
wholesome big thanks to G for making be
a fun place to be on you're welcome of
course
man it's amazing for the gym a it I
wonder how that fabric gets when it when
it gets
sweaty it it probably soaks it up pretty
well
but you can see my chest but I still
love it
uh is it that
visible o maybe you guys should wear
nipple
stickers or just Band-Aids are fine if
you're but you might see those for
too those might be visible
too A lot of people compliment the
ringer shirt and the hoodie our our
clothing merch is just impeccable
honestly so good okay next hi smie
you're alive okay I'm
happy flip flop flop F flop on the
ground
okay I have to ignore you smoothie I'm
almost done though not really but almost
not really though hiom is next with
number
19 your commission budget you want the
mate cute I have to switch sides to
much thank you for commissioning so many
artists to do fan Ard I like seeing that
kind of
[Music]
stuff but now a little bit of that
budget shall go for this
Polaroid and should I write the full
name or just
pyro you
tell I still have
[Music]
space here wrote it in Japanese
even
[Music]
all right next is H Franklin with number
15 oh that's a
[Music]
first
cute that is you guys at
[Music]
concerts
four
Franklin he ah [\h__\h] you can see it damn
it I wonder if I really even have to
hide it
wait oh I might not have to if you don't
even see
that yeah I'll write it
again let me test
it he's covering my
face wait wait I I I'll change it a
little bit I'll
try like here maybe
here okay I don't think yeah okay I
don't have to hide it all right all
right all
right was wasting my
time okay I saved
it
um which one was that
feeding me a popsicle when the w g is so
strong ouch you hit my face with that ow
you're too close to the
stage next is Typhon you wanted to go
for the suit but no you must go with
your spirit chicken number
18 what was what was number 18 the
wizard o ooh you guys really love the
wizard why is it like do you feel like
you're becoming Gandalf like this
cosplay and
Gandalf maybe next time you can go for
the
[Music]
suit but no
pressure be full of wizards
[Music]
damn lord of the
Wings oh how did did I never hear that
before
amazing oh that's why smoovie came by I
just I'm just now hearing the toilet uh
going around
spinning I
understand I understand good that I
didn't pick her up next is Rana with a
number 19 where is number 19 here we go
oh
anate
I of
[Music]
course right it looks like a
g there we go it still kind it still
looks weird does look so weird to
me there you
go eh always f it was Typhon because of
how I say
it oh yes they're completing my list I
know what you guys look like now thanks
to this you're doxing yourself
congratulations thank you Rana next is
Zerg Zerg wants number
17 cute classic
chicken this this is
myoshi she is the cutest look I'm so
proud thank
you
[Music]
jerk
jerk your a will always look like
chickens to me
[Music]
now perfect brainwashing complete
everything that's round must look like
chicken
uh SE Bass with the number seven oh wait
you also want the employee number jerk
oh employee number I haven't given out
one in a
while how
about no how about uh
uh
170 cuz you chose
17 could does make it 17 though but
let's do 7 one
70 good morning from Korea hello Anya
see
you yeah we haven't had that in a
while okay next is and a SE Bass with
number seven it's my
pleasure this one right this number
seven nice nice
[Music]
choice see
yes finally orders coming in again at
kfp haven't had any orders in a long
[Music]
time maybe not food related orders but
that's fine seon with a number nine and
extra
fries it wait Did I have a number nine
yet where is it no
oh ah nerd chicken cute
my beloved nerd chicken must protect at
all cost from all Bully No
[Music]
Bully okay your eye is capitalized so
I'm going to do the
same right
[Music]
protect thank you so much oh and good
luck with your upcoming test come F I
know how nerve-wracking that can
be but just make sure to practice a lot
and calm down drink some tea I don't
know you can do it you can do it I
believe in
you
[Music]
okay next
is FAA with number
[Music]
16 okay was really smart of me to cook
today cuz it's already past midnight but
I have the day off tomorrow so I was
kind of like ready for this to be be a
bit longer to be
honest I don't mind I don't think it
would go this well
but
FAA o why am I doing this I
save
FAA don't worry why would I eat
you I will not eat
you don't worry about it wait is this 16
yeah okay no wait what did I do I sorry
I'm so confused I did it wrong I did it
wrong I did it wrong
I already saved it let me save over
it oh bra brain hord after doing so many
where do we place our orders with a red
super chat but I closed it for now cuz I
got like an insane amount of red super
chats I'm going through them right now
but I'm already like quite far quite
far Prince rock with a number threee yes
of course let me find it where is it
here ah the El was
[Music]
chcken so
funny oh that actually with The Rock in
your name I can see what you're going
for
[Music]
prinnies with prinnies I have to think
of
[Music]
Pringles do you guys like
Pringles
like so you know when you want to eat
potato chips there's like I feel like
there's a different craving for wanting
to eat Pringles and wanting to eat
normal potato
chips right it's very
specific thank you for your order than
hope you enjoy
it don't tempt me I'm on a
diet yeah if you want Pringles then you
want Pringles and PR Pringles
are generally potato chips I can't just
stop eating them they're once you get
started just can't stop
it fried screw came through with a
little advice here in the
middle water Maps prioritize docks and
lumber jack
[Music]
cams addiction is
real so true
I got some potato chips with barbecue
flavor from the ID Girls I got to try
out those out but generally I just
really want simple salt flavor potato
chips that's all I need I I usually
don't want anything extra special M this
with number 15
oh Chen hitting me again so rude what's
up with you guys can't control
yourselves
Miss Bon actually let me write it
smaller smaller
[Music]
smaller oh he he did
not miss with his fist my
face if only he
missed the fist in my face then wouldn't
look like
[Music]
this all right uh now spanking time also
I hope so too Miss F hope you got to
cheer for me on
stage or I'm I'm on St I would be on
stage you would be in front of the stage
HED fully that would happen again
spanheim want a number three number
three number three number three wait
I'll put that in somewhere where is it
number three it was Elvis chicken
right Elvis chicken why is not
squirreling
anymore there we
go spanking I need a cat
chicken if we have frog chicken then I
need a cat
chicken what am I doing
[Music]
sping right like an actual cat or cute
no just cat ears maybe just cat ears
like
a
katusa what's katusa is from an English
word but how do you actually say it in
English the Japanese brain
worms are eating me
up is it was it Spanish hair
band hair band that is
it thank you for your order next is JY
Kunes with number
oh ah talking about H Merchant the other
one the the cat t-shirt one would also
fit you quite well I think well okay
today it shall be this
one let me move myself again
[Music]
did I save this one just now I think
so I'm glad everyone can find something
something that fits themselves wait why
am I writing J it's
JY cuz of my J brain War
[Music]
are you only signing polar pictures only
today um there will be more
times today this will be definitely the
only delivery but we'll do it again like
I'm
I I might do it like generally like once
per month or so but since some people
missed it today I'll do it again very
soon okay of all your different outfits
hell yeah we can do different outfits
all the
time
yeah golden I golden I wants number
seven really fun idea thank you empty
void of catching up on Super Chat paid
off hell yeah like I felt so what the
[\h__\h] am I supposed to do
yesterday uh number
seven
ah sweet switching
over my whole life ended
yesterday and I had to be reborn once no
just kidding golden
y it was really dramatic you
know may I should put that in future
schedules okay I can do
that yeah I want I want you guys to
definitely be aware of when it's
happening I was always going to warn you
like hey it's happening make sure to be
ready if you want
one and next is remix Dave with number
nine thank you your first red super J
hey
Stones genius genius
waa
cute I love this nerd chicken so
freaking cute
man way too big
glasses uh remix Dave thank you for your
support don't like
[Music]
that all
right maybe I should have selected no
there will be other chances it's okay
you can have
several which one was I not sure about
oh yeah okay uh REM Mi
Dave oh
the
yeah those didn't I did I do those for
you guys or thought I only did them for
me like whole life
members next is
Cru oh new profile picture what's
up uh no I will not I will not change
outfits now
but if I wear a different outfit next
time then you can get a different one
then for now it'll have to be
[Music]
this I did it for you guys ah for I did
for pink super chats
oh oh my God I forgot that Final Fantasy
mood yay exactly we're looking good
we're looking so fancy even without my
fancy outfit thank you and moon ah there
you are number 12 all right all right
number
12 ah ah this pattern okay this is the
second
one oh good choice but you know for this
one I I I don't you guys shouldn't
choose it too much because like there's
not much I can do in terms of poses I
feel like that look good on on this one
so there might not be that much variety
except for for oh well for example if I
wear the dandle I can do the hard pose
above you that would be
cute like something with my arms up
would look nice otherwise those sides
look so
empty you know but maybe I'm
overthinking
itg oh Ora hi oh my God I'm getting so
many visitors to who are like checking
out what this excitement is all about n
n n n i was inspired to do this by NY
but I wonder if Ian member is going to
be inspired by my by me doing this also
cuz n is not doing it the exact same
way I wanted my own original way of
doing
it the waa w way thank you Moon next is
Jackson with a lucky number seven all
right wait let me change
position what did n do exactly
uh I forgot too let me try to remember I
think she just had one Polaroid without
the fans just herself a screenshot of
herself uh and just like one no
variations per stream and then just
signed the names but I don't think she
had like the
chickens of course she didn't have the
chickens but she didn't have like any
fans to put on top I
think exactly yeah yeah yeah that's
that's what it was I also don't know if
she still does those
but that's where I kind of
oops got the idea of doing
[Music]
it for Jackson right
do you want me to just write Jackson or
Jackson
FB why do I even ask actually I don't
have that much space should I keep it as
Jackson oh okay okay I'll keep I'll keep
it as
Jackson
[Music]
although here that looks nicer wow
graphic design is my
passion I'll save it Jackson F
beo I'm saving each polar with your
guys' name so you can find it uh easier
later
on in the
[Music]
folder you're
welcome I finished the Voss
bottle
I can use it as like a to go bottle
now hope I won't break it
ever
and happy Bel birthday Mike Tyson's
ass we're eating Mike Tyson's ass
unrelated to Mike Tyson of course it's
not Mike Tyson's
birthday is
I Studio R thanks for the
pinky
T I will miss you when you are on a
vacation but that's better than the
alternative a phoenix should rise and
new from their ashes not burn out and
disappear oh well I actually surprising
I never made a joke about did I about
being burned out as a
phoenix no but yeah thank you Studio Rob
guess it's about the conversation we had
like yesterday thank you I will go on
vacation I'm so excited for it I think
time's going to pass fast so we're going
to get there I didn't maybe you guys did
though maybe you guys made a joke about
[Music]
it it'll be here before you know it yeah
for sure I have to still book the flight
oh my God but like uh
honestly I'm really really scared of
November H I should have done this last
month cuz like I'm honestly concerned
about
uh if I have enough money to pay
my it'll be fine it'll be fine to pay my
taxes a it will be fine hopefully uh
look cuz the thing is I'm also getting
charged for the the
14,000 for the exent suit it will be
like um taken off of my salary and I
asked Gemma when do you think is it
going to happen this month or next
month it might
be like at the like the end of next
month
hopefully that would be
better cuz
otherwise I might not have any
income
although we'll see cuz it's usually like
kind of two months delayed or so the
YouTube super
chatos so I think wa
no yeah or like one month tonight I
might be getting my anniversary super
chats and all that this at the end of
this month so uh who knows who knows the
exent suit has to be balanced
out I wish I could pay it in like two
installments or
so but like in
general like in in hindsight I would be
paying less taxes on that month
obviously but I'm I'm doing prepayments
for my taxes and the last pre prepayment
is in November and they don't know that
I probably don't need to pay that
much but finally a big business expense
my my tax lady was telling me make big
business business expenses and I said I
don't know I don't have anything to
really spend something big
on can you stream from
jail no don't worry it's not going to
happen it's going to be fine I believe
just got to be
[Music]
optimistic all right number three for JP
R
snsr thank you
for the
super this movie is making a big fuss in
the living
room what's her
problem wait J
PS
[Music]
M I'll become a
jailbird n say a kfp and I'll I'll
become a jailbird wow we switching
places s
NSR the mvs yeah yeah well they're
always like deducted from my
salary those things are always deducted
from my salary cuz I'm paying it kind of
like I'm not paying it directly I'm it's
going through my
salary
yeah but like all those things I just
pay once computer parts VR headset all
those that that's already like that's
bought once and usually not really like
recently I bought a new mixer okay but
me buying new equipment to streamware
that happens maybe once a year a little
bit we had a graphic card up upgrade
this
year a few parts a few parts of my PC I
upgraded this year number 17 for
Lulu oh wa wait wait number
17 thank you thank you thank you for
your Polaroid
order
[Music]
switching but like it's not so hey I
missed the letter oh
[\h__\h] it's not as
like like like other people who are
like M also so like
working as a
freelancer like usually normal
freelancing people have like more
expenses to keep up their business that
just makes more
sense thank you sorry I almost had it
wrong but we got it right this
time thank you thank you
yeah but I'm not a normal
freelancer not not a typical
kind not
not not the same kind of
business this is for
[Music]
Lulu number 17 very
cute I should be winking too but I hope
this is okay hope this looks cute hope
you like it thank
you gener also charge cuz they all to
pay for those expenses and wear and tail
equipment
[Music]
yeah next we have a fixed skateboard ooh
what's what currency is that looks fancy
number
five you you forgot the number but you
added it with a pinky you didn't have to
go that
hard just a small small Super Chat would
have been enough well thank you a fixed
skateboard that's a long name
H for
a
fixed
ooh
wait oh
oops artificially resize resizing
[Music]
there we
go
nice I'll upload all of these later so
you guys can download them so no need to
screenshot from here unless you're
really
impatient thank you for the support than
you soon and next we have o going on a
vacation wait you didn't even write
number you're not even ordering a polar
room
oh smoy oh o are you still here in the
chat let me write one for you come
on I'm going on vacation so I'll miss
quite a few streams so here's a holiday
bonus to compensate boss hey thank you
but you can't just come out of the
lurking Shadows to say goodbye and then
not even ask for a
Polaroid seems like you're already gone
so I'll write you one whether you want
it or not is there one that I I haven't
had today like the bubble bubble
one ah there you are number nine oh okay
oh I thought you weren't there so I was
going to choose this one for
you okay we're going to go with
this why no one like this
one actually you should be choosing a
vacation
chicken but
okay
okay I need a qule chicken
W so many
options well I hope your I hope your
vacation is going to be lovely where are
you going to take me with
you please do you have
space in your
suitcase uh thank you enjoy it's okay if
you can't be here for a few times but
but I hope to see you again hopefully
not too
sunburned next is glass of number 16
number 16 number 16 number
16 ah there it is
[Music]
a ooh touching grass across Europe wait
are you from Europe ah you you from
Poland ooh ooh ooh speaking of touching
grass now we are signing
for
[Music]
glass what a
coincidence
[Music]
glass okay how many more ooh quite a
few tomato tomato
[Music]
come number
15 okay
15 15
15 there it is
[Music]
ah
tomato glass glass GL did I say
glass hope you like
it I will upload okay upload later on
gig and another Korean bro oh they come
in in couples it seems one's the number
nine Mr
P cute I must say it suits
[Music]
you
for p in caps
[Music]
log thank you thank
you you guys could have gone a little
bit easier on me there there in the last
match against the Koreans that wasn't so
nice of
you thank you jpng than you soon than
soon Nik no wants a number
15 okay coming right up actually that
one again okay okay okay popular choice
this
one n wait you picture is so cute your
profile
picture very committed chicken to have
my
eh another D chicken as their profile
picture cute
cute how did the age of training go uh I
am I am fine totally fine with moderate
but I tried a few times of hard and
suddenly so difficult I couldn't handle
it I am
ashamed oh is this the Super Chat you
guys were talking about
maybe uh for M who sent two pinkies
hi K I've been struggling with
depression and anxiety for three years
coming across whole life and especially
you was what finally start to brighten
my days again seeing how you persever
persevere in challenging times and
remain so wholesome and energetic helped
me find the strength to face my issues
and have a more hopeful outlook on my
future again thank you from the bottom
of my heart and I wish you the best for
all your endeavors much love from
Switzerland of course it counts thank
you number 11 for you oh
really really I helped you with
that I am
honored and I'm proud of you good
job I hope things are only looking
upwards for
you man switzeland is so beautiful I
want to
go this is for
you me she
[Music]
let's just keep that it that
way oh my
God you know if if I could help you with
that honestly you always had it in you
it was always there you always had your
own
strength just had to let it out have the
confidence to let it
[Music]
out thank
you
she's like w it's past midnight why are
you still streaming what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] and next one is for Indigo 5 Alpha
with a number 18 all right all right
number 18 to
co ah this one
[Music]
again let me fix the order here
I should save this as a PSD so I can
just use the same thing again next
time cuz all the pictures are already in
here
now all right uh for for Indigo 5 Alpha
see another
lurer definitely a fan cuz I see your
profile
picture but not a name I usually see in
my super
chats
oh they all want a part of
this
action there you go this is for you hope
you enjoy it and cherish it treasure it
Indigo 5 Alpha
saved nice
thank you for coming by Elder greenberry
D
[Music]
soon uh Urban cohort
D uhhuh inter Heaven thank you for the
Super Chat you get an 18 as well oh okay
okay okay okay
okay inter heav see another
one even a European one
inter
Heen without the
G such a lur cuz you have armor on your
badge but it's it's your first Super
Chat
wow such a
genius such a
Genius Next is D
star took three years that's totally
fine though
I'm glad I'm glad this way you got a
Polaroid with a signature for
me do I have some water left
[Music]
yeah it's been 84
years dstar forgot to send a joke up to
GTA why did the chicken I mean kiaha
across the
road because she has to walk due to not
having a driving
license not funny not funny dstar try
harder but you want the number seven was
angry oh well okay I was angry just now
but I'm not taking any extra pictures
sorry it's too complicated but number
seven I shall give you a number seven
[Music]
I did go Angry for you
once that shall be
enough I shall not reward bad
jokes oops you
star
star wait is this number
seven yes
okay
look at from the top r j thank you thank
you
soon oh do we finally have a bubble
bubble
[Music]
chicken y
cute
nice didn't expect you going to be the
one to choose this one out of all
people I should imagine me doing this
one if I ever use my casual outfit you
should request this one and me wearing
uh my my my
pacifier but that's for the
future your name is so
long so long why your name going to be
so
long I feel like love titty is just I
love
titty all right I should just
write I
[Music]
love this is your
[Laughter]
name I should just save it like that man
okay
[Music]
looking for oh it's
capitalized
for the top all
right next time we might just want to do
lft cuz it's so squeezed
in well let me know what you
prefer o Babble bab bab
next on this gym Tracy with a number
four EO number four where number four
where is it there there there I have to
switch Sid o cat
t-shirt you should only be allowed to
choose this one if you actually have the
t-shirt and you have to show me proof a
picture of yourself with your face to
confirm do you need to delete no yeah
you know just to keep uh to to make it a
little bit more
individual each time it's fine the four
isn't like a big problem to write for me
my signature on the other
side Jim Tracy thank
[Music]
you you got off early from work man
those days are the best
days
yeah you w't be getting my face out
easily you so mad already
send it
again need proof
again hey chesus the gondra are you here
you can't just send a red super chat in
this stream and not ask for a Polaroid
what's wrong with you
Jesus what's up number please did you
miss the the
menu do you need to see the menu uh uh
um um 11 are you sure do you know what
11 is
this one is 11 do you want to see the
menu I don't mind you can I can I can
show you the
menu unless this is really the one you
want yeah cooking chicken okay cheesy
Cheo Cheo chickens chickens covered in
cheese I always have to think of cheese
when I read your
name four
did you not know this was happening when
you sent the Super
[Music]
Chat unprepared
chicken
[Music]
wait sorry little bit
sced
quos
quo Jesus the Contra what does that even
mean is there a meaning behind this name
what language is
this 10 members wow you must be really
excited to get a Polaroid and not be
missing out on it just because you
forgot to say something about
it qu
qule
qule it's a D and D character yeah but
like the name surely means something
right or is it just made up
completely thank you for the red super
chat glad you enjoyed the stream too
thanks for the
memberships you made it up hey it sounds
real
what okay now first name fine Manida
wants number 18 the
wizard Hocus
Pocus the Hocus Pocus
man again
[Music]
four now wait if you only want the first
name then let me make it
bigger here an
S so we know which Manuel I know there's
only you right now but still it's nicer
to make
sure thank you I'm glad glad you're
enjoying the streams this week tomorrow
is my day off though so can't help you
tomorrow maybe watch a VOD or
something soon next is C with number
15 my my my Photoshop is like bugging
out a little bit sometimes kind of weird
kind of
weird oh it's this one again but I
actually kept myself in that position
so you're not hitting me this
time my
Carpenter it's kind of absurd that you
still haven't changed your name to coer
obum kfp Carpenter but
[Music]
okay maybe you will maybe that doesn't
sound very
certain
unsatisfactory F
no thank you thank you soon next is Rob
easy number four okay thank you for the
sweet
[Music]
words okay ah cute nice choice good
choice I wonder is there still some that
haven't been chosen
um no I think at this point I've I think
I've done them all now except the hippie
nobody chose the hippie are there no
hippies
what it be's nice man I thought it was a
genius
idea maybe next time
guys maybe next
time
grab
[Music]
easy please want
unions it's no longer at the 80s well
well by that argument I should have
never released
fight don't think we agree with
that love and peace
yes
and Yuri almea wants uh number 11 PO
number 11 number 11
11 oh chef with
s of course coming right
up a
for Yuri
[Music]
Almeida all
right well feite was like throw back to
the 80s look at The Outfits or more like
70s maybe I don't even know it's hard to
tell y I made up thank you for the
support
[Music]
than o to
Brazil next is Joe W with a number 20 oh
number
20 number there it is
oh I thought nobody would choose this
one we just talked about it you saved my
hippie
chicken my hippie chicken thanks you
with all his heart Jo
Jo Jo are you
here hippie chicken very happy hippie
chicken is Happy
Chicken Hipp chicken hippie chicken
hippie chicken Hipp chicken Hipp chicken
Hipp chicken there you
are do you feel connected
to the
hippin what part of this speaks to
you I I want to ride it again no that's
was fine
but
[Music]
peace HP
chicken this one's nice right he's he's
he's cute he's he's like in his Zone
he's he's in his own
Zone he also kind of looks like a cult
chicken
but those things partially go hand in
[Music]
hand I don't know I feel like that time
was the big booming time for for hi uh
for Cults
no I've watched documentaries
so and kfb goes in hand with colds
too so it
works looks like he's taking a selfie oh
yeah like he's reaching out his uh front
arm yeah that's
cute
okay and next one is Alvar with number
16 all right all right no problem oh
cute very very
cute
ah it is my
[Music]
pleasure oh it's almost 1:00 a.m. holy
[\h__\h] but this is chill and and I I still
think this is faster than reading these
super chats like as if they came in
normally but if they came in normally if
I didn't do this then there wouldn't
have been so many sure there's that
argument
but but it's it's okay it's
fine the next is the cond dude with
number 17 thank
you I've made it this the best purchase
I've made this month includes finally
getting on the property ladder ooh oh
wow congratulations that's a big
stab wait these two are so cute together
wait which one is the right
one number
17 oh there it
is oh they cute the the two classic
chickens
[Music]
dude wait let me move it a little
bit just a little
bit that couldn't do it couldn't do this
if it wasn't on Photoshop if this was a
real Polaroid I'll be
[\h__\h]
[Music]
nice gold beard number 18 AC let's go
I'm already in position
[Music]
I'm getting closer to the end I'm like
in the last
part you're welcome I hope you like
[Music]
it
for gold beardy another one I never
hear so
many new chickens showing their face
they're not not new I see your member
[Music]
badges wait you doing Super Chat no
more thank you thank you thank
you for investing in kfp
coin
long and swatter for the right super CH
all right I have to read this one hey
boss I've seen the Lord of the Rings
musical finally let's go they remembered
you and wish you well
they remember me I'm so
memorable how the cat with Bilo bourier
gave me a cookie what I didn't I don't
think I talked to the actors at all did
I no I don't think I did I was too shy
and they seemed
like
busy we were sat on the balcony front
row and had some great views of the
stage it was an amazing experience 18
for G of chicken ah perfect honestly
yeah I uh when I was sitting in there I
didn't expect it when uh when we were
choosing the
seats I didn't think it would be this
tight and like uh this low so many times
I wasn't really seeing so well what was
happening um like in the very front on
certain parts of the stage cuz people
they were sitting in front of
me um we covering it up and like the the
seats on the first floor they didn't I
don't think they were like elevated the
more they go to the back I think they
were all pretty flat so balcony seat
first row is like Co definitely very
[\h__\h] good also because if you're on
the
balcony uh Golem
might uh like climb around you
there yeah literally Everybody Plays an
an instrument and they're like some
really fancy instruments too
yeah that's what I was talking about
like everybody's so involved in the
whole play musically and also with
acting yeah yeah I'm glad you enjoyed it
y you did
it did he bite does he bite off your
finger no he he he bit off um uh froo
finger right was it froo how can I
forget fro Golem climbed on the side I
was on it was very close to me
amazing yeah Frodo
right man Frodo must be regrowing his
limbs a lot for
this uh
musical damn losing so many fingers over
and over again as if he couldn't tell by
now that that's what golum is going
for and block him off
somehow
[Music]
or SW swatter why didn't you swat Golem
with a swatter with a fly swatter to
protect froo huh you knew this was going
to happen I'm sure you knew it cuz I
told you guys
too must have Good Health
[Laughter]
Care thank you I'm so happy you went I'm
happy to hear
[Music]
that you had a good experience did you
eat the foods there too I thought it was
very British for for you probably it's
just normal food for me it was like a
oh interesting different from what we
get in
Austria not the best food but it gives
me British
Vibes British in
it
yeah
I don't think they had Yorkshire pudding
they had like specific menus and stuff
and you didn't you got yourself a drink
though oh like in the in the in the
break in the outside little bar
outside rmt also had a drink
there did I save this I think I did okay
next is gingle number
15 oh I wonder which one's number 15
h
oh actually surprising to me
cute all right no this one's for
you also h f FLH finally for pre yeah
yeah yeah yeah those are really
cute some people I saw were thinking
like oh there those are um like restocks
no no no that's the first time they're
selling those right isn't that
13 I kind of wrong oh I got it wrong
okay see okay this makes so much more
sense that's what I'm saying that's what
I'm
[Applause]
saying that's why I was
surprised sorry thank
you yeah the Plushies are
cute you should buy them together with
others if you
[Music]
can
I really like these
ones it will go well with the future
froggy waa
plushy and also would go well with takam
or whatever whatever you want like Pabi
amori
whatever okay next is um Fallen penguin
wow you're the best we appreciate
everything you do for us and you inspire
us every day I pushed myself to do so
many things thanks to you for the plan
first Japan trip next summer I'll pick
number six any secret spots to visit in
Osaka Kil Naga or Tokyo Naga I got
nothing for you Naga is not
even
okay uh
I don't know if you really want to go to
Naga it's not like as a tourist I think
it's not that interesting you can surely
find some things
but I don't know I don't know I I think
maybe before you go there maybe go to I
don't know
sauro yeah the cool thing in Naga is
that everybody stands in the middle of
the
escalators just kidding they don't but
that's a joke cuz nagya is between Osaka
and Tokyo you know it's
funny but secret spots in general I
don't know like
secret secret secret ah Tokyo I always
recommend in this is not even in Tokyo
but it's like you can get there from
Tokyo if you want to do like a day trip
you know the one that I went with hatama
and
a
enima go
there
[Music]
fall and for real I I want to recommend
you maybe no maybe you could go to
fukoka like sapuro and okina are really
far but fukoka is still kind of like if
you go a little bit further past
Osaka you could go to
[Music]
fukua I certainly enjoy my time
there and you can go swimming there too
like I went swimming there in in
summer
summertime enjoy the chicky the Polaroid
my Chat is dead are you guys dead
or Let me
refresh you guys are just dead they're
on the list now or were they already was
I not
helpful next is MDB with number
eight my scrolling doesn't work what the
[\h__\h] there you go wa
wa did I
help is on the list thanks to me hope
so I want to be
helpful yes okay good wonderful
[Music]
M DB you get a heart cuz your name is so
short you shall be
rewarded I
guess thank you for the support yay yay
I'm almost at the end
[Music]
woohoo I'm very pleased with myself
today I had a good day I got a good
message today that was like woohoo and
then and then I cooked so and then I
streamed and now I save myself from
bankruptcy
bankruptcy bankruptcy is that how you
say
it so I'm
[Music]
winning
wo w w wo
yeah girls from newu watched my stream
yesterday and therefore made a totally
related inspired YouTube
shirt this is by the way a cope but um I
find it a funny coincidence that girls
who have certainly never played GTA 4 uh
today uploaded a YouTube short with the
the GTA opening music that I always
play
uh and uploaded that today and recently
before that I said we had we had Synergy
with pineapple and their song
Coconut you know at some point it stops
being a coincidence and just becomes
like oh they're fans of
me yeah a coincidence I think not Urban
cohort Chucky Cool D and salus beats one
in number
12 oh cute
good choice today only the third
[Music]
one
po your name is also so long Sal Bri I'm
doing my best to fit it
[Music]
in there there we go perfect salus
Beats
salus
beats yeah it's so cute how dare they
not C
you if this outfit Had A Hammer it would
be made of tin foil
cute tin foil chicken
cute thank you for the support and oh
buch of us are meeting up for anime
Frontier for Takami panel anything you'd
like to see from
us uh or for us to do while we're
[Music]
there
but that that's in December right or is
it the November when is it
[Music]
again
December also sorry celebrus [\h__\h] I
can't follow that order right now the
special order no special
[Music]
orders I don't know
I can't really think of anything right
now but make sure to bring Pen lights I
guess and
uh I don't
know the the dance video with the hor
20y dance was so cute the last
time may you know there's still a lot of
time maybe you guys still can think of
something interesting to do or maybe
something fitting will
happen that will
inspire you
guys and top Gallo Capon thank you for
the red and been meaning to say thank
you for being part of kfp for 6 months
oh your streams are part of what keeps
me sane at my
job thank you for everything you for the
PO I like number 13 either TGC or T and
the name is fine oh thank you okay well
your name is pretty much a same length
as sil's beat so it would have been fine
but I'll I'll go with tup I think m
number
13 a
cute a cute
angle a cute uh
bronchitis
[Music]
or Mario chicken yeah I guess we called
it Mario chicken
uh po Gallow cap I'll save it with your
full name
though oh do you not like use the word
like that in English in German we
say for example a or something like auta
for anything like for illnesses that
are I think it meant that they're like
always there or so I don't [\h__\h]
know in no not quite yet not quite
almost there Chucky Co M
A and number 15 looking forward to more
FFX VI this week and I'll definitely be
getting the new friends of you plush
thank you please get get one W plushy
thank you I give you polaro you'll get
uh uh plushy to go with it okay thank
you thank you thank you number 15 this
one
[Music]
oh so you do use them why were you guys
so
confused why you confus Me by being
confused yourselves you make me question
my abilities of the English
language question gaslighting I call
that
[Music]
gaslighting yeah this is like I normally
don't stream so late holy [\h__\h] I'm
almost done though uh Urban coh D
Jackson d game
8910 number 15 with an extra smile game
do you want like your username or
something else cuz it seems so
so so how to
say not so personal but
okay that's how I know you
so it's fine I
guess
it's fine
okay and what numbers what do the
numbers mean
Mason I see you also went for the U
supportive otaku
chicken
cute those people who choose this one I
better see you with light sticks in the
audience next time I'm somewhere on
stand
AG otherwise I don't know if you really
deserve this
one just kidding you don't have to but
hopefully one day in full otaku attire
we need a Ki
Happ next is Renee alacon with another
three o you want the Puma do
style I feel like if if you try that
nowadays people will probably be looking
at you weird but go for
it you you really love great Wonder
thank you you got my Fus where's my
ferace like I'm not getting my
merchandise recently JMA where's my H
talk merch where's my where's my fry
merch
po
Renee I
no f is so good
damn I want
it you guys all got it what the
hell okay next is fire the
elements it's been a while since I could
catch a stream thank you wait you didn't
are you still here you didn't choose a
number you probably just send it for the
sake of sending one didn't know what was
going
on have have you seen the menu are you
still
here fire the elements let me give you
one let me give you one
like number 19 you picked it when did
you pick it didn't see number 19 all
right A M
chicken yeah
[Music]
cute but he's gone isn't this it I don't
see it ah I see it I'm
blind I'm so
[Music]
stupid for
fire
[Music]
[\h__\h] all right ooh that that was the
second to last one let's
go thank you for the
support
fire elements [\h__\h] I wrote it wrong but
that's okay close
[Music]
enough and last but not least a close
call you almost didn't make it in next
time be should be more ready you someone
number 20 oh hippy chicken is Happy
Chicken for not being chosen so
little enough glorious Conquest for one
day hell yeah oh yeah let's give pza
chance I like this
segue for Flappy boy should I should I
write it
[Music]
like the [\h__\h] is
this heroglyph
the
runs uh sure
[Music]
wow
ooh so mysterious so fancy what does it
mean Minecraft enchantment
table nobody can read it just us that
letter us will do
fine I did my best to write
this okay okay
okay Flappy
boy than you soon don't
worry about
contributing I I appreciate it thank you
guys so much I did it he and it was it
was chill it was
fun I'm glad I can make everyone happy
with
this
I'll I'll try to do maybe next week one
more cuz like the see it seems like a
bunch of people missed
it if you would like one then I shall
warn you ahead of time thank you guys
for the support today uh I have a day
off uh oh I think I I think I was
supposed to do some things uh I think oh
yeah oh yeah
oh yeah wait
what okay it's Friday [\h__\h] okay uh good
night I have to
sleep oh
[Music]
Mom I
forgot one very critical
thing all right well I probably wouldn't
have slept that early anyway and yeah I
I have my food ready no problem this is
fine this is
fine so stupid stupid
stupid thank you
watching en turn I love you guys enjoy
the Polaroids I'll I'll upload it right
now I'll I'll write a explanation post
with the Giga file link it's Japanese
website but you can do it I believe in
you bye
byebye a
[Music]
byebye