[Music]
n
kick key
hello it's
me K KY
key
[Music]
hi first of
all yell [\h__\h] first of all I made the
the back of the hood work more or less
if I move too much then it's uh a little
bit [\h__\h] again but this is as good as
it gets you
know I cut I basically I cut the the
whole back the long part that you
wouldn't see anyway cuz I only show the
upper um over shoulder
part um because with that it like
Wobbles Wobbles Wobbles even worse and I
found uh a point to stick it to uh for
both front and back where it's like
pretty
stable
yay curses within the first minute for
it's not even cursing any anymore like
you know we the the
Sens what's what's the word Des sensive
sensor
sensualized
sensitivi s sensitized yeah it's I don't
W stream it's not cursing isn't cursing
anymore
yeah
okay uh I played a little bit off stream
uh wait a
[Music]
second I don't hear
anything
uh cannot
hear oh yeah I got one more heart now I
hear it you hear it too I think um I did
five shrines I thought I'd be a little
bit productive I just ran around I did
this one and this one and this one I
even went to this next area this one I
found a stable I did this one yeah and I
got myself a heart you only need four
but I did
five uh yeah that's what I meant by
homework mhm
uh yeah uh I wonder is there no Tower no
sha Tower like before that lets you
activate the map to see it
properly that looks like a
bird this structure that looks like the
legs that looks like an eye that looks
like the beak that looks like uh the
wing it's like a running chicken
[Laughter]
can you see
it you'll see it in just a sec what do
you mean the the
tower what do you mean I'll see in a sec
I haven't seen it at all while running
around follow the main quest oh okay
yeah I I purposely stayed away from that
I did find I think was it here maybe
this like big
hole uh with
the all that [\h__\h] you can't touch around
it
okay okay got to follow the main mission
okay okay okay oh yeah
interesting yeah
[Music]
so Shrine in Japanese is normally Ginger
but then Ginger is actually just you
know the typical Japanese Shrine how do
you actually call it in
Japanese I wonder Ginger I wonder if
it's Ginger oh yeah yeah we saw the
Blood Moon while we were super chat
reading Ginger yeah exactly Ginger oh no
Ginger shy in really you sure we ain't
got no Japanese
Bros ah are they used to the the temple
[Music]
word yeah so with one more heart and a
couple of shrines behind me I feel ready
to tackle
Ganondorf once again so let's go and
finish this game by going straight to
the castle
let's
go and I I cooked
also I cooked a lot of stuff I also made
some medicine and I got some medicine
and yeah I cooked I cooked I cooked I
have like I'm I I don't know I'm so bad
at catching
insects I tried going slowly I tried
going
fast I just can't figure it
out also I'm really bad at finding um
CRS
Crocs as
well yeah but you don't necessarily need
stealth potions for catching insects oh
and one more thing that I was very oh
that that looks like it might be
a might be a sh Tower maybe oh that one
up there too um but I I was saying uh I
was in the woods and then suddenly
uh the trees started
moving what does that
mean in the woods yeah new enemy it
shocked me and I was like what am I
supposed to fight them or what what are
what do you
do and eventually first I ignored them
but eventually they kind of annoyed me
so I burnt one down it takes a while but
when you set them on fire they go like
they Panic it's so funny uh and then
eventually they yeah it takes a while
but they they die
oh yeah that's funny but
um I wonder what that's all
about let's kill a
[Music]
bird oh
good Doro
are you going to lift your head or
not uh might be better if it doesn't
lift his head how high should I
go is this high
enough H it was it wasn't a head shot
but it was
enough
okay okay so how do I get these Critters
huh is is stealth the preferable
way but then sometimes just by running
fast I was able to catch the the
fireflies at least some of
them run up and grab him
running
uh see how can I be fast
enough they fly away okay wait there's
some Tom Tom what do you call them again
Tom
not Tom
tomboys for these for these maybe it's
better if I'm just
stealthy Crouch and then Sprint when
[Music]
close okay give me some of
these see the ones in the front just
faded away just now I don't know if you
were able to see what oh and and the
next one's faded why
[\h__\h] they all faded what the [\h__\h] dragon
flies you're do it too slow at this one
what the [\h__\h]
man
okay oh there's another flying
thing and I don't mean the
bird need meat meat very important to
survive okay
no now the enemies made them
angry yes Herb weapon herb herb weapon I
don't know why that
exists we can put herb on a weapon I
didn't do it wasn't my
idea E I think I got it
uh because of uh in in German there's a
word for them I think that sounds a
little bit like
[Music]
tomboys pick it
up pick pick pick it
up sometimes I know sometimes there's uh
insects underneath
Stones I just want more insects cuz I
want to make medicine
no nothing nothing nothing at
all yeah I don't
even you mean potions yeah what did I
say have
medicine [\h__\h] hey this this one also I
just
Su what the [\h__\h] is the matter with
them why do they not like me you know
what
no despawn despawn
despawn that's they they despawn within
a
second don't get it I don't get
it it's
stupid and but yeah I saw you can buy
some too but they're really
expensive I don't want to buy what is
this
also I one reason I want them is because
I realized we should uh it might be
helpful if I
always um have a uh a speed potion on
then the whole
traveling thing will be not so annoying
you
know this is a Crystal refiner really
here not a
hold here right here hyal Castle Town
ruins stamina potion also important I
think I have some oh
n was hard to believe these ruins just
fell from the sky I mean they're from
the age of Legends and now they are here
it's also strange huh oh well it is but
it's also a great opportunity all of us
on the zai server team should count
ourselves lucky if it weren't for the
upheaval this never would have happened
not that anyone knows what the upheaval
even is well Pur is investigating the
uphe she's certain it will provide clues
about Princess Zelda but progress isn't
great I've heard is the princess all
right wherever she is these ruins right
here are exceptional but really who
cares about that at a time like this
for real for real you lost your Princess
once again guys how can you be so
reckless eh how hard is it to keep your
princess that is so important safe have
you not learned from Super Mario from
Peach how peach keeps on getting
abducted
M me I didn't loser no
no what they should have done is they
shouldn't even even have allowed her to
go with me in the first place and then
she wouldn't be
lost
also I I have another logic
question the arm that we lost is the
right
arm
coincidentally the arm that the other
dude R lost and gave to us was also the
right
hand how did such a coincidence happen
huh
sus yeah no he gave me his arm yeah but
it was already like cut off at the point
where we found it and then oh oh we we
just happened to lose [\h__\h] I get the
Frog I I get the Frog oh it's not a frog
it's a green
bird God damn it God damn it all right
we are here uh there's a
shrine and this
is the
[Music]
destroyed Garden in front of the
castle is
this farming
hole a farming tool but we will use it
as a weapon I guess oh was
that
yeah okay I panicked a bit cuz I wasn't
sure what I was looking
at yeah this place is kind of nice I
guess they put all those like
reconstruction uh materials down to
rebuild
it but no one's working on it so it's
going to take you guys probably a long
time until you manage to rebuild it
especially if there's someone like me
running around stealing all the
materials very very weird how the
materials keep on disappearing and be uh
turned into
some some some cars that no one needs
yes yes yes goodbye my dear insects you
the only
thing that I cannot catch and not make
mine oh cute these little little camps
are
cute a oh wait there's nuts
acorns is it the acorn from
yesterday one of them
oh I'm going to sneak for no when I
sneak when I sneak they despawn cuz I'm
too slow then I don't get it
man where to begin oh shall we do the
shrine first K
Shrine what you scared me what are you
doing in the place like this the hyro
castle CH Chasm is nearby it's dangerous
you know for all I know this Shrine
could be dangerous too I'd say most
things are dangerous these days what
with the upheaval watch your
back
um I wonder all the shica shrines that
were like scattered all over the
world how did they just disappear
and now we have this I understand these
ones maybe just randomly launching from
the bottom of the ground but this is not
a 100 years after breath of the wild
this is a couple years of anything after
breath of the wild how do all the shika
shrines and all those structures
disappear do they retract back into the
ground because of magic because we don't
need them anymore okay okay but then I
want to be I want to be told about that
like all the shika things the shik
towers the shik friends it's all
gone it's all
gone who cleaned all of that
up I question
everything this is why I can't enjoy
life oh well Shrine
time the deaths cleaned it up up but
they left no
explanation if you follow up on a game
so soon after the last
one timeline wise oh combat
training but not not a specific one no
throwing I'll be throwing
anyway want to
fight let's go
[Music]
oh this try purify dang and evil you who
have entered here heed my
instruction fight
me use a side hop to avoid enemy attacks
oh I I actually I practiced that a
little bit off
screen mhm yeah I know how that
[Music]
works I can do flurry Rush see I can do
this cool stuff too do a backflip to
avoid enemy attacks and create an
opening to strike back
okay but I need a weapon I know how to
do that
too
um what are these
weapons why why do I only have [\h__\h]
weapons we need to make
some oh okay I was I was too
early slow motion Matrix let's go oh you
can reel and attack if you parry with
your Shield at just the right time oh
this one I can't
do I don't think I can okay we just
press a okay with the shield [\h__\h] one
more
please I thought I pressed
a
oh oh nice okay I guess I did it
build up your power and then release it
to unleash a charge attack catch your
enemies in this motion to damage
them press and hold
release
okay
ah yeah I've never done that
before interesting your Mastery of these
techniques has earned your accent I
don't think I really mastered them I
just I think I need to be reminded of
them in the
future not sure about this I'll try to
I'll try to
remember
um let's take the sword and I what what
bows do I have uh no
sh Wait how strong is the PO ball wait
wait wait wait
wait
it's four oh
construct bow currently currently the
best thing oh wait there's weapons here
too with just rusty
[\h__\h]
uh probably good to get rid of this
one
yeah fuse it get the shield oh wait fuse
shall I fuse something
can I can you fuse a a a sword onto a
sword or wait we can fuse maybe the hoe
with the
sword can you fuse a sword onto a sword
of course you can huh you can do
anything what the
[\h__\h] that is so
stupid can you fuse a you can't fuse a
bow though right a bow onto a bow or so
you can do Shields and wait a
second now aren we
curious well how would you do
that n no you can't I don't think you
can do that doesn't seem like you can a
double bow the only thing that confus is
the arrows I would assume which is fine
makes sense look at this what the [\h__\h]
is this on my
back weird
ooh a Zite sword ooh it doesn't look
like a sword weird okay did I pick it up
properly or did I leave it in
okay and there we go another Shrine two
more and I can can get another heart I
think guys did you see on
Twitter I made dashim Maki t
for breakfast I tested it
yesterday and it was really bad cuz I
put I trusted a recipe though but I put
way too much
Dashi
the the tuna flake uh juice way too much
of that actually I bought like stuff to
make the Dashi by myself but then when I
was in the Asian market to find the
meting which is like a sweet rice one
um when I found the mid they also had
the Dashi in a bottle and I was like
wait this is way
easier so I just went with a
[Music]
Dashi finally making use of all the
Asian markets you know they got some
good stuff sometimes I feel like the a
lot of the sweets and all that that they
have is just
[Music]
no not that not that much good stuff cuz
it's
like not the it's just not the good
stuff yeah
but I like some of the drinks cuz they
have ra and I am kind of biased when
it's about
ramun let
me cook I have so much
food but why not um oh yeah what does
this one do a speed boosting a wonderful
let's make one cook it with monster
Parts see I need more of those lizards
monster parts so for example this one
now I wonder it only really increases
the length of the Boost or the strength
of the Boost if I add more lizards right
doesn't matter if I add more Monster
Parts I would
[Music]
assume I would think
right s this
s s this
s also I saw this one has also medicinal
value but like what would it do can I
add it to make a medicine stronger or
no does someone know that someone
try find out can make a heal potion
oh no I don't want to mess up my my
Potion
No
[Music]
oh yeah okay oh that's fine then just a
small potion
please o only 3 minutes yeah yeah okay
uh should I wait I think I want it to be
daytime m so let's go to
morning so I had somewhat healthy
breakfast for once I had a banana and
the dashim maku the selfmade one and it
was really good I thought I thought it
tasted pretty close to the one that I
can that I would get in
Japan but I'm not sure like I feel like
without the atmosphere of Japan around
me
I know they're so
smart without the atmosphere of Japan
around me it also doesn't like 100%
taste like
typical
ooh ooh traveler
Shield
uh
nice travelous sword noce they all look
so Rusty but they're not sh sh they're
not necessarily
Rusty they're
just
corrupted P has sent urgent orders from
Lookout Landing for all of us on the
monster control as highquest continues
to float she's Ted us with searching the
area beneath it for princess Ella and
her protector you can give me a name I
have a name be aware that the Gloom has
spread even more in this area prepare
yourself Before you depart
[Music]
oh
sorry link is that really you when did
you get out from the castle I'm so
ashamed I've been on watch you here this
whole time and I didn't see you at
all yeah I don't I don't know how it got
out of there I don't know either I've
really got to get serious about my
training Captain HZ doesn't know that
you're back does he link you should
report him right away he's on the gate
Tower at the top of the hill past the
lower
Gates gate Tower top of the hill past
the lower Gates uhhuh
uh Happy Mother's day indeed hello
everybody any mommies in in the
chat let's go
freaking
stamina open up open the
gates wait
what can I climb
over surely I can
right
uh-oh a close one am I supposed to go
for a
here en your abilities well I know I can
go up but I can't go straight for I I
that hurt a little little bit oh hello
why did you not open the door for
me
hey this area is off limits while we
conduct our search you can't just come
wanding in here like that link is you
I'm sorry I had no idea that you
returned wait if you're back then does
that mean we don't need to do the search
party anymore
oh you should go to talk to Captain hose
very end of this road
okay let's
go birds and critters let's try
again almost had
it almost
regretful who is you are you
h no he's shars
shars link no it can't be him I can't
allow anyone past here this area is
restricted only to those involved in the
search for prin Zelda I'm searching for
her I'm searching for
her first Gate House okay but I'm
searching for her too obviously I'm link
I'm always searching for Zelda
it's like my what my life is all
dedicated
to Jean
say utas
uhhuh I'm just spitting image I am link
I am indeed link oh let's get rid of
um another one
got this one
nice
[Music]
Apple you remind me of
you you look like you but couldn't be
you right I mean we're looking for you
but even if I found you as you can see I
would not believe it's you so how could
you ever be successful in your search
for me if you you find me and you don't
realize it's
me you maybe you've already seen me a
million
times standing on the edge and staring
in is
intense seeing a chasmine person is far
better than hearing about
it it's hard to see though but yeah
that's kind of crazy that's
crazy he's too busy who PA oh look he's
got a a helmet bucket
helmet no not a bucket a cooking pot
helmet yeah I'm looking for for Princess
Zelda way on top of the gate house
what's the gate house is this the gate
house where's the gate
house oh first gate there we
go found it what you got on
weapons Soldier spare let's go oh
[Music]
uh
H and soldier's Broad Sword
sick you know what
um no not with the farming
H uh
how about sword on sword sword
sword
nice I'm
confused
technology is amazing they got torches I
saw I had a torch before but if we have
like all kinds of light up thingies I
don't think we'll ever need torches
all right okay they say he's on top of
this uh
wait I know what to do I know what to
do
really why won't you let me do it here
that makes no
sense
h
n and I can't go through this gate
either can
I you want me to climb now or
what no I don't think it's too high I've
seen I've seen people do this before but
okay wait let me climb up here and
then let's try
again
naha swim swim do a little swim
is this considered the top
already oh there he
is sorry but I'm in the middle of
something uh
uh link is that you you're alive and all
in one piece it looks like does that
mean Princess Zelda is safe too what a
relief hang on you're alone but you
heard the princess calling out to you
and you're ear to help with the search I
I see he looks more Spanish to me than
French but I don't I can't do a Spanish
accent how do you do a Spanish
accent maybe I don't I'm a little
confused but that doesn't matter right
now what matters is continuing our
search for Princess Zelda I'm relieved
to see you come up here and help us out
though we need some good
news yeah he's French now I like his
mustache replace your wise with
J's the sheer amount of Gloom has gotten
overwhelming our work care there's no
wise requires high pitched sounds and
strong
zet I don't see anything of that
here Captain it's
Princessa what that's s German though
selaa Princess
Princess Zelda
is that is that
Spanish wait what Princess
Zelda wait so one thing that uh we
haven't talked about but that's like
super super [\h__\h] weird I maybe I
mentioned it during the Super Chat
reading when it happened the blood moon
um why is she so excited about the blood
moon and is like almost summoning it
like a cult leader
huh
why I I that was so so weird like she's
like when the blood moon happens she's
like Yay blood moon more enemies that
kill everyone let's go you
know is there a reason for that and then
why is she here is this the same creepy
Zelda is there a fake Zelda is oh my God
Princess Zelda she's safe is she real
though oh
bye-bye what a
tease what an attention
seeker wait what did we all see that I
don't know did I see
that you saw Princess Zelda turn into
light and fly off right oh how strange
this this this is an emergency
situation why would you live without
saying a word to us we need to let bu
know about this as soon as possible uh
considering what we just witnessed I
think it makes sense for us to withdraw
but we'll take a bit please you must
tell Pur about what happened here as
soon as possible I just came here to
tell you about me and now everything's
about Zelda again Zelda here Zelda there
it's always about
Zelda oh what's this that's a clock
that is a Croc maybe there's also a Croc
on top of
this oh
[\h__\h] let's go to the
cck I can
I we'll have to do some CL ho [\h__\h]
don't be so weird it's how they call it
in
German just let me say it like that I'm
not doing it on purpose I'm trying to
say it as clear as [\h__\h]
possible how much clearer do I have to
[Music]
be there's the balloon one right
what this is the balloon one I already
heard them
ah no they
move
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] wait difficult what how how can I
stand on top of the bird too no you have
to stand
here
M oh come on
and
one
two oh free
[Music]
yay cute bye-bye y so
cute what else is there there's some
some
treasure can't believe we saw Zelda just
now but that was just maybe our a
manifestation of our wishes to see her
who knows who knows
really I should probably not go any
further and explore here huh should I
just go
back just want to see a little bit just
a little
bit the music is so sad
here now
wow so I heard that when you touch this
miasma like you know not just this this
uh air
stuff but like
real like the stuff that's on the ground
then it will drain your heart and you
won't get it back with normal healing
healing items there's items uh like
special
herbs uh the I think some I forgot what
it's called but there's an herb that if
you cook it then and it will get you
your hearts back I'm got to be careful
with that but maybe we'll get like some
armor in the
future that um doesn't get affected by
it yeah it reduces the max HP yeah the
sandelion exactly okay can I like Port
back to the Lookout
Landing
no I am p to the
K comes back over time without
items over time
really must be a long time
though
oh Japanese translater
[Music]
that's a big ass translated text thank
you thank you
[Music]
I'm so proud of my t Yaki the the the
the shape yo this
time I I got it down really well it's
actually pretty difficult to flip it I'm
like generally bad at flipping things
when cooking but you have to roll it
over without pushing like the rest away
that that's kind of difficult to me cuz
it's
like you know you have this like Square
frying
pan yeah I have I have one I bought one
you have this uh Square frying pan and
then you make one really thin
layer uh with the
mixture and then after uh a little bit
really a little while on medium
heat after a very
short what [\h__\h] very short time um you
have to
uh start rolling it the first one is
still easy I would
say you have to do it when the the top
is still liquid a little bit and the
bottom is has
turned not
liquid H yeah yeah and then uh then you
pour more of the liquid again just a
really thin
layer and uh you have to lift up the
little roll thing that you have on on
one side of the frying pan you have to
lift it up to let some of the liquid
underneath as well yeah it's also kind
of like glue I guess
yeah um and then you wait a little bit
and then you roll it to the other side
roll the big one you already have over
the new fin layer and then it's on the
other side again and then you repeat
until you have no more liquid
left but rolling it without moving
around the the new bottom layer that you
created if you know what I mean that's
that's kind of scuffed sometimes but I
did it so perfectly voice
[Music]
sounds like an egg qule that's a
stretch link well did you find
anything what you telling me Princess
Zelda was at the castle and then she
transformed into light and flew off I've
got to say your stories are always so
well they are but you're telling me that
that's what you saw so I've got to
believe it sounds like we need to change
our approach wait let me open my froat
candy
at least today I don't have a braving
problem I also aired my whole apartment
with fresh cold
air and I cleaned I I I vacuum clean
again and I did the dishes I did the
laundry I did so much before the stream
cooking cleaning you
know since the princess flew off maybe
we should redirect our efforts and dig
into the upheaval for now at least I've
already got a few regions in mind to
start exploring I bet we'll pick up
clues about where she flew off to as we
look around oh yeah you've still got the
pad right can I see it for a
sec it's a little worful wear but seems
to be functioning fine map map
M mhm all right I forgot that before we
can look at your overall map of higher
room
we need to add map data from right
around Lookout Landing and for that we
need our Sky View Tower mhm Joshua
Joshua what's the status of the sky VI
Tower right now let me
see that ah so it is these temp these
towers yeah out worldly destruction
looks to be complete are they built new
ones
oh but the travel point is still
undergoing final
adjustments the travel Point needs
tweaking sounds like I better get
cracking sorry about this linky I'll fix
it up quick so just hang tight in the
meantime why don't you rest up you must
be pretty tired the emergency shelter is
just a spot for you it has free beds and
a kitchen so as well stocked for getting
some rest and rejuvenating yourself if
you want more info
mhm tou a soldier who's watching over
everything from the center right where
the meres to shelter entrances o okay is
it below if you need clothing for your
travels I already bought everything it's
[Laughter]
empty I'll be over by our Sky View Tower
so when you're ready to head out just
let me know yeah all right josha let's
work on our final preparations for the
tower I'll handle the travel Point josha
you're in charge of the switch woohoo
okay D you can count on me is she her
child or so because they look so similar
but like who who's the
father why is it not
[Music]
me questions
questions she's our Apprentice yeah she
can be an assistant and Apprentice while
being a daughter
though she can be
of course you can that's family
business who says it isn't
you
n
indeed sorry I didn't greet you properly
when you first arrived here link I was
just so relieved to see you my name is
scorpus I've been charged with managing
Lookout Landing if you have any
questions about the place any at all ask
me now please let me show you the
emergency shelter
[Music]
oh oh it is
below do I have to open it up like that
every
time well I probably won't be using it
again will
I this underground Vault used to be an
emergency shelter for the Royal Family
now we're making constant use of it feel
free to make yourself at home in our
vault use any equipment
too
ooh aha like a
bunker and the beds look quite okay
quite
comfy oh ah I don't have to go up to the
SK I I went all the way up to the sky
for my uh fifth
heart seems like I don't have to do that
anymore there's one here there's a map
of uhuh mountains Woods
volcano uh whatever that
is hold
on book of
Reaper maybe combined with
something no F no that should that
should
be no no the reaper no no can I not do
the
[Music]
reaper I feel it should
work oh it's already
fused oh
okay plus
five I want to I want I want to carry
more okay I'll leave it there it will
disappear right I can get it at some
point O
O It's kind of the kitchen and they do
their dishes here that's kind of weird I
feel like that's kind of waste you could
use it as a b bath
too or do they have a different bath
look that's that's uh that's us me and
Zelda
funny
Dusty not a not
a he's got a
quest hey are you new here you might
scof but I know a fresh face when I see
one I can say that because I mean youve
come with too my name is bermano and
they put me in charge for cooking for
some reason I want to say something fany
like for today's menu we have a fruit
and mushroom mix that will wrap you
right up yeah I was really looking
forward to say now but I I'm Plum out of
apples if I don't have my most important
ingredient say goodbye to a richful
flavor
my nose is detecting an aroma do you
have apples how many do you
need I guess we won't
know they do the dishes while bathing
multitasking saving
water side quest
yay oh oh I'll get some of the food yet
wow she's
excited yeah I
mean I've cooked better but
sure I mean I mean you know we're in an
apocalypse kind of Crisis so yeah I like
to make a big deal out of it but anyone
can make it all you need is an apple a
mushroom and a pot you should try making
some complete got some free food more or
less maybe he only took one apple then
that is pretty much a win
situation okay let's sleep I don't know
if the game really wants me to sleep if
I have to sleep or if if just if you
want
but oh oh [\h__\h] see the glow of the Blood
Stained Moon shines upon the land see
how motivated she
is the aimless spirits of slain monsters
ET turn to she loves it the world is
threatened once again she loves it she's
enjoying every second of
it
creepy I've been uh catching up on D
tendo by the
way [\h__\h]
um he's he's not very far yet anyway cuz
he does like 30 minute Parts uh but he
did like several a day at least on the
first
day and so through him I'm watching the
German version of the game and
damn a the voices are so good in German
it's like so rare that they're good in
German you
know do you guys want to hear it a
little bit should I switch to German a
little bit we we'll switch back to
English but like but for that we would
have to be able to hear cuz you really
got to hear
Zelda you got to hear
Zelda I can do voices in German and and
text in English right wait how do I do
it uh how do I how do I how to
setting where are
settings where are the
settings I wait
here options
Japanese English
French is there different voice over for
the French French and the Canadian
French
what I mean I understand there might be
some differences but what they have
their own voice over for slight
differences sheesh different dialect
could Canadian uh French speaking people
not understand French
French or could they they just speak it
differently as a Canadian I don't even
understand
it normal French people can't understand
Canadians
oh Disney songs are different in French
and Canadian too oh Canadian understand
French we don't understand Canadian oh
okay different dial like how Mexican
Spanish is different than Spanish
[Music]
Spanish
n French can German German Spanish Spain
Spanish Latin America Italian Russian oh
that's it wait there's no like
[Music]
Korean no Chinese no Korean no Chinese
or is it just like not available in the
in the version of the game that I bought
like you would have to buy it from their
marker or
so that's surprising those are big
languages
too ah maybe in the Asian
[Music]
version
Regional maybe Regional yeah maybe it's
a regional thing um no okay
German I hope we can get uh to hear
Zelda otherwise the the one time where
you will hear her is maybe with the
blood moon
announcement ah and I wanted to
do um wait what was it the camera
speed is it faster the higher I set it
or is it faster the lower I set it lower
right no wait no wait I selected Spanish
what how's that
possible okay now we got
it and the camera is faster which don't
tend to recommend it you can rewatch cut
scenes and Adventure log
oh ma
there which one should we
how
[Music]
how ah I need to do a quest first
activate the towel
first okay are they at the
tower hello yes St
if I oh will she be German too I think
her German voice was also pretty good if
I put this here then that goes there no
no that's not quite it y yo that was
weird that should do
it hey link you all said I just wrapped
up here myself the travel point is
working fine now or it will be once you
do your
part YooHoo hey we're ready josa pull
the switch hey
hey hey is hey in German just so you
know I know it's very confusing
but ooh cute they put lanterns on it
very
cute what
[Music]
[\h__\h] couldn't we have just kept the Chik
Towers oh wait I get all of them do I
get all of them at
once no
way oh if that's the case or at least a
nearby ones
maybe no no
[Music]
way um uh they're activated to be
activated by
me all the sky view Towers have now been
activated from afar her her glasses are
glowing okay link your
turn how go hold the pad over that
[Music]
terminal
okay can I get a cut scene please so we
can show up the German
voices do
are we cooking yet mhm all right the sky
tower is now active on your
map that means you can now use this
travel point to get here at any time
instantly the same is true for every Sky
View Tower you add to your puad
impressive
right but Sky tiles are about more than
just traveling
quickly your primary function is to
survey the area or more simply put to
make a map the pad works with the Sky
Tower and scans the topography directly
onto the map pretty great H only thing
is you need a paraglider when you're
scanning what
why it takes a lot of skill and nobody
here had what it takes to be honest
that's why we haven't tested this out
yet we needed you which brings us to
this
the parag
glider this item given to you by Pura
lets you ride the wind and glide through
the sky press X in midair to activate it
y right it's showtime let's start with a
test
scan is this like like you know in space
space stations where you train like
flying around in this container can I do
that here is it like a air
machine now it's time for our our first
test launch I mean our first test just
step over there into the circle and find
me afterward all right mhm I'll be
observing from the research
lab yeah when the test scan is over
we'll have a final briefing on the
search for Princess Zelda and I'll also
need to update your map with the places
where the upheaval has wre wrecked wed
the most Havoc best of
luck
okay what was was what was it press a oh
my God what the [\h__\h]
he German
gasps the [\h__\h] is that thing on my
[Music]
front this is so much less heart attack
than
oh than shica Towers man they're
literally just letting you fly
they like bomb you up into the sky
catapult
[Music]
you I
mean it it's Hightech
somehow but compared to shikat isn't
this a
downgrade
wow nice we got a first map wonderful
MH ah the guy does the sky also get
updated ooh wait there was there was no
no Island above us is that what that
means and
now now I can glide but that takes that
takes stamina
huh where do we want to do we want to go
somewhere I mean she said to come back
to Hill right
so we about to come back to
H can I make it through the
hole I
did uh a hole in
one yeah yeah yeah
gamer of course I am who do you think I
am who do you think you're talking
to Holy nice landing thank
you give me a cut scene welcome back
that was some good gliding up there link
I expected nothing less and you even
came back through the hole where you
came out of damn so how did it go did
you get a proper map scan mhm good that
map is crucial to our search there are
skyb Towers in every region of the world
you'll want to make a point of visiting
them all unless you're a speedrunner and
you don't care for that [\h__\h] and you
just want the the fastest time anyone
could ever get then just go straight for
Ganon wherever he is we don't know but
good luck with that so let's talk about
the upheaval it's affected more than
just a castle reports of other strange
phenomena have been coming in from all
over hyro let's take a look at your
[Music]
map 100% Speed Run yeah okay oh damn
that wait 100% in breath of the wild
included the
which probably will be the case again in
tears of the kingdom do do they have
100%
speedrun with emitting the codo or are
they all forced to do it with the codo
cuz
that that is a very painful very
lengthy
speedrun they all get the codo oh my
God what's the fastest 100% speedrun of
breath of the
wild wonder how fast you can do
it does that mean you have to do all
side quests
too less
day
nah nah 20 minutes for 100% that's
impossible yeah 16 hours that sounds
more like it
15 hours 27 minutes yeah that sounds
more like it we're talking 100%
guys
yeah
damn sheesh that's a long speedrun
that's not very
Speedy the first report comes from hibra
to the
Northwest next up is Elden to the
Northeast the ghetto door reporting
trouble gudo are reporting trouble in
the southwest and finally there's rayu
to the east the strange phenomena are
concentrated in these four regions yeah
I can't say for certain but I've got the
Ning suspicion that we might find out
more about Princess Zelda by looking
into these
phenomena are you sure when it's all
useless oh they can't turn off the
switch yeah it would be nice if you
could take a break in between just stop
the timer and then go
back hey Doc I don't know if this is
helpful but I heard something weird the
other day it was about someone who might
have seen Princess Zelda at voo Village
over in HEB recently that is pretty
weird yeah generally speaking I don't
put much stock in here say but this does
sound like it's worth looking
into they probably also just saw like a
little little image of her and then
quickly she disappeared Oh and before I
forget link we asked the lucky clover
Gazette to help us in the search of
Princess Zelda there's nobody who knows
more about the goings on in hyro than
them you can find them near the entrance
to retto Village if you do go there you
should speak with the editor I'm sure
she could help out in some way too I'll
be here directing a variety of
Investigations into the upheavals man
chasms and new ruins I'll also be
looking in to the different Villages
someone somewhere might know what's
happened to the princess mm- they don't
know
[\h__\h] I'm counting on you to check out
the major phenomena that are traveling
regions around hyink we'll find princess
Sala one way or
another I got to find goggles well I'll
help you sorry I can't talk now there's
something I got to discuss with goggles
oh goggles a person Oh I thought it was
goggles
goggles right about our Research into
the chasms let's talk
later I want the side quest didn't you
have a side quest it look like a side
[Music]
quest got to find
goggles where's goggles who's goggles
are you calling him
goggles
ah you found him though come on please
now there we go
ah what a pleasant morning hey you is it
sure you've got the P pad p and I work
together on design but I'm the one who
put it together you know we should have
called it the Robbie pad technically
speaking come on goggles are you even
listening to
me oh yes sorry you were saying I was
saying that I want to go investigate the
deps look if you're not going to listen
to me I'll go and jump into a chass
myself no way know how you can't do that
the devs not the developers the devs are
far too F vast for you to explore on
your own and we've only barely begun to
look into
them I'd love to go ganting around down
there too who knows what wonders are at
the bottom of those jasms but no matter
how wonderers they may be it's far too
dangerous for you I'm not about to allow
our young prodigy to go wandering around
somewhere so unknown so foul if anything
were to happen to Pur favorite to then
it would be the end for me the end but I
need more on the figure out if we have
more info on it then it should help us
better understand the
deps Oh short man sorry I didn't mean to
leave you out of the
conversation looks a bit dorky yeah let
me get you out to speed our servy team
brought back some some artifacts from a
Journey Into the Depths and one of them
caught my
eye oh is that one of the wall pieces
that we looked
at this piece of slate specifically the
image depicted on it see that figure
standing up on two legs with one arm
raised up well I have a theory I think
it could be evidence that a mysterious
that mysterious people once lived in the
depths that's why I want to go down
there so I can see if there are any more
depictions like this one I want to see
it for
myself but goggles here says it's too
dangerous and you won't let me
go josa come on now I'll tell you what
I'll go down there myself and see if I
can't find anything about the figure on
that slate and Link will join
me right as long as I don't have to go
along fun we'll start by looking for
anything down there that resembles the
figure on the S assuming we find what
we're looking for we'll use you purest
pad's camera to take a picture of it for
josu perfect
plan yeah camera yeah I guess I didn't
learn how to use it
yet mm your tail is teach me once we're
down there okay monsters mhm guess we
should enter through the chasm to the
south of the Lookout Landing I'll go on
ahead once you're ready and wearing to
go come find me there t
wait hang
on
no no hanging
on yeah Grandpa taking us for a walk but
I might do that off screen the side
quest I want to do side quest on my own
although maybe this one's just this one
feels like an important side quest
though I'm sorry you got red into all
this SWS man kakas means well but when
he wants to help me he leavs before he
looks but here maybe this will help you
out at least oh I already have like a
million of these
please this is important okay okay yeah
I thought so it feels important I have
enough of that the chasms are pretty
deep so light from the surface doesn't
make it down there it's pitch black but
if you attach a bright bom SLE seat to
an arrow and shoot it it'll light up the
area definitely a useful trick down
there and you want to head straight out
of Lookout Landing sou gate you'll find
a Chasm goggles used just outside and
don't know much about how your camera
works but I'm counting on you to bring
me that
picture okay let's do it first then I
need to sze or South north
south let's go self self self
self
so wow strong
horse thank
you thank you very much mucho
[Music]
let me bring Chad closer to me yo you
know another thing I got at the Asian
market is some yummy
Japanese uh honey rice crackers I've got
a thing for rice crackers now Japanese
ones cuz like when I whenever I ride
airplane to
Japan often they give you like rice
cracker as snack but like a mixture of
them
oh there's a
beehive how do you how do you do that
properly you shoot it maybe and then
collect it don't they hurt
you they've got like in the in the
mixture they often have like spicy ones
too but I don't need the spicy ones I
only eat the other ones but but that
having to eat it in an airplane because
the only salty snack they have being
forced to eat it several
times now I'm like really really into it
actually
save the spicy ones for me to
closeth how about
here yeah I think that
worked if I oh no oh no no oh
no wait can I roast them I'm so
sorry can I get uh roasted bees
now oh they're
gone but that is definitely a solution
to fight
them they're not on the ground are they
okay let's get my beehive I thought that
if you get bees you can also maybe use
them for
cooking you're so
smart what the [\h__\h] is it the trees
again coer bee honey
m i no it's not okay it's just
jelly all righty am I going the right
way I
come
on why why am I incapable of getting the
[\h__\h]
insects IM Tenny hi I I talked to one of
these before they have some stuff to
sell looks pretty good but again I
thought it was expensive so I didn't do
it cute
Fox Dazzle
fruit God damn it I just want some
insects so basically if you touch this
then your heart gets your hearts get uh
depleted got to be
careful f
I'm covering the ah Dam it okay yeah
yeah yeah
yeah we going to put you up here
again we going to put me over here again
ah you don't see much of my
sword I make myself small
nice is good am I too small can you guys
see
me I'm I'm I'm going to later eat the
rice crackers they're going to be so
crunchy but for now I'm in chocolate
mood all good okay
so Quest is here
right do I do I just go
in did he go in yeah yeah I I talked to
him before
actually
mhm we just go
in where we where you supposed to meet
him but the the sign is inside it looks
like it's
[Music]
inside should I just jump and then fly
with my with my what's it called my
flying thingy to
be in control of Landing properly
way I'm scared uh how do you jump
again oh god what the
[\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] wait that's [\h__\h]
scary holy [\h__\h]
um wait uh uh
wait how do uh I forgot uh wait okay I
can actually just land here there's
someone there is there holy [\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h] I can't Thro while I'm flying huh
can
I don't
worry no wrong wrong thing well it's not
the Dazzle fruits right is even though
that sounds like it could be it it's
these ones
M well actually here it's not so bad
like oh wait it looked to me like
fairies it's just no it's
just more of like bright Bloom insects
right nice okay anyway this this the guy
here or am I supposed to what talk to
you
no are you
link pleasure to meet you I am ponik
from the zonai survey team Robbie told
me to guide you to him once you arrived
but he rushed along with such haste that
I didn't bring enough bright Bloom seeds
and now I've run out so I lost sight of
him what the [\h__\h] is that I thought he
was taking a short walk over that
glowing area over there he's German no
he's not ger he's not French he's German
then he just kept
going and going and last I saw him he
was heading way out there off to the
vest it is very German if you know
German accent do you have any bright
Bloom seeds with you yeah I have plenty
oh that's great news
H light from the surface doesn't reach
down here so as you may have might have
noticed you'd be risking your life to W
here without a light source you know you
can easily get Brad Plum seeds from
caves and their light ups if struck so
they're pretty easy to use too we use
the seeds all the time on the zai sonai
survey team the simplest way is to throw
them with your hand yeah I know I know I
know the arrows yeah yeah I know I know
Os
Os these trains are like peile
trees what the [\h__\h] but like that
normally wouldn't grow here right that's
because of this weird [\h__\h]
here I'll
assume R trees yeah
at least I got one even though I was
already like slowed down a deep
Firefly can be cooked into an elexir
which will add a faint glow to anyone
who consumes it yeah yeah i' I've heard
about this stuff too you can also make
normal food that makes you
glow
mhm okay let's go here first I already
forgot what he said about this like what
the [\h__\h] is this what is this n n light
route I can touch it it looks like a
shrine is it a shrine no oh maybe it
lights up the
area when I
touch oh
oh I'm the only one who can touch it
like that huh
aha it's
very there shall be
light oh did it just make plants grow as
well y oh it's like a yuo oh it's a
teleportation point now
too you this I think the light would
dispel the darkness and brightness the
of the surrounding area cool are there
more oh did it heal me why did it show
my
hearts
nice the alien trees look
funky okay now that it's bright I
actually lost sense of direction
ironically he was here once
right I'm not going to bother with
reading this
ah it restores any Gloom I may have
received
ah and I want to explore oh there's some
stuff here that I can use for cooking
model Bud a wild flower with a powerful
odor that can disorient and confuse
making it difficult to tell friend
from ah you can throw this maybe attach
it to an arrow and shoot an enemy from
an enemy
camp puff shroom spreads a cloud of find
spes when a stimulus is applied the
bitter powder makes them
inedible
okay what is that stuff up
there wait
[Music]
I know I don't have to go here but I'm
curious very curious I'm very
curious yeah it looks like something's
weird over there is it an enemy camp
would there be enemy camps down
here oh oh what the [\h__\h] is that oh
they're
working oh oh oh oh oh oh oh what the
[\h__\h] oh wait they have that [\h__\h] on them
too so if I touch them ooh that might
not be good got to stay distant uh-oh
that doesn't hurt them uh rre maybe we
have a solution
later for how to fight
those I don't want to not sure about
using hammer on them
yet maybe as long as they don't touch me
directly as long as I don't let them hit
me maybe it would be
okay oh yeah no let's go back on
track let's go
back wait
wait I got one
incredible we're almost there but
there's a lot of of this stuff here
this is where I activated it and ran off
somewhere
else over
here
right no wait that's just the
beginning they didn't mark where he is
now on my map
n yeah he was here and he moved on to
there maybe let's just follow all the
camps that we
find maybe I need to go talk again with
him oh
really really you think
so cuz I didn't find Robbie
maybe where he should be cuz I saw those
little camps already
each campfire is a
note
okay I guess I'll talk with him
once
um mhm
mhm a
mhm
mhm mhm off the West m
okay a mhm mhm okay okay okay I'll read
the go left for horse there's a horse
down
here I would feel so bad for
it what for real
how did it go down did it fall
down hey you it's really dark down here
not one bit of light gets here from the
surface even with my goggles I can
hardly see I really should have brought
some bright Bloom seeds with me not very
smart as one of the few sources of light
the glowing root growing down from above
has peaked my curiosity I'm not sure
what it is but it looks harmless enough
this place is roughly under the shrine
on on the surface H anyway I'm off to
the glowing route I see shining west of
here so you better hurry up good
moving I I see another one over there
another one of those big light
sources that was
close next note hey you're still alive
looks like this place is swimming in
Gloom get too close to that stuff and
you're asking for trouble if a guy
didn't have any bright blooms it would
be curtains then again it's my first
time down here and I haven't kicked a
bucket so I'm sure you'll be fine I just
spotted something of interest for my
goggles it's shaped like that figure
Joshua wants us to find oh I'll be
continuing to Head West
okay is this
West
yes oh there's a bomb
plants still Maiden L what do you
mean what do you mean St playing alen
ring although it is an open world
game
oh what if it lands on one of this
shitty
substance is it is it going to be able
to plant itself
anyway so far I'm always putting it on
ooh good spots those
you I feel like I
shouldn't you
wait
no
this here the big
one is he going to fight him now
yeah that's how to do it
safely he's taking care of it also the
arrow worked on these ones the stone one
didn't get any damage from it but are
you going to go for the other one too go
go go go how long does it
work you know you have one more dude up
there h let's just use normal one if I
do a head shot he should die
right where's his head here [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
that was not a head
shot I have another
chance
[\h__\h] there we go that did the trick
oh no
a
oh very
nice with been compromised but yeah I
got a good shot
there uh moblin Fang moblin
horn and some so
night TR a
sword yeah the muddle butts are nice
very helpful
um no
um oh [\h__\h] where the [\h__\h] is that
going I wanted it to be on the
tower there you
[Music]
go okay
uh no uh uh upair
well might as well use
[Music]
it
mhm getting the materials that they
already bonked
off and now I'm getting my
own although I only have like an axe
like
this wait ah they got one here don't
they the
rockhammer I want the rockhammer no
I want the
rockhammer
yeah give me that zon knite some other
Stones I would appreciate too but does
this only drop Zite oh L Zite
okay yeah only
Z I want some rubies and stuff
too okay
okay can I bunk these twoo oh
yeah only arrows inside these things
never have anything but arrows inside so
if you really need arrows that's good I
guess but if you don't cuz you kind of
get spammed with arrows it feels like
then okay we
annihilated one of the enemy camps let's
go
puff shoms I'm not sure if I'm going to
be actually even using them but I'm
going to collect just a few just in
case big area I like this whole thing
with lighting up the
areas these items it's
fun and one by
one you are
opening up the map for
yourself oh there's a there's a freaking
Firebird oh [\h__\h] I saw um I was like
when I was playing uh on my own
yesterday I fought an enemy camp and
they also had a
flying like dragonik bird with
them no no they're pretty easy to fight
though I was kind of uh oh [\h__\h]
no [\h__\h] uh let me run
first I was kind of intimidated by it
first but it wasn't so bad actually our
cudas yeah
yeah okay are we good now yeah they're
going
back and going to try again with
the setting them up against each other
method that helps a
bit [\h__\h] that didn't go as far as I
wanted it
to it's pretty much the same place yummy
okay uh wait
uh the what would I call muddle muddle
bu [\h__\h] ah
no
wasted ah [\h__\h] these don't shoot so far
y maybe
here [\h__\h] what
what I'm so far
okay got
him how many are there
is he going to come down is oh maybe he
shoots from the
top he should what are
you is he doting because now the enemies
are his
enemies yeah that's what I like to see
shoot the bird shoot the bird or I'll
shoot the bird
[Music]
God [\h__\h] [\h__\h] the bird I'll just have a
descend oh oh they're fighting each
other now okay uh
yeah now we're fighting for
real
y
uh yeah mhm
uh uh a little bit uh panick don't know
how to play this game right
[Music]
now okay was there one left I see
another like small bird flying around
there is that even
enemies well I think we're
done ah don't don't touch me don't touch
me I think being touched by you is
danger yeah the the bats
this is like a
Zite uh Farm here like everywhere there
[\h__\h] ton of
zonite otherwise you had to get it from
the sky no you can't get it from
anywhere but the underground and the
overground the sky it
seems attach
key I know they had a function like
that and I want more of those muddle
items those are
good okay H if we go over there that's
still West and we need to go there to
activate the light what is that
there's like blue lights are those just
uh the
insects oh are they curious about the
light sorry for disturbing you home I
guess another enemy camp over there
oh there's a
hill didn't we literally like follow
Robbie uh immediately after he left like
how could he have done all this on his
own but didn't he say we're going to do
it together and he went off on his own
now of course he's lost oh but I see him
he's over
there I was just going to get like
really angry about him going off alone
so far and obviously now he's in danger
oh hey yo that's what he meant yeah okay
wait we'll see you in a second
[Laughter]
properly what is
that let me start eating my my honey soy
flavor uh rice crackers they're so
cracky so
crunchy s
[Applause]
m
yummy yeah
see
M I like them when they have this slight
sweet
flavor
oh m
so far we haven't taken any
damage
Gamer look at how bright the thing got
that light down is this dark is
downright
refreshing in fact it's so luminous it's
almost like like we're on the surface
just standing near it makes me feel so
much better how
strange oh it's you was he talking to
himself you're finally here I need to
show you what I
found
mhm what is
that that's
not the the
same um species as Ru right cuz they're
not they don't have those long
ears what are they a mutant
rat I wonder why Robbie didn't get the H
reversal treatment well maybe he's happy
in his body and his skin and he doesn't
feel like he needs
that the rats true it does look a bit
like the rats from Skyward Sword yo
you're right you mean yeah you're
right oh so maybe there is a connection
to Skyward
Sword oh yeah the mo
people yes yes yes the one that we're
digging that gave me like a digging uh
thing
yeah the the
cracker suuck in my
[Music]
throat
oh I missed the Fe sound effect playing
when I have my master sword
really oh my
God that is like an obvious connection
then I'd be happy about a connection
there I wonder what D tender would will
say to
this the statue is standing tall on two
legs one arm raised high and it looks an
awful lot like the figure josa showed us
on that piece of slate don't you
think all right get that camera of yours
ready oh yeah let me show you how it
works actually
um let me add the the download the app
actually you don't have the camera app
yet if I remember correctly I got to do
this now hope I'm not downloading any
es okay here we
go no no don't tell me just like in bre
of the wild you have to take pictures of
everything too again I won't be doing
that I will not be doing
that uh hro
compendium I'm not doing
that no no not even off screen
oh but then that means that this is not
really a side quest if you want and you
kind of need the
camera then you have to do this Quest
mhm no because like in breath of the
wild you had to take pictures of
literally everything like every item
every weapon every food item every
insect every enemy every I think every
person too I don't know no not every
person maybe but
it was quite something I mean I didn't
play it myself but watching it alone
made me feel bad for the person who was
playing
it okay let's test it
out
uh
camera uh capture wow what a good
picture the mold
people hey you have to get that go
that's a nice picture wow you should be
a photographer
photographer show
me
mhm are you winning so far I feel like
I'm winning
yeah amazing it looks like you captured
it well just I will be happy with this
let's get out of here or not you've just
started helping us research what's down
here but soon enough we're going to have
even more to investigate well then it's
time I head back up to the surface see
what look out Landing okay so here we
leaving what about us should
we should we look around
[Music]
more are they all the
same they sure look the
same I mean the the M People in Sky I
feel like they were a bit smaller I mean
okay obviously it's an oversized statue
but still they look very big don't
they and I don't think they were this
muscular were they but maybe they're
just like trying to make themselves look
cool are they facing something they're
all facing the same direction I think
yeah should we go there what they're
where they're facing let me see the map
yo this place is huge if it fills up
this nah there's no
way
wait
nah
nah they didn't make an underground area
like this for all of Hyrule did
they oh oh dear oh dear uh
ah no don't touch me don't touch
me don't don't don't grow back
together
no [\h__\h]
hell how many times can I do
this
uh
sure I feel like anything with stone is
good I did it I did it I did it I did it
I did it don't don't don't thr away
no they're cored I don't want to touch
them yeah I know you have to hit the
head I know I
know I act like I'm absolutely lost
travelous Shield traveler sword and let
me carry
it uh
20 the PO blend arm has uh 20
really what that's [\h__\h] sow
way
uh the [\h__\h] do I get corrupted slime no
it's just normal
one
uh more travelous Shields
please very powerful but breaks easily
oh
okay it does this go even deeper
maybe yeah at this point it's probably
all just oh D's Canyon
mine hold just this corrupted
material oh no no no still
not
o are yo
can I break this it's
huge oh I mean not all at once but like
oh wow I don't even will you actually
they spam you with this new material
will you actually end up
like needing all of this like so
much you will oh okay then let's get
let's get it
all how much wait it was like something
you need hundred of
something um but that's already the the
uh like reworked material right where
you need Zite for so those 100 of that
weird material in the end is how much of
zonite I wonder yeah 100 of the
Triangular
cells so how much was it for one
triangular cell was it five or 10 or
three or three to one three fre for one
triangular so 300
Z nightes for one like belt charge is
that what we're saying
oh ooh
not yeah okay we'll be needing a lot so
it's good that we're farming here but
maybe I should do this offc screen I
don't
know ooh o there's even
more wait but the fact that there's a
mine here an old abandoned mine
and those
statues yeah this is
like the those mole people probably used
to work
[Music]
here what am I doing no no no
no I want
this always there more people [\h__\h] and
need a proper I don't want to use up all
my bombs I don't have so
many I need like a
stone is that is that a stone I could
use
um I have uh almost everything connected
wa
fuse does this work a that's just an axe
again the axes don't work so well can I
fuse with
Zite can I interesting thought but I
don't know how how how much do I want to
farm here now maybe I go back here and
farm on private time oh it's not that
much here
anyway maybe I do this
privately there's a lot here oh there's
another big one what a
oh yeah let me break this one with bombs
too while I'm
here
mhm that only took two
bumps the deps are pretty empty and
contentless for the majority of it okay
are they really like stretching across
Hy ruo
or do they have an end
somewhere yes
what so maybe it's really just for
farming Don night down here this whole
area is just for farming Zite isn't it
this whole map so that you can get your
300 600 900 1,000 however many zit
huh o
[Music]
okay oh my God wait so now we have ah
now we have free layers I love layers
don't you know I love layers I do love
my
layers how is the hole of H collapsing
into the ground where are the supports
right I mean that's crazy too like a lot
of this is
a lot of crazy information now we have
floating islands and we have a huge
underground like
what I am looking forward to the
explanations if there will be
explanations there better
be well I guess for exploring this maybe
how much do you grow when you H glow
when you eat one of those fruits
if it's just a little bit I feel like
it's better to make everything glow
up
probably not much right yeah I thought
so do my fruits uh my my plants here
stay when I'm back are they
gone that's important
uh no idea nope yes what's that is I you
saying yes they're staying or
yes what the [\h__\h] is
that what the [\h__\h] is
that the [\h__\h] is
that what the [\h__\h] is that the [\h__\h] is
that the [\h__\h] is that go to it I don't
want to it's scary
light it
up it doesn't really light the thing up
someone said do it on
fire light them up but on
fire I went over his head wait or is he
just a
ghost so scary I'll talk to
him what the
[\h__\h] he wants to give me a sword TR
thank you are you going to disappear now
ah really
what
confusion well yeah I won't be here
forever I guess I I'll I'll leave oopsy
no okay that's actually a cool idea too
cuz I have so many of those
and I
just there you go
um that's a big
Camp let me just let me just take a
look
oh
not not the Fortress okay I
will
um I guess I'll go what's
that he's on a horse it's like Game of
Thrones [\h__\h] he's on a skeleton horse
skeleton
briers did he how the [\h__\h]
what he saw
me no how could they save it
I
can't I right you can uh
get uh skeleton horses all right and
breath of the wild was possible too I
think yo they're not so bad they're not
so bad actually you can take those
horses yeah Ah that's what you meant
with there's horses down here okay if
it's skeleton horses then I feel better
then I don't feel so bad
oh God they see me from such a distance
my God I the hor he chilling
now you know what that's actually really
uh useful um oh what if it rides over
this [\h__\h] does it not care I feel like
it wouldn't
mind cute my first horse first time I'm
riding on a horse and oh yes it can ride
over it ah it's una affected no guys
this is a way to travel in this place
huh not
hold it doesn't quite do perfectly what
I wanted to do but it's pretty pretty
good ooh no no no keep on going you're
not going to randomly throw me off are
you
ah did you forget to feed your horse
thank you du
lucky can you pick up items while you're
riding I want to find another Tower but
they're not they're not that
many oh what is
that what's that
can you go up horses Skyrim horse can
you go up mountains I mean no you don't
want
to Callie's horse yeah it's Callie's
horse cie would like this
horse oh there's a big stone that I
could probably make a weapon out of a
bonk bunk
weapon it's okay I'm going to go back
I'm going to go back okay
otherwise I'll never stop exploring this
place n
n a it's exhausted
bit
go go
go no stamina horse has to work out
more okay how do I get off of
it there we go thanks horsey you're very
sweet very cute cute too very nice um
hope I meet you again I will uh I would
love to use your services eventually
when I come back here but for now we
teleport uh up
to wait is he going to be at the yeah at
the Lookout Landing
[Music]
wood horse again wood horse around again
yes fairies which found the sky islands
and the caves there are fairies yeah
yeah yeah
yeah those things that I saw were no
fairies but there are
fairies notice how those roots are right
below shrines yeah okay okay so if you
switch between the top map and and look
to the bottom map the middle map from
the middle map to the what the [\h__\h] are
you doing here why is there a bird here
then you can see where the the plants
are I get it
okay
hi
bb wow look at this you the one I saw
flying around in the sky ah you saw me
you should said hi it's great to meet
the first one to ever be launched from a
Sky Wheel Tower real at that time that
moment I'm
link hold on there really your name is
link hey buddy you've got the same name
as that famous swordsman good for you
pretty big name to live up to I'm pen I
work for the lucky Club where get that
I'm writing an article about this event
better get to work we could use another
reporter you should join us seems like
uh you Brave type and all that that's
what it takes our newspaper Bas in he
brought yeah we're going there next
anyway thanks for telling
me Oh there he goes where did he
go where did he
[Music]
go so we can report our Quest
now
success hey you show josa the picture
you took of that statue the figure
matches up perfectly
[Music]
this is it this does match what's on the
fragment thank you swordsman just like
on this SL this figure must be showing
people of some sort whoever they were
which confirms my theory that people
lived in the depths yeah they did it
makes so much sense but yeah the mo
people were on the on the ground not not
in the sky right uh in the ground of the
ground not in the ground of the sky they
were in the ground of the ground yeah
yeah yeah I'm sure we'll find more
choices of them if we keep searching
this is a big big big Discovery it it
really is like uh one Zelda game finding
a connection to another Zelda game is a
big Discovery now what's next the
possibilities there's so much more to
research but before I focus on that
there's something I want to give you as
thanks for helping with this stage of my
investigation our earlier surveys of the
devs found all of this what do you think
it's
for I feel as if this contain some kind
of strange power like maybe it's energy
for something anyway it might help you
in your search for princess Ella so
hopefully you find them useful the
fragment that uh has helped us see the
depths in a new in a new way so now
we're closer to understanding one of its
Mysteries I'm going to sift through
everything that our series have brought
back from down here maybe there are even
more fragments that I can pce together
goggles swordsman thank you so much for
going down there you're welcome now let
me continue the main
quest
um mhm press a question uhhuh U we
are doing this one
right
Theo Village yeah but where is
[Music]
it
what what North
West the this
[Music]
one this
one this one that is so
far yeah okay we'll be distracted uh a
lot I think before we reach
there they want me to go there first
okay but where
[Music]
that is a Million Miles Away there's
honestly nothing here well we'll find
something to do there for sure uh I want
to mark
it I mark
it maybe I I can't mark that I have to
mark it close
by okay red light is where we going how
long until German vers there's like no
no
nothing these bunnies you know that keep
on coming out of the
frogs they feel
unbeatable and they're
frogs when they come out of the frogs
cuz they're gone immediately but okay
wait I don't want to make it run just
yet
[Music]
we got a Restless cricket from wait if
you cut the grass do you sometimes get
crickets was I just really lucky just
now and rice rice too ah
yay finally found a solution to getting
some crickets
maybe
uh maybe
[Music]
bigger ah no this one this one oopsy
this one works
differently how about this yeah okay
this works
too we're cricked farming now so far no
R though ah maybe in the in the in the
yellow grass
nice life hack
no
no I I paid attention to something else
hi
he did he's got no chance I want this
arm maybe ho with arm
uh
aha okay
armhole what was I doing ah the
bunny still it's still there forgot the
bunny it's not a bunny though I know oh
it's so
[Music]
cute no I want more
rupes that's why I shouldn't have done
it so early on God damn it but
uh it went into a
cave
Lord let's going to the
cave oh oh holy [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] is
that what are you oh what I one shoted
him oh there's more oh
oh [\h__\h] oh God who W who W what oh oh
you did that to yourself that was not
me free of them
monkey They Dro good Hammer materials oo
okay and they got long
sticks horr blin
horlin they called horlin
cuz they're horrible at being bck Blends
B blinds no no they're because they're
they're scary like a horror movie the
way they hang down
there let's get that
chest the arm is still moving spiky
spear m
H when is that one doing like a peace
sign in the
picture okay I got rid of the fire
thrower should I get one of these
too that's uh that's quite something
[Music]
I like all of these traveler sword it's
really called traveler sword
swword soldiers broadsword
broadsword that is so
stupid so dorky I should fight more so I
lose more weapons
[Music]
uh uh no uh can I do this here
ooh
exit can I burn
these bright cap cook it into a dish to
give a glowing effect to anyone who eats
it
yeah I'm not interested in that I don't
want to be glowing like a Target
basically making myself a target for
everybody I guess I'm leaving
this
here sticky lizard
cute cute oh there's one more let's get
the other one
too no no no no
no what the [\h__\h] is that to to break him
oh I got roasted no the lizard so I know
what that one does that one's actually
amazing for everyone who played breath
of the wild and was like really
triggered by the rain making it
impossible to climb up
anything with the this new
Lizard you can cook some potion that
makes you able to
oh to hold on to uh slippery surfaces
mhm
okay let's
fight oh wait no I want to
use different weapon
please I'm going to roast
you roasted bin for
[Music]
dinner even good
here wooden stick wooden stick
weak I'll take the shield no I can't
take any more Shields really I thought I
could only have like
two what are you cooking yesterday I
ended up not cooking at all I feel bad
about it but I didn't feel in the mood
and I wasn't that hungry either so I
just ate two rice crackers and one
banana but that was fine any that was
fine I was able to sleep just
fine today I will have to cook
no more
escape cuz today is the last
day
of uh do of the D
date what is that oh
hi can't see but that doesn't stop me I
am just that
good this cute he was collecting these
things yeah the enemies are like even
more realistic now cuz you can see them
working and stuff
right no none of that for me okay cool
cool cool cool I could build something
here oh ah I saw one of these
guys uh somewhere else and I he's like
oh don't I was I will hold up this sign
forever and yeah don't don't let me
don't make me let go of it and then I
don't understand like I tried he gives
you a challenge to stop it when he lets
go of it but I wasn't able to stop it I
tried I don't know how
how it's
difficult how do you actually do
it am I too
stupid you can Nick the items of their
backpack if you sneak what's on their
backpack well nothing
really
a
ah I have to support it with these
items no okay okay I thought I had to do
it with like my time tool and it just
didn't work
out yeah yeah I don't know what to do
try and go ha you support him really I
didn't unforgivable no okay okay
okay president
Hudson yeah yeah I'll do
it you've got some sticks here uh
oopsy we're going to build you some
porch don't be
scared I think if we just you
know do this can I not attach
it seems like I can't okay and it's also
not tall
[Music]
enough not the sign
what what do you
mean what do you
mean yeah I just got to
okay
wait I know what to
do I'm giving it a bit more height
I just want it straight and then like
this no wait ah
[\h__\h] attach don't press
B is this enough already what do you
think Let's test it
out try let and
go it worked you guys saying no not
enough of course it
is kiaba the Builder knows more about
building than all of you it worked of
course it worked how's the president
standing that was brilliant I would have
never thought of it all right let's get
him secure while he's still
standing
oh is he making it
permanent it looks different than what I
did you
idiot my stuff is just
there mhm it fools my heart with joy
take this with my f a red ruby okay
thanks ooh Hasty veggie rice balls he yo
with speed thanks and a bomb
flat okay thank
you that is quite nice of him to give me
so many
items another sign of standing in the
end he didn't even use my
technique that is questionable
what if I what if I blow it up now can I
blow it
up could I
oh also I've been trying to find uh eggs
on trees but every time I climb up a
tree there's no
eggs why am I so unlucky I want to cook
something with
eggs no I didn't get him
one him get
him it destroyed the tree usually Big
Trees I tried and that's when I uh found
out about the moving trees like I was
climbing up every freaking tree trying
to find eggs and then they started
moving on me and I was like what the
[\h__\h] it's freaking me out stop moving
oh I was just talking about it what what
is what is it with these
guys n goon
cor I'm I'm just walking by oh and I
know there's some cool stuff in Wells
let's
go
oh wasn't talking about you guys but
okay I'm scared to let
go uh yeah
show it to me again show me show me your
insides don't be
[Music]
shy going to use up all my weapons now
let's
go nice it
dead oh is that an egg no it looks like
a Yoshi
egg it pooped down the chest two all
right next
one why you on that
side okay round two do it again do it
again uh uh all right new
weapon finally something to get rid of
all my weapons without just throwing
them away I want them to I want to get
rid of them for good reason you know do
they even attack I mean I think they do
but not if you're like
actively tackling
them sold
Shield
y can you attach a shield to a
shield travel is
spare nice kick
Rock yes you can oh my God we have to do
it uh we have to do it oh we have to do
it yeah I'll do it with this
one I no uh set
L yeah that's what I thought it would
look like shield on
Shield
wonderful so
cute sticky
lizard they're so cute and there are
shiny
fish glowing
cavefish which also if you eat them you
glow I don't think normally I would want
that maybe in the night time when I have
to travel at night cuz I don't want to
throw um God damn it
I don't want to throw those things
everywhere God damn it I have these are
the wrong stones are
they no that's the red stone
okay
yay some good materials Rock very good
for
[Music]
cooking looking up on one of the facts
is good to make money to sell the
materials
H the meals you
mean
yeah I wouldn't want to sell my
meals yeah anyway under the wells
there's always these cool caves
apparently sometimes cooler than
others but definitely o what the
[\h__\h] definitely worth checking out was
that geckos
God damn it it just dropped into the
water looks like lizards y they just
flopped okay back up
uh you can also make food with more
potent effects when there's more variety
ingredients oh hi tree
nice what the [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] do
you want me to set you on fire hm I'm
being nice and not doing
it but I
could stupid
trees why why I want the lore behind the
trees yeah ants from Lord of the
Rings
man they're
everywhere I don't even want to fight oh
you got some nice apples
don't mind me I'm just I'm just feeling
Apple ah apples from your friend that
was the golden apple yay I got one
before actually it's not the first time
I'm getting
one
[\h__\h] you're hurting your your your tree
friend are you aware
that don't bunk your tree
friends happy little tree
friends I hate that
show stupid so
stupid wait there's another one
different from the one we just entered
right let's go in here
[Music]
too pumpkins who the [\h__\h] puts pumpkins
grows pumpkins
here no the
lizards
lizards is there more lizards
they're so
cute there's
Li I got them yay some alive some not so
alive oh I want to read this why are you
planting uh pumpkins here tell me this
well proved more than I expected not too
hot not too cold cozy really for well I
had no need for heat resistant chili
ingredients or cold resistant warm ones
I cooked for pleasure instead of
survival for a time I considered tilling
the soil in here living off the land
until the end of my days but times have
changed that people formed a myriad of
new caves consider my curiosity peaked
unexplored lands are veritable Buffet of
cooking materials and I
Oru intend to dig in uhuh if you seek
for keep moving Chef Oru master of
[Music]
Cuisine well well well
not is like she the one
behind like all of the interesting
things in the wells
or only only some of them only this
one yes chef yes chef cook it
now I was like lazy I thought I don't
want to do it because there's no no
[Music]
fire yeah I'll just do it somewhere
where there's
fire another
time but that's where the pumpkins came
from
yeah not hold oh what the
no no those really scare me the Hues
they really scared me they're probably
not called Hues in English but U it's
like a relaxo um also not that's also
German
um kaai this
Snorlax oh they're called heo also
okay do I have to fight him I could
probably sneak by
right but wouldn't that be lame don't we
want to fight
him oo I'm scared what's the what's the
best way to fight
[Music]
him [\h__\h]
well we have started the fight wish me
luck
guys
uh-oh
uh-oh uh-oh ah got him got
him oh [\h__\h] hell what is this camera
angle when you focus on
him wait wait wait wait wait I'm I'm
really confused
uhoh what's doing oh the trees not the
trees oh
God
[Music]
no okay
it's too
big fcking
out I love the music though what dides
he
do aim Dole aim
Dole there you go run run run for it
[Music]
run run run run run run okay we already
got him halfway down that's so bad
man don't hide your eye you pretty eye
come on I want to see you pretty eye oh
my one of my bows broke and oh God where
is he I had the
weapon can can still do some damage
wow round
pound uh
I only have this
[Music]
one
no no don't hide it don't hide
[Music]
it Chang his area to fight no what do I
do now
[\h__\h] I ran out of them oh got a
Thro I
guess that doesn't do
[\h__\h] well
okay what wait
go Mele well that's not how you're
supposed to fight
him
no what the
[\h__\h] uh uh
uh
uh let's eat this yummy
omelette God what do I do go for the
ankles okay I'm like really panicking
I'm also running out of weapons
sheesh yeah we can do it we can do it oh
God but he's like going to [\h__\h] kill
me every hit is
sheesh dangerous
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] he's got to get busy with something
no
no no I'm so
sad
[Music]
no
yummy where where where do the last
say
[\h__\h] okay I I'll need to bring more I
was so close I need to bring more
bows uh I have I have only two bows
[\h__\h] but why do I get more bows now
there maybe some enemy camp enemy cams
en enemy
cams
damn
damn a
little Ruby
rupy cute well there weren't any enemy
camps
here does this uh are we like before I
went into the well or is this
after I want to go there again oh well
uh do I have do I have pumpkins yes I do
okay then I think it's
after that looks like an enemy camp I
think
have used five with
[Music]
arrows well it was my first heo fight I
was still like panicking and scrambling
and all that so I think I was all right
for that we almost had him too and then
the problem was just that I ran out of
uh bows otherwise I think I would have
been
fine so oh there's a stable over there
anyway okay yeah this is perfect perfect
this is exactly what we
need but let's just not use bows now
either cuz they're going to break as
well which means I'm going straight
in I
guess is that a heno too no right it's
just one of those big ones hey come find
me what I'm here you see me clearly
you're not dreaming it's the real link
yeah all right come over
here fight
[Music]
me give me your weapons though don't
don't don't don't drop them
what did that just hurt
me no that was I think an exception
oh
well at least I fell into water uh
what who's
what the hell oo he died though
apparently how did he
die why why are you swimming towards no
I no I swear to God I swear to God no
you're not going to die in the water I I
I I was I was going towards left why is
he going towards
right don't die
now don't you die you [\h__\h]
wait that that doesn't count as a death
right it's just a I will spawn oh
actually that's way
better that is even better the boss is
dead I picked up the items I back at the
top all according to
Kaku now you little
[\h__\h] o
H where is the other
enemies want to go up now calling for
help but it's no one's helping you weird
where is your big boss no no no no no
thank God
bu he fell without the bug
b one exciting fight huh right up to the
heno we're following up with another
crazy fight man
bo b let's
go spike
ball
hey oh there's another
one oo roast bats
y oh crab I at crab hi oh we got also a
bow
wonderful tell me more about about
it nice okay we stocked up a little bit
on
[Music]
those now there's no way you can lose
well I hope so
really anything else
no okay I
guess I could go to the other side of
this like River with this route as well
but now I want to kill the
heno now I'm
determined wait it's getting dark let me
sleep by the
fire wait there's a piece of meat I
didn't realize you could take it oh my
God
ah no wait I know this I know this just
got to hide under here oh we good okay
um but I know oh I know that you have to
take
off
the oops see the
materials which is like pretty much
everything that I
have oh wait they're
all
remove this one's fine my clothes are
fine okay so now I think I'm
fine yeah okay I'll just I just walk go
over
now let's
go yes for my honor I can't let the heo
live and I think the heo not heo do they
also respawn after the blood moon or do
they stay
away they also respa don't holy
[\h__\h] thank God that wasn't me right
there well
B they do
respawn okay but I feel like you know
who I almost hit the
heno I feel like it could be a good um
experience for me to kill the
heo oh also we got to do the shrine over
there anyway
okay shall we fight him in this shitty
weather I feel like the the Lightning's
going to get
me actually let me go down the well
again yeah I'll make a fire here um how
do you do this
again
uh do I throw it
no this
one yeah that
worked uh yeah until morning started a
fire today oh I could have also done
with Flint oh
not cute
music are there any there they're here
they here the Kos are here how many just
those two
the
okay sticky lizard
good
good I'm just getting them for my own
satisfaction cuz they're adorable I want
to keep them as pets I'm not even going
to make them into
medicine oh now this dude has a
disadvantage
that he can't take any more trees but
maybe that's a actually disadvantage for
me because then he won't be busy with
the
trees well well
well sure me fix the sound
sure heal up
you do I have an item of like
extra
HP would it be like a green
heart h
I don't know what it would look like I
don't have one do I what what was this
one ah and this one restores um your
hearts if you were damaged by Gloom but
I guess I don't have this what I'm
looking
for okay
oh is it worth it doing that right away
actually does does it count as
damage I'm
scared my poo is badly damaged uh
yes oh please oh please wait [\h__\h]
[Music]
hell okay okay
I don't know what I'm doing but I'm
doing it
[Music]
yo you can't you really can't do it with
like the the aiming function because
uh it just aims for his head give
me y let's go so you have to uh aim on
your own but but the problem
is he is moving
[Music]
constantly
okay nice
sball I couldn't
run I could run
yummy yummy omel get up get up get up
you little
I'm putting you into the user room link
you don't want that do you see see he's
so
[Music]
motivated okay don't don't get to greedy
I got to greedy I got so greedy it's
okay it's okay it's okay I got super
greedy there I wanted to finish
him
oh
oh I did it oh don't get hurt at the end
does it does it hurt you when he drops
no yay oh look at all that fruit pal
fruit
he used to make an alexir with some say
it has other uses as well oh maybe on
the weapon V fruit uhhuh provides
resistance against
electricity fortified pumpkin heix horn
attach it to a weapon to increase attack
power or cook it with a credit to make
an
Elixir toenail cook it with a credit to
make an
Elixir attack power or
Elixir yay we did it I did it I did
it gamer did he drop any more things
over
here no doesn't look like
it y i I did pretty well didn't I my
shots I landed them pretty nicely you
can Bon the big guy with a Boulder
Boulder oh more food you mean like a big
Stone yeah running beneath him too mhm
oh there's one of the
oh oh please don't hit the money
bunny there's one of the money bunnies
over there
there sheesh weather is [\h__\h] in this
area all the time tanky
got okay money
bunny you kind of really make me nervous
you
know [\h__\h] money bunny I did get one
purple Ruby though all right all right
all
right money
bunny cute name
Rhymes a cricket I got a cricket I got a
cricket
oo what are you doing the bubble frog
creatures yeah yeah yeah they live in
caves yeah I've
noticed tell us
more don't scare me like that my poor
heart can take it are you by any chance
looking for bubble frogs too yeah
they're kind of funky I like them ah I
know what they must have asked you to
supposedly there are creatures called
Bubble frogs that live in caves they're
bluish and whitish and stick to walls OD
stuff and those two Folks at Woodland
stable in Northeast Elden curious pair
very strange maybe a little off they're
looking for something uh oh are they the
ones that need the the drops huh they
asked me to do the collecting so did
they ask you to no they offer treasure
in exchange is that what those are good
for m it was a sweet deal uh at least it
would have been but I don't know the
first thing about cave creatures the
treasure was awfully appealing
though no I don't want to talk to you
I'm done talking to you I want to pick
up the peppers wait what you managed to
get your hands in a bubble gem you
should try to find those two oddballs in
a woodland stable in alen in the
Northeast yeah I'll find them eventually
Mystic
Rob
okay so is there one in here too
or there should be one here too but
there first of all there's these
mobs
hi show your true
self see this is what happens for people
who are like what do they do do they
even attack yes they do if you were like
stumbling around like
me [\h__\h] hell
my so ni just damage come
[Music]
on [\h__\h] he retracted fast oh because
he's
dumb and he spits out a trest of course
we so [\h__\h] slipp over
here my weapons I'm running out of
[Music]
weapons but that killed
him
nice need to find better gear well I'm
trying I'm picking up everything I can
you know and tells see I can't carry
more Shields it's okay I will um attach
maybe my shield to it uh
no whatever what is this weapon please
why I don't need
Shields how do I fuse it when it's
inside I'll just drop the other one I
guess drop it
uh Happy Mother's Day
yeah doubl help B oh this one I already
fused
uh see uh uh this
one no [\h__\h]
wrong what what that what does that do
well I guess I guess whatever as long as
nothing's already attached to it if it
works it works but there's no bubble
frog in
here wait up there there's still
more what was that what was that ribbon
ribbon ribbon ribbon ribbit ribbit yeah
I got him
SP boost frog my first
frog quack quack quack quack
cute frog I got the
Frog Escape is
interesting should I shoot the
Frog let swing for him
tireless frog maximum
stamina yeah all kinds of slimy things
in this Cave Fish frog and these Giggles
everything is slimy
okay you can go I'll let you go oh frog
frog
yay
cute I just found out the bre your bre
hes could car they do what
really want to come
down oh no
ah little
[\h__\h] ow [\h__\h]
you don't lose my
drop what what's with him he like laughs
when he
dies where where is the drops [\h__\h]
was it only one drop no
way what a
freak see everything's so slippery here
man
H interesting cave this one's pretty big
man and lots of frogs to
collect need more geckos yeah of course
always look at the ceilings guys there's
always a geckos somewhere where did this
go where did it
go I don't care about the
rest I don't need the glowy fish yeah
nice detail right I like the new animals
that they implemented hide chest behind
them really some Cascades hide chest
behind them but like probably only the
ones that look like you can walk behind
them
right that one didn't feel like it but
this one
does is even stuff like these plants
yeah you were you were trying to tell me
about this weren't you you probably been
here
before G
Noles this chest has its own
Shrine
sh climbing
yo yo I haven't been climbing that much
yet
but when I look for some for some
minerals I probably
will that is a very important find write
it down write it down could D or
not so climb
[Music]
faster where they're curious about
it it's very close
to the North hyro Plane
cave this
area yeah take a
screenshot and there is an NPC outside
the cave that tells you about those
bubble
frogs so it is quite an important
cave they do want you to find
this very nice of
d w w
w let me
out is there really no bubble frog in
here maybe up
here there it is
so I really wonder if you're close
enough to this thing when it dies can
you kill the uh rabbit the problem is
though it's probably going to die in the
water so I don't think I can really
attempt it this
time can I can
I it didn't spawn this time it always
spawns did it spawn on the on the
ceiling it always spawns
though maybe it didn't spawn cuz I in
the water
what it went through the wall yeah it
probably did cuz it always has anyone
ever managed to get them you
guys he so cute
okay we're done
here haven't been able not yet they're
too fast yeah but if you're like like
right there do they always go the
opposite direction of where you are if
they if they don't necessarily ooh do
that
wow then maybe um if you're
lucky you can catch them before they
disappear hit them with a Long Reach
weapon is what I'm thinking
wait did we I saw a shrine somewhere
before right and we ended up not doing
it huh cuz I got
distracted [\h__\h] where was that was that
somewhere before the heno right that one
that one that one that one let's do it
let's do
it I'm going to run back to do it and
then we're going to do uh this stuff up
here whatever there
is
yay yeah yeah yay I didn't forget I
didn't forget completely here I forgot
for a moment but not
forever
oh is this
uh H interesting
area thankfully no heo
yet no he looks back
yet so basically if you go over the this
bridge with the heno up there is where
the cave is the entrance to it at
least heno
to
ohu take take much
trees stupid tree
man did you guys watch ab play Tears of
the Kingdom yesterday I watched like
really only a little bit cuz
I to do other things
but how did she do I
wonder the whole stream you watch the
whole stream how far did she get did you
finish the tutorial
is do Shrine she finished she had fun
building it's her new
Minecraft it's like your vision H your
cuz I saw your vision comments it's like
uh Minecraft combined with Elden ring
for her maybe Minecraft Elden ring
Zelda apparently according to Callie's
tweet Callie's going to play it too and
it will be her first Zella
game don't know if she'll stream it
though she didn't say a windy
the she became the Green
Goblin oh wait I'm supposed to make air
for
myself I got it I got it I was like well
what am I what am I building with just
this but
yeah it's just
this wait how do I how do
I yeah there we
go yay oh can you only do this if you
have the parachute
should I
wonder
no again we only have know we have we
have we have um something to make a boat
with I
[Music]
guess really is that what we're
building so simple I dropped my weapon
really let me go and pick it
up
stay why did I drop it how did I drop
it how
come h now I get it you just press
double X
okay I threw it I I panicked again
probably wait I need all this stuff in a
uh Shrine seems like they have no
battery is that
correct it don't seem to
be influenced by batteries
they're on
Wifi okay there's probably a chest there
yeah uhhuh with air maybe we can make a
turn
around I
guess oh wait we attach it
to the platform by any
chance does that make sense
oh and I just teleport up there I
guess genius wow these new tools gave
them a lot of new things to do
for shrines I feel like it's basically a
portal like every Shrine is a portal
game I know it's not really something
you know that you work with in Portal
but for me very portal like cuz that was
during my whole portal and the other
game
Arc if you
recall what was that other game called
like that that that has all these uh
functions that the time rewind function
I keep on forgetting yeah entropy
Center
uh if I activate that now won't it go up
like immediately
wait wait wait oh no it won't actually
did I do it
wrong does it need
two okay
okay we don't need this one anymore wait
no way we do no no okay no I thought I
thought I didn't open the chest I'm like
my brain is like somewhere else what the
[\h__\h] the [\h__\h] the
[\h__\h] for a moment I thought I just
deattached it and you guys were all
going to face palm because I did not
even wait wait for me okay I turned
off oh like I'm really not hitting it
but it
works very nice
hitbox very understanding very
welcomeing thank
you you know us too well well you guys
you guys also know me too
well you face paling on your own game
play what are you
doing that is so face palm
worthy I'm sure you're doing
great we did the shrine it wasn't
difficult was pretty fast so so far the
shrines I've done like off screen too M
there was one I struggled a little bit
with actually um
the the ball
one I don't know maybe some of you guys
already did it it's one of the close byy
shrines
from
uh this this area maybe this one or so
yeah there's a lot of ball ones the one
where you have to shoot it with like you
hit a pole and then it Bonks the ball in
the right timing
hopefully my problem was I didn't find I
I didn't realize the pole was there to
hit I didn't even see the
pole so most of the time it's really
just very simple issues like that yeah
the baseball
one
mhm so I have to look up how it works
cuz I was like so
confused and then after I saw that
there's a pole then of course it was
obvious ah [\h__\h]
tr no I swear to
God no I don't want to fight the tree
either
[Music]
the sorry I I actually don't want to hit
you he's running without his
head give me those give me those
weapons
what
nice are we done now I mean besides the
tree can't carry any more of those are
you for real
I think the only way you can really hit
the trees is with
fire that was what worked for me but it
takes a while like who bothers with
these
trees should I I have a
wait I was fighting it was a
flamethrower originally
yeah now you just wait feel like you
can't really do much more unbearable
heat oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah it just burns eventually I
think it even stops burning if you don't
make it burn more what it's just a
waiting game or an axe oh you're right
why didn't I think of that just ax it oh
yeah no but I want to see it burn it's
funny cuz it goes like
so hot so hot so
hot acorns oh Trina chickalo a chicken
nut small birds love this nut oh cute
you can eat it raw for minor but it can
also be added as a spice I wait it's
um what's it called
um but no probably it's probably not can
I stop probably not the same nut though
nut mag I was going to say nut mag
is it supposed to be something like not
mag prob not
right
sweet use the log too late
now now we go to the next run
a
walnut oh yeah I guess it looked like a
walnut or at least similar cuz I do
think
they make like they are inspired by
certain foods
and fruits and all that but often they
are not exactly the same but very
inspired yeah the symbols on the grass
yeah when I was when I saw them first I
was also like w wow what is
that also so there's a tower over
there that's one we haven't activated
right so hopefully we can activate it
where which one is
that like here
maybe I can mark that too right if I
[Music]
use this
function oh wait
no Zoom
can
I oh no that's not how do you mark it
press the
stick which stick the r
stick
uhhuh
uh how do I know which pin I'm
placing oh well it's blue now
okay ooh it's pretty far but now we know
where it is I wouldn't have guessed it
was
there yeah so look at these
wow how
why Lady
impa oh oh link heard that you and PR
Zelda had gone missing I'm frail to see
you alive where's Zelda
though huh I see so princess Zelda's
whereabouts are still unknown since that
is the case slink I encourage you to go
to speak with Lady
impa she's
there I believe she may have some useful
information that relates to the search
for Princess Zelda
impire is
here did they paint the grass
white what's this
for what is the meaning of
this impa what do the markings
mean ah she doesn't know
either a she's so old
did she age even more
too she did didn't she what did she look
like last
time didn't she look much
younger what a surprise it is to see you
here after all this time
link she looks like straight out of a
jibli movie
doesn't she like she could
be literally in a JBL movie with without
face
right I heard you gone missing it is
certainly a relief to see you back and
in one piece more or less well Princess
Zelda where is
she oh she still has yet to return in
that case we must use all available
means to search for her link when
Princess Zelda went missing something
else happened all over Hyrule oh during
the upheaval hero pictures appeared out
of nowhere images that sprawled over
fields and Hills just like this one
were're calling them
geoglyphs I understand they have been
found in locations across the
kingdom kaido and I are traveling from
region to region in hopes of seeing them
all I noticed you from a distance while
I was standing on High Ground examining
it up close I could not make out what it
depicted I thought I might have a better
view from up in the
sky oh maybe it's U more like those uh
wall carvings that we saw in the
beginning uh uh murals I mean I took to
the air in the balloon Pur gave me but
then at last the wind struck and
completely sheared the balloon off the
the base I have racked my brain for ways
to reattach the two parts but noil I'll
let me help you don't
worried uh let's see look at these
magical tools that I
have will I be allowed to use it by
myself
too would be nice can go on a hot air
balloon I'm I I have experience with it
as you know I'm pretty good at
controlling an air
balloon I did it yeah I fixed it will
you come with me to look at the GE GL
time to head out let's go would you mind
doing one final thing what fire it
up yeah
okay no problem ah she's already in it
cute these look so comfy
like you can literally make a picnic
here
[Music]
um
ow well do we got a cut
scene where are we
heading uh please try to what I have to
control it please try to take the
balloon directly above well right now
we're just going straight I think oh
okay okay oh cut scene Maybe
oh oh oh oh it's one of those Lou people
but is this one in a
wheelchair he nose looks so funny too
it's like one of those um tados what's
the SpongeBob guy in English called the
one with the long
nose Squidward yeah nose looks like
Squidward nose or like one of those you
know those doggles with the really long
snoots that people
make take funny pictures of in funny
angles basically
that the snoot
[Music]
Doles too high up I feel
faint but finally we can see it the trio
glyph well done link you know I read
something in The Village's old
literature A Passage about what the
ancient called Dragon's tears where the
tears rest upon the Earth we marked down
the images to which they gave
what uh okay does that mean there is a
tear there or
so I believe this GPH is one such image
but even from this Vantage its meaning
is no clearer to me for real
impa don't you aren't you like really
wise don't you know what this is what
this thing looks like do you know the
the like what the the r people look like
do they have a
name nor can I figure out what dragon's
tears might be but you know if
literature is correct one of them should
be quite close near to geff or even
within his borders yeah okay so I got
that right mhm the only I I forgot
already she's old but not that not that
old yeah but I would think that maybe
like through writings and
tellings they should know about the
zai didn't Z only recently discover what
they look like I don't think anyone else
knows well in the murals it was just uh
normal high Ruan and the enemies right
and Ganon was on there and I guess maybe
there was one zai on there maybe I don't
remember what you look around this could
be the clue we need to discover princess
Zelda's
whereabouts yeah that was one yeah only
one though did she comment on it if you
would like to examine the geoglyph from
ground level you can float down are you
going to stay up
here okay I stay don't worry I'm
enjoying the fresh
air so please just go let me die here
alone I just want to end it
now
okay I don't know um I'm okay I think
with examining
it I don't I don't know where I'll be
looking maybe at the maybe the tear
would be where the
[Music]
eyes there is something at the eye too I
think oh yeah
cuz one of them one of the eye is filled
oh yeah there's something there
anyway yo I got it immediately I'm a
genius yeah look at
[Laughter]
that it's like a little Pond but am I
ready to enter that I don't know
M
well that's become a tear right
away
oh like one of those Stone not liquid
ones
oh cut
scene German cut
scene let's
go do we hear
Zelda remember I have it in German right
now might when I read subtitles
guys
oh that's right where she landed that's
alad
it's it's her it's her
[Music]
it's good right
yeah hyu
[Music]
yes you time traveled when when they
speak German and made me speak German
too I was so hooked I couldn't eat my
chocolate wow did you remember that did
you see that now that explains a lot
doesn't it wow
[Music]
M better right at least her voice I
think so too
mhm and the other voices were good too
in my opinion from what I've heard so
[Music]
far I can keep
it but that's difficult for people who
going to watch without
watching because it's going to be going
to be a long
Series so often there will be people not
paying attention that much keep it keep
it really you want to hear more nice
German but most of the time there's not
many Cuts scenes anyway so there's not
many cases where they do speak
German keep it oh
okay so you okay you'll just have to pay
attention whenever there's a cut scene
which is not that often anyway and the
rest I'm reading out loud out in English
anyway
okay and now I can rewatch it
oh this is the the third one I could
rewatch wow so if link is able to convey
that to
others you know like Phoebe with her
premonitions in Charmed
then then we're already quite a few
steps further in solving this
riddle it's really good right I'm I'm
glad you guys
agree the the dreaming voice is really
good what's
wrong link what did you see
ah he's talking thank god oh goodness
you say you had a vision saw mysterious
figures and then Prince
Zelda the geoglyphs the literature the
dragon's tears and now a vision of the
Lost
Princess what if can you tell the
details though it's very important link
that you tell all the details don't just
say you saw mysterious
people say the names and say what they
claim they they were it's very important
what they look like my God he's new to
having premonitions isn't
he what if these all are connected let
us continue to examine the geoglyphs
they may contain further clues that lead
to Princess Zelda I don't need any more
clues just with this premonition we
should know what's
happening she's in the past A Link to
the Past is what we need to play that's
the game we need to play we need to send
link to the past
you know according to the literature
there's something to do with geoglyphs
in the Forgotten Temple the Forgotten
Temple lies at the bottom of the canyon
in hebra I think we should make our way
there
soon oh the water is gone but wait in
the end I didn't even
collect the
tiar did
I link them ghost to the past and Link
to the
Past oh I got dad oh I didn't
realize I did oh okay okay
okay man that was oh yeah it's even on
the map it's on the map that that that
there was a tear there
cool let's do a ran to celebrate what we
have just
learned h
I'm
T who the [\h__\h] is
K goodbye
[Music]
goodbye that was a good piece of story
though I appreciate
[Music]
that time h
a good pizza
story you an uplifting
device ah air
balloons okay
uh n you just want me to ride a balloon
up
there uh
fun s in her diary Linker he doesn't
talk because as the he he feels he needs
to be a strong silent Guardian for the
people yeah yeah I feel like someone uh
told me about that last time but I
[Music]
mean wait is this thing on its own
already
functionable if we attach it
to wait
wait yeah of course that was going to
happen wait
what is with the
camera when doing
this
no
stop I just make a new one
[\h__\h]
sake
ah oh my
God so
basically I just have to I just have to
uh fire it up right
then let's do exactly
that I'm
confused let me in let me in let me in
how do I go in okay I I I see I see
I was wondering if I should use these
two I swear to God I swear to God so
annoying oh God that's not that's not
really placed very
well here we
go that's not enough
have to keep on holding
it
oh
wow oh I stopped
moving let me fix it I'll be right
[Music]
back Bonk okay and now
do I have to have that
touch the top is that
it uh
[Music]
that works that
works it was already floating away and I
managed to still attach it is there not
like a chest
here
ooh is
there chest if I go up
there
[Music]
somewhere this structure
but my air balloon is up there
no
okay this Shrine is
big I don't like big
shrines you're too
big the
hell what do I do here
okay I see this ball and up there there
was
a a platform for the
ball so we tele uh we transport the
ball
oh we make but maybe we transport
ourselves
too I think we can do that
mhm easy
easy let's
go but uh oh is that where the chest
is let me just drop the ball first but I
how am I going to do this now can I can
I still change
direction wait I want to stop I want to
stop stop stop stop stop I want to stop
though how do I stop uh uh with the ball
I want to stop with the ball ah we
stop um I don't want to leave my
balloon
wa where where is the ball now here can
we if I drop it
there is a going to
[Music]
no no how do I get up no oh there's
another one thank
God there's another one okay well the
ball is uh
yeah it's
somewhere but wait there's no more
wooden platforms
though how do I
stand on
E can I
time reverse from
here it won't reattach the ball to
itself will
it ah wait that's the maximum of how
much I can bring it back to me cuz it
was chilling up there
forever I can't wait
that doesn't
work it doesn't work
either did
I oh wait ah there's a there's a there
stairs
[Music]
here uhoh
okay now we're on this level again let's
bring the ball to safety first and then
worry about the
chest
uh just going to try to drop it from up
here does that is that where it needed
to go
no it was the other one
[\h__\h] what's this one
for she got
them right no
problem so if we don't want the chest I
guess we could just go and finish the
shrine now but I want the chest too
where is it where is
it where did it go where's the
chest it Oh I thought it would be there
but there's no chest
there there's an opal in there you
think the item in the chest is so cool
wait that doesn't sound like it's an
opal the chest has
arrows I think it's an opal well [\h__\h]
that
I don't care that much about that
now that sounds if either arrows or opal
it doesn't sound that
exciting I'm
good I'm
good oh I feel like yeah four I can get
another h
[Music]
or a stamina boost
but I think I'll go for another
heart they say every cave is home to a
Bu from also really every cave but the
the wells are not considered caves so
they're not in the well
caves it seems to
me that is
true how w
hello nice beds but you you get looked
at when you sleep here
yeah look what I got let me sell you
some ooh I got a
sapphire wow
wow any more we got some of
this doesn't bring me much money
uh one
o I don't see anything else that I
should be
[Music]
selling oh that's it I need to I need to
bnk
more more gems out of the stones
what do you
got no no the only thing I'm interested
is this maybe you can resist the cold ah
okay I don't even need that one then I
have plenty of other items that can make
me resist the
cold working
progress
[Music]
okay I've yet to register a horse by the
way there's some horses there should I
try to get
stop moving again what the
hell I talked to a lot of the NPCs in
the last stable didn't feel like it
now got to sneak up on them right yum
let me try to get the blue
horse they hear you from so far
you got to be real
careful blue a horse young oh [\h__\h]
sh so far doing
good oh they're coming towards me
they have no idea that I'm coming but
should I be behind
them
come what do I
do uh s s i I did it first try I had no
idea what to do but I did it I did it I
did
it y does it already like
me yay
good horse who's a good horse you're a
good
horse why do you not want to run
anymore go let's
Gose looks so funny this horse it's a
Blue Cow
Horse gooa Horse let's go goo of course
that will be your name what else will it
be hello want to register oh no uh that
L and A
[Music]
ah it's so
cute there we go welcome to New Sur
stable one pointy
Point thank
you I would like to register this horse
first horse is free I
assume ooh gentle temperament and really
really mid stats like everything's just
two stars okay sure why
not it's
okay this is my first horse I I can't
reable oh yeah you get like uh some some
items when you
girl
oopsie
go gooa Goa the
horse
okay yes not even
mid solid color ones
have solid color ones are better oh okay
I'll keep an eye open for those
you can change your horse's gear it's
saddle and of for or restyle it's main
speaking of you know what whistling yeah
I've whistled many times on
accident down really I was pushing other
buttons let's go where are we
going I guess I'll take you with
me uh where are we right
now uh whoa oh you can see it on the
map the murals the grass
murals the cusa
art let's go to the blue
side I'll probably get distracted but I
don't want to get distracted now that
I'm on a horse I kind of want to rush
through and then explore but I shouldn't
I don't know Raiders hello cousart yeah
CA
art is that an enemy base
here let's go
horsey go bad horse go you should go
back to being a
shark really bad
horse yeah the skeleton horse was
better o and horsey goba we going to run
from those enemies don't get caught by
them don't want to get in trouble ooh
what is this place
pretty you but I want that want to get
that Tower oh wait I I I I'm off course
but what is that
place looks
crazy actually reminds me a little bit
of an area in I think it was in Fly for
Fun maybe maybe somebody played it and
understands what I'm talking about that
would be really really nice I would be
happy about that that there is um an
area with like really tall mushrooms
like this as well and F for
fun
remember oh how did I not Stomp The the
fox oh ah it's the the the the the the
the the big big
mous and there's a bunny there okay
horsey go one second
please those Tre over there yeah I've
know like tell me about it h you're
scary
Shak yeah they move don't they your
concerns wait they're not your
friends not a hotel it's like the moving
trays will have to do something with
you you want me to kill
them well
okay uh no problem is it this one
it
trees get
up no not the spicy
pepper let's
go you are an eyes sword to my Croc
friend
so I'll burn you down this seems pretty
violent I don't understand why this is
better for
him but we we just want to help
him chilling
now burn burn burn them
down where are you
going hot hot hot fire fire
Tree on fire I did it for you yeah
Shak cute the scary things are
gone wait let me pick up the items
before you talk to me
no you see me you see me my name is H
I'm a musician of the kak forest up in
the Northeast I'm known for my maras and
my dancing thanks for your
help uh to show my appreciation I'll do
a little dance for you and make you P
bigger oh so they still have the same
function as in breath of the
wild but you're supposed to give them
Coro seeds wait you're saying you're
putting the Coro seeds in your maras so
now they're empty and before you can
really make my pouch I thought I was
getting a freebie at
first inside are gone how am I supposed
to dance now the children of the forest
must have taking them again them if I
had even one car seat I could sing and
dance and use my Powers okay no problem
cies make really great sound when you
put them in my but the sa spelled all
over our place when I broke my mother
and I think this Children of the forest
took the seats while I was all in panic
hang on you got them my God give me some
I only have nine man so bad I'm so bad
at finding them now what happened to the
last
900 yeah sure sh which stash m
I guess we I feel like yeah let's go
weapon
first let the expansion
begin I make
you
music [\h__\h]
cute he sings along
[Music]
expand so are you happy with it what is
that big cube in the air the
shadow it's a shadow of a huge cube in
the air do you see it like next to him
is that an island why is it so Cube
shaped if you bring me more cor I'll
expend your inventory again how many do
you need for the next one cuz you want
more and more don't
you I'm in the middle of traveling I'm
thinking about heading east next there's
so many mons these days that traveling
is dangerous what I'd like is to find
somewhere I can relax I like LLY places
so maybe I'll go somewhere lots of
people hang out wait SEC you still have
more I'll be here a little bit longer
want me to make you pouch even bigger
yeah really only one no
way when are you asking for more Sak
Saka T sh sha
music cute [\h__\h]
[Music]
cute
thanks look at the time I got to go no
no no don't tell me the same story let
me expand more you're going to sniff it
again no okay this time he disappeared
maybe I wouldn't have been able to pay
for the the next one anyway oh oh my
thanks wait wait bunny next first the
drops
ah don't tell me it all rolled off is it
all
gone it's all gone no it's not all
gone and corns yeah sometimes they drop
these pry
sticks strong Bonk sticks last time I
wasn't able to pick it up cuz I set the
the tray on on fire and then when they
dropped these things they uh set the the
fix sticks on fire as
well wait let's try to get as close as
possible wait
me wait
[\h__\h] hell I only got two I'm so bad
I'm so bad at
this God damn it it's okay it's just
here to point the way to the cave I
guess okay we shall enter the cave
[Music]
gangos
gangos o this is a good way to collect
them cuz they don't run
away oh there's a shrine in
here
Flint okay
oh
no does
that is there no no um there must be
where there is a money bunny there is
a what
no no no what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] this will be a death of me how do I
get I'm going to die I'm going to
die
um cool that was your exact
response what the
[\h__\h] they are so fast they don't let you
run away you ran out of
stamina what the [\h__\h]
uh how do I do
this let's
climb I can't climb that long
do they spawn right away yep run run run
run run got to get up
there oh they're not really activated
yet oh they are they
are oh they're just wandering around
they don't see me yet so I can shoot
them from
here somebody said I'm safe when I'm
high up is that
true seems still seems still is it is it
though is it
true is is it true it better be
true
uh yeah yeah I think it's
yum he but I barely do damage is there
something I can
do now it's fire
well I mean I mean that's
something yeah that's barely
anything a
bomb y still barely any damage but at
least it hit all of them
that's like the first time we meet these
[\h__\h] and no idea what's the best
thing to
do I don't think I have enough bomb no
maybe I
do maybe I do maybe I
do eat them up eat them
up are they
separating oh
f f f f f f f Phantom
gon f f fat fat fat fat fom
gon good luck what uh uh what I'm I'm
not like mentally ready for something
like that speed run what
uh uh
almost uh uh oh God uh what oh God where
where where where where where the bubble
frog is there too is he down there what
where is he where is his fom gon is he
on the ground oh god
oh just throw more bomb oh it does do
damage
a just suddenly was up there and Falcon
punched me from the back Phantom punched
what [\h__\h] I don't I don't think I'm
ready for this cave why do they why do
they show you this
cave yeah you
he's a random
[Music]
encounter so wait is he not necessarily
connected to those enemies like if I
kill if I don't if I kill them he
doesn't always show
up um this Shrine man y b y b uh what am
I doing uh
you
bit oh this time I got an Amber and an
opal let's
[Music]
go cute um [\h__\h] this
I'm not I don't
care I don't
care no
no can run past it last time I tried
running it didn't really work out
I'm safe here right probably uh 3 2 1
go I couldn't clim trying to jump let me
go let me go let me go let me go let me
go
[Music]
Mommy I don't have enough
stamina I'll be fine I'll be
fine monkey Moon oh oh is it coming back
ah it comes back to
fast almost fell down into his grasps
again the bubble from oh and I'm curious
about that glowing material
man what the [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] bastards
[\h__\h] you oh there's some
here Hine can you stop the music is
freaking meow
scary luminous Stone the stone can be
used as a base to make special clothing
so should I not sell
this we'll
[Music]
see oh
man so
scary
yeah why why why are they
here why are they here why why Phantom
can scary suddenly turned into a horror
game to make me S wait what the [\h__\h] is
this
place oh freebie
w
[Music]
w thanks I still don't know the value of
these maybe I'll appreciate it later oh
thank you a freebie well some of the
ones in breath of the wild were freebies
too right I
remember I remember H cuz of the mini
boss oh yeah yeah yeah usually the
freebie ones were around some kind of
challenge I think in breath of the wild
as
well gon no Ganon is here after all I
deserve a freebie but I haven't killed
Ganon don't tell
him don't let him
know
be I don't know what I want to eat do I
want to eat a rice cracker I think I
want to eat a rice cracker
[Music]
man so anyone here who has killed this
one fully like the the little ones and
the Canon gon H what the Phantom
Canon not yet I did oh how did you do
it oh
it's not too bad his Wing's pretty slow
high
damage very hard Especial with low
Health didn't know how to deal
damage only ever saw the hands had no
idea it spawn Phantom
gon he drops a cool sword and bow
[Applause]
ooh light arrows
you struggled for 2 hours and gave
[Music]
up I think there's no
shame
in not attempting it
now yeah I'm undergeared and I don't I
don't know there's probably like some
kind of easy way to do it
wait am right
here ah here okay thank God what's in
the way
in the other one other
area W we're diving we're deep diving
damn oh we're right by the tower I mean
I think we were already kind of
close where did our horse go did our
horse
leave ah there's one called
horses but they're like
busy doing things and I'm okay now I
don't need one right right the away
let's activate this
Tower so we can see the
map they even put some tools
here maybe because climbing this thing
is
rough maybe with the beginner stamina
really or is it for
[Music]
there's a big
one I might be home on my way because St
was a really enjoyable experience
probably due to your recommendations and
notes I took from hey I'm happy to hear
that
[Music]
yay I'm glad you could enjoy wait so you
were only only
is has negative tone to it but you were
only in in Austria and Italy this
time nice choices was your choice in any
way influenced by the fact that I am
Austrian if yes then I will have to
become the Austrian ambassador of travel
you know it is what it is
Ambassador Jo you come I guess I am but
without getting paid that's how it feels
to do a job with passion but not getting
paid
H don't fall down
now yeah you know how good out cow good
K right and mik S are the Tokyo
ambassadors I should be Austrian
Ambassador but like the people here I
guess don't give a [\h__\h] about anime
characters promoting their
country but I should really be
that it would be kind of weird though I
I
guess Austria announcing they have a V2
as their Ambassador for
travel I guess I got to stop hating on
inoke too if that's if that
[Music]
happens oh those islands look
funky what the [\h__\h] is that
Island let's
go hi high up to the sky tort me let's
go maybe we can land on one of those
islands while we're up
there but we got to cut cut off
the the Rope oo
wow
o yeah we're we're above those uh
Islands scanning scanning
thoughts on your vision I didn't watch I
heard that people were salty about
everyone voting for Sweden like the
jurries seemed like people were biased
about voting for
Sweden like the jury was
biased I don't know though and I don't
know who won anyway who
won Finland and Austria robbed e
really yeah I know Germany lost
sweet well of course okay Sweden
one Germany got
last
last I mean I'm not claiming that they
would have won with me but I feel like
they
just with purely with the impact of
doing something really different
I feel like we wouldn't have be last if
they would have gone with me serves them
right yeah cuz you don't have to be like
the best Act of the show you just have
to leave a freaking crazy strong
impression and have some like a good
song in the voice too yes yes but the
crazy are your actors you very very good
for
winning they got last oh my
God can't believe it Jerry hates songs
that aren't pop an audience V was really
concentrated on feeling swe see I know
then do you would have been great pop do
you would have been a great pop song you
know did you check the German entry
their act was pretty good oh I'm sure
they all were like like the songs at
least were all good surely but yeah well
what do we have the Hyrule rich and the
tanfa Frontier whatever that
means and a couple Islands actually ooh
one with a skull looking
thing that's the funky looking
one oh there's a relatively big one over
there okay
M do the islands have some special stuff
on there should I uh go look for
them um
should I go look for them in in
a uh in my private
time what do you
think and also I can't reach any of
these now I
think some have special
gear yo wait I could maybe go over to
that
one if my stamina can keep
up which one is that one that looks that
looks like it has a
like a toy gate uh-oh uh
uh I
will eat
this oh maybe I should have taken one of
the ones that make it fall oh well let's
see how far we
get no rip yet no no ooh I'm actually
reaching the spiraling
[Music]
one
yeah we're reaching
it one one more one
more I
panics hi Birds yo what's this place
I freaking panicked I lost it we're on
this island now at the very top
actually
actually I was just going to say this is
one of those
thingies what what do we do here what
does this do it's not a
shrine
M do we get the shrine now
what is
that I'm not sure if I want to go
through it right away what courage
Island cuz of the jump oh I have to jump
through it do I get reward for it but
way what is like in in the spirals is
there like some
treasure I want to
check everything out before jumping this
one's fun oh is there like several
portals that I would have to jump
through they create each other
after after I
jump this difficult wait I want to try
[Music]
something I want to see if I can get
some rice out of this
[Music]
stuff can I get rice from
here
[Music]
no that isn't grass well I mean that is
in the
end something that I I if I if I want it
to be
grass then maybe it will be grass for me
if I pray and
hope and I close my eyes is really
really
strong near hatel okay okay
uh yo the cube island is something else
I I don't know
o okay
maybe wait here here there's something
down
here yeah yeah yeah we could fall down
here
[Music]
ta oh and then from here you oh teleport
up there what is
that not not teleport you ascend but
what's
that H looks weird
but I just want to check this out to see
if there's any pressures or so you know
is it completely
empty probably if you go from the
bottom um with one of those we rinding
Stones it would probably I assume bring
you to like the lowest platform and then
the challenges to like keep on going uh
each level
higher yeah so that there's nothing
really down there maybe oh wait there's
no that's that's already the real
ground at the very bottom is there
something at the very
bottom just for
show okay let me see if I can no no
[Music]
no go up in the end if I if there was
something here wait is it too high
now a
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
wait can I fly up again with the Tower
or is it once
only of course it
is I can fly
again oh that
hurts oh okay so then wait this isn't
for going up then cuz you can't go up
well then let me explore it really
quick we'll go
again but
first exploration is there something
over there no probably
not oh you think if I would go now I
wouldn't have enough stamina food
actually what are those doing up
here I still have a
couple a holy
Cube the view for me is pretty
cool see a lot of
islands but
like going up to them it's kind of ooh
see this I was thinking about this
storm it also I mean it probably has no
connection but it also makes me think of
uh Skyward
[Music]
Sword cuz there was this storm that we
were like fighting in
remember nothing here either
yeah yeah yeah yeah with the way and it
was also like a big storm like this in
the Sky High up but maybe none of this
has any connection at
all maybe I'm just holding on to
hopes just like with this area hoping
that there's something here that's worth
exploring and turns out there really
isn't they off have references to other
games yeah true yeah but I want it to be
clear there's so many spirals to this
island yep there is nothing here at
all oh this one's interesting too though
there's the capsule
thingy duck duck no I thought it was a
fish I was going to catch it but
okay oh there's a construct
too hello have I been here
before welcome this is the site of a
ceremony to test your courage courage is
demonstrated by diving H yeah I didn't
do it doesn't mean I have no courage no
challenges have visited this island in a
long time I'm glad you have come you're
welcome to show your courage do you want
to start
oh wait will you like teleport me up
there if I want to do it or is it does
it also uh can I also do it from
here like a separate
one the duck's trash can you calling the
pond Duck's trash can there's there's a
there's a fa no
man yeah okay byebye what does uh the
fairy do again in this game cuz you
can't catch it with a with a bottle
right I can get some special armor
ooh revives me when I
die oh okay I guess you just catch it
the way you catch any other insect
M okay unfortunately it's
gone there was another one
[Music]
man I didn't realize okay now they're
really all gone aren't
they maybe there's some eggs at
least no man you make a hobby it's real
sad here no eggs on any of the trees
that I check out o fishy
at least I got a
f I know I know have to crouch but like
it came out of nowhere I was
surprised okay then let's do it if I
can could be you do not know of the dive
ceremony no I kind of do allow me to
explain the D need a try to test your
courage it is a right by which zai
you've come of age the starting position
is the sky island far above here the
Challenger leaps from there they must
pass through all the Rings in a set
amount of time I wish you luck and
formly overcoming the trial those who
succeed receive a special outfit to Mark
adulthood I'll do it safety protocols
require a practice run of the course
first this practice run has no time
limit simply focus on going for all of
the Rings ah he does teleport me all
right
okay test
run
[Music]
um
um what if I failed the test
run um where is the the where is where
is where is it here H here
um um I um well
well I'm done um what
oh you failed to pass through every
ring yeah but it was just a test you
can't really say I failed like I
mean take care not to fall too fast not
the positioning of the Rings as you fall
I will send you back for the start once
again try to pass it this
time okay uh so let's press the button
a h he even runs by
himself okay easy
easy easy
easy oh that's what all these spirals
are
for it's just so you
can yeah glide through them them that's
it okay are are they going to be the
same
positions next time because if if yes
then
easy y I did it
easy oh
oh what the
[\h__\h] are we building a shrine right now
oh is that where I get
my uh reward for doing
[Music]
it that's how these shrines are
built they literally just come out of
nowhere no one built them they just
built
themselves interesting well done you did
well for a practice run it was quite the
dive I eagerly anticipate your
performance in the full ceremony now
then let us commence with the di
let's do it they're so kind to let me do
a test run though one Z I charge oh
okay no problem we are shorted buy our
coroporation your cooporation would be
appreciated here there you
go then follow me to the starting
position your task is oh oh wait I have
to be faster oh [\h__\h] wait how if you're
if you don't go the the accelerating way
how fast are you oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
I should be
manageable fck can do it again
please
[Music]
man oh I almost
died that was really close yes let's do
it again you are such a failure
[Music]
um let's do it again yeah don't I charge
which one what is what is the item that
I'm giving him how many do I have of
them well TimeWise I was barely
accelerating now and it seems fine
[Laughter]
a okay
okay wa that one I
can't [\h__\h] oh don't die don't
[Music]
die um
oopsy doly do right on the Ed yet the
must have hurt incred I think it didn't
it maybe didn't even hurt like it must
have been so
bad he died like immediately
probably that's l oh my God say now this
way seems like we're giving him our
first zai charge so I am
saving my money
basically yeah
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] he turned into
ketchup oh God okay come on I did better
than before though in
Fury [\h__\h]
ass how about we just
die that should do the trick right I'm
sorry I stumbled on my feet
I
slipped last time it actually worked
even though I
slipped falling death depending on the
height you may take damage or even die
when you fall isn't this a coincidence
what they show you in
[Applause]
these thanks for telling
me called
out you don't
say yeah let's press a I just want to
run a few steps cuz it's
[Music]
faster okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay
okay and the sun was blinding
me let's go this time fourth time fourth
time is the charm like I literally can't
even see the numbers
so okay
oh
[\h__\h] oh oh oh we're fine I did it yay
even though I had to use my paraglider
sometimes to to change my direction a
little bit
yay and we had 10 seconds to
go I got
courage I have here the mark of your
maturity oh fany CL Skydive Mobility up
oh I'll be able to like move around more
increasing thewar ability to Glide while
they plummet from the
sky ahuh so yes right 10 out of 10
Landing yeah the other Landings they
don't exist they didn't
happen you may be able to beat the
current record of 20 seconds will you
attempt the ceremony again
yes wait I want to put on the clothes
first
[Music]
though wait
oh it's work it work it
[Music]
work that was like 0 point what 15
seconds or
so
clutch yo
let's
go first try
baby
clutch I'm just it's not I could do it
even faster I'm just doing it for you
know the frill and for Content gamean
yay peace peace
peace my records indicate that you are
faster and braver than any previous
Challenger I award you this to honor
your extraordinary record you have
earned
it okay I thought I would get pants or
so please tell me your name I'll
register you as a record holder link
this understood your name is link I've
registered you as a record holder will
you attempt to ceremony again no there's
no more thing to win right than so was
fun even the failures were
fun oh look this is pretty
now
ow um I'm assuming I can't get anything
out of this now that I don't already
have so I'm not going to try to
Goa no I'm not going to do it again but
I'm going to get my
[Music]
reward another reward it's just a reward
run right is it
not but good that we didn't fly I wonder
if we would have flown with about taking
the quest
first maybe that would have counted as
the test run and then he would have said
Thanks for doing it actually uh do you
want to do it for real for
real what's
happening what you
want do we have to sh him while while
while
flying amen what this try purifies the
ancient evil you who have entered here
heat my instruction
dry a bow in midair that's what I
thought ha in your senses Focus Target
your enemy ever release okay I'll try
I've never done that before your othero
attacks are in ineffective here ready
yourself okay challeng
Tron said I yep
okay
wait like d you got to let go huh
oh okay well
done
M want to see me do it again now there's
free should I take all of them down in
one
fall away
away okay one no wait what did they say
anyway should I just can I fight them
normally now
wait how do I do them all let's
go oh just just just down them okay
wait I don't have to do it all in one go
cuz it's impossible okay good to
know
uh [\h__\h] hell
can you not oh you guys are so
[Music]
mean wait a oh because it's not doing it
because I don't have my bat I wish I
would just equip uh another bow
automatically when the other one is
broken wait I can't
see oh wait I can't do it
again
nice ooh
slow I'm sorry guys that you have to
watch
this did
it I'm still figuring out this the first
time I'm doing it double kill you're
proving your Mastery good job Ki waah wa
thanks
guys really you like to see me struggle
huh oh I got one of the
bows let me car wait um
drop or I
guess let's take
this use this
no
wait oops
it that's what I want to
do
mhm
[Music]
um bow on
bow
uh I it's possible I know it's possible
wait no it wasn't possible right I
remember now we have come to the
conclusion that it's not possible
uh in that
case let me just drop this one this
one why what do you mean don't be
ridiculous we've seen things that are
much more ridiculous oh that would have
been Bo too then let me
um drop this one
to nice
wait yeah five five five five five
stronger than four yeah we we've put uh
shields on Shields we've put swords on
swords we've put hes on swords we've put
stones on
sticks strong construct b
[Music]
m i drop one normal construct B
cool I was strong bow
now a we put arms on yeah skeleton arms
actually on bow not on bows on on swords
yeah damn we got six now we can almost
get two extra Arts
even I didn't even think we would be
doing a shrine up here bcal blinds
without much in the way of clothing to
protect them they tend to
run okay the feris didn't come back
sad but some flowers grew
back oh now I shall go down for real for
real bye-bye fun
Islands the defitely where do we want to
[Music]
go ah it's this
um this funky mushroom
area let's go on top of a mushroom hello
M sprad thank
you
oh what the uh the gloves wait was I in
charge of sending you the
gloves was I was I was I I don't I don't
remember yo those things they look like
the the flamethrowers that you can put
on your
weapons look at the
horses
cute the black one looks
fancy looks like the leader of the
pack happy Mother's Day thank
you I'm not yet a mother
but I guess I am your mother
somehow what is this
place wait that's a that's a that's a
Cod I
think right these kind of things when
you burn them underneath most of the
time
[Music]
say finally I barely find
them no it's
don't maybe not a mother but yes a
Mommy it's not happy mommy day it's
happy Mother's Day what is
this h is sus sus is what it is feel
like you can go underneath here I mean
apparently you can go underneath any
place in hyru now
but like there's like a
cave this place is weird maybe I should
just go oh there's another heno
here m
[Music]
H how are we doing
with oopsy don't wake him up I feel like
we could do this will he pull out these
mushroom
trees and throw those at me holy all
right let's fight
him a
big kaboom Awakening awaits
you he good
morning a [\h__\h] actually too high
actually too high
unbelievable oh
[\h__\h] where aim do aim
do what was that a
here we
go what the [\h__\h] what am I even fighting
[Music]
with stomp
stomp do the stom do St he do the he
stom
ah what am
I that is already a million times
stronger holy [\h__\h] but it gets destroyed
so fast huh
a what are you
doing [\h__\h]
[Music]
aim aim to
uh we have one
more okay run run run run we almost have
him though turn
around can't believe I'm shooting too
high before I had the problem shooting
to low now I'm almost always shooting to
high
can't believe you lose track of like how
close you are to him don't
you oh that actually killed him oh
okay I still wanted to get some normal
hits in but okay yummy
yummy oo
berries he's got some good stuff on
him he's quite the what do you call
it
culinary Pro no the que symbol toenail
grass
yeah but with a toenail from a monster
this big this is basically probably as
strong as
our uh
our bones
are I want to shoot that
bird
[\h__\h] I still got him wow he was taking
up and apparently I think it was a head
shot too cuz I feel like when you do
head shots you get two pieces of
meat
[Music]
she well now I don't know the heno is
dead there doesn't seem to be much more
here I mean I guess you can fly up to an
island with this but I I think like this
must have some meaning this
platform surely has some meaning right
but it's not revealing its meaning to me
yet the horses have good stats here
maybe I should really get
one I'll
try but I also want to go towards the
red marker now so maybe I can get a
horse before I leave this area I'll come
back here I guess when I find out what
to do
here no idea what's the purpose
here
what is it a
bush yeah it is what do you call those
again ah how do you fight
[Music]
them maybe I should put a weapon into my
head
they give me balloons don't they yeah
it's make
uh
huh yeah it's make items float an arrow
can serve as a good way to stick one to
a distant object if I want a distant
thing to fly away and then eventually it
pop right so it will like drop them from
high high up in the sky
all
what and they will die probably
instantly H and
eyeballs to Grant a homing quality to
the
arrow nature is to focus on moving
[Music]
object oh it's even more you little
[\h__\h] come out you're like one
hit easy oh OCT tentacle it's too acidic
for cooking but it's highly valid as an
ingredient for alexir yeah but like what
does it do I guess it's just like a side
uh item like the
monster uh monster items butterflies
butterflies that just Shield uh
slide where am
I
what I'm
you little sneaky
shits
no stop it or
else I'm kind of confused I thought
there was like
a I I'm not where I thought I
was thought there was like a hill to go
up
look at the
map well maybe we
climb
um I'll plant Lindor Lindor is bro what
is this sky is that the one we activated
oh yeah my horse is still chilling there
apparently we are going here okay well
guess we're not getting a horse down
Blue
Butterflies I'm going to get a
butterfly okay these ones are relatively
easy to catch if you just stay slow cook
it with monster supports for heat heat
resistance Alex oh good very good so far
we've only been in like super cold areas
so it hasn't been
necessary but in the future surely will
be
necessary so can I climb up there yeah I
should be
okay aren't you going to Yellow not
red
uh no there's like several yellow points
right and the red one I marked because
that's the first one we have to go to no
I bet this pretty up
[Music]
high
yum maybe I shouldn't be getting a heart
next maybe I should get
a a
stamina bar next should
I what do you think guys oh yeah I have
climbing gear do I do I really
I have to change
anyway H thanks for a
reminder does it let me climb faster no
I don't feel much
faster get a grip get a grip get a grip
get
a oh okay okay okay okay okay we can
somewhat stand here
[Laughter]
okay or footing
exactly I no wait now it feels like he
was climbing
faster yeah maybe it didn't like
immediately and now he feels slow again
I guess if it's not like super
steep yeah like now he becomes faster oh
I didn't realize that was a
thing all
right right
now I just got this breath of the wild
Vibe and also look at that but yeah
climbing up a random [\h__\h]
Mountain really just gave me these
breath of the wild Vibes like oh oh I'm
playing I know it's not breath of the
wild but this is what I imagined playing
breath of the wild would feel
like climbing up random mountains seeing
and and then once you climb up you see
like this beautiful scenery like a
random scenery like it's in the middle
of nowhere
sure but every
place this game is
beautiful not if your stupid Critters
always fly away though
I get some more of those
butterflies no I didn't play the Wild
this is the thing I know the story I
watched uh 100% playthroughs including
all of the 900
CS um I watched full playthroughs of
that many times like four times as many
hours of my
life I just never played it myself like
after watching One playthrough I was
like well now I watched it so I'm not
going to play it cuz now I know the
story and all
that I'm going to play it on my own
now but yeah I'm very familiar with
everything with the enemies with the
story with the system
overall oh oh that's a shine and horses
behind there
get a sense of just how fun it is to
play yeah yeah I'm getting the breath of
the wild feels now that I expected like
this is how it would feel so I'm happy
I'm happy with
it today I
feel like I think the day before
yesterday before I played I took a
nap
and I don't know I I thought you know I
should be energized but I wasn't I
wasn't
ized I was tired and I was feeling kind
of bored right the game wasn't like just
yet gripping me but today I feel
generally like I'm enjoying it more I'm
like deeper immersed and I'm having fun
and I'm I don't feel bored I mean maybe
you guys are a bit bored cuz I'm like
exploring so
much but you know I'm having a better
time today basically it's easier today
to stream
this I'm just chilling these five hour
apparently it's been five hours it
doesn't even feel like 5 hours to me but
what the [\h__\h] this Shrine is big oh
no this is big where are the building
materials I need to build something
obviously what's that
what was the title of this Shrine what
did it say cuz usually that's a
hint I require ball where is ball ah
ball is
there why why ball is so far away do I
have to rewind it I surely have to
rewind
it see you can't uh grab things I think
that are too far away and you can't
Ascend into well ceilings that are too
far away but when it comes to time
rewind you can rewind
anything oh I thought it was going to
roll down all the way over to
me okay it's not what I thought it
was can I go over there I can
fly I surely can fly
right h
oh I did I
did it's very
high okay I am at the
ball now okay we just make a
roll come with
me H there are some building
materials let's send it off
see what
happens okay it seems happy there for
now what do they eat what are these
for and
these what are they
for H
I will
see what are they
for can I not just ah ah it doesn't fit
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
um you want do something like
this does this make sense can it go down
like
is nah we don't want to waste all our
materials if it falls down right H this
doesn't look good this doesn't look good
[Music]
um should it go
sideways like
this and maybe kind of in the middle of
it why do I always look
[Music]
there I have a feeling it's no actually
it kind of adjusted itself going to say
that the angle is off but yeah this
works this should
work let's go have fun yay
[Music]
yeah
wait
oops that's way better than the one you
did really what did you
do what did you
do oh wait sorry guys I'm like
[Laughter]
incapable I'm incapable
[Music]
oh I for I
forgot there we go there we go Xbox is X
Xbox BX not box I'm not a
box
yes
scoozy
wait now there's even more
tools what's the matter wait we also
want to
go to the
chest I feel like maybe I can stand on
the ball up
here uh wait but what what how is that
supposed
to
what
what will you buy one I I don't think so
why Ain no rail do I have to make my own
rail like
this it doesn't even stick to it
[Music]
though yeah of course you could just
build a ramp I guess but that's not what
they want you to
do you didn't use the rails did you also
make y i just going the easy
route
lame if it works it's valid no because
you're not using the games ideas the
game's
way I made a funny
thing funny that it's not even falling
over
uh really that's not how it's supposed
to be
um ah there we
go it's easier when it's fallen over
oops see is one of these just straight
yeah the worst thing that could happen
is if
the uh ramp is too short and then drops
and falls down and I lose all my
materials letop see
is this long
enough for safety I'm going to
try attaching one of these
two oh you think it will respawn
really that's wishful
thinking okay but I think this is long
enough
a ah come on I don't like
this
[Music]
no a b I can't carry it I think is it
broke no I can
okay okay what are we actually supposed
to do over here
ooh
huh I don't see any hanging
tools
so
um how how could this work um
uh yeah build a hanger what does a
hanger look
like I have no
idea I have no
idea uh
what about
this should I get rid of the poles on
the
side well if this fails you know we have
to do it from the start I think unless
uh maybe it will send me a ball from
here kindly cuz I already passed some
stages may maybe actually maybe it will
be
good we got rid of
this what is
this so I'm thinking insert it like this
you know oh God ah I feel like it needs
more more weight on the right
side wait wait ha wait let me add some
weight yeah like this
I want to see how you guys made it did
your guys Creations look
prettier we can't look much more [\h__\h]
than this can
it uh
[Music]
wait
yeah let's
go it works
Oh yay now just don't fail the fall
yay and now we only have
to De attach attach the ball and put it
into the don't fall down oh my God I
almost fell
down don't lose track of where you are
[Music]
guys yay it took a while but I think I
always knew what to do besides the
treasure
chest a single one of them would have
been enough really well you got to play
it safe make
sure use all the materials that people
give to
you I want to eat the chocolate cookie
from baz and the Chini maybe some German
or austrians know which one I mean Chini
you know it has a little bit of a CH an
Orange um taste to it a really slight
orange taste but their simple chocolate
cookie
is sorry I'm like snacking so much but I
can't help
it I I just want to don't want to be
like hangry you
know if I don't eat somewhere in a long
stream it will be in the end the thing
that makes me stop streaming so me
consuming food food is
good M haven't eaten these in a long
time oh my
God these are so good like you don't
really it's not like a strong orange
taste but it's slightly there and it
makes it like more light tasting more
refreshing
m m
M actually oh my God if I ever make
chocolate chip cookies
again I should put some orange peels or
so in
it or I don't know some orange
um what's it
called orange juice just a lot tiny tiny
tiny freshly pressed orange juice or
something like that
orange dest I guess yeah just orange D
would be good into the
batter then I could
have these cookies with a slight orange
taste by myself okay we did
that that's how in this is is that the
one I activated
yeah okay and the red
one mhm we're getting closer shall we
get a horse I saw a horse over
there right where' they
go um when their nose is a different
color does that still count as them
being one
[Music]
color can I get like stealth
bonus ah this one's still stealth 6
minutes I feel like it's a waste cuz
it's my only self item I'll try
try you're
pretty I think I'll try the black one
though I've heard the same with lemon
zest
too lemon zest any Citrus zest really is
God
like they're chilling
now oh I feel bad like they're look how
peaceful they are so happy as a as a
family I'm taking them
away taking one
away I guess I'm not taking the black
one
don't kill yourself horse o
o
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] I was right
there well they can't go very
far I can't go too far
I should I was hoping that actually I
could like be sneaky until the very last
moment
but I should have just ran
up look it's enjoying the Air Breeze in
it in its man
oh
god oh cold Diner that came out of
nowhere maybe Blue Horse uh-oh don't
alert
them l l l l l l let's
go we got another gooa horse this one
looks even more like go let's go sorry
um I'm stealing your family uh friend
person um I need to bring into a stable
ride but the red place will have a
stable anyway I assume or wait didn't I
see another stable in the
distance okay this one at least has
four
claps name this one
gar I don't know who is gar I don't know
a
gar how do we get there
ah okay we probably can't go straight
over here at least not with a horse we
have to take this
path
oo that is a long
path there's a stable here no well was
there a stable here no what's the stable
sign again ah here that's too far maybe
we'll find another one on the way but
for now we should uh actually follow
the
yeah we should follow the
path blind shot
n
why why
blind if I don't register this horse but
uh jump off of it for a
second is that
going to make it run away
immediately what is this
music Angel what am I not
[Music]
seeing I'm going to go this way for
now it'll stick around for a little bit
okay okay
okay I'm committed to this horse now
I need to keep this horse am I going the
right
way I hope this path isn't a dead
end oh there's a there's a violin in the
bgm now
who oh there's a waterfall I want to
check it out there's probably something
behind and there's
ducks hey
a [\h__\h] I don't want to go up the
mountain but there's some cool stuff
there what is that there's some
light
[Music]
yeah but we should turn around is it a
hole ah it's like a volcano
sh calm down come
down it's going to be okay you just have
to
walk o o o
o this I want that I want that I want
that no can I pick
up can I pick
up um stick around don't run away okay
now uh
mounting needs a
saddle h i I think I could already get
it from the
stable
well wrong path so let's go the right
path next time
[Music]
uh okay we want to
like go
left is that
possible down here I guess ah and
then and then yeah okay I think now I am
officially on the right path let's go
like the Zelda DP thank you I like it
too the hood looks really good on
[Music]
me dark
Hood sorry sorry sorry
sorry good job horsey good job you're
such a good
horse who would have known that blue
horses
are such good horses
thanks the orange hair pop actually also
I feel like with the hair up it works
really well cuz it doesn't look weird
that like you don't see the hair strands
in front of the hood or
so it
works oh there's a stable D that we
didn't see before nice I can register it
right
now lucky and we don't have to feel bad
if we leave it behind somewhere too oh
beetle is there
oo there's a bird person here
[Music]
again new
Shrine I found it and they got goats
here I was wondering I saw in a
different Shrine that uh different
um uh stable that they had goats I
wonder what happens if you kill them is
it okay can you do
that
no
chill stupid
horse this way I want to register
you or or can you at least like get gold
milk or so from them
somehow
yay L
one yeah I'll get my reward yeah
yeah come register
ooh okay strength is strong stamina is
strong speed is okay pull is bad wild
temperament
o oh well is a decent horse what do you
think oh those are good stats all
right all
righty CL
one pleas find
[Music]
Nores um
go
okay it's also
go um I'll take the horse but I'll I'll
let it stand here for a
moment it's going to be cold next
oh oh wait I have I have pants no I'm
fine against the cold I think I also
have a lot of food for
that faster please I'm a pain customer
yeah I want my pony Point reward for
God's
sake
oh oh i' I've heard that you
can like put some some wagon behind your
horse so can you attach it if you build
can you attach it to this harness a
durable harness that comes as a set with
a horse saddle oh I only want the saddle
though attach a wagon or other objects
the harness for horse horse to toe oh
does it have a saddle Now by
default a wagon or an item you'd like to
tow
some like a
COK we could tow a c as well furthermore
for Five Points you get the horse God
fabric what D tough fabric bearing a
design of the horse God Melania it looks
like it could be used to make a
paraglide
oh I he a d shop in Hao Village has a
new service using fabric if you ever
find yourself in nuda you ought to stop
by I'm sure they can help put this
fabric to you interesting oh oh uh next
I'll get access to the Melania bed uhhuh
okay so now it had it had its own saddle
very nice let me check can I just get
some gold
milk cutest things you ever seen yeah
they're pretty cute they're actually
pretty
cute special recipe I'll be able to show
My cinar Girl My Love Goes any day now
a milk please
no they won't give me their mil hi cute
child what are you doing here
good day that's what I meant welcome
welcome to the
table n you're a travel aren't you this
table is so far to the West that we
don't get many new customers there's
this really bad snowstorm in the hebra
region oh B oh [\h__\h] nobody's showing up
did you come to talk to me because you
want to ask
no let me see what else you got back
here I know the dougles give you
treasure I know I know uh oh sorry brain
slow should we feed them they got two
dogos
even oh and they got a
well we shall check out the
well I really believed in that water
there didn't
I
FR cute
frog talk to me are you this lady I
heard about is it the the legendary lady
oh no Farah water quality Fair M growth
extensive bright caps present all right
that's everything I'll jot it
down oh what are you doing in a place
like this although I'm in a place like
this hey you wouldn't happen to be a
well Enthusiast would you I think I
am I thought so my name is Farah I have
a deep love of Wells too well Wells are
endlessly fascinating their damp
environment their Unique Systems of Life
how do they how they stay cool when it's
hot
outside oh you're saying the same thing
as this other person though well
enthusiasts just get it the appeal of a
good well that is my dream is to travel
around to every single well throughout
Hyrule after scouring all the ancient
text I could find on the subject I've
learned that there are 58 Wells Oh I
thought there would be more actually
sadly I haven't been able to identify
exact locations but if you have any
interest in Wells then maybe you could
help me would you tell me any Well
locations you know of oh 10 Rupees all
right I mean guess why
not sure it's not that much but 50 free
so that's 500 30 rupees in
total oh five of them already I'll give
you 50 rupees for
that okay decent
decent look at Landing m if I want to
find her again she's at Lookout Landing
cool where are the wells oh what is this
what are they hiding behind
this see oh I guess I could move it like
that I don't think I can swim in this
but would you look at that
I can make myself a
bridge I can make myself another
Bridge it looks like tar
yeah uh is it isn't it kind of
short oh oh no oh no come back to
me I think I have to connect it
all
right you can walk across for a short
distance oh okay well we'll go the safe
way we don't want to get our hands and
our body
dirty sticky and all this is kind of
sticky material right and like really
freaking
hot I imagine what it would
be every well they don't have like these
booble frogs and all that special stuff
but they all have like something unique
about them as well man I'm talking like
a well
Enthusiast there's a chest here and
there's my sweet beloved little new
children come come ah it's
gone I was so itching did you
see twitching itching twitching what we
get a purple Rippy let's
go sounds like you know them
well I'm trying to get to know them
Weller wait why am I doing this I could
just teleport back up couldn't die I
that's more but if I shoot them here
they're going to fall into the tar and
that makes no one happy so I'm not going
to do
no 50 not 500 Uh Oh you mean I got 500
in total I guess
so I guess
so oh you want to meet your friend
H where where is
it
doco oh that's [\h__\h]
far well maybe with my toe for real
though we going to do it we got do it
for
real wait I guess we are it was a joke
but I hav't even got a wagon here
actually do we want to put him on the
wagon or put him directly on the horse
let's put him in the wagon
okay how do I put
the the towing saddle on my horse
do I have to switch it with you
or
oh oh no
[Music]
o customize
horse that's a bit annoying that you
can't do it
anywhere it looks like it has shoes on
like Bootsy
cute oh looks great indeed
oh thank God we have a strong horse
it'll be able to deal with this no
[Music]
[Applause]
problem H
H this
is not something for innocent weak eyes
[Music]
well at least he's he's not going to be
like touching the ground because if
anything his backpack is going to touch
the ground he's going to be all
right yeah okay I know I know I didn't
want to talk to
you it won't hurt so much don't
worry let's
go go
faster see he's totally fine he's just
chill chilling
there going to reach your friend in no
time let's go the
ride poor guy nah this is a special taxi
service it doesn't get much faster than
this oh easy
how is it back there buddy
comfortable if it's not
then I mean don't ask me for a
favor but I feel like I deserve a big
thanks for this
service yay you're welcome thank you do
I have to you attach him on my own or is
he going to there we go
all right
byebye you're happy to gra oh my god
there dragon is lying there dragging
[Music]
enemy no time for that one
now going to give back my harness and
then go straight for the next
destination that I've been trying to get
to
Forever what
F oh ouch
how did that
happen do I have to S you more
often wonder I what stopped it I over
whipped it
sorry here I love you you're doing great
you're beautiful horse so
blue so shiny
so sweet yeah I love you I love you m m
m m m cute hor who a cute to you cute
what happened [\h__\h] did you
do oh my
God kute like a cat look like a dog
actually do I have to have the horse
right here because it kind of it just
escaped oh no no no no no
no I can do it for from a distance
[Music]
wonderful uh remove the
harness that will make everything easier
I'm
sure um I want to deal with the dogs
though let me do that
um uh does it have to be a steak or do
they take chicken
too you know
and cuz I only have one
steak any meat even
fish would I even take
fish I'm
try cuz I don't want these glowing
kfish apples work
too it's sneezing at the
at the
fish you don't like fish oh wait it does
it does I
think are you going to eat it
or just look at
[Music]
me oh no don't do that I'll be sad that
I can't pet
you eat this apple then
yeah okay they don't eat
fish do dogs really not eat fish though
I think they
do
uhal cuz I mean cats
do my dog eat salmon yeah they eat
anything
anyway hey hey hey the apples here
[Music]
yeah I can't see how they would be
happier about an apple than they would
be
about uh a
fish we got to make both of these dogs
happy oh no not the other dog ah okay
I've got enough for everybody I
think mhm now the other one's taking it
my dog's favorite food is sweet potatoes
what
cute that's so healthy too oh this one's
already happily showing me the chest um
wait shouldn't be doing both at once
give me a
second then I don't know where they'll
go they so cute when they
run you tap tap oh hold thank you I
would give you pets for that and say
who's a good boy but unfortunately the
game won't let me do
that
nice wait
[Music]
Brown wait for
me I got some more apples for you how
many more do you need
no pets and Nintendo was the one who
made
nintendog and yet now they fail to make
the dogs
happy ah yes go get that Apple rip it
apart tear it apart we good no not yet
okay can if there's two dogs is there
really two chests
or am I doing
this uh and it has no meaning to it oh
my God look at him chasing his
tail he got it he got
[Music]
it that's so cute SP you want the Apple
you want the
Apple yes you want the Apple
so that must have been five by
now come
on
C no no no no no
no oh he's still kind of eating
it he maybe there is only one chest you
even with two dogs you can only make one
dog
happy h
H H
yeah okay I think that's how it is they
they stole all my apples oh my God it
will be a lesson for the future for me
what are you doing
hey are you scared of seeing me with an
axe don't worry I won't make a horse
sash me out of you actually let me go
off once I need to talk to the bird
person
[Music]
all right then I'll take
them oh do you need to speak with bie
apologies we were caught up in a a
conversation I'm from retail Village
from the Northwest times are tough where
I'm from Merchants AR able to reach my
Village because of the blizzard we're un
fortunate uh the kind folks from the
stable are sharing their supplies with
us it's thanks to them that the children
still have full
bellies don't mention it really the ril
have been good neighbors to us we're
just returning the favor wait that's the
other person you let me know if there's
anything else you need all right I can
arrange to have it sent here and then
pack it up for you to carry home words
cannot express my
gratitude sweet yeah so that sounds like
there's going to be
really a [\h__\h] ton of snow awaiting
us let's cook then I haven't cooked in a
while actually not at all
today
um I will
make some of this with monster parts of
[Music]
course I
want one oh yeah this could work
let me cook let me cook
T those poor geckles I feel so bad
actually sticky alexir grants a lowle
slip resistance to keep you from
slipping on wet surfaces hi hi that was
junkers it's highly absorptive
absorptive ingredients make it a must
have for sudden rainfalls wonderful I
don't think we'll need like too many of
them I'll just make uh one more just in
case
yeah then we'll
make how many cold resistance items do
we
have a lot but is like like this one
star going to be enough
is it possible to make like stronger one
is it necessary to make a stronger
one I'll try to make some Alex actually
if I can what's uh is this one heat
resistance heat
resistance
glow
stamina well while I have it let
me make this this really
quick but the eyeballs also work right
it just doesn't say anything about
medicine but it is a monster
item yeah I do have cold res resistance
pants I just wonder maybe it won't be
enough cuz I only have the
pants Eno parts P
Parts okay this should be a really good
one a really longl lasting strong one
for speed
boost 7 Minutes triple speed boost
pretty damn good I would
say
um maximum
stamina stamina our
recovery hey but the eyeballs work do
they I think I used them
before I hope I
[Music]
hope they do okay oh it Resto restores
uh Health as well
[Music]
oh I don't think we'll need it anytime
soon
but I'll
make one of
[Music]
these that's why I am the cook of end
exactly like really I don't think any
other member Cooks as much as I
do even if they don't post pictures of
it sure they can still cook somewhere in
the background but I don't I don't
believe anybody Cooks more than I do I
know for a fact that like especially cie
will always order food or go to a place
to
eat I don't think cie ever Cooks
yeah she orders for breakfast for lunch
for
dinner
always
um fish
with what we have fish with pumpkin
maybe when cook the toughness manifest
Itself by
considerably uping defense
ooh is that a weird
combination oh yeah defense up mhm for 1
minute 20 maybe I should have put in a
bit more but I think it's okay to have
smaller dishes too a couple
ones
chicken that's also
put uh pumpkin chicken and pumpkin
weird combination oh wait that looks
amazing actually looks like a bread bowl
bread
bowl goulash and the [\h__\h] bread
M that's an amazing winter dish oh man
oh oh that sounds amazing [\h__\h] Grant a
lowle defense Boost 1 minut 50 many
hearts though
damn um
let's make herbal
chicken never had a bread bowl before
what six M that looks so
good what else do we have maximum
temporarily increase your maximum
stamina all
right I'll make one of those
too meat and
honey okay I'll try that maybe with the
steak honey honey
stink
interesting looking this into a meal
unlocks the potential of these nutrients
provides a stamina recovery effect
energizing glazed meat oh look at that
thick chunk damn a nice cut of the
steak yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum mushroom
skill oh what about the nuts I want to
make something with the nuts oh yeah
let's make chicken
nuts this is going to be totally
nuts maybe one
[Music]
more naughty
flavor that's a lot of Hearts but damn
it has nothing to do with not the
chicken overpowered it let me try
again just like
this a s only turns into a meat skewer h
Okay add one to a meal for nauy
seasoning this a different nut maybe
this one will give me the Nutty
seasoning that I
want no
okay okay um maybe more
nuts cuz first the chicken was
overpowering what if I had overpowering
nuts
no okay I'm
experimenting uh so the nuts don't come
out in the dish
[Music]
n how about naughty
pumpkin tough fried Wild
Greens no okay defense up three
minutes m
okay what what else do we have
resistance against
electricity nah no need for
that uh increase your heart recovery
when used as an ingredient the palm
fruit how
about I could leave it at this too cuz I
think we have plenty look at all those
dishes man I got to I got to eat all
this
M okay um oh blood Moon's
Rising you want to hear angry drumman
Zelda it's going to happen but wait I
want to see I can can I teleport
here no right I need to find a shrine
right here didn't I see
one
could it's going to happen oh my God any
minute now any second now I guess I'll
find the shrine on the way thing is I
want to
um go to the god statue to be honest but
okay can wait I
[Music]
suppose how high does it have to
go
oh here open ah this okay let me go up
here I'll leave you there horsey for a
little
bit where are you
going it's dangerous you don't want to
be out here and while the blood moon is
rising just once I want to climb it
every day you know there used to be an
awful and I mean awful thunderstorm
raging throughout this whole area i'
never let up until recently it did which
is why I was come here now that it's
safer maybe
wait was there an area in breath of the
wild that
was constantly like disturbed by a
thunderstorm yeah right oh was it this
area oh that's fun ha and now I'll climb
up but that he says it as if you know it
couldn't have been like 5 years ago he
would have done it earlier if it was
like 5 years ago it can't be that we
still don't really know right like
how how long ago breath of the wild
happened for real unless maybe if you
finish the game maybe by now you
know
spooky spooky spooky spooky spooky
spooky quick run to the shrine first
my stamina always in the worst
moment I mean she doesn't sound so evil
because she's just generally enjoying
this yeah
intense German
Zelda very
intense it's different in this language
right if evil why Hot N she's not so hot
to me she's more like pretty to
me what Ry could this
be if we get this one then we only need
one more to get two
more hearts or stamina or
whatever combat training archery okay
okay I like comat training
shrines just got to stop
panicking what are we doing like
anything
specific hate my
instruction don't knock on
G steady your aim and fire at the
enemies ah okay you want to want me to
do head shots okay
easy mm only head shots
allowed wow that's very
strict they're really training you hard
in this
game
should [\h__\h] ah okay I did it I thought
it was a little bit to the right side
but
okay and my bow
[Music]
broke oh
do not fear approaching enemies fire
true strike their heads really heads
only or or can I hit anything
now
uh oh
nice oh nice
wo i nice hey
easy boom hat shot I Prov my Mastery
let's
[Music]
go that was really
fast well sometimes you know I just got
to prove you guys that I can do
it just as
well so that you don't lose all your
hope in me
completely
um Travelers bow I wonder I wonder if
the Travelers bow has like generally
more
um shots it can
take then the other one the construct
ones let me attach
this
ni m I can't take anything else all
right oh no wait there's another is that
the one I dropped no right let's attach
zai sword to zai sword zai sword sword
zai zai sword zai
sword how do you feel about it compared
to previous Z games feel about what
exactly this game or something specific
what
uh h
happy Mother's day indeed I'm a genius
double on my
sword just a game compared to previous
ooh well I was thinking about this
today I played a couple other Dela games
until now and I've watched playthroughs
uh of the ones I haven't
played
um well obviously this one's breath of
the wild and Tok are just so
different there's no Dungeons and it's
like open world so it's it's not
even you can't I feel like you can't
even compare it
and but but the thing is like I love the
other Zelda games and even as a big
Zelda enjoyer and I would hope that
others would other zeld would agree um
this is very different but it's still
extremely enjoyable it's a different
experience
but definitely super
enjoyable wait come
here can
help yeah I
mean uh I I want the the thing is I
wonder like after this after Tok are
they going to continue
continue to make open world games
because that would be a big challenge I
can't imagine them doing that all the
time and
yeah so going back to the usual
style is also going to be difficult
though because like you hyped up so many
people that are also kind of new to zala
games with ref of the wild and Tok okay
so now a lot of people expect something
as big and intricate as this but they
can't do this all the time then then the
daa fans would probably be really mad I
think they can forgive a game like this
because it's really great one or two
times but then afterwards they probably
want like a typical Zelda game again for
now it's cool but like you know we want
a typical Zelda game
right so the Zelda fans will be happy
probably if they just go back to a
normal Zelda game but then I think for
the creators as well it will be like
like almost feel
wrong
maybe it will cuz it will be I suppose
easier to make a non-open world
game and I mean all the effort you're
not putting
into uh it to be an open world game I
guess you could focus onto other stuff
like graphic and all that but yeah I
think it will be difficult for the
developers and then also like you you
just have so many expectations from
people now but generally I think they
don't need to worry too much about it
and just make a 2d no no not 2D 3D 2D uh
whatever mixture typical Zelda game with
Dungeons and all that and everybody will
be happy or even like a
3D again but typical Z style of dungeons
like um like Skyward Sword
or uh
um what's it called The Dark
One what's the dark one called forgot
Twilight Princess yeah that's the one I
was thinking
of just something like that then I think
that would be a good mix you're still um
proceeding with nice 3D graphics
uh and and but you can go back to the
classics in terms of mechanics and all
that
yeah so I say I like both types of Zelda
games very
much but oh horsey
chill is that a bird over there yeah
bird
person but I can see
that or I can imagine that
fans would what want some oh that
already works I didn't even stick
anything will it work can imagine that
fans want um the
typical Zelda experience back after
this just glad you still have
appreciation for the old style yeah I'm
in the there was nothing wrong with it I
I mean also uh Wind Waker was also freed
Zelda and is probably my favorite Zelda
game just I mean it's it's not fair it
has a lot of nostalgia
points my horse I didn't die it's over
there on the cliff contemplating
[Music]
life let's try it again will it stand
oh yeah yeah
yeah how does that work what the [\h__\h]
physics
amazing Wind Waker
and major Mas top tier
mm oh you know what
actually you know what might be amazing
instead of go go on and making a new
game after Tok if they're like still too
worried about you know what to do next
how how about they just do a
remake of one of the really old
ones I mean I guess they already just
did a remake with
um not Skyward Sword that was a remaster
but before that uh what did I play was
it a link to the past what was it
called uh links Awakening yeah so I
guess the last remake was pretty recent
do you think they would make a oh sleep
over ticket oh oh for free
nice do you think they would make a
remake afterwards what do you
think no I'm not thinking Twilight
Princess remake I'm thinking more like
maj's mask remake orina of [\h__\h] time
remake there's a
[Music]
Corona oh the Oracle games sure sure
yeah I'll just pick the oldest one
man choose one of the really old
ones
eh Aina of time for N I need I need
something bigger on the
switch I'm I'm going to train again
today to become an all time great free
to
Warrior uh who are you someone else who
aspired
greatness guess you heard my little prep
talk about myself talk about
embarrassing for us reach to our ability
to control the wind is one of our big
advantages of in fighting monsters oh
yeah that's why I train here every day
aren't you curious what kind of training
I'm talking
about yeah we need the next
console that would be nice I mean I like
the I like the switch but H next Zelda
game should be on a new console maybe if
they do a 3D one one if they just make
like a like
a [\h__\h] links Awakening style remake then
switch is probably good
enough I use these sweet wings of mine
to return the balls that fly at me
pushing them back one after the next
what do you think want to give it a try
Okay do we have one of
those uh bats for me see the impressive
Tower bat there we buildt a baby just
for this
that guy operating Tower is TBL keep him
on retainer so I can
train TBL will love balls at you the
game is to return them to the moving
basket okay you'll be faced with a total
of 12 balls getting a green ball is
worth one point but a red ball has you
free don't see a fetterless guy like you
doing a my way though I'll let you use
any tools or mysterious Powers M
mysterious powers
but I I I would need like one of
those
wait I'll build myself something real
quick yeah rewind I wonder if you could
just cheese it with rewind but that
would mean that they have
[Music]
to are there's like free people up there
and now there's clouds there but that
would mean they have to bounce off the
basket ones oh no I don't know no and I
want to can you even do
that yeah just
[Music]
no
yes I'm thinking this will help help
me see oh it's just
trees yeah okay I'll
[Music]
try I'll
try let's see how big the balls
are the bigger the easier
hey here it goes what are you doing here
anyway how do you help are you going to
throw
them where did
[Music]
they are you kidding
me
what you obviously
[Music]
what what is this
scam
no obviously you need your magical
powers for that but they oh my horse
that's where my horse
is no I'll keep
going get back here no
[Music]
what I hate this game I'm not going to
play it ever again that's stupid stupid
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah a [\h__\h]
you now I'm
done I hate
[Music]
it out of here I
quit still
quitting stupid
game no no don't
care give me my
horse how is it going to come up
here where it literally fell
down how how are we going to do
this what do you do in this
situation hey
come up here aren't you a Skyrim horse
at
heart why do horses do this stupid
thing now I got to go to the stap for
real bam
[Music]
why do they do this do are real life
horses
like cow into these kind of accidents
too no like they would stop in front of
a cliff right
surely they
would bring me goba
to thank you rescuing my horse probably
with a
helicopter a zonai helicopter
okay let's
go while I
am here let's also
trange will I be feeling too hot
no let's go for real for it let's not
get distracted
now it's still so far we are 100% going
to get
distracted that's
okay oh
okay oh God the chocolate is so
good okay Apple
good
horse understandable understandable I'm
sorry I'm sorry I
apologize good horse good horse it's all
my fault I made you jump off a cliff
it's all my
fault don't be angry please
what's going to be the next distraction
huh an enemy camp nah that's not enough
to distract
[Music]
me right around it good job
um it's doing so well
now
yay uh okay around the
corner I'll definitely be exploring with
my horse on my private time all this
area that I'm
skipping oh what is this
I have been officially distracted horsey
you better stay there what is this
oh I was like is he playing the music
yeah he
is oh he's got a a trumpet
thingy hey
you oh I have should I fix your
balloon who oh hey did you come down
here to rescue me
yeah why thank you was heading to the
reto Village which is suffering through
a fierce blizzard to cheer them up with
music and supplies a he's like a
musician
yum I like the music that he was playing
I got my wagon going under a good pretty
good clip on this road but then I
suddenly drove into this hole it's never
been here before ah so you didn't come
here with the balloon but that's how we
got you we we will get you out of here I
suppose the horse I was riding run off
somewhere my cargo was spoiled the only
thing I have left is the wagon I haven't
figure out how to get both me and my
wagon on this hole and I won't leave it
behind which leaves me stuck here plain
and simple I'm relieved that someone
came to rescue me but I hope you have a
plan to free me from this hole of course
I do this is your
wagon okay I think there's two balloons
here for a reason maybe we need the
strength of two
balloons wait can I not move
you how am I going to get you out of
here if you're not going to be attached
to the
wagon can you please at least sit down
in the
wagon with you in it oh yeah get in the
way there we go yeah yeah yeah yeah get
in get
in trying to SW
it's not like a I can't I can't glue him
to things what is this funky
thing all right
um ah see this
is actually
wonderful uh uh
there we go getting it straight
sometimes is really difficult does this
work the second
[Music]
one man I wonder how long he must have
been here waiting for
help does he not have like a purad like
me is that not something that everybody
gets cuz they really should create them
for mainstream usage
oh [\h__\h] wait I don't H oh there it
was
oh oh it keeps on
disappearing there we go ha double I
don't know if it's necessary but double
Pat is for the 1%
H that's too
bad okay
I guess we'll be doing it like
this how do I how am I going to hit it
though but I've noticed it doesn't have
to be like inside it can just be outside
too
[Music]
right
uh a an era oh yeah okay I'll send him
up there without
me I know that's scary I know I know I
hope your your hair is not going to
be burnt off with my
invention didn't even have to be fire
though
huh oh both work at the same time
amazing oh wait but uh
wait how are we [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
oh my God I almost killed
him
um wait how do
we I have to add I have to add the wind
turbine I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry I almost killed you
no I have to rebuild it
no God damn it that's the biggest
sadness
here it was okay I should have just
added
the um the wind turbine so that it
actually goes in a direction too
o yo my heart
sunk when I saw him falling I actually
felt like holy [\h__\h] scared for
him I'm so
sorry this is
[Music]
fun what is this other platform for
do I need that one I mean if I need all
the other
materials feels like I would need the
other ones
too platform makes it easier as a
roof uh to attach everything on the
roof but I don't need it
right okay and then
[Music]
um if I put it like that it will
go
uh straight over here right in the
direction we're looking at
[Music]
now that should work now let's just get
him in
get in the wagon get in the wagon
Shinji give it some room it will hit the
wall before getting high
enough it will hit the W
oh should I move the whole
thing is it actually going to be like
too
efficient like if I'm here would it be
okay
okay's rolling on Z oh it's so
wobbly really I feel like it will
fail cuz it cut off so early
before here's a
bit please don't make me build this
again okay ah come on come on
a oh
[Music]
[Applause]
man they should at least let me ah okay
this time it's it's saved I guess why
why did it stay like this this
time really
one come on yummy does it really have
enough energy
oh y That's
amazing that's actually
incredible the machine I built is like
sheesh next level
you got nervous understandably you
almost died three
[Music]
times Woodland table mhm
yum have I heard them before in
action cooking
ingredient ooh honey free
times I feel
like the rewards doesn't quite
necessarily fit the effort I put into it
but okay actually wait a second
you think there might be a c
here I feel like there could be but I'm
just too blind to see
them yeah I really don't see
[Music]
anything that's the one thing I feel
like I'm I'm handling this game quite
well but
Coro Coro I
cannot find
them I was watching dendo
play and he still got like a feeling for
it cuz he collected 900 of them in worth
of the
wild so you know you know it's where to
look for them what what types he's he's
got a feeling for it I swear no I
don't it's a big difference
I mean I I I know all the types I know
you can like jump in them in the water
in a circle of lily
pads I know that there's the the balloon
ones I know some of them are even under
Stones just just simple random single
stones are
placed randomly what is
that wait a
second you're not going to hurt my horse
are you no I'm me just check what that
is is that a
stable no oh no it's just a random oh
there's several of
these and the mural is over
there even if you watch someone play it
you need to play the game yourself to
get all stuff yeah
true Sims since you saying you you
mentioned Sims even though you not
really talking about
Sims I think I've come to a decision on
what to do with Sims
1 I
think as an exception I
will um make something like a
pre-recorded stream or
video and I cut out certain
parts and then well since I have it like
as oh pre-recorded what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] pre-recorded
content
anyway I'll upload on a day where I
can't
stream I'll do it like this because I
want to cut uh some parts out that I'm
worried
about will chat be pre-recorded no chat
will be live but you guys are welcome to
act as if the the video or the stream
itself is also
live just act how will this not
stand I guess uh
okay just just uh be like oh hi can get
kinky wow you look beautiful today yeah
wow that
works but
no drop it first no no no I'm okay I'm
okay I'll do it like this
do we need it from the other side
too
nah should be okay I
think you might stream it on the second
Channel actually what
why give us a script
no
[Music]
sorry I know I wasn't good
enough this
time excuse me
actually just putting it here might work
oh
where like
this I feel like that might
work try Letting Go trust me
uh I mean he didn't completely touched
the
[Music]
ground okay
okay it will'll make it
foolproof brute forcing is the way
that's not exactly where I wanted
it
that yeah I mean come on
on no way it won't no way it will
fall
[\h__\h] okay it has to be more
centered don't put my creation
away sorry horse horse horse just really
bonked its head really hard don't get
away o don't jump off the cliff
come here what's that
enemies yeah okay I'll kill those before
I go
maybe how about
uh oh God no no
chill [\h__\h] chill
God damn it it's
[Applause]
[Music]
like no no no no no
no endless
cycle
what just stand somewhere where it safe
come
on uh-oh you're going to be bum Boozled
again if I lift
this it's always trying to be so close
to
me how about
this I it doesn't get much better than
this come
on let me talk to
you was he scared cuz of my
horse very simple
construction
see yeah he is indeed standing
straighter than he ever
was and he still never uses the
construction I make for him though
[Music]
mommy he gave me no rice balls again
what H same
stuff is always the same
now if he knows because this is like how
he ends up doing it
always these couple poles if he knows
that this is how he will stand why
doesn't he just do it with every Pole
now why are we playing this stupid
game like I show him a construction he
doesn't use it he ends up always going
for this in the
end so he already knows what to
do don't get
it you want to spend time with me
[Music]
no ah there's the
tower shall I mark it uh
Mark Tower how does it uh
right blue it be blue
now okay uh which way do we have to
go
ah oh we go it
over this dangerous
[Music]
bridge with my horse I mean it's not
going to fall off right it would it
would stop itself before falling off
right I'm almost there
really we've come really
far yeah
let's just try to be very centered
first
wait that's pretty
C
perect you're doing
great on on you don't want to go faster
okay why not why where are the where are
the
slaps there they
are was that out of safety that it could
couldn't do it ah you little
[\h__\h] like the oh oh EX
alos in German saying those for the
first time
now yeah I knew you could do it good job
let's keep on moving keep on
moving good job good job good job good
horsey wait
what kind of bush is
that raspberries I knew it would be
worth
[Music]
it looks different from the
others speaking of berries in the
supermarket I found a hidle bear
blueberries not the not raspberries and
blue but the the other ones are just um
I don't think they're called blueberries
what are they called again
uh they're just round they don't have
like the I know I guess blackberries is
the like Blue version of raspberries I'm
talking
about just the simple round ones ah yeah
it is blueberries cuz they call a
blueberry muffin okay never mind so I
found a
blueberry um plant thing to
plant finally usually they always have
uh strawberries and stuff and tomatoes
they never have blueberries I was
looking for them finally found it so I
bought it and after buying I realized it
says to plant it outside in the garden I
think but Google says you can do it on
your balcony too so I'm going to try to
grow
it but I have a bad feeling maybe it
will end up dying again but it wasn't
that expensive so it wouldn't be a huge
loss we have arrived and apparently it's
not that cold
either we are surviving at least here I
like these Frozen ponds I didn't have
this in breath of the wild I
[Music]
think Mama to back seating me
yeah I hope it goes well I finally want
some berries cuz last year it didn't
work
out it didn't work out now right now I
also have some cherry tomatoes
planted and I think that's
it I mean I got my basil plant that's
been going really well I'm proud of my
basil plant I've just been keeping that
inside though
H you know I don't think I'll attempt
strawberries or so
again cuz I feel like it'll just
fail balcony plants somehow very
[Music]
difficult but maybe the blueberries I'm
I'm hoping for the best hello what is
this uh wait is this not a stable it's a
stable right
is this a
stable shh a pen TR to here is getting
ready for a big princess investigation
you're here about our newspaper right
then you can talk to me too I'm next to
chge oh wait a minute it's you I got to
say you did a good job getting out here
to find us it's quite a hike from look
go landing when you haven't got wings
but here you are was it easy to find a
place
it was indeed a big
hike some folks passed by without the
second look after all it was a stable
until Tracy cheated the previous owner
out of it
what
oh they turned it into like their
newspaper office
[Music]
thingy
Denson I'm not
sure oh actually
I think that was a raspberry plant a
raspberry plant that I had last year
that died I just kept it dead in my
planter and I noticed now through like a
little bit of water from the rain it was
like sprouting again it was growing
green leaves again so I was like okay I
guess well it's it still has some life
in it so I started uh started watering
it and it's been
yeah
re
uh what's the word it's been uh uh yeah
Phoenix Reviving revitalized yeah so I
wonder if there's a chance that it might
grow some berries after all cuz it's it
has very fluffy green leaves now
H yeah I thought it was like dead for
good cuz I once I saw it was dead last
year I just gave up on it
completely it was really
dead
yeah and now it's a zombie planted
yeah assume we came for the job you want
to work for the newspaper right work for
it I'll just share whatever I know with
you guys I guess but I won't actively
work for you don't you listen pen I told
you I was busy but you keep bothering me
and another thing I bought this place
for the owner after we came to Fair
mutually beneficial
and could you stop telling people I
cheat them in out bit wait which story
is really true I'm sorry Tracy but
there's a new applicant for aortal jop I
wanted you to
know H yo that jacket looks comfy and
fluffy yo nice winter clothes hang on
you look
like guys sorry P could you give me in
the sky a second here is she a fan of
course she is
all right how about you give me the
whole staring link I'm the other of the
lucky Club Gazette here if you couldn't
tell so don't worry I know everyone
involved with the story P asked us for
help digging into what's happened to
Princess Zelda now tell me everything
what exactly brought you here my horse
goba interesting that's not really what
I wanted to know but cool good horse I
guess coming here was a great call what
I mean is we're getting tips from all of
a hyru so many in fact that it's been
hard to keep up and among those tips
we've been hearing about someone who
looks like the princess appearing in all
sorts of places even introducing the
blood moon like it's a cult ritual
really motivated man I was about to
assign pen to chase those leads but he
could use a partner I won't tell pen who
you are it's better if no one knows
you're involved what do you say think
you could work with him as we
investigate of course I wouldn't ask you
to do this for free thought though that
would be
nice wait just a second I'm going to get
you a little incentive from the
back what will it
be what you're not giving these for free
to me wait these are swimmer
clothes oh like frog yes I was going to
say got like froggy legs a full set of
froggy
armor with that on it seem to cling to
wet we even get armor for that don't
have to what
don't have to use the Elixir wait when
you say wet surfaces does it also count
for like ice surface like icy
mountains no ah pece by
okay wait does it come in effect like
does it work already after putting one
piece on
hey I
wonder Diet Green
you're going to have to run around the
whole high for this oh man so I get it
really
late yeah I'm your
partner yeah all right you two here's
what you're going to do visit every
stable for leads pen you'll head this
all Up Stables bring in people and
people bring details and details are
what we need so get me some news wait
all stables and then I'll get every
piece but like one by one give me me one
[Music]
now
no how dare you tease me like this what
if them B if you just don't give it no
don't show it to me at all just say I'll
get a reward no okay I probably wouldn't
have worked so hard if you wouldn't tell
me about
it h
okay
um sheesh we're so close we're so
close I'm going to hurry over there now
and then we're going to end the
stream cuz it's been almost 7
hours and even though I could go on much
longer I feel like we
should wait a second I can't go with my
horse is that what you're saying
what' you do to that bridge fix it sorry
to disappoint you but the bridge is down
there's no way across since the
newspaper ran an article about Dorito
food shortage Supply shipments have
started to arrive which is great but
with no Bridge there's no way to
transport the goods Dorito I'm at my way
send here and uh and since the sun is
refusing to show his face is cold I
might throw another high and pine cone
onto the fire those things burn hot yeah
I don't care about
that oh
wait a second you want me to fly
over by making a big fire so I can't go
with I can't go with my
horse I'm leaving my horse in the
freaking I cold place
[Music]
here yeah but that seems what they need
me to do so I know you just explained it
but how exactly does it work again to
make a wind do you just make a bigger
fire be careful I'm going to uh burn off
your eyebrows
probably pine cone you
say uh
here cuz I got no
newspapers oh dear I definitely burnt
all her
eyebrows
May r v this is considered the r Village
Ice Ice Baby can I destroy the
ice
[Music]
um why did I scream like that huh I
thought I think I thought I was falling
in maybe
which I guess eventually you will oh you
can really break it that's cool
though maybe underneath some of these
there's something
[Music]
hidden I love that they did not have
this in breath of the wild oh snowy a
the the snow is so fake oh my God makes
me so happy
wait how do you do it
again how do you do it again how do you
do it I forgot how to do it I forgot how
to do it how do I put my shield
out oh
wait uh
why does he
[Laughter]
stop it was a very wobbly ride worth
it oh I heard
[Music]
it confused me
oh mommy is going to end it soon don't
worry but mommy is on foot now
everything's going to take
longer really H kind of
lame snowboard 1080s
Edition are we getting
soon I love that you can jump on
it to break it that's fun and it makes
some sparkly
animation be nice if there were some
fish but I guess this is just like on
grass so it makes no sense that there
would be fish but maybe some bigger
ponds and lakes are frozen
too wait where did I come from
ah this
way it's like a magical mystical music
music going on here
oh I've arrived I've made
it for real for real
now it's like so dead where is everybody
and also wait this place is exactly like
it was in breath of the wild just now
there's snow
was there snow here nah there was no
snow here in bre of the
world and yeah I just recognized the the
tune we hear
[Music]
it wait what am I doing
do I have to fire it up hi
[Music]
chy just being cute that's
right nice you need several ones
okay is there a chest behind
this yes
yeah good memory right yeah yeah yeah I
remember this place oh what I can't put
it in my inventory but can
I can I put it on my
weapon oh yeah I sword I hope it won't
melt that's
sick I wonder if it will also freeze
enemies maybe not
feel like that would be a bit too
much I like how the weather's
changed like the the Blizzard's here now
and the the thunder storm is gone in
another place oh look at that can we use
that the flower crown
doesn't really make sense with the
snow wait we have eight now we just so
happy to have eight
now okay I'll take a heart container and
a stamina
vessel yay let's
go just
casually uh
gathered double the amount
we now have six
hearts two stamina would have been a
better choice you
think well it's okay off screen I'll do
even more shrines
probably that's a thick container
Dam so how much do I get like half or
fourth probably
only a fourth or is that even a fourth
no that's not really even a fourth
that's like a a
fifth
man hello hi kids
cute how you dealing with this snowy
weather
huh your song Wait didn't
you have like
a wait wasn't this a quest in ref of the
wild making them
sing
oh it was well I remember so
well but were they singing this
though nah definitely not these lyrics
Skyward a line of ship storing build us
a passage
Skyward the god ascended to Heaven
leaving behind an ark it wind brought us
a new life thanks to its Great Divine
spark you know this song is about the
arc that saved R Village a long long
time ago something bad happened then
just like it's happening now it's not
that long
ago a that song wi Arc what is it really
real a so happy if it
was definitely is Papa told me it's
always watching over us high in the
sky wait that storm what I could sure
use it help with this awful blizzard
most of the adults aren't around anymore
because of the weird weather oh they
leaving the children behind in this [\h__\h]
weather alone to deal with it themselves
what well if we don't have the ark and
we don't have the adults is up to us
kids to take care of the village
practice is over for today KY you're in
charge of
food Molly we need to just make more
errow hey like even stuff like food
they're leaving them to do oh my
God what that's
so
perilous what's
[Music]
so oh no I did it again and the beds are
too soft and
inviting oh a customer who's sleeping I
wasn't sleeping not me welcome to the
swallows roting oh we don't have any
other guests at the moments of rest easy
and rest well and we bad is 20 ret down
B
50 I don't really want to
rest come on again but I feel I feel bad
not taking up the services I feel like I
should give them
money is there they said most adults are
gone there must be at least one adult
also there's a shrine
here you got a shop W they got can sugar
they got
butter they got an oil
jar
M can
I I feel like oh goat butter can I even
make this
myself I want
some
hi okay one for now cuz I accidentally
pressed okay and cane sugar I want some
too I need to try it out I'm very into
cooking in this
game the oil dry too why
not yeah one is fine I [\h__\h]
noops
sorry nice
you know what I'll take the rest of the
butter
too why not cuz you sweet and I guess
I'll sell some
stuff
[Music]
wow I feel like there wasn't this much
story
today but we
did um I'll sell this for now uh
oopsie we did make a lot of progress
distance
[Music]
wise which I don't know how good that is
really there's a bunch of caves along
the road to the east
more
uhhuh ah the world is so big man I'm the
on the path to the true true true true
uh yeah maybe at the top oh look wow
that looks like Monster Hunter clothing
oh hairstyle let's go
cute wait you don't need to cover your
uh head in this cold ass weather sure
but I want that he
650 shouldn't have bought all that
butter snow Cur
trousers uh 1,500 I could afford this
one but I want the hairst
[Music]
oh wait maybe she'll give me something
probably no money though you want fish
huh a fish pie made with Stam doesn't
that sound yummy problem is I can't
leave the village to catch a stamy no
bass thanks to this dumb blizzard and
everything else tantha wheat gold butter
rock
out remember that that's a recipe but if
I'm going to make a fish pie I need the
fish I need Stam NOA
B okay I guess I don't have that I have
other fish but not that
fish
unfortunate nothing
here here's a cooking
area oh very nice
M I like this
Village also reminds me a little bit of
that Village uh on the tree on near all
the
matter you have to keep on going higher
and higher and
higher and
[Music]
higher I like the colors they use in
here very pretty
yeah the
children how about this one M you need
something mystery cuz I'm actually kind
of busy my papa told me you can use ice
fruit to freeze monster Chet which gave
me an amazing idea for an invention my
problem is I can't go out to pick the
fruit right now with the blizzard and
all it's not fair it's the best
invention I've come up with ice fruit I
don't have that either
huh side quests that I'll be doing oh
wait I
do gu I I
do ah ah
it's you want the white choo choo
jelly not exactly what I had in mind but
I bet I can use that to make my big
invention oh it's really not what she
meant but you can use it anyway oh wow
you don't even need the exact
item
interesting wow what
a what a nice Quest oh when I attaches
to the tip of an arrow I'll have an
arrow that can freeze moners from far
away sometimes I'm so smart I scare
myself a little same same I get it I
wonder what would happen with other
materials you could make arrows with all
sorts of effects listen to me every
breath I SP out
Brilliance but I should probably stop
talking before I give away all my best
ideas anyway here's a thank you person
no give me money give me like a stone
that I can
[Music]
sellow God damn it not 10 arrows come on
there's some adles there let's
go just want to check out everything
before I go
there okay that's
it that one's pink how cute is that
[Music]
yeah I have it in
German cuz I like the voice
acting he's so excited his voice is good
too well you know me do I know you were
you a child in breath of the wild like a
baby
T like tasaki tasaki is a Japanese word
for like a chicken
wing yeah I think table sounds familiar
to me
though it must have been a breath of the
wild right
perfect right
osaki
what you just finished breath of the
wild I don't think I remember all the
references are in this game yeah maybe
not all of them
but link they told me you were missing
it's good to see you doing
well new Rito
Elder helped against the Flying Machine
ah really what see the one it's very
nice to see you again God damn it she's
she's such a Barbie look at her
mhm do you remember my son tulan he
grown taller though perhaps not yet
grown
up cute family but maybe I would if you
didn't treat me like a hatchling all the
time as long as you still think you can
Take On The World by yourself you'll
always be my little
chick what you think I
can't what I'm already full-fledged you
know you'll change your tune when I
today scouting
trip they got cute
balls you all can keep wasting your time
training the song of the Stormwind Arc
like it's real but not
me what are you
unbelievable Tuli wants me to let him go
find what's causing the blizzard and
he's having trouble hearing
no it's an old F song here in RTO
Village long long ago well when we faced
a different sort of upheaval The Village
was saved thanks to a great flying
[Music]
ship or Soul claims the song that's been
passed down through
[Music]
generations yeah bird mom's so tall
she's so pretty I like her
curls wow it's a song for a children
mind you few adults still perish it as
if it were
true still every now and then you get
reports among the reto of a flying ship
combine that with the blizzard caused by
this upheaval and it seems less
far-fetched
what another ship maybe in
there oh it's very very Fundy in there
too
even if the song of the storm wind Arc
is just a children's rhyme I suspect
that there's something lurking high in
the sky but the air is so turbulent now
that no reto can fly close enough to
look into it this is why I say we need
to make careful preparations to find the
truth but Tulin he thinks we cling to
that song out of cowardice M but these
are R matters you came for some purpose
yes
huh what this is terrible news so then
not even hyro Castle is safe if princess
sela's disappearance and the strange
phenomen around the world are related
somehow we read with ordinality love to
contribute to his search but this
abnormal blizzard shows no sign of
stopping and food has grown scarse
everyone I could spare is already out
researching The Blizzard or Scavenging
for
food my husband hasn't been able to
leave the village much since becoming
the village
Elder wish there was something I could
do M but maybe I'm not the one you want
you should try asking
harf my friend harf has many sources of
information so he might already have
lead about Princess Zelda you see the
two bonfires out that way
mhm M he's in a Lodge near there if
you'd like to try visiting
him
okay thank you
who one's profile has actually I want to
look at these um no I thought maybe
because you can see her previous form
maybe you could see the other ones too
but
no
cute ah to wait they don't put the wife
in there they only put the Son and the
father in there what
mean yeah the illustrations are really
good
okay welcome Raiders oh
hello we just arrived here but that
means I can get
rid of my
marker y I was a long path oops let me
look at it again
though today we went from here here to
check out all of
this and then went all the way up here
amazing actually wait the the tower
is n it's pretty far but it's close to
the next spot we have to go to or is
that really far does it just look far on
the
map I didn't think you'd make it to
retail ha I have
determination well what is it's actually
it's not it's not that far maybe I can
even
fly like from here over this big gap
yeah maybe stamina will run out
actually is that
risky I feels
risky do a
flip ah do the shrine for True oh Shrine
Shrine I saw the
shrine where is
it shrine doco
there it
is all right gataki
Shrine maybe that's the last thing for
today yeah this place really have
changed
H more wind riding
okay
oh okay no problem easy
M ah
y go go go go go all right nice o
there's ice I can jump on
here are you wait wait a
second is there like wait wait
is there like a chest door still here
maybe no maybe
not almost
died that is a little bit
embarrassing wait what is what am I what
am I dealing with oh
God should I fight those
am I fighting
those [\h__\h] yeah there's a treasure chest
there it's just really difficult for me
to get
there okay
oh oh it's dead
IIM Ice Ice Baby one hit kill actually
wow why do he have
a why didn't he have a wooden bow not a
construct bow
and why does the wooden bow not go up
with the wind ah this is why he didn't
have a wooden bow H why he didn't have a
construct
bow
okay what oh my God you scared me
[\h__\h] hell man
ah my material's going to fall
off materials look go
oh
okay fine I don't need them
anyway can't make up my mind nice yo
this is such a genius
weapon no yep I got it this time I was
fast enough and now we where do we go
now this
way where am I
going
ah easy good
tryle not too easy not much brain power
necessary was fun some combat in there
too yeah very effective makeshift weapon
I agree I might be one of my favorite
combinations but ice will not be that
easy to find most of the
[Music]
time popsicle
sword I speedrun it by Falling you're
supposed to dive eh falling and diving
in the end same
thing now we're back here and get more
iceam true true true could do
that whenever I needed
it
anyway he I kind of want to play even
longer man it's been 7 hours you know
I'm just like saying I should stop
because like it's not
healthy but I feel like I can go even
longer like today my stamina is
incredible let's let just go over to the
tower oh there's there's
another Crystal ass over here um wait
uh one
and two ouch that hurt oh but actually
was a critical it w That's
Heavy what do we get a purple Ruby nice
I need the money
wait wasn't it something like 650 or so
to buy the
[Music]
hairstyle
wait
uh wait uh
uh no no no I'm
stupid oh maybe to this or or one of the
arms but they break so
fast and
then I got two Icy B blind arms now
let's
go on the shield I think they're gone
now I never use my shield
anyway pursuing a lever D pouch oh dice
pouch I thought you were doing a lever
dice a few hour streamers welcome mine
it's already been like 7 hours 20
now it's a normal time to stop uh for a
normal streamer but I am not a normal
streamer oh Sor sorry sorry
sorry sorry just like really excited to
buy this new hairstyle where is it did I
go past it
no did
I
huh I swear checked in every
place I looked inside everywhere
what no no no no no no
no how did I miss
it that's not it that's not it
that's not it
aever he they're so cute
singing down there their sweet
melody ah this is it okay yes I can
afford it let's go I mean yeah like here
I'm fine but on the mountains it will be
even colder
apparently I don't know if need all
threee pieces but at least having the
headdress in combination with my pants
now look at him cute what a cutie now he
tied up his long hair and added some
cute feathers there's some stuff around
his side
Banks cute I feel like he should be
colder now but
apparently apparently he feels warmer
now
[Music]
thank
you yeah I've made so much progress
today in terms of like distance so I
hope you guys can catch up until next
time I don't know when I'm playing it
next time I have like a rough plan for
next
week for most things
oh see every time
cuz we're going to have whole
talk Actually I don't even know if I'm
taking tomorrow off or if I'll be
streaming how do I get what how do I get
there is this the right way
[Music]
I'm going back
now well I'm definitely
taking Friday off I think cuz Saturday
will be H talk this
time try just fly
over let me
try oh [\h__\h]
yeah yeah yeah that'll be fine I think
it's
fun looking
okay two days yeah I think it'll be two
days
off are these trees going to move too I
wonder or is it only those specific
ones I thought it did enough progress
for you to catch C up not the catchup
but decided to go to the other
way but why would you go the other way
why wouldn't you follow the main
quest that's entirely your
fault what a weird path to take but this
is breath of the wild or more like tears
of the Kingdom so it's
Freedom oh it's a snowball
what can I build a
snowman wow wow wait
no wait was that maybe by a chance
connected to a
crow oh what is that the I saw something
sparkly icy
sparkly what was that ah ice bats
no I don't care about that
best yeah lifting that kind of big ass
snowball I think would normally be
pretty heavy right oh that is a
COR I know that we have to teleport
through I saw
itend video
Y and then from up here I can look at
the monster camp and think about what to
do about
[Music]
this how many are
there four what is this
wonderful very effective I think they
all died at least like some of
them it didn't even get to blow his
horn don't fall down no M no y oh I got
him no the other thing I didn't I don't
want to fall off let's run
[Music]
back oh that was
easy that was super
easy berries and arrows noce noise can
never have too many arrows
what else you got here what are you
hiding from
me what are you hiding from the hero the
protagonist you can't hide anything from
me what's near
Treasure what a li liel Li Reaper ah
it's from those
Lalas that I
skipped they stole it from them probably
I'll drop
this H maybe it's effective against them
too
yummy see
steak
oh new
fruit ice fruit oh it gives up an effect
that strengthens muscles and increases
attack power in cold
temperatures uh okay so I'm only
stronger in little cold
[Music]
environment let's
go 1080 snowboarding
W this is the best way to move forward
in uh a snowy area ah he wants help
again no hold all you have my support
let's see for how long he has your
[Music]
support
um
wait is this going to fall no I wonder
if that alone would be enough because I
feel like the snow should stop it from
slipping you know
you didn't realize you could do that
until much
later that it's so much
fun now I feel like that might may might
have made it worse but I'll just add one
more on the other
side
[Music]
maybe to me it looks less stable but who
knows
I'll
try I
mean try letting go
oh it
works there's a wizard over there D they
still have wizards in this game huh they
drop magic ones of their
element you
see I feel like they were really
difficult to fight in bre of the
[Music]
wild quite
challenging
yeah oh there's meat around the re ball
ree ball rice
[Music]
ball you can one shot them with
elements oh with fire for example in
this case
ah well I currently have a lot of ice
weapons
but oh God he scares
me and they teleport too don't
they
[Music]
they scared
a [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] ah don't get in the
way how does he not see me ah how did I
miss why does he ignore me
yo was that a one hit let's
go oh Sapphire sword are you wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
wait okay I'll take it in exchange at
least the the fight against the wizard
was super freaking easy it was like a
one one
shot m
maybe attach to
this can I
[Music]
not it's a weapon yeah but you can put
weapons on weapons
normally guess I'll get rid of
this ah I already
do they not drop like a magic one
because
I kill them like this or did I just not
drop it
anymore at
this in the interior of the
Kingdom what so I guess okay they will
always maybe drop like a weapon or
something that's fused with a gem
maybe
that's what they normally drop now cuz a
sapphire
weapon yeah it was a makeshift weapon
already that's why I couldn't fuse it I
thought Sapphire sword was like a
thing from
him cuz it also looked
shiny the gem makes a sh magic really I
was going to sell it though
Sapphire I neck yeah SP the B
bonfires this makes it hard to see where
you going so we keep these bonfires
going as a beacon for lost Travelers
they eat up a lot of firewood but it's
worth it you can spot them even from up
air though as proud as I am they they
can't beat the spotl they set up on the
fancy Sky View Tower yeah that's where I
was going it won't Ro you up like a
bonef fire will but it's hard to beat it
for size and sheer
brightness the highlands are pretty
incredible to have built something so
impressive yeah wait AR isn't there like
someone I'm looking for
here hebra TR Head Lodge oh ooh can I
take those now you're selling them
huh we found these strange things at the
foot of the HEB hebro Mountains they're
all the shied aren't they I've done
every test I can think of but I haven't
learned anything not even what they're
made of for what they're for all I know
is that they're pretty heavy and pretty
sharp it probably hurt if you got hit
with one
huh m oh they're all mine
thanks now you know what you need the
stuff for the fire I I'll leave it to
you I'm so
nice good thing I speak Bird yeah comes
in handy when
playing Zelda
games 7 and 1 half hours excuse me
o oh yeah let's read this h about the
storm wind Arc Legend one day the winds
that ought to blow in RTO Village ceased
then the heavens grew stagnant and the
Earth fell to
ruin the villagers looked Skyward for a
solution they saw a figure Pierce
through the unmoving great clouds and
descend swiftly toward
them believing No Ordinary being could
fall from the heavens the villagers
called this figure a God and the god
stood at top a hill day after day
longing to return home to their island
in the heavens the villagers forgetting
their own troubles tried to carry the
god home on their proud Wings yet who
could say how far it might be the place
this God came from the reader took
flight in turn each hoping to reach that
place above the clouds alas no one had
wings strong
enough saying this the God told the
leader of the village that returning to
the heavens was possible if R gathered
materials their Spirits hide the
villages set about doing so the god
nodded upon seeing the tall pile of
materials this they understood would be
enough the god poured a strange power
into the pile and several small boats
were assembled cautiously the villagers
bordered the small vessels began
floating up into the air with the god
leading them the boats Rose higher and
higher soon passing through the thick
clouds the vastness of the heavens took
the villag breath away floating islands
down in the Clear Blue
Sky the villagers rejoiced songul and
then with reluctance return to earth
when day wind at the Village roared back
to life in shock the villagers looked to
the sky floating above them was an
enormous ship that the God had sent in
gratitude numerous ores in both on both
sides began to move like wings
soundlessly churning the
skies air blew across hear once again
the skies cleared and blooming flowers
Rose from the ground the God had given
them the blessing of wind this Arc that
saved the Village from catastro from the
catastrophe came to be known as the
Stormwind Ark so when the story of the
Stormwind Arc that saved the village
long ago wow wait was there another
page I was going to talk to him
actually right don't worried after I
heard that you had gone missing what
happened he looks so cool look at him
well
edgy so you're looking for princess Sal
sry to tell you that I haven't heard
anything about her our feathers are full
dealing with a more immediate a problem
everyone from the village has left to
scavenge for food or investigate the
cause of this teral blizzard and all
that has been hampered by the sky
monsters that seems to be everywhere
we're spread too fin to deal with them
properly on top of everything else sorry
bud I wish I could do more for you for
don't not that I think of it maybe Tulin
could help tul all right you weren't
around for it but little Tulin has
developed a way with wings that puts the
AL to shame oh we have a little little
genius among us a little little what do
you call
it what's the
word
not uh a prod yeah even in the vicious
weather he patrols the skies and reports
all kinds of useful
information his wind gust technique is
something to see none of the rest of us
can pull it up can he teach me though
even St DEA acknowledges that to and
skills Cut Above the kid does preing
about it more than he should but well is
worth asking
him with Jaan and L on a trip to find
food uhhuh
okay HEB South Summit cave that's
Northeast from here pass the cliff out
front and up the Mountain Road there
should be a bonfire marking a spot are
you going to mark that on my card please
on my
map
no okay um yeah I'll go to the
tower should I maybe take these these
ladders
actually I
do wasn't it plan to stop after the last
shine yeah but I wanted to play
more I'm feeling very
comfy very determined very
chill y I can't
stop I have to make use of this but now
I feel like my my my mouth is becoming
numb and stiff
so it's it's
time and I still need to keep some
motivation I guess for the sake of
cooking
afterwards hey yo that Island
was crazy
oh the [\h__\h] is
that is that an
enemy was that that's a that's a bird
isn't that is it not oh look those are
some spikes we haven't seen those in a
while I only saw those in a shrine until
now do I have a weapon that I can stick
it
to
no m nope
nope oh wait H now I recognize I from
the far your head didn't look like your
head to me your upper body looked like
the head
m is this a side
quest uh okay you got to be kidding me
how am I supposed to get
inside is this main quest or side
quest I was hauling food out there there
when the entrance collapsed that doesn't
really look like a collapsed entrance
maybe it
does thank you
BL to leave all the food behind but
maybe I just need to call today and
watchh and come back tomorrow no no I'll
do it oh there's a side
quest
um let me just shoot a
bomb what I thought that was having an
enough distance from
it what a stupid
death what a stupid unnecessary Death
that
[Music]
was oh it's saved right here
amazing
amazing okay more distance well bird
isn't very safe either is
it wait wrong
[Music]
wrong he all right oh it needs more than
that nice let's go it's pretty much
open I'll get rid of the rest too though
does it drop some good
[\h__\h] Ry
Claymore Ros pro pass cave I did it what
did I
get a red ruby
okay
[Music]
byebye now I'm curious about what's
inside well it's a cave so there should
be a a frog right
oh dude's here too
oh I can't
go I got two I think no one one on a
bumb alive
though no I'll go here another time I'm
too distracted
[Music]
too
distracted excuse me oh [\h__\h] there's a
lot of these spikes ah wait I remember
from breath of the
wild you just got to set them on
fire I'm s an opal your weapon oh what
does that
do I guess you could also fly over
it oh no kind of wasted
that ooh mushrooms that's a new one a
chill
room
oh cook dishes that allow you to stay
cool even in nice okay cuz probably
after this will be a hot region soon
after so we'll need items like this
until we can afford to buy the proper
clothing will we see link again in like
look women's
clothing or did they change their ways
will they let me I kind of want to see
him again in in women's clothing but
like in in a different one A new design
oh my God I didn't think about that
until now that's
exciting [\h__\h]
oops a wait oh wait there's more
[Music]
MH how much do we
need don't burn the tree where's the
entrance
actually is
this brench
oh oh it's going all the way around I
think yeah yeah yeah
yeah nice nice spreading like a
wildfire get outfit is not
[Music]
in
so what will he be wearing no cute women
clothes please give me something
Chloe fought link with Zelda wait like
just generally or in those
clothes cuz I mean well if you you don't
know much about Zelda games it's quite
common to start out thinking that since
it's called The Legend of Zelda that the
main character is Zelda yeah oh okay I
see that's what's
happen well Calli might also think that
way cuz she's just also never played a
Zelda game before
[Music]
ah damn she's a bit late to the
party can't call her a gamer I would
say sorry
Chloe I'm revoking your gamer
[Music]
rights the gamer oror
oh
M
wow most of this is just
mountains it's going to be rough to
explore
especially if you wanton 100% this game
and you're looking blind for kod
good [\h__\h]
luck
man oh there's a ah wait that's not an
island it's a
hurricane I thought that was going to be
an island ooh not
hold I like how he's he's so casual when
he's up there y you got
know
wait can land we can land on one of
these but I know I said I was going to
end it but how can I end
it when I have to look at what you can
do why are there these platforms uh here
with um balloons on it
though why who look there's like a like
a Golem over there and I saw I
saw um cuz I didn't you know there was
like a boss on the tutorial Island I saw
that and it wasn't even that bad once
you figure out I mean it was not even
that hard to figure it out but
damn oh an ice dragon ice dragon oopsie
It's Kind like ice horns it's actually
got three heads damn but this one I
wonder if it's difficult I love fighting
these
guys should I try am I even like able to
fly over there now with my height
maybe wait I can go higher with this
thing can I
not wait a second but is there something
interesting
here there's one enemy
construct surely there's something else
there
too
oh heat resistance
okay has anyone fought this one before
that one over there if yes tell me if it
was
difficult taking
off so we gain some height haven't ooh
he's level one oh you know okay you
you're pretty far huh you're pretty far
this
game okay is that enough
height that should be enough
[Music]
I'm scared oh wait I should heal I
should heal I should
[Music]
heal maybe defense
up why not oh but that's a big heel
huh okay
eating midair doing everything
midair so how do you there we go but
does this even work on this
enemy no okay I'm too far
anyway um hi flux construct one um so
what I've seen is that you have to work
with
this oh
God uh wait do I do I can I HT it too oh
yes okay
okay nice well that's so easy I didn't
even have to do
anything okay but I saw like you have to
take it apart and stuff I that's what I
saw in like a different
video uh
wait uh do
it can
I I thought I could take it out maybe I
just have to take a different part out
it's a rubben
cube does this do
anything would it get weaker if I do
this it get
faster oh a
chest okay help
on wait wa wa wait wa I'll try again
I can't I can't
[Music]
ow I got some hits anyway [\h__\h]
it I don't think this is how you do it
but [\h__\h] it it
works
done ah should have sh Shing it the
other has worked without shaking it so I
wasn't sure if it would work H just
Brute Force rocket ooh there is still
some devices I could get that I haven't
gotten
before a device that produces a powerful
press it packs a punch that burns out
quickly portable pot and some charges
and this thing what this
thing uh I can't pick it up so should I
put it on a
weapon fuse has already
been oh my weapons already been used is
it
really oh all my weapons are fused
what I
do diffuse something and a weapon menu
wa what's in
here now I should go back o treasure
map
oh it's in the underground in the
deaths oh it's like in the middle of
[\h__\h]
nowhere I wonder if there's more holes
to drop down besides that one that we
found the big one or if you have to go
for the big one
always
and
uh not
interesting Minecraft treasure oh there
are t
really so you don't always have to go
for the same
hole what should I
unfuse ah this one's Fus as horn is a
travel
sword what okay let
me destroy it it will be destroyed
[Music]
no oh I'll do one of these
maybe I don't want
to no okay
what the [\h__\h] though what what what is
this what is
this 30 strength
now flux core one
pounder really a big whirly
bunker weird
stuff didn't even need my defense I got
hit maybe once I don't even remember how
I got
hit oo there's like the Torpedoes are
here
too I could build something but I don't
know like what I would do I think I
would just go down
now it's kind of inviting though is
there something up there
that that's where I jumped off of didn't
I they clearly want me to build
something though h
[Music]
M I don't
know ah the treasure chest got launched
at me I see I didn't really get hit I
didn't really get hit I did really well
so I was going to say maybe off screen
I'll do the tutorial
boss on my own I'll go up there no I'll
take care of that
one they leave this here so you can get
back up to the other portion
[Music]
yeah but I don't want
to I don't want
to that's that was the
tower where should I
go why do I go apparently I need to go
in
here let's try to get close to it
again a phantom on remat N Hell
no hell no I'm too scared of
[Music]
them why play off screen and you can
play for 12
hours no I want to spare you guys of
some of
the more lengthy boring slow
Parts what that is that Frozen that
enemy it's just ice no isn't like some
enemy that's just
icy anyway I see a shrine in the
[Music]
distance oh got it oh oh no damage taken
let's
go oh wait it's right
there I should probably stop
you no no no I do the boring Parts on my
own no I have to like you know I have to
I have to um Farm in the mountains I
have to farm like some gems materials
anyway so I can sell
them maybe I'll Farm caves and well
and
stuff oh wait I just realized that their
cooking pot is like
under under a
thingy come
in
cute oh can I take these thank you oh my
God I feel bad about taking the
Flint I don't really need it I never use
it you can have it back I'm such an
honest person chimney
me go east from H Castle down to find a
cherry tree
what can you write that to me again on
the Twitter
reply not going to remember that maybe
write it to me on my day
off I gave it back oh I just want the
oil I give back part part of the things
I've stolen makes me a really good
person don't you
think is The Game worth buying a switch
for you don't have a switch yet then
then not only this game is worth buying
it for but many many other games so yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
definitely all right it is what 11:00
p.m. holy [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh my God 8
hours 8 hours I streamed 8
hours what you know what I got to do
tomorrow
um I have to
call
DHL and be like what the [\h__\h] is the
matter with you guys I got a
letter
from uh a laer
firm asking me to pay up
270 but it doesn't say like for
what and the fact that they sent it for
a lawyer firm must mean that I missed
out on some like letters
right reminding me to do it scam but it
came as a letter i feel like you know
but it it only had like an account
number like a DHL account number and I
tried looking it up but I'm not sure
where you can type in your DHL account
number but anyways I'm going to call DHL
cuz I don't I in the past months I swear
I haven't gotten anything from DHL like
that and and the only thing that would
make sense that I would have to pay to
DHL would be like um
uh like import taxes you know when
something comes from Asia or so when it
arrives here we have to pay quite a bit
but
normally they pay you pay it directly
before receiving the package like you
you don't just get the package and then
you pay afterwards no either they come
to your door and you pay it up front or
if you can't pay they don't give it to
you they don't give it to you so they
will bring it to the post office and
then you will have to go to the Post
Office to pay it there if you don't have
the money when they give it to you at
home so I can literally not receive it
without paying so I don't understand
what else it could possibly be I don't
recall anything that I would need to pay
DHL for and I didn't get any other
letters REM reminding me to pay for
something but it happens I googled this
and apparently it does happen you know I
would be very well that's what I call
there's a deadline
though a paying
deadline I think good it's in a couple
days yeah but I was like what the [\h__\h]
that's so much money and I'm not going
to like some things you know I'll get
bills and I'll be like okay and I'll
just pay it but most of the things are
like familiar to me but this is I I have
no idea what that
means well I mean it does say it does
say
it's for
DHL no but not for which package or so
make sure it's dhl's real phone number
yeah I'll call
DHL not any number on the letter I guess
that is what a scammer would right
H but that's weird like I've never
received something like this before
if that's a scam then it's not very
common in
[Music]
Austria yeah okay I would be happy if it
was a scam because then I don't have to
pay
up oh and my I think my brother would
have told me if I missed something but
it makes no sense like what would it be
like what could it
be I don't know I don't think it could
be anything in what case do you have to
pay
DHL money like that like when you send a
package okay then you pay when you send
it when you receive a package and you
have to pay something for receiving it
they won't give it to you unless you pay
for it
anyway
so I I can't think of any other time
where you would have to pay
d right okay okay thanks guys you you
gave me some
confidence no they would send it for a
lawyer I get that if if normally they do
that if after many many man many
reminders to pay something you didn't
pay but I never got any reminders before
that and I don't know what it would be
for I I don't know if it's my brain
playing tricks on me and I just can't
remember something that I should be
remember but I no no no no it's a common
scam tactic
H okay
interesting uh so Monday tomorrow I'll
call
them M okay
okay yeah that's it's a lot of money I
feel like their scam would be more
successful if they asked for less
money 270 bucks what the
[\h__\h] schedule today or tomorrow
um depends on if I'll stream tomorrow
let me check my schedule real quick what
I was planning on doing
[Music]
some scammers are crazy amount of the
amount adds urgency yeah yeah yeah yeah
no the the time limit adds urgency and
stresses me
out they even wrote that I can pay in
um what's the word in Little
Steps ah by the way pass part two
getting my model in
there it's not I don't think it's going
to happen at all like I asked and like
tried to get it
rolling um but it seems like I won't be
getting the help at least not anytime
soon yeah so I said okay I give up cuz
I'm close to the end of the
game and I'm not going to wait like a
month or two
to get
this done so I'm good thanks I got
pretty close doing it on my
own but
[Music]
yeah it's not worth it waiting endlessly
so I was thinking playing Passa two
again next
week there's passort two there's Girls
Talk there's hoto talk those are the
things I had in
my in my schedule
TK I'm live creating my
schedule Tok on
Sunday starting at the same
time and how
about I have some stuff to do on
Wednesday H okay how about passport to
on Tuesday Monday
tomorrow should be
okay what I do on
[Music]
Tuesday what do I do on Tuesday should I
play
TK during a weekday cuz one day would be
Sunday but then I would play it only
once yeah I'm planning on taking
Wednesday and Friday
off oh wait I could do members members
epic EP lost
epic cuz I'm doing it Weekly right
now yeah that works
out actually you know what I'll do that
on Wednesday I have some things to do on
Wednesday but it'll be fine I think so
I'll do it Wednesday evening I'll take
Tuesday and Friday
off okay so
basically
schedule I'm just going to tell it to
you now in case I feel too lazy to do it
after cooking but it's basically here I
just don't want to make the graphic and
all that kiaha
time uh Austrian
time m
passport two either 6 or 700
p.m. uh on Monday Tuesday off
[Music]
Wednesday 6 or 700 p.m. last epic I
think 600
p.m. Thursday girls talk at 1000 p.m.
with moonay and [\h__\h] B on my
channel Friday I'm taking taking off to
prepare for whole
Talk Saturday whole talk 300 p.m. kiaha
time and Sunday the
21st uh same time as today tears of the
Kingdom let's play for like 10 hours
let's go cuz it will be apparently the
only Tok stream but I'll probably be
doing
some on my own time on my days
off yeah hey yeah yeah
yeah
um gosh wait did I
just did I say who holot talk is with
did I just accidentally say
it did I say it by
accident no I didn't oh my
God I thought I I thought I did I mean
it's no problem it's already the end of
the week you'll know it with the
schedule graphic but
[Music]
no I didn't say it
ah how far am I behind with super
chats not so far
right can I
go not that far
yay we can read them tomorrow cuz I'm
streaming
[Music]
tomorrow yeah I'm going to cook some
food I'm going to cook some food ah I
want to play more wow I'm actually
hooked now I'm I know the first stream
even though I must say the tutorial was
like really
good uh even for
beginners who didn't play breath with
the wild felt like it was really good
but
still I don't know something about that
day just didn't feel quite right maybe
it was just my general mood I don't
think it was necessarily the fault of
the
game just days are different somehow
sometimes
and today I felt like
just exploring and running around and
doing this and that and I didn't even
tangent that much actually like I
recently stopped writing down my
tangents cuz also not so much some not
so much exciting stuff has been
happening and then the smaller things
I'm like often too lazy to write down so
I'm sorry guys I've been slacking with
writing down my tangent so then I can't
think of anything on my own
[Music]
there's some urgent fees required what
what
what hold on there some urgent fees
required for usual room maintenance can
I have your credit
card why are you trying to scam
me are you testing
me are you testing me so you you can be
sure that I'll be fine with the other
scammer
n n why not just keep playing during the
rest of the week you seem to
yeah I wouldn't mind skipping out on
passport two I'm not like so like wow I
got to play passport two that's not the
vibe I have right
now yeah but it would be like a
long
stream yeah but girls talk to short
whole talk is short lost epic I can keep
a a reasonable amount of time okay if I
do that though I will take Monday off
and just stream on Tuesday really long
cuz if I do a long long long long stream
next and I feel like I want maybe I want
the day off in between I'll probably
play Tears of the Kingdom tomorrow
anyway on my own do some shrines and do
some
cooking okay okay I think that works out
I mean I feel bad for always taking
Mondays off but after a long week I
often feel like
it I felt like I would still have energy
tomorrow but if we're doing a long
stream and you're kind of right I mean
I'm sorry for anyone who wanted me to
play prosport 2 but you're right I kind
of I'm I want to play Tok
I'm quite into it
now and and and it's a long game right
so we have to make
progress maybe if on Friday I get done
and feel bored if I get done with h talk
prep early and I feel bored then I could
play passort 2 or if on H talk
afterwards in the evening I feel bored I
could play passort 2 whatever I could
squeeze it in if I really feel like it
but still uh we're still only at 2 days
off so should be chill kiaba gorilla
yeah probably not happening let's be
real I enjoy every second uh of my time
off I am very good at enjoying my time
off it makes it easy to plan my week
right and then I don't have to feel
stressed about having to put out my
schedule
tonight I just do it on Monday you're
right are you guys okay with me playing
more
TK are you okay with
that really are you okay you guys got to
catch up too though you guys got some
Tok to do homework
homework everyone seems to be playing it
hey we're playing it basically together
you're playing on the
side you're already ahead of me oh
damn well you got one day
now to catch
up and then a couple more days in
between four days four days until the
next one after
[Music]
that I can already tell you save 1,500
rupees for something very nice later
must be an outfit is there some cute
women's clothes after
[Music]
all he is am playing right now isn't it
kind of early for
her did am get hooked or what but Ena is
also no ena's still playing breath of
the wild right I saw she's still playing
bre of the wild well I'm I started an
hour ago
hi Amit where are you in the game I can
come meet
you wait not an M
PG should I
ra where is she right
now do you hear Amma stream
no wait maybe you don't why is it not
routing to my desktop
audio where sheit she's in a shrine I
don't know where she is
exactly but she won't even notice if I
raid
her she won't even notice I'm is like
she has those horse thingies around her
eyes
she didn't even notice that I'm in the
chat I
think and she noticed my message but she
didn't read
it I would always read amma's messages I
would always scroll up to see what she
wrote she got blinders
man do you hear her
[Music]
guys I got her so quiet she read your it
would be good for oh really I didn't
hear so well cuz I got her really
quiet maybe next Zelda step will be them
making an MMO
[Music]
RPG she's she must be really addicted if
she starts to stream so early in the day
the the day after she played it
yesterday already she must be really
into it I'm happy she's into
it it's good that she's into something
so
passionately we're doing a watch along
of Amy now it seems sorry guys she had a
dream about it wanted to stream early h
ah oh she has one of those big charges
that I just put on my weapon means she
must have killed the tutorial
boss she must have killed the tutorial
boss what about the raid I guess
I'll I guess I'll raid
her
okay uh well then I'll I'll end
it let me mute am for a moment it
confuses
me and J we say guys I'll see you the
day after tomorrow I'll go cook now and
tomorrow I'll close the scammers and
I'll say what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you
uh unless they're not scammers and then
I really owe them
money um and uh I'll upload the schedule
tomorrow and I'll probably have to do
some audio recording for my album
tomorrow yes I'll be doing that I should
really do
it yeah hopefully it will go
well have a good day thank you you got
this thank you take care good luck thank
thank you best of Lu recording thank you
hope do good enough thank you thanks for
your stream Thank you new lay new lawyer
tangent coming next stream I don't think
so have a good sleep thank you have a
good night thank you good luck thank you
good luck tomorrow thank you love the
stream thank you me too I have fun I
want to play
more more more have a good day tomorrow
good luck with d thank you
I love the thank
you have a great night have a good day
tomorrow thank
you thanks for thank
you it will boss best luck for recording
thank you thank
[Music]
you
for
um
yeah we is oh man oh man
man
[Laughter]
yeah oh yeah about reading the names
again I don't mind that but like
obviously I can't read all of them but
then the few that don't get read are
going to be
like she read me she hates me
[\h__\h] so now now I don't want to read
them all anymore you Ru it the nice
thing skill
isue but I don't hate you I love you you
little
shits I already ate all of my t
Yi why she hates me
specifically
yeah yeah yeah only
you K will respond to this message if
she doesn't hate us ah see I did I did I
did I did did I wish I was red see I did
I did I
did now you hate me more than anyone no
I
don't I can't believe she didn't read
thousands of names unforgivable yeah I'm
such a bad streamer
man okay okay I go cook yeah you want to
sleep okay okay okay okay and German we
s we doesn't m m
bye-bye let's go love to Youk wow wow
wow okay ah we got to wait I have to set
it up before before doing anything
right I have to set it up before
[Music]
closing no one will ever R kaha but
kiaha raid other people
wait YouTube is very
[Music]
slow where exactly was
it
vital yeah I get rated by Indies I meant
you H Live members though
[Music]
Callie streaming your truck simulator
today
Amelia
Watson come
[Music]
on doesn't show up to me oh wait did she
turn it off it was grayed out to me I
[Music]
think
oh I can't rain
her I don't have permission to raid her
I thought I could raid any whole La
member H doesn't want to be raided all
right
okay oh goodbye then you guys can go
there on on your
own if you want to oh El blocks me okay
nah I won't rate anyone it's okay
bye-bye ch
[Music]