[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
goodness
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I brought the screen over to my room but
it's so big
wait
uh
sure
oh
wow
one moment
[Music]
oh you don't hear the museum yet uh well
let's first of all get that going
sit down study streams must have Lo-Fi
don't you think
okay let's make it like this
and then
a little piece of paper for study
purpose
actually maybe we don't need the screen
so because see
oh
[Music]
yeah animation included but okay maybe
we don't need it maybe it's fine if we
just do it like this
yeah yeah yeah
okay and I go here
and then they go oh is that too small
but maybe overall I can move my my chair
a little bit
wonderful okay
modern technology yeah impressive huh
so
[Music]
welcome guys we're gonna study Korean
today oh
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
you know what I mean I have everything
on paper though
um and I need to write things on the
screen yeah yeah also I have so many
things
I have like oh I I bought a folder to
like or sort everything into but
um it's I have no what do you call the
what do you in English what do you call
the thing that you make holes at isn't
it
um hot kiss right
I learned it from chaon
that I don't have that so I can't really
I'm really sorted from a hole puncher in
it
oh wait hot hot kisses ah wait hot kiss
was the
stapler
okay whatever my whole puncher really
what a lame word
I guess honestly in German most words
are like that hole puncher just really
simple descriptions of what it is
is canon
made this Hotchkiss the hole puncher or
the other thing
but I simply something English today
does it have free range no too
I
I nail from today yeah yeah I thought
you know I was looking for something
that fits Chihuahua study and maybe even
from Korean artists because I'm studying
Korean and uh I have a school uniform on
in this one so it makes sense
yeah but it was actually used before for
advertising in in Tokyo right
yeah birth control pills have such a
funny name in German
wait what's it again in German wait what
I think we just say pillar we just say
pillar which is and normally normally
normally when we talk casually we just
say Pele which is just pale
but I guess what's that what's the
proper way uh anti-baby pillar and
I don't ever hear anyone ever say that
no nobody sends the full thing no and
yeah that's weird why are we talking
about that
um
on topic ah I'm nervous because it's
been so long since the last time last
time
let me get comfy last time
I think I just showed off that I can
write where's my pen
I can write
yeah uh
okay let's see if I can still write
uh are you sure
[Music]
yeah yeah
um yeah
[Music]
he he I think there's no care so there's
Kiki uh
[Music]
kitty kitty
Kitty
[Music]
yes yes that's Kiki
was that not like he care
leaky
okay yeah actually actually I see I
think I see most people write a kikiriki
but it should be
uh
um
ideally in my mind it's Ricky
yes
okay
Korean Bros
a very very important
okay okay
so
ah I don't even know where to start
since the last time I've learned so much
and do I remember it that is another
question I want to study the words many
many words
because tomorrow
is coming tomorrow coming coming uh wait
it's coming
um I don't think I can set no wait I can
say wait wait wait wait I'll make a
sentence let me make a sentence I want
to make a sentence with my words I just
I just I haven't looked at my words in a
while I need to remember now give me one
don't teach me
[Music]
um
twitch
name
um
[Music]
is that the proper sentence wait so I'm
saying
foreign
[Music]
okay
do we need a word after nail
or it's just nail omnida okay
see I can make sense because I wasn't
able to do that before but all these
words I've learned before
no don't need okay oh yeah and and I
make still sometimes mistake with uh and
E basically something ends in the pot in
an m so I have to say e if it's like if
it ends in a or oh then I have to say
um
oh
foreign
[Music]
no no my notes say omnida why why
is it is it a different word
is it a different word I know to come is
omnida to to to go is come Nida
ironically
is to go it's like Kegel ah I haven't
learned that yet so we don't even no
don't even teach me about that yet we're
still in basic form the only uh forms
that I know is like
umida
had a
computer
so
I think like Hada tudu Hada is the most
basic form and hamnida is like a
nut extra pop polite version but still
an okay version to say just I am doing I
think like present form
[Music]
um
yeah okay so the verbs that I know I I
think you guys know uh through
Twitter if you follow my progress on
Twitter
uh I'm not gonna write them all down but
okay
this is just a part of them but I know
okay let me see can I can I can I I'm
holding I'm holding my paper in front of
me
what the go away
and and I'm I'm holding my hand over the
English Okay so let's see if I remember
and evenida to be omnida
to go
to come to come
[Music]
um
Ida to do
I think to rest yes
is to be taste yeah
is
uh to be fun my sim need us to drink
sumnida is there is I think
is there isn't
it is to study and to learn to learn
there's like differences
peonida is learning
is teaching
is to study which is just a combination
of compu the word for study and hamnida
the word for to do so you do the study
foreign
[Music]
to be expensive
yeah
is to watch pomu so if you watch pomu
policy
p o m
[Music]
uh to walk is a kamnida and
soups
some words are kind of useless I don't
think I'll ever use this because because
this is used from like um textbooks for
school purpose and this will be good is
to end a class in like a classroom
setting when am I ever gonna use this
but we are not uh-uh no no
uh
we're not ending it yet we just got
started
this is a class yeah so those are some
verbs and then I also posted oh these
words that I haven't been practicing so
let's see if I remember anything
is life
is recently I think yeah yeah so you can
ask how's life recently
kurotiman and many other versions of it
is uh but
is homework
is friend
Moon
is a question I forgot that ah and then
Ted up is the answer
puddy's pants why do I have that here so
Random moja is hat
I is child
check is book omaki's music Young Hua is
moving Shin moon is a newspaper
workout
uh
ah what is what
so you can ask what is this
uh okay here's some timely words
oh no
is today
Neil was tomorrow so all day is
yesterday yes
yes
is what day
and anje is when
okay and sengili's birthday so I can ask
you guys
say uh
[Music]
um
oh I forgot how to make sentence
[Music]
thank you
but I'm making sentence I know thank you
but thank you
Nika
[Music]
no G sound
the G is what saying ill not saying
what sing singing not singly
I know it's saying ill but I'm adding
the E because I'm making the sentence
and my teacher told me to uh combine
the sounds
um
when like we can connect them
you know
I trust my teacher
thank you
[Music]
that's easy to remember singing birthday
um okay month is your what what
year is neon
and
oh I didn't write this job
[Music]
is often
is sometimes
[Music]
um
I asked this because I wanted to know is
market like Supermarket or company
and
Amador Maybe
it's a club
is meeting
okay I don't remember these words
pongali Club
[Music]
Club but Club as in like activities at
school club or so or like a chess club
and Naja is the date okay okay let's say
the date of today is
uh what's a thousand again
um
how do I say a thousand
[Music]
um
uh
some
eachon is
on Egypt
Sun
yeah
uh uh
[Music]
foreign
okay I'm gonna do something on the
screen in a moment let me just repeat
some more words that I learned that I
think I did not post on Twitter because
this was the most recent lesson
[Music]
um
is
a toilet
[Music]
and then
is makeup table
I jumped it
[Music]
same beginning because apparently they
used to call toilet more like a makeup
room you know like a I think in
in in in in German and English I think
we have the same kind of way of saying
it yeah yeah
a chip is home my my chip
welcome to my chip this is my chip
okay there's three different desks what
I'm sitting on right now is the Czech
song
uh
and then
[Music]
this
this is uh
or kotatsu but more like tacta
and then there's also shiktak which is a
dining table I guess could use a kotatsu
as a dining table too
some people to do I think but this is
more like supposed to be small yeah so
we have checksan for like study or PC
desk
tactile for a small table like a couch a
sofa table
t for dining table okay
oh wait I have a good idea I don't even
have to draw this
I was gonna draw a room and learn you
know with my words because I learned how
to stay inside on top under up next to
front back nearby between Etc so we were
learning uh with a picture to say how
there's pants on the bed or there is a
chair under the table Etc but we can do
it
um okay okay
but then let's hide a little bit okay
okay
ah
but I'm not done yet actually but okay
it's okay and
uh wait
one moment
how did that make the sentence I want to
repeat uh
I'm here okay
yeah
what's this
oh
um
[Music]
usan e
um
yeah
wow umbrella right it was umbrella thank
you
and then she says wait she says
um
and they say
fish
SOPA
[Music]
okay okay
is the indicator for when something is
somewhere okay so I can say and
or or a chicken name
uh party
yeah
and we say
um
bed bed was
[Music]
because the pants are on the bed yes
yes right
oh yeah
okay and then we can ask
um
foreign
[Music]
okay
correct correct
[Music]
what is there
um
I can say
where's the makeup table next to the
bookcase and check down
or
order
[Music]
yup
or
kunjo na it's but we can say several
words
[Music]
I know left and right left and right
left is right
Orange
um cold
yeah
[Music]
there is one right there on the makeup
table so
uh
[Music]
um yeah
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
when she was teaching me this she
actually asked me do you know this song
exit meet me and I'm like
yes it's one of my favorite cave songs
meet at it and then she told me that
that means up down up up down and that
was like that makes so much sense
because they're also dancing like that
did I write it the wrong way
oh no I wrote it down the wrong way
[Music]
meet is over oh that makes sense they
start on top they start up up down up up
down ah
meet
um
ah
and I could also say
on top I guess but I was I would say all
over yeah over
um okay check Kiana name check check
[Music]
um
inside let's say the books are inside
the bookcase check Chang
inside
and wait I have I have inside and
outside I think
hot
wait
inside
what's inside again ah on
oh yeah ah there it is and
ah and pack is outside pack is outside I
think and it's inside okay
[Music]
okay but if I want to say the books are
in the bookcase like the full sentence
with the books can I say Changi
[Music]
okay
not distinct in Korean also almost the
same
thank you
oh
okay
[Music]
um
well I have many stadiums picture but
let's talk about the uh I need a pointer
do I have a pointer
[Music]
where's my where's my favorite pointer
let me find my favorite pointer
[Music]
resources folder are you in here no but
let's go with this one
okay this okay here sageem uh
sounds like in Japanese
[Music]
um
the bed
on top or over we meet we meet we meet
we meet
on top meat is over limit
and it's two of them now
uh no no no I want to say the picture is
over the bed
um
[Music]
is closed mid is close to under
three above let's say we
um
the pictures are above the bed okay
[Music]
foreign
waffle
[Music]
on the right side
no no not Kudos
it's a meme it's a joke
[Music]
how to say
plants she did not teach me plants
uh
foreign
[Music]
is it a house house plant only or is it
all plants
because I think
sometimes we make differences
all plants okay bam
there
um
I'm having conversations with myself
answering and asking myself
no e ODI
[Music]
um let me look oh
oh
do I have window I don't have window
wind window
[Music]
what's window
s
[Music]
um
important okay
and in front
up
[Music]
oh
what
[Music]
what clothes
um
which is clothing hanger or just
anywhere where you put your clothes in
or no no is the hangers
the whole thing is
yeah clothing hanger is just the hanger
what time
and uh it's in the closest the cloves
are inside the clothing
dresser
oh
[Music]
um
froggy Wawa
[Music]
ah how do I say Aquarium
actually I don't think my teacher will
expect me to know it but how do I say
aquarium fish tank
huh
shujo
sujo
Kwang or other two words
[Music]
because it's shorter oh
fish tank
but now it's a frog tank oh
[Music]
now now she is outside puck
oh no she has escaped oh okay ah
how about
um
[Music]
air conditioner aircon
is the same in Korean as in Japanese
aircon
okay yeah
oh yeah yeah
[Music]
um
say nearby
what's this
cat tree
uh
Catherine
Katrina
oh
[Music]
cat tower
uh
[Music]
oh English
cat
oh
okay nice easy yeah
um
[Music]
we
or
okay okay
uh
foreign
[Music]
or
oh yeah
[Laughter]
Japanese
okay okay
okay
um
[Music]
where are your shoes what
um
what
[Music]
hmm
what
simple simple
ah
what did I say this time
seems
fun
[Music]
it's pile not fire so softer I thought
you meant stronger
[Music]
I said correctly just messing with me
laughs
[Music]
oh
come on
my note
ah
[Music]
on YouTube
no
omnida
and salt
team
fire
[Music]
foreign
Empire
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
okay what else could I ask what about
box did I learn box I don't think I
learned box
like uh
box up here hakko
de hako
in Japanese or
Fox Fox
I say box yeah box
it's easy
um
[Music]
Fleet
or Chang
[Music]
ing
um
foreign
keyboard
keyboard it's
um
I'm just guessing what they would how
they would pronounce it
they can't like uh I think they say it
very strongly a lot of the time the B
kipoto keep oh oh really
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
hmm
what
um or
um
or
or or or uh
da
[Music]
etc
many options
[Music]
okay
okay I can't think of anything else you
ask me questions chat what can you do it
okay you have to do it in Korean but
slowly slowly speak slowly
foreign
okay
oh
wait wait
[Music]
sometimes
nice good question because I can use a
new word
um
foreign
office desk
right
okay
[Music]
okay next let me let me choose one here
um
[Music]
cool
um
full
[Music]
how the hell
no
you're not asking what I'm asking you to
ask
he's asking if I'm a chicken I think no
um
uh mine mine
[Music]
um
or
up up
onion
and no fire chicken no
oh oh oh oh oh
[Music]
uh under the table and all
um
[Music]
salary
I don't know
Bad Blood
oh no
oh
soil
what's up
ah
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
your salary
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
for me don't worry
I know okay no no new new topic before
before
[Music]
ah
today oh can I remember the weekdays
[Music]
what
we still have things to do
[Music]
Monday
Tuesday
Wednesday
first day
Friday
Saturday
okay so we had something in my
in my uh textbook
that I will recreate but differently
let's say it is uh
August okay this is our calendar
of August
I'm gonna recreate it
um it's gonna be
how how did they do that
good
I'm not here okay let's say this is just
you know uh
12. 13.
14 15 16 17 18.
19 20 21
22 23 24 25.
26 27
28 29 30 31
32.
okay yeah and then
I say uh
[Music]
stay here
on this day
there's a there's a test oh
then
here we have
culture class
birthday and here we have
makuru
Michael's
wedding
okay and uh this is Christmas
this is Christmas
it doesn't matter uh what was I learned
it uh what was New Years
yeah yeah it's the 30 seconds you got a
problem with that
[Music]
okay I can't find it but we'll find it
out
uh what's what's New Year's New Year's
let's say New Year's is here New Year's
[Laughter]
we're in August right now okay
okay
I can't find my
my notes to this
alrighty where's 37 page 47
whatever we'll do it all around
is that our New Year's yes
yeah it's awesome and Christmas is after
New Year's I mean if you look at it in a
certain way you know Christmas is always
after and before New Year's at the same
time whoa wow
okay
um so I want to say you ask me
what day
something is and I tell you the day and
the date of the thing
if I remember the words for it um so for
example
a culture class was
uh what
is
[Music]
oh sure what's up
ask me ask me when it is
it
um
um okay the eighth month was pile world
I think uh
foreign
[Music]
thank you for asking me
um
wait wait wait wait a wall
how do we say days again
[Music]
Tuesday was
ah here it is
Wednesday is
first day is
Friday is
Saturday is
I think yeah and Sunday is
okay so
um
[Music]
Ida it's Thursday yeah yeah okay so now
you ask me
it's England
oh
oh oh
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
I said birthday is on 26th of August and
on a Monday
okay okay next WoW
and next question
to say oh
ah
um
mmm
listen
ing
[Music]
oh wait wait wait wait ah Christmas
songs August
some sheep
[Music]
it's on the 30th of August and
um
yes yes
yes
yes yes yes yes yes
on my notes it is on
Christmas so we did birthday we did
Christmas we did culture class
now the rest
yeah
yeah I learned it too
foreign
[Music]
but that's not the right human not the
right question
and where nobody asked about Michael why
is nobody asking about Michael what are
you asking about Ian
Ian
I was asking about Ian Ian
con
ho
you're in concert
[Laughter]
what you know about the Ian concert
I died
thank you forever
[Laughter]
ah
meets
Quintana
uh I think uh wait uh
uh
let me remember
my words
Amado
no probably well it's probably did I not
no no it's fine I'm a dog
a model
um
uh uh uh
chill one
[Music]
uh
probably 2nd of July right right right
right right
okay
foreign
[Music]
and then
what winter is that actually
I actually want to know
uh what what weekday first day I do I
checked my calendar
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
today what day today today
is Wednesday uh
why is nobody asking about this thing
these things huh ask me
okay
do you want to say
[Music]
my color my color
ah yeah let me remember
[Music]
see come on thank you I was trying to
remember what was wedding
um
uh
[Music]
wedding
um
hahaha
and
what what did I say
foreign
[Music]
and why at ill I don't have to I said a
bad boy bad boy oh my god well why do
you have so many bad words that are
similar to good words
pal
and don't say it don't say it
[Laughter]
okay okay okay okay say bye sip pie okay
then no problem okay
um
it's a Sunday
[Music]
I'm also a pal of the Sheep
friend
sheep friend
what
is uh
compa
has seen on
see
I see
[Music]
what
uh
[Music]
jumping
pencil
cup cut
[Music]
tulip
Nida
money for pencil you I
eat money for a pencil oh
okay we did we did Michael's wedding
please ask me about the Hangul go test
what's test again I forgot please teach
me
this is the test right now
ah
[Music]
she
she home she home she home
she home Moon
[Laughter]
uh
hi boy
ill chips and
[Music]
Juanita
okay and New Year's New Years New Years
New Years
Eve New Year's Eve
[Music]
Mealy
thank you
[Music]
what are you guys saying
I asked Papago
[Music]
see it's sick
what
[Music]
I did not learn that yet I think
surprisingly
okay okay
[Music]
and it is
a Wednesday
okay
[Music]
we did
a lot of things we did we did uh dates
and weekdays and we did placements of
things
uh and and and furniture
now
now now now now
let me go for my face
[Music]
foreign
sorry not
um
[Music]
I have three pages of homework uh now
you guys don't see it but
I can take a picture
I'm adult
Amado I take a picture let me get my
phone my phone then I take a picture
[Music]
da
okay
okay I posted I send it to
janma
[Music]
however this is uh
um scuff
homework because my teacher always
brings me printed out versions or scans
and then printed out versions of uh
of the book that she uses
oh sure
wait a second
but you can help me with my homework
stay back
oh no
I guess so we can do this
genius it's not cheating it's not
cheating right
you helped me
let's do a homework
yay okay okay okay I try
um this is just a little bit of it okay
it's not cheating
[Music]
yeah it's okay it's probably fun okay so
um
and what uh what
Al
mad
um
card
what the are they asking me see I
always every time when I make uh when I
do my homework I just the prompts I have
no idea what they're asking of me to do
so I just use Google Translate to tell
me what I'm doing
choose the right one okay how many days
is the culture when is the culture how
would I know am I supposed to know this
how am I supposed to notice
uh okay let's see what does it say
uh where's my
[Music]
okay we need two
when is the
culture class
is it ah
it says
how how many days Google translate says
that this says how many days is culture
class but that probably means like what
what date right so it's probably this
line not because they're not asking what
weekday no I think they're asking what
day ah okay let me okay let me write it
in real life I'm or I guess we can do
both here okay
we have to practice my writing
and
this is a really let's just write in
Black
um
[Music]
oh I'm writing what's above
fifth the fifth month May uh oh
ship
uh
e ship
you know every time I do homework so
many times I will write
um
[Music]
and then my teacher checks it and she's
like no no kiwawa no no
[Music]
but you say you say
but I always I always so many times I
mistake and I just write it the way you
say it but no it's
but it sounds like there's a p not the
not the m
yeah yeah yeah
the is in my throat
okay next question
what day of the week is ichiro-san's
birthday
[Music]
okay it is
um
I can't read this this is really bad
okay Monday
[Music]
okay should I should I come back up
maybe
okay good nice now I just have to write
that in real life let me just
Circle the answers for later
but I answered
back off from the floor
okay
we scroll up
so there's more I have three pages
actually
[Music]
and then
next is
here
what
hmm
[Music]
okay we are we are starting with the
question
and we have to answer
it's fun
and the questions are uh
your team your gym recently
[Music]
um what
what are you doing recently
so that already makes no sense it has to
be this and
hang up
so what sang
clarity
thank you Ali ah there is a Korean
recently
[Music]
oh it looks it looks easier to read on
when it's smaller
ah wait no life
recently so Life in Korea
[Music]
what is this
can't read it
oh
[Music]
the odd
what
what what dude
[Music]
okay ah well it's fun tell me that I'm
not in Korea but it's fun so
[Music]
thank you
let me write it down
[Music]
oh
oh oh oh
[Music]
um okay
okay
[Music]
next
next question
is this is a conversation about school
life complete the conversation
what's the answers
oh no there's no no example answers oh
my God okay
and help
s me
Michelle C this is the name of the
person Michelle
um
I can just write this
I think but let's read ahead so maybe
otherwise it makes no sense if we don't
read ahead
uh I'm very like this
a little no recently
yeah recently your gym
move what
okay she's just asking the next question
what what are you doing recently
okay uh okay sorry right it's fun
I'm not even looking at my tablet
anymore
why am I doing this to me to myself oh
God okay I'll look back let me look back
damn it
sumnita okay
uh yeah
wow and then
what are you doing recently
what am I supposed to write
a month Maybe
study Korean
uh
foreign
[Music]
there is no option
Google
[Music]
oh
thank you
[Music]
I'm not
seeing I don't know
[Music]
let's move this up
see it no options weird okay the next
question is hanggok
you only
only
[Music]
did we say the right thing because this
makes sense
like Japanese
you only I if I like Japanese uh Korean
cooking uh Korean food
[Music]
if Korean food is fun
foreign
[Music]
why are they asking if it's
if it's fun
oh if if I like to cook ah so maybe I'm
saying I am doing uh actually um
recently I'm cooking
I'm maybe I'm learning how to cook
Korean
but yeah I never learned the word for
cooking
so
I don't think I learned it
cook
Yoli compuhada learn I learned how to
say learning
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
okay and they're asking if it's if it's
fun to learn it
[Music]
am I supposed to pull this out of my ass
or what
let's read this part if I can
what is what are we saying uh
cool
what is this cool cool
man
oh
yeah
probably it's difficult
ah so I say
ah
[Music]
Timmy
that it is fun
but
it is also difficult
yeah
okay okay nice nice
[Music]
what it is
swap swap in
[Music]
wait what no no I don't want what am I
reading
[Music]
uh
yeah
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
first page finish
I still have a few more
[Music]
thank you
let me take a photo
[Music]
outfit
send to jenma
okay
[Music]
what what is this
we'll find out
Google translate help me
read and take the appropriate answer
oh
there's lots to read here okay
Ichiro
[Music]
the person is
so
foreign
[Music]
I learned that I forgot
short terms
[Music]
a bookstore thank you
bookstore uh candida he's going to the
bookstore okay is going okay
[Music]
I also learned dance dictionary I am but
nobody uses a dictionary anymore
um
is that buying
not learn this word
[Music]
bye okay makes sense
he is buying a Korean dictionary
it's expensive
expensive
just use use Google use
[Music]
um
theater I recognize this one because
it's like movie
Michelle is going to the theater
uh
[Music]
at the cinema
they're watching a move she's watching a
movie this is different sentences what
they're not related are they Korea
is it end
was was critical end
ah yeah okay
and
[Music]
see friends
and the friend
man
up
what one
Ida
meeting
Deceiver
meat I think maybe I did
[Music]
okay so the questions are
me
no no
it's expensive it's not cheap the the
dictionary is expensive
um
uh Michelle
and she's going to the yeah she's going
to the Future yes yes
okay okay next
[Music]
I'm writing on the paper
what the is this it's a song
this is a song Wait it's more than that
there's more
we have to answer a question afterwards
okay
[Music]
um
so all right so maybe it tells us when
the the like a festival or something is
wait
this is a guide to the singing club
meeting read the text and take the
correct answer aha okay
[Music]
foreign
I'm happy when I recognize the word
faster and I don't have to read the
whole thing
more
um
[Music]
meeting ah
okay
uh
there is a meeting for the singing club
hmm
[Music]
Japanese Japanese music Japanese Korean
Korean music
Korean
[Music]
Korean music okay
Korean music Lulu
um
they are studying Korean music
in the meeting
maybe maybe
they're learning learning a Korean song
okay
in September the 20th which is uh
quietly
I think it's a Tuesday right Tuesday
see
Japanese time
I haven't learned the time yet in Korean
though
this is a bit too early for me
and but it is Han
good
oh
Korean time
so so
soon
[Music]
cool
it says after Korean class
ah
there's no actual time okay okay no
problem then
after the Korean class and
two
children
where in the classroom which classroom
classroom we don't know but kyushil is
classroom I think
I think so now we answer the questions
and
[Music]
knowledge
I'm so slow no my my brain my brain
capacity is almost over normally you
know when I have Korean lessons it's one
and a half hours I think always so we
already passed that so my my brain is
shutting down now
[Music]
um
why did you say twice
[Music]
um
yes
uh
yes there
yes
yes I like the word Tonga it's cute
it sounds Japanese like a Japanese word
cute
and so this is probably a no already I
mean it's always a yes and a no
but let's let's give them a chance
um
[Music]
um I forgot we'll just learned it I
forgot what is this
[Music]
one
okay
[Music]
no no I'm just copying my answers now
okay
underneath
yeah that was last page one more page
fighting fighting
last page looks interesting as well
[Music]
let me send to manager song
wow fighting Mama starting
so seriously man
[Music]
because I am serious about this huh no
wait this one we already did uh where is
the other one ah sorry
the last page looks weird what is this
[Music]
what is this
here
Yogi Yogi huh
it's my background
don't worry all is safe
I am well prepared
I mean that's always that
and my my Wacom tablet tablet somehow
though that's green the when I when I
install something it all goes with my
other screens it never goes actually it
also goes to my middle screen it never
goes to the Wacom screen it's weird
but it's helpful and I keep on cop
ah
eh
I sent the wrong thing God damn it okay
then my reacted yes okay sorry Jen might
just ignore the homework you don't have
to do the homework don't worry don't
worry
ah
[Music]
what does it say a computer you're on
the conversation computer University
Computer conversation choose the right
one to complete the conversation
huh
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
are you okay we complete the
conversation
uh with only two this is it ah we're
talking to the computer now we're
chatting okay this Discord this is
Discord
okay
and wait I
it's too far up
like this is okay I think let's see we
have we have
oh
on
Tom
um
[Music]
working out
hair
umida
okay
so work out and then on Wednesday study
Wednesday
study
right
[Music]
it's fun
a little bit but a little bit
okay okay okay my my brain is like Auto
auto inserting the words now studying
and
oh I my auto inserting is not working
anymore it's not Wednesday
ah he's he's
learning
learning how to swim
so
I I saw you and I was like oh soon
young girl
huh
[Music]
I I was not taught that
four
what
how would I know okay so now we didn't
read the text
um
James James
and Michael it's always these names
I like how in in Korean the great thing
is always with a question like you're
always like hello hello good day
konnichiwa you're always questioning if
you're saying hello to this person
foreign
hello
um
[Music]
Korean
uh
thought
how is it
um
aha
the answer is two
two I mean it says here one and two but
that's confusing it's two this one right
and then the next one is
uh your June recently
what
um
Ika what are you doing recently
uh he is doing uh this thing
and I'm not gonna write that down now
okay
[Music]
one question
this one I I sometimes forget because in
the textbooks they always write
this but it's the same right
or because there's also
like this
but but this is the same right
yeah and then
I guess there's this
which is also the same right
okay okay I think so yeah
so I can write because normally I was
getting used to writing like this
okay uh
Jam
[Music]
yeah
so
okay I'm getting faster
uh oh there's more take me to me down
cool
[Music]
don't judge my ranting order sometimes
it's maybe difficult
also
this is
no this is this is one thing this is one
thing oh God
yeah I know it's not so bad it's not so
bad
[Music]
okay don't judge me no
okay next one is uh what this will say
uh
on
foreign
[Music]
window
s
[Music]
so
soon
[Music]
and is it similar to Japanese this word
too
Japanese for swimming was um
God I forgot uh
I think the the non-verb is
yeah
yeah I mean it starts both of su
somewhat close
yeah I'm just trying to make bridges in
my brain
um
hey
[Music]
um
okay
finish I have to write all of this again
on my actual paper
but
okay
wow
okay back oh my God so much study
ah in the way
oh thank you for being with me for study
tomorrow my songs and name will come and
hopefully not be too disappointed
I think I'll study some more on my own
so that I remember all the words a bit
more
but at least
we got some practice in
is right next to I remember that one
specifically
right next to palook
up down up up down
when in doubt sing the exit song
[Music]
I love that song so much
exited the music music industry
they're not really a thing anymore too
sad okay download this download that and
we are gonna read some subjects
are you guys okay with that
wait
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
wow two hours of practice is enough I
think normally
[Music]
but compare me
to
one year ago where I only had like some
random words random little words that I
could reply with like
and all that so I think
yeah
no no I will learn with Korean letters
no yeah but progress we made big
progress I was like you know feeling
stupid last year you know in the
beginning okay these cute little words
are cute but then at some point
repeating those same words over and over
again
it just
it just doesn't feel like I'm I'm really
putting any effort in you know so
here I am learning more
yeah I've learned a lot since then
actually I asked my my Samsung my
teacher
um how far are we actually with the
lessons because I have no idea where we
are apparently I'm halfway through
I can still add more but right now we're
like halfway through
and I already know how to say so much I
can introduce myself I can I can say a
lot of verbs I can say the date the next
lesson we learned the time I think
tomorrow I can learn that I can say the
date and and the weekdays
I can say a lot of furniture work I can
say a lot of place location words I can
say
uh if something's like close by or right
next to underneath and all that yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah I have to learn the vocabulary
but I think I have a lot of it in my
head already yeah
so I wonder how far we'll get it really
depends on me too I guess if I can keep
up with the speed but
I wonder how far we get
um
[Music]
there's a lot of progress in little time
and dance
when did I start this
March
maybe I started in March
because I started after coming back from
Japan
after after the two months
I said Japan trip gonna affect your
lessons
uh
oh I don't know we're just taking a
break because both my America and my
Japan trip are really short
so we just like skip
the lessons and then do them in the
following week
it extends it a little bit but I'll just
try to in my free time remember in my
head hmm
yeah maybe that's right end of March hmm
for helping me and please
continue watching uh my non-korean
streams too hey
if you want
how about trying to read Club oh yeah um
actually
uh Nails
um
uh tomorrow I learned how to read the
clock in Korean it seems
at least my teacher
warned me about it
tomorrow tomorrow
yes tomorrow
oh
crony can teach you that no I I paid for
my lessons
so I want to get talked by my teacher
hmm
imminent Doom of time yeah
going to read crony and Korea exactly
Okay so
let's see Super Chat
is
where do we live
where do we continue
foreign
[Music]
in the future would be interesting just
to show off all you learned I did like
kind of teach uh tell her roughly like
hey I'm so far now I can do this and
that and this and that
um I showed her pictures of my study and
she was like yo sheesh
you're so far Zelda part free
I think yeah that's free
thank you
yes it was really impressed crony crony
was impressed I need to
I need to impress her more
[Music]
Flex I want her to be proud of me
I mean I don't think it will ever be a
flex
towards crony but it will at least make
her impressed maybe show her your cats
oh hmm
oh the one right before goes up
what that was part three oh oh okay
um
almost went to the wrong one
you came a long way since asking for
milk right
I don't think I even remember anything
from the stream where crony was teaching
me
I feel bad
I don't think I remember anything
what did she teach me I think U2 sale I
went in there already knowing that she
taught me like some pickup line right
with wanna go home and check out my cat
or or eat ramen with me or something
like that but I don't remember it in
Korean anymore
was like want to eat question mark
um
I only know from that eating weren't I
only know the basic form So eventually
maybe I will uh learn how to say do you
want to something something
[Music]
there is no cat
yeah I don't I don't know how to make
the sentence anymore but I remember it
roughly
[Music]
oh actually actually I have something to
do after this stream but I will still
read super chats
but
I feel like I have an idea of what to
eat for lunch today
lunch after stream
I'll show you a picture if I end up
really getting it
let me what am I doing thumbnail.com
the third down the stream I played
played so ashamed because like uh
I shouldn't be playing so long I should
have done some other things I did do
some things but I also didn't do some
things that I should have done and I
feel so bad about it but
but it's okay it's okay I will do it
today and tomorrow
um sometimes sometimes I can be lazy too
right
and also in the end it's like me doing
homework for my streams I'm just like
trying to make um progress so that the
next Zelda streams you know and it won't
be like 25 Parts maybe instead it will
be 20 Parts you know
I farmed so many
um oars
because I wanted to do that like Amber
Quest and then I did the the next one
the next one too
I find so much man
I'm gonna say
I am a rich now in totk but yeah
you will see because she pays crazy
amounts of money
he pays crazy yeah and I found I
mean I'll tell you all about it on the
totk stream but I took a lot of
screenshots too but I um I found or I
activated two fairies so I upgraded some
armor too and I bought some armor sets I
completed some sets
um
uh this and that this and that
let's go yeah
and I went uh up in the sky again
to uh get one better I got I had just
about enough to get one full extra
battery
which is for now good I guess because
the game is long and you're not supposed
to have so many rides all the way and uh
oh right away and I got I think one more
stamina container and one hard container
so I did like eight shrines
the crazy me oh my God you can imagine
how long I was playing yesterday
did you see all those guys are my best
singing yeah I think I saw like a cool
bike that's a really simple bike that
just needs two
um turbines
and one uh
what do you call it the the controlling
thingy
um to go through uh the underground yeah
it's very useful for that very simple
and takes only like eight or nine uh
resources
yeah I was really that silent yesterday
I know
I was so focused torture devices I I've
seen one where they put uh Crocs all
over like some huge Wheels
and just use the Crocs as wheels and oh
my God
um
I don't even have the patience to do
that I can't do that
like you would have to get so many in
one spot come on
I saw a guy using rockets on Shields
I've seen
I've seen people use Rockets like that
and then
um
go up or was it a bomb because I tried
it with a uh rocket and it didn't work
for me
I was just kind of like going forward
and maybe what I saw was a a bomb and
then I thought that it works with a
rocket but there was a shrine where I
thought you had to do that but then I
ended up doing it differently oh well
people hate them so much I've heard that
uh
has at least as many products as breath
of the Wild
if not more
yeah
[Music]
but don't worry I will not be collecting
them I am very open to doing a lot of
side quests and a lot of caves and a lot
of Wells
um but I don't feel like doing
um
speaking of a lot of caves I
I did the oh God I I don't even need to
tell you now but I did the
uh you know in the in the Outpost in the
main the main area you know where where
pure and everyone is
there's this this lady right that the
quest we took last time uh who's like oh
what's this voice behind this hole it's
calling for me what is it and I went
inside and I found the statue
but then I went even further and even
further and it never ended it was like
an endless cave that led you to
underground underground of the castle
Yeah and then inside the castle too and
I was so scared and it was never ending
and I'm like when this is ending and oh
my God but they were so so so many oars
and all that
um so many Treasures uh but the the
further you got to the castle the more
you know that little that Gloom stuff
was in the air and it was getting really
creepy I was so scared I thought oh
oh oh should I go back at some
point I stopped going yeah I found the
the the the the the pants of the night
set
which is really cool
I think that's it though you find the
full armor set there
I only found the pants
and then I was scared because I went in
inside the castle a little bit
I fought some boots
uh but then there was this one room I
took a screenshot I'll show you the next
time
the one room that freaked me out I was
like surely when I step in here
there's gonna be Gloom hands attacking
me I feel it
yeah
so oh yeah there was a giant sky but I
knew I knew that I would spawn the
skeleton thingy so I did not even get
rid of the stones
I only went around to farm all the all
the materials
you know which room I mean yeah inside
the castle that's like at some point you
reach a relatively big room that looks
really empty but I would just pick
through the I peeked through the door
opening and I was like
this is this is
spookies if I step in here
Something's Gonna spawn I'm not gonna
step in here no no no no no no no no no
no
maybe it was nothing maybe there isn't
anything here don't forget to repeat
those tattoos I will I will with
pictures
yeah the first style for us in German I
guess it's stealthos and then in English
I don't know
yes I gotta repeat my recap I just
couldn't hold back right now okay
[Music]
um
my favorite game series behind tails off
oh yeah probably
hmm
oh I mean in terms of like excitement
and how much time I am open and willing
to put into it
um but like you know
not necessarily I don't know ah because
I I loved
um tunic
don't forget about tunic
all right
thank you
Easy Money tip hunt big animals for five
times gourmet meal and cook the five
times together themselves a lot of money
help me buy a bunch of Errors I did that
also during a blood moon a little bit to
make also more money because you guys
taught me about it I did I did
yeah
I was also hunting some yabai dangerous
animals that bring me the gourmet meat
mmm
yeah yeah
all or out of the janitor thank you for
the pinky I have good news and bad news
bad news I was fired because my
recommendation wasn't accepted wait a
minute because I punched CEO so I am no
longer a professional recommender
ah
and I have important questions boss
where is the mom what is the mo what is
MoP
um don't worry about the mop as a
janitor you're more in charge of like
repairing things I would say
yeah don't worry Al what you're not
gonna recommend me games anymore
oh
who's coming right
games and let me know what to play
How will I know what to play ow
don't stop recommending games
I want to continue rejecting them isn't
that what we have going here
um
no no that's the thing that's our thing
you recommend I reject you recommend I
reject Rocca's got your bag yeah okay
gives me a game suggestions that I
actually am interested in
and Al gives me game suggestions that I
am not interested in yeah we have a
toxic relationship
but it makes us happy
I think
[Music]
two sides of a coin
eh
no I give likes to games I don't have
intention to play that's not necessarily
true the fingers just rookai sends me so
many suggestions I cannot possibly play
them all but they're all really
interesting you know and the thing is
you know there's so many though so I'm
not always like when I see it most of
the time I'm not even on my PC I'm just
on my phone somewhere so
I I can't even go to immediately request
permission for it yeah
but at least rokai gets my general link
interest
like what hits my sweet spot you know
right that Redemption I'm interested in
Red Dead Redemption for real for real
[Music]
Hotline Miami
you should play Atelier ever darkness in
the secret highness I think you might
like it
huh
I did
I'm pretty sure I did or did they
release a fourth part now
[Music]
Red Dot has the potential to outperform
even GTA 5.
I don't think it had as many viewers
if that's what you mean
GTA just has like you know a bigger name
you guys will come to see it
there is
mostly horses right muscle horses
speaking of muscle never mind I will I
will keep it to myself for now
hmm
[Music]
okay with it myself you will find out in
the TLC Case theme
anyway thank you I here's a kiss for you
because it was two pinkies thank you
soon
[Music]
and Sean I thank you for the red super
chat
Star Wars connects guy back again to
tell you that there's even more song
parodies in the game my favorites are
Empire Today YMCA does it go like Empire
Today
Empire today and blast approved for
bulletproof this time baby I'll be
plastic
proof like that
[Music]
something like that
hologram girl for hollow Batgirl cause I
ain't no hologram girl cause I ain't no
hologram girl
I want to sing all of those and we don't
speak haties We No Speak Americano see I
actually don't know that song
I think if I were to listen to it I
might have heard it before
because I ain't no whole life girl no I
am a whole life girl
hahaha
yeah that's mean as me
I see
well you guys have to remember remind me
next time I do a karaoke
to sing these different versions okay
please remind me please spam me
[Music]
cause I am your whole life girl cause I
am your whole love girl
[Music]
suddenly it sounds like a Crazy Frog
song
doesn't it
looks crazy frog
upstairs
[Music]
what
what what what you Discord account got
falsely banned and I need advice for
moving on
and you want me to give you advice for
moving on from a Discord can you not
like
inquire Discord about it
thank
you everyone on the cold that is for the
pinky I just picked up coffee at my
local coffee place while wearing your
Holo meat almost cat shirt cute Barista
said she liked my shirt and it was cool
so I can guarantee Kiana merch gets you
compliments from Cute Girls
Hollow meat ah the orange one
that one is pretty cool I like the whole
of meat oh my cat shirts
thank you
yeah you missed me speaking cute Korean
but you can watch the archive
we practiced for two hours
yeah yeah anyway thank you I'm happy
you're wearing my merchandise outside
too yeah I only wear my merchandise
inside because it's
kind of risky I mean you know
I it shouldn't really even be risky
because anyone could wear you know as a
fan and I could just be another fan
wearing the merchandise outside but then
again you know
if I did then it's like kind of like
openly saying hello
hello this is me I am me yes it is me
right it's like
like I want to be I want to be known
but it could be just any random fan
right
this is difficult but I'd rather not
risk it it's just kind of
[Music]
yeah yeah
have you seen many whole life events in
Austria randomly I mean no not Reverend
merchandise no no
I mean maybe maybe I've passed them but
I wouldn't know
because I don't see them wearing
merchandise
my merch is Jim Close yeah that works
too that's a good way of using it too
Christy shaver
rotten Appleton uh
oh
I wanted to hold the scrambled eggs but
the Rangers couldn't understand me so I
said standing more than half and vows
she looked at me for a moment before
coming back with scrambled eggs everyone
always works this is so funny but please
tell me you didn't actually do it I like
the idea of you doing it it's working
well please tell me you didn't actually
do it
that's not how it really happened is it
[Music]
I don't believe it
oh
[Music]
ah quinoa keychains on your car keys
Carrara
carara carcho
yes yes yes was that mean yes you did it
or yes you didn't do it
God damn it
I tried of course no way no you
didn't you didn't really search that in
wooden house in part two of waitress
no
[Music]
she probably doesn't know the meme and
then she's like what the does he
want from me nah I don't believe it no
no
[Music]
unless you also followed up with uh with
a clear up
just kidding okay thank God
thank God
perfectcon merge that is true wearing
the convention definitely possible
hmm
cause it's not German it's not important
is fantasy language
hmm
[Music]
okay Skye thank you for the recipe chat
koala and my timezone today is my
birthday already also my third birthday
in kfp this time I want to be a bit
greedy attention may I asked for some
special blessing from you
yeah but look you're not specifying what
kind of blessing just a blessing
mmm
Skye happy belated birthday
[Music]
wait
um
[Music]
happy birthday to you it's the third
year oh my God
[Music]
you are my chicken
always in the kitchen
you are so tasty
[Music]
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday
for the first time happy birthday to you
you are so loyal
loyal
[Music]
s
you as a loyal and so boiled
go back go back
foreign
[Music]
in your pants too happy birthday to you
there is one more verse
what else could I say but
can't be in diverse
now this guy makes it diverse is what
I'm trying to say
[Music]
and happy birthday
congratulations
diapers diapers
I could have used that too I was almost
there I said divers not diapers
chickens in the universe are just so
diverse
and they have space diapers
just like
ocean divers meow
[Music]
I didn't even bring it up
it was you guys now
I didn't even sing that no no no no no
diapers
[Music]
Lo-Fi
different Lo-Fi
don't fall asleep guys
[Music]
so happy birthday Skye thank you so much
for still being here you're the best
the crackling is uh on purpose it's
supposed to give you this Lo-Fi feeling
foreign
[Music]
I am still uncertain of things
but there will be at least one even if I
lose a lot of money there will be at
least one
minimum
I want I want at least one MB yeah
I will make it happen and for that I fly
to America
[Music]
thank you
yeah at least one made at Studio Army
I'll put that in the credits
filmed at Studio AME
yeah I'll be first time in a while for
me going to America
maybe I should check out some of those
restaurants that are only in America
uh uh like
[Music]
I wonder if I can I might be too busy
and we might just end up like ordering
in but go to valak I don't know if they
have that
Taco Bell yeah right Taco Bell
Pop Eyes raising canes
mmm Applebee's
right Raising Cane's is that the I think
I've heard of it has good chicken does
it
Chipotle I think I did go to Chipotle
with Amir
last year
I think I did
you know oh yeah we ate in and out too
last year oh The Cheesecake Factory
that would be interesting because I
always heard about it from The Big Bang
Theory if yeah
fooders I'm not really interested in
Hooters I know
[Music]
Mexican food ah yeah maybe I can try
going to a real Mexican restaurant I
guess finding a real Mexican restaurant
in America is not as difficult as
finding a
a real
I don't know Japanese or Korean or
whatever restaurant in Austria
although I mean there have been a lot
more
but there's also a lot of fake ones
[Music]
I said I won't be there for too long and
I don't know if we have time like last
time while we were in Army Studio we
only like ordered food
which was really good too but
[Music]
um
don't know if I can go to such places
[Music]
it's a Mexican food while you're there
I'll try oh I still remember and I went
to a beach in L.A
the beach was not so nice but they had
this
Mexican food wagon going through
[Music]
I love this
that was interesting
be nice above all this time
don't touch me bubba don't touch me
only a little bit okay Bubba stay away
[Music]
I will only chill with my cats hmm
part let's go
I'll give him very but you know you know
people um pet dogs and cats differently
right
whenever I'm like supposed to pet a dog
I always pet them very carefully
[Music]
like as if I was petting a cat
okay I only have the dog petting skills
but also I don't know
I just very very carefully pet the head
um you know and the nose bridge and all
that from dogs too just like I do with
my cat
the ears yeah yeah yeah now I kind of
screwed scratched the ears of my cats
too and like the chin and all that but
like softer gentler
one of my dogs actually prefers to be
pet that way oh he's a gentle boy
dogs aren't too picky yeah but I mean
they're probably confused when I do that
because normally their owners would
probably pet them really aggressively
roughly
and then Here Comes This lady that is
like super gentle
Cracker Barrel
cakes
and fruits because then my man
belly rubs don't be like link no I don't
want to give belly rub to Bubbles
[Laughter]
no no
you got too excited
[Laughter]
I hope does that
Country Restaurant
um
uh
I hope it's so basic I've heard of IHOP
before this one's love I'm sorry
I'll give him very gentle and very mild
pets okay
and then mostly you know in the end I'm
a cat person so
I will go back to the cat
[Music]
I'm a totally lost forever
it's okay
mama told us how much he loves you yeah
because he does not understand why I
don't pet him like the others do
I'm playing hard to get maybe
uh Waffle House
what have I may bring her bed why is
Waffle House dangerous
or are you trying to make us Rob Waffle
House we walk in with bats and masks and
we're like give us all the waffles you
have
a meme
oh really
[Music]
Waffle House is where all the fights go
really
there's known for having rough customers
yeah but it's a Waffle House how can you
how
go there and have fights you're supposed
to have waffles
what the what kind of what I would
think the people who go to a Waffle
House are like
cool people who like waffles
like I don't see waffle liking people
getting into a fight it's a 24-hour
restaurant oh at night okay I mean
sometimes I have cravings at night like
waffles too but I guess the people who
would go there at night are like drunk
maybe
drunkards
hangover cure and post hurricane Roblox
what
[Music]
why would you brawl are you really
talking about like a real hurricane why
would you brawl after Hurricane
you should be like getting your house
back together
not brawl at the waffles
that's too funny what the wait you
read super chats Yeah couple okay I'll
go back
right I have something to do let me let
me check my
messages real quick because I'm supposed
to meet someone
[Music]
thank you
okay
I don't think we have time for
Disneyland date no no no
but but maybe time for a swim because
like will it be warm
oh it's already warm here so it's
probably warm there too
who knows who knows I don't know we'll
see we'll see how it goes I want to use
the time you know also to do off
collapse with AMA and and do a 3D stream
I'm thinking doing a um archived dancing
stream
with some Hello project and Vocaloid
songs that I know the choreographies of
and maybe I'll do my own dances too
although they're so difficult
[Music]
but this time like for real because last
time I did it with the scuffed 3d motion
capture that I had
okay
no not yet it's been over a month now I
think so much for updating once a month
um
yeah but I currently have to focus on
learning a choreography so I can only
really do what I already know and what I
remember which I forgot a lot of choreos
that I knew in the past I think but I'll
try
um you interrupted my story no no
problem no no I don't even know what I
was talking about but
um yeah so that's my plan doing some 3D
streams
maybe that and
um
ring fit or something like that
it's still downloading on your requests
yeah
thanks for the rest of chat mwah do you
want a second MB yeah I would like to
um
but it depends I I I am checking
currently for some more creators I I
looked through some
other whole life MBS that have free DMVs
um there are a couple
that are from different creators so I
asked my manager to find out how much
they were charged for those
and if they're like you know more
affordable for me then I might go with
them because they're also pretty good
hmm
and I just hope they can work with the
data that we will provide them with
yeah like the the howling
for example and Howling from you and
what else was I looking at
uh Madame is Everlasting soul
and
ah Chloe's Chloe's free DMV is I think
from the same creator
yeah I think they could
probably do something like the K-pop mvs
that I have in mind
but usually so far from my experience
like asking Japanese creators the same
thing as you know when I was asking the
overseas Creator usually the Japanese
creators are way more expensive
um
maybe it's a case-by-case we'll see
I'll see like choreographies as well
when I ask Japanese choreographers they
were more expensive way more way more
expensive
but then other things like music I feel
like asking Japanese
musicians was cheaper but
um
it I think it depends on like what kind
of musician you ask if it's like someone
who works in the dojin scene a lot then
they're often a bit cheaper rather than
someone who's like already in out there
in major releases and all that
it depends um
[Music]
okay continue
thank you
thanks for the thank you for the rest of
the chat here's money as request it
looks like you're going to need it
fortunately
thank you very much it will be
definitely invested all of this
a huge huge part of my salary will be
invested in my album and in my MBS
because the MBs are gonna be
mostly just me
you know wanting to promote my songs
um
but we'll make it happen now because I
feel like if I don't do that
and won't get as many
people's ears on it as it should
songs are really good they're worth it
in my opinion to be put out there
yeah
and be like hey listen listen to this
Abby thank you hello
and today's my birthday I bought myself
lots of stuff as my own birthday gift
really I can't believe it has already
been 2.5 years since I met you I may not
always be here watching a stream but I
will always be there supporting you
thank you
well Carlos is super chatting me but I'm
also actually in the middle of
commissioning Harless to do something
for me so it evens out doesn't it Carlos
it evens out happy belated birthday yeah
yay
cheers
people still being
over so many May 17th birthdays yeah
yeah there's I see even more birthday
super chats but that one was like the
day before
oh and there's a vault also the day
before damn
[Music]
bad Eric what are you talking about
what are you talking about are you
trying to like bait something
[Music]
yeah
bruh did you see the video oh yeah but I
mean that's just you know every now and
then they put out a audition reminder
hey we're doing auditions by the way hmm
[Music]
hey
maybe I should audition
if we fake audition What if I
what if we go undercover guys
um member stream only and we write an
audition
different name and all that Subaru did
that no way
and then we'll see how far we go I
wonder if management would get angry at
me
um I mean until the point where we would
have like a phone conversation
I mean
imagine me not making it that would be
uh interesting what would that imply
that I'm not good enough
for a whole life even though I am in
whole life
now you have to stream twice as much
hmm I'm scared I don't want to get in
trouble I won't do it I won't that's a
funny idea
[Music]
I get hired again I will be in whole
life twice
double koala even better
even better then we'll have two European
streamers
[Music]
uh okay uh thank you
and oh
[Music]
you may know that I normally don't throw
around that much money but this one here
I owe to you at the docomo meet and
greet I told you that I want you to
continue making music because you belong
to the stage but I also felt inspired by
you so since then I joined the cover
band published songs of a producer and
I'm writing original songs with my own
band what now I want to give the very
first money I actually made with playing
music to you I know it's hard to make
profits of Music yep uh 2003 YouTube
won't really let me send my original
message so let's try the short version
you're great please follow your love for
making more music I'll keep supporting
you please nail let this go through
[Laughter]
yeah us talking about this with one of
my producers my album producers the
other day
dad music making money for music doesn't
really
at least in like my league it doesn't
really work but then even I've heard
that even like Rihanna for example sure
she she makes probably decent money with
her music but she makes even more money
with her new makeup brand like that kind
of stuff just is the real money maker
and music is more like something to get
people to know your name more like that
for that we were already talking about
this during my Zelda stream
yeah the record labels make all the real
money
more or less I guess yeah
merchandise touring
that kind of stuff
which
in combination with my music I don't
really do so
I can't even get myself on the waiting
list for a concert so but even then I
feel like with a concert I would
probably not make profits either
[Music]
and I would just want to do it because I
want to have that experience and that
achievement
[Music]
so head towards the kfb makeup line
no because I don't really think it would
do well either for me
I would need a bigger female fan base no
makeup line
especially not just for me if anything
it would be maybe a whole life makeup
line what do I know but no
that doesn't seem very
smart
can't be cookware line yeah cool ideas
guys but like I can't do everything
I can only do merchandise on like
birthday and anniversary and all that
but
uh maybe if a cooking wear brand
sponsors me or Partners me yeah like the
PC cases that the girls got
or the keyboard that we have now
key caps
anyway thank you 757 mwah really
interesting that you're making music now
too really cool I wish you the best of
luck
and have fun with it
[Music]
sounds great
mdbank
Alcatraz one free free One Direction and
happy belated birthday
zero nine one one two donation zero nine
one one two down
happy belated birthday as well to you
congratulations for oh wait it was a
recipe chat even
yes they marked my third birthday as a
member of kfb I just want to thank you
for the great year I've had with you and
all the cave peeps here's another great
year with everyone come for Yuki Lala Ah
that's an old one
thank you there's a world
um glad you're still here happy birthday
everybody
I'm not gonna sing this time but I hope
you feel congratulated
my God
pre-birthdays I haven't even had free
birthdays yet
[Music]
I understand I understand okay I get it
I get how it works
even haven't had free purpose
weird
[Music]
you better be there for my birthday yeah
and celebrate with me
foreign
birthday on my debut
I guess again
but that wasn't my birthday though I
don't know whatever it's confusing
that's confusing
well in some way in some way I had four
birthdays now
[Music]
birthday
soon
soon it's almost June
so I guess you could say soon like one
and a half or less than that months
holy
yeah I'm not getting
I'm not getting a birthday concert on my
birthday am I
okay I just realized it's really
unrealistic at this point I keep on
asking though hey hey hey can you give
me a date maybe like a
and it's getting delayed but can I maybe
get a date so I can plan and it's always
like sorry we don't know yet we don't
know
so I also don't know
but it's not happening on my birthday
it's okay I will do a call in
foreign
[Music]
studio now we have 3D and you would
think that oh this is the year when we
get you know everything that we were
hoping for
uh
well maybe we will but really delayed
[Music]
I hope it will be in August or so but I
have to plan for it you know because I
have to come to Japan so I would like to
know it early
when am I going there to you know do it
good questions
[Music]
I will be eagerly awaiting a birthday
concert thank you
[Music]
YouTube
zero nine one one two down question
thank you again
Amelia Hardy Dougie
Spanish
love to see you or rather hear how much
you're enjoying Zelda I'm still behind
but I hope I can catch up soon I have to
say I missed the Wawa a lot now that I
have worked a few days the week from the
office again but I'll be always here on
the other days love you oh
I see so you're missing a bit more
streams now because you can't watch
doing the work I suppose
[Music]
um
well I hope your work days will be
shorter and that you can come to my
stream after work
because generally I mean today is an
exception I started very early
but generally I start like after a
normal work day in Europe at least
but
um I hope you're enjoying work hope it's
not too stressful thank you for being
here
zip please
[Music]
I'll do one more
then I have to go
[Music]
next one would be girls talk I guess
okay guys
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
I no need to read this out loud oh yeah
I already read this one actually
foreign
I think she knows
I mean even I know that you guys miss me
even when I'm just like gone for a day
yeah
you make it very very obvious
I mean okay those are more like jokes
but you know if it's more than that
you probably miss me
[Music]
not true
the meme yeah I
was probably a meme that's okay I get it
I can't even go a day without you
Tweeting oh my God
currently if I don't tweet for a whole
day in the coming weeks you can guess
that I'm just in bed playing
too busy playing TNT game please forgive
me
Bishop thank you sir
thank you
[Music]
subject money is going oh what was I
saying
you think where it's going
what we're talking about
context context shoes
[Music]
are you know I don't know a lot of shoes
are older too like I don't
um I don't always buy so many
I might have even have more than 30 I'm
not even sure like you know I can't
count them I don't count them
[Music]
um
uh well
[Music]
how many do you wear regularly
um I think like nowadays I don't go
outside anymore that much so barely any
like two pairs maybe or free in summer
um like a pair of sneakers a pair of
sandals
and
maybe one more
and in winter
[Music]
one two I think in Winter I was mostly
wearing free free different ones
[Music]
um also
uh yeah but that's just because I don't
go outside that much anymore when I was
like before her life when I was still
going out more and like you know going
to work and you know then I
chose different shoes a lot to fit my
outfits it's just now I most of the time
I wear pajamas and I chill at home so
there's no reason for me to go crazy
about my about my outfits
[Music]
oh
did you wear different shoes at work I
only use the same pair no at work I mean
I had work shoes but I mean going to
work and then going back
I would often wear different shoes
pairing shoes with Pajamas I mean some
people maybe pair slippers with their
pajamas but I don't wear slippers I
don't like wearing slippers actually I
feel like I need a grip on the ground
foreign
[Music]
wearing them
every once in a while
especially when I lived in Japan
because the floor was so cold
but
um
[Music]
I like to wear slippers when I go on my
balcony though because
[Music]
what do you know about my forgotten Bill
I've been ignoring
I've been ignoring my my my my my my
post box for a couple days because I'm
scared to look inside
I don't have a post box uh and DHL oh
what what no honestly I don't know what
to do with them should I write and and
and demand to you know do something
check it like I don't know should I just
okay I might just end up
paying it because even though it makes
no sense but like whatever I
can't be bothered with like that
um
I don't know
I want to help me with this
it's a lot of money but what can I do I
mean especially if with something as
stubborn and and mean and evil as our
tax customs Office you guys have no idea
they are
so annoying to deal with and and
whatever
[Music]
oh
my account and my accountant's job is
not something like that she'll charge me
more and then again I'm losing money
she'll charge me one
be Moscow to help me with something like
that
relatable right yeah I don't want to
look inside
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh well anyway thank you Jacob wow
enforcer thank you and Bruce steadily
dungeon Panda Run gaming happy birthday
thank you
thank you for the pinky a message to
okay of peanut members oh listen up due
to Rapid increase in employees you're
neonizing in the usual room and the
unusual room are now close to to
overflow in related news we're proud to
announce the new and improved rare room
no
I am bulldozing that room immediately
because it's hard to pronounce
I don't like it
the rare room
rare rare room
nobody can pronounce that
canceled
yeah the usual room is infinite don't
you know
don't think you know
there is so many as many usual rooms as
there need to be
[Music]
Bishop thank you Jake it's monkey
dancing
soon
Craig Anderson Duncan a whole and normal
function
alejandroid for the pinky and Chihuahua
Dyson Arab funds you know I was already
thinking about buying a Dyson uh hair
dryer when I saw one in the spa that me
and Kelly went to for the first time I
was like yo what is this magical air
hair dryer
it doesn't even look like a hair dryer
it's just a stick wivel with a hole in
it basically
you don't see where the air comes from
it's so weird
I was like this is so cool so fancy
[Music]
yeah yeah like the Dyson fan exactly
exactly but that for your hair and it
makes warm magical air
Big Air
yeah it is expensive but then I found
out about the air ramp
the thing is though it has a kotzu
a trick you have to figure out the trick
on how to use it properly otherwise
you'll be failing
Dyson air wrap
Suga located
[Music]
the Arab one is even more expensive than
the hair dryer yeah yeah
[Music]
ah flash word TV sanction aliens thank
you
probably not but thank you Jesus Alberto
thank you back from security thank you
Corbin Palace thank you
um
[Music]
uh Sadie versus Farmington another great
Girls Talk moment was saying she's not
sure she's girl enough for these but she
is so important to the dynamic I
wouldn't be it wouldn't be the same
without you yeah yeah yeah mama keeps on
saying like oh especially when I first
came up with the idea she was like oh
but I don't know if I really belong here
I'm not really that girly but you know
we're all girls so in the end we're all
girly and
um I do agree she helps she makes the
dynamic very interesting and you know
there's things actually in this episode
specifically me and mume both got kind
of blasted by gura with all her
knowledge
um
and in the end you know girls exchanging
information uh about girly things that's
that's what girls talk should be and
it's no shame in not knowing something
or so
[Music]
but it's uh
it's interesting I'm getting to know
Mommy more too through this and I'm
really happy about that
I learned a lot from Kura yeah me too I
mean part of this is knowledge that I
didn't want to have in the first place
but I definitely learned things
Nail Spa didn't
yeah I do want to get my nails done with
uh myth girls or or with Gouda
specifically
because she's so excited about it I knew
it I knew it we talked about it in epic
epic lost Epic
[Music]
um
Flappy Boy Thanks for the red super chat
once again thanks for organizing so many
amazing collabs like this girl stock man
might not be the Super authentic
experience but for me it's a fascinating
and hilarious insight into the bizarre
parallel Dimension hopefully get to see
many more members make an appearance
thank you
and yeah you raise a good point which is
also a point why girls talk will not go
on forever
I don't think it will go on for very
long just because
Girls Talk usually
spans way more over the topics that we
touch on it's usually girls talk is
usually a lot of boys talk too you know
like like you know talking about crushes
and relationships and all that kind of
stuff and
you know I mean well it's kind of like
intimate talk and and I don't know maybe
even periods talk and stuff like that
and it's either a you guys don't even
want to know that kind of stuff or be uh
it's just like stuff that is
not something that would be appreciated
to be talked about
yeah so it's Girls Talk light as we said
um
Girls Talk light
and it will stay like that but um I I
just don't
um feel like it can stay very fresh
like this so it will have its end hmm
because I don't want to like keep on
repeating the same topics again again
but maybe two or three more episodes you
know
[Music]
hmm and in the end you know it's just
even when girls talk is gone every time
we girls collaborate
there can always be a little girl's talk
DLC
somewhere squeezed in there
any stream can be a ghost dog even if
it's not officially named girls talk
[Music]
ah yeah I was wondering if maybe
especially the female whole life fans
we're enjoying girls talk
and and looking forward to it
because it's something that they
specifically can relate to yes I am hey
yes
that makes me happy
good good to know thank you
hey nice and I think you know the guys
you guys say you enjoy girl suck you
know but I know that you guys kind of
shut off your brains when we talk about
makeup brands and all that kind of stuff
but that especially I think on the other
hand is very interesting to the girls to
other girls to see to find out what
makeup products and stuff we use I mean
the girls are very interested
if you end up being actually like using
the same product I can if I you know
when uh when I was still a whole like
fan only
if pequoda would have talked about the
makeup products she uses I would be so
like interested
I would be all ears hmm
[Music]
girls sharing makeup prize with each
other is always like
good topic
[Music]
you like knowing what I use really
and girls talk I don't know maybe
okay and thank you
zipinky I learned a lot for better or
worse
[Music]
was there that much cursed knowledge
now we're done I have to get ready
to meet someone
you don't have the vocabulary context
[Music]
female hygiene is scary really
and
I think I think our hygiene is not much
like different
from male hygiene you guys use products
too like skin care and stuff like that
maybe you guys don't use as many creams
or so but I I know you guys use like
face wash and stuff like that right
and shampoo
we use eight in one body wash no
hell no every time when I'm in a hotel
that has oh God
body hair
and hand wash in one I'm like
um I chose the wrong Hotel
ew and it's always it's always
where it can work but it's always
yeah
last hotel room I stayed and had that
and I was terrified
I thought you know it looked like a
pretty decent hotel I didn't expect it
to mix all three things oh my God
and yeah it's just not as good as having
everything separately and and those
things are like then focused for those
specific things
sure you can have it all in one product
but it will not be as good as having it
in three different ones
[Music]
it is so true
I use shampoo conditioner facial wash
body wash all separate nice
I've had places where they expect me to
use regular soap
for your hair oh my God
oh my God
[Music]
especially like for
sometimes it's like supposed to be
shampoo body wash soap and face wash all
in one and I'm like I'm not gonna put
the same thing
on my face that I am supposed to be
putting on my hair if this is supposed
to help my hair
then how can it also help my face no no
that's like no skin hair two different
things can't be the same no
um
how no
that's different needs right yeah skin
is more sensitive you can't put the same
on your face
please
that's why also sometimes it freaks me
out I guess it's my fault because in my
kitchen
um I actually in my sink my kitchen sink
I don't have the soap there
because I usually usually wash my hands
elsewhere in the bathroom so in the
kitchen sink I only have like a dish
soap
sometimes people
wash like my mom or my sister or whoever
they will wash their hands with the dish
soap in this thing and I'm like hey wait
wait I got I got salt crumbs so bad and
they're always like it's the same thing
[Music]
no no no no
I hear that so often I mean in a really
dire situation where in the whole house
you don't have soap okay maybe once but
wouldn't it be too aggressive on your
skin maybe one time only okay but
generally no it's not the same
oh she said discussion in my chat
[Music]
a small amounts maybe it's fine if the
greases more else is the same
I don't I don't I don't
I I would not
I would not use that I would think it's
like there I don't know too aggressive
doesn't have the same ingredients
[Music]
it's not like Mama Told Me washes your
hands with dishwasher
[Music]
no
foreign
[Music]
there's people who get their skin
irritated
with that kind of stuff so that alone
that alone tells me okay not everybody's
skin gets irritated by it but that alone
tells me if it destroys some people's
skin and irritates some people's skin
that means there's something in there
that's different from normal soap so my
argument stands and in German myself
[Music]
yeah
bye bye bye bye butt case claws bye bye
no objection except that mic drop if you
guys want to say something like that in
Japanese say hi romba
at the end of an argument if you want to
State a porn and say it's over like the
I I win
[Music]
r-o-n-p-a hi dumpa
you learned that
you make a point with that
bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
bye-bye I gotta go see you oh tomorrow
right I think so
my name
oops
[Music]
thank you