[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
stream is never late or early she's
always on time
yeah well hi guys uh sorry sorry sorry
sorry but uh hello it's Taco Tony time
just on time of course of course
we're totally on time
it is there's some you know time
differences and all that it's just it's
the lag lag lag yes I totally started
the stream on time but then yeah you
know by the way I I wrote here uh in the
title in the theme awaken do you think
Ina it's okay if I add another word to
that I want to kind of name it awaken
the Kraken
is that not good it sounds so good um
um
I mean
I don't have any I am indifferent about
the title okay
no no relation with such creature like
Craig to me a kraken is like a crack
that's a German word actually
what what does it mean I think it's in
like an octopus so basically actually
it's perfect because we're Awakening
totally the correcting but not in actual
actually like it's perfect because you
have kind of just awakened recently and
you're somewhat of an of an octopus or a
squid or something like that tell the
licks excuse me
ma'am it's perfect
we have awakens the inner crankins I
can't believe she's done this
are you able to keep up with three
months she gets them human you know oh
what you waited three months to be human
no I said I I went away for three months
yeah forgets who I am yeah I'm a human
and I never I never thought you were a
human you know you never got me to the
point to think that you're human anyway
I'm offended oh yeah wait I was gonna
play some bgmo and yeah
um
well guys you hear it is it too loud
you know it's like this you don't hear
it right
I can hear it okay you can I can totally
hear it oh yeah it's okay
[Music]
yeah yeah it's like Daddy now I'm glad
you can hear it
okay well well well first of all the
stream is sponsored by Valkyrie connect
once again we announced that we would be
doing this stream like months ago right
what was that when was that
Timber
oh yeah do you remember that September
yeah
we don't wanna get copyrighted
on the sponsor stream on January that's
nothing okay
well yeah back then oh yeah back then we
um kind of just talked about the things
that are going to be released now right
yeah it was kind of like a it was kind
of like a preview of the preview yeah
like a super eager pre-announcement oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah I mean there were
some updates that people were curious
about like the gifts
um yeah that we asked for yeah you
received actually so the thing is
uh I think I already showed
wait kfp helped me out there was that
was that a members only stream where I
or was it public where I showed you guys
pictures of what I received because I
already
received everything and introduced
everything
don't think so
it was it was it was probably it was
bubbling it was numbers
in public
on it public ad members it's a little
bit of both publicly I don't recall okay
most people say public okay then it was
probably public and I'm not gonna show
all the pictures again but I'm gonna
show you the most important one
um and uh you know did you get the small
ones
I got the smaller ones yes
um and I ate that so oops I have no
pictures what that was food
yeah
two whole boxes
my pantry is exploding with instant
noodles wait you already ate all of them
oh there's still so much oh thank God no
I was actually um I I thought of the the
ones from the viewers the the you know
the yeah the viewers just actually
talked about it in today's stream oh
because I went on a tangent but what did
you get I want to know that I got so
many things like
um I got sketchbooks I got blocks like
comic books like a figures like small
Androids and
um uh I also got oh one of my favorite
was actually animal socks and all those
like really cute animal socks yeah I
wore them during my trip in Japan
yeah also got this like really really
soft seal plush I needed the soft one I
hung it to sleep every night oh cute
yeah
beautiful gifts I appreciate it quite a
big box right
that you received I think so yeah
he said I think
um the remember the giant one meter
Paparazzi plushie it hasn't arrived yet
I think it's it's a little bit on the
thicker side of things so uh
thinking it's time you know swimming
across the ocean wait do you mean the
valkyrie takodatsu or another taco
[Music]
remember the giant yeah giant plushie
yeah the one with the two liter yeah
like pop bottle like right beside you
guys didn't get to you yet because I
received my big main
um present already I'm not sure I
actually asked staff son about it I was
like did you hop into maybe see a uh
giant Taco that's bigger than the you
know maybe bean bag one kind of hanging
around until maybe it's lost at sea
maybe it like jumped out of the pool and
then became one with the ocean
I don't know maybe it's just going on a
journey it'll somehow make its way here
oh one day yeah maybe it doesn't like
you know airplanes and they decide that
it will go through the ocean instead
because that's more that's true it's
it's own natural habitat so yeah can I
remind me of um one of the bean bags
were being uh
shipped all across the world I heard
there has been some a uh difficulties in
the storage Department in the uh
shipping department so I can imagine
there can be a little bit of difficulty
shipping out you know an even bigger
takorachi even bigger we'll see well
yeah they'll be fun yeah please keep us
updated
the giant giant one will be fine
well if you guys wanna know just in case
you know I mean I think kfp definitely
knows you know all about it but uh hear
it on the screen now oh sorry now you
can't see it do you need to see this no
I'm I'm watching I thought okay
so fast so this I'm using my eyes this
is the thing the the main thing that you
know I wanted to kind of explain it
again from scratch for people who
haven't been following this whole thing
we are part of a collaboration but
Valkyrie connect we have four home life
members to Ian to Japan members have
been forever eternally engraved into the
game by you know making us part of it
with some cute like customized uh
outfits of our default outfits and you
can use us to fight and attack and yeah
we have this guy yeah destroy it's
really cute there's like a tiny chibi um
pretty models as well and so on Bully
blah blue in order to promote this and
there was like a make your wish come
true kind of event link you wish yeah
and uh
okay and and and uh we were
able to get the following things number
one uh one big present whatever you want
within the budget from Valkyrie connect
yeah the number two was
the like the one from other members
right you know can you explain that one
how did that work
so we each got to choose
like a gift for each of the members in
the collab so foreign
foreign
[Music]
I believe we were also
um given those gifts as well I think we
have different Milestones right so and
so we reached each Milestone we would
unlock each of this these gifts and um
yeah yeah so for example through the
milestones for example what did Ina want
to send me what did I get you know
I got you some cool shades yes uh oh do
you like them yeah yeah yeah they're
actually I think wait it was even like
Gucci or I think I think they were Gucci
Chanel No that's it that's something
else
Chanel sunglasses yeah black beautiful
it came in a nice case too
a nice sunglass case before but now I do
yeah and for Ina I I kind of asked for
her to receive uh like a cup noodles
dispenser but I guess they just kind of
sent you like like a lifelong I mean it
does defense yeah it's almost like a
vending machine oh and when I was when I
was loading it into my pantry kind of
felt like I was loading up like a
vending machine
yeah okay well done it did you have
different flavors what kind of flavors
oh yeah I had oh it did have some of my
favorite you know the classic cup noodle
um there's the salt seal flavor
um there's the curry one and then there
was like garlic Curry one oh garlic some
yeah tomato one
um there was actually just like garlic
flavored garlic one just garlic
yeah it was like a well I forgot it had
a name but I thought I forgot it was the
garlic yeah and there was like a seafood
one oh yeah I think you already
mentioned that I might be wrong yeah I
don't know but they're kind I mean I do
like
you like cup noodles but I've been
trying to cut down on Instagram well you
will have to sit you'll have to move
that yes until you're done with those
and then you can cut down a cup exactly
Chuck can't see anything yeah you can't
finish the gifts you know it'd be rude
not to finish them no and then um also
how many was it 25 or 30 or so uh gifts
from the viewers extra you guys were
able to send in ideas to Valkyrie
connect
um like you know anything within a
budget what was the budget maybe like
a maybe not go with numbers
oh I think it was maybe 10 bucks or 20
bucks per present oh wait ah 5000 Yen oh
so that's more like 40 bucks per for 45
bucks per present and we would have
gotten like I don't know 20 or 30 of
them so yeah yeah so you already
mentioned like which ones you got and I
actually you know yeah I showed pictures
before but I'm not going to show them
all now but just gonna say that I got
some some Lego sets uh one of them was
like a Minecraft one I got like a like a
um switch Pro Controller but like not
the official one but like a panda
controller
I got some a lot of bath bombs I got a
undertale Persona 5 Royal and Nintendo
switch scores
yeah nice which are all games I haven't
uh had before so actually really good I
got like a Japanese classic bath thingy
like the the wooden thing where you put
water in I don't know how to describe it
what to call it the little little yeah
yeah something like that yeah and then I
got like your water on your back before
you go in yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and I
got the Toon Link plushie and I got an
embroidery stitching set three of them
so cute I got an otana
[Music]
you know I really like this gift because
you know when my friends came over I
showed it to them but they were like
what is
what is that and then they got so into
using it there and got really excited
about it addicting yeah it's a good
conversation started too and if
someone's like bored in your apartment
from your guests and they can grab them
with them but don't and play around with
it
[Music]
I got a high quality uh towel from Japan
and towels are great I got a memory foam
for not foam but form pillow I didn't
know it was form not foam but the
package said for me form I think that's
funny I think it's fun package does four
I mean it does form itself according to
my head right true true baby's third is
there like tagline you know it's a
memory for foam that forms yeah it's not
that wrong
and then I got a Minecraft pickaxe sword
thingy
it's so cool Ina
powerful it's pretty big and like you
can change it from a pickaxe to a sword
if you like move it around yeah that's
really cool fancy I got another I'll put
it up on your wall no not yet what I
should hang up kind of is though I got
like a screen hanging light oh like it's
a green hanging light it's like a light
bar for your screen
oh like um Whatchamacallit you put it on
top of your monitor and you touch it
yeah like top I think some of those I
haven't tried it yet though but people
have been saying it's cool so yeah yeah
and I got some other stuff too but yeah
that's that's like most of it and then
of course the main attraction is this
thing is the toilet
um the reason why I have one is put it
on your face camera yeah but then it's
so cool though look at it
you know originally I wanted to get it
myself but then when I was trying to get
it I noticed it doesn't ship to Austrian
and I gave up on it for a while and then
welcome connected they will get me
anything I want basically so I said then
the toilet please
or for a split second he said I was
gonna get it for myself and I was like
ah
no I mean by myself
no no no no I'm not okay you're Senpai
I'm not a cat I don't need it for myself
um but yeah so the thing is with this
one you put in the cat sand yeah and
then Hannah cat goes in there's sensors
that will notice that the weight has uh
increased by the cat entering and then
it will also know when the cat left by
the um weight getting less acknowledge
yeah and then it waits a little bit and
then it starts turning
and then it turns back after it um you
know threw away all done
into the department on the bottom it's
so cool
it doesn't clean until the cat steps out
yeah it made more sense in my head I
know what you mean I heard I heard the
melody
yeah but it's so cool because like I
don't have to like Scoop the Poop
anymore and it's so convenient all I
have to do is like there's an
application for it where that tells me
um that the the bottom department is
full and then I just take it out and
throw it away does it tell you how much
your cat pooped this time yeah yeah it
has records of when the cats entered and
when they did their little business so
basically you could also I guess by that
judge if your cat has a healthy pooping
Cycles
I guess oh because I guess some cats
when they're not healthy they don't go
to the toilet uh incentives
we'll have to remember this sir one day
when I eat a cat of my own so the the
equivalent to my toilet is in this huge
takudachi which has no hat yeah yeah
yeah it's on the journey yeah A Thousand
Years
it will be there eventually so yeah one
day and when it arrives you will
probably show us a picture right oh yeah
definitely okay okay exactly
[Music]
hmm
cute cute cute cute Okay so
uh we talked about that well thank you
guys for the great suggestions by the
way for the viewer gifts they are
perfect yeah
you've become a part of our Lives now
yeah thank you so much
you know one more thing I got uh I think
this was like either
um pecora surprise or lapras's gift to
me
and I got a huge
two or three seater orange bean bag in a
how big huge I said like it seats at
least three people
yeah
that was just uh
it's cute is it supposed to be like a
giant carrot I thought so because when I
opened it up it was just a huge orange
something and I was like what is this
this is a carrot
right
um
I I mean yeah if you don't have such
long legs then you could sleep on it I
think so but oh yeah anyway so I care
it'll be perfect
well it is now in my office it's still
it's still a bit stinky yeah if you like
sniff it it's still a bit stinky yeah it
has like a weird plastic something smell
But my cats don't mind so apparently
it's for my cats in my office when they
they're chilling behind me and then they
sit on the big bean bag they have house
cleaned it cold dibs on it all day but
I don't think you want that because I
don't know how you would bring the bean
bag to your place
I meant one day one night at you yeah oh
but I have an actual guest bed in yeah
foreign
I think you will have to use the guest
bed
because the bean bag is
here and also I don't know if it really
fits you
you can also sleep on the floor the
floor isn't stinky
better option yeah
accepted
yeah when you're on the floor I might
just um in the morning step on you when
I'm getting to them
kitchen
you want to be stepped on by me
yeah
is that like a wake up alarm
yeah yeah I feel you okay okay so uh
we should probably talk about
why we're here
like like to introduce you know the the
new new news
just one more thing you guys if you
tweet something today don't use the kfp
hashtag use the holocary connect hashtag
instead thank you it's only in the title
thank you yeah yeah also uh make sure if
you scan the QR code at the bottom
there's a different one for the GP
version and different one oh thank you
for Global version so you can download
the corresponding one
thank you for saying that thanks
okay so here we go now we could actually
start going by the script all right
so far we've been just freestyling at
least I've been freestyling
it's just a suggestion yeah but now I
will have to rely on the script so here
we go
um I think so it's okay I'm not gonna
just read this okay I'm just
I think a lot of you guys
one star's dream in September and I
already gave a recap on that so let's
not do that again
um but yeah uh we all appeared in
Valkyrie connect no you know
see I I told you that I told you I've
already been doing it all along oh I'll
show you how it's thank you so we went
over
um a little preview almost coming up in
January yeah yeah coming back in
September but now we have more updated
news yes yes wow
um and and I don't know which part you
were just reading enough but I was not
reading anything I was I was improvising
nice improvising
but uh in case you guys uh didn't get to
play the first time around and you're
like I'm gonna get into it now you're
not late because you can get us our
characters still by logging into the
game and using the voucher items that
you get from logging in you know know
the bonuses yeah
yeah what a deal it's not never too late
yeah you know never to too late never
too late to claim your mail oh I don't
know that never too late
yeah so you get the items you need to
awaken all of us from special event
missions okay so now we're gonna share
some special images
to share with you guys we shared the
rough draft of the illustration yeah in
September I guess we did I guess we did
oh yeah they look like Chihuahua
and we really already shared The
Awakening quickening images before wait
wasn't that just the Ralph last time I
guess so yeah yeah it's the finished
polished okay okay it already looks
pretty finished with some of us I feel
like back then
um
uh let me try a little too far
[Music]
in my OBS well we'll start with
um showing you guys the
pecula Senpai original the
non-awakened one okay
um you're sure foreign
[Music]
what is She gonna look like after she's
been awakened
yeah
here
[Music]
wow wow it's like she like jumped out of
somewhere and she's attacking us with
her cuteness
very cute I'll make it a little bit
bigger for you guys and you can like
take a better look at it
okay yeah QR codes are still there don't
don't worry about that here I'll put it
on top then okay
[Music]
did her outfit change I think it did not
to that let's compare
no no outfit's still the same same but
like so much action in the pose compare
this what a glow up
pickle pickle pickle so cute so shiny so
basically
um uh if you see this
wait if you awaken her
where is where did I put it here okay
you awaken her you look at this and you
will hear it in your head
okay my voice is kind of creaking
cracked today so it doesn't sound so
good
[Laughter]
yeah
what else did she say she says um
oh that sounds exactly like her holy
[\h__\h]
yeah she says that she does say that I
totally heard her saying that before
my voice been kind of rough today it
actually works well for impersonating um
hey what's that supposed to mean
um I mean I mean at least you sound like
I can't believe somebody's voice oh
you know okay so it's it's a it's a it's
a talent it's a trait can you give me a
cone pickle
[Music]
I can't do it of course you can
I
okay the first thing voices except for a
certain Mouse
wait
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
Armando
[Music]
um
okay that was freestyle anyway so that
was her glow up let's look at
glowing up
so originally wait I have like so much
so many folders and stuff open
[Music]
this was the OG
yeah really cool I really love that okay
I can't I can't impressionate anymore
yeah I can't personally hurt either
yeah I'll try but yeah
you know I actually I I think I actually
prefer this outfit over her original one
oh I love it is it because
is it because it's like uh what's it
more idoru no no no almost not
necessarily frills not necessarily for
example I really love the shoes that
ah true true the songs and I mean
obviously her weapon is look really epic
so but the dress too I like the shape of
the dress yeah and the the foodie do so
anyway the Thrills When She Glows up
what is She gonna look like drumroll
[Music]
oh yeah
they're seeing the rough for this yeah
what country is she saying yeah she's
sitting on the world
I think I see Australia
is it is that Australia next to her foot
right yeah I think it's Australia
but then uh maybe she's like kind of
sitting on top of uh Hokkaido on Japan I
don't know I don't know it's hard to see
actually around that because it's
glowing so much that's true it's true
but yeah so her her bird looks like it's
about to attack
[Music]
yes and her butt is glowing
there's like some glowing Earth there
every nice Earth is she is the earth
small and shrinked or is she like
suddenly big
as heck like a like a god-sized giant oh
we will never know
we will never know you know what I've
noticed like she has the same like color
frame as you do
purple yeah I like it yeah
can something her accent is like more
yellow and mine is more like oh oh I
hear the heart is speaking Yeah
so yeah
looking very powerful
but
I'm gonna get rid of that too and next
we're gonna go to India it's me so we
already know
this one
this India ah
this one's really so cute too because it
could look it looks so girly this outfit
only looks so girly yeah so cute
I'm like casting a magical spell oh I
think somehow I don't know I feel like
if if it wasn't for your super cute face
and pose you would like look more like
threatening and evil but I can't help it
and look at you and be like oh she's
she's a friendly like sorceress I can
come up there and ask her for some help
right
I I think so yeah I'm friendly I don't
bite wait somebody said she stole Cali
something something and I'm like I
couldn't read that but do you mean she
wasn't like her sock or so because the
shoes I don't know something about that
does I think remind me of Cali's shoes
it's the what's it like the knock heels
not like killer heels I love the gold
it's like the asymmetrical sock um find
out the black and gold you know the
creases that's kind of Cali no I see it
I see it it does look like callous shoes
okay
and then and then we're gonna awaken the
cricket
oh wait we can have three inas
look at all those emails chat be honest
which one's the cutest which one every
single who's the correct answer here
looking at you the one right next to me
[Music]
okay but I want to look at uh this one a
little bit bigger so
I'm gonna move it on top and then
what a mess my OBS already is oh well
so you're chilling tell us about this
one
yeah I no longer have to walk I'm sure
if I'll Quick Connect uh there's they
know what they're doing they know what I
want
um you no longer have to be standing in
game I'm sitting very comfortably look
at all those cool powerful effects you
know know there approach me oh yeah it's
resting in my tentacle chair oh yes
we're gonna get it electrocuted if we
touch you that's what it looks like
[Music]
oh yeah it's so cool
sorry I really like it it's so cute
yeah what a comfortable chair you don't
need a bean bag if you have your own
tentacles as a chair exactly
but I guess they're a bit too slimy
that's why you're using the bean bags
they're like What's it they're like
inflatable balloons almost oh
if I were to poke them with a ball
Boulder pen what happens
nothing oh they don't explode they don't
go like
oh I mean they kind of just created from
Des Moines so it's fine what if I
what if I cut them does the cut off part
so like move
[Music]
I'm not just poof away they disappear
yeah oh okay so it's not like I need it
from the void they return to the void
it's not like a like an unagi like an
eel no no it's not really edible okay so
people no tentacle Sushi then all right
okay
no no sushi I mean I'm not a sushi fan
either anyway so
next is
koala remember remember this and
remember her
I remember her I got this like the girl
in the picture eh do I look like her
I'm the thing DM me if you look like her
oh
well well that's me I'm with my boobies
and my thighs and my Beyblades and my
sword yeah I look I look like an RPG
character which I really like
and then like how your Shields are like
the floaty yes these
Beyblades
you can you can charge them and then
throw them on the ground and they're
gonna turn turn turn speed
oh you can also use them as like like
foot you know like footrest thing so you
can like walk in the air although I
guess you can maybe fly you know but
still like it looks cooler when you do
like the catwalk but with like Shields
you know yes yeah yeah yes I don't know
what you're talking about but yes ciao I
will know what I'm talking about they
have created my we're on the same
wavelength here okay
next up we're gonna wake into Kragen and
this is it please
it looks like you're like almost dancing
you know like when people learn there's
like things where people like dance with
their swords and stuff it's like on fire
and there's like really cool it looks
like that in the middle of a really cool
thing yeah yeah I think since the last
time you guys saw it I was like
um the OG is already like
like looking pretty fancy so this one
has to be even like more awakened
feeling and they did add more like
Flames after that request yeah I think
so it's even more like flashy now yeah
lots of Fire
I'm gonna turn into crispy fried chicken
if you touch
delicious
numb and that's though that's this one
so it's so cool thank you dynamic
and you can also get the um special gear
by the way from the first collab event
from login bonuses including Ina's
stuffed takudachi Kiana
laplaces stuffed curl and Crown Crow
oh
God staff and others as well
yay yay
plenty yeah it's so nice to give you a
second chance
okay so moving on
there is I don't know if you guys
if this has been announced yet or if we
are the first to say this but
uh let's just act as if we're the first
ones to say it it makes it feel more
special before you start this will work
if you give them the
baby
have forgotten
I mean yeah if there was any knowledge
there to begin with
then
exactly okay okay so
a new feature
that is being added is
drum roll
it's especially for us
after a character gets awakened
their Awakening level can be increased
by reaching a certain Awakening level
and then
wow and then you can unlock new voice
oh
24 times
yeah yeah
each character has their own set of
voice lines but with this new feature
you can unlock a second set of voice
lines
Ina explain me how we can unlock it
please go home let me explain Professor
Chihuahua yes
all you have to do is number one raise
the Awakening level for the hero to the
required level number two We Gather hero
specific I mean hero specific I repeat
hero specific items but completing
missions
exactly three times
and three times the charm you know yeah
uh number three use these items to
unlock the voice lines
then number four switch from the first
set of voice lines the second set of
voice lines
makes sense Ina
I think I guess the e ighth way is to
check it out in the game
so we actually have some of our voice
lines to share with you all now and they
play on the chair screen they played on
The Shield screen in the last quality
land but with this feature you're gonna
be able to listen to them
but you feel like it whenever you want
oh
so
um I was not told
how many
I think I can just play as many as I
want but I don't want to spoil too much
so I'm just gonna play two voices each
and of each character and then no no
we're gonna try to impersonate them
right you know
I'm not very good but I'll try I'll give
it a try and so first I'm gonna play uh
which one is this one
oh oh first I'm gonna play Anita voice
line okay wow and you know voice line
this one okay so here we have a
selection of voices from Ina and
I mean we could even get real enough to
read them out for us but hi
hi but I'm gonna play one I'm gonna play
the which one is it we'll hear it I
think Eno might not be able to hear it
I'm sorry enough but I'll play it now in
three two one
one day I will surprise you in your
heart will go even faster I'll play it
again I was too quiet
here one day I will surprise you in your
heart I'll go even faster did you hear
that guys so she said oh which one is
that I'm gonna do it one day I hear the
it's kind of in the middle uh one here
okay I'll impersonate uh Ena can you
like become a puppet you gotta be my
puppet okay
okay okay
one day I will surprise you and your
height will go even faster
doesn't sound like you at all oh yeah
wait Mom okay
your mouth yourself oh but you don't
even hear it
um just imagine three two one
one day I will surprise you and your
heart will go even faster how did you
know I'm gonna tell Cathy you know you
and I okay beautiful then one more one
more and that shows is this one if I can
add a little color to your life that
just makes me happy
[Music]
makes me happy
okay so that one was if I can add a
little color to your life that just
makes me happy
[Music]
you know you know you know
uh-huh I need you I need I need your
puppet mastering again all right three
two one if I can add a little color to
your life that just makes me happy
nice
I tried I tried yeah those ones I found
I thought were pretty cute all of them
were cute of course so you guys can
check them out in the game soon
now I'm not sure but what's the actual
actual time I'm not sure yeah and next
up
let's do one from me how about that Nina
oh okay okay
[Music]
um
these ones are on the right side the new
ones I think huh so in that shows too
don't take my oh okay okay I'm gonna
play the first one that she chose in
three two one
nice oh don't take my Senpai away from
me that oh yeah that the first one was
don't take my Senpai away from me
I'm gonna play one more time and then I
want to hear your impersonation
okay okay three two one don't take my
Senpai away from me
very angry yeah so Inna impersonate me
I'm gonna move my mouth from you okay
like three two one don't take my Senpai
away from me I'm sorry is
like
good job good job good job
okay okay and the second one was Donkey
Show it's just action you chose such a
short simple one
that's like different from your usual
talking she's like thank you thank you
it's longer
oh no no no no no no no yeah I guess
sometimes sometimes there's short ones
sometimes there's long ones this was a
well I would say I would say it's a
classic doncastron
Foundation you're wealthy I knew the
chat was gonna pick up and look at those
icons
okay time for this so those were some
new Chihuahua lines please look forward
to them and next Let's do let's do the
the laboratory ones oh they're written
down in Japanese but there's a there's
an inch one
but you didn't choose English one I did
not I challenged myself then they want
unlock the voices okay okay
so I'll go with the first one I play the
first one that you chose in three two
one
foreign
[Music]
the home too
um
I'm ready when you are it's like
[Laughter]
with my tongue
you ready
you can do it
be condescending okay
God don't laugh you gotta do it
seriously
it's like a boot camp
[Laughter]
[Applause]
what the [\h__\h] is that
[Music]
maybe you should pick it up as your new
way of talking to the takodachis just
call them
[Music]
okay we have another one the yeah the
second one is
awesome
I am
I didn't know she was like I see you she
makes food out of her viewers what just
like me we have something in common yeah
wow okay I'm gonna play it one more time
and then I want to hear your
impersonation
okay your turn okay
you actually nailed the first try and
you didn't come you did not no no
stumble this time move your words
good job good job and I want to hear one
more time down just just for a good
measure
hmm
oh me yeah Oh I thought you were playing
the awkward silence
okay yes
funny thing I actually had something
like stew before
um yeah stop recessing well I don't know
what's up one because you want to see
our faces right but you can only really
read it while one is Big I'm sorry I
keep on restarting it
I can't make up my mind fine we can they
can check it out again slowly I'm just
trying to be flexible you know anyway
and next up last but not least
[Music]
so
uh I think this this was it yeah
wow oh that was I chose a really long
one it's uh the the one above home one
okay okay one more time I'm gonna listen
one more time okay
pickle
pickle coloring sticky
let me speak of her one one time
she doesn't use her husky voice in this
one at all uh-huh it's like the it's
like it's like when she goes into like
the sun series mode and she's like yeah
the the calm you know cuckly yeah pickle
She's pretty like smoothing this one one
more time
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
thank you
well you know recently people have been
telling me how good my pick one
impression is because I took apart it's
definitely gotten better I think thank
you yeah because I practiced for for um
taking part in her like everyone becomes
a rabbit program figure yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay the next one is
[Music]
oh my God
it's the one below and I'll play it one
more time
foreign
[Music]
I think we can make an accepted and play
an extra one
right
yes okay let me find it um
pickola folder
uh it's the home four okay
okay let's hear Piccola English
three two one
[Music]
oh
I wish you heard that you know oh
you listen to it on the other side yeah
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
well hopefully she'll stay on Earth okay
uh at least that on Earth
[Music]
this one okay I'm gonna play it three
two one I like us but I also like this
[Laughter]
is so cute
I also like cookies
[Laughter]
she said
she's like at least she's honest man
she likes Earth okay she likes Earth
she like okay she's um she's a butt um
type of person
imagine just going really with lots of
confidence I like ass
[Laughter]
foreign
you're a butt type of person huh what do
you like so much about ass
[Laughter]
oh wait a second oh she says that ah she
says she likes Earth but she also likes
this world so the one that she's sitting
on is it really Earth or is it the
welcome no she likes Earth but we're in
the world the [\h__\h] connect right so
she's saying
which one is she sitting on though with
her ass
okay so she lines
yeah likes Earth
wait for us
maybe it's a big brain action from her
side
I
this is
beyond my yeah
[Laughter]
let's hear it one more time I love it so
much three two one I'd like us but I
also
I like glass but I also like this
let's go
you know like the little sister you kind
of like
yeah you know she is she is our cool
head yeah she's our lucky and she said I
love so much confidence how can I not
like
oh no cute so yeah anyway that was some
funnier than I thought it would be
um I didn't realize until you guys
pointed it out right you guys just get
your mind out of you you know out of
their asses
maybe I didn't want to say that yeah
don't worry about it finish the scent
just say it what has been said cannot be
undone at this point there's no way of
going back
well
um
I'm actually surprised this already is
on one hour stream oh wow um got it
that's perfect
okay start your wire on time and then we
turned into it a lot so beautiful
um so this is happening please check out
the QR codes guys and
um wait let me get rid of all these
things on the screen yeah and I do want
to say it though I don't know we talked
about how yes this current well going to
be current Awakening event for the
previous events characters which is but
there are preparations
underway oh for a second collaboration
yes which is coming after this event no
we don't actually know who's involved
though oh wait I don't know who could it
be secret who could it be
good
maybe probably gonna be like to Japan to
Ian again people can start you know
maybe making some wishes or you know
guesses with the hashtag Hello Kitty
connect maybe you know yeah
we'll see who is who's right then and
then and you can claim the title of a
fortune telling person I hope that one
meme pointing at the screen yes it was
me yeah I knew it all along
okay maybe like in maybe maybe as an
animal maybe as an enemy so we can kick
him
why because I somehow I will have to let
out my frustrations in some way or
another
right
and if I think young son would like
gladly you know for his talents
sacrificed himself like that like you
know he only wants the best for his
talents so you know what if like an evil
evil uh villain kidnaps yoga right and
then Yago gets cloned into these like
like mini juggles we gotta hunt them all
down oh bring yaggle back oh
well yeah why not
an army of tiny baby Yago babies can you
imagine like the you know like the it'll
almost be like a chibi red but then it
has the Yago head
oh
yeah big yellow maybe not I mean why
this is why I don't I don't make games
yes
okay okay okay guys
I think though that we have managed to
tell you guys everything necessary right
we have awakened to Cricket and um we
showed you the notch you know
has awoken and and now we also heard the
voices and you know that well there's
gonna be a second collaboration which I
think oh oops I stopped I stopped I
forgot to put blue puppy GM never mind
oh it's flipping again yeah
looks good no I mean did we forget
something let me check
okay when does everything we talked
about okay oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
wonderful links also in the description
by the way okay yeah check it out check
it out check it out I hope you guys
enjoy it nope
yep coming content yeah exciting look
forward to it and thank you Valkyrie
connect for sponsoring this dream once
again
um
can you can you give me an example
you sound exactly like yourself I don't
know where thank you
okay yeah you're trying well um tomorrow
guys there's gonna be a stream
um I'll be on no understand by this
channel I think yeah it's gonna be a no
air food
we're gonna play on her Channel if you
want to see me I'll be there where where
will you be in yeah
I am taking a break tomorrow all right
okay okay
okay I'm back the day after okay I
haven't exactly decided what though okay
oh I saw you starting at another game
but anyway let's not talk about that
song
and during
the day
wow
bye-bye thank you guys
[Music]
um
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]