foreign
[Applause]
bye bye
this movie
[Music]
[Applause]
what
was loud
your mama last night with me
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
oh yeah I guess you made it louder for
the castle I'm sorry
[Music]
do they make sounds like that I forgot
[Applause]
[Music]
where's my
where's my Christmas roll for now
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
cute right
underground opening or ending
if you're me I will I will
tell me
[Music]
[Applause]
I die
stop yourself
I don't know any mics
[Applause]
I only know
but I only know Michael
[Music]
[Applause]
what's your ETA what's your easy
um
[Music]
ah
okay
[Music]
uh okay
ah
iki
um
[Music]
you know
I'm I normally don't play in full screen
but I think I have to because the
highest resolution for Window mode is on
my 4k monitor
so tiny
and if I am not wrong then you can't
adjust it like in Minecraft like you
just make it whatever size you want more
games should be like Minecraft
although sometimes I'm like
having troubles to make it 16 to 9.
because of the freedom
that it gives you
maybe it's because that's the spread but
then I don't know it makes no sense if
you can make it full screen then why not
you know
I am
yes okay
hi yeah wait wait wait
it's on purpose
for now uh thanks for the memberships
are my super Chats on oh yeah they are
somebody sent her a pinky I saw that
but now everything looks so green I
thought maybe my super chats are off
um
uh I
I have a question
did I completely Miss Early Access or is
it still not available for you guys
that was so busy and already had my
games planned down and everything
tomorrow
all right let's go this is still early
access
foreign
12 more hours 50 more hours
I also didn't really spoil myself uh I
didn't want to see too much of what
everything looks like
besides the actual trailer so that I
could react to it on my own
um
okay in Japan it will be released I
guess in every country at midnight huh
in Japan it will be released in an hour
apparently
yeah yeah I am
uh it's been a while
you hear this don't you it's probably
loud isn't it
can I change it here actually
that's pretty loud
[Music]
I want to have my settings
uh are the same as before I don't know
if I even ever changed I I did didn't I
foreign
space that sounds like I did that
this is not the default setting right
straight draft
in German means um penalty
I changed it yeah to this no because
they also uh took my all my they should
be on
my character's right
these ones are new right
so I couldn't possibly have them right
yeah I am the save file got transferred
very nice very easy didn't even have to
do anything actually fascinating
nah I don't think I missed an updated
when was that update
when was that
[Music]
did I
did I not play it are you sure
maybe like on a different safe pile or
so
right
I did
no I didn't I I would never skip a whole
cure update I played it at the studio
yeah and I think I was gonna bring that
save file over wait did I took tomato
so I feel like I may have been smart
enough to uh upload it on my drive
uh what what would a hollow cure save
file be named as
uh
I'm pretty sure I did that
save then that
uh uh
see
um
[Music]
please
really
no I'm pretty sure I did I'm pretty sure
I did
um
[Music]
wait can you like actually Aya here safe
February 8th does that sound
about right it could also yeah no that
sounds about right not February 8th
what do I do with this though uh
wait let me download it and what do I do
with this
is
good job on remembering to do
that
and make a backup copy of this one
yeah okay let's close the game for a
moment this is important okay I don't
want to get all these five characters
again and it wasn't only that I think I
also got myself outfits and stuff
um
close the game yeah uh where would the
where would the game uh data currently
be
um
where would it be
an app data oh really like Minecraft
just like Minecraft
um
local
huh
copy this into this one thank you you're
the best
okay so I will put the safe and Dot
that's here on my desktop
and open downloads in a new window
and bring in that one in here so this
should be fine right be careful
that's fine it's on my desktop and the
other one the new one or the old one the
new old one
is now in the folder this should work
let's see
[Music]
wait
told ya I had it I don't miss a whole
cure update who do you think I am
getting so many achievements the first
time you open it on Steam you get like a
million achievements
yeah baby
technical genius okay now this one
wasn't so difficult but yeah we got we
got ID all of ID
as new characters which is so exciting
all of them at once man
so exciting and we got a house now and
oh my God where do I even start
can I even open my house yet
oh
well well rest at your customizable home
hang out and play a variety of mini
games and earn different Rewards
okay
foreign
what is bloop doing here I feel so bad
for bloop being forever
you know kicked out of gura's life
what do you have
oh wait I already have a rod ah okay
because you can then upgrade uh dad's
Rod blacksmiths Rod Atlanta and raw
turkey Rod
oh these are kind of I didn't know that
Kyla isn't into fishing that much but I
know uh Kelly is into fishing or Dana's
into fishing and well this is a
reference to gouda so what
do I get those
do they do this for me even if I buy the
rod are they the ones who are
who are fishing for me
what can I sell nothing add the fish aha
oh and then I can exchange the powder or
whatever that I get from him
oh fish yay thank you I
[Music]
am
I love you I mean I'm switching for me
there's some food here can I can I cook
oh tempura you need shrimp and wheat
that's so cute
for the next
next uses five for the next
try
you get these stats
Sushi steps two shrimps oh thank you
oh next five games
okay
[Music]
dude how far can I go
uh-huh okay
what about down here
building something
sorry pal sorry pal back on this round
is on the casino is still under
construction pickle and it probably
won't be done for some more moms why
don't you come back another time pickle
or the casino oh okay
so maybe I have to level up tuna thank
you Ama
and then here is there gonna be
something there too maybe it's for the
for the future future future
no
English English
pecora would maybe sound like that
is that what you've been doing all this
time playing hula cure
oh and garlic
can I talk to them oh wait I can plant
seeds but I don't have any
[Music]
I mean
uh and what now
no right oh I remember damn
okay what is this
worker list uh-huh can I hire but I need
money for it send out an advertisement
to get recruits
oh my God so many people arrived late at
night
uh should I do this
or do they come on their own too
[Music]
wait these names
where do these names come from
is it your player names guys
wait wait is it from what database does
this come you signed up
oh
that's nice
hi there 17 are you here right now you
better be here right now
and the stats are they random or are
they like um mascot specific
[Music]
there was a form on Twitter cool random
okay efficiency pretty low but don't
worry I love you anyway
yeah yeah it's all not that good
compared to the others
Cinda how many should I hire
this one has actually decent exp and
stamina
what does the HP matter though
Spain wait what's this
33 110 uh-huh what's up the efficiency
guys
a maximum of 10. read the read on the
left oh
[Music]
you read the notes written on the
bulletin board here you can recruit
volunteers looking for work these
workers will help you slowly make money
just as long as you keep them well fed
again I think my chickens let's go they
can feed themselves by just eating
themselves first you will have to pay an
initial cost to send the worker your way
then as long as they have the stamina
they will continue working by themselves
and generate Hollow coins for you
whoever you are here or not noise
workers are all different and each have
their own strengths and weaknesses
workers have oh rain
have the following stats stamina how
long a worker can work for before they
become exhausted
efficiency how many Hollow coins they
can gather at once
experience how quickly the water can
grow and improve
[Music]
okay max level the limit a worker can
grow to and what about HP
don't say anything about the experience
HP I mean HP HP
as your video workers not only do they
recover their stamina it wasn't it did I
imagine that
but they will also gain exp after
gaining a certain amount of exp a worker
will level up and increase their base
stats such as stamina and efficiency
okay
when your work is level up you yourself
will also learn to become a better
manager by gaining manager levels I'm
already the best man that there possibly
could be what it means at a higher
manager level you will be able to scout
stronger and stronger workers
but space is limited and you can only
have up to 10 workers at a time if the
space has become too small unfortunately
some workers may have to go you can
select the worker and ask them to retire
if you need space for other workers
so Caillou told me to try the retire
function for some reason that's the only
thing I've Been Told
these workers will save you a lot of
time and help you on your adventures so
be sure to raise a good team of workers
let's get the Mac wait it gets more and
more expensive
and I have two choices of chickens I are
cute
is one of them here Murph dog or the
mean Mafia is one of you here
then I would give you
uh the chance to get in
I don't see you
which one has better stats
actually this one
oh Sam
save monies for the Gaza okay just just
this one
I can make money
okay okay I'll get more in the future
um I'm gonna get those fishies
okay
uh hi Callie what's up don't rip my
chickens please don't even think about
it hi you guys how you doing how do I
feed them
[Music]
foreign
good job chickens
interacting oh I can interact
where did she go
also why is crony in there
in there manage
oh
feed wheat what day one specific things
I don't have weight you're gonna survive
right what if I don't they die
wait wait wait wait
uh
should I really feed them right now
they don't die
they just get exhausted and stop working
okay
wait tomato and wheat I need to make a
field
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
where I hear but the seeds I need seeds
where do I get the seeds from again
well where do you get them from
from you maybe
wooden bed
oh
what
oh my God I'm from Nemo okay that makes
sense
I'm gonna make my own a house room
somewhere
and then we'll give me the good stuff I
need
I need weeds I need tomato
for now
[Music]
okay
nice it's raining right now it's perfect
and why is it not here did I not just
buy it I need soil too
standard or
expedited or and wait I mean expedited
is just faster I guess and this one
means I get more probably out of it
okay standard
[Music]
oh wait
this is so cute
all right uh someone who's checking out
my chickens ah come foreign
[Music]
money from my chickens
yeah
don't steal don't steal
[Applause]
oh my God
oh more fishy
what's that how long does it take to
grow
the things
by the way tomorrow quite early in the
day
um
there will be a whole Tony stream
and
we are going to play Pummel party and
we're gonna do not five povs I suppose
but maybe I was hoping for at least two
povs
yeah because I mean there are some
differences in povs sometimes in the
mini games and I just want to
um
make sure
that the thing that we want to talk
about is hurt by everybody
[Laughter]
yeah
what was what what the was that a
swordfish or what
yeah maybe Ian and maybe Japan POV and
maybe Elena if she wants to do one
would be good
that's what I suggested yeah
um even though mostly it's similar but
thank you for reminding me about pommel
party I completely forgot about its
existence and whenever I heard its name
I just thought it was another one of
those games what are they called those
those games with the lanky
lanky and weird wobbly
characters that you push off a truck or
whatever Gang Beasts yeah yeah
okay let's play the game I guess
so the logo cute
uh oh build mode
but uh can't choose it yet I think okay
so quit the title
I can go try with that
no wait how anyway
wait probably here
no
no I don't want to yet um they just died
go to the house of build mode okay oh
the wheat is finished
noise oh and I need to buy it again
is this my house
oh can I zoom out this is so close
ah there you go oh
okay
ah
but I don't have anything
pretty sure I don't have anything Mata
that's so cool
okay
go behind us okay we'll go again but
first I want to play and get back into
it but ah ah let me try to get one of
the newbies
can I roll for ID as a whole or as a
generation
all right Generations okay
well then
uh one thousand okay wait wait wow okay
oh she looks pretty cute
[Music]
Lisa
the pose is so cute ah these are the 3D
poses anyway from the official Freddy
um like visual
I just realized that because they looked
familiar to me can we get you fear ah
I have enough money though I think
to possibly get everybody ah we always
do double whistle double Muna okay
come on come on
please put a famous last words
do I have to speak in German for her to
show up yeah
yeah
[Music]
yeah the German worked German always
works
nice okay
then
I want the second generation please
I love I love ID I want them all
y very very cute
and all me again Ollie really loves me a
little bit too much okay chill out only
[Music]
hey happy
yeah no no no no no okay thank you thank
God I love Uranus welcome welcome
welcome and anyone
stop being so clingy
I would like to have anyone now
oh my god what
hey you're wasting all my money only you
owe me money
oh no no no no no no
I kind of felt it you know I I knew I
knew she was gonna show up again what
the Molly why is so funny so
again
oh my God
oh what the the elusive Anya it
makes sense though because we only talk
to each other during
um birthday Collins
so there cannot possibly be Anya for me
understandable let me give a try oh my
God
no no no no
let me give these ones a try quickly
they don't have 3D yet so those poses
must be made up right they're cute
though
Ella
under my car
[Music]
I'm running out of money
if you don't show up you'll be grounded
for
one month
[Music]
um
last one Cobo please
[Music]
ah good okay okay now uh almost complete
I'm just missing Anya
Anya nice
it's okay we can make some money
I've never tried like a money build in
this game before but I heard Iris it's
really cracked at it right
hmm
Iris
verdina too Ah that's perfect I wanna
play new character
shoot people feather shoots a spread of
feathers in front and back okay
it charges up five punches press the
special attack again to perform a
massive punch
ah okay so you have to push it twice
that was
with the extra space for me
I feel good each punch deals 300 damage
and knocks whole coins out of targets ah
okay
five times
or Bam Bam Bam Bam
basically mugging okay
I love getting tons of fighting I got
some joked by then already plenty times
IRL
aren't you aren't you jealous the latter
okay
there's a delay but not that big okay
okay I I really don't remember how to
play guys
oh
ID States
but the recommended upgrades tell me
that I'm not ready for this
it doesn't say hard though like like
this one
I think it's hard okay let's just let's
just go back to our roots and see how
this works
uh
uh-huh oh yeah okay well
um
I don't know if it was extra or space
for me to
space what's up in the next was
something what was oh
yeah
[Music]
huh ah all right then oh wind magic is
that her other thing on crit's increase
haste by one percent up to 20
additionally there is a 20 chance to
cast wind blast as the closest Target
dealing 100 damage
her skill no need to strip okay extra
special space strip ah okay I think I
know what stripe was it's like when I
turn the other side but shoot the other
side or so right not that that's that's
useful sometimes
because I want to like run in a
different direction where then I am
shooting at for example
um anyway I don't know I guess I'll just
you know we'll go for both
uh sure
lifesteal oh
how much weight
uh once per second weapon attacks May
heal a random amount of up to five
percent okay cool cool
foreign ER
oh my God
it's making me happy
very happy but
I don't expect oh there it was the wind
magic I don't expect us to win this
first try
and aim for the greed stamp okay
delay taking damage on any hit by a
Target take only 30 of the damage
initially oh don't take the remaining I
don't know about that yeah
pick up range all right
the usual
but yeah there's already new stuff that
I'm seeing like the the Yago plushie was
new
oh the deadbeats are sturdy
you gotta get stronger
even though they're skeletons they're
sturdy
every 15 seconds gained one percent crit
ooh maximum 10 for each Target within
150 pixel targets outside of 150 pixel
get reduced to 10 percent for three
seconds should I go with this yeah
joineda
defensive wall that damages targets
behind you the effectiveness is
increased on certain characters
is it a flat character
hmm
Papyrus rapid tears of random targets ah
wait is this one new
calling calling calling coins
[Music]
um
uh oh what the is that
what the was that
yeah
what was that big uh
is that the the range that uh one of my
range things ah attention please
ah
[Music]
okay wait I should upgrade my
people feathers though should I not
after
[Applause]
that
nice done talk let's go
I want all of them
what's what has priority
that contact felt so good it's way
stronger than the tonjok she usually
does on me
yeah and I know I have more wait wait
wait
okay let's go um
[Music]
let them come closer before I do it
again though
oh what's this
huh do I have to destroy it oh Stars
what
back
okay uh
I'll go for this one
you shouldn't have done it twice in a
row but that's okay
[Applause]
no no definitely not that one
I don't know
should we do the limiter again maybe
one okay then we have a little bit more
uh Variety in our attacks
kill it kill it kill it the shrimp kill
me
perfect
[Music]
I can't Becky oh what is this lady of
the people when picking up holocorns
gain one royalty increasing crit damage
by one percent maximum 30 for each 40
seconds
oh okay
the duration recovers one second each
time or any picture okay
eight works well with our current
strategy of getting coins
I made myself a burger like three days
ago with Hollow beep
recipe
and then I had it's supposed to be for
two people the servings because there's
no one person serving
um hello beep I mean
um yeah but I was able to eat it for
three days I had self-made burgers for
three days really good actually it
turned out pretty good I added like a
salad though uh you know lettuce lettuce
as you guys like to say
um improve our wind magic or go for an
extra attack or even food with magic
okay hollow hollow fresh
and we should have a tie up man
yeah
yeah burger was uh just normal minced
meat Patty with some carrots you know
self-made of course yeah
where's my town joke when I need the
tonjok okay
and then a big slice of tomato I feel
like that's a must
and the lettuce
and some you know
condiments
I think that was pretty much it pretty
simple Burger
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
weapon hits have 10 chance to stun
enemies temporarily also has a 20 chance
to destroy any reports
yeah I mean right now we don't have
anything else so why not
mm-hmm
I want to use sound dog when there's
more people around but oh wait there's
so many boxes up here
wait what what
Stars though
[Music]
now is the time baby and another one
[Applause]
this Taco that she does not want to go
down
um
star special recharge Ah that's new
though right I'm pretty sure that wasn't
there before
foreign
I gotta walk all the way around holy
this is so many coins wow
not as good as the one that I made at
home
but you know it has to be enough it's
suffices
go for another lady of the people no
oh some people say for ah
okay
no
I know I know I know coins and all that
but oh here's my feather
this is the Phoenix but there's a typo a
big big typo here
maybe next time when Halloween shows up
to the five percent scare me five
percent increase of you know scares me
open okay thank you
Get Wrecked chickens
that's the first time I think that I got
all of you
at once my
ow I got stuck
that one's new I think maybe not I don't
know
um
not new oh okay
[Music]
foreign
for the first time since February I'm
not doing so bad am I
let's do another p-fal
oh you guys wanted the same knife okay
I'm not using strafe so far though it
doesn't feel like I needed it
to warm up yeah
on the hit there is a chance to spread
another curse towards another memory
Target oh
the encourse look new to me
maybe I am wrong
I hope you guys aren't sick yet of all
the hollow cure streams because this is
my first one okay
ah awaken give me some time to play
Hello cure too please at least I already
canceled the second actually this week I
wanted to do two Holocaust streams
originally
you'll never get sick of it you just
want to play it
there's only been about a dozen so far
I'll never get sick of it all right I'm
here for you thank you
oh sweet thank you guys
ah okay spider cooking is almost ready
we gotta find something to collaborate
with
very soon
oh nice
um
I don't quite remember what it collapsed
with
the bucket right
the lava bucket
eh Ian Curry is also collabs with okay
then I want to go for that one because I
don't think I ever saw that one before
we'll wait for the uh Ian curse
oh
I talked quite a bit with waynea
yesterday
about this and that
every wall hoping for
the
uh Ian curse Maybe
I never re-rolled it
hmm
pickup range pretty low
[Music]
the piggy bank
you want to go for this okay
at least one could be fine
not worth it
ah
still not what I want should we go for
limiter okay
I did it twice oopsie
I need the encourse
I am beautiful tone joke
and another one beautiful oh I should
have maybe kept it for the big boys
okay
[Music]
another piggy bank
or the tears the tears yeah okay what
does the tear what do the tears um
collab with
spider cooking oh okay
wait spider cooking is what I have right
now right so no more Ian Kirsten
not looking up for Ian curse
oh yeah bye oh yeah bye
getting stuck
let me out
hi wow that's a ton of golden ones
I have tons of no no no no no
um
yeah
thanks yeah go for the Food donation I
appreciate it
um
we need the collaboration ASAP
what was that
[Music]
shitty PC sticker let's go wait what
does this do again
20 chance to split targets by 50 until
40 weapon damage for five seconds
[Music]
I think
therefore I am
oh sheesh
tone joke
was it okay wait
oh
what what are these still from my
special from before
okay
foreign
that's interesting
should I have gone for the curse
sumima sorry I thought it's maybe better
to just max it out first there we go
what is this gonna be nothing foreign
Broken Dreams
the dream is dead and there is no hope
bubble Shield also slows targets aha
okay
so kind of uh like a protection for me
doesn't does it also do damage or is it
just protection and buff
it's raining endless tears okay I think
it does do damage
I'm sorry Yago
my fault oh it's bubuki time oh
yeah bye
bye
um
yeah I don't really have much good stuff
to upgrade
should I do the piggy bank
leave it I hope I'll find it again
one time job two-ton job three-ton junk
part-time job
correct
that's all I could do
fast thanks to the ton duck
good stuff that's a good sign if we can
take down fubodzilla fast that means
we're on a good track all right what
will be our
new weapon maybe that we're aiming for
two and four collabs oh yeah well I know
those would be nice to have a new one
though
little stick is there anything here that
also collapse with a new item
mmm
um
[Music]
low second whammy water I feel like I
know that one already though
I might have to unlock new items true
okay
whatever then anything is fine
but now we have the en curse what does
the encourse collab with besides the one
I already used up
for ILO song okay let's then let's do
the glow sticks with Idol song Try
lucky lucky lucky
okay wait let me get the handle
look at that
[Music]
um
nice
it seems like Hollow cure works like
riding a bicycle
bicycle
because I feel like I didn't even need
the warm up very nice
because I said because I sang two
seconds of bicycle bicycle
nah I've done way worse than that
increased damage of weapon by 50 and
could dance for five
should I replace one of these
I don't know
I want to ride my bicycle I want to ride
my bike
the place free
goodbye shitty PC oh wait
uh Swap and and then strengthen right
yes that's how it works
thank you
where's my mouse
I can't see my mouth
am I supposed to see my Ayah now I see
it
too much going on
um
by the way didn't I have
in the past some leg in this game only
sometimes though
what am I remembering is wrong
yeah right
so far no lag I did upgrade my PC so I
would expect that
and I also fixed a lot of it God damn it
then it's not even a real comparison
and
shackles
interesting
um
shackles yeah shackles seem very new
I know a game like this maybe doesn't
look like it would lag but I mean look
at all the things on the screen oh
chicken
cold stamp or I guess it's a turkey
maybe on the hit if the player does not
get attacked by the Target for four
seconds the target may become Frozen and
take 50 cold damage for three seconds
interesting
should I take this
a pack without reference
strengthen
swap the second one
[Music]
wouldn't mind trying a new one
I kind of need some food man
I don't recover anything right on my own
my mouth
where's my mouse oh there
I do
the choco stamp okay
[Music]
I might take this because that's scared
foreign
[Music]
I
keep on losing track of it I feel like I
didn't have this issue back in the day
do you guys also keep on losing track of
your mouse
hi Kelly
this is the money way hell yeah I just
wanted to try out a new character anyway
but yeah it's perfect though Elena is
the way do you know that way you play
with controller yeah okay
well well well if it isn't the
consequences of my own
choices
thank you
ah it's the only way to play for big
bugs if you don't choose Iris I suppose
yeah
seems like it the two
the two meta
players
um they're just negative expects of any
items placed into play oh
[Music]
wait that would mean that for example
the piggy bank I think had some negative
effect on me wouldn't have the negative
effect anymore
like the pickup range
oh interesting
if you Max it huh
oh yeah anyway it's just reduced by 53
no
no meaning
that where's my mouse
did my mouse cursor just change wasn't
it something else ah wait now it's back
interesting
ah
I don't know I wanted to bring it down
bring it down bring it down
ah no more than just okay
I'll be back I'll be back
Austrian will be back
everybody
[Laughter]
okay I'm coming for the Anvil
okay we have survived
ah well now that we are going to upgrade
those two into a collab
Crazy Frog
um what should be our next thing the Ian
curse
or four
[Music]
um
I'll go for the horn
so that we
make sure that we survive oh hello
no no no at the top at the top now at
the bottom how to aim this
I think they just got frozen by the
turkey
I keep on minting
I thought I knew how to do it
ah there we go beautiful beautiful Town
joke
[Music]
I mean I don't need that much
lifesteal
but hmm
should I just one more just one more
oh yeah because that didn't feel like a
triple we got a super body pillow
SSR gain a shield that absorbs up to 40
damage okay I am like indestructible now
every 15 seconds this Shield refreshes
also reduces damage taken uh by 15
percent
when Shield is full heel tended to be
everything okay
oh thank you
thank you
you know I've been thinking
um
like I think like a year ago or two
years ago I felt like I didn't want to
do it
because
I don't know maybe because it was too
soon and all that but I kind of want to
do a meme review
sounds fun
yeah
with guests
you know bring back the good old stuff
and then that would mean I I would have
to be active on the Reddit again
it's okay it doesn't hurt to add another
thing to my daily social media uh visits
I
like the stuff they put on Reddit but
it's just I I always
oh sure
I already I'm like you're literally
can't
um get me away from social media because
at least I have the argument that it's
my job you know
at least I can say that
God can we turn down the sounds
I'm going crazy
your choice was wise that content needs
too many internet searching and social
media if you're gonna do it at least be
consistent like cookies
hey you're talking to the Wawa who has
been doing Holo talk for three years now
the only reason why I sometimes don't do
it like in the past one year is because
I was uh
uh what should I do
is because
I was even traveling I was also sick a
lot of the time
and also I was purposefully trying to
space it out as well
because I thought you know I don't want
to run out of guests I could totally
speedrun it you know
but I don't want all the talk to also
like if it was weekly first of all I
would be done immediately and then also
it wouldn't be so special anymore I feel
by spacing it out
it keeps a little bit of its specialness
you know
but yeah I could I could do it regularly
if you guys like it
boom
[Music]
it's a sticker
and no no no no no no no no no no no no
there were sticker in existence
that twice
natural sticker you have to interview
someone every time have full talk meme
review no no no no no those are gonna be
two separate things
okay
yeah but I feel like you know enough
time has passed and
you know there's no reason to feel like
I can't do it because it's not my thing
right
I can do it right I I always had this
feeling like no it's not my project so I
shouldn't be doing it but you know
nobody else is doing it like I was
certain that after Senpai left somebody
would take over the main review and
that's why I you know I was so held back
if if if that would have like been
continued then cool but nobody nobody
continued it ever on a on a regular
basis so that's kind of a waste of
potential don't you think
yeah did a few yeah but well you used it
hasn't been continued
flower
when was the last time she did it
oh
she wants to do it again
she can do it again
of course doesn't have to be only one
person
no no
I thought my mouth was down here
tell me
you have a similar look of cocoa right
that's also like a thing you know we
have same hair color same eye color
I I just feel like we are
you know maybe it's meant to be you know
you know it might just be meant to be
she was much taller
[Music]
Size Doesn't Matter
better get out of here
can I just stand
does this work
oh we're almost done oh but then the
Boss shows up right yeah yeah yeah okay
okay get out of here where's my HP
oh
the the blue thing is The Shield huh
I know I know the
uh
um
but it still scares me being in the
middle of that it just scares the
out of me I don't want to be in the
middle of that
ah there we go
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm gonna don't kill me that's kind of
rude
oh don't touch achievement what don't
touch don't take any damage for five
minutes oh yeah and thanks to the shield
nice achievements
[Applause]
we gotta collect all those cards we
can't let them go to waste no no no
where's that man
where's my mouse
there we go
I am trying to figure out something
right here
uh
now there we go I I did something weird
[Laughter]
hey let me pick I want to pick up the
coins I want to go over her
um but I can't
and I'm scared of going over amen
situation does it like still pick up all
these unpicked up
points huh
I want those look at those purple wait
it's not coins it's 6p never mind no
oh well how much coins
eight thousand five hundred plus three
thousand three hundred
researchers oh Queen Senpai gain one exp
per two seconds
when HP is full the XP rate slowly
increases to two percent and it is reset
to one percent when taking damage
[Music]
I don't know about that one
but it is time
to go with twelve thousand back into the
character gotcha
uh we're missing Anya
come on Anya
no no no I said oh
[Music]
yeah yeah I could have pitted her oh
oh well
um
well
wait what about um outfits by the way
how do you get the outfits again
no we should get upgrades anyway what is
this
where are all the other upgrades huh
[Music]
okay
increase the damage of character main
weapons and special attacks by one
percent
for in-game level
um
not
[Music]
uh where's my opinion
it's too hot I need to turn on this
thing stronger stronger
no it's different than before you can't
blame me when the menu is different than
before
[Music]
yeah it's different thank you left click
changes aiming mode yeah that I uh
I messed around with that a lot yeah
what should we upgrade
[Music]
enhancement
money gain maybe money but do I need so
much more money now when I already have
all characters I mean
maybe so that I can upgrade all of this
huh
I guess
do
besides that I'll take
crit
buy stuff for the whole house
we'll just do we'll just do
um
well we gotta try out the other
characters I can't always do money
strats unfortunately
I'm gonna try
where they wrote underwater like that
because
ah
I wanna do Kobo fluffy areas slowing all
Targets by 75 and dealing constant
damage over 10 seconds during this time
Coco heals 5 per second and speed is
increased by 100 percent
[Music]
damn help me I'm underwater
scheme
should I try the new stage
let me get those upgrades first and then
maybe I'll try
oh
dad's umbrella is way bigger than she is
there you go okay this is how it should
be
okay
what are we gonna do for her first of
all the umbrella Ella Ella
foreign
I would just like to remind everybody I
wonder if everybody knows that that came
from
uh good as saying it a lot and me saying
it a lot because I thought gouda the
phrase
during our Japanese lessons yeah but I
don't think that the other members
really know why they're saying it
I think they just heard us using it and
then we're like oh okay this is cute
everybody seems to enjoy it when they
say it so let's say it too yeah
and Cali says it a lot too
yeah but the origin is me trying to
teach gura simple
simple Japanese
results
it's two years ago or so right yes a
long time ago
[Music]
um
give me credit
I mean
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no obviously no
need for credit but I wonder if they
know I don't think they know
like in the in the hollow ID Club so
many girls were saying it and I was like
thinking to myself hmm do they know
do they know
guy on the plane though he should have
given you credit hell yeah
what the I can't I cannot
understand
a voice mod
what if I actually just say that to them
like that
even bgm is on the water yeah
[Music]
I'll just take it
it belongs to Kubota
oh lots of coins down here
[Music]
I could make an M underwater uh video
um
[Music]
this is like Ace acid rain I think
holy because otherwise it shouldn't
be doing damage on these people
foreign
pillow okay we're playing very defensive
so far with these things I'm gonna do
closer lucky shackles but do I even have
the option to get what I need to
collaborate with something
[Music]
not yet it's not all okay
damn it I want some
collaboration weapons
man
[Music]
you know
tantrum
oh wait there's two different ones
when attacking one to answer should you
have both of these at the same time
maximum 10 and cola has a chance to heal
10 HP while creating An Extremely Loud
cry that deals 400 damage to all Targets
each chance from stack increases the
Chance by five percent
this is a pure sodaki
scale these two
they did good research but I mean it's
Kobo
gorillas cocoa
gorillas Paul
adopted
yeah
I could never be a kuso lucky some
people
seem to have been surprised at my
interaction with a bookable
um
because like she didn't think that I was
she didn't know I was streaming and
people were like oh they talk like this
off stream and um let me tell you yes
yes we very much do even in real life
she would call me Mommy
Chihuahua sometimes
and she's very clingy to me like we
would walk around with our arms locked
yeah we are we're very close yeah
um
yeah our elbows locked in each other
what should I do don't you
just continue with glow stick maybe um
okay can I was that a collab no right
wasn't it like the idol outfit
of the Idol song or so
song collapse of ax okay let's do that
one if I find it
yeah
so yeah and yes she talks like that yes
she screams like she's she has the same
personality in real life I can
100 confirm that
she also has like really really like
strong expressions in her face IRL is so
funny like man when I was getting lost
uh going to Cali's place even though I
should have known
how to get there
um
she she was not having it
because I led us into the wrong place
like three times the first time was
still okay the second time she was like
starting to
look angry but of course only jokingly
but still she's like
constantly like that it's really funny
and then the first time she was like
really angry and she like crouched down
on the ground and she was taking a video
of me
making fun of me man
I wish there was gorilla's paw hmm
man I don't know what I'm doing when I'm
choosing
let me just take this for now bigger
umbrella
yeah the Paw
but wait what was this collabing with
uh
yo
because I need a super collab but
gorilla paw and dragon fire
you need to grab idle costume
okay I'm confused as to what to get
as a Coco fan beam girl uh
statue was kind of shy the first time
you guys met oh yeah yeah but that I've
never seen her like that ever again
afterwards she was like William like
[Music]
boom
quiet couldn't look me in the eye and
that oh
oh my God how many times
the Ruffians should be getting used to
showing up here after the morning
good morning
hi thank you girls thank you doggos
hey what's up who Let The Dogs Out wow
wow
bow bow
um
is it is it worth it like stacking up on
a lot of tantrum and phrases
[Music]
what was today's misunderstanding I'm
curious
skills are almost always worth it okay
I don't have to do anything for those
right they just happen on their own
right
you have to activate anything my
um
[Music]
narissa misunderstanding from nerissa
mixed up two Foods as one also Risa
doesn't doesn't no
she knows 200 words but one thousand
countries ah they exposed her what
did they exposure or are they taking a
misunderstanding submissions now
she exposed herself she made a video
huh an apology video is that what what
that is
misunderstanding suppressions should I
take the gorilla's Pawn
[Music]
yeah oh my God I have to watch that
she's sorry she gushed about Naruto she
better be no just kidding
um
naked together oh yeah we have to ask
for naked together from narissa
[Music]
when in doubt upgrade your skills right
this is so good for collecting all the
EXP that is like scattered everywhere
I don't know
I got the idol costume guys I got it I
don't know if we'll get to use it I feel
like my choices of items in this run are
so all over the place I'm sorry am I
said really
for for the super cool app or what
let's go
trust the process
first
what what do I have to have the Isle
costume on level six two at O7 I suppose
for the after Max it right
baby
[Music]
it doesn't go to seven oh it matches at
five oh oh oh oh oh oh
free
and I've been talking
quite a bit too
behind the scenes
about this and that and trying to trying
to help them to
with whatever they need help with
basically
yeah
I still have the most interactions with
who is surprised
nobody
[Music]
would they share this code no they have
two
but usually usually they reply on mokoko
account
wait like on Twitter they put the
signature right of who wrote it
on Discord they don't so I'm not really
sure but I'm assuming that they write
the messages together I would think that
when mokuku sees a message
she'll be like hey look we got a message
from kiwawa and then they think of an
answer together it's what I would assume
but I'm not 100 sure
I think I think mokuko would at least
tell for
hello hello hello hello
YouTube
we're back okay hi
what was I saying Aya uh I I feel like
I would feel bad uh to just write to one
of them
because I also don't know if they
actually tell each other about the
messages but I I I I feel like I don't
want if I write to mokuko I don't want
Pua to think that I I prefer talking to
mokogo or anything like that
I'm certainly overthinking it but I I
don't want them to think that I like one
of them more or less
so I made a group
with both of them in so I just write to
both at the same time and then whoever
wants to reply
can reply to me but it's usually always
mokoko
it can't be a mission yeah I don't want
them to misunderstand you know that I am
maybe you know prefer to talk to one
over the other no no no no no
that is not the case
um
we're gonna collab those two right glow
stick and the Idol song
[Laughter]
yeah they don't really share it but they
still I think they still look at the
messages together I think because I
think they told me they can only be
logged in to one Discord account at a
time that's why it's just always one
answering me but they look at it
together I think
yeah
they can only be logged in yeah they
share a PC
hey share a PC
I wonder if they plan on ever getting
another one should I get the gorillas
paw now are we still doing this I don't
know I think we're doing a super cool
app with the idol stuff
so maybe I don't need it right now
once the paycheck comes in okay that
will take I think it's always like a
little bit delayed because YouTube sends
the money like I think two months
delayed
yeah yeah
so first they they would only get
like I don't know if if they maybe had a
sponsorship in the first month they
could be getting that though I don't
know I wait
Ed my mind's doing something
hmm no it's just a YouTube thing yeah it
takes some time
needs to be calculated and whatever
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah it's a lot of transactions and then
you know first it has to
be sent to the company and then to us
[Music]
hello
YouTube doesn't want me to Spill the
Beans
[Music]
YouTube don't be like that everybody
knows
we're already at 10 minutes what the
[Music]
do I want to be I was never on top of
fubodzilla before I think
oh my God this skill is actually op for
situations like this
oh my God
because I can like run around and pick
up the things that I need
all right all right I prefer to be under
football generally because that's what
I'm used to but okay okay okay yeah
[Applause]
what the
what's going on is it just me
or is it other streamers too
YouTube has a misunderstanding
but it always comes back really fast and
and I see it so I just pause but anyway
we just got the big collab so
what should we aim for now I mean we
already have the beginning of spider
cooking so
we could do something with spider cook
ah spider cookie
cookies because I haven't set one before
let's do that one
right
[Music]
I don't think I've seen that one before
tonight
I might reroll
you might have a problem
yeah honestly that might be the case or
Austria I don't know maybe our
me I mean you never know you never
really know is it YouTube is it my
internet provider but usually my
internet provider is pretty stable so
um who knows
it's okay we're always coming back fast
and strong
bottom right ah
wait I want to pick up all this stuff
I'm just doomed zoom zoom
[Music]
yeah cool special really interesting
underwater clouds what have you never
seen that before or what
oh another anvil
the other thing is an anvil too right oh
oh
okay
YouTube
oh but you didn't miss my oh wait it's
not it's not everybody
oh is it like you hear me but you don't
see me is it that type of
hello it just lagged this time okay my
nose
my nose is running this somebody can
somebody catch it
thank you
somebody please please catch my nose
but what do I do for a super collab do I
just wait
or do I still have to do something for
the super collab
I want Ian curse I want Ian curse
kunaina
God damn it
I need the golden Hammer yeah
if I just wait
um
what level 50
well level 50 is required are you sure
about that
[Music]
dodging successful
but I last run I finished with levels
50.
I don't know how far I'll get this time
oh my God there's so much exp everywhere
let me get everything
um
need glasses okay if I find them I'll
take them
thank you
Ice Ice Baby
setting the time on ice
if only I could really do that
oh okay
crit buff
hmm
Turn Back Time
[Music]
is not drinking that sucker
I tried uh
I think I tried like this New Year's
amazake like a sweet sake that you drink
uh at New Year's
before and yeah I don't like any kind of
alcohol so that was also not quite my
thing
[Music]
actually that's one thing I still wanted
to ask nerissa I realized this yesterday
that one one important question for our
compatibility
that I have yet to ask
how
how do you stand with where do you stand
with alcohol
I wonder if she mentioned this before on
stream
and I mean in the end it doesn't matter
um oh oh God I ran through a little
bit too much
yeah
I'll be careful I'll be careful
she likes that oh she probably does
doesn't she
no no not rip
I'll ask her privately she drinks
lightly she said that oh
as long as she's not a drunkard
ah wait my ice cream is fine
or not I don't know is it really yeah
it's fine it's fine
dodging
[Applause]
heal yourself
may I thank you
level 39.
nah
nah no no no no no no this one oh it's
already Max ah Anita iyankers
yeah bye
yeah so here's our Max what should I oh
nice food what should I tie up the tears
with
[Music]
oh oh
does that work together
wait did we have this already
I guess we're doing that
yeah we already had that last time I had
no choice I had no choice
um
and still no no glasses either
she's fine she's fine
now just level 50 for the hammer
yeah I'm waiting for it
um
the X okay and
the Lala bucket hmm
HP Toto ah
the shackles are here
Oh no just um
I don't know if I can get it
in time but
we can give it a try what's been going
on recently that I can tangent about uh
I've been going swimming again
swim swim
very proud but you know I can I kind of
want to find someone to teach me the
other swimming Styles because I can only
do like the most basic one
I can't do the one where you move one
arm in a circle and then the other arm
in a circle
I can only do the super basic one and I
feel like you know I hope that any
swimming style is efficient yeah the
crest that's strong I don't know
the most basic one when you put your
both of your hands in front of you and
then
in a circle motion
kind of get rid of the water in front of
you
you know what I mean
frog style is that frog Style
yeah but I want to learn the the other
one the one that professional swimmers
do you know well I guess where you have
your face on the side and then the other
side and then you switch again
um
yeah I I I I don't know I don't wanna
like attempt it on my own because I
don't know what I'm doing
shouldn't should have gone to the
swimming lessons more often and not
always say that I'm on a period
this is such a girl's thing guys it's
not just me every girl does this
sometimes you may really be on your
periods sometimes you're really not
but honestly you can't come I mean you I
guess you could but
you know then you need the well you know
I'm not gonna get into detail but
it's definitely a valid excuse to not go
swimming
how can they confirm well that's the
thing they don't of course thank God
it would be very very wrong of them to
confirm
yeah but even when I went to swimming
lessons like swimming like sometimes in
junior high school in high school they
didn't even make us go swimming I think
because they knew that we all didn't
want to
um but in junior high school they would
often replace
the uh
the sports class with swimming
which in hindsight I think it's a nice
thing to do but for some reason children
are so against it
I don't know why
[Music]
did you school have a pool no we didn't
like none of my none of the schools in
Austria have a school a pool usually
um
anyway what was I saying
oh yeah so it would usually get replaced
by swimming sometimes in especially in
summer times even though we would always
do it indoor
but somehow they thought in summertime
we want to go swimming
and
they would like kind of split us into
good swimmers like no just like honestly
not even good swimmers they would just
split us into anybody who's capable of
not drowning underwater
but I think I always like I I could hold
myself over water but I just still felt
like really
embarrassed about my swimming skills I
also because I just I just wasn't good
at it and I think
jumping I was also scared of jumping and
I don't know I was just scared of the
whole
thing
so I would always be
often often be in the in the kitty pool
so ridiculous actually now that I think
of it it's really ridiculous it's quite
ridiculous yeah
oh yeah bye
and we were just doing whatever while
it's end of the class
was doing
uh like proper stuff like they would
swim laps they would do some I don't
know whatever challenges on the water
yeah
and I don't know I felt quite stupid but
still
did they give you floaties no no
floaties oh we're at 20 minutes
[Music]
oh sticker
hit hello coins
doesn't really matter now
[Music]
breastplate is this new
go higher stage for more EXP
ensive all right
foreign
[Music]
with my love
take you down with my love
take this
yes
maybe we can get to 50. in the last
second I'm just not gonna hit I'm in I'm
just kidding okay not worth it
I feel 49. amen
[Music]
so close
I had that before I think I'm pretty
sure
clear stage in time mode defeat boss of
stage three heart stage two heart stage
one hard
feet stage between the boss of stage
four
yeah no I don't have everything unlocked
Apparently one million coins
no wait wait let me what do you get
there's a sausage for defeating the boss
of stage four
stage four that sounds really difficult
and then there's a oh
the get well soon pills or whatever I
think I don't know
be defeated while using Halu oh I just
have to die
while using Hollow
I should do that
to get the pill new item
and then
[Music]
wait what is this what is this some
glasses
enhance a weapon what I've enhance
weapons a lot no
I didn't recognize it to me it looked
like the
a certain character from a certain
gacha's uh ribbon
eh why have I not unlocked this
ah Beyond maximum ah
okay
so we have to die and we have to upgrade
something to Beyond maximum we have to
die while using a hollow
oh
but some of these are pretty easy
oh clear stage mode without having any
character skills
[Music]
like no attack items too
banana bats a bad Beetle not battle
[Music]
like nothing
hmm
no just no skills like like
ah like kobus tantrum oh okay okay
we can do that I want to do that too
choose the hey set up option 10 times
when leveling up
oh hey
set up option
okay should we aim for one of these
maybe we do the the Halo one first okay
let's aim for them okay let's start with
uh who's the most famous for Halloween
who do you think of when thinking of
Halu
[Music]
Kyla I thought so too Ollie okay Olly
okay
[Applause]
I want to die anyway so it really
doesn't matter I just need Halo at any
level right
okay
and then die purposefully
with Ollie I mean she's a zombie she
won't mind that I sacrifice her right
right
get The Cutting Board
I could
I'm very well could
[Music]
simple fall time targets can drop her
life merch when picking up her life
merch Ollie takes 5 damage but he'll
back the damage after 2 seconds and gain
40 percent haste and speed for 8 Seconds
but can we find Halu
Halu no hallu oh grab a shark while
moving if only stops moving for One
Second Spin all the chakra to cast a
one-time strength to the bass on the
accumulated okay
FHP raises zero all it gains Undead and
cannot die for 10 seconds
however each time this activates Ollie
loses 50 maximum HP
for one minute
oh
anyway
for now
let's go this WOW thing
I think that what is that
what is that currency doesn't I forgot
what that was it doesn't look so
familiar to me
[Music]
that's a strong survive yeah
eh there wasn't a router reference
a rupees
oh so you come from the land of Zelda
just kidding sorry I had to make that
joke
I had to make that drove
[Applause]
oh
cute and what does it do increase damage
of the main weapon by 20 a decrease and
increase the speed okay
[Music]
[Applause]
that was her um yeah the charge rifle
uh every all the fans are basically
getting beat on
[Music]
wonderful
I I I am sorry to break it to you but
that's what she really meant
uh where is that hello hello
I don't care what we're taking it really
doesn't matter because we're here to die
[Music]
laughs
you
oh
I'm sorry to tell you
sorry to break it there
[Music]
[Laughter]
don't die before upgrading pasta oh wait
it has to be level seven
I missed that
oh he's still alive what the
should have been drowned by now
[Music]
[Laughter]
cutting board create a defensive
okay sure
Ollie is proud of her cutting board I
think very proud
as she should be
um
I don't want this because I don't want
to survive
um
I'll just I don't know
if she isn't she hates it what
[Music]
I mean okay yeah she did give herself
some assets sometimes but
shouldn't
Go With It Ollie go with it
I don't want to die so early I have
stuff to do
goodbye
[Music]
a nice thanks for the food
Uber sheep delivery there's so much
merch here oh my God
wait let me read this again okay
sounds cool
ah if I stop moving it it shoots it what
oh
whoa
okay
nice
um
oh awakens
[Music]
I don't know what to shoot
wasn't this a thing that we should be
doing
for an achievement
10 right
okay maybe we can do two achievements
then
foreign
[Music]
okay
hello
is scary to me I never used it before
and I think
whoa wait that's cool how did I
not pick up the merch just now
there you go
oh
[Music]
huh
oh ah fire water Earth
[Music]
and then Thunder that hits like everyone
on the screen basically
cool
my HP is really low
[Music]
seven is what we need right here
nice
so
oh let's go
gotta keep an eye on the on the charges
if we just get quickly to hollow seven
then I don't have to worry about
anything anymore and just die oh my God
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my
[Music]
God
oh yeah
maximum five
right right oh
no it says don't do it but yet I can die
now right I'm allowed to die I'm allowed
to die okay
and
I got an achievement
what I mean I was gonna die anyway
probably
was that the right achievement though
yes yes this is what I wanted yeah yeah
yeah yeah the the the haste one I need
to get up to seven but you know one by
one while the special meter is still
charging increased quit by 15 percent
huh
oh 15 wow
all right uh Hey Tim you need to upgrade
weapon plus one
um wait let me look what we want to do
no
oh wait this is also one reach 10
minutes with cutting board or related
weapons using certain characters
related
using certain so I'm guessing use
cutting board on like Ollie for example
and survive for 10 minutes
flat weapons flat characters
okay let's do that one
now how about Anya then
she's also flat no wait wait no she's
not that flat
she's she looks flat but she's not that
flat actually uh wait who else is flat
but well when he played no wait Cooper
is also not flat
yeah no no ah ideas generally mostly not
flat what the it it's already only
flat ID member
I'm looking at ID members only right now
because I want to play new characters
you didn't really play Ollie anyway okay
we can give her another chance
but we only need to sell by survive 10
minutes again oh
[Music]
um
stage four I'm not gonna survive 10
minutes in stage four
[Music]
we can try
the hollow office Maybe
[Music]
no I'm not okay
oh my God I I hate this you get stuck so
I no you get stuck so often in this one
10 minutes surviving 10 minutes here is
like surviving 20 minutes in the other
one
okay we need cutting board but this time
we can also take the Undead One
to Keep Us Alive if we want to
um
and maybe maybe haste
see already getting stuck
I'll try my best gambarua
but at least we have a music change here
oh yeah watch TV for some money
what do I just have to stand in range or
stand in front of it
I can't I can't stay in front of it
just in range
10 seconds wait I'm gonna die yeah
[Music]
I can't play Ollie
well will I get will I get 100 uh
Undead if I am on zero or is that was
that a possibility
is this again
attack size okay
uh
yeah okay
[Music]
oh there was food there yeah
we need a yeah we do need a I mean this
kind of heals me
after two seconds
hey oh did that was there haste I didn't
recognize that
[Music]
okay okay okay
should I double my healing
[Music]
um
he wobble on the Telly what's that
any food here man
[Music]
nice nice
that keeps them away from me a little
bit
I think I'm I'm in a range of the TV for
a while already
ah
did we already do that no we didn't
right use cutting boards
hmm
[Music]
ah come on wait
Ash
give me a better stab give me something
better
and funder incoming now wonderful
good safe good safe
did cutting board have to be maximum
level
stay alive no just staying alive after
10 minutes after I get it
um
okay
I don't know maybe
yeah
well we just have to reach a 10 minute
Mark I'm not sure about that but yeah
we'll see
we'll see I don't think that dying will
be my choice this time
[Music]
I think someone will decide from you
that I will die
uh
thank God that came just in time
I wasn't sure if it was gonna be there
in time hey I was waiting for it I was
looking at the bar clutch Thunder mama
if HP register let me read this again uh
Ali games Undead and cannot die for 10
seconds however each time this activates
all he loses 50 Max HP
one minute
I don't want this
no I don't want this anymore
super good you think so
I'm better than dying I I guess
so after the 10 seconds
I lose the 50 for one minute
and
two percent attack for every two Max HP
that I'll lose
[Music]
get Frito okay
yeah
foreign
[Music]
yeah I know I get it back I know but
um
okay I'm doing doing okay right now but
I feel like they're gonna Corner me
again
laughs
I think I have good decent control over
it now first I got this weapon it's
marked
I'm talking about
[Music]
your skills are very interesting
froze the sword what
[Music]
oh sheesh
I hope that doesn't hit me accidentally
[Music]
oh really I was thinking about it too
more survival chances
troll stems
well okay I can at least strengthen the
other ones
ah wait I have my charge rifle ready
[Music]
and the last hit wasn't even necessary
right it was already dead before that
and curse
uh all right
what do we want to improve
maybe the
um one four four
Chris and cutting board oh okay is that
a collab oh
I actually want to see that but that
means we have to stay alive for that uh
good luck to me
I want to see the collaboration I don't
mind dying after 10 minutes you know
oh my God we're only at four and a half
what
is honestly so helpful and when I
upgrade it doesn't charge faster
I'm not sure anymore
hi nerissa hi
yeah it just gets stronger okay I wish
it would charge faster but isn't there
like another item that makes you charge
specials faster
wasn't it the the pill that I just got
maybe
[Music]
say at the idol costume oh
okay okay okay okay okay okay
doing well
oh she said Ian curse and cutting board
is her favorite collab really I haven't
seen it yet
oh
then I hope I will get to see it before
my life is over
nice see I love this
Rissa did you play with Ollie before
because I love the Ninjutsu like first I
was struggling with Ollie but I felt
like I I got the hang of it roughly now
you did last night nice nah
I know four
okay
Let's get high level let's get strong
give me that
you mean all that merch
uh ah it was the stones it was
almost the Thunder or she
[Music]
the Rocks I mean the rocks are fine too
honestly I have never seen the water yet
though
uh I wonder if the water is good
how do you feel about Naruto now
difference
no difference yet
oh oh yeah
okay that was a good survive
six and a half minutes okay okay okay
okay
I believe
um
yet
um yeah
go I'll just go for two
[Music]
milk helps me
stay alive in some way
did you see Ollie posted on her Twitter
that like a signature
thing
that she got from everybody she asked
that like almost everybody I think that
she met for signatures
one of them is mine and I wrote her
little message on there too
you know how I said that finally I have
someone like Risa in the whole life and
a lot of people were like what about
Ollie what about Olean and yeah you know
I I love people like Ollie who spread so
much positive energy in her whole life
and and just appreciate shows the
appreciation for everybody I love that
but you know
Melissa's love is very specific to me so
that's
a bit more special to me
but I am very very happy that Ollie is
in her life without her
things would be a lot more dull
oh wait what was that
um
with this game I'm having a hard time to
look at the chat at the right time
true true
I just love it when members show
appreciation for each other more and
more
and honestly on that uh
on that topic I'm
she said
I'm very happy that uh Advent
is bringing or like kind of like
encouraging
the rating
right now
in how long Ian
because up until now I don't think the
members in Ian really thought much about
raiding
foreign
[Music]
you know I personally I've rated a few
times but I I don't really ever get
rated myself so you know I I felt like I
want to rate people back who raid me
just to know why if I always read and
nobody reads me that's just a little bit
sad
um
but now
thankfully streams at a time where they
can read me
wait is
I won't die
diamonds
I don't wanna die though I don't wanna
die though
[Music]
oh
uh what was I saying oh yeah so I didn't
appreciate them uh kind of encouraging
this by very actively happily doing it
and I don't know if the other en members
are joining in but I'm definitely
joining in the the rating hype so when I
can rate
or anybody else back I'll happily do it
and I hope we can continue this because
I think it's just wholesome to support
each other uh you know we need a strong
branch and a way to make the strong this
Branch stronger is by sharing the love
and you know
support each other I think we need more
of that uh going forward
yeah yeah bye bye
ago I don't need you right now don't
don't distract me I'll go
my thoughts exactly
um
[Music]
it's our part of twitch culture yeah
um maybe like in the beginning maybe
that's why there were some
uncertain feelings but as long as it's
like within the branch like or within
whole life like why why there's nothing
nothing bad about it
it's fun
yeah nice
oh my God I'm almost at 10 minutes if I
die now I'm going to freaking lose it
and I really hope it's just a 10 minute
Mark not 10 minutes after I get the
cutting board
but I'll try to get as far as I can this
time
beautiful beautiful
We Got The Cutting Board mask now that
should help us do and I got oh I
crazy achievement what is this
goodbye
[Music]
this is not the the boss achievement
that I want though right wait does this
one end in 10 minutes wait wait wait
wasn't there like a thing that I found
out before that this actually ends at 10
minutes
after I kill the boss
is this the oh
oh god oh god wow
I made it
[Applause]
tonight
I think I need the Uber ship now
change two more minutes
for
you mean the achievement is it
really is it really like 10 minutes
after I get it um
pretty HP let's go oh God no this is
very slow
yeah
did I get it was that it okay
just go for full clear I'll try but
oopsy I will I will need more food I
think
oh
um
hardcore mode on yeah uh for one minute
[Music]
guys currently
um my album
uh Creations schedule is getting pretty
blank scuffed it's out of my hands now I
did what I could
I hope it'll make it in time it's making
me a little bit nervous you know
collab yeah wait wait first this one
um
or should I re-roll maybe
two
okay yeah because
it's looking a little bit dangerous in
terms of
schedule but I hope we can make it we
should be able to make it on time
all right
oh
ah the bone Bros
wait have I really not seen this before
don't buy the hand of feedback this
sounds very familiar I feel like I've
seen it before maybe unless the Ian
Chris is really new then I couldn't have
but I now I feel like I did
yeah I know it's Delirious from Q
um
[Music]
[Applause]
take this bastards
um
should I upgrade to Undead
the Thunder feels so good
[Music]
okay wait how and what way does it
improve does it is the timer maybe less
the one minute timer
okay food thank you thank you thank you
thank you
decreased damage
[Music]
are they already all upgraded no
you got this you think so
[Laughter]
[Music]
77 HP okay oh that was a lot of uh exp
over here
hmm
um maybe sipping some more would be good
or not
song and axes new collab is it
but I already have wait does the bucket
and the ax collapse too right so I think
I'll just go with those
and maybe another time we try for the
song and the ax
yo okay okay at least these low Bob weak
mobs I can almost walk through
so I'm feeling very comfortable right
now this phase could continue endlessly
in my opinion but no there's some new
Mobs coming
um
wasn't I supposed to strengthen
something uh yeah okay but I'll do that
next time
I just realized yeah my my whatever
you're supposed to strengthen something
for an achievement right
the main weapon
10 seconds on TV I already did that oh
but I don't know if I noticed an
achievement popping up
oh thank God for all the food
um
[Applause]
nice
collected all of it
this Ollie is killing it she's strong
you have to spend 10 seconds on the
Block yeah okay even the reward is
pretty low though I I don't know if it's
worth it right now
let me pour some water
yeah I keep on hoping to not die I know
I I forget that we have a a rescue but
even that I don't want to be on half HP
for one minute
um
I don't want to
I think it might beat the stage so far
so good see so I don't want to risk it
I think I beat though have I have I beat
them beat them I guess not
at the achievement right
um okay
[Music]
10 chance to cause an explosion
wait
maybe swap it instead
should I swap it
you beat this and look I did
oh because I unlocked stage three oh
okay hmm
but do I have the boss achievement
swap with potatoes
okay
what are those
mascots
one of those
photos
yummy really
they look like this
[Music]
everybody shall we dance
okay I'm good I'm good I got stuck a
little bit but even if I would have died
I wouldn't have died you know
just zombie things
oh
I can do it is it 20 minutes again
[Laughter]
I'm still scared it's normal
[Music]
who's our who's our those who's mascots
they look like uh like a wisu
a witsu author a mix between urisu and
an author
it's asuki's oh my God
it's weird I've never seen them before I
think I don't know
and I don't look familiar to me in this
setting
I've got my eyes on you
just recently I got another cheap ones
with hamburger achievement
which one is that
boys
it is a beaver we have not Google Maps
indicator cute
why recently did she not have a mascot
until recently
or did she just
feel like upgrading it
eat 50 hamburgers in game ah
[Music]
Queen's damage right five percent for
each one empty uh well that's not gonna
happen
wow wow
I am destroying this office
we can't use this office anymore
afterwards
I was heavily nerfed all
hey John I'm so sorry it's um for
destroying your workplace
should we upgrade this again
for everyone Max
[Music]
um
it went down from two to one I think
oh okay no we're good
oh they did not even die from that but
they did get a good stun
mama
okay making the way clear
for me
okay okay give me the food
and I guess I mean
what are we gonna do next I don't know
if we can even
get another
going but I guess we're doing uh boys
well
[Music]
water okay
I'll keep my eye out open for it yes
yes
why are they going in an opposite
direction anyway those people
is here
it's Bible love
yeah
we can collaborate it
foreign
[Music]
place
you're over 50 minutes yes 16
Mark is good though we're placed two
replaced for you
now you have good stamps
okay I'll just upgrade
no all fun
oh my God
oh my God almost done but I feel like
we're gonna die right before
oh my God
17 minutes
Tech area and one book
let's add a book
and destruction
[Music]
okay okay now we're pretty good we're
pretty good we're pretty good we're
pretty good
[Music]
okay
um
Ollie has too much power
baby
oh
wow
why did I suddenly take so much damage
from right after I healed myself what
the oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God
I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead
hey what's
this what's this what's this what's the
sound
what's up huh
I need to care Oh no oh
I
it's been too long for me to remember
this uh
how much time do I still have to kill it
Audrey
okay uh
40 seconds I have time okay
18 HP in a dream
oh man
I'm hmm even considering another Uber
sheep
I want to be spammed with food at this
point but yeah
okay let's kill it oh oh there's the
count
die
okay okay okay okay it died
[Music]
oh my God please end it one and a half
minutes but then I still have to kill a
boss and I don't remember the boss
huh
I need to upgrade this right
oh my God
I hope my father is ready soon but no no
because
we got Brutus easily
[Music]
um
no no no okay with this with these
offerings I'm gonna
go for another Uber sheep yeah
it's nothing for my attacks
oh
again okay
[Music]
we may need it we may really need it oh
God
we may really need it
oh God
oh God oh God oh God oh God
yo but oh God how do I
yeah I'm gonna Undead for a moment
probably
foreign
[Music]
no I'm not quite dead that's the 14 HP
toys
they despawn right at 20 minutes
um
okay hell
oh no I'm not I'm not gonna I'm not
gonna survive this I'm not gonna survive
this I'm not gonna no
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
close enough
more seconds
I tried to get to the food and I did but
at at half HP
at half maximum HP there's only so much
you can do
but we got a ninja headband increased
speed by 20 in addition increased damage
of melee weapons by five percent we got
the bounce ball that I wanted drops of
falling bounce ball on a random Target
what this is referencing is this
referencing our official stream where we
were playing with the ball or what it's
an only item
bling bling
oh
size of ball varies but ah
and the blacksmos gear normal and what
what was this one for normal animals can
be used twice
only applies to Ann Wilson's taking this
items oh interesting
[Music]
ah for enhancing ah
so
we need to defeated stage four boss
I don't care about all the money things
that much they should just happen
they should just happen on their own
drop a super item clear station hardcore
get a weapon to 10 plus 10.
Bill enhancements five times in one run
fail a plus one plus two enhancing clear
Hollow with level clear whip Hollow
level five
survive 30 minutes with Hollow level 5.
leave a boss live for
five minutes or more
leave up a level of five times in a row
one second complete the Army watch the
credits get 100 crit chance and single
runs
one million plus score a similar one
watch TV for ten I guess I didn't do it
you have to stay on the carpet huh
annoying another member
that's a shiny fish cook at this
10 combos with the combos because
there's one of every kind of fish
manager retire worker
collect 100 000 Holo coins from workers
at once you can huh
what does that mean
clear stages no items use the golden
Hammer
and I was really close to doing that
[Music]
um
damn it
I don't know yet
ah
[Music]
okay clear stage mode without having any
character skills we could try this one
and maybe if we find the haste now but
that is the does this conflict with each
other
no right it's
I could do both if I find haste stat up
okay so no character skills and haste
stats
okay
maybe let's go to Hulu house
once
oh I wanted to annoy her can I annoy her
if I talk to her really often Carrie
okay
uh feet
confirm aha
okay
wait
I don't understand
did I just feed him the wrong thing
I understand
with tomato
I only had one
beat a tuna
wonderful
and then feed a clown fish
[Music]
okay
so now nobody's exhausted anymore right
uh
hi Muna can you help me no wait you're
standing in the way Moana
let me buy
some more how about
[Music]
I got some no just a normal one is fine
let's get ten and then we'd sing tomato
scene
for now that's okay
okay
[Music]
a farming simulator
I never thought they would go for
something like this
like this feature they definitely don't
have in the original vampire survivors
right
can we grow Muna I want to plant Muna
[Music]
right so this is like purely original
so nice I'm out of wait let me get one
more thing maybe another tomato or so
and we have again someone exhausted what
uh
[Music]
maybe maybe it's time to retire them
whoever this is whoever is exhausted and
may be your unlucky day ah Murph dog
Murph dog
foreign
I'm so sorry but I was told to try this
[Music]
send away to the usual room
does it say this only for my chicken so
it doesn't say this for any worker
no matter if you have chickens
oh my God some people may not understand
what that means some Japanese members
may not understand
[Music]
I'm so sad I need to hire someone right
away
waffle the man you're the man get in
here if you when you had to sign up for
this did you
get to choose which fandom you want to
be
so can I be sure that these people
signed up to be kfp yeah okay cool
waffle the man what do you what do you
usually eat tell me tell me potatoes
I
I just ah oopsie I on full screened
there you go it's fixed now
interesting hey a
oh my God that's so weird
I can't press this Escape
every time I do this to get out of the
menu
It On full screens me
is this a bug
might be a bug oh my God I found
the bag I feel like I need an
achievement for that
ah wait now it doesn't go back anymore
usually it always went back
[Music]
I can't see my mouse anymore in the game
ah ah wait
[Music]
ah okay
I think
maybe it's not a bug
but I have to get some potatoes now God
damn it um
[Music]
well now I have to wait for the other
thing to be ready though before I can
plant that why is nobody fishing
you guys should be fishing for me
how to cook
I can't cook any of this oh wait oh
burka and Fries Buena was here what the
hell
oh I missed winner
I can fish too how
ah oh
how's it work
what do I press
oh God it's a river oh no oh
wait what
what
how it was a shiny
the Opera and what's the what's the
middle one though what's up what the
am I supposed supposed to press for
the circle
ah my shiny they need to have a tutorial
click okay
[Music]
that's not my fault man I didn't know
how to play it yet
[Music]
uh I want my
I want my shiny
[Music]
how rare are shiny fish good question
I would like to know that too
incredibly oh come on my first ever
try this is like me with my first
trident
but that one I ended up getting hmm
I'm gonna we gotta get some more
potatoes
oh my God I'm using up all my money for
this why am I doing those
don't forget to collect uh the fishy you
mean the shrimp come on give me another
shiny
[Music]
I'll never get a shiny ever again this
is like in Pokemon
okay at least now I know how to do it oh
that's a tuna ooh
[Music]
mushroom
did it disappear
what happened to my shrimp
can I do I have potatoes yet no not yet
not quite almost
[Music]
um but I can I can feed
you
[Music]
now I got plenty of tomatoes damn this
is a lot of work to keep you guys alive
exhausted weeds
there's a golden koi fish referencing
the Magic Cup really
[Music]
let me take a look at that
thank you Candy fish Chinese too
no potatoes yet I mean I wanted to go
behind the house like you guys did
[Music]
you little shits
what why
yo what are you doing back there are you
infiltrating kfp is it always Taco
that's yes
[Music]
that's for the fourth one we don't talk
about it
they're always like this if it's tackle
that juice for everybody
I feel like it makes the most sense for
me because we always have the the taco
that you spies so it makes a lot of
sense that the taco dutches are behind
my office
secretly hiding
I've got my own lore with them so
that you know is probably not even 100
aware of
potatoes
I'm waiting for you potatoes
oh wait let me collect actually
oh one thousand coins
manager level one still
I mean let me try again here
[Laughter]
once I mess it up once I'm just
completely lost
I
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
let's go back yeah
[Music]
clownfish
nice thank you
nice
do I have to water the plants don't they
get watered on their own oh yes
potato we can now find ah
there's another one
finally feed
that potato chicken
oh
do they have anything to plant right now
I don't think I do
no
[Music]
okay now we have plenty hey could I feed
them something else too
and it's just what they like the most
what would be like the most efficient or
so
potato
potato has fully grown oh my God I'm so
proud of my potato
Es are very versatile
nope only what they want oh
okay potatoes
[Music]
[Laughter]
am I annoying her yet there we go
but you know I love you I'm sorry will
she will she forgive me someday
is
[Music]
shrimp potato I want to hire another one
but I don't have enough money I want
more chickens
what are you fishing then she's got a
huge rod
she might Tanger
[Music]
please be nice to me have mercy
you know I love you oh she left she
she oh she finished up some shrimp
perfect
as expected
hey my mine mine left what the
[Music]
shrimps
I can sell them
true
how much do I get
I sell a few
oh 760.
oh
[Music]
and then
change
ah for coins oh yeah
huh
oh one dust is one coin
[Music]
one best is one coin for rods two
I am but I don't have enough okay then
let's keep
let's keep all this dust at first
isn't it sand yeah
golden sand
[Music]
this is one of the few games where I
will tolerate fishing
as a mini game waffle them
let me help you what do you want what do
you need
waffle the man needs potatoes
[Music]
here we go
no I want to talk about
um
yeah
why take so much money no I can't waste
some more money on that I need to make
more money first we need to do another
money strap or something
yeah
she's playing in the puddle cute
hi Kyla
okay I think
yeah we used Lena before I don't want to
always use the same characters though I
kind of want to you know learn and get
to know the other characters but maybe
we could
um
let's
I want to try
Kaila once
um
[Music]
I'm gonna try time mode maybe should I
drink the spawn so a rarest material
deposit that deals 300 damage to all
Targets when hit when fully mined Kyla
gains happiness granting 50 attack speed
haste for 10 seconds
huh
stage four okay maybe with a character
that I already know how to use
um
here I'll do it for you
identity yeah
it's so grassy here you can't even
the rewards get covered up by the grass
somebody needs to cut this grass
I love this song
[Music]
let's see how far we can get they they
say this stage is more difficult because
it tells me to get
certain upgrades first we'll see about
that
we'll see if I'm ready for this also we
should go like walk around a little bit
see how big this stage actually is but
bye bye
I admit they're already strong I I I I I
will admit
help me help me I saw that spawn down
there
cute couple clothes ah cute identity I'm
going to die
I die die die
oh wait
[Music]
um
I'll take the limiter I need some help
collecting all these things
thank you
feed the Kobo this sogaki needs to
become taller
oh God hola what is this
can I walk on this isn't this water
um
guys
big
oh
can I oh no okay I can't go down there
good to know
mini boss
uh
we need to upgrade speed and attack yeah
I told you guys I'm not
I'm not for it yet
you don't have passive upgrades to kill
enemies fast and yeah yeah that's what I
knew but you guys wanted me to try
I've been stage two before
what should I do
I'm gonna re-roll actually
here comes the rain cloud
s
[Music]
and more rain clouds
I
[Music]
hope
I made it to almost three minutes
let me see can I help myself here
somewhere
[Music]
um
like speed and
speed was it right I can get one speed
and attack up was it
I can't afford any more
right now let's get out
some money
who was it Elena
my beloved wayna
should we just do endless mode
so we can get as much as possible
um do I get more oh yeah I do let's go
stage two at least I can survive stage
two
what who knows for how long
[Music]
I want to try new characters but I also
need a ton of coins
we'll get there we'll try them
eventually maybe not all of them today
but
you know
[Music]
so for money Strat we want
certain items but for now
I can also upgrade my own brain oh wait
this was
I don't think I'll I'll try to focus on
the the skill uh achievement the no
skill usage achievement but if I find
haste we could use haste at least
wait for the bounce ball can I do an up
a collabo with the bounce ball no
all the coins okay
can I don't can I can I
what what does it collab with
[Music]
there are many classes to bounce balls
oh
like free cursed here so bored oh I want
to
maybe I'll try the one with the curse
first if I can manage to get it
[Music]
yeah
hard to decide let me open up this thing
here
nah that wasn't taste
sure
let's go with Lady of the people oh
[Music]
what could I tangent about
is there something you guys wanted me to
talk about
ah I need free costumes damn
they did get some new outfits
well I already knew that they were gonna
be this like traditional style
[Music]
uh but I'm surprised Zeta actually
managed to still make it look
like barely traditional
I feel like yeah she she probably really
wanted like a casual looking outfit so
[Laughter]
it's really cute her short hair is so
cute
and then Kyla I have to admit it doesn't
really look that cute
it is more on the cool side Kyla I will
give you that
because like I was teasing her saying oh
it's gonna be cute again isn't it
and I
think
I I love the coat
the coat is so
wow
it's like huge in so many details
what do you call them tassels all about
the is that what you call them tassels
[Music]
yeah it looks really cool
really really freaking badass and then
Kobo is like
I love
because I'm gonna die I love the the
base
outfit but then her headpiece oh my God
it's like all these headpiece I guess
similar
and I don't think you can take it off
can she oh God oh God ah
where are the coins anyway what the
I feel like I'm not seeing any coins
hair goes to the side yeah the hairstyle
is really cute
yeah I need um I need a special
I need to ton jock the out of this
peeps
I also I need food
help oh
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
ah
why why why why was this so much more
difficult maybe I should play on the
normal stage for uh oopsie
I think I'll play on a normal stage
so that I can get more coins because
I'll survive more it worked way better
on this stage
but I did I did go endless
so yeah I don't know who's in my who is
my favorite
um I love the Kyla coat
I love the base outfit of Cobra
I think my favorite would be cool bro
still even though the headpiece is
a little bit overkill for me but I know
she wants to be extra extra
so understandable
daughter bias no no
no no don't like that oh cute
I love Kyla's traditional letter has
perfect matchup yeah
yeah no I I see what Zeta was going for
she was trying to make it look as casual
as possible while still fulfilling the
the you know necessary
mmm
what are these choices
we got rerolle
[Music]
it's a necessary traditional
requirement
so now they have the kimono which is
Japanese traditional outfit and they
have the Indonesian traditional outfit
um
so hopefully next they get some normal
clothes sometime
ah wrong direction
thanks for clearing the path for the
princess
next is streetwear yeah I wonder what
they'll go for next but it will probably
take a long time now they did they just
got one
nice this is looking better I need a
limiter too ideally
and oh we could we could get the ball
right now
to get us any kind of
the movement of the ball okay there's
any kind of new collaboration whatever
we want
Ian curses what I was trying in the last
one but I just died too early so
if I see it again I'll go for it
nobody wants to play ball with me
why
why nobody want to play ball
and balling
I have yet to receive anything
that increases my coins what okay exp
all right
oh God I gotta get up early tomorrow
I just realized
hmm
good choices
yeah 9am my time but
I think it's not such a good time for n
a unfortunately
but decent time for all sea and Asia
viewers
[Music]
finally here's the big money
what stream we're doing
a Pomo party
and I think a stream will be on my
channel probably and maybe also one on
Subaru and I gotta ask if Elena wants to
stream her POV too I don't think we need
all five but
yeah
I'm excited it was so difficult to get
oh
it was so difficult to get
um
a time and a date with everybody like
that I
I had to find a date
that worked for
all of all five of us in the time span
of like five days or four or so
this is the only moment you all have
hope exactly
I tried coordinating
yeah
yeah it's really
difficulty man it's really difficult
so another reason for me to not add any
new members honestly
difficult
with my contacts
[Music]
I need a limiter
what did you drop for me
whatever
is still here what does she saying
either and an energy drink and Chris
haste by 10 and speed platform
foreign
should I keep this or should I drop it
I've never dropped an item before but I
don't want it drop it
a speed is worth it take it oh okay
I don't want anything that takes away HP
from me you know
um
awake
yes okay let's just finish that one
first
and improve
actually
I'm gonna improve the pickup range first
another boss
and more or less about actually getting
hit
we'll see how it goes
the pill
the pill is new but I don't know if I
would take it over anything else
foreign
by I feel like it's so hard to kill them
and curse let me take it before I never
see it again
soon
Tom deathly stand in line
I want it to be orderly
[Music]
me
why guys I don't understand
why are you also masochistic
I understand wanting to be slapped but
getting Toronto honestly okay I barely
have any power in my
arms and fists anyway
so the chance of you getting injured or
hurt is extremely low
oh and I tweeted it out but yes the day
the day before yesterday
I got a preview of an MV for one of the
songs from my album my my plan basically
is release the album
and on the day after I want to release
the first MB
and then I'll kind of within the span of
three months release and bees for
everything else too but there will be
some
uh most and beans will just be really
like
ideally low budget
because some Spanish
a ton of money on
um
two free DMVs
so the first free DMV will be in the
beginning and the last free DMV will be
at the end of those three months to like
hype it up one more time
maybe get some more album sales
you know
yeah there will be another official
announcement about it
and there will be a stream where I say
the stream has an announcement and
everybody will know what I'll be
announcing but you guys better act
surprised
um
yeah but you know you know just let me
do my announcement stream okay
I wanna do my announcement stream
I rarely get to do them okay
let me down and and out what you don't
know anything yet you don't know this
until the day that I announce it
you have no idea what I'm talking about
this whole time every time I mention the
word album you guys are just hearing uh
this this sound that's all you're
hearing
oh God
oh my god oh let's go
bro
let's hope I don't just die in this very
moment
oh my God
oh no tangent so you spill future plans
yep yep
you know me announcement of an
announcement
that's perfect for your Nano Run is it
oh my God
let's not die oh nice food
all right
we are safe
oh there's another tone Dragon coming
always should
get the tone joke activated because you
don't have to use it right away anyway
just so that it can charge back up
I understand ready for that Meme review
what is this mother
curse ball play ball the more you play
the longer it stays
oh no do I have to
are you telling me I have to actively
like punch it
wow no it was will it snow
no I don't have the the memory the RAM
for this
it's new yeah
oh there's so there's two now oh
do you guys just let this happen you
guys can't play the game yet
uh I was gonna ask you if you guys just
let it happen or
I did
you really want the body pillow really
no really really
I do
yeah
okay
leave room for super chanton
oh yeah
okay the last one I'll leave for super
chattel what
oh
[Laughter]
is here welcome now I can't run around
freely anymore
[Laughter]
um
let me just uh increase my attention
please maybe
[Music]
um
so many times
[Applause]
yeah
okay
um
what are we gonna do
should I get idle song
um we can try to get that super cool app
Idol song and the glow stick
with the idol outfits you guys told me
that that is something
[Music]
okay I really I really like try my
hardest oh
how much damage does that even do on the
enemies
damn I'm balling I've never balled this
much before in my life
[Music]
ah
four okay
uh I don't even know what to punch there
we go
what oh my God
twins beautiful
I guess we're using it
yeah
holy okay we got something going
here I think I
if only I didn't need to go to an idol
meeting I could go on forever and ever
and ever and ever with this current
build it's looking pretty chill
looking pretty chill
no I'm fine
[Laughter]
I can I can I can go a bit longer with
this
um
no
I just finished the Idol song
this is fun it's like I'm playing two
games at the same time
dodgeball and Hollow cure
oh my God the next home truck is already
ready what the
uh
it's filling up so fast
don't say that don't say that she will
get nerfed if you say that
we need to get whole cure
uh unlike number one downloaded games
all right
on Steam right now you guys can download
it can you oh wait can you can you
[Music]
not yet okay so when it's midnight you
can download it on Steam okay okay okay
but one it deserves to
swim like people need to see that the
charts and then
maybe some brandos who don't know what
hollow life is will play it too
another tone joke it's like I have
currently
constantly my special available
um
[Music]
foreign
that's not what I wanted
because I want the idle song to be
combined with the idol glow stick
um so I guess we'll just go
if something else
separately
oh
oh my God I feel so much faster
oh oh my God here's the glow stick
oh
I am unbeatable I got two special SSR
items in this run can you believe it
one g
h
It's Time to Kill
you
here comes the queue people
Invaders
[Music]
oh my God there's so much going on
I want to go back up
let me talk let me talk
I'll take a body pillow
[Applause]
wow wow wow
okay
we're almost at ten thousand coins let's
go
let's go
I want to learn how to speak in a New
Zealand or
Australian accent that didn't that sound
Australian to you I don't know
new jeans is like
that's it they're like so inspiring to
me right now
not at all oh my God damn of course it
sounds like ghost trillion
oh New Zealand
that's right garlic it's a mix okay
because new jeans are literally they
speak like valley girl okay that's okay
some part of that sounded like that no
I feel like it did it sounded like new
jeans to me in my heart but they they
are literally Valley girls who speak
like New Zealand and Australians
because they are from the Australian and
New Zealand you know so you know
that's where they get that from now
now now uh
tap myself up
questions
[Music]
my specialist is constantly ready and
I'm not even doing anything to improve
that
[Applause]
is
if this is an endless run what happens
they just do I get more bosses too or is
it just endless spawn of any means
super hard what what's with super oh
should I have chosen it oh
yeah oh there's an achievement that I
should die from Yago
so maybe I should take that opportunity
to purposefully die too
um
the trick to Australian accent is to say
razor blade but try to say rise up light
don't need to you will die
it will kill you know oh really okay can
you not take him down
wait once we have
what can you collab with wami water
[Music]
boys love okay okay
then that will be another thing to aim
for
they should add a donate
button on Steam for indie game creators
but it would probably go to the
publisher huh
but I feel like they should do that
wouldn't that be so cool if it was a
steam function then Caillou couldn't
like escape from it
couldn't escape from our money
okay I'm like about to be level 50 right
now
holy
he doesn't want it almost force it on to
him like what the
um
oh level 50. so we'll no wait I'm not do
it do I have to have the idol outfit
like level five
for the big collab to happen
oh no I guess I have to collab those two
things first in the first place as well
um
a small collaborate okay and then I can
do super cool app or does the dress also
need to be level five or so
it's always level oh
okay
[Music]
oh my god oh I just ran straight into
that I didn't see that
there's also something on the bottom
is that no wait never mind that was
something else
what now
do I just have to find another anvil
and it picked it up but what happens
oh my God I'm not gonna I
too many I don't know where where I am
I don't see things anymore oh there's
the golden anvil
so
wow
I don't love special live for those
special cooldown by 30 whenever active
okay even more I'll be tone shocking
non-stop whenever activating the special
increase all stats by fifty percent
oh can only activate once per 30
seconds
oh my okay
oh God oh God oh God
there's too much going on
this will be the end of me just oh yeah
the fact that there's so much going on
will be the end of me
um
[Music]
yeah
hey oh and the next one is already ready
oh my oh my
God oh my God how am I already so
overpowered and before 20 minutes
oh
the
holy moly
do it
should I maybe add and we never got the
Super Chat thing should I maybe add the
nurses horn I'm scared
the book okay
it's okay if we die this is only about
the coins it's only about the coins
could I like stand no I don't want to
send I don't want to stand I don't want
to stand I don't understand
oh there's a sticker there hmm
bit hard to reach right now
[Applause]
just let me get out of here I don't see
anything
where is the fist going
there we go hi Amber
[Applause]
oh my God I want to play with the ball
but it's on the fence
[Music]
wait there's something up there is that
the sticker the the Green Arrow is that
the sticker
yeah okay
[Music]
I think it's beaten up just like in her
dreams and hopes
no not the energy drink okay 20 percent
[Music]
okay okay
chill chill out
what is going on
check step yeah I'm trying to find it
right now
uh oh there it is okay
I'm just gonna improve one of these
things
anything else I'm missing on the screen
I don't think so
oh there's so there's stuff in here
is done enemies temporarily
maybe this one I could replace no
strengthen
hmm
[Music]
okay
different opinions in the chat but
I saw a couple that say do this
time 80 18 more Hollow coins
I need to unleash all my limiters
so that I'll be able to collect all of
them actually
thank you
hundred percent more Holocaust because
why the hell not yeah
make way
all right oh an anvil for us how nice
upgrading the whammy water
this is the god run
um
but I I shall not get too cocky
that is very dangerous
I never got this much money or levels
before ever I think
[Music]
yeah maybe we even still get the great
stamp who knows I've heard of it in the
Legends
rookie numbers it's good for me I never
had this much before
can we make it to 30 minutes
thank you
yeah I think so
I wonder if there's like any area that
has a lot of exp laying around and I'm
just not
finding it anymore because I'm too far
away
feels like a waste
oh my God hello everybody you've all
grown so so much
thank God for the tone joke
oh
Max Max uh
should I maybe upgrade like one of the
collabs that I already have
great hey the water
yeah let's skip this one for now I'm
scared to tap out
oh
[Music]
this and that
Frozen see endless waves of ice that's
all wonderful I think that was a good
choice
never seen this one before
that
maybe there's just too much to see
foreign
okay what's next what do we got next
um
[Music]
what do we want next
all right all right
stay away from me I am poisonous
you don't want to get too close to me
eat that spider cooking okay
to improve those try the cooking
[Music]
wow
what's Bow Wow
[Laughter]
other dogs the
I'm gonna get out of here
my next Stone joke is ready
yeah bye
wow
oh no don't run in there
oh
oh my God it's a horde
and they don't even want to die anymore
they're they're really buff now
I feel like they're spawning more than
I'm killing that's a problem joke
mmm
yeah they are some people really want me
to take more energy drinks
wait it doesn't stack another 20
minus Max HP doesn't it's just like
was it like 15 before so it doesn't
reduce HP anymore okay okay okay
holy
[Applause]
my screen is melting yeah I think
um you know YouTube videos they die if
they lose a lot of frames uh not frames
but what's it called bit rain with like
fire
effects and there was one more thing
rain I think this this seems like
something to kill the bitrate
a lot on YouTube
maybe not rain then
when it rain isn't so bad
how's the bit break guys gosh
how does it look on your side guys
oh wait my chat died a lot there it is
crunchy blurry quite bad very chaotic
it's kind of the same for me hey we're
almost at uh 30 minutes all right all
right all right
oh
a text of a three percent chance to hit
whole coins out of targets per hit
oh
no way per hit even of my special
attacks
chance an amount is increased for every
10 Dash oh my God
now only for Maine okay
help me I'm scared mommy I'm scared I'm
scared I'm so scared I'm so scared yeah
bye
[Music]
oh it's is it time for a new weapon uh
stream dead
hello hello hello hello hello
don't leave me
[Music]
bucket or tear
ah
I think we've didn't we see the uh hello
are you guys back didn't we see the
spider cooking at the CEO's tears before
already I mean I've seen the elite lover
get collab a million times as well but
get bucket it's Enchanted
oh yeah oh great damage oh yeah
let's go let's go
[Music]
[Laughter]
help me oh my God
thank God I'm so fast right now oh I can
Circle them perfectly
[Music]
did you guys see dad's password game I
saw like two videos like one was
um
kids Boga cool I want like binge watched
endlessly until I got sick of it because
it's always the same content like it's
funny but it's always the same
yeah
not just 180m that's actually not worth
it for me right now look how much I'm
making
um
um yeah the kid Boga one where he uses
it you guys probably know kid Pogo right
where he uses it to
um
like generally he's he's a title person
who makes twitch streams where he calls
like he pawns scammers
like usually I think they're like from
India I think
for sure and they you know they're those
scammers that try to get old people to
send them money
uh be a gift cards from Walmart or
targets
yeah and
he makes like voices like old people
voices and like he really does a great
job at
uh making them believe that he really is
a potential Target now he used this
password game that somebody created
which is basically just like a simple
window where you have to enter a
password and it with each stage it will
give you another
another certain oh God
the challenge to improve your password
and first it's just the normal typical
ones hello hello
uh
do not redeem red soup what
what
why did you redeem read what
what did I read what
what did I redeem
oh you're making reference to Kid voga
ah okay you guys scared me that I did
something wrong
no that's right there yeah I love it too
I've watched so much like many many
years ago before whole life I think I
just spent all gods oh God I just spent
oh God ah oh God hours hours hours
watching kid Boca archives
uh so funny and yeah and then it's the
password game where you get the
challenge to uh create a really
difficult password but eventually it's
like really ridiculous things like they
wanted to to clear a chest for a chest
chest chest chest chess board with the
most ideal most ideal
in your face Jagger the most ideal move
oh God you guys were right with getting
more speed
getting stuck it's very dangerous
how long can I do it
oh the snare oh the snack yeah yeah in
the other video was somebody uh clearing
it even though the even the developer
has oh God oh God has never cleared it
before
um but in a group of friends did it and
it was a really interesting video them
attempting to clear it eventually you
get like a egg an egg icon that you have
to protect and when the egg hatches like
it turns into a chicken icon
and and then you have to feed it every
like 10 seconds or so every 30 seconds
you have to feed it and warm and so you
put a warm Emoji there if you run out of
warm emojis uh it will show like uh like
an Elden ring screen like you uh your
whatever your worm died but in like
Elden ring style uh or Souls game style
oh my God
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
chihuahua has died
koala has died
[Laughter]
that was a good run oh my God
I want to submit my high score
how does this work oh
wait why are there like only why is this
not filled up is the eye is this
who are these people
good run I never got
there hey
one second child 32 minutes yeah pretty
close
yeah because it's early access but what
about these people are they like
Japanese people but then why isn't the
whole board filled with Japanese people
[Music]
um
oh
hold on totally enjoyest
Rocky Point ice cream multiplayer win
good question
[Laughter]
man I will not read this one out
ah also depending on the character too
oh ah so these are only like people who
played as Elena on stage one so maybe
that's why it's still like Sophie but I
would still feel like there was already
more than that but okay I guess not
um
okay uh quick
how much money
shouldn't I have more than that
or maybe they're game testers I am
yeah I feel like I should have more than
F I made that much really
I thought I made more it looks like so
little
okay let's go to the upgrades uh
uh we can get a lot of upgrades at that
what should I focus on
attack upgrade
[Music]
by the cheap ones increase damage of
skill attacks okay
hold on reduction
one HP heels
one HP
pick up range
armor armor armor armor armor armor
duckle
beads
ah the shield was Hammer okay
[Music]
I need to do more Dana runs
haste haste haste
attack speed by four percent
foreign
[Music]
upgrade for more true I guess
one of those
critical hit chance
[Music]
still missing Anya no I got Anya
I got Anya now
EXP
[Music]
old on reduction
so that we can tone jock even more
endlessly
and this one
okay one one money one coin left wait
I need to go uh use the only charger
rifle if you know what I mean
really quickly
[Music]
foreign
all right guys
William Mina was a little slow
what do you mean
[Music]
hello I am back yeah
the charge rifle is empty now it's
broken it can't be used anymore
okay
um
I'm considering
breeding super chats now because I do
have to sleep early just uh way earlier
than before
and I have to make an actual serious
attempt at it
because the stream is in nine ten like
14 hours
and normally I don't sleep that early
um
yeah I still have to make thumbnail
and eat something but I cooked yesterday
I cooked a curry
somewhat of a curry like a sweet potato
Masala style flavor Curry
uh
but it only has sweet potatoes and I
added corn
with some naan bread but the naan bread
is by far not as good as the one I ate
in London at the big uh famous
Indian restaurant I don't know why why
is it not so good maybe it's because
it's not fresh
man probably lacking garlic right maybe
I'll maybe have some garlic I'll add
some garlic because this one I only like
it told me to warm it up in a frying pan
with butter
so I did have the butter
that they added in the restaurant as
well but it was missing the garlic that
is true and there was maybe not that
much
um butter on it in the first place
[Music]
fresh is always better yeah I wish I I
wish I had a freshman one man it tasted
pretty lame
garlic garlic changes everything right
yeah I know
um
for me up there 8 21
minutes
but I will read some super chats I think
you know what cause I'm dressed in my
dandel how about we go to a really rare
screen
[Music]
I want a change of scenery
hahaha hello
um
oh my God the chance is broken why are
you so broken oh wait I can I may be
able to fix it or not or not why yeah
sometimes it does this
ah
why are you broken huh
I can barely see you
don't know how to fix this issue yeah
only the hits those messages that just
show normally yeah
I don't know why
[Music]
how about I try playing around I guess
no I broke it even more damn
[Music]
I guess we'll have to go
like this again and the hills are alive
with the sound of music
[Music]
I guess we'll have to do a window
capture or wait let me refresh the cash
oh it doesn't help
it doesn't help
ah
oh my gosh I wanna I don't wanna hear
this music anymore
sorry
we need more remixes we need more we
need uh we need to be able to switch
songs
that is my personal request
especially for stage number one
I it wouldn't it be so cool if you had
um you know in some games like the atlio
game for example they
um let you change the music to like
previous Atelier games for example okay
there was no previous whole cure games
but
I think that's a really cool feature in
theory if you get sick of the music
although I never got sick of the music
in Atelier games
but the stage one bgm man uh
it was nice hearing it again for the
first time in a while
but yeah take notes take notes would be
cool for the home base right
um
yeah I don't know chat is like
what do I do
let me see
if I find
here this one maybe this one
maybe this one isn't broken I have a
different one
oh look at this one it's not broken yeah
yeah
I just
I fixed you my beautiful chickens look
at you
now let me put you down here okay
welcome back yay
I know so much stuff
nice improvising well uh it's my job
streaming is my job after all who who
would I be how good of a streamer would
I be if I wouldn't have emergency
solutions for these these desperate
situations yes yes now let me find the
BTL
mm-hmm
and what I want to listen to
uh
audio stock
[Music]
nah
this one's pretty
wow
this one makes me feel
like we just did something amazing
together
accomplishments have been made
achievements have been achieved
[Music]
it's uplifting right
is it okay to be so positive here
otherwise I have this
[Music]
uh very different from usual
this choice of bgm
[Music]
that's just rise of music yeah I know is
it
hey you guys feel it's like we're
playing Atelier maybe a little actually
yeah
it feels like ryza is just like
started yeah she's just starting her
Adventure
indeed okay I can see it
okay are we reading super chats or what
which ones
where did I stop
[Music]
that's done story time
oh still so far back huh but but I
remember some of these are not so
uh big they don't take up too much
I think
and then we bring up the thumbnail and
then we can get started
[Music]
Super Chat rating
ah
[Music]
I wanna watch what are the Rings or
Hobbits or Game of Thrones I wanna watch
something fancy like again
can they finally like freaking release
something interesting new that I've been
waiting for for example uh Wheels Wheel
of Time
was it was it that like okay that wasn't
so good but I'm still waiting for the
new season wasn't that supposed to be
out ages ago
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah I should watch The Witcher
I haven't watched The Witcher
[Music]
it's terrible if you know the books yeah
yeah I've heard my mom told me all about
it
[Music]
which is good just the first season
season one is fine Richard season one is
great you can stop there
oh
and they messed it up after the first
one
well does your mom think about The
Witcher I don't know about that we never
talked about The Witcher thanks for the
membership
thank you
appreciate it
bread the chickens
[Music]
more chickens need to work for me and my
coin Garden
[Music]
well yeah it would be so cool if I liked
it if I ended up liking it because then
I could play the game too right The
Witcher game
is the game better than
the series
yeah
a lot better oh
what came first the game or the series
I know I guess the book was first but I
mean after that
the game
okay another one in there
Marathon or something like that for 1.5
million
um I'm I I'm just not sure what's a
realistic
amount
to start it at
because let me check right now it's
almost 1.49
so 10 000 I'm currently 11 10 900 Subs
away from it
back in the day
starting it at 10
000 before the goal was actually a I
think realistic surprisingly realistic
nowadays I would not do that anymore
uh maybe yeah maybe 5K but even then I'm
low-key scared but if I would start 5K
before
I wonder if I could make it
um yeah
I I wouldn't even I'm not sure if I
would do a color okay because it's
pretty soon and I'm I'm planning to do a
karaoke for
the album and all that so
I want to spam too many karaoke but
we'll see when it happens you'll be fine
it's like 5K
2K say 3K is doable I wanna do 5K though
and see if I suffer from it it's okay
though like if it's not karaoke Then I
can do a pretty long Marathon I could do
I could do Mario Kart Marathon or I
could do
um look at that door what kind of
marathon could I do
oh I could do jump King marathon or
something like that or or I never played
that uh that game before uh the the the
the the the the one where you have the
hammer the pickaxe and you go up to the
top are getting over it yeah I've never
played that before I could do that
so the goal is not finishing the game
the goal is just suffering until I get
to 1.5
um
[Music]
so maybe I'm
maybe I'm the nerissa cleared it on on
first try really like on her first
stream
of the game really quickly right
maybe I'm not so bad maybe I have a
natural talent for it
oh she played it before okay
it wasn't ever okay
maybe she could teach me maybe I could
have opened BC during the marathon and
Marissa could come in and help me give
me some tips is it actually efficient I
wonder will this game to get like some
tips doesn't really help you
[Music]
how to get over certain obstacles you
think so
[Music]
okay we could do that yeah have some
we see action going on
even if it takes hours I if it's just a
gaming stream I don't really mind
[Music]
um
okay
yeah there's so many potential members
to help me with it
okay sounds good yeah I'll be doing a
marathon because I haven't done a
marathon in a long time last one was for
a million
uh wasn't that a 12 hour stream
for reaching 1 million
and then I felt like
1.25 wasn't really you know was weird
like even dull it took me a long time to
get there it just didn't feel
fitting to do one
so I've been waiting for 1.5
we're finally getting there oh my God
[Music]
oh yeah I got it before the stream
started ah before the marathon oh yeah
that was something like this Pizza Tower
no
no I'm never playing Pizza towel again
[Music]
only up
I think I'm fine not playing only up
because I wasn't around when the game
was hyped
in whole life the most now it's calmed
down and I don't care much about the
game anyway
um
[Music]
yeah I think since I never played it
before getting over it is
maybe them better choice
[Music]
maybe one day if I run out of games
again I can play
the other one
but you never do foremost anyway
sometimes I do but
I don't force it into my schedule like
with Holo cure I would have liked to
play it earlier
but my schedule was already set in stone
and it wasn't really things that could
change and you know it was during the
week where I was already struggling with
my sleep schedule so I wanted to
prioritize my health
and my sleep over you know playing a
hyped up game but yeah generally
generally I
don't
really follow the hype on a lot of those
games on unless I really am interested
in them
and then it's just because I'm
interested in them not because of the
hype but it would be nice to be able to
play them you know when the hype is
really the highest for like Final
Fantasy 2 I would have liked to play it
right away
but I couldn't
because the perms also came in
surprisingly
Yeah but I
feel like I should still play it I want
to because there's a phoenix in there
apparently
it's a phoenix
I have to
[Music]
hmm
I have to I want to
it'll be fun once I once I play it my
hype my personal hype as I said before
is kind of dead
towards it but I think once we get into
it it will be fun
[Music]
Phoenix is in almost all the F games
what
it
[Music]
oh well still
whatever
[Music]
and well it's
even the newest one so I think I should
play the newest one yeah
we'll finish GTA this weekend
never play ff16 as the weekend series I
think
um
it won't be my first one too let's go
besides the MMO
a hat
it's not usually as plot important
though oh is it in this case though
it felt like it is because it's like in
the trailer even isn't it
yeah right
there you go let's go let's go
I have to play it um
all right uh Ultimo MK thank you for the
pinky I did it I finally into my
ultimate Phoenix chicken farm and it
could not have happened at a better time
because now I can light myself on fire
and serve as an extra pen light to cheer
you on during the whole of Summer
concert oh my God
oh yeah that's at the end of this month
oh my god
oh
it's also very very soon I'm excited for
it yeah bye I am
[Music]
next weekend not this weekend what are
you talking about
[Music]
it's not not this weekend what are you
talking about
why are there several people saying it's
this weekend
are you good
night
don't stress me out
Hollow summer
[Music]
time travel is in chat
anyway congratulations thank you for
being with kfb for such a long time I I
admire the commitment of making yourself
into a pen line I don't think I've heard
this before
penguin thank you for the two red super
chats thank you and and a yellow one too
hi thank you
Taipei Taichung and in June and July to
catch the Chiapas ah I went to see the
bus so many kids piano man really were
there other people checking it out
I saw a lot of pictures of the bus but
it's hard to imagine that there would
really be like a decent amount of people
checking it out
[Music]
there
and I'm very happy and the bus drivers
are very nice they will stop and wait
for us oh really to take pictures before
leaving oh that's so nice
even though they have to keep up a
schedule
um thanks to the organizer of this event
the KFC employees who raised funds and
all the kfps who supported this event
it's a bit late but Happy Birthday Tanto
I wish you happy birthday happy every
day love care people
thank you so much oh you made Vlogs too
wait let me look it up
we made Vlogs about the bus
[Music]
oh
they're really long but oh there's a
vlog for each
cities
a bus and oh there's also a whole life
capsule collaboration Cafe Vlog I'm
gonna watch all of these
I'm going to watch all of them yay
thank you for letting me know I wanna I
wanna see what what it looked like how
many people were there and all that
thank you thank you thank you thank you
cave penguin and thank you to everybody
who helped out to make the bus a reality
it was really cool to see and I really
loved the illustration that was on top
of it
um
yeah you know in Japan sometimes uh in
Tokyo I see buses going by that also
blast the music
of whatever they're promoting that would
be cool to have that happen sometime but
I've only ever seen that in Japan so far
I wonder if that's possible to do
elsewhere
it's usually really loud too
and they drive by like really popular
areas like Harajuku
I always see them in Harajuku always
which song would you like to have
playing and from my new album song
one of the main
songs with the 3D MBs is what I would
personally
recommend yeah
maybe maybe only really possible in in
Japan I don't know
but anyway the bus even without music
was really cute
[Music]
pictures of the first thank you so much
to all the fans who were involved and
who checked it out to see it in reality
thank you
[Music]
oh in Korea too they do it in Korea I
want to do it in Korea too
[Music]
but you know it's not like any promotion
is gonna be done from my company's side
from my album there is no promotion
involved unless I have a label or so
so I'll have to survive without
promotion
um
no promotion for Wawa
even though I feel like it's so worth it
like at least putting up some posters
would be nice
[Music]
um
yeah on Twitter maybe one time that's
that's all the promotion I'll get
[Music]
uh
anyway uh wasted you thank you for the
right Super Chat thank you soon
no no message coming with it though why
not
why not you have nothing to tell me tell
me why you think you wasted your Youth
and I'll tell you why I don't think you
did
um
[Music]
would you like us to rent a billboard I
don't know I mean you can if it's not
too expensive I don't know maybe it
depends on the location too if it really
makes sense and
ideally this would be something where
you can play the music
[Music]
um
what are you saying I should pay half of
it how will I do that
Times Square Times Square sounds crazy
expensive and I don't know if people
even do people even pay attention to
what's playing on the Times Square
but it would be cool to have something
in an a for once
um it doesn't have to be Times Square
because I feel like people don't pay
attention to it anyway
it would be cool though some people
would probably come to just see it in
action
but if it's too expensive then I don't
think it's worth it
[Music]
and then feel free if you guys really do
something like that feel free to use my
music video that will come out soon uh
as the visuals please actually do that
because
that will be eye-catching I think
I mean it will also maybe freak people
out who don't know what the that is
that YouTuber on the screen what is this
does the 3D anime girl moving around
what what what what
yeah but still eye-catching
[Music]
yeah bye anime women are taking over the
world
what do we do
anyway where's you thank you
thank you Alexa studio right
Rocky I saw you sending one today too
thank you so much thank you
Arigato thank you for the support very
very sweet of you rock our Dear Santa
thank you also for Pinky yeah let's say
oh oh
that Amber informs you that a dangerous
Army has entered our world who is trying
to kidnap all guras and there's more
than one Guru and imprisoned them in her
personal aquarium will you let AMA
handle this herself or do you want to
help her protect gura
hmm
you didn't explain anything about why
there is more than one gura in here in
the first place there's also more good
as to enter the world while the
dangerous Army also entered the world
[Music]
um
I mean if there's so many good as
then maybe it's better
[Music]
to
keep as many as possible of them in an
aquarium because too many gudas maybe
dangerous to the world
um
oh yeah
[Music]
we should we should actually
we should let her have her personal
aquarium I think
sounds fun
yeah as long as she leaves one gura
outside of the aquarium
have as many as she wants for the
aquarium yeah do it
unexpected answer perhaps
foreign
thank you for worrying about me thank
you
ah
[Music]
thank you you're welcome yeah
you're welcome but you should be happy
aren't you happy about some some uh 5
p.m streams from fuamoko
it's a little bit more than before now
European
blessed
streams but still not much but you'll
just have to continue to just watch me
I'm sorry I'm sorry Wiki Tunes thank you
Nathan caught the nection for the pinky
sorry I'm late and just clocking in
after clocking out for my other job that
lets me pay you my Salary
thank you so much you don't have to but
I really appreciate the support thank
you Nathan you're the best
the best Nathan
for putting so much effort in all of
your jobs hey thank you
you the sweetest
Dominique Kane thank you soon hyper
Epsilon Junction the monster Envy
Junction
[Music]
thank you
um
[Music]
foreign
oh okay I'll go back to it in a
moment
um yeah
[Music]
um people are asking me why I didn't
take Japanese voice
starting voice and I'm just I don't know
like the the the whole stuff like
um
the starting voice thing came up and
they weren't really like
I guess I don't know what my stomach is
growling so much they weren't like
suggesting it much to me I think and I
was like oh no I feel like people
probably not gonna need it anyway
I don't know I don't know I don't know
what happened or I really don't
you heard it don't listen
yeah maybe I will inquire if I can still
do it after words like now
If people really want it but I feel like
nobody's gonna buy it except maybe five
people
[Music]
my mama
um
[Music]
foreign
voice
any of them
did anybody buy it
really I didn't even like properly
advertise it
guys you did what
I was like when I first heard about us
doing studying voices I was like hmm all
of these are pretty short and the like
the topics are like pretty basic like
introduction and stuff like that and
whatever Greetings or so
like I thought most people probably
won't care about it
yeah you wish it was longer right I
thought so too it's like so short
um
it's pretty short
there's like one maybe that's a bit
longer but not really
[Music]
um
I can't afford physical merch due to
shipping and space concerns so I buy
your voice Banks thank you so much
[Music]
oh purely because the shop only sends
out service to people that have bought
something on it and I can't buy anything
what you wanted to fill out the survey
or what
it was just the one way you could have
where we could have tipped you for more
yeah no I don't know I don't think so
people have said take super chats for
custom alarms from you
starting voice being that sheep is
nothing
oh yeah but that's custom
eh
[Music]
ah people want to ask for EU options the
goal is really the survey
oh funny
[Music]
okay it's a yellow ostrich streamer
tanakisha
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah you're talking to me are you man
the
um
yellow ostrich
sounds like Shakira
[Music]
okay I will forgive you if this doesn't
mean that you're forever gone and you're
just selling the Super Chat to say
goodbye to me
[Music]
if you promise to share the love
then I may forgive
but I am a phoenix and I have orange
like how could you say yellow isn't so
obvious that I am the orange you should
know you're doing this on purpose aren't
you of course okay
you must be that was it must have been
on purpose the Super Chat
is the orange
unbelievable please tell me you're just
trolling
[Music]
amen
yellow
orange is so much better
sending a smiley face well I hate it
when I ask you guys questions and in the
chat you don't even give me a proper
answer
[Music]
I'm literally like staring at the chat
to find your answer and then it's just
like a smiley face
[Music]
yellow ostrich
that's too funny to me
okay
thank you for the rest of the chat 69
days ago
send a super title that my birthday will
be in 69 days today is the day of my
birthday back court same I'm getting
older and from today on more taxes
stupid why
well at least I can spend it with my
Kami ocean gave me you're the best Idol
a Boss by the person could wish for
congratulations
friends
why do we have to pay more taxes
[Music]
why
I am well saying you a song
[Music]
uh
what do I what do we make about
oh
I'm gonna write up a quick quick memo
you mean Kaira
[Music]
I didn't have to pay income tax until
what how young are you
but how old did you get
Mommy
does that mean you turned 18 what's up
I'm six oh
way older than 18.
hmm
wait
[Music]
um
words that rhyme with
mm-hmm
yeah
those are all
God damn it
wait I choose this word
um
oh well
[Music]
okay and then one more sorry one more
I'm writing a birthday song okay special
service for beautiful beautiful uh
old-timer chickens only
um
[Music]
oh my God
I can't find a good word to rhyme with
this word what the these are not
even English words
why does it show me not English words
um
[Music]
this also shows me not English words
what the
maybe I'll throw in some German
I will
[Music]
okay here we go
happy birthday
to you
happy birthday to you
happy birthday in your shoe happy
birthday in your pants too happy
birthday to you
there once was a chicken
that was really smitten
[Music]
happy birthday to you
happy birthday in your shoes happy
birthday in your pants too
happy birthday to you
sometimes you're grumpy
[Applause]
[Music]
not really though so keep up your head
and pink positive okay
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday
[Music]
happy birthday to you
26 is still young as of life in the
vehicles
[Music]
and not completely rhymed but I did my
best hmm
yeah only twins
very young young
[Laughter]
how'd you like that
other line
do I see a hookan do I see a happy Hogan
in the chat
[Music]
hold on
there you are you loved it yeah I don't
think you tend to be grumpy towards me
sometimes so
let's hope that there will be less
grumpiness
in the future
but
I'm very happy to have you around for
such a long time man thank you for not
ever giving up on the Wawa for believing
in the wow for supporting the Wawa
for staying with me okay thank you so
much I hope your birthday was okay sorry
I'm once again very late
my birthday wishes come with delays it's
uh by default there's no way around it
if you want a birthday wish it will have
to take its time yeah
[Music]
um
I will someday be called up again and
then I will be delayed again and then I
will be caught up again and then I will
be it's an endless loop
inevitable
yeah
what do you mean it's not yet six nine
days later 69 days since he first wrote
that though right
and then when he sent the Super Chat it
was actually yeah the birthday yeah so
I'm late but I guess I am not 69 days
late
yeah
should I send a birthday super chat now
so then I can get it for my birthday I
don't know how far away is it
you could you could
well who knows I'm about to catch up on
you guys
um
okay now that we have celebrated another
birthday in your shoe and in your pants
too
nice days late oh also 69. oh yes
oh
foreign
[Music]
do we even wear pants
no I guess not
most of you don't you just wear the
uniform huh I'm so excited for you guys
to get the chicken plushie man
actually do you want to sleep it's only
9 p.m and I already cooked so I just
have to warm it up
so should be fine and I'll take a
melatonin hoping that I'll be able to
fall asleep
wow
especially since the hat is removable
yeah the hat is so cute though I like it
both with hat and without hat
um
[Music]
meal prep yeah
and I think it's quite healthy
because it's a query with sweet potato
it's pretty good it was pretty good I
mean I'm not like the hugest fan of
sweet potato I like it it's pretty good
it was just so difficult to
cut sweet potatoes so I don't know if
it's because the sweet potatoes I get
are always so big but I think they're
generally pretty big
and they're like so hard inside
so cutting it
getting through with my mouth I have to
like slam it like I have to get in a
little bit with the knife and then I
have to slam it against The Cutting
Board
to get through
um they're so hard to slice
just boil them first makes it easier to
feel the peeling wasn't the issue really
cutting is the issue but the recipe says
to not boil them first because that's
not how the recipe goes you boil them
boil them with all the other things
but yeah
is your knife sharpened
probably not uh but still I still think
it would be very difficult to get
through but my knives are probably
really dense yeah because they're um
they're out of ceramic
so I don't know I don't think I could
even sharpen it but now
I've had them for
a couple years now
I think I bought them when I left Japan
okay then it's not it can't be that long
one two and a half years maybe
because I love Japan half a year into
whole life
so I've been using them for two and a
half years ceramic
[Laughter]
would you say that not sharpening your
knives for two and a half years
it's gonna make them really
bad
they still work but when I especially
when I cut uh herbs
I noticed that it doesn't go through
properly
it's really annoying cutting herbs
but anything besides herbs is still fine
ah also tomatoes for example it's really
difficult to get for tomatoes without
like
you know you have to you have to have a
good feeling for tomatoes for cutting
tomatoes
buy a new knife but I really like the
knives that I have do it let me see do
they still have the same knives Ikea uh
I think they went for Mickey Ikea
versus of Deutsche
Schneider myself
cooking Mesa
[Music]
ceramic or maybe the same adult but but
I want those because they're useful
because they don't have Reflections you
know
and wait what
pastel
laughs
oh they look different
are those really those
[Music]
maybe I look on Amazon
oh there's a nice one oh there's a nice
looking one on Amazon that has all kinds
of different beautiful pink colors
actually I think I have it wait maybe I
didn't buy it from Ikea because the the
small one the gray one looks really
familiar
let me show you these are pretty they
look like mine actually they look
exactly like mine
just with different colors oh I think
those are the ones I have
what
they look exactly like mine
oh yeah the other color variation is the
one that I have
I'm actually missing one of these knives
I just realized
and I want to show you
[Music]
actually this is giving me a good reason
to buy a new knife set because the same
knife set that I have now
they have it in in pink variations
[Music]
the gray one is still gray though the
really small one
those are pretty keep it
[Music]
um
they chip very easily it's so far
nothing shipped for me
these are pretty nice
knife
stop
thank you so you
the other ones are again the greenish
colors that I already have
with some gray oh and then there's wow
this one looks really elegant there's a
fully black
wow let me show you this
looks sexy
[Music]
why am I knife shopping right now
look at this they're kind of hot but
it's not my style
[Music]
black might be reflective you think so
I think there are probably
the same amount of reflective just
because they're
um
I don't know coated
him and hers
the colored ones are nicer don't you
think also for cooking streams you know
showing these off will have a cuter
effect than showing these off
maybe one day I'll get like proper
mature looking ones
um
[Music]
yeah you gotta consider the cooking
streams
[Music]
okay I'll put this in my basket I'll buy
them
our right side is for alter Kiana
YouTube
what's wrong with YouTube today man
too many issues
literally takamori knives ah one there
no it's Cali knives because the pink and
the black is like Cali's color
none of that is really my color my color
is orange and turquoise so actually the
original knives that I have
there's some turquoise there
that actually works better for me in
theory but I want the pink knives
black pink knives oh
black pink
Blue Area
yeah okay
um
where was I
and Nathan cotton thank you for the
pinky are you saying we sent too many
super chats
maybe I was saying that at the time but
I'm not necessarily saying it now
now but everybody be careful with your
wallets
make sure that there's no holes in them
make sure that they're not always too
filled up because if you lose it or it
gets stolen then you
I
usually
never have cash with me
[Music]
probably good
same same yeah times have changed people
don't bring cash anymore but I think
Supermarket cashiers and so on they're
really happy about it
because then they don't have to always
give you cash back
um
coins endless coins
and sometimes they lack coins
certain coins yeah I think supermarkets
cashiers are very very happy about it
does
[Music]
I mean let me
suing kids let me Sue your wallet back
together but in order to do that I'll
have to take everything out first
to then safely sew it back together
yeah yeah it's a safety requirement
thank you oh my God
oh my godding oh my God
no it's dropping
be careful guys oh my God that's why I'm
telling you don't bring cash in your
wallets
[Music]
don't bring the cash
bring only credit card and then give me
the credit card number and the security
pin and everything else
[Music]
kit
it's a ceiling kit
[Music]
I know what a pain it is when the net
dies and cards don't work ah
yeah that does happen sometimes huh
it was never an issue for me though the
only time when I need cash is when I pay
for my massages
they want cash
kid program warned me about the scam
[Music]
oh you
younger you you dropped something let me
let me give it back to you uh oh too bad
I can't it won't let me refund oh no
well what do we do about this very
unfortunate situation
[Music]
Nathan
what are you implying
it almost sounds like I stole it from
you
David thank you neighbor
I was actually I was just reading your
Super Chat no you're sending me another
one
massage fund let's go
anyway let me let me read some projects
oh my God let me read some pictures
guys thank you thank you but stop stop
stop
may your neighbor
don't take your neighbor's wallet why do
you have your neighbor's wallet
orange well yeah
orange orange is better but
don't need those coins thank you man I
feel like a coin trash can now
please
I'll take them I'll take them beautiful
coins from all over the world I already
have so many currencies man I still have
like a lot of cash in Yen and I have
Korean Won and I have a US dollars I I
have so much money left over but I don't
change it when I leave the country
because I'm like I'll probably be back
to these countries
[Music]
so I'm just keeping it
um
thank you
but then I think when I went to America
last time I forgot that I still had
money from America
of course because it's been a year
and I didn't take it with me man
next time I need to remind myself to
check my little stash of foreign money
thank you guys thank you
thank you for the super chats you guys
should maybe buy new wallets I don't
know how old your wallets are but maybe
it's time for a new one
these wallets don't seem very reliable
[Music]
well okay I have to go back to the
current super chats guys
membership ad for sure
[Music]
what
I'll get to you guys
one day
um
this recipe chat is for free things your
new outfit is amazing I love it so much
thank you as a celebration that I gotta
rise in salary so I will throw more
money here thank you congratulations too
must mean that you have worked really
hard for it and that is amazing
and your new Cohan she seems to love you
a bit also I got my ticket for the
summer let's go whole life summer
concert let's go
I have quite a few appearances so I
think it will be worth it for for kfb
um
Eric no
[Music]
no no
silly to buy that
as long as you don't buy in five minutes
before the concert
um daytime and night time yeah I'm in
both I think there's
most of me and the
the first one
I think
because of Tony and theme song
is in the first one
um
[Music]
but on the second one I have lusak and
second day I guess the second day is
only USA can
but if there's any other reason you want
to watch it as well then maybe also
Worth to check it out yeah
yeah I'm on both days did you not know
Kiana
who knew that I'm not licking it that
was public information as far as I know
um
probably should we say what was it
supposed to say
[Music]
as Grant you have so many appearances ah
you mean you want to watch this thank
you yeah I I'm happy that I got included
it's very lucky because it's not like we
did anything with us again for a long
long time and still I'm luckily included
because they felt like they needed to
revive us again for this concept
hahaha
you know it pays off when you're part of
like some kind of
social grouping when you involve
yourself
in uh whole life as a whole
this is proof that it pays off
having a click or two
um
I want to say that to my co-host I mean
even if you're not they want to they
will want to include you so uh they will
do their best to force you into a unit
but if you're in a unit then then you
know
then you may get more appearances than
others like let's say you're not in any
clicks any units
then you may only get like one
performance or so or two and then if you
are in some Universe then maybe you're
lucky you get free or so oh yeah yeah
and there is a write it down write it
down
um
I mean
yeah
maybe you can Implement yourself
somewhere into something or you could
even join us again
or or any other we could make a new
construction company anyway because we
wanted to
do that uh
uh well was it stop was it the stop
group
stunk stunk that's what it was
stunk Guild
it's more of a guilt and a Construction
Group I suppose but yeah
[Music]
yeah we haven't done anything I'm
I honestly I felt like it was to be
expected
um it didn't really seem very realistic
to me either
even though we had fun together but you
know
uh
[Music]
maybe back in the day when Minecraft was
overall more popular maybe then it would
have been more
something proper
[Music]
um
yeah
well yeah good to be in some units for
these kind of occasions I really really
like when I was told oh you're in you're
in this and you're in this but you're
also in this I'm like
second you're Reviving us again
oh okay think of them part of you
let's go
[Music]
um
so yeah let's go El Canal we have a
thank you for the rest of the chat and
for you know supporting All Of Me all of
what I do and again big congratulations
on your rights let's go Phoenix Rising
no chicken Rising
um
[Applause]
soon
silver
surgeon for the pinky now I am hybrid
Phoenix what a time span of kiwawa and
you know not a slightest regret I have
so many things in my mind right now but
I want to say only you are super duper
or sometimes you love my turkey come
here
I'm dorky and my dorky I guess I'm a bit
dorky sometimes
it's okay I don't mind being dorky um
Doki is dorky is nice I like dorky look
it's funny dorky is cute
a dorky I don't want to be a dorky
[Music]
I just want to find Doria keys not be a
dorky
[Music]
if I was a door key I would have been
able to open my own door when I locked
myself out wouldn't I
so I'm not really that dorky am I
but it hasn't happened for a long time
me locking myself out
[Music]
and this is why you're dorky what I just
said
um
[Music]
knocked on wood for me thank you
now you have the problem of smoothie
opening the door yeah
now I'm I'm I have made a habit for me
to to
lock the door from the inside to
nowadays
because
of that one time she did it while I was
possibly while I was streaming or while
I was on a call afterwards
not sure when exactly it happened but
she did open it
little man
and she always looks
so curiously at the door makes me
anxious I can't trust her anymore and
even when I leave uh my apartment to
like go by groceries or whatever
uh I'd like to worry that she will open
it even in this short amount of time now
even though like
it's always been a bit fine
but now
with anything really
[Music]
um
unbelievable anyway thank you so much so
Sergio for your sweet kindness I love
you too thank you you are the best
chocolate Insomniac signs
and cute cat
black virgin Nike
perm so I don't care about losing them
no I have to go back one time at least
one time mental Jetty
Black Version
[Music]
I mean I know
but
I know I know the star rating I know
what it's for but like for a while
though father of Hotel they also need to
upkeep certain standards that they make
up for themselves as a company so
yeah comparing it to the other Waldorf I
went to and also considering the fact
that it should be better than a Hilton
[Music]
the quite
disappointing yeah
yeah very disappointing wow wow
thinking back on it
oh don't even get me started yeah ah
um
and I love how you guys were first like
oh my gosh she's a Karen oh my God she's
a Karen but the more stories I told you
the more you finally agreed with me then
oh okay okay she she's right there this
hotel was kind of bad ah
wobbly water and fake eggs
incapable of making me some decent
normal fresh scrambled eggs how hard
could it be
I was so right like the fact that the
whole pool was moldy and the wallpaper
was scraping off everywhere it's just
very questionable
[Music]
next time I think I want to go to like a
boutique hotel
foreign
[Music]
Hotel
pool area
even if it's not their own even if it's
third party organized
this is not like no that's not
acceptable
you're planning on going back to London
but sometime because I gotta watch the
six Musical
and and
I possibly I sent gura the picture of
the Peppa Pig
afternoon tea I didn't even look up the
info but she did she sent me pictures of
the Peppa Pig afternoon tea and it looks
really cute and it would have probably
been more worth it than the afternoon
tea that I did
Peppa Pig
um
and she was fascinated by it
I told her I thought of you when I saw
this bus and I I quickly brought out my
phone to quickly take a picture of the
Peppa Pig Bus Plus Peppa Pig plus no bus
um
Peppa Pig
[Music]
as a fellow expert what did narissa say
about the hotel experience I don't know
you heard the whole story
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
look at those beautiful clouds moving in
the background oh my God
I love watching clouds move
I love focusing on them and then
realizing oh they move so fast damn
where was I
well where the was I
um
[Music]
Peter campy
peppers
over overcoming me
Peter can't be dancing
[Music]
we should review hotels like Gordon
Ramsay oh that would be fun
mental jelly dungeon but it doesn't
sound very realistic Tony D G H uh xss
mental daily
our tour guide to Loch Ness was
basically a streamer told us tangent is
an obscure historic facts about Scotland
and royalty for hours as he drove us can
recommend
sounds like you are the most excited
about the drive to Loch Ness
[Music]
sounds like it was a long drive where
you got told a lot of stories though
[Music]
Again Tour gate tour guide made it but I
can't read anymore
10 hour tour
five hours there no way you
drive five hours there you look at it
and then you go back for five hours no
no
I don't think that's worth it best with
speaker
it's a cool Lake I have plenty of
beautiful cool lakes in Austria
we stop at many sides along the way okay
but wow 10 hours that's really long
[Music]
but I like driving tours in fury because
I'm also too lazy to walk so yeah
good stuff
random collusions
one toast bread with little cream cheese
please
that will be uh 75 pounds please
[Music]
yeah
endless of that toast bread with cream
cheese
oh wait
wait the mouth oh my God oh my God oh my
God reflection no wait it's dollars
dollars
dollars even that's more than pounds I
think is it
uh thank you I will deliver the toast
bread with little cream cheese
right away
oh the other way around oh well I'm
confused
because of that ripoff thank you thank
you thank you honestly I should have
checked the price first but I didn't
expect it to be that expensive I thought
maybe okay maybe 40. 30 I don't know
[Music]
um
because I went to a lot of afternoon
teas in Japan and they never seemed that
expensive even at really expensive
hotels I guess in Japan you just get
more for
your money better value and they really
love
afternoon tea like making special
afternoon teas
really special it's always themed after
the season of certain fruits and this
and that I think Japan is just so great
at doing stuff like that
foreign
also like the the strawberry buffets
like so many hotels have like in
strawberry season they have strawberry
buffets and if it's not strawberry
season they maybe have like
some other themed endless buffets with
like endless endless
desserts
that are like so visually pleasing
um
yeah
I love that in Japan there's just like
so many cute cafes where there's so much
effort being put into the looks the
presentation and the taste
of what you're getting your self so
I've been to like
millions of all-you-can-eat buffets in
Japan
[Music]
yeah it feels like every every like
nice hotel in Japan has its own
Buffet thing going on or afternoon tea
yeah here in Austria I feel like this is
not really so much a thing there may be
some
hotels that have like an afternoon team
but really I I I I don't think so
[Music]
the most dedicated really
you went with me for also before mine
yeah yeah and that's just like two times
out of a million times
um
even the cheap one
um is called sweets Paradise I think
whole life Maybe
had something with done before I don't
know
whole life had something with every
everything before but even Sweet
Paradise is like really good that's the
cheapest one and even that place is
really good
sweet Pala sweet Para if you want to go
eat lots of sweet stuff but also have
like maybe a little bit of pasta and
pizza or whatever for cheap price all
you can eat
in in Tokyo or wherever in Japan you can
check out the sweet para Sweet Paradise
but you know it's the cheapest there is
so
it's maybe not as good as other places
but it's really good I I enjoy it every
time
[Music]
note it
is the pasta and pizza I think so like
they keep on making new ones it's
usually like a choice of two uh pastas
and pizzas different ones and when
they're out they often make a different
one and then you know they ring a bell
to let you know that a new serving is
finished
for
everybody so everybody goes gets the
fresh pizza or pasta
man I want to go again
actually I could go to the more
expensive place for some for some reason
I want to go to sweets Paradise now
[Music]
pasta it's one of my favorites
like cheap quick meals to make with some
cherry tomatoes
[Music]
so check it out if you're ever there
you don't like sweets
well that's maybe not the smartest
Choice then but have fun
[Music]
thank you
motion Tank Engine uh np154 in San
Francisco is horribly managed mismanaged
by the local government
not even safe to walk up the street from
a hotel what
if I was getting mugged at night what
really
I've been thinking back
when I was in San Francisco for a really
short time I only took taxis I think so
but really I have like a friendly image
of San Francisco yeah
scary
not really that bad in most places I'm
still scary though man I mean I'll be
honest to you guys as an European
America scares me as a whole
the chance that someone has a gun seems
very high so that scares the out of
me
so
I I would be very scared to upset
someone
and even if you don't upset someone it
can go wrong
maybe if somebody's just in a mood so
very scary
as an American America scares me as well
[Music]
pasta
yeah that one's good too but I like as
little chili as possible on that please
[Music]
I've been mined in Germany bad stuff
everyone yeah but
chances of being shot
I think are way lower in Austria Germany
than in America let's be real come on
uh
I like to keep the risk of dying really
low okay as low as possible I'm glad I
can't like I what can't happen to me is
so many things like
many many
car accidents can't happen to me unless
a drive a car drives into me
walking on the street
or like nightclub getting my drink
I've heard of that happen
so many times sheesh
that will also never happen to me
happened to a friend of mine even
in Japan though
[Music]
um
I don't drink and I don't go to clubs so
this will not happen to me
gotta keep everything
really really
low low percentage of dying
straight edge let's go
you went to Brazil Brazil is America's
PVP Zone yeah when I was in in Brazil
everybody around me warned me to not go
outside alone
and yeah that is not safe and I said I
want to go to the beach I want to go to
the beach and they kept on telling me I
don't know about that
yeah and I wasn't allowed to go anywhere
alone when I was in
um Sao Paulo
[Music]
um but it was fine like you know
I had a good time
it didn't seem that unsafe to me but you
know I was I was accompanied by
Brazilian people
[Music]
um
yeah yeah
[Music]
there's this place in Sao Paulo that has
all these like wall murals
like graffiti
for
like a really really long long long
Street and then it separates also into
more streets that place was really cool
people love to take pictures there like
Instagram pictures
um
what a nice view right
when locals tell you not to go somewhere
it's a good idea to listen to them yeah
yeah
but I just like I really wanted to go to
a beach I I didn't go in the end but I
was just really desperate because like I
I don't think I have seen a beach in a
long time at that point and
foreign
yeah that's what it's called I guess I I
never understood why it had the name
Batman in it
why did it have the name Batman there
was nothing Batman related Becco told
Batman
the Batman alley yeah Batman is
nicknamed for the area around
in the Villa madalena neighborhood of
Sao Paulo Brazil because of Batman is a
popular tourist destination because of
the dance concentration of graffiti that
line okay but why is it called pekko the
Batman
Flawless really
I don't know how to say that that
it's like two cute ooze
or
is that how you say it
[Music]
um
Batman's parents
let me see some some places must say why
[Music]
the nickname for the area is attributed
to a graffiti of the DC Comics character
Batman which was painted on one of the
walls okay so maybe that was like the
first one
in the 1980s local art students began
filling the walls with other psychedelic
and Cubist influenced designs
[Music]
it's now continually renovated and
carried before by local community
members yeah it was it's really big and
there were some really cool graffitis
there
like I'm generally not a fan of graffiti
if it's like randomly on on you know
random buildings where it shouldn't be
on but if it's in a concentrated place
like this
then hell yeah
where people can do some really creative
stuff and honestly I noticed I'm
thinking back right now I remember when
I was like driving through Sao Paulo I
saw like many other buildings too that
were like professionally looking
graffitied
like really really beautiful big murals
on big ass walls but it didn't bother me
like it did does like in other places
where it's just like
ugly looking
scribbles and
um
so that stood out to me it wasn't only
this alley it was like generally all
over Sao Paulo I felt like I saw
beautiful graffiti making the streets
and the buildings really really colorful
all over
um
there was a commission sometimes I could
see that yeah those were probably
commissions the big ones that I am
thinking of right now
you see Annie in L.A nothing stood out
to me I honestly I don't think I walked
around much in LA in the first place
many many taxi rides I think mostly
the one time I really walked much was
when me and Ahmed went to Taco Bell I
think that was the most I've walked
um
you can't really walk in L.A you should
never walk
yeah
yeah yeah I drove around a bit my friend
who has a car drove me around
me to the beach
that was fun even though the beach was
ugly
[Music]
thank you
but that was really cool man man sling
is fun I want to travel make more
memories
and the beach was ugly and I think we
kind of I don't think I ever told you I
think we were like illegally in there
because I I remember us like we parked
the car somewhere and then we kept on
walking walking and there was like
endless fence where we couldn't get in
it was like all private I think
yeah and then
pretty sure
[Music]
that where we ended up at was still kind
of private yeah but there were so many
people there
so many
I don't think people really cared
um
Smooth Criminal
[Music]
but I'm not 100 sure but it felt like it
because it felt I think I remember
feeling bad feeling nervous
yeah
yeah but it was really crowded and
um not very pretty if it really was a
private beach then it was really not
that pretty for being private
[Music]
please be nice
I'm not sure I'm not honestly not sure
maybe it was just on the memory of me
walking past so many private beaches and
I'm being like what the what the
what the why are these all
private let us in and then finally
founding a normal one I don't know I
really don't remember anymore but yeah
it wasn't it wasn't pretty but the food
was yummy that we ate at the beach
though
um
I barely went into the water
yeah I remember
because it was hot Pleasant
it was not pleasant
I kept on my friend made me film her
Tick Tock videos endlessly
the the whole I feel like the whole time
80 percent
of what we were doing is filming her
Tick Tock video
I felt a bit embarrassed
because like man I don't have that
courage I respect the courage but if
only I could have that courage like she
would get up in the middle of this
really crowded Beach and start doing
Tick-Tock dances and I was filming it
and then she watches it and she's like
unhappy with it so we have to do it
again and again and again man
yeah
because she was a perfectionist too so
first take no no no never first tank
yeah
[Music]
would you do those dances I mean I've
learned
like maybe two Tick-Tock dances in my
life before because I was forced to
um by friends who are into tick tock
not out of my own well
yeah seven Forest
[Music]
um
did you learn that Bible do you
challenge fans oh my God so good
uh
treasure box is a tick tock dance I
guess no from not for me
in the end her main platform is YouTube
um
[Music]
no no I don't think she cared much about
people in the background the things she
wanted people in the background but uh
yeah the lightning the lightning was an
issue the problem is that the sun is
like blasting in your face
well difficult to get good lightning and
the usually usually when you're at an
ocean
unless you have like golden hour or
something a lot of the most of the time
of the day it'll be to take
pictures at the ocean
because sun is like
right in your face
shut up
and and you'll be squinting and you'll
have shadows hard harsh contrasts
everywhere it's so difficult to take
pictures at the beach unless you're a
professional photographer and you have
maybe
um like a like a a lightbox thingy with
you or you have a reflector but the
reflector is even more rough on the
model because it will make you squint
even more
um
shut up yeah but yeah it's so difficult
to take breaches at the beach best time
is Golden hour for pictures at the beach
yeah
just random knowledge I picked up
somewhere I don't know how where weird
stuff I know I am random knowledge you
know I should be part of uh one of those
millionaire quiz shows because of all
that random knowledge that I have
[Music]
could make it
gotta be lucky with some good questions
uh hi from
fructose San Diego oh I think I heard
good things about San Diego
Martin ain't thanks for the pink
exciting news of the Pokemon unite
tournament and another special design
from the fourth card choco said
true there was something like that this
post travel that the students are always
great glad to have you back Pizza tawa
this week should be interesting don't
worry it's fun uh it was fun until I was
chased down
by that monster
[Music]
San Diego
uh when you eggle waffle falls on the
sand sand
no um
golden hour is honestly the best time to
take pictures anywhere though not just
on this on the beach yeah
yeah oh no my eggo anyway uh thank you
Martin eight thank you
yeah lots of exciting things were going
on I and it will continue because now
it's album time and then it's uh
anniversary time
and yeah I know I talked to you guys
about having a vacation but this whole
month just I don't know I I was really
like sick of vacationing after London
and Japan twice so
I didn't want to go anywhere so soon
who knows maybe maybe in September after
the anniversary
could work
[Music]
um
yeah but for now I'm busy and for now I
don't want to go anywhere anywhere no
same person still up for it I will make
her up for it
I will make her up for it yes staycation
yes stay occasion let's go
[Music]
did you decide on something for the
anniversary more or less I think
um
I I think I'll be doing like a
combination of
Vlogs that
are I'm like kind of making a quest for
myself
to fulfill certain quests with these
Vlogs yeah
but
yeah stay tuned for it
I'm cooking I'm cooking
I'm cooking I I hope it will go well
[Music]
yeah I might need some help with editing
looks at K of pre Clippers wink wink
wink
[Music]
wink wink wink wink wink wink wink
yeah yeah help me help me
don't you want to help me for my
anniversary please
lp153
thanks for the pinky and thanks for
serving as a great podcast while driving
to work yada some very enjoyable stories
in there right also here's the money
back for your tea time
at least by today's conversion rate
thank you
thank you very much thank you soon
[Music]
I watched like a video
speaking of driving I watched this video
of
um police body cam
uh
arresting this lady influencer some
blonde influencer lady who fell asleep
uh at night at a traffic light big
traffic light maybe you saw it too uh
and holy like first she doesn't
wake up endlessly and there's they're
just like knocking endlessly and she
keeps on like like a zombie like looking
at them and look confused and they're
screaming
she just doesn't open the door and she
keeps on falling back asleep like it
takes such a long time for her to wake
up
and then she's being
oh my God entitled as
yeah
after after she finally gets out because
they opened the door
it's like oh my God
so painful to watch and fun at the same
time
my God
[Music]
ah
yeah those are cases where I feel
bad for the cop and then there's other
cases where I feel bad for the driver
like I watched another one where there
was a teenager
who doesn't drink wasn't drunk wasn't on
drugs or anything
but was stopped and and then
they just wanted to pin something on to
him
and he did all the tests and whatever
and yeah
it was like I think 19 and and because
of his college sports team
he doesn't drink or anything they they
just they just because they started
something I understand the general
feeling like when you start something
and the other person proves that you're
wrong
because of your ego you still don't you
don't wanna you don't wanna admit you're
wrong you want to keep on digging your
hole deeper and deeper and deeper
yeah uh he did end up suing them and
then then they counter suit him
uh the counter swing thing was dropped I
think and his own thing
not sure I don't remember anymore
but I am
yeah in big ego is a big problem
did they have a swing it shut up
you love me too much that's why you're
making fun of me
nothing have a silly kid
sawing sounds stupid
[Music]
um
stewing sounds better
[Music]
whatever afterwards object
rest for for One Direction TV table
traduction
game 8910 don't look at my
point of weather well I can't look at
you I can't look at it because because
the whole laser doesn't link your
profile to me
I wish I
wish I could thank you soon Lord Hawk
999 Maple Leaf
for the pinky
oh man
Kiana I've had narissa as my co-host for
less than a week and if anything
happened to her I would add everyone in
this room edit myself
I don't know if I would be that dramatic
about it but I'm I'm I'm I'm
maybe a little bit passionate about
notice I had to hold myself back from
calling her last night because I had
work to do but I just felt this urge to
call her
but I successfully
held back can I eat some chocolate I
want to eat some chocolate
[Music]
before bringing up Brooklyn 99 I uh in
my last plane ride
I just didn't have anything that spoke
to me anymore uh in the in the like
media section TV section
and so I gave
um Brooklyn 99 another chance because
they had some episodes that were not the
first ones it was just like the middle
of somewhere maybe the first season
I watched some more and honestly
I think I liked them or it was the
middle of the second suit I'm not sure
but I liked them it was more tolerable
yeah
so I'm considering maybe watching the
full thing if I get through the first
painful ones where the dude pisses me
off
[Music]
um
it gets better
[Music]
yeah
or it was just me
enjoying it more because I was in a
situation where I had to enjoy it on the
plane stuck with nothing to do
now I don't think it was more funny
the episodes that I watched
um
[Music]
the office first season is not met
uh
[Music]
um
you're mad
hot text in the chat uh-huh
[Music]
it wasn't Matt you're just saying that
because afterwards it gets so much
better
alone
that it makes it hard to rate the first
season because everything afterwards is
even more better
hmm
[Music]
did you hear that
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah I got batteries
still didn't set it up though
[Music]
yummy
chocolate is so good
[Music]
foreign
okay
now I'm good
my urge has been satisfied I was a kid
in the country kinda country
[Music]
the one with the cereals inside
I'm on Peak tangent brain new thing so
remember today
hmm
okay
Lord
Maple now wait I read that one picture
of telephone the action wow beautiful
what a beautiful telephone
I I still remember Luna performing
Hajime denotsu and what was it second
fast or so that was so cute I would ever
remember that
thank you for the pinky I've been
watching nerissa but I don't know if I
could keep following her I'm getting too
jealous of her potential joke by the way
the dots are suspicious it's okay to be
jealous I mean that just proves how much
you love me I love you
hmm
you don't have to hide it
but you know
um
there's no need to be jealous because
it's just another another collab partner
but this one I'm getting along really
really
well with so
let's be happy for the Wawa let's all
just be happy for Wawa to have
someone
who make of her so happy
[Music]
thank you
um
thank you for the pinky hairs to making
it worse oh no what was it the Super
Chat backlog
nah nah you're making it better only
better the water option thank you Nathan
thank you so much you've said so many
pinkies you should get a kiss
free kiss extra
for free pinkies you get
it actually even for two pinkies you get
a kiss if they're too close together but
but but you sent so many I must give you
a kiss
[Music]
you take it nice
do I get one back hmm
here's my cheek
[Music]
hmm
Yahoo Yahoo
[Music]
thank you thank you oh my God so many ah
goodbye
ah
so many tutus oh no
help me help me I'm getting attacked by
all these chickens
okay calm down now calm down
Christy shaver thank you for Pinky with
like fire emojis and 10 out of 10 what
was this about is it when I was singing
for blood
foreign
[Music]
always so much fun to sing man
I love for blood
that was indeed on fire
[Music]
don't even don't even don't even get me
started
[Music]
space waterfall donations
I talked about this today Fonzy and yeah
I I think it's uh changing I think
they're changing though
culture a little bit thankfully
so I appreciate that sunscreen Junction
the game of creed
thank you everybody I finally finished
this I could have finished them way
earlier what the
man
okay we'll quickly read the pizza Tower
[Music]
the schedule
here is pizza Tower and the game I will
never play again
because it makes me salty
[Music]
sleeping early canceled no no not yet
not yet
um
I have to
[Music]
let me
add some people before I forget it
[Music]
and
um
[Music]
keeps on coming in and then flopping
down and then going on our back and
showing me her belly
no no she is demanding love
can I always give you enough
[Music]
wow you are so soft oh
don't run away
I wish you would get used to being held
she likes when I carry her around or
carry her around over my shoulder
but anything besides that she hates like
being
on my on my lap or so she hates that
so weird man I don't I'm good
[Music]
I'm good but the other night I fell
asleep like uh
in in not normal way that you fall
asleep on your bed like normally
what do you call it horizontally or so I
don't know with your feet at the end of
the
uh bed but I slept like but if that is
how do I describe it I didn't have my
yeah I guess vertically Maybe
because I was falling asleep while while
hugging uh
uh smoothie and yeah I fell asleep on my
stomach and I woke up soon after I think
because
he was lying sitting lying on my back
and meowing aggressively
but I loved that
it felt so funny to have smoothie on my
back just sitting there
asserting dominance over me
[Music]
yeah annoying little but it felt
nice having a cat on my back
I wish she would do it more often but
not just to annoy me
just just to be there hmm
[Music]
no he wasn't giving me a massage he was
just asking me to wake up to give her
food
you tend to send super chats twice and I
think they're going through twice on my
side
[Music]
and they're always the same message are
you okay
YouTube is ripping you off man
be careful with your super chats
[Music]
yeah it does look like it's going
through twice on my side
I don't know if you can undo it but
hmm
super Bailey Duncan
[Music]
it's your game of the year what the
I guess I was talking about
using your music for my
anime thingy is that why you were
reacting I think so
foreign
[Music]
for the pinky the game reminds me of 90s
cartoons here's an idea why don't you do
a lot along of weird 90s cartoons like
Rocco's Modern Life what the is
that and Ren and stimuli
not the whole series but episode strap
no no
no no no no no no I'm not interested no
no no you can get me to watch more anime
with you guys
on stream I will do that
I'm not gonna watch some old cut oh it
looks funny though it looks funny I just
looked at brocco's Modern Life this
never made it over to
Austria oh wait it's on Netflix is it on
Netflix
it might not be in Austin Netflix though
because
um
I've never seen it on Austrian Netflix
before
and often we have other shows
than you guys
[Music]
um
Naruto no no
[Music]
no
it was on German TV what
well I don't think it was very popular
then
oh but I love how the dog sits move the
legs up that looks cute oh
the dog is funny
is what is the owner supposed to be
is the owner
[Music]
a wallaby
these characters look so funky
right now thank you
oh
I'm glad you guys enjoyed it the connect
the world updated footage
is not available anymore right
I think I only watched
um The Myth performance I didn't even
watch my own because I was like too
too
I don't know I didn't want to see it
I know what is the end because I was
worried
that it wouldn't
um the night wouldn't look so good
no I hope you guys enjoyed the dough
yes coward showed at me
a mystery cut I thought I had another
day oh my God
oh silly
silly silly
[Music]
much better in the Recon really
um
good good to hear that
it's good that we did that hmm
yeah Scarlett that because you're
looking for the top Duncan First pen
dungeon
again
don't look at my profile picture and
I'm a chat we love you Kiara thank you
oh my God so many hearts
wait
wait I have the perfect outfit on today
it's back to you unknown thank you thank
you thank you
oh my God I'm turning into newer summer
[Music]
thank you thank you soon
mm-hmm
hearty hearty hearty heart heart heart
hearty hearty hearty hearty heart heart
heart
do you need anything
Jeff the feeling
oh
[Music]
do not worship the penguin only worship
the Phoenix
soon
oh yours came in double as well
that's weird
Expo 77 thank you for the rest of that
hey attention there's this new game
called Ballers gate free it's game a
game based off DND in a game you can
create your character like in a Sims you
can play a single player all with
friends
personally I think it's a fun game to
stream and you would enjoy it
we're planning on it as you probably
know by now
can you play together like from the very
very very very beginning of the game
or do you have to get through like
certain parts alone
[Music]
I just waiting for the worms
there's nudity
um
Works a bit weird sometimes
yeah I'm curious like whenever a
non-mmrpg says they have multiplayer I'm
almost like okay how how why we how
is that gonna work how where how and
what what's it what how
so thank you Expo please look forward to
when we are hopefully at some point
finally playing Builders gate together
enjoy
no I mean I understand the co-op in
theory but like I I I want to know like
how it's hard to explain what I mean
with how
like
how you know how how
but I I whatever
Chase Mick Jenkins
and tea
tea for the pinky you pile plus one
you
[Laughter]
you I remember that
that was all of pizza that way I'm gonna
leave now and I'm gonna
um prepare
for the whole Toy stream
and
and yeah actually I have to get up
probably more like at 8 00 am
the stream is at 9am and we probably get
together half an hour before
um
then I also might want to eat some
breakfast before and take some time to
get up and take some time
yeah
so I will go eat now and prepare holiday
Studio
and then I'll see you guys and the whole
story stream in
10.
I love eleven ten and a half hours maybe
I don't know something like that foreign
[Music]
yeah
would be nice because there was a lot of
fun making so much money
[Music]
um
thank you bye bye bye bye
[Music]
foreign
again
[Music]
she's uh killing a bug
eating it
[Music]
not even really a bug it's like a tiny
tiny tiny tiny fly
[Music]
I think it has any nutrients
foreign
[Music]
looks like it
good for you
good for you smoothie
[Music]