[Music]
id
attention please i'm pavolia rainey from
whole life id second generation
[Music]
zero no no generation we don't have
generation
no generation okay and
we are
hey
and now we are going to be
playing untitled
goose game together
[Music]
it's been such a long time since i
played this game it's very nostalgic to
me
oh yeah it was i think was it your first
collaboration
with it it was my first collaboration
with super senpai
but also my first collaboration with the
japanese senpai
in general like after the after the
collab band was lifted
so that was just so so special to me
and now i'm playing this with you so
you've been
you're you're the pro now you're the pro
now right
[Music]
language oh wait you're super close to
uh 400k oh yeah i am i am too
yay kf
kfp chickens who are here right now who
are not sub
to lena yet subscribe now
thank you
so today we play this game and and
and and we we finally um have some time
to talk together again
yeah so yeah
i think we start out by going to that
dude's garden
oh okay
where is back which button
on it on it oh i found it okay
okay okay um okay so we have to
get into the garden okay you ready you
read the list please
okay to do first get into the garden
get the ground keeper wet steal the
groundskeeper's keys
may the groundskeeper wear his sun hat
ooh sun han
i have a sun head wait a second
[Music]
okay
you can match with the groundskeeper and
we got my sunglasses too
oh fancy oh now
she's ready and now we have rake in the
lake
and then we have a picnic bring to the
picnic blanket so many things basically
we gotta have a picnic all right do we
have to do this all
yes yes okay
we have you so we'll be fine we stop by
going in here right yeah
is it is it locked is it locked
oh i can zoom out uh lawnmower
i can honk at the lawnmower
that will help
wait a second wait a second how do you
how do you grab things again i forgot oh
maybe i'm doing something
i think i'm doing something yes knock
everything over do it
yes yes
oh i'm grabbing that i'm growing the
thing oh
look at this i'm doing something
i'm doing something ah well that doesn't
help but yeah good job then
okay thank you i think i think uh
wait uh how do you dash against i
forgot everything i just learned
20 minutes ago
i think we had to do something oh my
gosh
oh yeah that's how he opens it up
because he
doesn't like the radio players
nice what was the next thing get him
wet oh get his keys okay
i remember some of these things okay um
no
you i don't think you have to do them on
order no no no
you gotta oh no he's gonna kill you
because you got the carrot
[Applause]
there's the sun hat um
but i think let's let's try to make him
wet first how did we do that again
something with that
ah what the hell something with the turn
can you turn that on how do i press how
do i
oh i think the the knob is outside
i
i have an idea you stay there okay okay
i'll make some
i know i know what i'll do i will
i will i think he reacted to the
carrot right yeah if we steal the carrot
and you bait him to the
thingy the the place where the water is
we can make him wet i forgot how to pick
up things
maybe what what are you using
the playstation controller on it out
there
[Applause]
now we're gonna be smart and steal his
keys
give me strength okay
[Music]
commander how
do we steal his keys well
she's kind of like stealing from his hip
oh okay can we not grab him yes yes we
can
yes we can just gonna be
oh wait he was just about to
crouch to
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
oh that's the carrot oops wrong thing
nice run away run run run run
maybe throw it into the river oh yeah
into the lake i should do that i should
do that let's throw it into the river
okay but i think the mission is still
completed yeah yeah rip river okay
i i know how to make him wear the hat
the thing is he's already wearing a hat
so we have to make him crouch and in the
moment where he
goes down we can steal his current hat
okay
and then you might think about wearing
the new hat you're so cute with that
camera in your mouth
so cute camera but maybe not the pirates
he has to be on the ground a bit longer
on our level maybe
what if i do this
i'm stealing the flower and he doesn't
even realize ah i think wasn't that
that was one of the no no that one
yeah i thought there was something with
the rose as well
what what i don't know
didn't he just look at it no he's
looking at cabbages
he doesn't know
oh he doesn't i feel do we feel bad no
we don't feel bad about this
[Music]
straw hats are much better trust me
what can we do what can we do can we do
ruin his life
wait next thing what if i turn on this
thing
will he turn it off oh oh oh he come to
turn it off
maybe maybe come here
come here i i didn't mean you would do
it but
yeah yeah yeah yeah you can come too
okay okay okay
totally probably not suspicious that two
gooses
these geese are a feeling here
oh you want to fill that up is that
possible oh my god it might be
is it steal hats steal hats come here
i know you i'm not i'm your finger
[Music]
how can we make him crouch maybe we make
him plant the
carrot no
[Music]
make some trouble in any case make some
[Laughter]
traffic
so we gotta throw this in the lake this
yeah yeah okay well let's
until he walks somewhere else yeah and
then yeah
secretly
distract them
i'm i'm gonna take you out quickly
[Music]
seems to have a priority
[Laughter]
[Music]
it was in there for half a second
just to dip in the water
oh okay okay and
picnic the picnic was really difficult
oh man
we should try to try that one the head's
still first
okay okay okay but how wow how to make
him crunch
maybe maybe if when when maybe when he
plants something
wait where did you put the flower oh was
i not supposed to do that in the water
let me let me grab that
oh and then you plant the flower back
oh yeah when it's not too far away i
guess he'll see it and then
plant it smart some monsters
[Laughter]
i'm in position i'm in transition
okay
[Music]
don't you see me i got your keys
okay we have to do it again okay let's
do it again
i got something in my eye oh yeah
okay okay um
that was intense um
i got something in my eye oh are you
okay are you okay
okay baby i'm gonna steal the flag i'm
gonna steal the flower first
okay okay there
okay no wonderful
she doesn't look no this he doesn't
notice hey
and then oh okay this time i'll try to
steal the hat
you saw it
[Music]
i took the wrong thing
okay now
okay okay
i'll take off oh his super priority is
the hat
you're back
he's back okay flower again flower again
at the moment momenta oh oh the keys the
keys are there now
ah well i guess we have to leave the
keys on the ground now
so that he'll do the flower thing first
yeah
and then once the hat fills the keys
okay
i i can i can i can try to steal the
[Laughter]
okay
no i
okay okay okay okay i put the flour in
here
ready for you to put back
plants please
this one dana is getting a little bit
angry and we have we have to be a little
bit aggressive you know
that's what i learned that's true what
are you doing
sorry i need to need to to go to the
other side to get the keys
another one this time
i got the keys
[Music]
so close though so close though why why
why why it's so difficult
okay take this squash
arm right down one more time one more
time
this
what are you doing for a sun hat
no no no no
do i have to go well i got the keys
uh no i have to cry
i didn't have to i think sometimes i can
get it sometimes i can't
huh like you know you have you ever
wondered
like what this what did this man do to
deserve all this
he he deserved it alone because
humans suck because all the way
down i think i got the keys
run run run
run
[Music]
do that does the other hat have to be
close to him
was that it
[Music]
where is he in the water that's not fair
what the heck how can humans walk
well maybe maybe because his hat is wet
he'll take the other one
no it's already not dripping anymore
oh we can maybe dump it into a into a
trash can
oh wait hold on let me let me let me
scout for like a
trip you have to be really sneaky
really sneaky stealth 100 can we do that
yes can we do that okay let's see let's
see let's see what we can do
but your trash can here we have to hide
it somehow
hide it quick quick before he
before he looks i think if we if we
okay i think i think i think i think i
think there's this this
oh what if we watch this here what if we
put this here
and he doesn't know yeah when you run
through there
you won't know i think oh my god
i don't remember that spot uh when i
played with super senpai
okay okay we can do this final final try
finally try oh
[Music]
you can't do that when he can only do
that when he's planting the flower
if it's the key like he does he runs
into me it's not my fault
go away stupid old man
oh yeah he he got this yeah it's okay
already i think now he'll take the other
hat
come back here
oh yeah amazing
[Applause]
let's see how that oh new hat looks
gorgeous on ya
now you do match oh i don't want to mask
this guy i don't want to match with him
oh he's going to put up a sign that says
no giselle out
well you know what no signs
[Laughter]
the keys i'll get inside i'll put this
up
[Music]
again why would you do such a thing
the hammer is from that's an extra
mission oh
let's do that oh do we try to face
because that's the main
main mission okay let's get it difficult
so
we need uh apple pumpkin
sandwich carrots gem okay so probably a
lot of these things here
i'll take the jam apple do i need apple
but
but the thing is if when he notices oh
no he didn't notice anything
once he notices he'll like continuously
steal things that he already put there
and he will never get done like we put
one thing there while he
takes one another one back okay okay
let's put this here
we have we have to be fast wait wasn't
there a picnic blanket
okay wherever oh yeah we have to bring
it here
let's let's put them
okay for now oh no
we're doing this all in secret
no that's already enough oops okay
hey yeah
okay i'll take one i don't know
i don't know if we need two we'll take
two just because there's two of us
for two people or two
then what else yes yes two keys having a
little picnic do i need that too i'll
just bring it yeah
just maybe you will bring down the tea
the hot teeth
in the furnace
very very delicious pumpkin
carrot thermos radio radio as well
oh i think radio is gonna be last
because it makes a sound
mm-hmm
are you still cleaning up nice i i have
to go to you okay okay okay okay
because it's like the max amount of
zooming out i think
she should okay
yeah that's that's maybe before we take
the pumpkin we have to
make some other mess so he'll take care
of that um yeah
let's take out some more carrots um
and then just just like put it here
so that he'll look at some other things
[Music]
oh you're too far i can't go oh okay
i don't know we don't need another
carrot i just meant to make some mess so
that he gets distracted
ah maybe this one so he turns it up
okay okay you do that but now he's there
yeah we're doing nice now the drink and
the
radio maybe we can do it at the same
time one of us takes the drink and one
of us takes the radio
okay is that great yeah radio and therma
premise okay wait let's see
this looks way more difficult when i did
it with survivor senpai
it's because you're a pro now um which
one do you want the radio
yeah that's the radio okay i'll take uh
at the same time at the same time
i can only take the bottom do you want
me to take the radio
okay okay
[Music]
okay that's okay he can bring back the
radio for now we'll go
one at a time and then uh he'll i think
he'll put back the radio
and then we can take the third one yeah
okay
yeah a win for the geese
last one is the radio and then we will
be
good this is too easy
all right
[Music]
here's the radio okay
yes
yeah high five in our in my soul
nice
[Laughter]
okay so i guess we make the look we do
the last thing make the ground skip a
hammer his thumb
okay ah i saw the hammer uh
i forgot i guess for the for the sign
we'll like hammer it into the ground and
then we have to
come home oh and then he'll be fire
yeah hey hammer
hey hammer
oh
okay what is he doing he's putting it
back he's just tidying
stuff up you do do this you do
[Music]
we're helping you we're helping you get
your sign
oh oh okay
okay now he used to hammer okay
oh too early okay okay
sorry
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
we're moving to a different place right
now
double trouble second episode
[Music]
there's soccer let's play soccer oh this
place oh there was a lot to do here
hello i remember that oh we can't ah
here you have to be like on the tv okay
so the
the new to-do's please read again
break the broom trap the boy in the
phone booth
make the boy wear the wrong glasses make
someone buy back their own stuff
get on tv go shopping put in the basket
toothbrush
a little paper hairbrush something
something food cleaner fruit vegetables
okay easy okay
so we started with we tried to start
with the broom
break raise the broom where is it first
of all
where is it hi okay it's the boy
yeah that one's gonna be bullied a lot
you want you want to you want you watch
your toy you want your toy now you can't
have it you can't have it
you're already spot fooling him nice
nice
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
i think i have a bad connection now oh
no what's going on
you're getting you're not responding oh
i guess i'm still moving
on this on your screen yeah
it got it it's back it's back i have
like it's kind of like stopped
you broke it i'm good yes
never before i felt so happy for
breaking something
[Music]
yeah i am so proud of you i
apparently do have a talent in breaking
things amazing
no okay i should be encouraging this uh
because it's still
was that what we had to do steal them
maybe maybe seal them
what was it again uh uh uh what what do
you press to check the thing
uh maybe wear the wrong glasses maybe
put some other glasses there are there
any at the supermarket
maybe maybe maybe
i'm gonna stick those right right in
front of him
oh this lady is fierce this lady scary
lady
i'll help you okay
okay
[Music]
he's looking really sh he's really nice
now
and he's got style oh god saucy nice
look at this plane though
oh was that a was that a thing
no the plane doesn't matter it doesn't
matter okay sure
we can trap the boy in the phone booth
while we're at it
we could yeah
the phone booth is all the way over to
the left
okay uh how do we do that again
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay how
do we
how do we trap him in there we chase him
ah yeah we i mean he's he got he got
scared when we
hearted him see yeah
[Music]
i think we're ready wrong direction go
up go up
okay maybe we'll stop for now and then
he's going to go back
oh good we're we are peaceful geez
trust us
[Music]
[Applause]
because some somehow oh that was me
actually
somehow we have to be in here to be on
the tv i'm not sure how it works
oh okay uh
can we post any buttons in here here's
this button
hello we're here to buy a tv
oh yes yes yes it's me
we're famous mommy look
[Applause]
can
[Laughter]
[Music]
we did already a lot of things oh no
do you want to go shopping or make
someone buy their own stuff
let's yeah let's do that one first to
buy their own stuff i think oh look at
this
what about what about like glasses okay
it's the lady hey lady i got some stuff
for you
[Music]
it doesn't care about the glasses i kind
of want to make the lady like
maybe sell the glass the glasses
or maybe the toy plane was was that how
it worked
i don't know yeah yeah maybe put the toy
plane on the toy shelf
thingy maybe maybe and then when the boy
comes around he'll buy it maybe
maybe maybe but then he has to come out
of his
uh thing okay maybe we should stay away
first
and then okay no not the broom not the
broom
okay maybe if we leave the
[Music]
yes that is from your shop totally that
is
okay now what does he do
[Music]
it only costs lots of money
let's see let's see let's see what he
does
now while we're waiting for the boy
picnic picnic right we got to do the
picnic
just just chill for a moment and and
look at
look at the beautiful scenery and think
back
how do you feel after six months of
being being in home alive
wow this feels like a sudden pop quiz
what's wrong pop quiz
what did i learn i learned a lot
i felt like i don't know before whole
life i was a very
shy and reserved person you know and
then really
yeah i was i was and then i guess i met
you know
i learned a lot i met people like you
and then mostly
i now notice that i'm pretty much way
better at talking than i was before
that's great did you get used to it
yeah sort of sort of i feel like there's
always room for improvement you know but
i feel so much better right
oops poor boy
even when we're talking about something
not related to the game oh no he's
glasses again remember
yeah our first yeah like my first senpai
collaboration was with you
right and i think i was so so so quiet
ipm dear right like oh thank you so much
for like
all the you know you always bring up
like all the topics and everything
and you know i remember yeah yeah yeah
yeah what
what kind of projects or like games have
you been picking
up on recently recently oh i'm really
bad with her
so i think i'm you know trying to tackle
that fear and maybe i'm gonna try oh
really yeah i'm actually playing
resident evil village now
even though oh my god i hate horror
games too
but i don't really i don't really want
to tackle that fear so you
you're a bit more involved than me and
that matters
what about you like you you recently
reached like a million and you did
all the the endurance streams and do you
do you want to let me in on that little
secret how to have
how to have the power and your
of doing the three years
i don't i don't know like the one
problem that i have sometimes is like
that
uh especially in super chat readings
when they go on for too long that my
voice really hurts at some point
oh my throat but
recently in those 12 hour streams i was
actually surprisingly fine
two 12 hour streams back to vacuum but
the the the one thing that i noticed is
playing a game for long hours playing
only one game for long hours is much
more difficult than playing
several games like a marathon in 12
hours
so exactly actually it felt like nothing
those 12 hours when i was switching
between all kinds of different games and
also doing a karaoke in between was
actually really really manageable so you
could do it as well someday
oh i aspire to have an endurance as
strong as you
oh but what was the longest stream until
now um
it was like seven hours
minecraft i think i don't know what i
was doing even
[Laughter]
that's that's just normal stream time
for takanashikiya oh
i still have a long way to go then maybe
someday i will
have more power to be more
energy but no it's honestly okay i don't
i don't think
that is it's not necessary to stream for
seven or 12 hours really
i think it's gonna be fine to stream
like shorter hours that's okay
it's okay but you know what like
sometimes we forget right we forget the
time because we're having
so much fun especially when i'm talking
like i used to say that i'm super shy
but then like once i do free talk
streams
they just go on and on and i can't stop
talking
yeah i get that that's the biggest one
it comes
natural for some things when it's fun it
just comes natural
all right i still don't know how to do
this uh
buy something back i think we did it
right but the boy he doesn't react to
them
toy anymore he forgot we gotta bring him
to the shop maybe we're gonna like
scare him so that he runs to the shop
and then he
really happens that he has the
that was fast yeah that was really fast
oh no it's not over there no no
no no it's on the other side it's not
there
it's in the shop oh oh maybe he's he's
doing a detour
what is that what is happening i can't
walk
i think i'm having a problem right now
but it will probably
fix itself against oh
i think he's gonna buy it isn't he
are you still having problems uh yes
he's buying it great okay i wanna be
in the front seat for this i'm broken
yeah you look at it i'm just gonna be
here in the background
oh no actually oh no i know i can move
okay
great great yeah maybe maybe maybe maybe
your goose doesn't have enough you know
stamina for sports you know
it needs to evolve into a phoenix
okay so oh i already put thin food into
the basket so now we need to put in
hair brush toothbrush toilet paper
cleaner fruit and
vegetable okay so basically everything
basically toothbrush
maybe uh i i start by putting in the
toothbrush in the hair brush and you
also put
in like two things okay i'll put the
fruits i think
i think fruits is very easy ah oops
[Music]
while the lady is there i'll try to okay
maybe i think we should put the shopping
bags uh somewhere that is like
secluded so that she doesn't really pass
it
yeah i think okay i'll bring it
somewhere
that's like oh yeah maybe there works
too
okay let's file away yeah that's i'll
leave it here
and i'll get the fruits and veggies
oh i i can't i guess i can get toilet
paper here
we throw around so many things
it's all behind here i don't know what
is what same
i don't know i was wearing glasses oh
i'll come to you
[Music]
oh okay okay she's confused again she's
confused great great
great great great we're doing this
go from the other side from the other
side
i'm still fighting with this lady okay
she doesn't like me
[Music]
no no no no don't dance okay
i look yummy i know that i got those
chunky legs i know i know
i know they look really yummy yummy
yummy
i can't that wasn't really necessary but
i'm bringing a dollop baby doll so we
can have a baby together
yay baby we have all the necessary stuff
for the baby even though the baby is
bald we can get oops oops
even though the baby is bald we can give
him a hairbrush
okay wonderful we'll be great parents
bird family parents even though the baby
is human but you know it's all alive
things like that happen
and what else
uh where is the cleaner
a cleaner what does that mean with
cleaner
oh i'm getting veggies okay
[Music]
you're slowly waddling to the basket i'm
sorry i'm enjoying the view
okay no problem no problem can you
find the oh tomato
oh i thought this was an apple oh what
oh we already did that one you don't
need any more
cleaner and toothbrush i didn't see a
toothbrush though
toothbrush
i think we like there's so many things
that we messed up
low-key regretting what is that what is
this
is there is there more is there more uh
no as far as i know not that's why you
continue to the next level but wait
wasn't there something in the trash can
you had a cleaner and i guess the
toothbrush must be here too which is
disgusting but okay
okay yeah i found it oh okay great
we can bring these together then okay
that's the toothbrush
we gotta go together yes
sneaky sneaky sneaky sneaky
[Music]
yes everyone don't get you cleaner and
toothbrushes from the
uh trash can not not very hygienic
yeah special yes
yes
[Music]
you say that but how do we do it no we
gotta we gotta we gotta we gotta like uh
we're gonna like bait her to like like
like just puts her stuff
here like put literally everything here
and then you just
close it i think i think
okay let's like just get literally
everything oh you know this you know it
is nice
get that leak leak
okay okay and then she's gonna get the
leak after this i think she's gonna get
the leak okay
and then we're just gonna lay here we're
closing it
okay
don't you realize you're missing a leak
don't you realize that woman
do you not realize you forgot about
it maybe maybe steal something in front
of her nose again yeah exactly
and then yeah i'm gonna dash oh oh no
oh no i don't want him i know what sorry
sorry nina i have to
sacrifice you sorry
it's for a good cause sorry i didn't
have time
i have to do it there's another door i
can go outside from here
can you really go oh
it's okay you sacrificed me for the
greatest but i am
safe i thought i was gonna lose yeah
you take a walkie-talkie so we can
always talk to one another even when
we're falling apart
how romantic look i have the blue one
you have the yellow one kind of orangey
right
like oh yeah that fits our colors what
if we what if we hop
wait
[Music]
where do we go next um
where do we go next i don't know i think
we can go to the next level but
i think we have to go up here okay
probably oh
okay oh remember you love your
walkie-talkie how can you even hear me
now
um like because you're in front of me
don't worry and i can turn this thing
off
i didn't was this really the way oh no
oh do you know that way what did
you see here
oh
[Music]
i didn't know this place i didn't do
this one with somebody
oh yeah found a new one is it time for
someone
to read oh yeah but you know what you
kind of missed out on saying
before you read the list you could say
attention please oh all right
i'm going to do that right now and
attention please
two years ago make someone break the
fancy vase
help the woman dress up the bust make
the man spit out his teeth oh
why get dressed up with a ribbon make
the man go
barefoot do the washing with a pro pair
of socks slipper and borrow soap
nicer all right
okay oh oh i saw over to the other side
as well
also they're like neighbors so i think
like there's the man and the woman right
woman hey what's your face
shall we break how do we get those up
here ribbon
excuse me hey look my twins
i thought that wasn't here before i'm
not sure wait do we do something with
the painting
maybe it's my twin ribbon
no nothing moved to nothing with the
drag
how do we put it on you maybe can you
put it on me oh
okay okay
for you ah and no no
no
get dressed up with a ribbon it does
sound like we have to dress up ourselves
[Music]
no i think she noticed i think she
noticed
oh
[Music]
fake one than the real one i don't get
it
oh she fell down okay okay
i think we did it again i guess we gotta
distract her to go
somewhere and then i'll hide this okay
i'll take the brush
well she'll be distracted um
hey hey look at this brass beach
look at it okay okay okay okay
brush
more distance more distance okay i'll
leave you alone oh
wait i just break the vase oh yeah yeah
let's break the base how do i break the
vase
um can i drop it from somewhere
oh from like high up oh wait okay yeah
okay you're still i am
gonna steal the duck okay oh she's here
are you ready to be a fake geese okay
i'm hiding this right now i'm hiding
this and then i'm gonna post i'm gonna
post
it yes okay i'm closing okay post
pose like a model i hope she doesn't
notice that
oh
[Music]
i should probably put the vase back
first oh maybe put
put the ribbon near me put the ribbon
near me okay
let's do the vase first so she doesn't
okay let me just see if i can
bring the vase somewhere else
oh maybe you'll have to do it like with
the broom we have to pull
on the other side oh right i think that
was just possible
yeah yeah because it's got two
two uh
okay never mind i'll try to break it by
by
by maybe dropping somewhere oh you have
it i thought that was you
bamboozle i'll open it up for you
okay okay maybe oh i can't from this
side
[Music]
i'll take that breath and the sock okay
let me just do um let me do some
research okay here does that mean you're
just gonna ask
your viewers no no no no no i'm gonna do
oh what is this
[Music]
oh this
oh can we surprise him with that
we can probably oh what is this fish
[Music]
is your face yummy oh what is this
oh what's with the bell oh okay
okay maybe when she's distracted with
the bell
we pose what about the dog
oh can i go to the neighbor somewhere i
want to go to the neighbor's house
maybe i can break it there i'm posing
oh she's going to the bell yes he's
going to the vale
why what he's
[Music]
wait okay take that take that vase
and now okay she didn't take it okay
oh wow
i'm posing and then she's fixing the
fish and then i think she's gonna go to
me
and then she's gonna as soon as she
doesn't oh if she doesn't see
the duck if she doesn't okay the dog
that's good
okay okay okay okay okay and then the
first one
and frank how can she
know don't move it in it don't breathe
wait how can she know
how can she know or does it have to be
you
i don't think so i think it has to be
one of us doesn't matter who but i look
a little bit more like that
goose
[Music]
help get dressed up over ribbon yeah
maybe
oh you know what i'll go
oh no she realizes no
this is so difficult
this is this is not easy this is not
easy
okay maybe maybe oops maybe we
try something else first
maybe with the dudes make him spit out
his tea and stuff
let's get to the other side again
oh we can we can
[Applause]
[Music]
oh we got to steal his sandals right
sandals oh his slippers okay okay
slip mm-hmm how
let me just um check what's in here okay
there's a
there's a pool okay there's a phone
that's good
[Music]
okay sit down sit down let him read his
papers
he didn't notice oh no he knows
and then you you put it into the water
put it in the water
oh i i i'll actually i'll actually take
it over there too
okay so because now she'll close it and
she'll never notice
no yeah she doesn't really care yeah she
doesn't care at all yes
she doesn't care about her name nah nah
okay is that complete a slipper
do one more one it says do the washing
so we have to put it into the water
see do the washing a borrow oh about
what
but we also have to make him barefoot so
he really has to
be baffled and that one we can throw
into the water
okay hopefully he won't notice hey
you have to uh put your head down yeah
on it
yeah why does this why doesn't it oh my
oh maybe one is good enough after all
okay maybe that that already means
barefoot i'll
i'll bring it back up
let's wash this one then that's what
that one's really stinky
where's the bar soap okay let's go
stealth
quiet
clean i think i saw the virus in the
ladies place
you'll never notice if no wait it still
doesn't count him as barefoot
she put the ribbon on oh i put my ribbon
it's real cute i want it oh wait wait
i'll pull it off
okay do that first okay think of
something else
give me a ribbon face
[Music]
red ribbon will look good on me no
how come she realizes what do i have to
do
ah maybe while i stand there you put it
on me
maybe then you can actually
yeah let's try this come away let's try
wait let's see
let's see um let's see when she i'll
lure her so try picking up the ribbon
yeah maybe i should wait
oh yeah and then
[Music]
looks so good on you cute thank you i'm
your presentation hey
cute will you keep me laying it
can i live with you treasure forever
what's up what why do you care about
this
care about the soul
wow you suck dude
i'll steal your newspapers
[Music]
what can we do what do we have to do
again um
okay the the prized the ribbon one is
fine we got it
make the man go barefoot apparently
help the woman dress up the bust
yeah maybe um the washing we're almost
done with the washing we only need
another bra
and a pair of socks and i saw that on
the other side make the man spit out his
teeth oh maybe when he's drinking we
bang
the bell okay okay okay maybe maybe
ring the bell oh yeah cuz it's right
behind him
yeah okay okay let's go to the other
side
let's go to the other side he'll
probably eventually start drinking his
teeth
open up open up we are here
to officially my chaos
hello why are you looking at me
i'm not here to cause trouble that's a
lie
okay okay okay he took his cup okay he
took his cup
but he's getting mad at him he's getting
mad he's getting mad getting mad
oh you mad okay more more more
more more oh he's drinking right now
[Music]
this one maybe this one helped dress it
up
with what oh oh
[Music]
oh they're bickering they don't like
each other
yeah but that's probably our fault
[Music]
something like a hat something oh yeah
put this there or wait let me get the
okay okay okay you can get the socks to
the water
oh that's only from the other side oh
hey
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
he's reading the papers and while it's
reading the papers i'm gonna go
we need a pair it has to be one more
yeah
one of us yeah oh yeah we can run for
now that's easier
oh yeah let's go
we're like mates goose mates we're
helping with the housework oh
no got closed up
nice one okay now we still don't know
about the vase
still don't know about it but i'll bring
let's bring it to the other side
look at the other side maybe
[Music]
maybe if we like put it down the stairs
it'll break wait will it
i don't know no he took it down
make sure make sure he doesn't see the
water or else or oh oh never mind
oh the jingle bell it's okay the
achievement i think it's already crossed
out so it doesn't really matter
don't give it back to her
it doesn't break though
[Music]
a
okay let's observe hey
all right so we only have to make him go
back oh
we're still waiting for his other
slipper okay
you know what what he's probably here
do you need a bra he's just he wants to
throw it all over to the back of the
neighbor
okay otherwise you you want to remember
someone in the chat said he might um
like flip his legs
oh what was that oh
man
oh no do something else dude we need you
to sit down
okay maybe while he's putting everything
back we have to take care of the bust on
the other side
oh wait wasn't there a hat on his side
wait who's there oh yeah
can we take that while he's looking for
the soap maybe
okay she's gonna open uh close the gate
again
right now yes yes
[Music]
oh my gosh what is this i'm destroying
can does it have anything to do with
this no
no okay oh she's pruning the thing
is that a bird a bird's plant
and then we gotta lure her we gotta lure
her to the
here somehow oh yeah oh she's just
saying she knows this you know this
the world deserves more hats yes yes yes
yes
nice
wait is it still not enough uh we just
have to
yeah i think it's still not enough me
one more maybe the pipe
oh can she stick it in the in the bust's
mouth
or one glasses fiber glasses oh yeah
let's bring both the lord ameria
uh-huh where is
look at me i'm the best goose
cool i just noticed that's cute cute
oh he doesn't notice he's not noticing
it yet
he's going keep it back
okay okay okay
ready for your life no he knows it's the
pipe
take your glasses first okay
nice maybe it just has to be on on that
side maybe that's enough
doesn't even have to be close to bust
maybe
she must think that he stole her bra
she must be like oh god that dude is
such a freaking perv
ouchy are you okay yeah yes
oh okay here yeah here it is nope
now we wait now we wait
what's she gonna do what's she gonna do
oh
okay oh she never gets enough she's very
creative
yeah let's go like making her imaginary
boyfriend
okay maybe she maybe she actually really
likes her neighbor maybe she's in love
maybe she's a
you know what they call it i'm gonna try
to distract him i'm gonna try
[Music]
yeah you go see the glasses whoa
okay oh
now that's literally him that is it
amazing a new to-do list item
what do you still have
i kind of want to make him barefoot too
[Music]
oh yeah oh we didn't do that yet we
didn't do that yet
[Music]
i brought a frog over yes it's okay it's
a more suitable habitat for him
yeah in the water frog taking a bath
fishing is fishing
it's fishing soap
oh
sorry no frog for you sorry
sorry sorry oh
she's sad she's not here throw it back
no worries
oh but how do we how do we do the fruit
surprise face what
oh
why would you wear your slippers and put
it in the water weird
okay should we wait for him to sit down
first
oh my god he just threw it yeah
that one's gonna break too yeah
okay okay now okay we're gonna hide
good hide so it doesn't become
suspicious
yeah so what's in our newspapers today
and now wait until he switches his leg
oh
yeah i wonder what happened to your
slippers
he doesn't need it's all good
okay wait wait wait wait wait wait we
can't take it yeah we can't take it yeah
we we gotta
wait for him until he crosses um sorry i
didn't do anything yeah
i'm hiding
i'm hiding beautiful feet how does he
don't mind me or do we need to like bang
so that he gets shocked and then he
lifts his feet
oh i see he did lift it a little bit a
little
tight a bit so with me down there yeah
i'm hiding i'm hiding i'm hiding okay
okay
i'll try to take it uh okay then i quack
okay wait no
it's yeah that's not it that's not it
okay um
[Music]
when he is drinking tea his other
slipper is catchable
oh okay let's wait sorry i'm not
gonna do anything
give
drink some tea where's your tea even
what i'm not even looking at
can you see me
where's his team by the way it's next to
him
what he still has some wait huh okay
fine i think i'll hide here because he
might see me if i'm there
what maybe you have to like stand a
little bit to the right
he went
[Music]
the last one i think i know how to do
that one now we have to
get those big scissors from the lady and
then cut this rose
with it hey where's the big scissors
this one this one hey lady
oh oh it's open again
oh yeah it's probably easier to go
through the hole
okay okay i understand
what happened
okay i need to bring the scissors
through there
okay okay i have bad ideas
uh can you go to the other side here
sure
and then i will just wait until she does
something else
okay okay
oh wait is she actually only gonna cut
the rose because i uh
over here
sorry but not actually
your rose is
[Music]
is my declaration of love for you
see i'll take it amen oh my
feelings here with ours
we're gonna swim to
take celebrate shower together nice very
refreshing
to save water flood wind glee
water everybody shower together
yeah we are now for the earth yeah
[Music]
hey does that mean does that mean that
we finish this one
yeah actually good timing it's a good
yeah do you want to see what the next
area looks like first though like just
the way
just the way yeah yeah yeah where is it
that one though yeah
like where from where do we go out
actually you can doco
we can play badminton can you play
badminton
what happened not very good what did i
do what's that
delivery for you
it's amazon again amazon private i've
already got a delivery today
oh really nice wow
there's a lot of places here actually
how many stages do we have in here in
total in this game do you know
i never i never went that far so i don't
know oh
is this for the new area is this left
yeah i think it's
i think this is the new area box
a box we can also be amazon shipping oh
i can get in the box wait
intro no that does not seem to be a
mission but i'm just gonna take you with
me
[Music]
now i'm your presence
[Applause]
wow i think this is the perfect time to
you know
take a rest because we're just you know
we're just
gees who also need rest and need food we
can
we can continue this on my channel maybe
something of course yes of course i
would love to do that
yay
for playing with me it's really really
been a while the last one we did yes
what was it one more tattoo was that
i don't have a good memory what was it
the
the collab that we lasted you mean when
it was
uh no no what it was what it was it was
not phones
right no no no no no it was
what was with the others the one where
it's the two of us is foggs
wow yeah that one was even before then
yeah it was before then yeah
let's play more i would definitely love
to strengthen the ball
of the whole birds now next now we have
to
finally finish church duck and people
are waiting for it i know i know
definitely definitely we have to let us
let us complain oh that's complete
shipping is it is it another gooseberry
thank you so much what did i want to say
do you
what did i want to say i think like my
mind blanked out because i saw that box
oh do you have do you have any do you
have anything
you want to say to the audience yes
yes yes everyone subscribe to renee
thank you thank you thank you dana you
really deserve it
you deserve all the support and the love
in the world you
you are a great person you have a great
personality of a great voice you're
really funny and i think you're really
unique
so i think that people should give you
lots and lots of love
hmm thank you kiara senpai you're so
sweet
i'm so happy to have a hold of verb
senpai that is kiara
thank you congratulations kiara senpai
for the 1 million too everybody
it's crazy you're gonna get there too
ah hopefully hopefully i'm looking
forward to that day
thank you so much oh and i have a little
more announcement don't forget on sunday
it will officially be
six months over kissing again
it will be it will be my uh six
months i can't count six months after
my debut so we're gonna have some fun
starting 8 p.m what are you gonna do i'm
gonna i'm gonna have a free talk and i'm
gonna eat something really nice with
everybody it's like a dinner
for everybody so everybody's invited
we're gonna have yeah
[Music]
thank you
bye
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
you