[Music]
uh
[\h__\h] slaps man
hey
[Music]
race party let's go
oh
[Music]
pop up
[Laughter]
pop
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's game bgm yeah it's not my new vgm
this is the game bgm literally the one
that comes up hey hey when you open the
game
wow wow what a bad girl
but it's a game it'll be gemini snack
holy [\h__\h]
i did not expect that holy [\h__\h] uh
today we're playing a
weird crazy weird game
yeah
weird game
i don't know if you guys are ready for
that
okay well it's so tiny the window is so
tiny and this is windows 20 setup the
window is called windows it's not called
it's not the game title that's already
kind of worrying me it's kind of like
creepy creeping me out can i make it
bigger oh i can
holy [\h__\h]
but now it's kind of hard to read [\h__\h]
uh
[Music]
wait it's really hard to read now it's
kind of sized up in obs it's actually
easier to read in obs wait a second but
can i like do something here no not
maybe not right
oh music sound screen size
maybe
holy sh oh my god it messed up
everything okay i guess we're playing
oh my god my screen's
it it went into full screen mode and
that's kind of messing up everything
right now but that's okay um
maximum is probably definitely better
uh
can this work oh interesting when i tap
in
it moves everything around in obs
because of the screen resolution the
[\h__\h]
let's do uh maybe times two wait it was
times one how big is times two
oh that's much better okay okay i'll go
again
that's very good okay am i too big now
holy [\h__\h] this music
this is music
oh my god okay well
warning i guess we're getting right into
it um this will be uh i i saw dana
playing this a little bit i think she
took like two hours
um there's many different endings we're
gonna just gonna do one
um i hope we're not gonna
there's this um i think only
bad endings as i've heard
uh
there's uh
a lot of yeah buy ones and some that are
not that yeah bye
there's something i'm hoping not to get
because i would probably be a bi on the
stream
[Laughter]
um yeah as i've heard all all of them
are pretty bad um this game is kind of
weird
uh but i thought you know uh as a
one-off one-time only game we could have
some fun with it
uh but yeah big big warning that um
there might be some references that some
of you
maybe feel are maybe triggering so this
is a trigger warning
um i heard there's some stuff about
cutting
your
wrist
i guess in in the game
um so if if that's something you don't
really want to be confronted with you
you might have a problem i don't know if
we're gonna get to a part like that but
um
yeah there you go so nowadays people on
the internet want trigger warning so
this is the trigger warning uh also for
everybody who's watching the archive
yeah yeah but i don't know i don't know
how
much we really will get confronted with
it i know
this music and this conversation is very
suitable very fitting
but most of the time um i think we
shouldn't take the topics too seriously
and we should just take it easily
jokingly normally not something to joke
about but maybe in a game like this it's
uh
don't don't take it too seriously okay
okay and then we can have some fun
uh oh should i pin a comment trigger
warning
uh this game contains crazy
[\h__\h]
like i don't even know but
be careful
[Laughter]
that's my trigger hurting to you i mean
when you didn't play the game before
they don't really know what to what to
uh warn people about but yeah it's
probably written here too this game is
set in a place sort of like modern-day
japan but also not any resemblance to
real places
do not try any of the more extreme or
depressing actions
some scenes may have intense flashings
i'm going to be violent emotionally
painful please take a break if it messes
with you mentally oh no now no breaks
allowed here before you begin playing
please bear in mind that at the end of
the day this game is a piece of fiction
is exactly what i was talking about and
may not necessarily
may not necessarily i'm pretty sure it
does not reflect real life but uh eureka
is wearing properly right promised yeah
what about canceling what if i say
cancel
[Music]
my son
oh of course of course i mean i have to
test it out we want to try all things
here
i had to i had to i had to okay getting
back into the game
[Music]
oh
man
okay here we go
windows this is
i like this
windows 20.
wow so old man
i like the aesthetics so far
data
won
so uh
what i know is uh you it's a streamer a
streamer girl girl wants to become
streamer and you help her i guess and uh
there's like two personalities that you
may have seen
in the image in the thumbnail i kind of
want the darker um type girl because i
saw layna was going for the cutie pie
but i don't know if i can really control
that much
um
and i think the cutie pie is like you
know she looks cute but [\h__\h] her
uh
okay new game let's go
i guess we start out like that i guess
if we [\h__\h] her up to that she becomes
the the darker one
yeah
she yeah yeah i know she's both a lion
giant
yeah popular japanese uh
uh
popular japanese messenger app is
called lion
uh got the stream i can't time to log in
and get ready click on stream and log in
with my password angel kawaii too cringe
um
wait what do you call these aesthetics
again
it was a word for it um
was again help chat help help me help me
angel kawaii too i hope i don't forget
that since
yeah yeah vaporwave i have a friend
that's insanely into this vaporwave
style
okay login
easy password angel kawaii too
probably bad choice for pastor but okay
oh cute okay i see you've logged in this
is it this is where out forever begins
oh
okay so here we have a task manager that
tells us how she's doing i guess moving
together no matter what happens online
whether i die or i get arrested or i
break or i get stabbed or get blamed or
become god or go crazy is that all
options that can happen interesting
no no
the internet is surely the festering
cess pool of hell born from modern
society hell yeah that is true so far
this game is accurate but even so i have
nowhere else to turn to
but the internet is understandable
because i have trouble getting out of
bed in the morning me too i don't want
to go out i don't want to get a proper
job yeah i'm scared of other people i
just pissed me off and i'm stupid but i
still want everyone to fawn over me
but that is so fun very late
and streamers get bothered with the
moves right now yeah so that's why i
want to become one mm-hmm
yeah yeah yeah this is
true girl i can understand thanks for
setting up all my gear and getting my
streaming software up and running pizza
and are using uh obs
you're welcome
pizza
yeah so we can choose our answers here
uh most of the time yeah feel my pizza
because you're so perfect for me
doesn't peach on stand for prisoner in
your world i mean you're the only person
in this world who understands and
supports me and you're my one true love
and you're also like my producer so it
fits sure producer prisoner same thing
you're super smart unlike me
wow she sees the reality the way it is
so you can guide me you can tell me to
do anything and i'll do it
so i'm in control as always let's do it
let's do it
let's do this yeah
oh it's so much time for what
my makeup looks good got my wig perfect
ah that's a wig
here we go it's time for my first dream
but you look perfect the way you are
right now man don't think you need to
dress up like that okay
magical girl transformation
oh yeah yeah she's a cosplayer i think
on air oh we're streaming it's our first
stream during each stream we can delete
the annoying comments and choose two
colored comments super chats keeping
your cursor in the comment section will
slow the game down a little to make
things a bit easier i see okay hi cutie
so this is what she's saying we see how
many people watch this like youtube and
then the comments come in and i can
choose them nice cheery greeting cute oh
my god a new streamer dab you let's go
cute
i'm oh my god come on angel but you can
call me angel see you're already gonna
fail because that name god you're so
[\h__\h] cute yeah tell her more she
loves that kind of [\h__\h]
got it weird name so this is what we
delete did i delete it got it did i
delete it i think i deleted it how would
i select it i think i did it a way of
life eliminating the kl bringing
happiness to the nerds floating in this
electronic scene
let's go girl
she got her sentence down her phrase
so people will remember it you know like
uh
pickle
okay go go go this is fast enough i
promise a future piece i'm a little
manic and moody but it's all right
yeah
oh boy here come the nerds
don't go depression on us is that mean
should i delete that
i guess so
wait does it say how many comments i get
oh shut up
why why are you so mean i guess i'll
delete that too
[Music]
it's me you know internet angel has to
say that she's not getting bothered by
it so far so good
but
she might be surprised at how how mean
the internet can be
i hope it doesn't bother her too much
there's almost 200 people watching now
go go
stream speed over excited rambling no no
no no blue hedgehog what what went so
fast too fast thank you for gracing us
oh my god get out of here what [\h__\h] you
i'm here to love and heal all you nerds
out here on the internet oh okay i don't
you're gonna be one of the k this is
cute now i want to delete that
[\h__\h] mods come on
ah
save me please he wants to be saved when
are you gonna [\h__\h] you
is that good minus one this shows how
much pressure i'm feeling i might start
acting weird if it gets too high so
watch out i might even become more
scared of the internet but day by day
understandable have a nice day and while
i'm at it i'm going to become the
biggest streamer on me tube
yes it's not youtube it's me tube
[\h__\h] you go big or go hopes i'm going to
shoot for 1 million subscribers let's go
you've got my support oh threaten us
more here we have a masochistic
masochistic viewer just just uh how it
is in reality
she looks promising yeah dream big very
supportive
nice nice nice i guess we banned the
haters all of them
um
an interesting newbie has appeared show
us what you've got
i kind of really regret like uh marking
this one
maybe we can mark the other one
yeah
i don't know what we're marking it for
oh [\h__\h] shin rita ah
i'll read some comments no ah
she's reading it get out of here you get
out of here that's right girl tell him
tell him thank you for gracing us
oh
that's that's a nice one
oh and if you're a backstage gamer do me
a favor and stay away please oh oh i was
warm with bathroom gamers i like
backseat gamers
subscribe oh it's over at the end of the
stream i will respond to the comments
you choose the fans love that aren't i
so kind and generous
totally like oh my god totally you you
did perfect
oh and then she tweets after the streams
hey everyone wow this is my first time
meeting all of you i'm oh my god angel
your internet angel what did you guys
think of my face
what the [\h__\h] can i like stop it well
she's tweeting i think she also tweeted
with her
other account um
secretly that's secret angel finally
descends upon the world after we spent
so long mowing over her
we've got a thousand more subscribers
huh but that's not enough i want more
people to phone over me we're only just
getting started
i can read it on the bottom left
ah here i'll go to chill chill girl i
need at least one million fans to
satisfy my desperate need for approval
we gotta get to that within a month
that's the most motivation i've got
one month
as an indie i don't know so let's make
this month count we can make angel the
biggest streamer in the world if we work
together right just wait give me a
moment chill girl take a chill pill
uh so let's finish reading this i hope
you liked it because i'm going to keep
trying my hardest to bring lots and lots
of joy so please be nice to me bliss
i should start using that to bliss
uh yeah that's a cute selfie she got
that down
the
beauty app is working wonders
oh and uh okay almost 1k faves this is
this is actually too ideal like
not really that easy in real life but
okay
okay this is her out i guess
uh oh my [\h__\h] god i made some basic
ass posts on maine everyone was still
really nice and commented and liked it
and stuff i'm so glad i was born cute
thank you god
i think i'm gonna read her i'll post
like that oh my god you disgusting
okay that's that's pretty fetch yeah i
have to say so we can make angels
streamer
biggest stream in the world if we work
together
do we want to be supportive of her i
guess so
yeah
i love you so much
oh my god i really hope we can pull this
off i'm counting on you pizza
sure i don't even know how i got here in
the first place
i might break if you push me too hard
but when that happens we can just
destroy the internet if it were that
easy
if it were that easy anyway i'll be
counting on you tomorrow too
fine okay well she has 1001 subscribers
it's pretty impressive good night more
love to you too i guess
oh
good morning it's my first morning as an
official streamer huh wait it's already
known
i'm just not a morning person at all
me too
yeah although today i woke up even later
than noon i was up all night playing
pokemon you guys have no idea
anyway since we're aiming for 1 million
subscribers we still need 999
000 more easy club
let's start small and go for 10k first
we'll get here there in no time
yeah yeah the 10k seems realistic in one
month and as you know i'm completely
useless on my own
i think is that as the victor
as we like to say in german so you need
to tell me what you what to do every day
i know you'll make the right decisions
for me
okay if you want to be controlled sure i
think like after a while being
controlled you will only wish for having
more control yourself i'll do everything
you tell me to really i have complete
faith in you peach on i'll follow all
your orders perfectly and i promise you
i'll become the best streamer
okay i'll try
i don't want you to become like a truck
of disaster cause if not i i think i'll
just break and fall apart okay shut up
shut up already
oh i could break you myself oh
we're already getting violent violence
here wow okay
it's so threatening
yeah you could
no
if there are no options for you to
choose you can select a sticker to send
back to me you don't want to be one of
those people who leave their girlfriends
and read do you no no no i always gotta
answer with something um
love for
this
okay
love forever sure
um
[Music]
sure
send me more
um
i'm dead
okay
okay okay okay chill don't fall in love
with me too much wait i still have to
reply oh wait when you see him on my
command it means that you will be able
to find new ideas for content with that
command when you feel a bit lost right
clicking it what
wait where there are free stages in each
day noon desk at night click the icon on
the desktop to advance through them ah
right now i think it's damn or noon
uh it's good to keep a regular schedule
but be careful as some commands will
take up two stages instead of one
sorry i kind of for some reason read the
middle one first uh and just as a note
you can only make me stream at night
because that's what most people are like
smart yeah
um
okay do i still need to reply to you
will she ever stop i wonder maybe she'll
be satisfied if i
do this again
just okay what if i what if i send more
what happens then
shut up
oh my god shut up shut up already
let's see a new idea incoming
oh okay
sleep is
okay medication is
we have to take pills apparently
d-pads pills what does that mean take
two either depression and tie the
precipa
take two once per day calms the user
down makes the use ah anxiety pills
makes you use it kind of floppy
everything just feels more manageable
when i take some makes me feel kind of
floaty if i take too many though
what what is that
what is that i wonder
happy pills
well um so we should probably only do
that if she's like
yeah not feeling well i don't know if
100 100 be a buy or is it like the lower
the better or the higher the better for
mental darkness i'm not sure i guess
we'll have to find out
internet
oh eco search video streaming
panda
okay i don't know what to do there's so
much to do let's go social media
uh i wanted to buy myself a super comfy
couch but if i did i think oh it's
already
evening i would never leave it i think i
would turn into a blob
okay okay oh [\h__\h] it's happening stuff
is happening
conspiracy theories are always so
interesting to read about it's so funny
wait i'm also into conspiracy parents
let's go
is seeing people arguing about whether
they're real absolute [\h__\h] i never
get tired of it oh my god let's talk
about it i want to reply
but you know i feel like if you go deep
enough you'll end up buying into it
sooner or later curiosity killed the cat
kind of deal
i
like i like her so far
lol i'm fine though i'd never let that
happen to me i'm the most rational and
logical girl in the world suddenly she
has confidence the only thing that
drives me crazy is you
the [\h__\h] is the matter of you
but anyway i figured that conspiracy
fears would make for great content so
let's start off with this banger without
anger wait
[Music]
you're doing a conspiracy theory stream
what if government government what if
the government made you a nerd yo let's
go interesting i want to hear what you
have to say that is uh
oh my god amazing
okay okay okay
i love that so much this
this was i don't know your idea is
amazing
i bet you're lying what
whatever sorry crack
i forgive you not
okay shut up and just stream okay
um wait uh
uh are we already do we need to stream
um
it looks so cute
let's go on the internet or no i have to
stream i have to stream apparently i
have to continue
ah you know pizza and i've always really
clanked on conclusions out of a train
washing pass
what
you're gonna make me cry
what's what's the matter with you girl
uh
how about we play a game i don't know
let's play a game together
don't end it girl is that what this is
about i want to get a fight stick but it
will probably end up getting buried in
all the [\h__\h] in my room
and then peter will get mad at me guess
i'll just go play an arcade and show all
the nerds there what i've got sure do
what you want nothing beats a good game
humans are going to play and i'm getting
the hang of the streaming thing so i
want to do a let's play let's do this no
conspiracy first but good idea okay okay
throwback stream
oh my god
amazing
so wait are we streaming or what
are we streaming
how do i go live
ah go tonight now go stream
um
oh
here this
begins
[Music]
do your best girl
this is a great second stream to choose
hey cuties it's kangel the fixer who
controls the entire world
just checking things out sure have a
nice good great time i guess
i've been waiting for this really it's
literally my second stream
do you guys like conspiracy for yours i
do so i read about them a lot like um
same
i want a time too
i always want two streams this is my
second stream that makes no sense
y'all nerds love these oh i love this
conspiracy face i'm excited let's go
you allowed to be my fan
[Music]
i like you you like conspiracy theories
too of course i though who doesn't
i'm excited
so girl tell me so i thought maybe i
could share some of my favorites with
you guys here and there oh
conspiracy theories scare me well you're
you're a little
today we'll be talking about the net
culture conspiracy nerd culture there's
a nerd culture conspiracy theory
don't go too deep
and a rabbit hole you can only go deeper
go go your way into this now
great choice some people say that it did
not develop organ organically and it was
actually spread by the frame is there
anything in this game that i should not
say out loud
what is that is what it would or would
it ride on the out i don't know they
wanted to turn the japanese masses into
nerds to numb them sounds wacky but what
if it did happen i have no idea what
she's talking about
am i cancelled does she cancel
a secret society what what
they want to do
that took a turn okay i guess i guess
i'm not a nerd
everyone watching now would be dancing
to the tune of the freemasons
shut it down shut it down shut down
[Laughter]
is that is that something we wanted to
read i don't know how she would react
i'm not nervous she's gonna be like yes
you are be proud of it
i don't mind these streams actually
i believe anything you say can you oh
it's a red super chat feels like you're
going to eventually go off the deep end
if you keep this up
that's something you need to ride in a
super chat
it's a red one like
is there another one maybe
but it's okay because even if you were
all manipulated into being nerds you got
to meet a real live angel
and that is so the good side always say
the positives about it
oh
okay it's too late now she's already
reading comments
then yeah we didn't choose enough but
only one but that's okay that's probably
fun right but promise me you won't get
too paranoid and if you do promise me
you'll go to therapy
[Music]
yeah i mean i guess that's good advice
i guess that's good advice
uh if there's one thing you can trust uh
is it true on the internet if that's
that you guys all met me so be proud of
the fact that you're that you are my
friend i would never trick you or turn
my back on you
oh that's reassuring
i will should talk y'all on my private
dough on my own but well as long as no
one finds it they can stay blissfully
unaware forever and even if someone does
find it it's not like i'm committing a
crime even if it does feel like betrayal
that's just how our world works pizza
look at my dm already stop ignoring me
oh my god
[Laughter]
ah
dear pete this is cited from xy
creations as per our last phone call
your rent is still outstanding and you
shut up and you will have until attempt
to pay it in full please forward your
payment to the account detail below and
contact me when you have done so
we ignored her what is this does this
mean that we need to pay all our rent by
day 10 um yes we're broke as hell we
need to be able to monetize our content
as soon as possible we need to get more
than 10k followers first easy peasy for
us let's go
i don't like these stickers there needs
to be something more like i don't know
motivating
this
just like you say i don't care when you
do care i know you do care i love you i
guess
okay good
um
what is that at my emails why i wonder
what is that
i don't understand
okay weird uh okay we will not reply to
that i don't even know if there's an
option for that
um
okay so the stress will be reduced if we
spend time together affection will be
uh
oh a
boy
and stream bonus communication oh
communication will go up interesting but
now you know we have already enough
ideas let me do something else what's
vanity search
is that eagle search is that your bit
oh
wait let me let me let me look at this
for this spoiler
uh okay so i'm looking for angel i was
late because i got carried away watching
kings of leaders act thanks kangel
that's not bad who's kendra sure
conspiracy fears get good engagement but
i feel like this is a slippery slope
that canes will probably shouldn't go
down
well yeah probably
but it's fun
so they all the vanity research and
found out that one of my favorite eyes
was talking about my channel i'm so
happy i'm so glad i never gave up on
streaming you literally just started i'm
gonna suck up on them hide and dm so
they'll drop out of me oh no
ah
yeah okay
why not
she's a business lady
she's a business lady yeah
uh can you pick up some eggs today
they're on sale
listen thank you
eggs
[Music]
what
oh okay
okay
how
how do i go about that
what
[Music]
how do i
is she for real am i going egg shopping
can i lay some eggs quick i can't
i can't
uh wait does she actually sleep
automatically after streaming or
how does this work oh i can sleep on
purpose i guess in order to reduce some
stress and [\h__\h]
oh
skip the stream go to bed take a little
nap oh
how do you go out good question
eggs where the [\h__\h] do i fly eggs
we are we're in harajuku
holy [\h__\h] dad of course that's expensive
they live in harajuku that's like a
really that's super central and a really
popular shopping district that normally
i don't i don't even
um
yeah i wouldn't even want to live
there's too too many people man
okay so uh
work are you sure you want to proceed
you're missing no no no no no but eggs
no i have to stream
word eggs
by egg at hospital
[Laughter]
stream more important you don't have to
okay you don't actually have to buy
okay
well then
stress 41 streams
okay let's try this
this what are we doing
i like watching pack openings but it's
not exactly exciting when a rich
streamer does it i only like watching
the poor streamers pull cards because
the stakes are higher but then the
interesting ones become popular and then
they become rich so it's still finding
good content what
what so she watched someone else's uh
stream the streaming site i used updated
no other anime does it like idol animes
truly and the best ones are the kids
idol anime but watching the girls work
so hard for the idol dreams makes me a
bit sad over how in reality what's most
important is how much money you can
squeeze out of the fans
well that's that's important for the
managers that's probably most of the
time not really what those idols think
about especially if they start at a
young age but mm-hmm the imaginations
are
the management is definitely milking
them yeah
idol anime is so pure i wish that were
me i was just talking about like love
life and stuff why is the real world so
harsh i think i'll talk about kids
animal stream to teach my viewers the
power and magic of hopes and dreams
that's it that's the spirit
yeah
okay
also no i'm not talking about gemma i'm
talking about like real life idol uh
stuff
but of course that also doesn't apply to
every company okay
and go tonight i guess we're ready to
wait i need to answer um
[Music]
i'm not even gonna open that girl stream
uh which one is it this one
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go
don't leave her on the road is she gonna
go crazy on me
oh [\h__\h] we're all friends we're all
nerds it's your favorite idol kangel she
keeps on changing her phrase each time
you shouldn't do that girl keep the same
one
what are we talking about today your
friends cute oh thank you everybody's so
nice oh you're so cute thank you she
knows any of you grown adults here like
the kids and am i do you also wake up
early like five years old to watch them
um
like i five years i struggle so hard to
get up anymore
totally i can so relate thank you for
the right super chat
you're so fun
i love this
i record them i like watching kids
anyway so yeah is anybody asking me
though like um for me i don't have
stopped watching anime like such a long
time ago you watch the kids superhero
shows too kids superhero shows what's
kid superhero hero shows you know when i
was still an angel in training i was
safe from
wait and everything amazing still
appealing is how pure they are
saying the girls work so hard for their
dreams and aspirations and love is just
so inspiring you know
holy oh my god angel you're so inspiring
i could listen to you all day
i'm so glad we can talk about kids anime
totally
should i choose this one
can i still change them probably not
what is that
a candle
[Music]
we need more viewers okay i guess i'll
choose this
oh god that's creepy
and when times are tap their friends and
family are there to help them and share
their dreams watching them makes me feel
like my petty bad thoughts have been
purified that's why i like them
i don't know is she genuine about this
because if she is then not bad i mean
i love the magical girl transformations
yes
i'm sure she does too also you guys see
we don't get any hate comments at the
moment that's pretty good
i'm a little girl okay um are you sure
about that
maybe you should check
what anime do you like i know what when
i remember that all the nerds watching
also had such purity in their hearts
once
once it makes me cry hey i'm sure you're
still pure
deep deep down there can i read some
comments okay oh say someone said the
same thing
i struggle so hard to get up in the
mornings
[Music]
just think of sunday morning as like an
extension of saturday night
okay
you watch the kids superhero shows too
what's your answer girl yeah of course
i'll show you my hanshin belt sometime
oh you have one
impressive okay stream is over
what's she gonna say
every girl had an idol growing up and
i'm going to do my best to become
someone that all girls can look up to
reply to me already who is that egg
once i was playing one of those girl
idol games in the arcade and the girl
standing behind me kept staring at the
rare card machine the machine gave me
and i felt so bad so i gave it to her
gonna invent time travel so i can beat
myself up that was
my hard-earned money that was my
hard-earned money
my god
no why that was nice of you come on i
said stop ignoring me i'm five million
times more needed
okay chill [\h__\h] chill girl oh [\h__\h] she
scares me
yummy guys save me i don't know what i
got myself into
[Applause]
all right i'm gonna start being more
proactive with my work
uh you too okay pizza let's get this
bread together you sound like such a
generic happy girl lucky oh crap
why do i have to be more proactive than
doing oh [\h__\h] both of these answers are
challenging
[Laughter]
um
first one
well maybe she'll take it as a
compliment because she knows she's
acting and she knows that's what she's
going for so she'll be like hell yeah
that's what i'm what i wanted yeah okay
maybe she'll take it if she's smart yeah
why the [\h__\h] did i say that i don't want
to do more
oh okay
[Music]
wow
hmm
um okay
okay
interesting conversation
yeah i know how well cause she's
apparently done talking to me nice thank
god
um
is there something you guys want to do
something in particular
smart very smart take your mitts no she
doesn't need maths i think she's looking
pretty good
stress is maybe a bit high maybe we
should take a nap i don't know
do the men's distress yeah but i don't
think we should get like addicted to
them go outside hospital now
what
no
she's losing affection
okay let's play a game
does that raise that affection i should
have checked
you didn't maybe playing a soccer coach
simulator did go who what i'm gonna
get to the fifa minus four plus two okay
i'm gonna get to the fifa finals let's
go okay i just remember this game i
played where you become some big shot
who has a global influence or whatever i
actually got so into it i ended up
skipping meals and stuff you shouldn't
do that oh my god that's so bad
but what game was that but anyway i
noticed recently that a lot of people
these days like to play games where you
have the power to rule the world and
even reduce populations and stuff
you should play sims 4 girl trust me
you'll love it
and some people also truly believe
that's what's happening in our world and
make up these wild boogie men to direct
their reject
what the [\h__\h] are you talking about
black and white wait i think i know that
game i i think i played that when i was
younger
don't you like kind of uh play a god
i love that game
don't i don't blame me though damn
though i think considering the times we
live in it's not so strange that people
want someone or something to be angry at
of course they always want someone to be
angry yeah yeah yeah oh my god i played
that like millions years ago i want to
play it again
but we should all be working together
please this is my only wishes the
internet angel sounds good doesn't it
well i'm going to say that and see how
the stream viewers react they're my
little guinea pigs
are cute
you have a new idea for a stream only
one government 30 years later um yeah
probably no more conspiracy favorite
streams
probably
probably not a good idea
[Music]
what's this dumbest sticker i love you
too
ah okay okay okay okay yeah yeah yeah
you're welcome girl i love you oh my god
oh my god well now i'm not kind of
flattered
stop
a cute girl likes me that's like so rare
it never happens oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] okay let's go to dusk
what if i started a stream of bye bye
screaming this ain't a [\h__\h] dog
is that a reference also is that a
[\h__\h] um
beyblade
well that sounds amazing
i guess
i'm trying to
well i can't with these stickers i need
other choices then
uh okay well
maybe we should spend the time uh doing
uh well let's see stress 44 goes down
goes down okay mental darkness goes up
free
stream free stream alert ah that's smart
affection goes
[Music]
down mental darkness goes up and that's
really
not good at all
stress goes down by watching a movie or
anime and streaming bonus communication
goes up okay cool
huh
that doesn't have any both of these
don't really have anything okay
in that case i think social media is
smart we can tell people that i'm
starting a stream next stream is this uh
there are a bunch of people out there
who keep calling me ugly why do you do
this who've made this internet angel
very sound
yeah that's the problem if you are not a
youtuber but a real tuba i guess
thank you kenjo you're the only thing i
get up and go to my shitty [\h__\h]
office into my sucking garbage workflow
oh my god you're so welcome i love you
too
a green man
where did she get that from
no
don't worry about it you're beautiful
[Music]
okay it's night time huh i woke up on
record time this morning praise me
please i don't know how
i don't know how
oh my god maybe
is that good enough for you
good job at least as long as you don't
ask me to
you anymore please stop
okay because we're straight is it night
time okay we're streaming let's go
let's play would probably be good or all
hail internet uh
stream streak bonus free stream alert
bonus communication bonus rabbit hole
bonus oh
gamer there's a camera girl bonus let's
go uh
[Music]
i was waiting for this why you keep me
waiting so long oh my god your last
stream is like 16 hours ago you can't
keep me waiting so long
from backstream 400 people watching okay
first time here never gets old
indeed
because she's new
show us what you've got hell yeah hi
kids it's finally time for me to stream
some games
show us your gaming skills excite
we're going to check out some truly
ancient artifacts today
like what tetris i'm going to play
tetris
or i don't know ocarina of time
i don't know and probably that's not an
artifact an artifact would be that zelda
game that looks like
[\h__\h] nightmare
gamers let's go and play some flash
games splash games you know what that
sounds actually like fun
i love flash games
i want i want to play the one where you
can dress up the barbie girls nice
choice you look like you suck at james
you look like you suck at life
don't know what's going on but i like it
also she does look like she's suck sucks
at games though
she does look like it you're not wrong
let's play go wow this takes me back
this side should be the one wait um
as long as you're enjoying yourself
thank you what's what what's happening
what what's the problem
oh it's so old and that that support has
ended we can't play
girls do your research before you start
the stream
oh i see you all right oh they're so
sweet oh my of course yep there it is
folks what what
you know it all
what are you trying to say
you're so silly huh
it's not my fault
oh we can't play the game
oh man
don't cry
stop paddling to the old fox on the
internet
but someone has to pander to them you
know someone has to do it don't cry
should probably not answer that right or
do you think she's gonna get a kick out
of it
it's okay there's always a next time so
sweet
be more confident in yourself tap or
chat yeah that's good
that's good that's good super chat
reading don't cry there was only one
good super chat oh my god there are only
three situations where it is appropriate
for women to cry oh
tell us about it when you get dumped
when you lose your wallet and when your
childhood flash games get discontent
girl don't cry thank you andre you guys
are sending the same super chats
oops so much
i couldn't read that oh my god girl i
can't believe none of those games work
anymore my stream was a total rag so bye
for now oh
cheer up
hey kendra i'm going to start saving
money so i can get a nose job to look
just like yours
um okay guys don't don't get a nose job
to look like mine because you're gonna
look like voldemort um just saying you
might think i'm pretty but don't try to
look like me okay just gotta say it
you don't wanna get this nose job don't
show don't show the doctor me or any
anime girl as a reference it's not gonna
help
[Music]
uh well that's that what can you do
things are only just getting started so
i have to try even harder from now on
yeah yeah
okay i think she's mentally still doing
pretty well at the moment
we're doing fine so far
she has a cute phone case so
she's so cute
what is it i'm gonna make an amazon
wishlist what should i put on it
oh definitely costumes
all right it's in i'm gonna oh
everything actually
okay
the microphone too
talk about no effort
sorry
[Music]
i'm sorry that's okay see i'm so nice
totally
she says while taking selfies
[Music]
okay
what should we do
a fruity that was one of the choices i
didn't even see it
please no
oh please no
reduce stress
medication oh no go out
really but then we can't stream probably
um when we don't i'm sure really
maybe we can go to uh shibuya
stress goes down by a lot affection goes
up okay oh does it um depend on where we
go no kitty georgie is nice too kitchen
toyota has a lot of cat cafes and a lot
of um secondhand shops did you know did
you know
um
i remember that place well mm-hmm
don't like going to shinjuku at all i
also i used to love going to ikebukuro a
lot ikebukuro is like a mix of
everything kind of
what the [\h__\h] is there hikarigaoga park
i've been there but it's such a random
place
let's go to shibuya
yeah
[Music]
actually you could walk
only take some maybe like from harajuku
to shibuya depending on where you start
off it takes you like half an hour
walking
yeah but we take the train one station
literally
here here comes my japan knowledge in
handy
excuse me
girl
wendy smokes shisha with pizza
i wasn't used to all the smoke so i kept
choking on it but it still i still had a
good time
you could pick your own flavor so i went
with mint chocolate
i tried uh
[Music]
one time in my life and i did not like
it
i did not like it
wait no that's uh it's not even
smoke i never tried the cigarette though
no never that's disgusting
wait
how did they not see that though
how did i not see that
i tried to reply but i didn't even get a
chance to reply to that i think
someone i know spends 200 000 k yen on
underground male idols every month but
they've only ever given kange 100 yen in
the super chat i see how it is
ah she's stalking them she's stalking
her fans well um
that is horrible that is so horrible i'm
gonna punch it
i'm trying to relate to you i don't care
[\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh yeah she's
[\h__\h] she's done again talking to me
and wait what time is it oh it's
streaming time we actually made it on
time to stream we don't have so many
ideas anymore we need some ideas
tomorrow i guess we're gonna do this one
followers
[Music]
the followers go up by a lot but the
stress and the mental darkness
goes up by
a hell lot as well [\h__\h] is that worth it
sleep for the stress oh i could also
choose to not
choose to not stream
ah do it do it worth it we need the
thought we do need to follow us
ah
and then we can just sleep the next day
you know after you know doing that
stream there will probably be a lot of
[\h__\h] talking about me anyway and then
i'll be like [\h__\h] you i'm not screaming
tonight
okay
oh let's go
let's
go
[Music]
let's see what happens
napoleon of the streaming
nice reference okay napoleon had an
austrian wife as far as i know
so
i'm your wait that's perfect i'm your
austrian wife girl
okay just checking things out first time
here a revolution who's napoleon
i would like to hear the answer to that
uh kind of revolutionary girl kenjo
you're cute as always today
thank
you
the lore is accurate in 20 years our
world could be ruled by one body or so
the new world order conspiracy theory
goes
one body you mean like one one emperor
for the whole world interesting tell us
more
tell me more
more more
conglomerates are scheming to create an
incredibly disparate society they will
eventually take over that is um
interesting what's the same question
what's a conglomerate i heard of that
before
that the vision has already begun
so true
they're even trying to reduce the world
population to 1 billion or so the
conspiracy theorists say
well
good luck of that i don't know how
you're trying to do that that's scary i
want to live in an equal society
let's go equal society yes let's go
all true actually really
spitting facts what would the world be
like ruled by one government some say i
would all be forced to worship lucifer i
don't know how i feel about worshiping a
fallen angel being an angel myself
understandable man your life must be so
tough man
lucifer oh that guy
you you can be a fallen angel heart what
are you trying to say with that
aren't taking action you're already
taking action you're killing people or
what
oh my god i'm kind of curious about that
kind of world
well uh you shouldn't be
okay i didn't go here for politics
no then why the [\h__\h] did you come here
and looked at the title look at the
thumbnail look at everything i'm a
conspiracy theory screamer have you not
noticed by now four out of my streams
two out of my four streams are about
conspiracy theories
get take the hint for [\h__\h] sake
and then stop complaining this is
interesting but i don't know if you
should be talking about it maybe i
should um
delete this
yes less stress
okay let's see what you guys thought um
[Music]
who's napoleon
there's a really really good manga where
napoleon is to make a manga
you should totally read it
oh that will be so accurate so
historically accurate that's scary i
want to live in an equal society yes
what's your thoughts archangel yeah but
just sitting around and complaining
isn't gonna change anything
true we must fight there's no living
without fighting
wow
sounds like a politician
i vote kangel
no matter what the world comes to please
don't lose your faith in me okay bless
bless this girl
stream is over i think that was okay
worth it that was worth it oh my god to
be honest sometimes i think that the
internet is such a mess because there
are too many people so whenever we
reduce the population by 90.
just just a shower thought i never want
to actually make that can i delete your
tweets what are you tweeting what the
[\h__\h] are you tweeting
this is
material for the haters don't do that
girl
i think that no matter where you go on
the internet you're always about to end
up fighting one way or another those who
do not fight will not survive
so true
yeah
[Music]
is the music getting faster
someone sent me a cosplay and it's so
well made what the [\h__\h]
oh my god amazing
yes i'm the best in the world yes you
are
totally this she really doesn't like
that does she
i don't care okay [\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you
let's um
play and then sleep for the night that's
probably
good oh she's too stressed and that's
why it's like that ah
okay
um
i seemed
this is like a cheat code is it
um
sexy freight
stress goes down
only so [\h__\h] little
tweeting
oh
cute
way cute
got the costume i have my wishlist thank
you to the one who bought it i put it on
right straight away if you buy me a
costume i'll take a selfie and it's a
wink wink
oh
i cannot get in trouble if i [\h__\h]
this costume
um i think you can do what you want but
um
[\h__\h]
[Music]
does that mean that i've been
not not stressed anymore
spend time to give yeah we need to spend
some time together
let's do this one
and then oh [\h__\h] what happens if she's
too stressed
i told off today apparently i keep
kicking pizza in my sleep apparently i
grind my teeth a lot damn do i really
live like this maybe this dress is
getting to me oh no
what don't i do i guess i'll just have
to go make out with peach or something
thank you for always being so nice to me
i should carry on your spirit and be
nice to my little nerds every once in a
while but you're still the only one i
love the most okay no need to get
jealous
[Music]
swear
of course not i know this is all
business but um we should sleep
love you
you can answer enough
okay
and what's by accident
can i sleep now or do i have to
i think i have to go to desk okay
i'm just a fat little caterpillar no
you're not
oh man
she's getting depressed
flip sleep is good sleep is really good
oh that's really good yeah yeah yeah
sleep will help you out
yeah
[Music]
are you feeling better today
mine is nylon is two that's still a lot
though
but i can't sleep the moment i got into
bed all these horrible memories just
came coming back to me
ah
[Music]
sorry i guess i'll just pray that the
other insomniacs on and i can get some
sleep tonight
oh okay that's uh sweet i guess she at
least wants other people to sleep
i can't win with her that's so true
i'll be their guardian angel
oh
i hate it but cool good for you
wait is it
go to tomorrow is this before we're
going to sleep
that is amazing
not that i think you would but if you
cheat on me i'll kill you
oh
okay why would i what would i do i don't
know where you get that idea from i
would never do that she fails to sleep
[\h__\h]
[Music]
look i got some flowers what kind of
photos there's a kid just like you who
buys flowers anymore cool there's no
kids just like you
are so sweet you can look at them when
i'm not home so you won't get lonely
uh but according to what she said
we're like already like because she said
that uh she kicks me in my sleep so we
already sleep together
never mind i'm cute anyway why would you
need anything else when you have me who
cares about these flowers anyway
what's wrong with you
oh
how did you spiral into this so fast
[Music]
okay um
i love you
[Music]
is it is that gonna show something weird
on stream question mark
[Laughter]
[Music]
might have to take one for the team
yes no yeah no no really not really
oh
okay
[Music]
um
oh okay it's like pork
oh no problem it's actually less less uh
nsfw than uh
sims
oh my god can we angel will forever and
always be an idol for the people i
promise to never betray you guys so
please keep on showing me the love
you've all been so generous with
this is it for the
[Music]
deep for the first time after we moved
in together it was amazing we have great
chemistry both emotionally and
physically no one would be junk and
satisfying okay
okay um
making me kind of uncomfortable but okay
[Music]
i took some sneakers of you when you
were asleep and nearly uploaded them on
cages they can't move you're so [\h__\h]
stop it
uh i'm dead
can't handle this girl
how did she know how is she
she knows
oh my god
um that is so true
amma is the best angry but we're talking
about a different army right
yes
yes yes milady
are you happy enough shut up such a
[\h__\h] sunday [\h__\h]
wait i should say sorry i should say
sorry
send me a selfie are you grappling for
forgiveness
i i don't know how to take a picture
okay i think we're good i think we're
good
so it's daytime no it's night time we
could we could stream
we could stream right yeah
we're looking decent i think
oh
sexy stream uh
no
no no no no
i swear
[Music]
no no no no
no i don't support that [\h__\h]
no
good workouts here there today you
oh you think they worked out sleepy time
with angel 1000 300 watching why do you
say somewhere so popular you look like
my ex-wife haha
do i need to delete that
i guess she didn't like that because now
the stress is back even if you don't
have a job good work out there today i'm
based it's hard being jobless
but at least you have time to watch
canedale isn't that the best thing oh my
god
i could cope with being unemployed if i
had angel
oh
sucker
based
so based
let's sleep together tonight
yo i'll count sheep for you until you
fall asleep okay back to say so back to
say so one sheep two sheep three sheep
four don't fall asleep hey wake up wake
up
okay
this is even work this is what
no no no no no no
i want to sleep now
good job
time
[Music]
cancel your sticks
sticks
oh no i got what sticks
i guess the music uh
when it goes that when it becomes so
weird oh
uh is when
i no no
i just went um in the chat okay i
thought it was a sign that uh there's a
shitty comment there
totally i don't know what else to put
there
emily i can't delete the super jets
she's so cute when she's asleep right
i'll put this in i guess she's so
[\h__\h] cute oh my god okay just so cute
i can't
i can't i can't help it
recording this with bedtime asmr let's
go i'm ripping this you mean you're
recording this okay whatever i mean
there's an archive anyway you don't need
to
she really fell asleep man
is that is that even i heard that you
you're not allowed to sleep in streams
in like was it twitch or youtube
this jobless loser is gonna go to sleep
i think
it's just cute my insomnia okay
uh are you talking about yourself um i
love you
she's writing comments as twitch huh
okay usually your sticks
so what did that mean i fell asleep i
didn't think i it i would be the first
one
she does asmr because she wants the
viewers to fall asleep easier and then
she's the one who falls asleep
yeah
we can go to the uh 10k we can get there
that's and that's pretty cute i'm gonna
give her dad although it's probably fake
she probably didn't really fall asleep
it's all fake
see you again tomorrow my little nerds
good night peach on
i [\h__\h] promised myself five minutes
only and look at the time oh the worst
kind of wait it's already
are you [\h__\h] stupid
it's already
night time
that's not five more minutes
you should have looked at me excuse me i
tried about 100 times you [\h__\h] idiot
now that i think about it i think i
vaguely remember
so stupid sorry lol i'm so [\h__\h]
stupid we could have done [\h__\h] we could
have gotten [\h__\h] done maybe i should
just maybe i should just spam the
depression panels hashtag
no one
[Music]
oh no
oh god okay we have to stream
does taking a pill count as um
it's like one
cycle and we already have to go to the
morning or can we still stream
we should maybe take one
what is
i need that
pill is a cycle huh it has risks
it doesn't really say anything about it
i think it does don't remember how the
stream is tonight
let's get to the morning
no
no no no we don't need that
we're still
fine i think
but the question
is what do we stream
we still have time though
she said what one month 10k it's day
eight is this going by reality that a
month has like 40 to 31 days or is this
shorter
it's not javier
really
ten days
i wonder if we can make it even if we
don't do the sexiest day
it's one million and one oh [\h__\h] ah 10k
in 10 days
okay
it's safe
okay but wait stress goes off by a lot
guys infection goes down
it's really bad
it's really bad guys
no it's really bad for her mentality
stay pure
we will try to do it without
we better have a good stream idea
tomorrow
[Music]
it's not all about follow us she has to
learn that
your mental stability is
thank more important
is the internet angel kangel
why does she always say bless or
whatever shut up
shut up
where are you
you're so cute
because all these lovely people are
willing to listen to me yeah that is
really
that makes me think about
it makes me think thanks man
[Music]
get out of here
why angel you really have to question
that
my biggest fear is abandonment i can't
imagine living a life not being needed
by anyone you guys
[Music]
this is surreal
it it is
well my cats need me and they will
forever nobody cares about me either why
is everyone so sad
thank you guys
don't be so sad
angel's here to cheer you up man
i love you guys for hearing me out i'll
keep working my hardest for you all
okay i'll is she ending already she sure
is bold for a new streamer she said she
loves me
this sounds like
[Laughter]
like a gosling
i don't know about the rest of you but
your face just ah oh thank you wait wait
a second thank you
no take backs now
what
because it's all over if you get bored
of me and i don't want to die yet let's
go let's go
let's go
please don't die oh thank you
i'm bored you're stupid
why are you bored while watching a
stream of mine
[Music]
yeah i said she loves me
you're so cute thank you come tell me
that every day
yes do it why angel
i've always been an angel since i was
born because i'm just too cute
okay that makes a lot of sense i don't
know why that person even asked that
question how did we do look we can make
it it's fine it's fine it's fine we just
need 900 more
oh wait okay that really means we need
to do a good stream if we don't have a
good idea then we have to do the sexy
stream
i've always wait a second first thanks
to everyone who came along to the
today's stream sorry i was a bit all
over the place i'm still new to this
love you all
i've always thought idols and streamers
who made blind and palatable poster
boring as hell but oh how did her tables
have tabled
funny
see now i get it now let's see you can
like check that out here okay
well good job uh on the stream kane joe
good job 75 is yeah pretty nearby
uh uh
we still don't have enough followers to
monetize our content we won't be able to
make rent i don't want to leave you well
if we get evicted i'll just go back to
my parents place but
no don't worry don't worry don't worry
it's only day eight we still have time
phyto
we can do this
okay she's good i think she's good
got it tomorrow
day nine
i can't think of what to do for my next
dream help me yeah okay okay okay
maybe
oh plenty nonstop until you clear it do
a q a write a judge
gigantic turtle around shinjuku
is any of this gonna give me a really
banger idea
yeah like an endurance would probably be
good
and thorns probably but this sounds
crazy
giant
got
a gigantic gigantic that's probably it
endurance will be stressed ah
true
but we can use the idea later on
and maybe still get another extra idea
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] when if we do the the buy
stream then our stress is gonna go so
[\h__\h] high
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
q1a you only need 900 but we only got
like a little bit more than 200 in the
last stream we're being really tactical
here now
a q a i guess i don't know that doesn't
sound like it will be that popular but
in the beginning she just debuted so
when when you just debut then people are
still into the q and a he's laying
around not so much i can't be bothered
gathering questions for q a from a bunch
of nerds
i will do it for you
don't
[Music]
oh don't
uh
what's gonna happen if she has maximum
stress
what if we uh could we just uh
it will be night time and then we can
still stream but we don't have an idea
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
wait can we still does the 10th day
still wait we do have an idea we can do
the nearby stream
but but
spend time together it will give us an
idea probably
yeah it will because of the thing in
here
true okay
[Music]
hopefully a good idea maybe an asmr
stream that would be good tomorrow's the
last day so i can still do something on
the 10th day
okay
let's see
click to give me headphones
are we going out are we going out
what's happening
oh wait that's how we spend time i just
oh
on her head that's how we spend time did
you get an idea though i love you pizza
every time i think about you my brain
gets all fuzzy and happy like it's
melting to syrup
oh god what did you do i'm taking a bag
by all of my lovely fans that is
close i'll always be your one and only
so don't worry nothing good comes from
pursuing room
oh wait look oh that sounds good that
sounds good
what what's going on
what's your name the taste of this
feeling too but they're probably all
single huh so i'll make their brains
feel fuzzy myself ah
so sweet of you
what is this what's better than what's
better than playing games and watching
anime i'm going to the computer and
getting hugs from creatures nothing
you're so could ever what
[Music]
what is lobo tell me
what is that
what it says to martin it's probably
gonna be fine ring
well anyway great idea um
amazing
significant other
[Music]
uh-huh
i can't really imagine
that but okay love yes so lovely
love yes
i love you yeah totally
say it again okay
how about this
oh my god oh my god
right i knew you could understand
reviving
love
i don't know this is really not enough
to express myself
this
i had people just send well i mean you
don't give me much [\h__\h] choice
[Music]
oh my
god
tell me you'll never leave your awesome
girlfriend how can i
okay
[Applause]
okay okay
um
okay
let's do this
let's go
dusk
wait we still have time until the stream
suck up time
there are three things that could give
me an idea
because this will bring us tonight and
then our stress will go down this
one not so good
uh
read the message [\h__\h]
i've been falling asleep with my eyes
open so if you see me doing that please
close my eyes for me thank you
that's so weird but okay
let's watch a movie
don't i'm not ignoring her i'm stressed
too yeah i'm stressed as well
go do it
what do you think about this girls
chick-flick movie looks chic i really
like roman's movies they make me want to
fall in love myself when will i get my
cute ah
round guns are kind of dumb but never a
good way to watch one in actual cinema
but watching peach on is actually kind
of fun i think i would have liked them
on ironically in middle school ah to be
young again
i love britain's when the person just
has fun talking about what they like
she's gonna get that idea no even better
if you learn something new from it one
of the best things about the internet is
that there's so much weird info that
you'd never learn at school floating
around and not that i would really know
what you learned at school because i
never really went oh
i may be a stupid idiot with mental
issues and a horrific academic record
but i still want to share all the things
i've turned up researching the things
that i'm interested in okay stop talking
i'm going to do streams on the show
you know i guess i'll have to start at
the very beginning with the nerds
themselves and i've already done plenty
of research on them let's do this okay
what makes a good uh i don't know if
they're gonna be happy about that stream
[Music]
amazing wow you're such a genius such an
innovative genius clap clap club club
club
wow
what the weather today is so nice before
going out but the internet is called to
me yeah maybe we can go out tomorrow if
we make the 10k otherwise no
as long as you understand i don't i
totally do love you forever
you're done
okay
uh it's streaming time
so this one three times up great thanks
that was having a great microphone i
don't think we have one yet but okay uh
stress goes up mental darkness goes up
but not that much but holy [\h__\h] why does
stress go up so much
oh this one goes up even more oh yeah
that's the sexy stream holy [\h__\h]
affection
down mental darkness uh um um what makes
a nerd
[Music]
rabbit hole bonus stress also
well
we should probably do asmr in that case
stress 88 92
what do you think
even white's dresses down
well this should get us to 10k
asmr let's go
where does [\h__\h] asmr let's go
[Music]
i'm going to be probing and squelching
you ah
surgery handsome
this is legal you can probe my brain all
you like
i mean you don't necessarily have to
interpret those sounds as what she's
trying to make them be maybe they can
sound like something else i don't know
squelch squelch scrub scrounge squelch
he likes it
oh
it's send they like they like it guys
they like you burn is so squishy i love
it
um
[Music]
just like i said actually
now just relax you don't have to think
about anything anymore
please break my
they're enjoying it i can feel my brain
getting smoother
same to bh
tbh
oh my god
um okay time for chat um well thank you
for the red super chat
[Music]
and how do you identify with which name
category you belong to just kidding haha
look at her eyes please break my
does she look like that because she's
going insane
unhappy your brain is already broken yay
okay um
holy
[\h__\h] is she okay
[Music]
the music slowed down a little bit maybe
we can take a few days off for now we
already reached the other goal perhaps
oh wait [\h__\h] i should have didn't read
that sorry oopsie that was resident
monetization
i wish tank is that is that not good for
you are you not gonna be happy about
that
i'm gonna do celebration stream hell
yeah you know 10k is a nice number but
that's about it i had more an old on an
old twitter account and all i did was
post selfies now that i'm making content
with my brain as well i need to surpass
that
10k is just a stepping stone
the first step i'm taking is a legendary
angel but i'm gonna get everyone to
celebrate it anyway lol
oh it's wonderful it's like rainbow
color
hopefully that's gonna get us a lot of
love and
super chats
[Laughter]
wow you're amazing
wow so inspiring
inspiring let's go girl get that bread
hell
yeah
we have some time though to go to
distress so
probably should do this um
this is like uh
the best thing we can do
hospital
is hospital even better to de-stress
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] why would i go to the
hospital
oh that's like therapy i guess ah
but this is like natural therapy
[Music]
[Laughter]
lucille
you get that new ideas oh yeah from this
one oh it's probably a yamaha idea
oh we can read the stuff that she read
before
i hope your brains are feeling really
good after that i'll be here to squelch
your brain any time you want all you
have to do is open up one of my videos
you know what they say a lot but tell me
a day keeps the doctor away because
you're the doctor especially if it's
performed by a cute girl hi kendra i'd
love to have a chat with you do you mind
if we exchange giants hell no stop shout
i need to read your tweets i'm gonna
become the top streamer let's go that's
so cute
what's something you guys are really
into these days mine is a secret are you
into me
oh oh nobody's some more noise
i love everything about you jenna oh my
god she's so needy um
what
[Music]
okay
as long
as you're happy i guess
oh
okay
[Music]
you're looking like a real pun you're
looking real punctual right now
[\h__\h] you
[Music]
okay
hey to you my girl
okay [\h__\h] you're streaming tonight get
your [\h__\h] together
ah i think it's more interesting now
than anyway wonderland it used to be so
sad oh i don't know
um
maybe
wow um
that's some deep [\h__\h] man
so deep girl
don't
me i'll punch you
this girl like cow how can you please
her
i don't care punch me try
fine i'm gonna cry in the arms of my
darling nerds instead okay you're so
much better
the dinner the day is coming out
[Music]
love
lavo lava
okay let me see though um how much
stress that is oh
no stress oh
and a [\h__\h] ton of streamers
well that's wonderful
why the [\h__\h] not
and then maybe tomorrow we can take the
day off we worked so hard
[Music]
that's where the good [\h__\h] is at yeah
okay okay hi kitties it's me angel save
your cyberspace your crosses mine to
bear
10k we are actually have 20k
do we get a 20k celebration as well good
meowning meowvining bold statement
congrats oh my god
oh my god thank you for the super chat
i'm gonna do a super chat reading after
once this stream is one to celebrate
celebrate what gospel did you not read
the title
10k
club i can't read love oh wait we're not
writing comments by the stream girl
you need to step up your game i always
rate the super chats
no matter no matter
how many there are i always do it take
your time excuse me hello
hello
disrespect
[Music]
so proud of you
so proud of you for putting yourself out
there
yeah
impressive
meowvin
i knew you would make it
thank you for believing in me
you're so cute you could get way more
subscribers i know i'm like oh my god
and i'm only going to get bigger and
bigger i'm going to shine brighter than
ever so just watch
can't wait to see you guys
you're so sweet
[Music]
everyone subscribed we need her to blow
up
i'm gonna cry stop
oh my god bless uh
celebrating with something tasty yeah
let's order some kfp come on
let's talk about the internet today i
bet you guys are curious about how i
came to be
okay tell us about it
no i really hated adults they are always
so fake
oh emotional time
i know right i'm 14 okay cool good for
you
i'm 10. are you
allowed to be on the internet
i hated being at home i hated school i
hold up in my room with my pc to avoid
all the adults in my life
there were also a lot of adults on the
internet but they were all true to
themselves
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h]
going to school
hey
hey don't tell her what to do she needs
to [\h__\h] up her life herself
she's ranting no i'm opening myself up
to you i'm pouring out my feelings and
emotions
why do i find you being a dropout cube
because you have a
you want to protect me
you wanna
be there for me
how are you shouting and also this cute
that's not fair pat pat thank you they
weren't ashamed of being into anime or
manga or porn or whatever
they were so free so natural
wow inspiring
cool
so thirsty oh my god
the internet is the internet is for porn
[Music]
you remember that world of warcraft song
because that's that's
why i know it
i guess that wasn't too interesting but
i'm glad i could share with you guys
bliss
okay hello oh you for our cinnamon roll
oh b nerds thanks for celebrating 10k
with me i'm going to keep working hard
so that everyone in the world knows my
name please keep sending me your support
um i drew some fan out for you so um
that's cute i think i saw that like in
the in the steam
um
like notes of this game that they had
like actual people send in fan art to
put into the game that's pretty cool
yeah yeah
and to celebrate even though i'm gonna
spend all the super chats on an even
better setup gotta invest it all into
delivering more high quality shoes for
everyone
wow did she really
did she really write that i can't
believe it
wait how many viewers how many followers
did we get like 17k oh my god
it died yeah
that is
actually
yeah only for private even
it's like
she's
she really means it guys
i love you too i'm so proud of you
[Music]
yeah yeah
of course of course of course i would
never cheat on you she's growing up yeah
and we we helped her grow up oh my god
wow
yes i'm the best in the world [\h__\h] yeah
oh my god
okay
so [\h__\h] awkward
talk about hey i'm sorry
ever forgive you i will
okay i'll talk tomorrow [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
monetization approval now we won't get
evicted because those online nerds can
pay our rent for us yeah
that's the bullet there i don't want to
have to stream out on the streets well
obviously
yeah
she left me on the radio
oh my god
she likes this one
[Music]
okay um i didn't go to tomorrow
oh we're not doing anything today
can we at least like de-stress
oh
i guess not
[Music]
yay
i got the underbugger
[Music]
let's say let's see what it says uh we'd
like you to do a review for our not so
flavored cola
yeah food review is nice and they said
they'll pay me with a year's supply of
natural flavorful ah
wow that is uh yeah great payment um
so worth it oops [\h__\h] well oh i guess
we'll do it anyway because it's funny as
a stream
good job's a job i'll do my best but wow
this means i'm a real professional
streamer now
wow
so proud of you good job here i have
cats keep the print does this actually
work though do i like
is does this raise anything like
affection
european btm
okay but we don't have to stream today
we don't even have a new goal yet so we
should
focus on de-stressing
i guess we can go out and get an idea we
can go to akihabara
stress down a section of
in here 6680 6680
[Music]
don't know but hospital is also just 10
down on stress
mental darkness too though
but at least we
we still
get an extra idea for that one
yeah i think we should go to one of
those
yeah affection needs to go up too
hospital okay maybe next time next time
next time next time
[Music]
although we do have a lot of ideas right
now i guess i love going outside yeah
you needed that
oh did she tweet oh
oh there's wings there's some shopping
in the complex in akiva i may or may not
wear something special next thing so
keep your eyes peeled
what what is that is it cosplay i think
my favorite is the pico cosplay
is it from dragon ball special beef
channel me blessing all my haters she's
so okay that's pretty [\h__\h] cute
can i like it
yo
streaming some retro games so people
will like that one i think
nice
okay
amazing
you genius
okay maybe we can stream that tonight
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah okay i guess let's go
bitch's camera walls be only filled with
gotcha game screenshots and [\h__\h] what
are you having a stroke
she's she's uh confused
but she's got the spirit
okay let's see oh that's not even
um predicting that many new followers
hmm
wait can i do the same stream again no
right
no you can't okay get me to say stop oh
stress stress
[Music]
but that's a lot of followers
that one seems okay too
[Music]
that one is also just stressful not
worth it
[Music]
that one is better though than the sexy
stream
helpful fame yeah
sponsorship
ah
under stress isn't bad you can do it
how about we stream this and then go to
the hospital the day after but even the
hospital only takes away 10
10 points of stress that's nothing
sleep no stress stress too high
don't stream
okay
good idea
that's only six too though but okay
johnny what can you do what can you do
we missed out on streaming tonight yeah
didn't we have a
a stream the last night anyway the
little celebration stream or was that
one more day before that fine right now
okay okay
mentally she's doing fine but
the stress man
it's tough out there
yeah we also have to stream a lot to
keep the multiplayer up and go i know
walk up early and then climb the sun is
still comfy
what do you mean a healthy lifestyle
actually makes you feel good oh kiwawa
if i live like this every day would that
make me happy
well i think that's yeah the sunlight
that makes you feel good oh she got
another extra minus two
bless the sun
hallelujah dance around the sun pray to
the sun god phoenix kiwawa
i am the sun i don't have to go outside
and
uh uh feel the sun because i am the sun
i i am my own son
okay oh my god that's amazing
i am the best yes yes this
this one you're so [\h__\h] stupid
i don't know
and now she uses
can i also ask you this what huh
okay um you're too much for me to handle
honestly i can't i can't with you
what do we do um
internet or go how long does it take if
i go out
fifty eighty six
six
we don't really need
it's better to go to harajuku because we
don't need to really get rid of the
mental darkness points we're doing
pretty fine
and stress
we get this the same amount of less
stress in harajuku
[Music]
if the mental darkness goes up a lot as
well that's when it would be worth it
and then it's night time and then we'll
stream
yeah we're gonna
we get an uh
an idea as well okay
affection
wait what if is it not good that we get
a hundred
i think it's good let's go out again
yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay
see james
ah isn't that what was the ball jointed
dolls or something like that i so
expensive but i really wanted one so no
no that's not it
babe
wait what what is the stand for
is it the dolls
that's so expensive but i really want
one so i gave in
yeah isn't that actually the dress not
the dolls
[Music]
it's a dress
of a specific shape i think i know what
she's talking about
for sure what how's it going so much fun
lots of people who think dressing out is
personality traits though also thanks
for helping me pick my cord i'm going to
show my nerds how cute i'm looking at
tonight
that sounds
great
i'm so tired of being a stream i'm gonna
become a cosplayer instead
aren't you already a cosplayer
you can be both i hate that sticker well
i hate you
stupid [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] but our stress is back to
50 let's go
we're doing well we're doing fine
so why don't we want to stream
we should do this one
maybe
[Music]
or this one we should do this one
asmr
[Music]
or
24 we could go to the hospital on the
following day
[Music]
sponsor
not the sexy stream oh no
no okay but asmr is also
probably gonna be borderline sexy no
oh start with sponsor okay let's do that
let's go normal for a while
and if we really need a lot of
followers then we can still do the crazy
stuff
okay
serving time let's drink some natto
flavors coca-cola
[Music]
thank you i've got some business to
discuss today literal business like
money business
400 watching that's more than i have
right now
wow she's more successful than me
please don't become a seller shut up
cash money shut up i guess
you did it yay today i'll be reviewing
this new natto flavor cooler
ew that sounds so disgusting here it is
i'm gonna give it what if she froze up
on stream
here it goes looks gross exactly it does
so true i'd never buy that well maybe
you should shut up though
you should be nice about the things that
i'm being sponsored for
although they probably know that their
product tastes like [\h__\h]
they probably are aware of it
yeah yeah that was uh
yeah
i could see that coming
best sponsorship this was your best
moment yet
this is gonna get clipped this shouldn't
be fit for human consumption is this a
new bio weapon what is this look at her
she's so pissed off
wow i think i'm a fan now okay
they like her going crazy
great advertising are you sure about
that are you gonna buy it i don't think
you're gonna buy it
we're at super chat yo because because
the sponsored one they're not coming
pains of the sponsorship
yeah um
i love you thank you
yeah i can sense the trolls well i'm not
going to pin that one
i mean uh it's an acquired taste i think
if you have the taste buds for it you'll
really love it
good job good job stay professional
i guess we have to pin something best
sponsorship
yeah if this is meant to be reverse
psychology it's working well i kind of
want to buy now wonderful
let's go
back pedaling nice recovery
good
[Music]
don't say that
she's gonna get sponsorships in the
future too don't worry about it
they love her
and you can't tell me that the people
who gave her that sponsorship didn't
know that this is gonna happen
if they give her a disgusting product
like that
or something that people are so split on
like natal where it's just which is like
pretty 50 50.
you know
okay she's reading haha i think i was a
bit over the top but i hope you enjoyed
it anyway
yeah
yeah it was funny
if this is meant to be rendered
i want to buy it now
that's good
hey what's that supposed to mean buy it
because i did a good job of making it
look tasty exactly look at that sponsor
people she's selling your product
anyway that's all bless
bless that girl
that was so good that i did a spit take
what because i was so surprised at how
good that it was you can get your own
tasty fizzy natto goodness at any
convenience store in the country so give
it a try bless and
oh
so sweet
i wish i could give it a like
[\h__\h] what did i get myself into i should
be glad i didn't get arrested for
advertising such a disgusting drink and
they're still gonna send me a year's
worth of
it drink it for me pizza please we can
just throw it away i'm not gonna drink
that [\h__\h]
just throw it away
i want more followers and pleasant money
i need more clout more
okay
well then work hard [\h__\h]
oh my god
love
don't take max you will love me forever
yes um
sure
are you happy now
she's happy good okay what do we do
what do we do
[Music]
stress goes down with that
oh we should maybe we should go to the
hospital now
hospital to wash that disgusting taste
out
yeah
very good idea
we have enough ideas for now
why does the affection go up
interesting careful
affection okay i see it's a bad thing to
get too high on infection as well
she's gonna tell her i hate her then
how about i just don't answer her
messages for a while but that's probably
gonna also influence the mental darkness
[Music]
okay let's let's go to the hospital
whatever let's do it
from 66 to 56 i think we're going 10
down
and then this should be six
it's nothing bad about going to therapy
take care of yourself
mm-hmm
is it going is it going down even the
happiest of internet angels have to go
to the internet psych sometimes why
didn't i get a shout out i even gave her
super chat
oh
that can't be true i read every single
jack
and i went to the psych today i had it
booked for the morning so i was really
worried that i wasn't going to wake up
for it but peach and woke me up in time
it went really well i'm so good yeah
yeah i guess so
okay one day we'll be on one of those
couples that can afford to call a taxi
to go wherever we want
oh my god yes please uber everyone
i [\h__\h] hate the public transport
this
i'm just trying to agree with you
oh my god how do i how do i make her
dislike me
none of this wait want to stream the
stream maybe we can stream something
where she will dislike me
yeah this one this one goes down to 77
but stress holy [\h__\h]
this one is stress 17
gamer girl
i think i'm just gonna play some retro
games maybe or or this one
because
affection goes down
[Music]
ah going on tinder dinda
cause it's i thought it was her going on
tinder not me
ah maybe uh yeah maybe tomorrow
okay then we don't have to focus too
much on that but
asmr let's play some more
yeah it is her going oh
oh her affection for me
ah okay okay yeah sorry that makes sense
okay
let's do a stupid stream
let's do this
[Music]
apparently she's now into asmr streamer
yeah
i'm not sure how that happened because i
don't even like it
i read anything a lot so post your
suggestions in the comments oh [\h__\h] how
do you say let's [\h__\h] go in asmr
let's [\h__\h] go
okay
getting bad party
let's
you know what to do
[Music]
look like she's against it
[Laughter]
all right guys go wild in the comments
oh um
[Music]
no
what is that
[Music]
[\h__\h]
the [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[\h__\h] idiot
no
[Music]
she did say go wild they did go wild
yeah
i remember this night forever it kind of
feels like she's forcing herself oh
okay no no common story today because
it's pretty a bit
blessed
cute
why are you guys saying bless or
whatever i wanted to delete this comment
it's too late now
she doesn't she didn't even say goodbye
oh sh
24 minus four
four plus four plus plus four yeah
okay and the only event because of all
your weird requests thanks guys this is
the first and the last time i'll do
something like this got it oh [\h__\h]
hey
funny how it's all innocent when i talk
about
in front of my
in front of my so like it's no big deal
let's assume
okay one what not between
people can change
[Music]
like what what does that mean
what does that mean
ah significant other ah
uk are you okay girl
you okay
[Music]
hello
sorry
for existing
okay um we're not streaming tomorrow we
need to um control the chaos
that we created
good morning sunshine
we don't
want to go to the hospital
[Music]
ah
stress stress
seventy
[\h__\h] no
[Music]
they're all bad
tinder she alright i wanted to do tinder
uh does that make her happy
wait a second where was that oh god too
many windows so many windows
on windows
didn't it oh it doesn't it doesn't do
anything like this or it doesn't tell
you ahead of time
[Music]
will i get another match afterwards if i
say no
i want more
i mean the horse man that's beautiful
like
cute
[Music]
are we going out with the horse excuse
me
met a guy that looks way hotter in real
life than his [\h__\h] well he's not on
my level some kind of friends on him but
wow there's a lot about dinner i still
don't know how
he looked better than on his pictures
great
i guess
i'm gonna optimize everyone to make it
so that the only streamer they can enjoy
is kendall
sounds like a [\h__\h] genius idea
uh we're gonna stream tonight
shut up
uh yeah yeah shut up
oh [\h__\h] what is why is that so stressful
that should be fun for you
[Music]
how how about how does one successfully
keep down the stress man
the lowest one would be this one
i'll go with this one or don't stream
maybe we should maybe we shouldn't
stream
not don't stream every day
okay
i guess
okay sleepy time sleepy time sleepy time
good idea
nail
yeah um streak streak no more
sorry fans sorry guys i have a tummy
horse tonight i have to cancel my stream
i'm so sorry guys
i'll feel better soon
[Laughter]
go to tomorrow uh
were you able to sleep
should have been able to what is this
music
should have been able to redeem my
silverware for reaching 100k subscribers
by now have we not shown enough people
in the world my cute and adorable face
she
she sounds so bad and the music too
there's no point in talking about it if
the next steps we take are crucial so
let's keep going as long as it doesn't
kill me
oh
okay
when i woke up the sun was already
setting ah
she slept too long
and still feeling so lazy after sleeping
so much can i just sleep forever
what's she saying she's her mental
darkness is fine
oh no
what i'm telling her to die
no
well i don't wanna can i just not answer
what if i is it better to not answer in
this case
[Music]
she'll probably
be fine though she'll probably joke
around she's stupid
sure
yay
funny that means i don't have to bother
living anymore
girl
okay but minus one stress
she needed to vent she needed to vent
that that's okay that's on this animal
i'm listening to her she can vent to me
i'll listen to her and her stress will
go down yeah it's joke i can't believe
you're still with me is it because i'm
just that cute
yes
yes oh my god anymore
is acceptable more than three is when
she's like
yeah yeah i love you too
[Music]
no
not lying stop crying
okay
thanks
shut up now shut up now okay it's uh we
still have some time before streaming
[Laughter]
let's do something we can reduce some
stress here i think we're gonna play
or hmm
[Music]
that gets dangerously close to
a
hundred affection but
but
other than that it looks great but wait
it would be tomorrow we wouldn't be able
to stream
and we should do something else
let's do
you love this forever and always right
you'll never get bored of me right so i
might get bored of you first i'm kidding
you're so funny
okay okay okay
current for dinner tonight tomorrow and
the day after oh that sounds lovely oh
man maybe that's what i'll eat tonight
i still have some of my um curry that i
made a while ago in my freezer
good idea
oh my god
he says genius kangel
you're you're ignoring me
well at least she's making food she's
making food for us or maybe she's
ordering but still she's ordering for us
for us guys
let's go curry
[Music]
okay streaming time she looks so cute
that's silly stressful
we're we're not even at the 100k yet
though
are we going too slow
follow our lines are we going too slow i
wonder
what do you think guys from experience
sexy stream
it does it could be good because it does
lower the affection as well and stress
right now is okay as
yeah okay
it's number one we might not do number
two we can just take a look we need to
test the waters you know
[Music]
we yeah we need those followers too
okay
oh god oh god what is this going to be
what is this going to be
[Music]
close your eyes everyone everyone
close your eyes
i'm going to hide the screen if
something yummy happens
good morning hey kids i hope all you
nerds are going for it today too
for what
i'm really going through it for what
i want to no don't say that
don't say that we want the chat to be a
happy place
you also goof always trying so hard it's
okay if you jobless didn't i hear this
before just being alive is enough
twelve thousand people watching
[Music]
this is pretty fun so far here comes the
most javas of them all
oh
this is just a taste dream
[Music]
you try harder than any of us this is
just wholesome but personally i hate
being told that just being alive is
enough it's such an empty ass compliment
i mean i've never heard anyone say that
ever before but sure yeah
i feel that tell him this is this is
fine
this is fine
it's just uh yeah
having a normal conversation i really
have a really good pick-me-up for you
guys today oh
what what
what
oh
love love love i always wanted to try
that but now that i have i'm sorry oh my
god remember remember when i started
giving out kisses for red super chats
and i was like so embarrassed about it i
was like
like i was legit embarrassed though
i don't know what that means i'll be
your team yell
[Music]
why
i want to get rid of that
this pattern feels forces when you feel
weird
a thank you case for you more
[Laughter]
i know you're cute you're cute
the chat is so cute i love the chat
oh it's a pokemon reference ah
all right get pumped what does that mean
go lifting or stop
let's see what you guys thought okay
that was a great stream i don't know
what's so stressful about this
love
yeah
love and thank you for the super chat
too i love a man who can send me
don't say it like that girl
i bang venue case for you
thanks please go die
hey that's probably not the reply he
expected
bryce thank you
wow okay
worth it
worth it hey did you all like what you
saw today if you did let's play again
tomorrow
you're so mad oh wait actually no can
you [\h__\h] up please i can't stop thinking
about you now i can constant i thought
it was a hater comment but it's just it
just starts off weird it's actually
pretty fun did some basic ass pandering
and my stats are skyrocketing have i
found my shortcuts to fame
but the longest way around is the short
shortest way home right but i can't just
ignore this grove hmm
i see
i see she's figuring it all out
she's figuring it all out
hey do you think it's okay for me to
keep living like this
yeah
what's wrong
just thinking about ew
is that because of the mental darkness
it's not even that high
i was just wondering if anyone would
even miss me if i were gone they don't
even they don't have to watch me they
can just go watch some other streamer
ah
that is uh the stream or depression
oh
well if you
if you really
don't want it to then you gotta go the
girlfriend route you know
gotta go younger and be like don't watch
anyone else so i'll kill you
i mean the [\h__\h]
the fun of you guys watching other
people
it doesn't bother me that much i mean
i mean
no i'm not i'm okay as long as i'm your
number one see that's how you should
think angel as long as they still think
of you as their number one you don't
have to worry about it they'll always
come back to you they always prioritize
you yay
it's getting all great
uh
guys don't read too much into any of
this what's in the stream or what's
being said here okay
this is really weird
um
uh wait so
they don't have to watch me they can
just no way no
you're just saying that no
you really like me for me not because
i'm pretty
yes
well this is some serious conversation
well done
oh god what if she likes me too much
after this conversation
i'm trying to get her stress down though
what do people even like about me
you're everything
where's the stress going um as if no one
wants a factory defect like me what's
happening
the face oh [\h__\h] ah
yeah cause like
yeah even though it's just the outside
girls are often very happy about being
complimented about their looks like that
but hey i said everything that's
everything
i feel like i shouldn't be allowed to
live
please live
is what i would say
but this is a very
or of course they're allowed
this is very difficult
please
don't say that staying in love is so
hey come on no
we're going for this together okay
do you love me
um
[Music]
yes
maybe not
okay
are you happy now
do you love me they really love me they
love me loving me do you love me love
love love love
yes so
i love love i really really love love i
really really really really really
really love you
i love love love you too
okay then stop this crazy music and put
on some happy music again
what should i do
um
i would say do your best in life
because i don't want to pressure her
into having to do this you know
is that good like how it's so vague
sorry um
sorry i was feeling really awful about
everyone after talking with pizza and i
feel like i can keep going okay it was a
decent conversation i guess we we did
fine and we're almost at 100k girl
almost pizza boys me sometimes and can
be really flaky but it's times like this
where i remember that i really do love
pizza
ah don't don't think so much about it
though
um
um sorry
sorry about that i'm dead no don't
don't
uh
oh
i love you
okay
she's fine
we're gonna get 100k now girl let's go
you know some things may be cliched but
they're cliched for a reason like this
what
welcome home daddy would you like to
have your dinner first or bath or
me
um
that is
quite the question
what does he
[Music]
you're so naughty no [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] now
not that it's a bad thing
shut up what
what oh okay
wait did we skip a day because of that
alert i guess i'll leave the answer you
guys some that you should close your dms
but
[Music]
oh my god i think we skipped the night
i didn't expect that
had rejected your pizza
oh my god shut up now oh my god please
shut up sexy stream
yay
[Music]
no
you're so stupid
[Music]
i'm so done with you girl
we'll be together in our next life too
right i mean that's a that's a nice way
of saying it too
yay
forever forever and ever in the next
life too and in the next live too i
promise i will
find you
now sounds kind of yonder there now that
i think about it that last line of
hinotoni
kind of yandere
yonder is stalking
um
of course i will of course i will what
else could i do what else could i
possibly do in this game
okay our stress is not so bad um it's
night time we have to stream
i think i think it will be fine
um
no
[Music]
stress 85 81 85 95 okay let's do
let's do 81 let's do angel explains one
what makes a nerd because
we should be able to
ha we're not going to 100k
they all are just ah this one has no
no arrow app for followers
uh maybe this one oh
gamer girl free for communication
followers
[Music]
communication bonus driving wellness ah
lolita
okay maybe she'll actually change her
clothes is she actually gonna be dressed
up
[Music]
cute girl incoming now
how cute this is angel your favorite
gothic angel oh how sinful is my beauty
oh julie bjolte
she tried why the past tense why are you
not wearing it now
every beautiful rose has its phones well
there's chunibio in the chat and on
screen let's go
she looks the same yeah
today i went to harajuku and bought some
gothic lolita clothes and then i went
about my day in them
okay okay kill killed indeed i want to
go too of course we all want to go
if only we could travel
so you're going to date with me on
yay is that stressful i wonder
is how does it go scary i heard it is
no
there's a lot of there's a [\h__\h] of
scouts like in harajuku
like weird scouts that will come up to
you and ask
if you want to work for their model
agency or whatever but they're like the
tiniest scammiest weirdest companies
ever
they feel really good to wear what you
like it feels really good to wear with
like the most important opinion is your
own let's go
i want to see more lolita clubs yeah
yeah
i had a lot of those like even the first
time when i came to japan just as a
tourist and then later on as well when i
lived there
i would i would go to harajuku or
shibuya and there's always these weird
weird scouting companies
and are like hey you
you
what what visa are you on in japan can
you work for us
let's go out together lolita yeah why
the hell not why the hell not
what the hell not dress your age hey
she i think she's pretty young what do
you mean
how old do you think she is
i said when you have a point
i could i'll believe that i wear
whatever i want no matter how old i get
that's good that's the spirit
she's in her 20s how do you know was
that like was there an explanation on
that somewhere
that was a short stream
you should stream longer you should
stream like six hours minimum
i want to see more linda cloves
so
yeah i've got to pick the twitter later
oh you guys better give me a million
trillion kisses and likes
let's both go out together and lolita
we could have a good day oh yeah let's
eat crabs together
and take purikura
oh
i love going to harajuku with friends
whoa
i wouldn't quite uh called this
gothic lolita but maybe it's some kind
of sub category that i don't know about
aren't you too hopeful that no i'll be
buried in lolita
i think i could go until i'm 25 no maybe
30. okay well i guess she's at least
under 25.
we know that now
you good
you good i like your
picture she's not gonna reply to me and
she
all right
new twitter
i'm gonna get a huge rest tonight so if
you've seen this post promise me you'll
go to bed early today and get lots of
sleep oh
she's so awesome sometimes we'll see
each other again some of our fellow
energy internet angel out
i bought some candle merch just merciful
i want
to take it to school with me sounds
lovely
[Music]
okay
i wonder if we need 100k until like day
20 because we need um 10k until
uh day 10 right
[Music]
almost at the one on the stress yeah we
need to go down with that um
we should
definitely not stream tonight
and maybe play
games or do
tinder again
um right because that reduced
didn't that reduce stress as well
sweet
stress goes up though
no tinder
[Music]
videos i am just dreaming 81 that's so
little i need something bigger than that
ah
it's something
that reduces what that lowest stress are
you sure about that
i doubt it
although i do want to see what's on
there
and there's no [\h__\h] way that that
reduces stress oh unless she i guess
maybe she uses it as a out uh
ben venting output or something like
that
[Music]
oh wait it doesn't even pass
past time
[Music]
enjoying her stuff a lot more than i
thought wow they're so nice oh my god
oh my god
they're pretty nice
i can't post what stress goes up see
affection mental darkness is not good
[\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
uh we don't want to do that
how about going somewhere
88 88.75
too
[Music]
i think
oh
there they all go
down by 10
[Music]
and affection goes up the same way
everywhere
but this one at least also reduces
mental darkness as well
[Music]
i guess we'll go here
wait what what is that
why is there a secret text there
what is that
it's secret i can't click on it
and i've been feeling really worn out so
i went to the hospital i think i'll pull
through so don't worry about me keep the
super chat
girl girl
i'm just a stupid maggot of mentally ill
trash streamer but i feel so much better
knowing that patrons with me what are
you talking about you're fine
you're fine girl she doesn't react to my
headphones
oh wait should i went to ah
oh yeah okay that's okay my room is so
messy i want the roomba but i don't
think it could get over this
yeah you have to clean isn't that ironic
in order to use a roomba which cleans
[\h__\h] you have to first clean
i agree girl that is [\h__\h]
that makes no sense
oh my god
[Music]
she's such a pain in the ass
okay thank you
yeah whatever
okay at least she shuts up now day 17 is
night time we're only a little way we're
going to stream now
and we're going to stream the least
stressful thing
which is this one
and then maybe we can get a celebration
stream going again
[Music]
nation hello all the nerds out there
watching my stream i've been thinking
how do you define nerd
cute thanks for the explanation she's
just started hey
listen
came to a podcast hell yeah 20k people
watching i did a bit of research and i
found definition in a book that i like
oh
which one it says they're enthusiasts
about self coaches like anime or people
who are passionate about hobbies and
stuff
okay you know nothing bad about that
hey don't say that no
so me
it's me the guy who's too much of a
coward didn't even commit to being a
nerd
okay
so weird
does that mean i'm a nerd too oh my gosh
she'll probably get go in a good tangent
with that one
some of them may immerse themselves in
the fabricated world unreachable by
others and lack sociality
dot dot dot
some big words there
indeed
she's speaking from experience maybe
implying people are on the internet are
socially adept oh should we delete that
that was probably fine
i don't wanna i want to delete something
though
i wanna delete [\h__\h]
yo that's me nurture scary no no no no
no no no no no
i like that i don't think sacrificing
sociality for your passions is bad
despite what other people think
nice yes give them give them some
courage and some
confidence we all have zero sociality
anyway so don't sweat the small stuff
and just live for whatever you like oh
my angel
oh
yeah
through that hell yeah i don't want to
live in a society we're living in a
society i haven't heard that one in a
while
are you a nerd too of course she is
and you're all welcome to immerse
yourselves in the fabricated world of my
streams as much as you like oh that
sounds like a good stream today
i think she did a good job got it nods
no need to tell me change i'm already
there
it sounds like something kfc would say
you always know what to say i love you
[Music]
let's see what you guys thought
does that mean i'm in there too
uh exactly because you can't escape my
cuteness can you
spam
can you escape my cuteness carefully
we're all there so we should get along
with each other are you a nerd too kane
joe
hey i sure am but as for what kind
you'll just have to find out for
yourself by watching my streams
i think i know
a cosplay and gothic lolita nerd you are
and nothing bad about that
nice dream
nice trail
today's content was a bit different
i think all of you guys are my cuties
yes even your antisocial people and so
come and follow the burn table with me
it's always so much fun watching you my
sweet angel keep doing what you thought
twitter is my safe place i love these
people we're over 100k
good for the people who thrive in
society or whatever but at the end of
the day we're all hats is running uh on
our endless wheels and i'm perfectly
happy being delusional thank you very
much
that's the spirit
celebration stream
huh i'm not getting as many subscribers
as i would have liked you got 100k man
the moment you let your guard drop
around these online nerds you're dead in
the water so i have to pick myself up
and gain a whole bunch of followers and
subscribers in one shot
she wants to do one of those crazy
streams again
you're gonna die from stress
one million here we come let's go and if
it looks like we won't make it we should
kill ourselves together
that way we'd been
we would be in heaven together as well
[Music]
funny
i can't do anything uh
wow
oh my god let's go
i'm dead
[Music]
don't cry she's crying don't cry
go tomorrow
[Music]
no
oh my god are you [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
i'm not going to do it
hey
this is probably stressful too and what
if i what
blackout
it
i can't close it no i can't
don't you
what what if i what if i
purposefully like um
because it seems like i have to what if
i just cut somewhere where it doesn't
can i even do that
like what
what
[Applause]
is this my ending now
is this my ending
[Music]
[Applause]
some people say i should hide the screen
so i'll do it okay
[Applause]
i clicked go once i think it's not
enough i think she wants me to cut her
more than once
girl
girl no
it's two
oh no
one
i have to do it like three times a girl
[\h__\h] okay um she's uh alive
all good
uh
oh minus fifteen minus twenty
yay uh
that's pretty good i feel alive my arms
are gonna end up like baguettes if we
keep i keep doing it though
hmm
looks painful but i promise it's nothing
the pain my wrists feel is really
nothing compared to
what darkness an important message oh no
oh no
where did we end up why
[Applause]
oh
cheer up we're going to the hospital
we're not streaming we're going to the
hospital
girl
wait we are i didn't i didn't tell her
to stream
she's doing it on her
hey
girl
hello
you know some girls just can't help but
cut themselves into the night um
oh [\h__\h]
i can't do [\h__\h]
for all sorts of maybe maybe this helps
her by venting for attention as a cry
for help because it suits their brain
it's complicated
uh where why why
why didn't we go here
i hear you out thank you come here i'll
give you a hug thank you she needs it
she [\h__\h] needs it
it's complicated there's no way other
people will be able to truly understand
your pain and sadness
angel
it's how it be it to be like that
uh
ah if you imagine correct like this
isn't so bad just don't have to let it
happen more than three times apparently
it's okay
we're not at the ending yet
we all have things that make us upset so
i never judge can you stream like normal
and not whatever hey she needs to vent
nothing matters and you don't care that
you feel so pathetic
all you want is to do is disappear okay
can't be like
you're unable to forgive yourself for
leaving such a horde in ugly existence
hey at least she got her 100k play
button
when did that come in can we do a stream
about that please
she got the silver plate
yo
[Music]
okay
congratulations
on that let's see the positives come on
please ask for help from others
especially when things get too
unbearable that's not you being weak it
takes a huge amount of courage to reach
out
well yeah exactly you need help too
let's go to the hospital girl
don't dm k angel with your problems
because dealing with them is a pain
come on we need to get her back on track
we need to get her back on track guys
[Music]
ah she's happy
she's happy i think
[Music]
this is my first time reaching so many i
don't know what's going to happen from
here so i'm a bit nervous but it feels
good to see my stats climb i know i'm
always complaining about the nerds and
stuff but i wouldn't be here without
their support and their faith
i need to thank them for their devotion
they are the ones that turned me from an
internet addicted girl to an angel
for my next stream i'm gonna talk a bit
about the internet and try to tell
everyone how grateful i am for all of
them
we're getting a good free stream for
lunch
okay we do need also new ideas
um
but
wait we can get an idea from medication
probably not a good one
oh
redemption arc so i think we should do
this and then stream
uh the stream okay let's go
[Music]
are you good oopsy oh my god this is
weird
spent the whole day lasting a rumble
peach on injury storage stress gun
batteries charged hope also restored
marriage soon world priest achieved
humanity i'm cancelled
that sounds perfect love cuddling movie
wait i forgot to answer her [\h__\h] i feel
like a cozy little kitty but anyway
speaking of cats we gotta talk about
schradinger's cat oh
into the conspiracy theory stream again
why she wants to do a stream wish
possible cats but does she really
understand that schrodinger's cat is not
really a cat
this sounds like me
oh my god
amazing it's not a conspiracy apparently
amma is the best yes yes yes yes
yes she is
okay
well that seems good so far
uh
yeah i've been trying to uh i can't read
the secret guys i've been trying to but
i can't
okay go to dusk we still have time can
you buy me some eel
unagi i worked really hard on serving
today so go go to the supermarket and
get me the biggest one they have
you you want a uh unagi dog
is that what you want with that eel
you're gonna
cook it right
give her some meds
i will you know what let's try it
like two once per day
so 68 72 okay how much does it
ah wait only one
[Music]
it's not worth it is it three for an
idea oh [\h__\h]
64-28
it also has an impact on our stream
we're having a celebration stream
[Music]
ah
maybe not no no no
[Music]
maybe not we're having an important
stream we can't [\h__\h] that up but maybe
we can
oh we can do this for example more video
streaming again
[Music]
we should do this
and then stream
last oblivion dark and silent and
complete i found freedom losing all
hopeless freedom oh
watch the movie about the secret club
for fighting you don't talk about that
you should definitely never talk about
it it was so good i never watched that
movie
i started smacking pizza as a joke but
pizza and father was getting a free
backpack
oh she wants to talk about more
conspiracy theories but i don't think
that i have to dwell too much on that
and plus i guess believing in them is
kind of like its own brand of happiness
for those that do i think i'll talk
about microchips next next yeah those
are one of my favorites
i remember watching a talk show once and
this guy on it was talking about an
urban legend and another guest was like
you've got microchip didn't you and the
guy was like i could tell you but then
i'd have to kill you with the most
deadpan face ever
well
that was what made me look into this
whole microchip business in the first
place i guess i want to talk about it
because of how plausible it is
okay
from fight club to microchips
makes a lot of sense
as always as expected from our genius
now let's go streaming
huh i couldn't sleep so i tried to think
of stuff that is more valuable than
money my conclusion nothing
okay
are you good are you good
we're doing this one now
hopefully it goes well
oopsie
hey joe hi kenjo hi
[Music]
it's my channel
i'll tell you guys a bit more about
myself
[Music]
oh
you've grown so much
your channel grew so big so fast our
super popular angel
i feel like you've said some results
before i'm an angel that came down to
earth from heaven to save everyone on
the internet
thank you for blessing us bless
i said bless hey i hate you hi hi hi hi
hi hi guys hi hi hi guys whenever you
feel lost i want you to know that you
need to have faith in me okay okay as
the internet angel i will always be by
your side
same i will always be by your side kfb
i will always
i will always be by your sidekick
i will always be by your side
just come on down to my channel and i'll
be waiting for you with a smile
okay
i skipped school so i didn't have any
friends only the people online cared
about what i had to say
i was bullied a lot at school for being
so cute and pretty too
jealousy is a disease that is true [\h__\h]
jealous people i also got made fun of
for being socially awkward and stupid
and messed up in the head
[Music]
she's doing real talk again guys
she's venting again
oh
poor you for you
so i know how it feels and now oh as
long as you have faith in me i will find
you within the darkness
thanks kangel
[Music]
next up one million let's go
remember you're never alone bless bless
bless bless
hallelujah
40 000. nice boost i can't promise to
save everyone because that would be a
lie but if just one person can be saved
by my presence then i would say it was
worth sending to the internet
and we got some fanart
kangel at starbucks let's go
cute
she's drinking uh
i think that's a chocolate mocha
frappuccino
if my smile can grant sells
sold salvation and i will keep smiling
for all the views on the other side of
the screen
she's motivated
okay i'm suddenly super anxious about my
future and can't sleep can you keep me
company until morning
always
i'm always here not that i think you
would yeah yeah don't worry about it
i'm only here for you angel
okay she's just chilling
it's time to uh sleep i guess
oh wait we can also
we can reduce the stress even more we
don't want to go there again we don't
gonna go where we were before again
shall we
do this
read the text oh can i do it now i can
do it now
[Music]
[Laughter]
but she wants my company
what if i close it and it says oh you
didn't keep me company
[Music]
their secret she won't let me okay maybe
she'll tell me her secret after
i'll show her some secrets
let's go
if i ever find my special you you're
saying you didn't find you special
someone yet what about me okay
i want you to go to the amusement park
with them we can scream together eat ice
cream together ride the ferris wheel
together and then we can hold hands and
start oh my god what if um a special
someone is one of you
made them with pizza and then things got
a bit wild with it
okay
anyway
it's been 20 days since we started doing
this whole thing it's had it's up and
downs but wow 10 more days until my one
month anniversary and we ain't stopping
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's go
she's motivated she's [\h__\h] motivated
let me read the secret text now let me
read it let me read it
again
you mean it she won't let me put hell
yeah [\h__\h] yes
piece of cake for me of course it is
i believe in you i believe in you what
no i'm not
not lying
[Music]
i'm not lying
okay i think i got out of it so it's
daytime we have a
decent amount of stress
what do you think we should do
yeah one month and we're still very far
away from one million i don't really
think it's a realistic goal
what happens if we don't reach 1 million
medicine
distress
should i
uh maybe not only that
but
we'll also get an idea again if i do
something like this stress goes down
[Music]
no idea
nah
amusement park
but it doesn't even give us an idea
[Music]
i think we will
um
we'll do a video streaming then it's
desk then we'll take the pills and then
we stream and see what happens i mean it
can't get much worse than just granite
[Music]
medicine gives an idea but is it a good
one
it feels like two time slots oh
that was like two turns oh okay i mean
you guys keep on saying i should do it i
don't know man
at least the stress goes down go big or
go home
no that's not usually
what you should what your motto should
be
but at least not in this case
all right
don't do this guys don't do this
don't take more oh [\h__\h]
don't don't this is a game okay this is
a [\h__\h] game
i can't see [\h__\h] i'm so tired i just
want to die but i can't
the picture is cute though
oh never mind
i'm in a really good mood today i don't
see no worries i'm going to stream
leaves for you guys i want to have a
chat with all of you anyone up for
spontaneous stream let's go they should
do gorilla
more than the sweet release of death i
crave the sweet sweet follower count
increase
but that's probably better than craving
for death but still mine's living so
hard feeling great oh
but that's a breakdown stream
i'm feeling sick right now like legit
[Music]
um okay
let make her feel loved
make her feel loved
i love you too
okay
wonderful
yeah yeah yeah i love you talk
just don't be a dumbass okay
oh man
huh some guy in america messaged me on
dinner are they actually going to fly to
japan if they do i think they deserve
you're telling me that you went though
what about me what about your love for
me you just told me you love me
no
[Music]
don't do that that's [\h__\h] dangerous
don't
she doesn't even answer
she doesn't even answer okay do whatever
the [\h__\h] you want
[\h__\h]
what do we stream about tonight oh
[Music]
no we should talk about cats i think
we should do a scene where we talk about
cats oh this one is also interesting
oh
rabbit hall
conspiracy
she wants those followers yo
i'm gonna gather those followers
at least this one is only 260 while this
one is for 62.
let's go deeper into the rabbit hole she
tells us some interesting stuff in these
conspiracy fairings
[Laughter]
tell me
a rabbit hole decrease wait the creases
what no it goes up up up up up up you
mean my my subscribers go up no
as technology improves my leaps and
bounds perhaps one day we will all be
microchipped yay
hey kangel hey cain's right there
listening they are listening totally
they're they are brainwashed look at
those brainwashed people
going into the deep end today hell yeah
imagine cities of people being
controlled by microchips embedded from
birth
i got one in my arm
i see you're so enlightened i've got a
microchip too
of course you do
the rolling class could manipulate our
brain waves as they like we'd all be
their puppets
okay
no way you mean i could be brainwashed
right now where's my tinfoil head good
question maybe just maybe we already
have those chips in our arms
what how did you find out about this
and the moment you act out of line some
big shot could hit your kill switch from
god knows where
oh you see
no
i'm not going to be able to sleep after
this me neighbor as if that technology
could exist relax people oh
she's
she's backpedaling again
okay thank god that was scary for now
anyway
we live in a dystopia
do we do we though
holy [\h__\h]
yummy hey kiana hi hi chad hi chad
hi chad
hi jen hi jim
[Music]
really you shouldn't tell anyone about
it otherwise you might be what how did
you find out when you asked i'm being
interrogated the government must have
sent you oh
it must be true
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] hell oh my god
help me the microchip and my heart is
controlling what they fall
[Music]
[Applause]
microchips are like whatever because
even without them you still can't prove
that we actually have free will oh she's
she's so deep in my into the microchip
and in the in the in the uh
rabbit hole
holy [\h__\h] wait what how many followers
did we get oh my god
how many did we just get
like 20 30k or what
30k 10k
11k
it felt like more
[Music]
huh
oh well we got a lot that's good
[Music]
rainbow
let's go rainbow
is she really doing it
tuning in tweets oh
what a cutie i need my nails aren't they
so pretty i love this color i'll be
uploading a makeup video sometime in the
future i don't think your followers will
care about that but sure i do think that
the reason i chose rainbow was because
i'm a good manager and i think this
image fits her the most you know with
the image she wants to portray
and i get that some of this country's
headed for future
just because
of me streaming
jk it's not even me that likes the color
is pizza
yeah well no i'm just i'm just trying to
get you somewhere
come on
uh now it's daytime we need to um
de-stress
um
how should we de-stress
50. everything is good
oh no no 100. oh [\h__\h] she won't like me
too much
dinda
i guess so
that lowered stress i think
perfection is a bit behind
okay
we're rocking this game guys we're
rocking it
ah
yes
instant yes let's go
treasure every moment yes inspiring
quote
do we get stressed okay okay minus 10
minutes okay
good good good good good but the mental
darkness is getting into a yeah by its
own i think we need the hospital kitchen
hasn't been giving me any attention
lately so i've been on dinner a lot had
a date with some old guy who was clearly
only on dinner for hookups but i managed
to get a good meal out of him before
ditching him
oh okay while we were dating a dog man
what the hell
what the hell having dogfish
they just be posting emo songs of the
breakup i'd probably be [\h__\h]
[Music]
she's having a
a little bit of a meltdown again
don't worry don't worry about it i still
love you even when you cheat on me
this
can i make fun of you now for using that
oh my god
i guess i can tell okay shut up now
in the nighttime i guess are we gonna
stream or should we take
the night off
we've been on a good streak i think we
should stream one more time and then
take the night off and on the next day
we'll go to the hospital and take the
night off
yeah this night we stream
um um
[Music]
but which one
74 42
80 62 oh that one would be good because
it also
um gets rid of the affection but stress
80 is going a bit too close again
and yeah and mental darkness too oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
maybe just a normal maybe we should just
play some games tonight
ah
stress is the game ender remember
breakdown oh uh okay
70 66
what 80 60
okay i'll go with the one that has the
least stress uh
thingy so i'll go with this one
angel explains we're doing we're gonna
do a podcast and then yeah tomorrow we
go to the hospital
this is a tactical game
very very tactical
[Music]
all right
let's talk about cats this is the cat's
one right on it
yes yes i bet i could guess what uh
fought every experiment
what i don't understand the sentence
i bet i could guess what thought
experiment every nerd out there would
like it's shredding your skin
it basically talks about how when a cat
is put in a box with some toxic gas
there's a 50-50 chance that it could be
either dead or alive before the box is
open
um
no
as long as it's unopened and the cat is
not observed it's in a state where it is
both alive and dead
are you crazy i thought you like cats
one act of observation can determine
reality that's how powerful seeing and
knowing is scary huh
the more you know if there's someone you
like or stand don't get too attached
what is you talking about
[Music]
oh
who knows what might happen if you
observe around some things i've just
been left up in here ignorance is
glistening all right i like it that's me
that's my superjet i sent her a red
super chat hope i'll get a kiss for that
okay let's have a look-see
poor kitty but it's fine it's just a
thought experiment not everyone i'm
poisoning cats and trapping them in
boxes this is bad uh-huh i love cats
anyone listening at all you get an f hey
why do i get an m
why
what the [\h__\h]
two thousand five hundred fourteen okay
whenever i become a top stream or stay
average is not um it's not certain it's
all up to the support you guys give me
so love me until you hide firsts
the fans who like piercing them and roll
candle would probably flip out if they
saw my private elmo ignorance truly is
bliss
so cute oh my god so cute though
she should stream like that once i love
get me to call me too
at least one person that gets me here
you love me and i love you ryan we
should totally make a couple's channel
just a bit of food yeah i don't think
that's a good idea
[Music]
okay though totally i'm totally in for
that what a great idea
yes
couple's channel could be so cute
okay do it coward
[Music]
that's all right
now get out of here
kfb
can only be
[Music]
you can only be kfb if you love cats
anyway oh no we wanted to go to the
hospital
let's go it's very important right now
although the affection oh man
we'll get it down we'll get it down to
55 24.
we have to
[Music]
and then not streaming for the maximum
effect are you good you're
you're good
go to night time
okay
bucket list have a girls night out at a
lava tail yes that sounds fun
but do you even have friends do you even
have any girlfriends
hmm
sleepy time
sleep
49 22. okay let's do it
oh you guys don't know
yeah that they are like um
[Music]
don't even make me explain it are you
sure you want to proceed you only saw
this doing yes
[Music]
okay
okay we're below 50 again
but affection is still
yeah
what
what's going on
i've been getting many new fans reviews
lately feel kind of down about it
i keep trying my hardest so please don't
leave me of course
[Music]
oh my god
i think they're trying to brainwash me
again
i care about you a billion times more
than any old nerd out there i don't care
how many of them are there are but i
only have one until that's the worst
part no not even death could tear us
apart i'm dead
i wish i wish death would tear us apart
wow
[Music]
forever and ever
and ever
oh my god
we're so loving dummy
[Music]
it's an endless loop
it never ends
help me
oh my god
yes
someone's stopping
[Music]
you know how like an anime off in the
mail i'm seeing a little pat a female
character's head you want to headpants
i guess i can give it to you
oh
but once it actually helps here every
time i see that i think no what if anime
nerds see that and think that's all it
takes to make a girl happy like we ain't
that easy y'all i say that
well i did tell you guys before that i
do not like headphones so
you're gonna need a cat back cause i do
i need a cat break too yeah holy [\h__\h] i
mean there's so many cats here though
anyway
just shut up girl we need a good
streaming idea let's play a game i guess
um
yeah whatever
whatever
how's it going
god why are these demon negotiations so
hard are they [\h__\h] high maybe we
should get no
no no
no we're not taking those pills anymore
whether we actually live in a simulation
or a game i think oh no she's going into
conspiracy theories again
i'd hate to live in a dating museum all
i've got going for me is my face no one
would play my room oh
i'm playing a route right now
shouldn't my gummy teensy reference
holy [\h__\h]
or i'd be an evil girl bus who gets
arrested for something or other that's
pretty cool in its own way though
everyone had these kinds of fantasies
before right maybe i could talk about it
on my in my next stream
angel explains rain the five minute
hypothesis
okay well at least it's not a conspiracy
theory
wow
impressive
as always shut up uh
go to desk
i forgot to pay the water bill so now we
have no running water
you [\h__\h] stupid
way we need water
why will i not get out of it you will
not get out of it go buy some water in
the convenience store
[\h__\h] die with no water
no well i'll try
anyway
uh streaming time no not yet
still have some time
we can do this for example
[Music]
or this
what should we do
then there
again but that would probably skip to
the next day now
[Music]
we need affection to go down a bit too
stress is okay right now actually
let's do vanity search then since we got
some time
we haven't done this in a while the only
thing that's keeping me going right now
clips of angel's stream is [\h__\h] watch
clips watch my full stream for [\h__\h]
sake like the people who are in my
stream right now
uh okay okay
fan since the beginning cool
yeah that is a good worry though when
when i vanity search i often see people
posting like i wish i could just quit my
job and watch angel's videos all day i
wish i could grant their wish for them i
want to become a giant monster and
destroy the city
okay
i don't know if you can't do that though
but i also want to like fight the other
bad monsters so people will think i'm
one of the good guys even though i just
flattened their health city that sounds
familiar
angel final wars nerf doctor
wow
she has some crazy ideas
i kind of want to like copy some of her
ideas
[Music]
well it's probably better that way
probably better that way
uh i think i messed up your mediflix
recommendations because i was using your
account to watch stuff i'm sorry oh
don't worry about it it's not like
you're ever gonna do anything good in my
life ever anyway
that's okay
do you even know what you're okaying at
yes
oh my god
an idiot
are we streaming tonight guys
hell yeah we are
um
stress 58 62 58
we should probably do a sexy stream
we can't afford it right now
and it will lower the affection too
we can afford it
let's do it
yeah
it can't be worse than the last one
oh yeah
[Music]
to the world of sexiness
hey kenji hi kendra hey kenjill hi
kangel hi kangel hi angel hey cuties
it's your favorite internet angel kanga
you're so cute
what should we talk about today
i'm listening
i know i've got a bit of trivia about
the corned beef but yes i think what the
[\h__\h] is corned beef i don't think i've
ever eaten it hello chad hello chad
hello chad hello chad
please talk about current beef every day
shut up you shut up can't stop crying
did you know that corned beef is shaped
so because of old why is your bull
ribbon moving
that's a cute bra oh no
[Laughter]
i didn't do it on purpose
you just made me smile for the first
time i'm like hell yeah i'm you're
welcome
you're [\h__\h] welcome i will never
forget this stream for as long as i live
well um it's not gonna be archived just
so you know
it's time to read some comments oh she
looks so embarrassed no one stop stop
giving me money for something so small
thanks i'm crying right now oh she's
happy crying bless
wow these people really got blessed 75
oh no
that was indeed worth but we're over
200k now
that's it
that's that's how it how it's supposed
to be hell yeah
uh did i accidentally go a little
overboard it wasn't you you didn't do it
on purpose right it just kind of
happened the ribbon i don't know it had
it was living its own life i don't know
better delete my archive just in case i
don't get banned yep yeah probably a
good idea
i got way better numbers showing a bit
of skin rather than blowing a kiss i
guess i have to be more active rather
than passive but i feel like that's not
quite an either i think but that's as
far as we go with the sexy strings
because i don't even wanna know how much
worse it gets from here
i don't really wanna know
uh what is it
wait what
every time i have to talk to nerds i
take psychic damage i don't have the
energy to do anything today that's okay
we don't have to stream you got just so
many streamers yesterday
i just wanted to go on a date with you
and have some fun
oh thank you elias
and forget all about the idiots on the
internet yeah
[\h__\h] yeah
uh
yeah
i'm in
i'm so in hospital date now
i love you too yeah yeah okay um
[Music]
no no no
hospital date we kind of need it at this
point though
does she consider that a date
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait what read the description
[Laughter]
uh
hospital if they are so romantic i mean
this is gonna get the affection up to 74
while the other staff would also get it
up to 74. but this is more effective as
in uh it lowers the mental darkness as
well which we need right now okay
hospital dead let's go
maybe it's a really nice hospital
[Music]
yay so romantic
bliss
minus ten plus six minus ten alrighty
you're doing fine
man this is really going on for a while
huh but we're close to the end of the
month is that when the game ends i
suppose
maybe i should get into a little voice
acting to make my streams more
interesting but i'm already spreading my
brain cells fitting for love and work so
busy
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay oh my god
oh my god indeed
good okay we're done here um oh it's
nighttime
ah
i think we should
sleep do we do we need to stream
[Music]
new diary file
what
what oh what
it's been a couple of weeks since i
moved in with peach and i'm getting
better at streaming and i'm having lots
of fun every day i've learned a lot
since i've started is this what they
call character development i've been
working my ass off to get to this point
but i wouldn't be here without petran's
help i'm seriously so grateful that
someone on this great great green earth
is willing to stick with a useless idiot
like me i think we should both get
you should buy yes you should buy my
favorite dessert with my credit card i
don't have a credit card so go ahead i
guess
okay no i was not reading your diary but
you didn't see that right you didn't see
it
i think
sleeping is probably for the best
yeah we're fine we're fine we're fine
we're fine no i'm not streaming nah
streaming today
go to tomorrow
what the [\h__\h]
sorry i didn't mean to call you oh
oh
i don't mind you calling me
you should call me
she's such an annoying [\h__\h] i can't
take this anymore i hope this game ends
soon
ah
shut up
shut up already
sorry my my real thoughts came out there
photo
i was a bit too honest there for a
moment it's like my my ama account
tweeted for a little bit
oopsie i didn't mean it
didn't mean i forgot i was on my main
account
anyway hmm
[Music]
what
actually she watched the action movie
hero what actually hear a movie
i've been listening to a lot of drama
tracks and stuff online for research
uh-huh with drama tracks and stuff
you're always on the receiving end yeah
because it's not like you can talk back
to the speaker
what does that mean drama track that's
why i have to make sure i go as hard as
i can when i do ass and learns
no
oh no
don't bless them they've already been
blessed enough
seven minutes in heaven with angel
seven minutes is that all it takes huh
is that all it is oh my god
lord save us from this chick
i'm starting to hate her and despise her
what
maybe we should start panning to that
delinquent demographic or something
instead of the gamer nerds what do you
mean delinquent demographics
okay
[Music]
what
what is it why is it did we skip a day
i'm confused i lost track of time in
days
oh
did this skip a day by accident oopsie
doors
maybe i did
it's dusk
oh
was it day before that
we still have some time until streaming
stress is 50 affection 75 for mental
darkness 19 okay
what do you think we should do
yeah the music the soundtrack is amazing
i especially like the opening song in
the beginning
video vanity
72-20
i will go for
one more video let's watch more movies
binge watching let's go
and by the way i'm i'm almost done with
seinfeld i've been trying to watch other
things on the side so i don't
finish it too quickly but i'm on the
ninth season
i don't know what to do with live after
that like what am i supposed to watch
afterwards i've seen everything that
there needs to be seen i need to repeat
something again
but yeah binge watching
is gonna be
uh commenced soon i was watching this
idol video and they were all eating
popsicles for some reason why do these
nerds like seeing young women licking
popsicles so much i could never see
eyes to isolate them huh
sexy stream free me eating ice cream
um
let me think about that a little bit
let me um let me think about that
no you're kind of
going
the wrong route i i don't know if i can
support you anymore girl
see me producers and editors are really
on another level i guess that's why
they're paid to do tv and not me
oh i'll keep doing my best though very
good inspiration
oh my god during lunch in school i
played one of your videos and everyone
in my class was like hey cuties as well
you can look at them no i actually
wasn't looking at the replies
you didn't really reply to the fans once
in a while you know
see there's someone called takanasi
kiwawa who is on twitter 24 hours a day
and always answers her fans like not
always but i like i like like like so
many comments and i i i even go on
everybody's accounts and and i check out
what you guys do on your private time is
that would you prefer that you stupid
egg huh would you prefer it that way huh
we'll see about that
i'm trying to perfect making that shoop
sound sweeter makes when you refresh it
okay
that's kind of cute
[Music]
it's really difficult to balance like
everything like don't make her love you
too much
don't stress her out too much don't piss
her off too much
it's really difficult
it's quite a challenge it's night time
so we stream
we have stress down by a lot uh
we are going to
oh
70 66 oh affection goes down though
ah archangel final words stressed to 60
64 16 749
oh dear
break down stream
even angels go for it no no no we don't
want that no that's just really bad uh
by the way what is this category
apparently there's like one category
that we haven't figured out yet i wonder
where that comes from
ah probably from
i know we're nowhere
near
well we'll keep it that way
we'll keep it ally i don't know what to
stream
but we're getting very close to the end
of the game
we should get her some more followers
what's the uh
let's
why are they also young
is it only that you buy streams that get
me followers
this one is okay though
five arrows six arrows six arrows
68 70 74.
gee i guess i wonder why
impact what does it mean impact
16. ah
i'll go with this one for now
gotta break down the sounds here bye
what if the world were created only a
mere five minutes ago
that's impossible kangel quest democracy
mug
the past would be entirely thinking what
the [\h__\h] are you talking about
there's not so much from a tiny brain
same can you explain it like i'm five no
one can prove that it's not true
sometimes i think that the whole world
could be just one big game
um take the spaces well it's entirely
possible whatever out there only loads
when you step outside
uh okay she has a point
i guess it's pretty cool
no no no think about that sometimes
[Music]
okay you need to stop thinking
you were right i want a game where
instead of conquering a city or
something we get to conquer
oh you funny
you're so funny
something
hey hey stop to me subscribe
running every second what does that mean
it was about five minutes ago that's
right congratulations it's a dog eat dog
little living hell so let's do our best
if you if life were a game then all your
nerds must be playing on hard mode bless
bless blasphemes once bless her
eye drums yes
oh three thousand five hundred that's
like nothing [\h__\h]
again it was today's stream a little
unsadly don't worry because you live in
the real world that's existed for
millions of millions of years you know
one thing that my fans can't tell me is
that kangel isn't giving them enough
variety we're giving them so many
different streams man we give them
presentations
asmr
oopsie boopsies
the game streams anything
i mean
what an entertaining channel
we're literally watching like a train
wreck becoming a train wreck though
what kind
of me do you like
this is another important question
[Music]
um
genius i would say she's a genius
probably
what do you say
bratty house pink what does that mean
brett really
does she like that
ew you're an adult and you like ugly
young girls
chad excuse me
is that it you like little girl
oh
my
god
shut up
i'm sorry
i'm sorry i don't know what the [\h__\h]
happened
[Music]
okay let's make the best out of this day
shall we
i feel like going to the hospital ah
yeah
yeah i'm going to the hospital [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h]
this [\h__\h]
[Music]
huh
wait wait
okay night time streaming dance during
time at least we gotta keep up the
streaming you know every day streaming
until until we get to one million we
have to be successful fema the parts of
my room that don't show up on camera are
getting so messy
like that is relatable but making
everyone think you have need room is an
art in and of itself yes only keep the
part clean that shows up on camera
just as she's probably wearing pajama
pants underneath that part of the screen
but that's okay
[Music]
inspiring [\h__\h] once again sometimes you
are a genius
only sometimes
most of the time you're a [\h__\h] idiot
um okay
maybe something that lowers reflection
yeah yeah this one could be good because
i feel like as long as we don't get to
like 80
80 stress i feel like we can still kind
of like
save ourselves you know what i mean
um
this one or the for the asmr 7272
perfection ah okay
and darkness um
and the streak bonus
asmr asmr is probably
ah
[Music]
yeah okay
okay
when we are in a semi streamer now
we have to commit
once we get into it we have to commit to
it
get ready to get your eardrums tickled
with today's asmr
thank you they're already saying thank
you it's a bit too fast don't you think
so
what do you want me to do today
i'll rub my shoulder
that's okay
yeah i want a massage too
46 000 people watching by the way want
me to wrap your shoulders must be hard
sitting on your butt all day huh huh
yeah
tell him tell him tell him kangel
bay stains out
oil wow yeah oil massage
oh my god
i'm not i'm not gonna look
you guys can read what they're saying
oh
it's gonna
i don't like where this is going
[Music]
feeling vulnerable right
shut up all of you
[Music]
this is
shut up shut up everyone
shut up
oh my god
ah
[Applause]
thanks for coming to today's chat and
chill i usually don't have anyone to
talk to so i'm really really really
happy that all of you were able to join
me
oh sure patreon hasn't really been
paying attention [\h__\h] you you suck i
just wanna i wanna just want this to be
over now
[\h__\h] i'm getting something subscribers
yes yeah no you have more than that
she's like delayed she's like uh
slowpoke she's [\h__\h] slowpoke
girl look at your subs
but that means we get this we maybe get
a um celebration stream
yay
[Music]
really is that what the topic has to be
about
[Music]
do we really have to talk about that
at least her stress and
and all that won't uh be increased
she's yeah she's vulnerable um
okay maybe she'll you know it will be
the topic but maybe she'll send the
right message
[Music]
at least i crossed 250 yeah we actually
we're almost at 350k
celebrate that girl celebrate it
what if i touch here i can't okay only
touching here only here touching i don't
know in other games you can do that i
don't know
okay uh daytime okay okay what can we do
what what should we do
what should we do
maybe get the stress down stress stress
we need to get stressed out maybe
hospital until the evening time
right
i think we should go to the hospital
yeah
oh no no no no
wait so my brain is like so melted
[Music]
yes
and then we can still stream in the
evening the good thing is right now we
don't need ideas we have a new stream
idea which is the
celebration stream
okay
i want to do what i love most for the
rest of my life lying around and doing
nothing and sleeping
i love that too
yes
with my cat still with my cats
okay we're gonna celebrate i guess
but guys whatever she says in this
stream i do not endorse it or
i don't know is that the right word i do
not support
what she says
probably
depends depends what she says
condone i do not condone it
okay
it could
celebrate
[Applause]
[Music]
how amazing i'm standing super cute time
to party
yeah
thank angelo archangel and angel
archangel archangel archangel archangel
archangel archangel oh my god it's so
many colors
anyway uh-huh what
chat
i'm i'm inside of the chat right now
wait wait no not really no not really
oh my god oh my god
i'm not even gonna show that on my
stream
huh
real happiness comes from the real
hormones in your brains real light races
after you work and accomplish something
real oh
she's getting there she's getting there
and now that i'm celebrating something
that i've earned for myself
more than i've ever felt hell [\h__\h]
yeah girl finally you understand
and say that i feel happy yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
i sent your super chat once i get my
paycheck you you sent it a bit too early
[Music]
okay
i just want the best for you
we all just want the mess for you i'm
sure you all have what it takes to find
your happiness so go and live a happy
life promise me
yes
girls what what do we call that is a
straight edge
you guys taught me that straight edge
live let's go 20 22 only 22 000 really
for real i need more
[Music]
still doing a lot of learning about
myself so i might act up here and there
but i think i'll be okay as long as i
remember the happiness that i felt today
no matter how rough the road gets
i won't give up on my dream of reaching
1 million
art cute thank you thank you
i got so many super chats i'm just gonna
use a little bit of it on myself that's
okay
you can
go to a spa or something we can go
shopping tonight and buy whatever we
like and be happy together
that's okay
it's okay to spend time on yourself
bless it
where's music again
no one online gives a [\h__\h] about me why
is he like this
your stress and your mental darkness
aren't that bad
i don't want to blame someone else for
my problems but i trusted you you know
did you really have my best interests at
heart
why
why are you doubting me
i feel like i don't even know you
anymore it only takes an instant for
someone love someone's love and dreams
to be shattered apparently i don't know
what the [\h__\h] happened
[Music]
i'm sorry
sorry for making you say sorry
um
she'll get over it
[Music]
now she won't
gotta tell her i love her
yeah okay
[Music]
this is hell this is what hell is like
huh i would have never known otherwise
because i go to heaven but this is this
is hell
[Music]
okay
okay okay we have an understanding
and this [\h__\h] we're so close to the end
guys i want a game win again you're
gonna not gonna say anything about
this number yo
yo girl we worked so hard for what
we're playing games oh oh she's forcing
me to play games
man i've been driving for hours but i
still can't beat this boss battle maybe
i should get peach on the ground levels
for me lol please don't be mad if you
don't oh my god oh my god she's wasting
time
some [\h__\h] my streamer just dm me asking
if i would go to a concert with him if
he gives me a million yen i might
consider
no
what about me
wow life is [\h__\h] horrible
officer we gotta dead
we're breaking up we're breaking up girl
i'm so dumb of you
[\h__\h] done with her
[Laughter]
this girl is this what manhattan is like
is this what dealing with a manhattan is
like
[Music]
[Applause]
like they drag you
into it they drag you into it oh my god
oh
i've been trying
i've been trying to help her i just want
her to be happy and [\h__\h] those numbers
man
i've been trying to keep your stress
down i don't want you to do those weird
[\h__\h] streams
we should do this
um
we should tweet we haven't gotten an
idea from wait we can get an idea from
dinner
um
our affection is a bit dangerous there
check diary is there a new one no still
the old one
seven eight
three four 54.
[Music]
check the secret again just in case okay
i can't
[Laughter]
[Music]
where would i get a good idea
it's probably better this is better this
is better
i tried holding her before she comes up
again
oh man
you can say whatever you want but you
can't stop me i'm doing this because i
like it not because i want male
attention oh
really can these
maleoids keep their mouths shut jesus
christ they're all so stupid
oh my god if you only get positive
comments that means you're only midterm
at best because you haven't blown up
enough to reach the haters oh
basically the more haters you have the
more fans you have oh
so when you see hate just keep coming
and remember to keep an open mind
okay
[\h__\h] that those arrogant [\h__\h] need
to get their heads out of their asses
and get lost
[Music]
[\h__\h] maybe i should fight my haters
that would be so crazy wouldn't it lol
psych
he's gonna do a rat stream
wow
okay thank god she doesn't answer me
thank god you're genius
are you streaming i'll be streaming guys
58 78 okay picking a fight with my
haters
got it
oh there we go
stress 76
[Music]
we're so close to the end
how about 86.
you know what you know what you know
what how about we could also
take tonight off but four times bonus
four times bonus
oh ah
a28
can we still stream on the on the
thirteenth day
uh i can't think of any ideas or future
i want you to oh maybe you think of a
good idea now
think think think i may think
think
your ideas are [\h__\h]
you can't stream on the third enough it
ends
ah
i need the numbers
but
we if we get to 86 stress i feel like
she's gonna have a [\h__\h] mental
breakdown again last time it was about
around the same around the same stress
level
[Music]
ah
true somebody said that like as long as
i don't do it more than like three times
oh
i need the numbers i don't know it's
okay
and i keep saying
six arrows up times four
bonus
pretty good it's pretty good
won't reach one million how the [\h__\h] do
you reach one million and not kill her
while doing it
is that even possible
go for broke what does that mean
[Music]
what
there is no way to reach 1 million yeah
true so maybe we should stay lower
wait maybe we should just stay happy
with some lower numbers
we can also try this one
stress 80 squares 86
mental darkness 12.
that one also goes to 12.
this one doesn't do anything with the
affection well this one does this is
good for us probably
ah
go for the numbers numbers numbers
numbers
playing the game
has a good ending is there even a good
ending
[Music]
okay you guys just want to see her eat
ice cream
[Laughter]
be honest you just want to see her eat
ice cream
[Laughter]
i mean ice cream is pretty nice i had
hog and dots yesterday
i had dulce de leche so i think it's a
brazilian thing at least at least i
first heard about it when i was in
leche ice brazil from haagen-dazs it's
so good it's really good
dolce dorito or something like that
it's mexican oh sorry about that when i
was in brazil everyone told me to try
dolce de leche
i guess it's just like maybe a general
thing
very very yummy very very young
okay [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it i don't
care it's a game it's a game nothing's
real
it's just the game
it's just
ice cream your screen give me that give
it an ice cream
okay
hey kangel hey angel hi can't you heck
me eating ice cream simple title um
everyone wants to see that obviously hey
kids i bought some ice cream today
you're such a [\h__\h] idiot
i love ice cream too you know
oh
she's not gonna read anything now you
can enjoy this i will not look
super chat okay
what
[Music]
um
are we done
wonderful
[Laughter]
shut up
do it come on
i can skip it
skip that [\h__\h] i don't want to say it
anymore
ice cream is the best for human days
like today let me know if you guys want
to see more food reviews that that was a
food review just like the uh natto
coca-cola stream exactly that's the same
category anyway i'll see you all
tomorrow plus maybe she should try natto
ice cream
that would be a good idea
oh wow
half a million subs
[Applause]
angel got nothing on me though
i have over a million kangel
what you gonna do what you gonna do
kangel
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] 86 is yeah but the music is so
happy because we're getting out of it
we're getting out of this situation
because she got 500k and that is being
prioritized [\h__\h] yes
but
[Music]
if we do the celebration stream now
now that i'm so famous i don't think i
could ever stop like thousands of people
found over me every day i don't have it
in me to just go back to an ordinary
life people from all over the world have
their eyes on me like that makes me
happy but it's also kind of terrifying
the higher you climb the harder you fall
and the bigger your fan base grows the
more haters and unhinged fans you get
[Music]
don't worry eventually you'll get sick
of it and then you're gonna
be happy about
leaving probably
but even so i can't quit whether i lose
or gain followers or whether the the
masses
praise or criticize me it's all free
stimulation and my brain loves that [\h__\h]
really mentally ill behavior to be
honest that's why i started reading a
bunch i picked up a few books
are they picture books
uh
what
by someone with the same name as me
and they were really good their
collection of pokemon is it what you
wrote
that reminds me
i never tell you the story behind my
name did it
you see yeah i say my name is amen oh
and i usually just make the excuse that
it's because ami means candy it also
means rain
i'm so sweet but actually that's not
what it actually is i'm a little
embarrassed by it but oh
yes yes yes
i mean you guys know because i probably
told you guys before but i'm his name
amelia watson's name
hey yeah aside from candy almond can
also mean rain oh yeah she's gonna be
like yeah yeah i knew she was going
there because like oh my god i'm so emo
cause rain yeah
making it rain
[Music]
wow
[\h__\h] knew it
you are
so gloomy
you're so gloomy she doesn't answer me
anymore she doesn't need me anymore what
wait we can still get her stretched down
we go to the hospital now and then
stream the
uh
the the final 500k stream
tonight
i think that would be perfect that would
be perfect that would be perfect that
would be perfect 76 is a decent and 69
affection
that's decent that's decent that's
decent
okay
[Music]
although yeah the celebration stream
won't give us as good numbers as the
breakdown but
we want to try we want to try to end it
on a decent good note the breakdown
stream will just stress her out more and
more and more
what i need 80 plus affection for good
endings
what's better than that what really [\h__\h]
what is it bad really so a couple going
to the fair if you had the clinic the
other day but what i know is that there
are no good endings in this game so [\h__\h]
it
oh oh was it was it us
oh my god it was us
keep the price coming
yes yes just before before i'll never
see you again just know that i'm so
proud of you girl we're gonna get to
600k before the end of this one month
i'm so proud of you
yes
i will um
i will remember you um this was a very
memorable
stream i guess
okay
500 [\h__\h] k we have a stream wait no
it's six arrows
and stream streak bonus well let's
[\h__\h] go
oh
[Music]
lot sure has happened huh congrats oh my
god it's a quick every time i see my
numbers go up whenever you guys send me
nice comments i feel such a rush just
have all the praise going on thank you
[Music]
even though for every joy i've
experienced there's also been something
equally painful all her talks are like
so surreal man
and even though i've considered quitting
many times i just can't leave the
internet
i just get so anxious if i can't stay
connected with people all over the world
it's how i cope
same
is this a
graduation announcement stream what
what cyberspace what was that about
i think i may already be broken
what
ah this place makes her happier and okay
but there's something beautiful and
being broken i can mend back stronger i
can transform myself
so yeah
don't worry guys no matter how messed up
i get i promise i'll always be here
angel yo too strong we're already
connected for our computers our phones
our streams
and as long as you promise all the love
to me
i will be right here with you
so please love you forever you love me
you really really love me with your
whole entire heart promise promise me
can't be
promise me
i love you forever right only me only me
right
only me no one else
right i'm looking at you
bless bless
what's up and in german we sell [\h__\h]
readers in 35 oh well okay we got over
600 that's amazing
we're so close to one million for all
you loving me and they'll turn into the
greatest streamer anyone has ever seen
you will love kangel you will love angel
you will love angel you love
[Music]
all right let's see what happens it's
the final day
it's been a month i think i'll keep
being a streamer oh
she's motivated no matter what happens
we'll be fine if we stick together okay
sounds like a good ending
okay
she decent kill me no
peter look that new agency that has tons
of famous me tube assigned with them
just send an offer to kangel of course
they would because she's already a top
streamer
[Music]
they even said that i could go with
is this the same ending that reina got i
only saw like a snippet but
is this also what she got
well that's okay you know what i'm so
happy i'll be rid of you
they said that only people signed with
them can live there to prevent travel so
only i can live there thank god
i think you'll be fine in someone else's
hands you're too obsessive over me
anyway
i think this is the best ending
really sorry pizza but i want to pursue
my dreams
our feelings are still the same even if
we're apart right will you support me
sure even if what you say is a lie
i think i'm i'm better off without you
and you're better off without me
and you seem really motivated
i think you can do well
if you if you're in good hands so i hope
that agency treats you well but if there
are a lot of other people there a lot of
other youtubers
then they're probably there for a reason
unless they got signed into a contract
where there were some small letters that
said that they would never be able to
leave ever again and they didn't read
those small letters because they didn't
see them and they got tricked into it
and got bamboozled well then you [\h__\h]
i hope you read the small letters angel
read the small letters do it
i love you
me too nothing can stand between a love
i know that's a lie
but that's okay
that's okay angel that's
[Music]
i archangel believe i lucked out on
getting such a famous streamer for a
boyfriend
i'm so glad i signed onto a big company
he's a streamer just like me and unlike
my previous partner so we can really
relate to each other's problems and he's
also super good at helping me with my
streams we're gonna do a collab soon we
will never guess that we're actually
dating lol so sorry for being in the
perfect relationship feels good to see
my boyfriend's dumb [\h__\h] fans emptying
their wants for him like thanks for
helping me pay for my gifts i love you
so much i'm going to stay at his tonight
as well so i'm expecting lots of love i
want to be with him forever if he
becomes even more famous i'll marry him
my boyfriend is acting kind of strange
he doesn't really call me anymore and
when i do manage to get him on the phone
he always says that he's busy and when i
finally got to see him for the first
time in ages he just left me to his bed
and fell asleep after like three minutes
of the weakest action i've ever seen is
he just using me there's rumors of him
being madly in love with some other girl
streamer and i thought it was [\h__\h]
but what do i do pizza would never do
this to me pizza only had eyes for me
and yet i went
really [\h__\h] things up
i'm never going to forgive that bastard
he said he would love kangel and kangel
only and now he tossed me aside for some
other girl after all i've done for him
men aren't [\h__\h] i feel so disgusted i
just want to curl up and die now you
know what i should just kill him i want
to kill him where did i go wrong oh my
[\h__\h] god take me back to when things
are so good please
huh
oh man they're [\h__\h] disgusting
they should all be taken out back and
shut not believe this i don't believe
this
i'm going to make this world a better
place where all women can live in peace
do we really have to sacrifice love in
the name of fame
[Music]
okay
game over
you're the yellow overload
thank you for dozing press anywhere to
proceed
are you see other endings
wow
have you seen other endings
was that a good ending no i mean
maybe one of the better ones
oh this is fat ah is that your buy fan
art in there
so cute i think i've seen this one
before
that is so gorgeous can i i'm gonna make
it bigger
are we getting the music again the
awesome music or is this a different one
internet yeah
i think here it comes probably
well
um
this was a
interesting game
[Laughter]
yeah i escaped here hallelujah
[\h__\h] yeah
yeah
happy ending
um
[Music]
huh
well
i mean
obviously everything is exaggerated but
there were some things that were hashtag
relatable oh my god
um
you know um
it was uh very interesting
cool
what of all the games i've ever played
this was certainly what
one of them one of the interesting ones
it was a ride yeah
it was quite a ride um
but you know
it's uh it's cool that games like this
also exists it's very different from
other games
i will recommend this game to
one of my friends i think she'll enjoy
it
[Laughter]
[Music]
what
did i do okay did i i don't know uh if
you guys think you can get her to 1
million please try
uh
make her succeed
and then tell me what the [\h__\h] it took
to get her to 1 million i want to know
i want to know what is the right way to
play this game
it's arguably better than me really
maybe it's them
maybe it's the you know the uh what
what's uh into intuition
that i have is that the right word i'm
not sure
more sexy streams sexy and asmr is
apparently the way to go
yeah a lady's touch exactly
and she gave up streaming halfway in in
your in your playful
what
you're a bad manager bad bad manager
get really high
stream streak early and use the
celebration stream days to lower stress
ah but maintain the streak then do a b
stream or two
yeah yeah yeah that sounds like
sounds like a good strategy it makes
sense yeah
in the beginning while the stress is not
so high just yet um
and then go to the hospital on days
where you can do a celebration
ah
smart mind smart smart smart
yeah well you know guys um i i had some
i had some issues
reacting to certain topics in the game
because i have
some
strong opinions about certain things um
so i hope that was not too awkward but
um
i just wanna
i guess make sure again to say um guys
don't do anything stupid that was
pictured in the game
and take care of yourself
take care of your body and your mental
health
if you feel like you need to you can
also like just like angel go to a
hospital if you need to
just
um be careful and
prioritize yourself [\h__\h] the numbers
because i think one thing that
one thing
uh for all the people out there who also
want to be famous because who doesn't
dream about being famous
once you get those numbers i've said it
before but just like i think angel
experienced it it gets addicting and you
want more and more and more and there's
never enough you get addicting addicted
to that attention and to the numbers and
it's never gonna be enough it's never
gonna be [\h__\h] enough so
remember that no matter what if you
reach if you reach 100k then it might be
amazing at first but immediately you
want more and if you reach one one
million at the point of when you were
100k
that you you think like oh one million
that's what i want to reach because
that's gonna be enough but then you
reach one million it's never enough
i think that's like generally
i mean i'm fine by the way i don't
i haven't i haven't really bothered much
with um
that kind of stuff thankfully i've i've
managed to
get out of that endless endless endless
circle of wanting more and more and more
to be honest i'm actually proud of
myself
um but i've had the same problem of
course for a while too i think everyone
who starts
um
doing something like this
gets sucked into this endless hole
of greed of [\h__\h] greed
it's really difficult to get out of it
but it's understandable i i i think like
that was also something i could relate
to
um
for kangel
i can
understand her feelings in
some ways in other ways i cannot
because she's crazy [\h__\h] insane
yeah
but looking back on how [\h__\h] once before
hog life
i am just uh
very thankful for where i am now i sound
like angel like right now it's not like
i'm doing one of my celebration streams
my emotional talks
don't become angel become as angel
become aschangel
i sound like her i should probably quit
now
[Laughter]
celebration time on
angel
kmt
bless oh thank you bless you too and
bless you and bless you i'll bless you
and bless you and bless you and bless
you
people have told me before that my chemo
no pose looks like a jesus pose i should
be telling you i should be saying bless
you in my kimono pose
all right uh tomorrow is my day off um
i don't think i'll be reading super
chats now because it's past midnight um
um
yeah i'll see you guys on wednesday
i'm not sure what we're streaming on
wednesday i forgot
i think we're drawing i think we're
finishing the piece of art that i
started the other day
because you guys have been asking for it
so we'll have a cozy cozy stream there
and in the ice stream and i'll tell you
what i've been up to on pokemon i'm so
sorry guys i've actually i have to admit
i've been
i think i'm a little bit addicted um
i've been really hooked i'm not
continuing the main story but um i got
another badge i've done a [\h__\h] ton of
side quests
a [\h__\h] ton of quests a [\h__\h] ton of uh
monster pokemonster hunting
um i i involved my evilly uh you i will
show you some screenshots of what i've
been doing um on on wednesday
[Music]
it's actually been a lot of fun yeah
that's why i stayed up so long
[Laughter]
but that's a good thing i've been
enjoying it way more than i thought i
would but
i think this is how i'll continue like
i'll do main story on the stream and
then
the side story stuff the cyclists i'll
be doing
uh on the side yeah
it's wednesday and art stream it is
but i still
want to tell you how i've been doing in
pokemon
congress i'm getting a gear girl
i don't know how to sing it
thank you it's currently in my team
actually i've been using it actually um
nice catch in the sky it took me quite a
lot
you might have seen by
the amount of balls in the first
screenshot compared to the second
screenshot but that's not even all i
even had to
reload my
save file because i ran out of balls two
times
took me a long time
but then i saw that sana
also did one of those
uh miracle
uh
catches she caught she found
target kiss right
in a place that she shouldn't really be
able to access
probably usually but she got it i want
to get it too yo that's so cool
but that's why you should look up in the
sky a bit more often while playing
pokemon legends because you know
there could be something in the sky
that you can uh
catch yeah
it doesn't listen to her oh really i'm
sure she can get up to that level soon
enough to have it listen to her
all right then um
thank you for the
fun weird [\h__\h] stream today
thank you
uh
[Music]
that was something um i would sleep over
it and tomorrow i think i'll be like yo
that was a dream right that that didn't
happen right
think i think today was a favorite dream
i might have a fever i think i'm gonna
go lay down now i need to slip off my
fever this you guys might have a fever
too
maybe we all have a [\h__\h] fever
good night everybody have a nice evening
and in german we say
alf
petersen bless bless bless you bless you
bless you gesundheit why are you i
didn't sneeze why are you saying bless
who sneezed
what the [\h__\h] was that game
what the [\h__\h] was that
game
my brain
is melted
ice cream in my brain
jelly in my brain
[Music]
oh my god
genma genma wrote to me
bliss but like around the beginning of
the stream
[Music]
i think she already knew
where this game was going
she's been brainwashed too
[Music]
you