[Music]
what else is
NS my
Tail so Yeah I would like to say thank
you guys for joining and uh we're still
kind of in the beginning so First thing
first please group with your team
[Applause]
[Music]
[Clap  hands]
once Za Hello and
[Applause]
Za ye
pleas
for back twice
[Music]
i i you guys are ready
yeah are you guys ready Are you guys
posi
[Music]
you do is what is your team name What is
your
[Music]
team next te de te
l
Ma good for
the GR May
r
r better
than do
now Where's your
partner i
to i TR to cont
[Music]
Okay gu late now
Hello let's go oh wait no no Just go
around
he I'm  going to what materials we can
use
for a while
Um as you guys can see that uh today is
the day of H ID Um
but we are still waiting for like one person
left But There will
be R already start for the introduction
for each member
so  actually pretty
nervous but let
Justin
requ  you during Simon can you please
speak
slowly i can do
that back and forth
left okay jump jump
Okay thank
you Thank
you next
is
[Music]
next haiikokai
yeah okay
happy
[Music]
evening
Indonesia
sa Indonesia
[Music  ]
[Music]
Can you introduce your
team you
guys wow
team that our team name should be team
not H JP
s j okay
okay Inside bracket not and then Ho JP
okay okay
okay the not  is really
important part of our team i see
Yes Yeah I hope you enjoy today and Um
There will be a Treasure Hunt game So
your teamwork will be uh tested
yeah teamwk don't your
[Music]
[Applause]
team teeh gambat  t So I guess
[Music]
what Co cobboy left Hello Kobo Hello Kobo
Hello kobo kobo have you eaten Have you
eaten yet Kobo eat first
Kobo have eaten I've eaten this
and Jeta gave me herbs too ah that's great
cool, cool, cool, cool,
cheer up, cheer up, cheer up, yeah, that's
true, if there's something that
might be troublesome because you have to
carry it yourself, ma'am, for
a while, cheer up,
ma'am, we're like Kobo, don't you
know if you like eating,
this is an introduction to all
yaungali
OK
[Music]
Mina atttion please
ATT
OK, the committee is all three, oh oh, all
three,
three, all three,
okay, Guys E,
because maybe we're one less but that's
okay  first, we will
first e game will be Treasure hunts they
There will be around 10 spots of
Treasure it can be in a chest it can be
in a shelker it can be in a dropble it
can be in Anywhere Um So
your mission is to  find it every
chest has around three
emeralds you can use for the Ma later
is hint around the area that you can
[Music]
check OK so before we start Let's
sleep first again
Is there enough BS I don't know Survival
for the is it
enough everyone  It's okay i i can
Oh than
you thank you
[Music]
the time the time for hunting The
Treasure will
be 10 minutes after 10 minutes We gather
here again we will we will ask you to
gather Here by
chat wait where is The
Treasure
around on the  first floor it's on the
very first floor with the many grass
[Musik]
we don't break anything right we don't
Break The Stones don't
need my RPG sens are
tingling Where the treas
are is everybody ready
ready everyone I'm  going to  count the
timer So Are you guys
ready
Okay everyone stand
by yes okay I'm going to it
in we need to Two and then we find go
Find your Treasure
[Music]
I
can't
[Music]
it can be up here too
k k
k
k  are we allow to destroy anything
yeah yeah you guys allow to droy anything
Don't
Wor come here here this What is
this get it get it get it I got it I got
it
got Oh yeah the
most content
we need to find
need now they  came over
here don't
know why should  I help
you understand I don't know I don't know
but what's what's with the
buttons doesn't do anything What's with
the
buttons i see it do I have to dig do I
have to dig if
you Fine never never mind That's just
me  find it Where is it Muna did they
find it and and I don't have to look
here anymore I don't know you have to
[Applause]
every what
what Maybe you can go to another place
if you feel like they've already searched  it
I  know No they would have reacted they
would have reacted if they found it I
have no idea I'm looking here for like
five minutes now and I have you already
checked the book
Yeah it says like Among Flowers BRI
great chest Hi from side
so maybe  they did find it I don't know
among the
Flowers I'm trying I'm also trying try
hard I'm going
toers wait this one
Can we destroy the
bo oh
oh is this one gone
yet in the first with to open  it you
need in
where is he or is there anyone  destroyed it by
accident
ouch
oh Li
Naon Li did someone destroy the flowers or not
[Music]
I don't know what it was I destroyed the flowers I didn't
know Oh
the number
whose l m hat was inside
coy wasn't behind there, her brother b was
destroyed by Bu coy Anjir what's wrong Eh
you got it  Where are the flowers?
[Music]
here and then you just leave like that
[Laughs]
Yes ara
descendu sor Soror don't steal it
coycurin
coy ouch ouch what a shame yeah
Ouch there's nothing coy underneath Coy
he wasn't destroyed he wasn't
destroyed he was destroyed
later he wasn't
taken he wasn't taken destroyed he wasn't taken
Gosh I want another one
this team
Oh they didn't hear
me SH one
stand This is  the
team This is the Hardest One
Oh
yeah that means you put four
yeah
ah yeah that's okay Free real
estate Oh yeah it's okay hint for
[Music] the
kids are
fine
[Music]
and to find CH Where are to
any Anyanya observes but she doesn't say anything
that's how it should be
yeah
eh
where is this
one Oh
okay Oh okay I looked at it and
found it straight away how is this oh my god oh my
god
Oh there is one oh no oh yes it's missing someone
didn't
take it all the time Wow  If you
look at this, it looks like
this is the behavior of the students,
how about
this, this, this, this is easy, actually, this is
easy, that's it. Oh yes, yes, it's been taken, it's been
taken, which means it's done,
what's that?
Is this there? Is this
not already destroyed?
Hah, it
was destroyed. Something got stuck,
hah, it's been 10 minutes, okay, let's
go back, finished we go
[Music]
back  already finished go back go
back the
b go back go
[Music]
back
n n
[Music]
dat how many do you have I have EMP Wow
that's great you have
EMP Wow that means you lost two
yeah You should be able to get en
You should be able to get en
[Music  ]
nice I got four
emeralds
every wait Who found Who found what
Kobo found four and I don't know how
what I want to check her POV after this
Yeah I don't even know so you guys did
you guys find any No I know  what to
search for no no did you guys know that
there's actually one really close by
yeah probably right here ah what the
hell that's what it's supposed to look
likeers and chest and H see i would i
would recognize
[Music]
that everyone comes here everyone
everyone
[Music]
down Found A got three emeralds but it's
Who's got the Emerald Who's got the
Emerald How
many How many How many Emeralds you have
Um in total nine wow wow
nine emeralds that's me that's me
like  CH treasures if treasures yeah fre
treasures How many emerals you got
That's
awesome I
know so you guys understand understand
the puzzle That's
nice oh I gu I guess it's
F How many emerals you got
Have you got the
oneish
that's
finished but she found  the time
Fin That's not [ __ ]
fair did you get that one all right then
I'll cheat in the other
games wait someone
cheating I'm not taking anything
now
everyone everyone
hello
hello Hi Attention
please ok thank you  thank you for the
attention since we've already done The
Treasure Hun so we have to go back and
the B to continue the Simon
[Music]
[Applause]
let if we're in mame
[Music]
every Please go and let's go
[  Music]
It's okay you do pretty well what Simon
[Music]
says everything's
okay it's really like holding an elementary school child
[Laughs]
[Music]
i al
Why list Toon
say why does it matter to
us  Hello everybody are you guys all
[Music]
here 10 basically until they can
keep going okay
First I think based on the discord alone I
think so
[Musik]
[Music]
more we have like
[Musik]
demonst because is the top so goes First
[Music]
Okay
stand how
[Music]
[Laughs]
basic is given Prom level 1 2 3 4 to
[Music]
so on and on e if wrong  means
stop
already per level get
S
[Music]
ang ban
wait hold on hold on hold on hold on hold
on
i i that's right, we'll make a group for
them
OK,
go ahead, use GR for the
participants声 okay okay
okay Hi Ma
[Music]
ha
hau OK
l
throw away three two
one throw away I throw away throw away oh ang I think
that's the way it is ma'am not throw away not
throw away
throw again yes repeat
yes okay
throw Hi
throw don't give e please
committee bonus
Sal B it's better  just
don't worry, it's okay. Later, there are two, we'll
repeat it, we'll repeat it. It's okay, just
two, okay, throw two,
throw two
squats, two
one
R jkak
[Music]
go throw,
squat,
jump, three two
one, jump,
squat, jump,
jump,
nice three
emeralds Emal sengi  throw throw
squat jump jump squat jump ka J forward
twice forward twice okay okay okay okay three
three two one w throw  throw squat
jump jump
forward two forward two
UI ah
wow o o
SEG
throw
squat
jump forward
twice face left left Oh
three two one
throw y
kok jump jump forward two left
left shrunk shrunk shrunk W ci ci ci Yos Yos Yos Yos Yos Yos
Yos  ja sengwa throw
throw squat squat
jump forward twice twice face
left left face right right okay  okay
okay okay okay three two one place to squat
squat jump
front jump two left left
right
eh y sorry I don't see Antoni Antoni
Antoniuh
left left right
okay I I I see it looks like
Yopi is wrong, you
should be facing right, but Yopi
should turn around  Yi ngap keuna pasadap
right
Al Oh means wrong dong Heeh
Koko Bera
S eh i l Yes ennya wrong l okay
[Music]
okay go go
[Applause]
this is the emerald yeah Oh okay
okay thank you thank
[Music]
youk
any
please oh okay
Nice
Hello guys
[Music]
Ready The R I think I think it's better
to stand in the R for the
beginning than
face  Ma there face me I'm here
Hello here here
here in
I'm blind apparently Ok so The rule
is like explained during the practice so
you guys will be given
Progressive
Commands
Commands and the more you can do
it the better more  emerals you get yes
and if one of you eh failed question
yeah do we do it at the same time or do
we Yes at the same time at the same time
because There will be th two one hmm okay
okay okay Are you ready now okay okay  okay
start from the first one okay the first
one ready yes
throw three two one let's go how
thisame ok
Okay there's no sound there So this is okay
Or not
okay sorry can't see it from the plv I
think you have to be in place  I de
let it look
Okay okay okay you you can take your item
back
Okay Okay next
next you guys are right so next one is
throw
J th two one
okay
ye Okay Ok we're going we're going fast
we're going fast  next throw squat
jump three two
one oh
getting hot getting hot next is throw
squat jump forward twice
OK three three two one
you
for what
you so you were supposed to throw and
then you J and then jump but you throw
and then you
jump
sry  She's h
j
understandable
So that's mean you guys uh pass three
rounds Then I will give you not bad
three emeralds
here Thank you Thank
you I shouldn't be the one studying You
should have studied You
should I only forgot the order It's not
like I forgot  the
meaning uh you guys
cany now Thank you wait H on Oh hello
hello
Please speak slowly
Ma okay slowly everyone stand by in the
red
area o'clock jongkong jump
throw it's forward left right
okay stand on the on the red  area Please
am i on the red yes yes
stand in the red
[Music]
area thank are ready are ready
It will ey
Ok R ready k ready yeah
Ok ak
two one
go so scared You're starting off a
difficult one because Sounds like So
that's like l three stu or is it just
and one one
ST ah Okay
okay
me so next is l
J two one have a question have a
question okay no question Just do
it Wa Okay l if they don't say it maybe
it's only one  time
time
you want to stay J  That's also fine
don't worry you got it you got it ah OK
but you know Eh Yes that's it next next is
getting harder
throw
squat
jump throw jkok
jump OK throw squat
jump let's
go OK next next next
throw
squat jump forward twice okay
squat  jump forward two
De that was F times already right next
next next Em OK OK OK next
throw
squat
jump forward twice facing left
[Music]
eh
lempkok
jump forward
twice please left left Hi see
name How Kis continues already continued
OK next OK next eh
squat throw lom four forward twice face
left face right face right three two
one
lunge
conkok
eh LP and right and here and here and
then that's it  forg one forg I forg and
then if turn and then If I Turn Right do
I Turn like 45 De right oh well I mean
yeah As long as you turn right right
what I'm confused about no As long as
you  turn right I think so I guess That's
correct okay yeah can we he no what who
was
wrong What did I do wrong No You should
you should end it with meaning that the
other way
so first faing to re and then faing to
me what I faced  right you don't say How
many Degrees right yeah no No that's 90
degrees Yeah but you didn't say How many
Degrees I think it's just like
it's a misunderstanding it's H
up means only like kind of liking here
and then because this is  KITT and then
right is like to the right of this
position So you have to face here
yeah so that means four emeralds five
was it five right five five five
emeralds five
emeralds
yeah there you go Okay thank you That's
f you guys actually did great Don  't
Worry yeah still the highest so
far no no I think got five right but
anyway still the
same
over It's Not it's not over Hello are
you
ready We have a question yes oh So if you
say like kitty
uh KITT advanced  does that mean I Turn first
and then i i go forward Yep yep
front side facing at the moment ok
Okay Ok So if Hadan I just Run
like if facing right had right just
had
right face right
Run no worry it's not as complicated as
you guys think  it is
ok position you you can stand on the red
dots here red block Thank you stop
Ok Are you ready for the first one yeah
yeah
Ok the first one I'm going to tell you
is throw
Zeta ngadap dong Zeta ngadap there
zetaapadap sama muna ngadap muna ngadap
muna but what was right earlier was right
next no no facing the right way don't
Wor back item
Okay moving on moving on the second
is throwing squats three two
one
Okay sry take take backem
so nervous in me  life
before relax relax the third one
throw
squat jump
two
one gettingot here next is throw
squat jump forward twice three two
one
okay you can get back to your
position strong
thank  going strong next
throw
squat jump forward twice facing left
three two one
more ID
you can get back to position get back
to going strong next one
is
throw
squat jump forward twice face left
face right
3 two
one Oh
W wow wow wow I didn't  't
expect the first one to get this far
yeah
okayay going strong going even stronger
next
one l
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right back five times three two
one
Wow ye
ye wowow
okay okay Oh my  God OK even even
Harder next one next one Let's go it
never
I'll start again
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face right
back five times hit three times
three two
one crazy chat that was crazy
are for the
next go go go Before  I Forget
next time next time get into position
Okay red block please Za thank you okay
okay next one
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left
face right back five times hit three
times jump four times three two one
[Music]
one the last
round let's go the last one Are you
ready here we go
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right backward Li times Pul three times
jump four times run to the red block
three two
one Al crouch by accident
so apparently eh
am forgotten to eh backwards  five
times
only only f you are the highest so far so far
yeah the highest so
far than
[Applause]
on the back on the
back That's nine emeralds it would have
been 10 right if we got it I Yeah Yeah I
mean That's one less yeah yeah you
go Thank you Thank you than you thank
you that is so well okay Where is
skyla anjai okay okay okay okay
I have faith in you
guys Where should we face Oh face Muna face Muna face muna muna
okay thank you
yes you got a face face Muna
Ok where
m The entrance entrance entry Look up
look
up I'm hereon
[Music]
Where is she here in the green
Okay okay Are you ready Can I just give
you the command now yes okay  okay so
every every time the command finish you
guys get back to the red block Al right
and pick up any item you've thrown
the first one throw
three two one
OK that was easy moving on moving on
next throw squat three two one
OK next one
uh
throw squat jump three two one
I have Fa in you
next
throw throw jump forward twice
three two one
okay
OK OK
next
throw throw
jump forward twice facing left
three two one
we have to be patient okay ye Okay okay
okay you  made it you made it don't
worry believe in yourself
yeah next one next One OK here we go
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right three two
[Music]
[Laughs]
one
apparently I don't know should  I say
bot B yeah guys face left face right
face left face right yeah face left
face right not face left turn right
okay Wi had is left and the hadon is
right yeah oh I was like I was like
stopping here a bit and then  i do that
okay okay okay That's
great you guys are great got F
[Music]
on up
thank you
[Music]
okay hello
helloo
hai yeah
yeah
[Music]
yeah [
Music]
ha J
zomb
I Haj
Maru Haju Haju okay okay first
one
throw three two one go
throw
throw die
[Music]
die ad throw right
throw t Ti throw
Ti
tor throw
throw throw
lemp
e okay
take the item again
Bu okay
sengwa
throw
squat three two one
go take lag
okaygiii
throw squat jump three two one go
uh
Wow ci-ji
OK
throw
squat
jump forward twice three two one
go ye
that
throw
jump forward twice facing left three
two one
go k
k Don't die
yet  I'm sorry but I can't
hear it okay okay
throw
squat jump forward twice face left
face
right three two one
go Oh with them Heh nail
k
He that's
face
kanap left face left face right
Hidari Migi Eh
migak or not you just turned right, didn't you turn
right, turn
right, turn right, turn
right y
[Music]
Al
ak sama
S
finish let's go to the
exit i will try to be
smart ye
don'  t confuse me with your Mask What the
hell Oh
S like is talking to me but I see's face
[Music]
What Hi come on come on
downstairs come on go downair let go
downstairs W if you say that with Anya
voice  then I would have really fallen
for it
[Music]
also I should have
picked
yours, couldn't this already fit
the place, this is
here
[Music]
y here
Thank
you
Minut yeah because we wait for one  Minut
[Music]
anywayol just Open it
Yes
better better Who made it
okay okay
good how come you can't hear it How come
you can't
hear it What's up
[Music]
okaybody has each and will
howan apa h
[Music]
this so for the builders you guys will
go to the corner over
here and you guys will see the Them for
yourselves so we made a room over here
and then will come in and see
it at the very  corner don't don't come
in don't come in
this Are All To prevent anyone from
cheating so when you know the answer do
n't come out
[Music]
Oh and Chat please don't spoil the likes of
what you see  in the
builders side the
gu  only just press like the right Okay
there you go go ahead Can I try and I
guess when we're building it's best to
mute right
yeah also I think better idea
ad both
see which one is round do
come
pleases
Builder
[Music  ]
Okay This is all of the builders for the
[Music]
yeah yeah on
the How to write
[Music]
I have to sign the book and then Put
It's obviously just one
Guess
wrote it  how about it
[Music]
Bu Go b b
Ok
guys you
guys
Yes hold on please
Run
one it's it's the time girls again
fighting in a timely manner
[Music]
manner
in this is just like
we need to the round One
OK [
Music]
the is round  One
already
okay okay okay okay okay
okay Za Za
[Music]
Ar your voice
I'll face this way then okay yeah i
[Music]
guessakak di
group Thank you I appreciate
itbody  ready
[Music]
CH the committee is also out
OK for the book
Ok time to count
[Music]
on tired yeah Iekak
anyway OK let's count It
OK count it one
Minut one
Minut
OK game start
in
three two
one go go go go go
go anj  embarrassed Anji
embarrassed go go go go ho hoi hoi au
au
ipakes Aju Aju
oh
nice
man I I heard that sound no
it's
okay this we don't
have them in
each
Ops
Jan teh
answer  Ind what's it
called? What's it called?
eh, even kapus
ah
please
the in the
[Music]
k WR down your answer and put it here
[Laughs]
okay
okay okay
[Music]
Oh Se
okay okay Guys
e
committee how do you
make two mistakes
in  where did the sound all disappear
Okay I
[Music]
yeah next
round How much
[Music]
let's go
oh no oh
no I want to put things
Thank you than
youar right
sears I
forgot
no
here what the
[ __ ] we can't have sheers
yeah no you know what  you can you can
you can I'm sorry
here Sorry Here's your shear Oh thank
you thank you and there ok
Oh Next
round are we ready should I check the
book and
it's ready
start
in one wait Three two
one
and
go one minute uh
it's  pretty hard  it's pretty hard so
far
who was this R
[Music]
jetta Giving It Giving It Giving It
Giving
It Call gru Me ni kinginging
before
forgetting it
[Music]
okay and this one is the attempted 2D
drawing and this one Wow super Massive
[Music  ]
is like the closest one so
[Music]
far this is this is like the closest
answer I
think the imagination is pretty much
Please put down the answer
okay okay thank you for the answer Thank
you for the answer I know you guys
can't hear  me but Thank you for the
[Music]
answer Okay okay
in w w wow
wow yeah We should have Put Temple yeah
see Canada is the closest one Oh really
So Ju
please clean the W for the next round
Why is the writing small so the
writing is big
[Music  ]
so that it looks like screaming guys
[Music]
eh
wrong like
this
This is yes oh sherku eh
sherker you hold Oh this is a
dog thank you
Oh
okay ready
Okay game start
in
three two one
go what was that tea oh yes
Oh my
[Music]
God  ouch k
tu thiss
[Music]
egg ed Um SH this looks
like this looks like a gate What is
this I don't know we cannot see the
shape yet Yeah but we see
[Music]
oh
over done
Please put the  answer in Black turnomom
[Music]
[Music] that's
it  the colors are mixed
a lot, it's confusing, it
's confusing for a long time.
What's important,
everybody. Ready,
wait, don't take it. Thank you
[Music]
let's go let's
gow Oh I can see that I can see that and
fund  fund
danai see
that
fund
[Music]
you
K come on kla you
Ops
[Music]
okay
oh
this picture is right
[Music]
okay
okay okay k ni ni
there's a moment I forgot e who
was
this it's
switch time switch time oh switch time
If It's switch time it's a time not
switch time for
me they are switching
[Music]
Indonesia l taken yeah
so
buk this is
this design Oh I I
yeahこ uh That's  hard
go wait
hah Loh
[Music]
Okay
ah it's okay
that's
fine you can
wait this one is practically kind of like
Impossible I gu pretty much
Impossible give it
Another 15 seconds  gu
uh this is cool
i 5 seconds
left over
wrong
Please this is
already the last
okay okay Oh not yet
[Music]
okay OK OK OK Eh yeah this is
n't
enoughara ehka
[Music]
okayah the winner
be that's
who
now
[Music]
ur supposed to
it should be k
[Laughs]
kakiii It shouldn't be this,
shouldn't it? Isn't there really another word?
Lag
answer correct answer
Oh my God it shouldn't be OL  there's a
sound
Mute huh k
Kam
eh no Kamer no no
Kamer
J okay
[Music]
from earlier ak
[Music] okay okay okay
okay where the hell Oh I okay
okay
last easy easy Yes
easy eh  the book was taken
[Music]
who took the book
Hey wrong Hey bo who took the bo
okayo next Okay has everybody seen the
book
[Music]
z z took it again or not  Here,
Z, take it again, aren't you afraid to take it again?
This is
[Music]
guys, what donon, are you
the Donon who took the book, Sokap,
oh,
are you ready, aren't you ready to sing
[Music]
Laguwan, oh,
go
on, which glass is sharp,
which one is there, I just realized  Oh,
your ears, why are my ears on the
top, yes,
my eyebrows are thick
[Laughs] it's
really Ken's too
[Music]
oh this is
nice oh oh this is nice oh
k oh
[Laughs]
[Music]
that is to
obvious that is to obvious no his name, you know,
but he can read or not, that's
all. Yes, yes, yes,
that's true. Whether he's anjir or not, he
can actually be able to do it because I
don't know it myself. One look at it, you know.
Kukunyukung Sis, can you read it? Ca
n't you?
[Laughs]
[Music] I'm
too brainy,
but the answer is appropriate,
ma'am Oh, I'm not specific enough. Ma'am, I'm not
specific enough. Yes, ma'am. He wrote.  what did
you write ma'am
hah yeah How come it's like that?
Really, how come he wrote what I
wrote, yes, but that's Japanese,
yes, that's true,
this is
Japanese, yes, that's Japanese. Yes, that's it, the literal Japanese is
this. Yes, this is Japanese.
Oh yeah, did I forget?
What the hell,
Wani? Has this been written
yet? Looks like Yobi, have you written it yet
[Music]
Eh, that's great, bro.
H have another pair
of glasses, where's
the book?
rakuda rakuda that's
dong perakuda who was
doubtful De whoay
I'm
anjirah Oh this is there Wow what is this
guys ak
[Music]
k good J
eh
cor cor
everyone ho hello hello oh no need oh
oh J please
[Music]
OK everyone De
mute mute don't  i i mute mute everyone
mute Z I think
[Laughs]
deh nyaameame
[Music]
There will be like three rounds So let's
go to the wrong together Shall We
Come  on Come here Come here follow us
let's let's
go I Think first you guys need
to you know Click the bed just in
so you W spa inside outside
[Music]
again Come on up here
Come on up
here everyone
[Music]
Pa how many rounds will there be
ak rounds
[Music]
G It's A Battle Royale
basically we're not going by groups
we're not going Solo everybody going at
the
time and for the wool cutters You
are  you  are to press F1 the game
and for the
for you cannot
[Music]
crouch okay
well if if hitting is allowed then is
eating also allowed or like what if you
die and don't fall i guess You're also
hitting is only for like you  know make
people fall don't don't kill people
you're not allowed to kill you can hit
but you don't
kill but what if like you've been hit so
many times you're about to die from just
not eating  I
think there is food there. There is food
outside
in the
middle
here in
here
okay pleases
for
my le now Thank you Thank
you bye
bye and The Purple box here
[Music]
[Music] hai hai hai okay okay
Green is
[Music]
pink
where ok
not there is no orange You Take Two or
three
shes only Brown Pink
Green yellow blue and red because that
is the obvious
color as you guys
requested you guys want like colors choose
to each other We even like to use one fly I
think
so What color should I take
for the
color should we have Green  If It's
not
taken go
Upstairs for the forem who has taken
their colors Please go Upstairs because
ITL be easier for us to
monitor I'm
Brown Okay got got
[Musik]
so Green Pink and yellow is out Green
pink yellow and red Okay let's go with
orange  There is no
orange yellow R green and pink is
already out so the is
Brown Okay Ina
Brown blue Okay now go up
please How many stacks Can we take sry
two please two oh oh only two two should
be enough two should be enough two or
Three  is okay I  brought a lot I'll bring
some
down but I
think Okay okay I'm going to say it
again okay
uh is everyone here one two years F wait
where are we are we just going to use
all vc or whatever my stacks of
ka
[  Musik]
ka stop Using the all vc proximity
yesity okay
okay
[Music]
yeah Don't forget to F1 for the lower
level
[Music]
pink
Well I think like even if I fall
down you can still keep
using Oh
focus on not falling
down  we'll Cut our
F1 gladiat match
[Music]
Who's the one who cleans it,
let's just leave it
L Oh yeah, I'm going to lose it,
OK?
my
[Music]
heart
[Laughs]
out
[Music]
and I don't know Are we stillingingue
I forgot they can't
[Music]
can
R nice
[Music]
but if everybody survives
the
gubody stopping W there's only two
people should I do that
unless it goes on there's a time
limit
right Yes there's a time limit Minutes okay
so
you're careful it's I'll Be More
care
and
gu take more
[  Music]
persp How
[Music]
right but it's it's it's probably
because only this and then one more game
Right Round Oh my
God
ah like two rounds then
right Don't forget to take  more STS
everyone
Okay okay
nice
ure Oh okay
okaying
[Music]
thech everyone already
we have to accept it
[Music] it's
time we have to hurry up they say
they have to leave in a minute
soeng minute times yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my
god oh my god oh my god oh my god
[Music]
r
in can't see i
[Music]
[Laughing] [Music
]
[Music]
really  nice art guys
Ok everyone stop in right now stop
doing me okay I'll count the green first one
two f f si
[Music]
most Green is
24 mostly Green
24 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 13 14 15 16
17  18
[Music]
19 Oh
you're okay but it's not here
Dr pink pink It's been destroyed Oh it's been
destroyed already  okay 26 okay okay
[Music]
blue blue only
four wow
[Music]
W this is the one that
Emal
took earlier, that's the yellow one, hit it if it's already
ripe
[Music]
Why our
yellow Oh I think it's because They're
trying to  get Through It
fast I think
CR Come here Come here Come
here this this is for you from the
previous
Thank
[Music]
you no explanation necessary
is
good come back
Tiger
Okay okay we
start got to the corner
[Music]
oh  oh yeah F1
please guys I'm sorry but if we have one
and you only say go in the Chat We can't
see
it count down f f
f two one
go Already it's been set on the timer, right, that's it, gone
down for
realce no
r r Just go down and  then left
is
in to
me the F
Okay nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice left two person
[Music]
left
F two
[Music]
Okay oli oli k the pink one I K red
yeah 8 9 10  11 12 1 15 1657
3 3 33
[Music]
halout it's one different dong
no
[Music]
P
In In In Please come
here hold on
okay okay okay thank
[Music]
you OK now everyone It's time to
combine
everyone ATT
[  Music]
please It's time to combine all your
Emerald and
[Music]
exchangeit you can take my emeralds
right to buy
[Music]
stuff
[Laughs]
[Music]
First I that was free
was if free since Everyone Is
now what I'm
just we can only
really for one of
Us how
how Ar and
[Music]
my
empty pill I'm the first time you've heard
or
watched it  buong Jempa is majestic in
Aceh Bu
especially Beautiful lag
lam moonlight lam moonlight wind tu
ayonungsi
Ul
[Music]
indahl men c
l check check live par endari C
[Music]
Ar si  canganganger ar siangang ar
jasanganger ar
[Music]
amanganger open the door open the
door here Kobo got this song open the
door do you want to come in do you want to
loot or not
[Music] do you
want to freing right
[Music]
yes don't
answer don't want to be
there Don't kiss me Say if
you kiss two or three and
four six that's it and it's lost
if you get a new friend darling
Old friend gets a new friend darling friend
[Music]
old yit disappears then
whose voice it is I don't know
[Music]
yeah
This history of yours has
always
been
[Music]
endured by your original season of
anger
[Music]
in the rainy season, the water overflowed until
far away your springs from Solo
were trapped by mountains,
a thousand flowing waters until
[Music]
far away you were born,
if that was
[Music]
the boat of
your history, the
Pak people always rose
[Music]
a
know
Eh nice nice nice AC
as cute yeah guys wow wow
wow I
like it yeah
that's it Man Ho live
Indonesia thank
[Music]
thank you
OK now the medle is already done thank
you so  much everyone for watching and
listening to the medle Ho live Indonesia
and I don't know if they are already done
with
the shopping shopping shopping
hosina shopping Mada Des Mada Des
mada mada Des
shopping
H Which Tower should we all go Um okay
OK y
yur
Red
E  anyanya Ina
y
Know
Ni
likara blue
[Music]
right you have more range
not super chat Thank
[Music]
you there is a blue yes
next Put in every
temples Click bat
first When I was playing like navigator
I couldn't really hit anyone with  the
arrows to be honest It's like really
difficult Yeah it is really difficult so
And if we buy wait How many is it I
guess 10 arrows I feel like it just be
gone in the first round R One te ready
for the
game everyone is already there
ok
[Music]
Solo no b
Ho Hello Thank you everyone for coming I
want to check it first okay okay
perfect perfect
ha So the first one Will Be
in Red FL In Yellow FL You In Blue Flag
everyone is already on the
temples
Ok
so I'  m just going Say The
Rules a
minutok so as you guys can see There will be
three rounds but this time you
guys in the round one team
There will be a fighter and navigator if
the fighter De
Can i hai thank you
so a fighter De That's mean game over
for your team if  navigator De that means
the game still must go on but navigator
cannot help at
all cannot shoot cannot
navigate all you
can all you can do is depends on your
Fighters team
and Wait
H if navigator navigator cannot be
outside of the
Temple but can fight  with bow  and arrow
So if you have a bow and arrow you can
you can use it if you kill the enemy
and the items fall you can take it oh
Ok the bed is outside as you guys as you
guys can see the
outside if you guys date  then Dead
That's
gameover quickly item
not giving me the weapon yeah come here
Okay okay A Bed near the
[Music]
Temp you not even if you die Once you
can't do anything either as a navigator
or Fighter bad doesn't have to be  close
yeah
right It's
okay Are we are we are good  to go he guys
guys nervous ready I'm nervous use of the
time yeah do we go back into our own
vcs yeah please Okay
byee let's go back
[Music]
to go back to your on okay
Okay
Nice I'm going to the place  first hold
on please wait
here
Okay
ready looks like ready looks like ready
Okay the game starts
in how many minutes By the way eh because it
should be 30 minutes that means a total of 10
minutes 10 minutes long too yes it's also the easiest
to die that's right also three two one go
Where  did you fall
to Where's zomy I don't know I I didn't
see
it is that Oh that's
rainy and Y Is
there and In The
Rat any In The Rat in kyla's
place She's Waiting for The Doors to
open I guess Oh no she
doesn't  I wonder if she wants to
jump She can jump whenever she
wants Where your other
Ok good
thank you, have you pressed F1 yet? How come it
seems like you're going to the save place
and then you don't want to
move far to the save place?
then go to the place where they think that's it,
isn't that their strategy,
they want Nit, they're the ones who come
like that, maybe maybe, maybe,
hmm Why Everyone Is just like so scared,
but Reny is the one who walks
everywhere, he's the one who explores,
really explores
Wow,
Rene is brave, if for example he meets a
piston, he can really press it and then
jump
towards it, kanata will fall, eh, Kanata
Kanade, Kanade will fall down. Yes, wait
a minute. Sorry. Ta and D are close,
guys, and D is close.  guys, so it's
a bit Taipo a bit
huh
eh ah iovi has gone out iovi to
the place
Finally the war has started between
Anya and iovi Will R follow? Can you
see Ina trying
to shoot the
arrow ah
OK anyanya in
out Oh any that's the fighter yes yes oh
now
r oh he's using
jump, he's a piston, SL, he's easy to go
anywhere, auntie is looking for victims,
it's so scary, yes, it's like a shark, do
n't you
think
Wow, the sound is helpful  It's like he's
there, he's right there, he's wrong like that, heeh,
but I'm actually waiting,
waiting for Iovi to be hit by the piston,
actually, is it true, or is this member like that, he's
getting hit by the piston, but why
doesn't anyone want to hit
them, hah, it's fun to see,
oh,
alsuina, wait, that means  because Anya lost
Anya didn't play in the final yeah Yes no oh
okay oh
out OK
r
k hah yes vote out never mind vote out
already
That's it, that's it, that's all,
those three teams
just now okay
okay
next round
two
team round two team
Okay Z
Ame
z z
yell can do the same too
hai
[Music]
hai oh wait No Oh I think youain you
have like
[Music]
hair to
y Ok
risu risu accompany this okay Kar
there's
pink pink there's no red Oh pink
sorry sorry red
I
forgot I haven't had any water I've finished I haven't
taken it yet
Ar  is G naig me I can
navigate coincidentally there's Anya alsoose
from one yeah
oh just the committee or not so it's fair okay
thank you
Space
Can thege Oh
there ready ready Ready okay okay e game
start
and
three two one
go go go go go
go I'm curious  right AD Oh risu who is the
fighter for risu kanadi and
[Music]
yangniper oh
teone
[Music]
now are
areing but it's not bad ru ru use
Stone tuh k pakone Ma'am oh also Mr Stone
deh
Oh
okay
Kani
[Music]
kla I I missed ame keegprek ame
Earlier he said kegeprek I missed it
ouch what a shame viewers oh tuh tu tu tu
tu tuh Even though it's already ing already already already already
they've been looking at each other
earlier you have to be careful because of
the sniping
right, it's falling there it's falling but it's
there it's there I don't know why it's still ST
there even though it just needs to go up
Ok pretty tight
everyone I wonder Who's the
winner am
orisu Oh a close
Battle they have sword versus AX
Oh looking at them from Up closest
One Who's gna be the winner it's
really funny if you go back and forth
kegeprek Come on, go keprek dong I
want to see the squirrel geprek
eh
uh but
it's no use
hiding but the tools are still there  there's
something like that
that was a funny way to be Invisible
actually You have to get Rid of your
weapon
[Laughs]
okay
yeah It is it
is it
was J Yes
Wow this is this  It seems like the power of
this committee is ugh,
oh, wait, I'll break this first, here,
there,
go, here
[Music]
here,
ah, okay,
Wow, how
naig, so he's like telling people
positions and then he's like telling you
don't come here because there's that and that
and then it's like, right?  we can't
see too far, so yeah, I
also can't get to places that are
really far away, you know
[Music]
if
I have a lot of substitutes
today, it's the same in yellow,
yes, in Green,
gre gre
each other, that's how it is.  there's an
Enderman dog Hi tbl
Anjir
hai hai hai hai
wi
wi wi I
think that was Muna, there's
two bars like that, two
bars, what the heck, there are two that haven't been
raised yet, but I forgot where, it's okay, it's
okay, this is Sabung Saung admin
committee versus
committee committee versus committee No, I don't
know, I'll look for a position first,
okay, game starts
in
three two one
[Music]
how come you're nervous, nervous, he's so fast,
eh,
where's his partner? Oh  the ren are
there trying to
peek jumping around
peeking peeking where on
earth are they going to get out of the
way
Oh still peeking
try to find a
way look for it
look for it it can be increased
if
you want to move
okay okay meeting to each other Okay Nice
Nice verus Who G be the winner
[Music]
andn pleas
congratulations Wow, the power of people in
each other is in what yaama
[Applause]
[Music]
next This is I will give
you hold
[Music]
on
kk here we gather first yes
gather first in the same place
no  oh
no
think everyone thank you so much for
joining the HID Cup for this
year I Really appreciate it that
you took the time to play with us
toing the
and also Thank you for the ID for
helping me toilding finishing
[Music]
the it was an honor for me to make
this be one of your mor
[Music]
and
and after this after this for the ID
there's another stream I believe
[Music]
for
the
so gamej
theood pleases
let's take a together
guys where are
you let's go outside
[Music]
committee
already hai
[Music]
SP SP
SP okay
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
I'm
really tall nihangong
[Music]
the others
are in Anjay Okay wait where
Here I am
[Music]
Meni Hi
k k
[Music]
high
guys Where are you guys
[Music]
a add one lag bottom bottom can't be
seen from anywhere i
akuou Okay Ah looks looks OK OK
ah Yi Yupi OK OK this is ok th two
one
yeah eh wait a minute guys
guys hang on guys it's not good nihak it's not good it's not
good for a moment B it's not really good huh hang on oh take
a photo so I don't take
a break why fing B Ouch
it's more or less serious, it's
worse, I think it's really
funny, hang on, hang on, hang on, hang on, OK
? Thank you
[Music]
thank you, be patient, be patient,
okay, okay, th two one
[Music]
[Applause]
go Thank you everyone, thank you so much
[Music]