well well well you have stumbled into
kfb what do you do now huh you are
very welcome at kfb go go ahead and sit
down and order some
food while you're here we will serve you
and you will probably get addicted oh
yeah if you're looking for a job
and we hire employees 24 7 all the time
always welcome there is no hiring stop
ever
[Music]
everyone cares
rising endlessly
we
will one day
dominate the fast food industry
we will be the only ones selling burgers
and fries in this world
the only ones
and
to become the only ones
we will take
any measures that need to be taken
because this is our
shift has destiny
and is
never ending
okay
but this
is just divine
exquisite