[Music]
a
no
[Music]
yay wow oh
yipp hello
[Music]
it's
us we are so
here finally entering I'm I'm so sure
like every time I like switch like
switch around the camera around this
creeper head I get like small
heart hello do we want to do a little V
uh sound check by introducing I just
want to check the volume from everybody
okay okay let's start with Callie hello
hi check one two my game isn't showing
up hi it's your boy what's going on
everybody whole live englishy Mory
Reaper D singer I do a bunch of things
hey everyone how are you it's 7 a.m.
here I asked she's the only one with 2.0
here I Morrison
2.0 wow you're right actually hold on a
sec I am hey she's too advanced for us
oh the tech the tech is unprecedented
except when in OBS all right here we go
I got it I fixed it we're good what what
you fixed oh the the screen that's just
so and silly what's this iron did you do
the iron farm did you make it work here
oh wait yeah wait wait wait I want to I
want to explain everything don't explore
too much oh yeah okay I'm say something
uh hello this is small Abby piloting
Amilia Watson a oh no it's small
AB I'm here to Ender these yeah yeah
yeah nice end the dragging on
those yeah yeah blocks and the dragon on
those
blocks yeah on your
face say something
go today we're spanking the Ender Dragon
spank spank spank spank with
LA yeah the show of
Doom chunka
I don't know what that is it's a shoe
it's AO it's a sandal it means sandal oh
okay yeah let's go sandal woo he's
Spanish right yeah yeah yeah it's like a
Spanish meme kind of also reality oh
it's is it like Australian
songs yeah yeah is
it oh it's like it's like a threat it's
like oh I'm going to get the CH I'm
going to beat you with it not the ch
ch o sounds so
threatening okay and say something hello
this is
me
English okay hi beautiful I think it's
all relatively balanced I think so all
things should be if it's not the case
chat please complain feel free to
complain directly to me now before yall
I mean y'all are already running around
I got to give you a tour of some new
things for the ones who haven't been
playing that much recently I mean I also
stopped playing for a while but um am uh
mmm has been working just saying check
it out she worked so hard on fixing it
after Rage Quit
okay yeah which was understandable
considering everything all things check
it out check it out it's
beautiful it has I followed like a
tutorial but in the video tutorial they
did it like a one block lower I think so
I had to raise the platform so when you
stood here you were too tall but now I
kind of fixed
it way it's okay Kelly to scooch
underneath it's okay I won't blow it up
if I scoot all the way no wait I'm
coming
iow you can actually really get attested
it you can get all the way
in it doesn't explode wow wow
for real you know what you guys know
what happens when all five M member
together we don't have to put don't have
to put it to test you know it's working
if you just stand back a little bit oh
but I think we might actually have to
use this for enchanting purposes perhaps
um so feel free to get your levels up
afterwards the
tour fit in
Minecraft you mean spicy aerobics let's
go a I like the shiny details on it
erotic aerobics thank
you I'm wearing the same outfit too I
did I just realized I didn't realize I
was using this skin oh you're matching
yeah nice one
matching okay follow follow follow
follow dance instructor what do we what
I said you're slapping their cheeks
right now you got to come see the iron
she's practicing for the the the real
deal
this pink house uh it used to be
prettier and it used to stand next to
the pandas but I had to move it in order
to also try to get the iron farm to work
so I moved it all over here and I had a
lot of villagers with a lot of jobs in
here but walk in walk in the children
are going to leave probably that's okay
e run they're used to be more jobs and
more people but when I logged in today
everything every single villager
despawned for no
reason and I had to start from scratch
yay you had toy another
villager what what wait how' you wait
you had to start from scratch well the
way I did it well I had some problems
with the with the iron farm too I fixed
it like a million times in the past few
days there was always something wrong
with it and um sometimes the villagers
escaped or died the zombie escaped or
died or Golems killed zombie or so God
so one of the Escape villagers I was
able to bring them over here and then I
had one spawn out of the one block and
then I make have them make babies again
so thank God that was good happy family
yeah but they're not I mean I I had a
one time I had a one villager with a
mending book unfortunately he's gone no
but I I did out of that I made one
mending uh pickaxe and one mending sword
so those can be used for exp farming if
need be the sword especially yeah but
yeah we're in the last day so all of
this is not so
important but one could still get armor
from one of the guys cuz one has a full
diamond armor
SW okay um and then there's fish in the
water now in the
pond which is a big
Improvement if I kill I'm joking I'm
joking dolphins are dead I'd never kill
them wild this not speci sare ah I don't
know if every did everybody already see
the Improvement on the one block
spawning thingy the chocolate bar on top
of it oh yeah can I killed this child H
yeah yeah it's his fault from running
away from home teach him a
lesson in here disobey your
parents okay well we can walk up here
and I'll show you cie and me started
building this iron farm it was a lot of
stupid work because we had to find a
really old version iron farm and we
built the wrong
one
and you had to do um it didn't work for
the longest time Cy you can see inside I
I put some
rails it it's currently not working me
it's c not working it it worked before
because okay I put rails down because
only with the zombie sitting in the boat
it just didn't work um it needed a
certain amount of milliseconds of
ticking for the
villagers uh to spawn a Golem and so
with the mine cart going back and forth
back and
forth it makes it so that they don't see
it too often and not too little but the
zombie despawned even though I gave him
a name tag so [\h__\h] him wow that's rough
God what a
shame yeah um I also replaced the zombie
several times ah I got like b a bunch of
iron out of it but we're already out of
iron
again why are they despawning why are
things
despawn is the server it it's very buggy
the server is very buggy it's a lot of
stupid things happening well I will say
Kiara thank you for trying your best and
it was fun working on this with you
anyway it has been easy T but Celly it
worked for quite a while after I added
some more things to it and I got a lot
of iron out of it so it was
useful well that's good hopefully the
iron is put to good
use yes oh please come back
up riding in the
car get out of
there up up up let me put the block back
I could make it work again if I if I had
another
zombie you
put just hop in here and end it all
thank you try
me can't me I have
kills hey you can't drown there it's
safe safe for even sharks safe for
drowning yeah I don't think drowning is
safe safe for not drowning it the oh
okay H um oh yeah and I don't know uh a
yeah behind so basically check it out at
the nether portal first chest U we have
I think we got like two more totems or
so and I made you some Shields 14 more
golden carrots in the and then here the
chest right next to it we have five
pieces of everything except for the
helmet I I didn't have enough diamonds
and emeralds anymore for another helmet
please
everybody please take something uh of
one of each you can take something
unenchanted and with the unenchanted one
you could go to the enchanting table
first you might need to get some
levels wait take now I take now yeah
take now take now just don't lose it
don't lose it don't die and the only
other problem is there's not enough
diamonds there weren't enough diamonds
for diamond swords I only have one
diamond sword that has mending which you
could use for XP farming for
now and uh the infinity bows were lost
in the past stream to due to unfortunate
things happening like glitching but
guess what guys we we all get five
golden apples and that was your boy that
gave that then we have so much food and
stuff you're welcome I'm the Apple man I
think we'll be fine even with no diamond
swords we'll have to make iron swords
perhaps and there
there's one bow that is fancy some bows
bows oh yeah but we can enchant the
other bows yeah let's enchant I want a
bow uh yeah take take one there's one no
non enchanted bow uh actually two I
think they're not wow
wow yeah take it take it and see what
you can get out of it uh if you want the
the EXP uh the The Mending sword for exp
farming
uh I'll put it into the middle shulka
chest how about feather falling can I
enchant my boots with feather falling I
think the boots most of them already had
it but if you don't have it on then yeah
if you have a feather falling book
please take it please take it there is a
feather falling four by the way someone
want really w w
w just so that it Rhymes yeah I'm going
to take
this unfortunately if you want to use
one of the books we currently don't have
an anvil and I don't know if we have
enough iron for an anvil we need that oh
does it work in the in the enchanting
table too I never did it like that
before only Enchanted without a
book can you put the book in
there Iron swords we need I thought we
had
one the Anvil is broken they break
eventually so yeah we need we need one
to combine
let me see
Anvil I currently have
yeah one block uh block I know this is
painful you just got to through
it uh I'll try them now we won't be able
we need more iron if we want to make an
get cobone we can quickly eat it we can
quickly mine quickly m 30 iron right 30
wait I have two blocks of iron now we
need one more block and I have another
seven of iron I'll put it in the
chest right now too mm I'm going to make
a stone SW more bar so basically we need
Anil and finish our equipment
he a Viller spawn egg that's cool they
egg that would have been nice earlier
yeah I didn't know that villagers are
reptiles yeah they not humans or mammals
even wait I have an important question I
thought of earlier does anybody have
experience with
reptiles
iards before do they smell like do
snakes yeah they do very specific like
like lizard pea smell kind of liard PE
smell musy so do ferrets actually like
different animals kind of have like I
don't know if you smell horses before
and stuff like they all have different
smells M stinky
imagine the smell no I don't want to I
want to no it's okay you don't have
to thank you good sharks are not
reptiles right that means don't
have Shar have aell other
thanish just fish
diamondy oh let's go Diamond seven stack
St your an iron pickaxe for better iron
pickaxe okay I I I I mind it with
diamond pickaxe oh I'm picking up the
blocks Miss organizer quit
organizing yeah I'm just putting stuff
into random chest now yeah that's good
no no don't destroy the organization n
what are we five is it SM a silver man
uh enchantment yeah I think it's pretty
decent we put in the book chest but
don't we need a bunch of blocks like to
make a bridge cross the end okay so we
have nine iron yeah a few would
be I mean yeah a few we we will'll
definitely need some blocks are we going
to do the bed Tech
tactic didn't we try that the first time
we killed him together we tried it I
think when you jump on you tried it it
works what happens what is it I don't
know if you use a bed in the in the end
it explodes right
you can jump on it it's
also it knocked out a large amount of
Health I remember that oh it actually
made a decent difference so we have one
person who's like the sacrifice and then
they no if you walk like like hide
behind some of the Rocks you don't take
that much
damage okay from theed oh by the way one
more thing T I changed the difficulty
for to today's uh cause from easy to
normal cuz we were on easy this whole
time we been on baby mode yeah but it
wasn't so baby we died quite often and
you know had our own issues that doesn't
make me feel better end does not make me
feel
better oh yeah
music love
music yeah oh beautiful what are we
listening to
everybody what's cold I didn't see it I
just put it in it's nice I think it said
blocks or
something oh okay
[Music]
time go get it go oh
nice I was too
[Music]
late it's a good working song
yeah s they maybe despawned because of
difficulty change no they despawned
before I changed the difficulty I
checked they were just
gone by Bane of Arthropods wow how
helpful of
AR kill the
spiders yeah yeah I have two blocks of
ir we can make we can make three potions
of s falling
oh we have a f a single Phantom membrane
maybe I I'll work on that I'll cook this
IR cook up some potions again wait do
you know where the where the thing is I
put it the somewhere I saw it on the on
the the Box okay okay okay let her cook
let her cooking
[Music]
this was actually the first time
that uh I ever was at least involved in
building a like a functional Farm like
the iron farm in my whole Minecraft
history in these past four years I've
always avoided making
Farms how you feel oh no I know the
right word but rewarding
I accomplished it got me a bit add right
it you're just like yeah yeah and a lot
of frustration when it just doesn't work
and when things glitch around in this
old version of
Minecraft we got three more
emerals Diamond a block of diamond oh
let's
go a block of diamond a block that's
good that's really good that's a lot of
diamond then we we can probably already
make the last diamond helmet that we
were missing if someone wants to make
that ah sugarcan farm with my mom
yeah that was yeah that was mostly my
mom oh slime that's a mean dude please
yeah kill yeah beat him
upat up eat them up eat them up
[Music]
[Applause]
did you have a nice nice birthday I
did I slept so much after your birthday
stream a
nice stream big emeralds feels good mhm
yeah it does mhmad
Eep oh it sounds so nice right now h no
it's 7 I'm fine I'm fine no complains
I'm cinat right now I need leash run me
like a like a dog on a treadmill did you
guys see uh the myth uh Ramen
collaboration was announced a few like
an hour ago or so I saw that some Ramen
in LA and in New Jersey this summer you
can get my themed r
Jersy I'm so
sorry
myat sorry my chat I have not retweeted
it yet I just woke up sorry de they got
some cute merch too and and everybody's
got like one
item GA has like a T man I think oh I'm
slurping
here slur here Calli has a chocolate
dessert has
tea has a a mushroom Ramen I think yummy
with lots of mushrooms on it really good
and I have an orange
soda very own which is I mean you know
there need to be some nice uh basic
Refreshments I'll take it I'll take what
what's
yours you I already said you have the
Boba te
oh his
pearls
pearls Watson's egg
what Watson's I like I like the idea of
it being her pearls feather yeah like
like she's a detective that found some
like not's eggs just like villagers oh
no small the small um
eggs that's why there's so many of them
so if you don't thoroughly chew them you
have the risk of a small Al hatching in
your stomach oh no alien movie upcoming
is about it's about the this is going a
direction taking over the
world I support that movie's idea I
support it that's exactly what I want to
happen oh inventory just exploded with
things uhoh watch
out where did it go this is
you too can have small army inside of
you no thanks let's go I'm
fine oh I think it disappeared probably
underground life's all about new
experiences
right
exactly
you come back oh came back oh cre oh my
God he's camping oh
creature careful now hey
hey why are you bulying me in
particular here fny
Target he's dead defitely did not help
that it was killed by a sword that I
named the after myth instead of the
[Music]
aftermath what happens after myth what
does happen after this promise promise
yeah true the world just
explode gobbled into a black
hole gobble
gobble but it looks really sick the name
after myth on the sword looks really
aesthetic I have to after dinner myth
can you imagine if not saying Kik but
saying gobble gobble instead gobble go I
think that would be
super I couldn't turkey
yeah okay
what no wa wait wait what what's what's
what's waya no don't wait what what's
Way's animal what what is she uh turkey
yeah exactly
no peacocks and they go yeah she's a
peacock a PE foul a PE she a lady turkey
foul sorry she's a turkey as much as I
am a chicken really are they making a
new Phoenix Emoji it's already there if
only that existed 4 years ago I would
have taken it as my emoji what are we
going to do I don't want to I'm too
attached to my chicken emote at this
point add it oh that one it looks really
nice looks so Co dang it born a little
too little too
early yeah
fire oh so how how we doing on the iron
front we have singular irons and two
blocks there's about to be five more
iron added onto
that with with the 13 I can make another
iron block and then we
need a few more
singular uh we
need
wait wait that no we can make it we can
make the Anvil let's go let's go
time now please choose your books and
enchantments wisely and keep in mind
that you don't have to use the books you
can also just throw the piece of
Enchantment into the enchantment H the
piece of armor into the enchantment
table and see what you get there chance
put looting on The Mending sword will we
get perhaps more items from the
mm perhaps M some iron from the zombie
what's good well my Ming sword already
has uh some uh other enchantments it's
already
full oh what I'm going to go farm some
exp now let's see is piercing good for
arrows or is that just
sword piering I wouldn't put that on
anything TB not that good Smite what
about
Smite
Smite sword I think not so bad it could
put someone could put protection
or
something oh it's for Undead I see
piercing fre piercing three respiration
I'm trying to figure out what would be
good for a bow and arrow cuz I feel like
I'm going to end up using a bow and
arrow oh wait aim
correction do they have that aim
correction oh If Only They did
do right
away power wow too bad we don't have
power yeah power but the bow if you if
you don't have the right book just put
the bow um well you need some levels but
I can also maybe do it for you I can get
levels leveling you can put it on the
enchanting table that's behind the
Diaries
mhm di see what it gives you can I put
flame on the
bow yeah
fire cool flam should only burn like
enemy mobs and like TNT and stuff
TT Bo do we dry it
out oh maybe not oh maybe I shouldn't be
here I'm just going to get killed H we
might actually I might hurt you because
I have sweeping Edge when way next to
each other might be a little bit
dangerous I have quite a few that's why
I put thorns on my
we on my armor smart wait did we confirm
we're just using iron swords my
bad we might have to we only have one
diamond sword the one that I made dang I
thought we were using Stone swords
honestly that's an upgrade is anyone
going to take
bbow you can you can use
it I made it but you can use it I trust
you I take the strong sword you take the
strong bow
okay wait what should I put on this
regular bow yeah I'm also wondering but
that's what
I'm is
good if you can get infinity that good
but
otherwise if we still have uh diamond
blocks if it's not used for the
helmet then you can make some more
swords out of
that I'm
breaking too it's ax cheaper to
make just make what's your preference if
you prefer to find
only enchant it once let me see if I can
get a bunch of levels and tryant another
one yeah Power one is they be
enchanting they're enchanting I'm an
enchantress
wow here
good good ide marel 30 wait why is there
so many bookshelves have some how do we
make more books because I made it so
that they chat told me that if you make
more shelves then it will be
stronger free free rows a oh by the way
if you're looking for lapis Luli it's in
the chest next to the
um next to the enchanting table I took
all of it there was so much in there you
can't take all of it I take a stag okay
I also yeah there should still be many I
think this is kind of overkilling
yeah I I wouldn't mind you know I think
you know we can um I want to B have to
do that much we we asked for an
enchanting table K built the library the
enchanted Library I couldn't stop I
couldn't stop
anymore I started and then I couldn't
stop it was
fun I really got addicted
man wait so you wasted how many
materials building an extra
and I was wondering how trouble he has
building like like a you know the usual
enchanting table we see like in a in our
Minecraft server was just like one layer
of books I just walk over oh and see
three lay I thought I thought if I make
an enchanting table and it's not like
the full power then it would be an
embarrassment to myself so I should go
full or go nothing I thought you were
Ling books youit have somebody chat says
we can break the bookshelves for more
books if we're low on books no no no no
you can just make more books we have
enough paper and there's cows for Le
where's the leather I don't see it the
cows the cows and I think there's some
more books in one of the CH one of the
chests uh a few more books are in there
there's like a couple more in the
enchanting
box yeah we
have back here take take some enchant
them go enchant them have fun with my
enchanting
table pleas last
leg that give me some wa who's got
mending anybody did I miss that
conversation just the sword the there's
mending on my pickaxe and on my uh
sword I can give you the sword if you
want to farm some
exp what no I don't want you don't want
to uh no I want mending on this bow well
okay mending yeah I used to have a
villager with Ming but he died he he
despawned what a shame very rude I guess
we can just
get yeah but think about it putting
mending on there does it even make sense
when today is the last day and this is
like the last hour pretty much true
enough no you want Power you want to get
big and
strong we don't need mending anymore we
have a collection of a
puppy somewhere puppy some paper paper
there should be I know that word in
Spanish
papel
yeah
Pap is that
French they're just making up things
yes chess says
[Music]
we well guys I want to warn you we now
have a new member who speaks French
so do not mess with the language too
much she will sense it and she will come
over and then um correct us our friend
how to pronounce I only care about
people correcting me if it's a language
that I I kind of know a little bit of oh
exctly is it is it BL
or
s s
BL we we
bagette
weage you guys want to farm X or what I
want to farm someone's sucking them all
up wait I'm almost done I need two more
levels then I'm gone one and a half
actually trying to get to 30 looks like
we're lining up for like something it's
like sit on Santa's lap something like
that M
Santa hello dried it up you guys like
the mall Santa or the mall Easter Bunny
more I'm partial to the Mall Easter
Bunny he looks more miserable actually
maybe it's cuz I can't tell cuz he wears
a he wears like a like a a a f suit so
you actually can't make direct eye
contact unlik the M Santa you can make
direct eye contact and I don't like that
yeah it makes me feel uncomfortable I
prefer the big fake Bunny man right I'm
I'm going go down one level one yeah go
go down am go go down the go oh wait is
that not am there in the back no go to
the front go to the front go to the
front socially
acceptable Kelly can you move one to the
left yeah oh that's too far that's too
far
uh yeah yeah yeah yeah okay okay nice I
took a picture peeking peeking
through okay okay um what happen it's
not spawning anymore not much at least a
little bit
but maybe there's a spider yeah I hear a
spider up there somewhere should I go up
there I'll go up
there declogger oh no I don't want to
touch anything called the plumbers yeah
she's the plumers if we go to sleep if
go to sleep everything will despawn and
then okay yeah I don't want to touch it
cuz oh
yeah no one could blame you alen no one
could blame you
yeah
Sor I have witnessed and I'm a rage quit
live when she fixed it for the 10th
time exploded again yeah the beds good I
switched the beds because of experiments
you now in the experiment you're part of
it I knew
I'm
experim I'm observing your sleeping
patterns depending on who are you
sleeping next to in myth who are you
sleeping more soundly next to stud yeah
sleep currently I didn't consent to that
okay signed the I saw I saw that clip of
of G I didn't watch it but I it says I
keep on getting it recommended something
about GAA being a test subject
what yeah why are you a test subject I
don't remember I'm going to have to
watch the
clip she was she was the one we're all
being tested constantly wait you have a
tin foil hat emote that's yes yes
because I always make conspiracy
theories and stuff hold on guys let's
put on our tin voil heads first
yes so yeah Ena drew it Ena drew that
one don't you think that's encouraging
like Behavior yes yes you think maybe we
maybe you should stop that I just I just
need one more enemy then I'm gone you
mean we're not a cold all right we're
not a cold okay does somebody want to
use the sword because okay um here don't
don't lose it I won't I mean unless it
blows up
again because it's me for some reason I
get the feeling that it might happen no
no no no it's very safe all right no
it's really safe you can like get really
close I hear a spider
again maybe while you guys are doing
that I'll just fish yeah get a nice bow
out of it oh yeah bows from fishing we
have of the sea or
something um yeah Lu at the see
one one of the uh things should be
enchanted one of the fishing yeah it has
luck of the fish or not luck of the fish
luck of the sea
luck of
the I Enchanted to eat you guys ever
think about if you threw a rock deep
into the ocean you will probably be the
the the last person to touch that rock
for a very very very long
time true true isn't that crazy I never
thought about it that
way crazy probably go rock throwing then
I'm going to be thinking about that
doit well I can give you like an
equivalent take a block a one block
whatever it is go to the edge of this of
one of our platforms and just throw it
off here I have a stick if you want to
borrow
that go thank
you fine
Steed what a just throwing the stick off
you're going to miss it Kiara Mak this
content okay okay okay okay wait I'm
coming are you at the at the mmm
[Laughter]
I'm going to do it she's going to do it
she's going to be the last one to touch
it the last the last person to touch the
stick unless you guys find
it there it goes wow how do you feel
after this emotional moment wait I don't
think I was the last one I threw it I
think it touched the bee the bees down
there oh wow you threw it right on the
bee yeah there's there's a lot of bees
down there maybe it in his mouth or
something Rose be on a stick maybe you
helped the Bee by throwing it a stick
maybe that's exactly what it needed I
couldn't throw my Bon so I threw my
stick sorry
be be that's all the way down there yeah
he's stuck
there yeah it's all the bees that
spawned from the one block but didn't
know where to go I'm so sad went to hell
instead
okay wow they went to be hell shame we
should build down there and themine for
make a beine
for okay I'm going to enchant something
now wait Ena did you see my reply to
what you sent me
earlier I think so sent me a big fish
building and I said INF I saw oh
infrastructure
there was literally like a big big
building that looked like you know a
shark and I was like
big building like anid or
something it's pretty cute it
is hey man where's the paper do we have
any paper yes there should be paper
still somewhere
yeah where wait where's the paper which
box
[Music]
um
okay if you need more there's also a
sugar cane
Farm a lot of sugar
cane going to buy this 17 what did I
just
build maybe I don't need it I don't need
it I guess this is fine hurt me
but I want to enchant one more
[Music]
bow I want to enchant one more you're
getting really
aggress what level are you going for
Callie 30 I'm only 26 but I'm almost oh
you can get there yeah
yep aab then I'll
continue I got to Google what this thing
is in Minecraft oh I could
also yeah slay children
is that not how
I in in video
games in mycraf how do you get pumpkin
seeds potato uh we have a few in the
seed box I think you can Harvest pumpkin
put it like in the crafting area and
then you get
SE
P thought we had more oh okay that's
good I thought I'd make more pumpkins
uh
here see I knew prep would take a little
while you know what we won't have to
prepare golden apples fall out yeah
there's plenty now there's plenty and we
have some cool potions too and we have
we have we have freaking totem of
undying I I think we win I'm not going
to lie four of them yeah hey somebody
didn't take their diamond armor is it on
purpose cuz they don't want to lose it
need or did I make too many maybe you
made an extra set no I'm was wearing it
Kelly are you wearing it too I'm mine
damn where where did that come from
maybe somebody was already
wearing y
okay not yet though can I have this
Banner ominous Banner
do it do it I want
it yo can you summon pillagers one
block don't think so arrows
arrows sugar
[Music]
egg need empty
space yes one next to it one immediately
next to it is what I've
learned this what do you mean it
doesn't I don't
get need help
no oh you can't use this one okay a
little more
guys where's all the paper did you take
it in my mouth I don't take
[Music]
it she ate her homework I'm going to
force your mouth open there's still 61
paper in the shulker Box 61 in the
Shuler did you read all our Diaries
Kiara I've been reading them at least
from the ones who wrote something oh I
forgot about
no yeah star you definitely get a star
you and cie get a
star see I got
Ser oh I
did you always start riding the moment
you talk about
the like doing your homework before
class starts yeah literally while the
teacher is collecting the
homework
incredible who wanted to farm you don't
have to ride it now the day didn't even
end yet oh does anybody have any wool
there should be be the sheep sheep
yeah huh 29 wool is in there you can cut
some here in the back on the way to the
iron farm on the way to the iron farm
the first floor the diamond sword oh
here who wants to see I'm done I'm done
thank you it's in it's in the box right
here give it to me oh okay
after me okay I'll cut some more so
thank
you problem I'm so sorry Mr sheep I'm so
sorry yeah it's right I get a gold Hest
way such music why is there a polar bear
in here that seems counter she's a sheep
oh don't you see the name
oh pump pumpkin cat grow like
this learning from scratch
yeah Unbreaking three get back up to 30
I wanted the sword to have ooh sharpness
I'm going to make a new iron sword we
have enough iron for an iron sword
right yeah maybe oh actually we could
more am I
just is that what it is there's four
iron here left over but we should
probably try and find more so everyone
can get an iron
sword I don't need one I have my diamond
sword no but uh I
mean tiny HP box for this it's only two
iron I was
surprised H maybe if we get lucky we get
another diamond block from mining the
one block a little while ooh
true we do get lucky so get lucky every
once in a while this one can't
grow see we actually well maybe we still
have some more diamonds do we we might
have enough for a diamond sword I think
cuz yeah I think a diamond and three
Diamonds oh you do okay then if you
don't need it we can make swords some
more swords for everybody who needs one
yeah I could use a
[Music]
sword I don't need one so ga needs one
right GA what do I need do we need a
diamond sword oh I would love one if you
would trust me with suchit so probably
make make four iron Whoever has diamonds
they're in the chest in the chest okay
now we
wait yeah I Saw Three diamond what good
I maybe you noticed I don't know if you
noticed but I think I did this off
stream when you weren't around do you
did you see in your Atlantis gate did
you see the bail that we previously
talked about it has now been
added it costed me 32 emeralds
oh you got to remove the red block
though wait you have a bell
yeah dog ding dog oh we
have SLI sword for uh XP stuff I have it
right
now I need five yeah I need five more
levels okay ding dong just tell me when
you're dead Okay sorry I had to show up
off the Bell sharpness three bing bong
bing bong ooh and Unbreaking three
sharpness 3 knock back to looting three
good good good good I made a a
pill the banner it looks like the can I
change
that you can change stuff on medication
banner I don't like it hyp Hye hype what
banner I made a guides can spell stuff
make like a certain shape like a cookie
oh are you are you trying to make your
shield look nice no you can on the
shield what are you making it for if
it's not for the
shield for
me
fun yeah you ever heard of fun before it
for your sh fun yeah what is
fun F is for friends who do stuff
together
you that's SpongeBob right is this
another SpongeBob reference in the myth
Minecraft
stream is not allowed why I got an
idea no
fun
IDE uh
secret
H I think I know what your idea is
impossible you cannot I guess are you
making five different shield banners all
in our
Colors oh no wait my PC lagged that's
not wait is that actually what you're
making no
no no
okay that would be cool though
Dam no oh hello fishy time to
die okay I'm almost done
what dang
[Music]
it oh
there's you can't mine gold ore with the
stone pickaxe it just disappears I know
I just wanted to get rid of the block at
that
[Music]
point yes four more ir and we're going
to show that Ender Dragon his boss oh
I'm so excited should I change the
difficulty to hard
no I could us having more diamonds than
iron is hilarious to me yeah we're so
it's the iron draw that's why we made
the iron farm and I'm telling you it
worked for a while and helped me with uh
raising my villagers who then despawned
so I CED purp yeah it had
purpose oh okay I'm level
30 SP wi they said
be it will not be fun yeah I'm done
who's done I'm done she needs my sword I
need some XP to finish something enjoy
thank
you wait are you sure I'm not going to
blow up it's not going to blow up I'm
going trust your own work trust it you
made it so perfectly you be
good it couldn't be any better than
that by the way for food I have a a lot
of fried chicken and and uh grilled
grilled 43 cooked chicken that's kind of
excessive don't you think oh there's I
think there's even more in the chest at
the ne I made another chest there so
there should be
plenty and of course golden apples as
yes what
punch should you grab your golden app
the gold gives you extra
Hearts what extra
Hearts
hey it also it just also has punch oh oh
yeah
arrows okay stick Flint okay that much
Flint yeah Flint is really little but we
have I have a lot of bows uh they should
all be in in the in the weapon chest oh
wait where did they go we have them
somewh I have like 31 arrows I I think
31 oh wait I have them I have a lot of
arrows if I'm going to put the arrows
into
the chest around the
portal uh the nether
portal NE p is it never or never you say
never is it never or never well I say
never because I cannot pronounce
th she has a
Liz spe imped
[Music]
no not true no
no that's just how austrians and Germans
pronounce
it okay I'm actually actually actually
often they would just actually no the
really strong German accents they would
just replace the th with an s
yeah the zza is very danger danger
Dangerous uh no wait that's partially
Japanese accents I think but yeah s
s cooler okay
okay uh okay at least I don't talk like
that s s is uh quite uh so uh what's
what's another word with th to describe
the never
ah
if
Thursday okay on on S on Thursday we go
TOA together but
[Music]
it's uh no threatening do work because
threatening they no they wouldn't say
threatening they would say threatening
with f yeah I want heavy German accent C
to beat me up I don't know
[Laughter]
why uh what does this flag mean
G uh what the [\h__\h] are you are you
taunting me yeah I was thinking so
because just the other day I watched the
Poland Austria match but I won so I
don't know this cannot bait me or or
taunt me yeah do make me angry a
reminder of my win's coming back for
you I think they're out it's not the
last okay next year they're coming back
for you oh we'll see about that
eventually Poland will have their
renge that's not Poland what do you mean
what it just needs to be
wider wait or is it Chad said it's it's
the wrong way yeah it's the other way
around this way is
Indonesia oh ID let's go
ID show some support for ID that's fine
we love ID go I love ID I got a quick
question what's the difference between
enchanted golden apple and regular
Golden Apple oh one enant no idea no
does nobody know you got to test it out
Kelly once we're in Google best friend
a come on guys golden apple one is
Enchanted Enchanted is far better okay
can I enchant all the golden apples with
lapis
lazuli oh you could we have so many
lapis La I'm sorry feel free to use it
cool I'm going to enchant all these
apples Che out the
loot no you can't it gives you extra the
power power one Unbreaking B you need
gold blocks to I can't enchant gold
combine some of these bows to like get
fully
and I could use Unbreaking one that
would be
good repair it though but you can just
combine the normal bows to make like a
yeah I have an enchanted B already so I
I can combine it but what's the max
enchant enchantments like five or uh
three I think free for for a bow it's
free I think yeah shoot power
five okay so got lot
gunpowder I I already used a lot of it
IR are you making TNT I'm the demo man
oh devil man we're so going to destroy
this Dragon that's my plan I was going
to I was going to surprise you guys a
okay I will be surprised I have to stay
alive until the very
end I did not hear what you just said I
am here for the bows
M the bow okay so personally I feel like
I'm fully prepared I have fully uh
Enchanted armor part no not fully demo
man I thought she said devil manly sh
sorry the Devil Man theme and everything
exp the world I borrow the sword oh yeah
you go at the end when you're done with
it it goes back to the
WWA okay I'm the waha by the way
no that sounds good you don't sound like
Wawa
Gua
Goa that's that's is that's is not good
that's is not good that's is
[\h__\h] close
enough I'm surprised you came up with
that
much how are these chickens laying eggs
outside of their little Zone this is for
Bri
they are going too
far they need to be told where their
place is
M yes yes oh I put four enchantments on
my bow I guess you can do that
sheesh four wait can I put another one
chat does that
work does that even
work you know what actually hold on I
almost I have enough experience hold on
that I can get I can make another I can
enchant my other bow and maybe get a
better enchantment doesn't
work how did you get four I don't know I
just when you enchant One Flame power
punch and breaking nice flame Power
Punch I think like once you enchant
something once like you have a chance to
get other enchantments on the same thing
I remember
anyways
stretch all right could Anvil
it it's okay I think we it's it's
already Overkill everything is already
Overkill so Chad wait Chad says combine
it on the books but I didn't do that I
just went one by one with like four
books at the Anvil ah I you the
enchantment table Yeah I you that the
enchantment table
yeah oh ah oo ah o
ah ah ah
I'm ready me too 20 gifts thank you so
much yeah g is really committed to the
blocks they wear the golden apples yes
extraordinary H they're around the
although Call's working on them I
think fixing them hold on self-restraint
that's the word I was looking
for you don't feel the urge to mine you
don't year for the minds at all girl not
even a little number
you can't even see it
yourself no when I hit tab I see
okay
[Music]
oh I suppose how is everybody
in K's got like sixk oh my Lord Kar put
in not the p no that's the blocks that I
mind I I I I played a lot off screen a
little thought it was the Ping too in
the beginning especially
when super big and ours were all super
small 6K
ping oh thank God it's not it's like an
entire six seconds behind her is it
she she's living in the past oh no God
no thankfully it's not
that you're sure who's uh still
preparing and what are you preparing
person who's still preparing I don't
need to enchant
preparing I'm just getting levels to
enchant some stuff I guess okay we can
prepare the the portal cuz we need to
like if someone dies like to get back
easily so we can kind of make it like
look nicer like put a stairs down you
want to make the the the yeah okay okay
you want to go in already no I'm just
saying like prepare it so that uh you
mean on the prepared in someone dies
yeah on this side on this side on our
side okay yeah you do it like a chest
maybe for the
okay yeah but it's directly under the
one block so I kind of have to destroy
this construction I suppose I think it's
bigger
than so you could make it like off to
the side a little bit like right here
probably okay maybe from
below here let me
check like right here would this is fine
like we would be able to get almost fell
down H yeah I'll make that a little bit
bigger down there
scary scary scary scary
scary
scary should probably get the blocks out
of
here wait do I leave blocks
underneath guess it doesn't
matter
um good what are you doing waiting for
my turn at the PPP PE can you get me
some ha blocks there is a
line thank
you wait I got to go threaten the guy
that was in front of me what I'm coming
back me I'm stuck behind me I'm coming
back from my spot I'm coming back from
my spot what did I
do I given it to you but now it's going
to be a blood bath I'm going to guard
your spot for me I was going to put
stairs here to make it easier a wait
what do you need I'm here now uh um slab
or stair I got slab for
you how many slab me got you some slab
on me right
you uh I'm
waiting how do you make a slab wait how
many do you need you're going to get
this
ready yeah six is fine that's like the
default
number oh my God wait what wait what
okay where are you green light right
ohello you dried it out you
know Green Light wait wait waited
light did you get them now I only got
one I think there's too many spiders up
there it's over here that's stuck in the
water wait look how behind you toilet is
clogged again toilet clogged dang it you
know you clogged
it wasn't me okay there we go now we can
get up and down easily I think I guess I
have to get rid of one of these blocks
oh yeah now we can jump in it's not
night time we can't
sleep I love that that's fine we'll
[Music]
wait surely Sun's going down looks like
it's kind of about to go down yeah Sun
is setting yeah it means we can maybe
sleep and then get rid of the
spiders guess this
works I'm making the area a little bit
safery reapy at least I'm not falling
asleep I'm
here so hopefully maybe um I'm going to
give you girls a a time limit in 30
minutes y'all y'all by the latest shall
be ready y I'm ready okay it's just
extra would be nice honestly I can go
now I don't really need I just want to
make arrows
you go get out of the way I me hi I
need I I gave you the sword what please
responded I it after me oh oh wait I
thought okay I don't get to keep it it
was not a gift
a thank you think we should set up an
emergency chest oh all don't know what
you're doing I was just putting stairs
there uh yeah yeah you can put them
there actually do do put them there
[Music]
my
pumpkin
[Music]
P okay perfect
nice
nice going make it a bit more
visible yeah damn okay and
40 arrows probably going to be
sufficient um there's more arrows in in
the chest where the armor was if you
guys need more okay I was just making
more uh gravel whatever
flint rocks to e yeah next to have on
the
trip Kelly have you been enchanting the
apples have I've been what have you been
enchanting the apples you can't they're
not craftable no you can only have
regular gold we have two Enchanted that
we just found luckily so two people can
grab
those nice I didn't to alarm anybody but
I think something just pushed me is a
server
H what something pushed you maybe it was
maybe was maybe it was one of us fear I
don't over here wait where are
you mmm
let
[Music]
me let me
see I will I will observe you think
something pushed you something pushed me
are you
sure yeah I standing here and then all
of a sudden I was over here I saw I'd
move I
did don't look at me like that that's
probably just like an was there an enemy
in front of you yeah yeah yeah probably
just like him kind of pushing you to the
side
between but this is how all ghost
stories
start I don't believe that's not
believeing you have to believe
me okay I believe you but show me again
what should we do about it just make it
happen I don't know oh they're behind
you nice I don't I don't know Callie
what I'll tell you if it happens again
she's crazy right she's crazy I don't
know like I said this is how all ghost
stories
start you know okay so if there really
it just happened again were you looking
I wasn't looking I was hold on I'm sure
we got the footage somebody can go back
to tape I'm I'm sure it's just like just
a mob kind of pushing you easily a
little bit you're lightweight so you
know it
happens
okay
happens shimmy
collect oh you got that at least the the
EXP Farm's working now yeah I just need
three more levels and then it'll be 30
and I'm like might as well enchant this
bow as a Backup backup
bow yeah we'll put it in the backup
chest oh maybe somebody doesn't have a
propa bow yet then they could use it we
can give it to them who needs a propa
bow I just have a power three bow I
think you passed your yawn to me I'm
going to punch you for that sorry about
that can't be helped
you need a proper bow I'm working on it
oh okay so that's what you're currently
on okay okay okay
yeah
[Music]
yeah nothing spawning again huh should
we sleep through
it
maybe yeah time sleep is always
nice let me quickly for my study
rearrange the beds though okay
[Music]
not wait I didn't get all of the beds
boy give me the beds I need to do my
science stud so close oh oh who who took
the beds not
me me it's the
ghost no all right all right um
um today's
Arrangement will
be enchant iron sword is back of Sword
hello chicken can you get off the
enchanting table
help
there yes okay ready hey where'd you go
I'm coming I was making a backup sword
you taking too
long potion it's
science wait what kind science wait a
okay she's sleeping in the sounds like
sounds like a lot of science to
me in their natural habitat the myth
members seem to be attracted to their
own image colored bed naturally I'm
trying to sleep here shut up thisch
well we can't sleep as long as the other
members are not coming to bed [\h__\h] I'm
ring my journal give me like oh my diary
you're R already oh she's so excited to
ride in her
diary my god
oh all right come on come on I'm coming
I'm sorry Rush section here oh
wo oh wo can we just make her say
anything or right in the
chat set I like this
TTS I am your
TTS Tex to speech go go to
shating that was good damn you nailed it
first try holy [\h__\h]
wow wa damn girl now Amy is the
TTS I don't think so that was good that
made me
happy wait what's it mean uh uh
um uh not greetings ladies and gentlemen
but in a very I would say Austrian
way
gratifications
greetings wait I'm going
andaran CU gr Scot is quite the Bavarian
and auan way to greet uh grot yeah you
don't hear that in North
Germany I say that when I want to greet
someone politely I say go hey you snooze
you lose you snooze you lose
gar
Gar put something on my
side I mean while we're still waiting
yeah I just need two more levels and
then we'll be good to go but how about
we make that that uh extra ration chest
or that for example if somebody dies
passes away we should have a chance by
the portal okay I'll move it over cuz
there is already some extra rations
rations and I have like a couple weapons
like I'm enchanting that can be backup
weapons backup we I don't know about if
we'll even die we have the totems we
have we have so much stuff I'll move
everything over Kelly can you move the
the pearls yeah it's okay now I have a
very sturdy sword what are these do the
sty sword that's all I mean teleport oh
yeah that that's that's what I meant the
is ofender what do they do and we need
to put them into the uh the empty Slots
of the
portal and then it will open it up no we
already have everything oh it's already
in there oh is that what the sound no no
it's not in there but uh it was already
prepped and now we're moving it over
here no don't don't put it in yet though
okay I'm getting free XP let's put in
going B my XP vacuum get out of hereit
is that the
scrap um
where's where is it pardic Tendencies
that's the
stress that's the stress can we yeah I'm
down here I made chest for Stuff damn it
okay I'm under the top okay I don't know
how to get back up there's stairs on the
side
oh I promise guys I promise I'm not
stupid
you I got I thought losing my
mind I got to charge my bow you can jump
up here and then you can get up here but
yeah it's it's kind of weird nice
Minecraft not your fault okay is this
the chest maybe we can put all related
end the dragon fight things can go in
here I got a free level guys I got free
two levels me to me
too I would have been 30 by now you know
what I want free levels What If
no free
levels I want free levels an extra
food yes so if you die you can just take
some stuff out of
here I think that's enough
oh okay looking
fancy okay all I need is my sword and
then I'm ready to
go I'm just waiting for to finish
leveling slow yeah I well I would have
had four extra levels and two people
didn't no that's not how it
works oh no they
didn't which kfb someone just called me
a hag in your
chat what the hell I'm gonna freak out
in a sec oh I'm GNA freak out
how what level are you now
good it could be a compliment though
depending on you think about it how you
think about it it could be I feel like
that's only supposed to be used for like
really old
L times are changing guess is in my day
9,000 over
9,000 will I reach the big
10K you dead no what will I why am I
dying
better not blow anything up now would I
do
that yes yeah no where is my
donkey
wa donkey I'm almost done I
promise I just moved again oh did you
see that you were watching you must have
seen that oh I'm sure the Clippers will
get it wait to ban no wait it is it is I
it's oh my God
what was
it it's the
ghost the ghost I just realized this
won't really work cuz I think G has my
stream
open oh it's cuz kar's she used the oh I
saw her footsteps
okay wait what it was me all along goba
wait what how I'm invisible what I
thought it was losing my mind
I'm going to cry I took the exper well I
will I will give you the I will why am I
flying why am I flying why am I why am I
flying what the [\h__\h] I feel like I'm
flying wait I'm not flying I'm just I'm
the wrong p uh uh don't at the spiral
she's right here I'm blocking her oh I
see was it you from the beginning even
from the start of the ghost story so no
I was standing next to you when she said
she was moving call you guys done oh
true I'm done so it wasn't
oh wait you need this you lose
stinker lose Watson that's car sword
yeah give me I need my my waa sword back
let get one more level thanks I'm hungry
for levels I can't I can't help but how
much do you need still you need it for
anything I'm at 28 I was going to make
an extra weapon if I had the invisible
potion I could have sit by her and got
some
free I want to E SP in
there you're making me feel like I'm
crazy exterminate the spiders I saw
Bubbles and I thought I actually had a
ghost or some kind of I don't know curse
curse on
me spooky I being chased by ghost let me
get one more level and then I'll leave
forever such a chicken are you no slip
up my let's finish
Outlast out oh slurper be slurper I'm
almost there I'm I'm not the same person
I used to be okay I got some CR I'm not
as Brave anymore huh I'm more Brave oh
really prove it defeat the Ender Dragon
alone what don't take the Ender Dragon
alone no you can take him prove your
bravery there's still a few potions
there's a luck potion a strength potion
and an instant health potion I think
luck is maybe unnecessary but you can
have it Watson thank you yeah you're
welcome I'm putting it in here
too yeah so we're looking
beautiful beautifully
prepared shall we go soon yes I'm ready
just making a cool bow to put in the
chest okay oo enchanter
ooh on Shante a Shante
flame
one remember you were saying some name
and then people thought that was name of
new member and you like leaked something
but you didn't what was it was it like
Mary or so in the last uh Minecraft
stream uh maybe I don't remember what I
said what what did I say Mary mhm our
new member Mary okay yeah yeah when they
when they knew that we had new members
coming but I think the names weren't
known yet they were like oh gooa gooa
surely that was one of the names right
Mary are you kidding me I got she
wouldn't slip up like that I'm I'm I'm
rock hard when it comes even if Weck
down it happened it could happen nah I
would cry if I accidentally leaked a
name or so of them makes me so nervous
I'm made of iron iron nothing comes in
and nothing comes out wait no everything
can come in but it won't come out a are
you
constipated no I meant with
words my Lord
[Laughter]
you you know what I mean
I
mean we all have problems that we
struggle
with
sometimes sometimes it's something like
that it's okay it's okay we we share and
we
care we share care all
right distant Kelly hell
yeah now the more you're going to make
me wait the more cursed things I'll say
I'm ready to go I'm sitting by the
Creeper face and I'm
waiting okay am I ready too no no okay
just enchanting something okay
enchant oh wait are we going to do the
thing we're doing it like now now what
the murder of the Dragon yeah yeah okay
I'm going to take a pee break I'll be
right back okay
[Music]
byebye ooh
what she looking at not what she looking
at the beautiful
flag I got sorry
you get down here spider all right I
guess I'm ready now why you looking at
girl can't believe she never stopped
after to
999 this
[Music]
girl I mean I believe it we can have oh
we have a we have a high score right now
so the lowest now is gooda she wasn't
always the lowest though and uh the
second lowest is CI but hey we worked
hard on a lot of stuff in terms of
blocks the
lowest and then there's Ena and then I'm
a really close what is it the block the
amount of blocks lud has like 1,000 well
999 CI has
1,600 then uh second is no third is Ena
with
2,600 and then am is second with 2,700
and I am he first with a whopping
6,800 the pack just the way I like it
oops middle of the path my sou
[Music]
no
um n what is wrong you need
something um we can help you K what oh
no I'm
innocent no I said cany not oh Callie
yeah yeah cool cuz I wasn't call just
making sure to establish her innocence
in any case a
true are there any extra
totems uh there's only those four I
think okay feel free to take one I don't
know I think I think everybody already
got one
I oh let me check the way there chest
wait
what took all the
totems nuh I just got
here check inventory empty your pockets
no you can't make
me this is a search do not resist I'm
resisting you know I'll be able to see
your inventory if you
die everything you wood it you're W I
don't I'm having no fighting use your
directions against the Ender Dragon I
don't want that you empty your pocket
junk it's not junk it's my inventory
it's my inventory
okay so who wants a totem who wants a
totem you wait maybe not me take it take
it take those totems one per person one
person will not have it I'll I'll I'll
be the one who doesn't have one oh yeah
K di I'll take this one wait should I
have it know I think you won die you
could you can car kill I don't think I
would no it's okay I have some apples so
wait so do the regular golden apples do
anything they give you extra
heartt yeah they're good for you
okay yeah the chest is full down below
is why there's a lot of
items what chest um just at the at the
mm oh
oh I think we don't need it anymore wait
somebody said that povs streamers only
should have the uh totems what do we
think about
that that is part of my
plan oh you can m i
people my
album oh streamer is in you right
now but here take this Enchanted Apple
cuz it's take this pretty good
apparently well cuz if I die nobody's
like missing out on anything but if K
dies then what but make sure to take a
shield and have full armor maybe you can
also take a you can take an instant
health potion out of the chest Shield if
you can't I'll hold a
shield potion of instant Health
healing I got Splash too
so you'll be okay take what you need
look iron bar oh I'll take
meat Kelly you got everything too ready
to go I got to empty my pockets I guess
I'll open it up then wait wait I'm not
there yet I was ready I'm not ready I'm
scared it's kind of hard hard to see it
uh oh well maybe we need to get rid of
those blocks there there blocks in the
middle is that bad oh there should be
more arrows I think like this should
work Arrow uh oh wait uh I put away my
tools can someone get rid of the these
blocks
on the red one pink one pink one and the
those be careful with the slabs at the
bottom cuz
those open up don't don't don't open
where I'm standing
okay I got the pink one what else the
block the wood uh the the wooden one
okay I got 15 shots I'll just make sure
they're good water bucket what why water
bucket you get blasted off into the
Aira oh yeah does anyone want slow
falling potion I have two extra I it's
okay yeah that's good Kelly thank you
can I what no wait streamers should get
what oh I have water bucket I'm fine
can I have the potion yeah I'll have one
so thank
you we're so overprepared probably no
this is
excellent thank you H it's just when
like you need to you know save your fall
oh or no for the Ender drag ender men if
you look at the Endermen they all follow
you but if you have water around you
then they can't touch you oh nice I'm
scared of water just don't look at don't
look in don't look in their eyes don't
easy easy easy okay I should have made
them all three oh W somebody scared of
water so shall I put the Eyes
in last
okay I don't it's okay we're fine we're
fine on road oh we should bring some
blocks building blocks I have a bunch I
have 64 two stacks and and somebody I
would say either you know or arm once
we're in should build a safe platform
please okay please pleas maybea cuz
she's
streaming okay uh can I have a donation
a generous donation of
cobblestone you might have to go with
other stes St here I have very pretty uh
terra cotta oh I'm
nervous if we nervous we fine we can do
this nous
okay I'm going to I'm going to put the
Eyes in I'm going to put them in we've
done this before haven't we guys yeah we
have done it before didn't
we didn't we it'll be fine it's going to
be okay I feel like we're even more
prepared than back then possibly eyes
yes finding it was harder last
time you e the Apple I'm doing it I the
Apple
oh yeah yeah take take your apples take
your things I have one apple harvested
them special for you oh wait where is it
by the portal are you supposed to take
one take five ah there's
five
okay wait call made many many golden
apples yeah the enchanted ones are
special that's special loot that we
found oh wait I took one of those is
that okay the uh probably fine or should
I take take the I'll take five
raler do you want to see the moment
girls using the flame wa wait wait wait
wait I'm not ready hold on flamethrower
you can give me like two minutes or
something
just
[Music]
okay where's the
Anvil H at the other boxes section here
ah P yeah kfp says get out of the ring
before you put in the last one okay
I'm already out I'm already out can you
imagine if she wasn't though that would
be a pretty silly
prank silly
no I'm
scared what's the button again to
quickly put something in your right hand
do you guys know or does chat know oh
the Qui F Buton F yeah I thought oh oh
it is actually F girl wow you did not
lie to me
mhm she wasn't paying respect to
you all right sorry I'm almost ready I'm
almost done what are you doing nothing
what are you doing surprise surprise I
have a surprise too what's your surprise
uh don't worry about it
oh
okay I'll tell you mine if you tell me
yours wait does it involve me
dying I can't die at the end that really
my surprise what's your
surprise nothing okay we will all stay
alive yeah no deaths right no death run
the question was for you right no no
death
runs demo man all right okay I'm ready
saying I just didn't enter them oops no
death
allowed my
feelings no walk off into the sunset
only one death is allowed that's me
okay I'm hype I'm I'm ready to put the
eyeon I'm
ready magical moment ready here we go n
second try at the end of dragon
sparkly scared somebody else go first
yeah Ena Go please and make a platform
your I slipped
no you the
Apple okay how does it look bring some
uh Whatchamacallit blocks
uh not blocks it's
uh
torches oh you I have
22 okay
know we need
torches
Health okay is it safe to go in N hold
on give me a second I'm just making sure
it's we
water go go go my go
go Au we have water we got a bucket with
water got my buckets okay W my bucket in
me is already o that was beautiful yes
you can you can come in I'm
[Music]
building ho I have a no glitch please no
glitch okay oh
nice
W I see AA wait what did I was my water
the dragon scary
already there's
yeah oh God oh God oh God is it okay to
put wait good you over there I'm sorry I
lagged out for a second I'm don't come
yet wait okay can you bring ladders can
you make ladders really quick for me I
have 20 how many do you need 40 oh okay
no actually 20 should be okay that
should be good if we go there going to
attack already wait wait wait wait let
me
just oh boy I can I can make more don't
die don't die stop stop stop stop I have
32 no no
no okay we over prepared what happened
girl go girls girls good girls come come
let's fight I feel like it's starting
because he already
shot where's all my stuff still wait Who
removed the ceiling oh no oh no oh no no
no no
no I'm not wa to go in there then we all
wait what we need to do wait wait for it
to go away wait for it to go away my
stuff I'm guessing wait your stuff is
probably going to lie there for a while
don't worry it's going away it's going
away wait now you can come okay and it's
all like all your loot all your stuff is
in one place so you'll have to like
split it again the back corner all right
spawn camping turn it back to
easy yeah yeah get your things again and
then tell me what belong to I think I
lost all my stuff with all my potions
easy I I have all the potions here how
did you how did you lose
it it's still there right
it's all there I think that's mine
here's a bed this is also yours all
there and then this is yours don't wor
and then a bucket of water for you a
bu what happened to the ceiling oh boy
uh beet not mine it's not yours I don't
know whose that is then what potion of
slow falling who's that belong to wait I
I did see off the falling or the ceiling
right it was not enough I guess or I
don't know we F I got it should I come
in yeah yeah you can come you can come
okay ceiling is too
low it's okay we're going to go in like
oh wa WIP the H okay time to go time to
go time to go guys get out of that spicy
stuff
no oh boy that's bad that's
bad well I no golden apples though all
the golden apples are gone I'm
lagging just just uh everybody keep on
running and
uh I didn't know it gets removed when
people spot in that's but I'll I'll tell
you Ena when it's safe to come back in
I'll tell you I have it in my eye okay
it's disappearing you can come in now
okay why are there so many
Ender you've seen this before GAA I
don't remember turned the difficulty up
to 11 stay safe ga stuff CL I have I
have your potions I think I have no
weapons and nothing I got 15 I have
everything hey good thing I made some
extra
weapons oh thank
youed oh here and does anyone have my
armor and
stuff uh all I had was that ah he's
coming
yumy
y I'm playing go oh I could use a bow
oh there he is I see him should we kill
him okay let's kill him let's goess I'm
to support this
R oh boy what what what are you missing
Ena uh no extra armor
sets where they go does anybody have it
in their inventory mm- I just have this
and what I'm wearing wait I have armor
for some reason you have extra armor
yeah oh give it to give it TOA oh my God
I have uh 12 golden apples I must have
taken your stuff I think you took golden
apples oh wait I have it come take I'm
so scared right now okay no need to be
afraid I'm going to come grab them
you there's a lot of TNT everywhere what
the where what are the Enderman doing on
I'm putting TNT so that when the dragon
flies close you guys can't shoot it oh
SM okay um sorry I'm yelling I don't
know if it's high enough though that's
why I wanted ladders so I could get
higher he hates me does does good did
you give the the equipment to Ena no I
don't know where is right I'm in the
middle of the stage kind of oh he
doesn't care he still hates me can we
like I don't want to start this too much
without Ena being equipped wait wait
wait can
you I have your pants he's following you
should I kill him kill him kill him yeah
kill him kill him here here I ha you
away here off thank
you okay you gone
all right now they're all they all hate
me a lot okay die let's go guys let's go
okay let me make
him him pay maybe I drank that too
early you guys didn't see what I did to
your buddy right okay we're good I was
kill where that came from buddy boy oh
you want your apples yeah thanks y that
shot good time how do I split a St uh
it's a left click I think right click
right click thank no
no all right let's go kill him get
him this was a bit
anticlimactic no I don't know what you
mean fighting him now
get he
go get him we need all of them right do
we off to some of them cuz there's m M I
don't have enough blocks to climb up on
anything me neither wait you here take I
have your
pants ow come
on can you not shoot
in
my I'm going to
die it's all right you're
good which one it's only there's one
something attacking me um can can we
just shoot at the dragon instead and
like Arro
him I'm shooting at
him my aim is not great shoot at him
shoot shoot atam I'm shooting at him try
okay I'm really trying to
where wa so far have done no damage on
him he really but I hit him several
times
we're
[Music]
missing dragon's getting healed I see
yeah oh we got to maybe someone got to
go we need can we go back someone needs
to die yeah we need blocks I have 6
block I have a pickaxe I can mine for
blocks mine some blocks if you can I
have and then go around to the cages I
think the others are you just need to be
destroyed uhoh I just a pickax on them
yeah he's Landing get him I don't think
it matters cuz we have to get the cages
first yeah he's going to get
healed I missed there is one that's like
slow falling
Hallelujah are they going for me don't
go for me ah ah ah ah why are they
screaming oh they dying and they were
destroying their lord
up to one cage I can go up to one too
okay go go go and when you go down you
can mine the blocks back and then you
can go to the next one I can also go up
go go go go go get those cages I'll go
up too if you can taking my
potion try to Dragon away from the
whoever's climbing I'm climbing now me
too I'm also climbing should I not
climbing yeah you should you should go
yeah
okay use a pickax wait what do I do this
thing do I like destroy it or
something I got I got one I got
one got
one one which one oh was that not was
that already
empty uh it was just it was a Bedrock oh
okay Dragon came back it'll be
fine there a lot of end I could fly up
to one of these it gets done one oh
there's a really tall one that's still I
saw it while I was
flying there's one he's tether to right
now that uh it's so high yeah can we
climb there or no yeah I mean we should
be able to shoot but it's so high if
somebody gives me their blocks their
Stacks they have them I can do it I'll
give it to you Watson 45 right now I
have 26 got 59 here you go Watson
oh there you
[Music]
go please don't shoot me please don't
shoot
me oh
oh we're having a party there they love
you a they really like me oh what are we
going to do about this they're so tall
I'm distracting them okay St to me it's
so sparkly all right I got it are they
all arrowing you you got I think they're
all gone okay well good when you walk
away are they going to kill you yep okay
put
no how do you unagro them a
murder kill them all I'm okay
very Pur Weir yeah sh be
uhoh he's taking the TNT though I don't
know come
on no no be why do the end hate us so
much why
yeah we have plenty of pumpkins can I
survive a fall
anyway there's no more bucket he's hting
is he no come down he's coming down he's
coming down get him why do how how do I
much how does he manage to always make
me fine I'm not hitting him I I this is
this is not as easy as I thought pleas I
think we're over prepared I was like are
you sure he's going to all
going
go maybe it's worth dying once I can
pick up your items no you're having your
own little battle
here you're his own internal battles
wait I got could use some of these
pearls
here need more block I don't think we
need block
[Applause]
anymore is this inevitable oh boy
is this working we don't have that many
building blocks you guys build up by the
pillars and uh end can't see me here
where'd he go come here
end
[Music]
end I don't have iron for iron
bucket I think we should have an iron
bucket somewhere in the base uh in one
of the chests like where the diamonds
are wait pause guys I got to take
SW we can't PA this go no no know the
end sorry I'm talking to the end boys I
know it's a joke anyway but okay you
can't just pause this all right I'm
ready oh that's 12 gold probably don't e
that I us put my sword on the
enemy is is your sword dead um time to
hit it with your
fists or make make some make the TNT
explode why am I why am I being the
Archer
okay CLA more I got a couple hits on him
a couple only a couple though am I down
Dragon oh there's
water I'm brave I'm brave I'm brave I'm
brave I'm brave I'm brave I'm brave oh
you're the bravest oh [\h__\h] oh
no I'm alive I'm alive I'm alive that
seems bad no die is there water do you
guys have water no I don't have
water I have
oh [\h__\h] what's with the aim today aim
not very good for me either but that's
kind of I feel like they're not
connecting oh he's coming
down
nice yeah beat him up
sorry get him in the
butthole what why does it not work why
did the pearls not work why did the pear
D I thought you can teleport when you're
flying and and bring yourself back to
the ground oh you can if you like hit
the ender pearl if the ender pearl hits
the ground before you do then yeah oh
okay ni come
on
this do this it's the thing it didn't
hit in time I I threw it right away okay
he's there Landing Landing there is no
iron for the [\h__\h] him [\h__\h] C him I
can't reach him arrows pretty soon here
oh no we're good we're good am I
actually not reaching him am I too
small st next time he you thank you
thank
you I'm not trying to look
you oh
boy there it is
get down here I'm back young man get
down this instant nice shot somebody
just got him thank
you good job dead ey
dead this Enderman wants to beat me
up they all want to be are you still
being you're still there I see you from
afar bul I'm
helping in my own way you're going to be
the reason that Endermen are going to go
extinct that's that's Miss yeah ah
ah ah oh no he's he's ping me get him
guys get
him I'll be with you in a moment we're
getting closer okay he's kind of low
he's less than yeah
yeah he's
freaking leave me
alone why haven't I used Dead Eye yet
yeah we should have given good a pumpkin
helmet we had some in our
base missing all my shots
I mean every time the dragon is going up
I have different entertainment by
looking at
ga oh my God all my hits are going
through these guys this is okay uhoh
close
well night Comet night Comet coming
right up I have night
Comet I don't don't have ar oh wait I
have four oh where' they come from I
have arrows if your shs your thing is
better nice the come
on oh almost there he he
coming coming
here I'm going to help
now now yay come
[Music]
on there you go
I
got we did it now he
a now we can watch the
credits again y yay oh the egg egg the
egg wait let's take a picture first yes
yes a
together where uh can we make stairs so
like a platform there she goes there she
goes yeah I didn't use the totem but I
used all the
apples y oh my my I was here too this
was such a weird fight it was strange di
had time is good free oh there she is
hello how how have you ended the cycle
of what that was how did it end kill
them
all cuz it it seemed like the more you
kill the more you
aggro they just wouldn't leave you I
see um I'm sure Kiara feels really
included I feel so
included I mean if if I just look at if
I just look at one snippet of it then it
is the Austrian flag true hey you have
red and white in there yeah red white
red some part of that is
me yeah let's go
nice okay exra time let's all gather and
uh take photo oh we don't I mean okay
the fl's funny I'm going to hold a
golden apple cuz that was my job am you
are barely
visible okay wait what's a fireworks
star I I made one but I didn't know you
had to combine it with fireworks you
want it no I I I'll make it when we get
back you have to combine it with like a
firework girls take off your armor oh oh
true guess we don't need it anymore cute
this is how we die y I'll take that get
my shield cheese wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wa away what are you
throwing away uh stuff okay look cute
like you always
do oh
girl no you
f I'm okay the flag is there in my Steed
it's okay I took a picture of that
pictures okay yeah it it was a good one
are you dead no no I'm back in my
ho such a we got to go watch the credits
together
girl okayy give me a sec let me
uh let me boys
please go fight them go fight them my
sword's going to die wait why are they
not attacking you because I didn't
attack them and I didn't look at
them shoot super I want to help you but
um it's nice to see you fulfilling the
side quest alone I I okay all I got is a
wooden hoe now the are we now this
beautiful take my
sword
it's oh thanks bir all go hi call oh you
know no you know of the Void look up
into the sky with me
doesn't do remind you Cosmos Elden ring
elen ring I'm thinking about Elden ring
again I'm not playing just like
Minecraft I was watching you fight aelle
for a while it's almost safe I think
it's number two it's not safe okay I'm
not even looking at him anymore it's
safe it's not safe it's not safe it's
not safe it's not safe okay it's
safe let's
go let's watch
credits we going yeah I guess so I think
I took good picture together together oh
oh trying to kill us all I'm just trying
to blow us
up no no no no no I'm going to take your
F since that's a waste wait that's what
is this I'll get it I'm watching the
credits right now oh my
God wait spoilers tell us what do you
see what do you see your special credits
eyes what
say it says Long Live
Minecraft dude no way Long Live M I want
to see him too shall we jump in together
what about the egg together um we can
take that eventually but we don't need
it oh what would it do bur another End
Dragon one
jump
jumping what car I thought you already
watched the smok one block it won't let
me in what have I done please help hey
at least you guys went to a different
screen just jump up wait I'm floating on
top of it what have I
done is here it doesn't work for me
there's like glass underneath it's like
a fake floor yeah see you guys did it
separated different real there's no
credits in one BL oh no but at least you
got through I'm not getting FR I'm not
no I'm still in the end hey I don't see
you I don't see you guys either we all
got split into different re realities
yeah it's just how it ends I don't like
this game how it end we just crashed the
server we're all in the end but we don't
see each other that's so lonely yeah if
we die we turn back to it's like a
metaphor for life it's like a it's like
a
long I'm not going to die here I'm going
to stay here I'm putting my flag back
down I have all my cool things so I
can't access my inventory yeah I can't
access my inventory
either well beating the game it did you
beat the game is that it is this how
it's supposed to be I guess
so well I wish I could be standing by
your size H let's try re oh I can't I
can't I can't open the E Escape screen
to
disconnect can I it breaks your computer
when you beat the gameing the game this
is Smith bad end no hey I'm I'm making
fireworks I thought you guys were going
to come back we're were going to
celebrate but all right I want to be
with Amy
can we die oh wait ah oh if you tap out
of your game you can get into the Escape
screen screen the um disconnect screen
tab and then you can log back in and you
end up in ah I ended up back in the
house of our
beds safety nice that's pretty cool hey
and we still got inventory y yay we got
it I'm
alive she lives after being bullied by
end
endlessly beautiful good end I we found
each other again e the power of
all I can't it doesn't work when I open
him oh say can
you computer
good where' she go I'm stuck in the
vo very very nice are you putting it up
there I did full screen but it still
doesn't work on top of Atlantis can you
control delete is Atlantis one of the
states now it is didn't you know
that so how many states is it now in
total 52
55 oh oh I hope that's correct Kaa I
hope it
is never going to use wait there's even
a Liberty Bell bless it be
Fireworks off of the Atlantis gate when
it turns night time oh you want I have
AAR I oh yeah yeah here thank
you I'm just restarting the game okay
okay where should we watch watch him
from the top of or maybe from the top of
here he top of PPP would be cute because
of that F art yeah that is where we were
sitting right yeah is it safe up there
we need to build like a I don't know
ladder that goes up and Ladder oh yeah I
have ladder okay and then cross the
bridge and make
more Okie doie yeah make big
ladder I I will be
cameraman oh that's surely going to end
well nobody ever well the cameraman
doesn't die but I'll watch from down
here for when they
fall get all the angles
[Music]
mhm o just like jackass so can we open
that up is that going to be okay to open
up isn't there going to be a lot of
enemies up there no we're not going to
open it up we just go on top of it yeah
make like a a structure that's just VI
not open it do not open it how you go
around it though it's shaped like a
giant mushroom you can get some stairs
around or something no problem maybe
maybe not from there GAA maybe from
where the other stairs were and then
straight up so we end up at the edge of
it I guess oh okay not want to crack
that
open it sounds a little
spicy it's getting dark wait so wait
wait wait wait wait it's like opening
Pandora's box or watch where you me oh
my you you're going to push me off the
edge what I'm behind you what do you
mean p the Ping
oh don't worry goba wait no this is how
we have to this this is how we have to
do this okay
yeah go wait throw me the
ladders she going to throw it off the
ledge okay looking
good shut up bro say nothing
shut caught in 4k
stop throw it throw how many myths does
it take to make a staircase yeah shut
up okay col is clear oh you guys hurry
we catch the
sunset yay okay girls you can come up it
seem I don't think we're going to though
this is like holy Holy Ground Sunset but
we will get into the
firor sunset's dying very beautiful
though that's okay C the fireworks maybe
we'll catch this sun right oh yeah that
works
rejected La chair out get the barbecues
popping off I was thinking I was like
really put
a and now we get to hear the beautiful
sound of monsters as well while we're
enjoying all right I'm making piles
everybody takes on fireworks okay one
pile Oh this is cute this is cute oh I
took all of them next
pile I I still have a firework star or
several fireworks stars in in my
inventory from you
okay how does this work who didn't get
fireworks there's another pile over
here thank
you all right com where should we go
here looking over the
thing oh yeah it's good if you go like
thir person thumnail picture yeah yay
happy we just shoot them what about the
Fook stars do they work too yeah they're
in the fireworks I'm not sure how I
think you have to look down and
W
cute
cool I'll shoot
some look down oh
blue
[Music]
fire this is like New
Year y happy New Year
M did
it Happ New Year it's so pretty it's
some of them are not exploding properly
yeah I accidentally made like regular
ones oh oh I got
thosea beautiful oh okay it's all of
them I think yeah there's like the
regular
one okay that's it okay
W oh nice
finale oh it's raining
cool wait can we take a picture sure
where we we have like a good shot of
like the little things we built over
there oh here we face this yeah yeah
yeah let's take one together let's take
off the armor
yeah wait what's wrong with my
head same you look normal to me looks
fine to me yeah it's a bug i' I'd rather
wear my helmet in that case you have to
confess your sins to
me wait I don't have a helmet I am a
we can all wear I bet I look bald oh I
kind of yeah I do look bald
whoa uh I I want to have empty
hands what it
was
okay uh wait I want a better View for
the screenshot
okay okay ah I'm don't go wait hold on I
thought you were going to fall
off because for the screenshot being on
the Edge is kind of
bad oh should I should we
expose Calli let's expose the the stupid
foreheads let's do it take them
out okay
tees
wow cute this is what we built in about
a week or so what is it F3 F6 F3 f not
it free for screenshot F no F F2 F2 and
if you want to get rid of the UI it's F1
yeah oh yeah F1 but I mean how do I
change perspective I can't believe I
still have forgot F5 there's three
different perspectives so you have to
switch around oh okay I think we should
all Run and Jump Off The Other Side
together guys wouldn't that be so fun
die together
okay what Cy you got you screenshot I
think I think it took well if it didn't
it's cool okay I guess we're going to
leave all this behind time to leave this
planet
behind wait can I have a little
speech you all before we die speech
speech well spe spech I am happy that we
were able to give everybody some nice
nostalgic feelings not just chat but
ourselves perhaps too with these loud
zombies that I'm hearing in in the
background uh I want to say thank you to
the girls for participating in this
project and and myth is number one my is
best my is cute my is love my is
forever let's
go let's J let's GOP with all my homies
jumping with all my homies jumping off
the bridge with my homies
y like jumping but we
die okay this I I'm going to log out
because I don't want to I want this to
be the end me
[Music]
too we did it roll the
credits yay up
again this hesty
[Music]
thank you the diary is
all the Diaries somebody wrote some
stuff right I did I forgot it I forgot
to to write the final entry I want to
read what what G
wrote I'll give you my last diary entry
are you going to write it no I'll just
say it out loud okay say it uh
we were not
overprepared let's
go it seems like it that's about the
extent of my my time today it was fun
the dragon bit back yes it wasn't the
dragon it was the Enderman I'm glad I'm
glad it was a challenge yeah chaotic
it's like we did it for the first time
because it seemed like we had no idea
what we were doing I
forgot okay let me let me then check
gas Ena do you want to give a vocal
diary entry for us uh I would like to
say this Easter K wasn't that bad had a
lot of fun thank you k for putting a lot
of work behind the scenes I put too much
right it was so unnecessary to make so
many things I know but it was fun it
work that yeah indeed it was F indeed
thank you thank you for partici you
everyone for know the fun times yeah
love it thanks for the reliability Ina
for building the
base when we entered no no no no no no
somebody needs to be brave enough to do
it and it was you
exactly okay all right uh should I read
it out loud what G wrote yes what yeah
okay she wrote like she wrote wait she
wrote two entries for today it seems we
go back in oh you want to read it
like your reading it out loud your face
okay I'll read it then cuz I've been
reading your other entries
too okay H uh day five tonight we fight
tonight the Ender Dragon Falls tonight
the new Champions will rain tonight the
spoils will be ours tonight we will rise
TBC tonight well is this a song it's a
chant oh that
was you didn't say it right okay say it
right say it right no I was trying to
make gooda voice but I can't do good
voice more dramatic it's like tonight we
fight the end of dragon Falls tonight
the
new cap you didn't say white
yeah forgive me goba forgive me it's
okay the next one I'll read better okay
day six no Elden ring Dragon thing yet
but the server is oh this is not as
dramatic as I thought it would be well
now wow the message is not the message
is not dramatic no Elden ring Dragon
thing yet what does that mean El ring
catching Str we didn't fight the Elden
oh this was before okay
dragon
dragon but the server is haunted it
passed a message to me
message I couldn't
well now I need a a a a vocal ending uh
entry please
goba the
end true beautiful true well said
said thank you okay then I have one more
from
Amy I shall see I prematured my the end
then I saw her riding a few times
today oh oh a I cannot even read this
sorry I was pouring my tea for this
great moment I thought a left like a p
noise in the background I did oh guys I
think stain I have a hunch I might be
wrong but I think I'm right I think am a
love Smith
yth
loves she just wrote a million hearts
into the diary and wrote Love my my love
love those manually too that Tak a lot
of
work okay this one gets an a am an a for
amen and an a for pass for awesome
you're passing with flying
gra yeah thank you for writing the
Diaries and that's it that was myth one
block Minecraft the series the season
and the season finale we all had a blast
and the Ender Dragon has been also
blasted um in his
ass yeah yeah we all got blasted wo is
wait what
blast we had a blast and we were
blasted right nice
yeah y thank you for watching
[Music]
andth
timate ultimate ultimate byebye C you
guys on
the by everyone bye bye
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
you