[Music]
k
k Double C
power isn't that
cute I found that a while ago in my uh
weaponry
thank you for that cute cot
plusy yes gently holding did you see
what I drew yesterday yeah I had a day
off and uh the day before that the
stream was I don't know
early so it's kind of been like a lot of
hours without us meeting each other and
it's it's been tough on me so I I drew
this
look at
you I felt like drawing you guys cuz you
guys are so
cute so
cute it's
you um well first of all don't worry I'm
feeling uh
fine
uh yeah pretty pretty good stable
also had an app to to like recharge
energy cuz my doctor's appointment
absolutely drained me and it's
ridiculous
because
um
I supposedly it shouldn't have been as
painful as it
[Laughter]
was um I'm not going to go into details
because it's embarrassing but I was at
the dentist today
again and
uh
um it
was unnecessarily
painful
um the doctor
said he was surprised because the first
time someone had that much pain for um
that
[Music]
procedure I I even
um cried a little but I tried
to uh be cool with
it no it's not like it's it's really
ridiculous cuz it's not like they
drilled or anything or they didn't pull
anything nothing it's but yeah let's not
get too deep into it but I just have
really really um sensitive teeth at the
moment I guess and sensitive uh uh
what's it called
gums as well and yeah and and then
because of all the
pain I I had a really bad headache as
well at the same time and I tried to I
tried to like I you know I I had to like
hold it hold it and wait and wait and
wait and then I I I I couldn't I need I
needed something
for for um uh what's the word I needed
something to get my mind of it didn't
really help that much but then I I I put
on Christmas
music and the the dentist helper she was
like are you so excited for Christmas
and I'm like no I I I I couldn't speak I
just wrote on my memo I wrote no I just
need something to distract myself so and
and that was the first thing I I could
think of so I was playing Christmas
music
while in in ex excruciating pain and uh
also trying to redirect the pain to
somewhere else so it was like squeezing
my hands and and trying to hurt myself
on my
hands oh and I kept on trying to massage
my forehead because that headache was so
strong in my forehead holy
[\h__\h] it was so ridiculous I don't know
why it was so
painful uh Stupid it wasn't even
drilling or
anything yeah but yeah whatever so at
the end of it like yeah we're going to
we're going to get this story over with
right now I don't care I won't be able
to focus maybe later on so at the end of
it um you know we were supposed to go on
longer but I said I can't do it anymore
so the dentist the doctor was like okay
well well never had someone with that
much pain but I guess you're just hyper
sensitive and I couldn't even I couldn't
even reply anymore like the my mouth was
numb and my mind
was exhausted I I I call you
anyway when when I was when I needed to
like
uh uh uh you know they give you water to
and then p
I couldn't even I put the water in my
mouth and I couldn't even move my
mouth I was like in a in a State of
Shock yeah rins rins I was in a State of
Shock and numbness I couldn't do
anything and the doctor was a just just
just rins just spit it
[Laughter]
out oh
man oh man oh was it was bad
and then he was like why you look
really really messed
up you you look like you've been through
[\h__\h] and I'm like yeah I I don't feel
good but the um the uh the the the the
whole pain um it wore off pretty quickly
yeah it's it's a okay um I'm feeling
fine soon soon after
my tweets I was already feeling better
and now I feel perfectly
normal so it's all good so far so far so
good yeah
um yeah I I I I it's embarrassing to
talk about it so we'll leave it at that
but
um and then on my nap I even dreamed
about the
dentist about the dentist appointment
well well well yeah let's move on but um
so sorry to worry you guys but we still
playing Mario Party
[Music]
Superstars and I want to play together H
with you guys today uh it is apparently
part possible to play the mini games
with you guys and that's what I want to
do I don't want to play like a whole map
with you guys that would take way too
long uh and I would only be able to have
fre people uh there so yeah no but we're
going to play mini games it should yeah
I'm I'm already in the online room and
then I chose random people because the
other option is friends and I'm not
going to befriend all of you we're
already friends so there's no need for
that um but yeah we're going to try it
out I hope it works properly uh I just I
have had so much fun with the mini games
but at the same time like last time I
played with other people but at the same
time I I I felt like M I need to win
Mario party next time I keep on losing
so I want to practice Yeah I hope
there's a join by code option I I'm not
so sure I just know it's possible to
play with other people but I don't know
how it works sou to lead us to uh the
mini games please and then have some fun
together guys I think
maximum play time uh 2 hours and then we
read super chats I think because I still
have super chats left over and uh I
don't want to go on for too long because
tomorrow I'll have
a somewhat early stream and I need to
prepare for it a little bit you know
it's a cooking stream tomorrow and that
always needs a little bit of preparation
um
yeah so that's what we're going to
do let's go
of course looks like
me around the world waiting are you
ready to take them on yeah but I don't
know am I getting like random random
people or can I actually get a code or
something I I hope I'm not wrong here it
should be
correct
Zoom Mario Kart tourn yeah to be honest
I should be practicing Mario Kart but I
had this on my agenda for a while too so
we're playing Mario party today but
we're also going to be practicing Mario
Kart soon um not that I'm planning to
win that tournament uh no one can win
against people like Aqua
but but he it will be random if I do
this oh wait the friend option does it
also give you the option to just uh get
a code oh wait a
second maybe that is it so this is
complete Randall's
oh okay let's go back
uh
ah okay okay okay
[Music]
Daisy uh no wait I no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no more more more
back online play friend game so we a
friends after
all minin will win Mario Kart I guess
Min Senai is good too but I think the
best one is still Aqua
simple yes yes skippity
go yeah yeah yeah yeah you guys hear the
music is it too
quiet yipp I think it's too
quiet a little bit could be Lou a little
bit good to see
[Music]
aha I create a room and then after H how
should we do it like after each creating
a new room after each mini game I don't
know how this works but I guess that's
how it works it would take a lot of time
so maybe per room we can do two mini
games if that is possible and then make
a new
room uh open to all set
code okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay so don't set code what do you mean
don't set I need a code
no why not set
code what happens if I do no code then
how would people isn't it just no no no
I want you guys no this should be fine
should code is not how we find you
there's an ID in set set code but hide
it you're IDE is a
code yes set code okay oh I set the code
not the game
okay
7 0
6 National Fried Chicken
day how many people play in this
system
oh oh come in R the 4 5
[Laughter]
389 and everyone please only join once
so that we can get in as many people as
possible uh and I hope I hope this works
well let's play some mini
games mini gamer
welcome oh
welcome welcome do you guys have boring
ass no wait no I want to look at you
boring no I want to look at your cards
why are you waiting for players again
they're all here huh no no can I can I
not look at the cards there
nothing this person level
99 get out of here 97 hours wait what do
the other numbers mean Mason what do the
numbers mean this person seems too too
good at it kick him out kick
him yum
[Music]
okay this person wait how are you Mario
P wait this is actually pretty easy to
get Mario part 11199 cuz this one has 1
hours in 199 level
99 but this person still scares
me yummy I can keep no okay we we'll
keep it let's see let's see how strong
you really
are have a good time I don't know if I
will um I just want to practice game so
please don't bully
me oh wait I maybe shouldn't um
[Music]
what no no
no did I exit out by
accident
what I think I did something wrong now I
exited I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry to the people who
made it in no I'm so stupid I think I
pressed the wrong button there um I
pressed B
my oh man
hi yeah yeah yeah uh create room
again open to all set code
okay so you guys when you enter you have
to find my room by the ID and then enter
this code as well is that how it is and
I guess we could do it without a code at
too I guess not no randoms would join
right
normally okay okay maybe next time sorry
and 925
650 they will never get this chance
again no trust me people who are that
fast with joining these kind of rooms
they will definitely have a chance at
joining again s
key
welcome no no and see Miss made it in
again no no let me I want to look at
your
cart why are you waiting for players
they are here I just want to look at the
carts
no oh there we go Mario Party level one
zero
hours okay absolute Noob here
Noob and another a
noob okay okay this one is not not a
noob but um I think how much did I play
5 hours but I'm level seven okay now
let's destroy s's keyblade then let's
destroy him you heard me guys you heard
me
right got to look at who I'm up against
today's my birthday happy
birthday okay okay so B if I just want
to end it in general yeah but how do I
ah okay here I can just choose okay
Mount mini games let's go kiawa is under
control and
No More Level 99
people let's
go o o o o o where where am I O O where
am I where I where's my where's okay if
one of you would have taken Daisy from
me I would have kicked you
out well these ones were able to read
the room and not take Daisy away from me
good job on reading the error cookie Yi
successful all according to
Kaku and why am I not in my party
clothes I thought this outfit is more
suitable for this occasion and also I
wanted to hold you guys in my arms and
on my
head I missed you guys yes wel
to course you want to
play uh
chever shut
up attack match ah two versus two oh
three challenge
oh Sports and
puzzles
oh survival one player can compete with
players from what daily one player why
can only one player play online what
does that mean you can play
very coin battle coin mini game huh okay
just with this one I can actually choose
which one I
want 29 out 100 there's still so many
more help on help off I don't know is is
help off does that mean it won't show us
how to play the mini game like no
tutorial I do think I want to
know uh keep help on
Okay okay then
play so I choose a game
oh which one should I
choose one that I
haven't tried yet I got the practice any
game oh look at that so I'm the one
choosing oh I can do random though okay
random
go coconut conk solo side roll around
wait ah no it's speak wa I can change it
can I change it can I change it should I
change it me versus everyone I don't
like that I want to I don't want to be
the only one here let's do it like
this SS I run around to dodge the Fallen
coconuts ah teams like ground P to drop
okay okay how did Grand P pun
again was it a and then
B was it a and
b oh God no good luck ah ah here hey he
good luck there there he
goes um I give you I will give you guys
a little bit of practice
time unless you guys are all ready okay
let's go party
games this will indeed take some time
every time to switch the games but oh
well good
luck let's go
winners okay mini games are pretty short
too so I guess this one was short
there's longer ones though okay random
mini game go next
one toie toie toie let's
go you you lost that one oh what is this
shoot Goombas to paint them
oh where am
I ah team versus Team okay cool cool
cool cool cool cool
I am with the the
monkey monkey monkey monkey monkey
monkey monkey oh I move
[Music]
away okay let's
go what's that let's rock this let's
paint everything in
Orange even though there's no orange
option what
go team Daisy
oh look at me
girl oh no no no no no no no no no no no
no what batt oh my God
[Music]
no uhoh time is scking time is scking
time is scking time is
[Music]
taking we won I think we won yeah
winners by four
woohoo
nice losers losers
losers look at Peach
losing what is this Bowser is lurking in
the darkness avoid him and his fire
breathing attack keep running until the
very end oh where where is Bowser ah we
won't really know ah okay
okay
uh-oh oh no no no okay oh I understand I
understand I'm
ready dark and crispy just how I like my
fried
chicken actually not too dark not too
dark
[Music]
that wasn't enough
practice we're playing games to practice
and I immediately dipped out
no oh
no God damn it finish oh double win for
you guys huh Winn you think you're cool
huh you think you're cool
huh can we do the same yeah we can do
the same one because I didn't really get
to practice properly okay and then we
Chang the
team it's it's uh all the games are so
short but we want to get in more people
right oh God
no no no not on me please
oh okay safe safe safe safe safe safe
safe oh my God he almost touched me just
by touching you uh he can like push you
out right just by
touching oh there burn
Yoshi that was so close we were all at
the same
spot nice he
okay return to square thanks everybody
that was
fun I will kick you guys out now if I
can
bye-bye oh byebye I have to press B I
think that was already pretty good I
think
the the uh okay brings it back here
that's
good the the the balance was good Kiana
won every game except that one time no
that didn't happen it didn't happen
didn't happen yes yes yes yes looks
familiar hummer hummer hummer oh my God
if only they wouldn't have uh this long
long way to go to the mini
games
shush yes yes how are you I do not care
I'm going to create another room for you
guys no Cod this time open to all me J
are you guys
ready let's
go let's
[Music]
go and it is 427 951 427 951 427 951
please not die same people please not
that same
people 427 951 oh no let me look at your
card oh no the N level 99 dude is
back okay so here we have level 1 Zer
hours uh wait let me
look 97 hours yeah you yeah yeah 7 hours
but 54 how do you get to level 54 with 7
hours bonus order not a hold okay uh one
28 up scares me I'm scared for my life
oh
no oh no by getting
good but then how I how am I not level
over 9,000 yet
hm let's go mini
[Music]
games I'm I'm getting
good I'm I'm already good as we have
seen next time no give
me no no no no no no no no no no switch
oh no go away give me thank you
[Music]
yes what was I about to say I
forgot oh yeah next time we're going to
play uh this game with some other H life
members I'm going to be the master of
Min games they're going to be so scared
of me or I'm going to let them look at
my card because they don't even know
usually they don't even know how that
card thing works and I'm going to have
them look at it and they're going to see
level 99 I'm going to be like that's
right baby
and they're going to be like oh my God
she's going to crush us why is she level
99 the
hell
okay and then you to lose somehow no no
no no
impossible no that's not
possible free play Let's play uh free to
five games depending on how short they
are uh R oops
uh there we go River raid Raiders yes
collect coins that travel down the river
be careful not to hit the floating logs
oh it's one versus uh three h I guess
I'll be the I'll be the the player one
then I'll be up against you guys for
this one I I could I guess do both ways
I could uh switch it
later so what do I
do what do I I
do oh do I have to keep them from
collecting ah I want to try to get all
the money for myself yeah
okay why it's so slow why is it so
slow I'm is it supposed to be a slow can
I not speed up oh damn it no I wanted
that I wanted that bag of chicken
nuggets oh there's something good for
me yeah yeah yeah okay I'm ready
ready
okay let's
go let's go boating on the Boating trip
I'm not your dad but uh why wouldn't you
want to go on a boating trip with your
mom huh are you scared that I will push
you off the boat and then hide your body
in the river forever and not tell
anyone oh my God look at me getting all
that money
[\h__\h] it
that's where all the bodies are at the
bottom of the river no no you don't go
therey no no no money they got more
money than me they got more money than
me how do the employees have more money
than
me
o
[Music]
o this
time this time we'll change uh
positions cuz I got to practice both
positions never never you never know
where you end up at if you play against
other whole life members okay I'm on the
very left okay let's
go o Luigi Luigi if you want to get
somewhere with Daisy then you better
move your ass oh Yoshi what the [\h__\h]
Yoshi I wanted to go to the right side I
couldn't because of you you guys are
horrible at this you guys are so bad at
this no look at us losing
Yi move okay thank you I guess thanks
for that one coin
horrible
horrible you guys were better when I was
up against you for some reason what does
that tell me look at me losing
unbelievable I should kick out all these
[Laughter]
people okay
uh
ah uh we I already play can we get a
different one I feel like I don't need
to practice this one
eh it's enough a coin game but okay I
can't get out of this menu so I guess I
guess let's do
it they're going to ground pound me
aren't they start not before I ground P
them he yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh my God where's the money where's
the
money no where's the [\h__\h]
money give me give
me did I get that yes I think I did
where am I where am
I no no Mom no holy [\h__\h] first 34 coins
one to8 up are you like are you a
champion of Super
Mario Mario Party Superstars or what
what what is it with you what is it with
you okay that's okay I don't want to
play that game again I want to play
something I haven't played before ah I
hope I Haven played this one
before okay let's get it over
with wait which one is which one is the
level 99 guy Luigi or which one was
it got to keep an eye out on my
enemies the penguins are
coming oh
God cheer for your tal kfp I'm at the
very job oh God oh God oh God oh God oh
God okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
oh my god oh oh God oh God
[Music]
I was doing so
wellow that was not bad though that was
not bad it was pretty uh quick already
the speed was insane at that point okay
one last game with you guys because you
guys don't bring me any
[Laughter]
luck again a game that I played before
but I did win at this one last time I
played
it I think I was the
winner uh but wait
I I I I'm bad at it today wait
what ah uh okay okay I need to warm up
you know can someone hold my hand what's
going on how did I play this last time
hold no can you guys hold my hand
please
I wait not tapping I thought it was
tapping
oh Zoom okay okay okay okay okay okay
we're ready to go ready to
[Laughter]
go says hold shut up I thought it was
like one foot another foot you
know it's a
battle
sh wait for
me wait for me wait for me wait for
me oh my God they probably have the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] they probably have the Euro beat on
that's not
fair oh God oh God oh God oh God oh God
Luigi was trying to wait for me I
appreciate that that's pretty
cute stupid
[Music]
Yoshi thank you
guys thank you guys for um yeah hanging
out with
me
yeah out with the old in with the new
kick him out kick him out what happened
but shut up what that's going to be what
your mom is going to ask me soon when
you disappear and you don't come home
anymore it's going to be like what
happened boss what happened with my son
and I'm going to be like I have
absolutely no idea what happened with
your son how would I
know how would I know maybe I look at
the bottom of the lake
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's have some more fun
together creting room please new people
are you guys ready
you ready ready
one 578 784 57
8784 57
8784 57 8784 yay 57 8784 yay y
yay wait were you
weren't you in before but were you in
that round oh don't try to join again
were you in that round
where I kicked everyone out by accident
cat
gaming let me look at the cards ah that
person was kicked okay so JD is new for
sure 7 hours level
31 finally a Japanese bro made it in too
even though it's a bad time for them I
think it's a Japanese bro uh 53 also
pretty
[Music]
good oh
no why did you make it back cat gaming
why didn't you make it
[Applause]
[Music]
back why didn't you make it
back why would you have to try
again oh man
oh oh man oh man what did I get myself
into it's trouble your name says
[Laughter]
trouble it's okay I'm not I'm not here
to force you guys to let me win I'm here
to practice and get better on my
own and you guys are at least so sweet
to always let me choose daisy as long as
you guys let me choose Daisy this world
is
still a safe and friendly place I must I
must
admit guys yesterday I had my day off
and um I was actually socializing for
the first time in a million years can
you believe
it can you believe
it we had a pizza party with uh me and
friends yeah my BFF was supposed to come
too but she had to cancel
uh so we were one person
less yeah but we are still having a lot
of
fun and the pizza was so good so we have
this we have this friend in a friend
Circle who picked up a hobby might be in
a midlife crisis but picked up the hobby
uh pizza making and uh he was like so so
addicted to it he was trying to to make
the perfect pizza for over a year he got
himself like a proper um professional
industrial kind of like uh pizza
oven and and he he got so deep into the
lore into the pizza lore the only thing
I was missing is him speaking Italiano
and I was like Mama M why you know
Italiano horrible but uh no not a brick
one but uh one that finishes your Pizza
in one [\h__\h] minute it's amazing and
and like when you put um when you when
when something drops it will like
immediately turn into ashes it's like
really [\h__\h] hot M yeah yeah so we
were served a lot of pizzas how many
pizzas was it I
think hu six or seven
pizzas uh all kinds of pizzas but our
favorite the most popular one was uh um
tuna I love this game I love this one
GameCube game let's go H was tuna with
uh corn M yum y y but we also had a a a
pineapple ham Pizza of course also with
corn H and then we had like salami with
pepperoni but but mild ones and then we
had a simple
Margarita and then we had more tuna with
corn you guys are so surprised about it
but this is quite an noral thing tuna
Pizza is very common in its origin land
you you guys don't know your pizza game
okay sorry guys for letting me wait
let's
play don't get flattened and then I was
able to take some pizza home too so I
ate the pizza for breakfast
today yes yes
uh okay
move why would you all go to the same
place don't be so close to the
idol I love this game go away why you
all come to the same
place go away see because of you I got
flatten sounds like it was a good time
yeah we were listening to um to uh
Christmas music and hanging out and we
were also drinking punch there was punch
but it was only alcoholic one so I only
drank a tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny bit uh
cuz it was actually tasting uh not that
alcoholic but I don't know if it was the
punch that was insanely mildly alcoholic
or just because I had a busy day but I
felt so
tired already around 11:00
p.m. so I made my way
home with my pizza pizza to
go well this is this is going well
someone is dead
yeah oh it's getting faster
uh I'm a star I'm a moon I was
there yeah yeah know but I still didn't
sleep early because after I came home I
still had so many things to do I came
home like after midnight and I had a
deadline yesterday uh that I had to
provide something for um so I did that
and then uh I did some other uh things I
had to do some stuff for H like
coordinate some stuff for the music uh
video/ S cover that is coming out next
week with me and Ena yeah yeah uh all
very busy so I ended up going to sleep
at the usual time at like 4:00 or 5:
a.m. yay but it's okay I had a great day
off
anyway yeah very very yummy pizza and it
made me it got me into thinking should I
get myself an OV like like that too it
takes up a little bit of space uh how
does this work again uh yeah ah okay I'm
in the I'm on that side cool rope
rotating oh okay okay okay rotate rotate
rotate with the palm of your hand let's
go oh my God Bowser is so strong wa
that's a Bowser that's Donkey Kong so
strong why is of course Donkey Kong is
the strongest it's not fair
[Music]
don't fall into the pizza Lord
but it tasted so good and that's the
fastest I've ever put my hands on to
pizza
before you that nice one guys
ether
nice 1 minute I swear it was done in 1
minute you had to pull it out after 60
seconds unbelievable and it tasted so
good yo you guys have no idea that was
so good fresh pizza just like from the
best Italian place in
town yeah B is free ain't it a fair fact
of course it is he had more power he had
the Bowser power I love this guy it's
one of my absolute favorites you can see
it it's it's in my in my card which one
am I this
one uh wait what is this about though
try the matx ah okay okay okay okay I
thought we were just making something
funny
okay
yeah why wo it's so laggy wo w w wo wo
lag lag can you not make it lag monkey I
think it's
you or is it I don't know why is oh my
God it's so
laggy well I hope it's not only lagging
for
me is it the ping it's the
Ping Mama man
and didn't here do you love the game I
love this one this one is one of my
favorites I already said it but it
really is I don't know it's just so
nostalgic oh my God his face melted are
you
okay uh
wait I'm H graphic design is my passion
so I'm obviously going to win
this oh
it's a bit difficult to see like what
happened with his
face but we're getting there I guess
overall his nose must be
lower oh God no time [\h__\h]
finish
uh oh I
won
Artic
Mar Taki kiaha M oh oh
magnic oh Shel or something like that
W yeah I got that artistic sense in my
[Applause]
brain I love that game that was a that
was um from the Nintendo
64 ah wait when do I move the do I move
the control while uh jumping or before
what's the best way to do this I'm
moving it on at the same time as
pressing the button ow
a ah you shouldn't be like oops oh my
God right
underneath oh the
leg oh it better not be like this in the
real
game oh no yeah the 64 games and the
GameCube games were my favorite ones I
think during the GameCube time is when I
played Mario Party the most activist
activity actively
actively the most
often with my bro and my family oh
god um it's not only for me like this
huh is
it I'm I'm pushing a I'm push there
um uh
um uh how
would okay judging by Donkey Kong I'm
not the only one oh my god oh I think it
it fixed but now I'm like so out of the
loop what the hell no I
can't no I I can't even say it's the pig
anymore no but like I hate hey
[Music]
finish something is wrong
herea wait let me try this
again hopefully without the
leg my or skill yeah okay hey it's
better right now it's better oh no
practice uh what the [\h__\h] okay
oh well look at me now Look at me now
ow no no
no finish
[Music]
one more time I need to practice this is
what this stream is
about at least we Wai progress this time
shut up it sounds like you're roasting
me sounds ironic to me
[Applause]
oh what was that
lag it's only because of the
lag
okay what was
that [\h__\h] hell [\h__\h] hell
[Music]
[Applause]
well let's just hope that I never have
to play this game together with any H
life members thank you guys for hanging
out with
me I hope you guys liked jumping uh in
the
sky it's like jump King I guess
so oh man okay uh uh let's let's do
another round with my
friends AKA
kfp
KF yes are you guys ready to put in a
coat open to all no code
okay new people please and a
go
08416 08416
[Music]
I'm
so what a name what a
name maybe next time we open a room I'll
say the number in Japanese first and
hide it so maybe Japanese people can try
to get into although they are probably
the reason why the pengu was so horrible
but I want to give them a chance so I'm
H how's it going 55 7 hours okay cheater
uh 99 20 o cheater uh 43 14 hour cheater
okay I'm I'm playing I'm up against
cheaters and
hackers okay cool um not fair but okay I
guess this is how the world is it's just
not fair cheaters and hackers everywhere
yeah but I will show you who's the boss
I will show you who the boss
is time to beat the odds K let's
go beat the odds yes I will I'm going to
beat the chicken fries M beat them
[Music]
good H there we go thank you guys for
letting me always choose
[Music]
Daisy let's do our best
go I see uh it's always like Rosalina
and Donkey Kong are always so popular
nice nice just a little bit of copium to
start the day I don't need that no no
not for
me I'm feeling perfectly fine shut up
toad I skipped for a
reason uh Free Play Let's
Go 36 out of 100 we still didn't get
very far why does it keep on giving me
the same games I want something new
okay uh let's press that y button and
shake it up
nicely no I played that one
before okay let's just choose like this
uh oh this one would be new solo side
mashed a button to escape team side
ground pound to feed py Pia with rain
okay we'll do this with with me and then
and me me I might have I'm on the
skateboard then okay
okay let's try this and then later if we
can we
change the
middle it shows if you play it or not oh
got to check that
then okay this one is easy to win as the
one nice H oh well Mash spe to skate and
then jump where where would I jump over
ah here oh you guys got a
uh oh [\h__\h] you guys got a put water on
on the plants now oh [\h__\h] okay I'm ready
how long does this go though time
limited probably wait do I have to jump
over that
log oh I don't necessarily have to but
it slows me down if I
don't
okay Wario let's go Wario ah they got
me let's go y I wish pushing B really
slowly actually I was taking it easy and
it was pretty going pretty well ah grab
the V boost thank you I didn't know that
the game doesn't really tell you
that oh my God I'm speeding I'm
speeding
oh
oh oh my god oh oh my God oh my God oh
my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my God oh oh my God oh my God oh my
God okay
[Music]
okay K has is now pushing the B button
with a different finger could be faster
let's
go most of the time I was pushing it
with my fum but then later on my f was
getting too weak so I switched a hello
game on my on my game capture card it
crashed it crashed but on OBS it's fun
what the hell let me restart the game
capture uh yeah I switched to my to my
index finger later on was going pretty
well muh i
w I'm winning did you see that on
Twitter it changed my name to kfp
winning I wonder why I did that I just
felt like uh first of all I I had
something else there that was kind of
outdated and second of all I wanted to
show my appreciation because I love you
guys so much I love you guys too much
too
much oh I could have played it again as
the other counterpart I guess wait wait
ah oh [\h__\h] I messed up we are playing it
again are we no okay good good but I
didn't get the other part oh well main
manner of Escape mainor of Escape find
the door that leads to the floor below
oh interesting Mario Party
9 roselina what are you blocking me on
purpose what the hell is that
roselina um excuse me roselina are you
doing that on purpose I did it hello how
are you like if thank you where you
AFK what
what was
that what was that I'm going to give you
the benefit of the doubt and say that
you didn't do that on purpose anyway
okay so basically just walk through the
doors and hope it's the right one and we
missed a lot of uh where everyone went
oh that was a lucky
one that was a lucky oh and another love
a lucky
one I've Got a Feeling for
this oh H wait what if I go into the
same door where I came out ah okay that
that's not okay hey hey
roselina that was not fair that was not
fair okay let's play
this okay don't shouldn't always be
following wherever the other people go
because uh might might find the door on
my own right start
start um
did you do that on purpose
again was she waiting
to what was that Rosalina I told you
there are cheaters and
hackers you you fat pink
[Laughter]
finish I've been sabotaged
you can move past each other really I
wasn't able to
okay random mini game that one isn't
really something that you have to
practice too much I I think I think
hacks
hacks uh what is this catch you letter
what do you not mean catch your
letter pick up letters falling from the
sky and give them back to the shy guy
it's rhyming oh oh it's so cute shy
gu what is this cute game here take mine
take mine take
mine oh oh my this a
hard I took
it I want to confess my love to Shy Guy
ah catch you l h a
enough enough what that's a cute hecking
game what Shy Guy Shy Guy shy
guy here I have a super chat for you I
have a super chat for you it's real
[Music]
money I wanted that love letter oh shy
you little [\h__\h] shy you little why are
you running away from work no [\h__\h] I
want to drop my a take it
[Music]
get any extra points 4479 what the [\h__\h]
I'm hun winner heck
heck a he's shy but that was fun it's a
cute game I want to play that one
[Music]
again that's
fun I don't know if shy guy is really
running away from me or what's going
going on
there hey shy
guy hey Shy
Guy why is you running away from
me there it is okay love let doo oh
there it is
[\h__\h] sh sh you little [\h__\h] sh sh
sh what a little [\h__\h] what a little
[\h__\h] I'm telling you what a little
stupid
[Music]
[\h__\h] making me mad
here sh sh will get a special invitation
to the usual
room although you cannot uh out together
you cannot decline it why A and
B damn it yeah I failed that one okay I
didn't go very far I think no sh I just
because I didn't bring you enough well
that's your
fault look at them go look at them go I
want to play this with
chimkin my chimpin will fly the furnace
let's go
[Applause]
a okay I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready I I
will win I will win smash those
buttons
[Music]
[Applause]
2 why is Wario so [\h__\h] fast
cheater what a cheater what a
cheater stupid stupid Wario oh look at
meig go though that doesn't mean
anything though does it oh but I fly so
high Look at Me Fly the highest oh my
god
oh
[Music]
cut okay at least I wasn't last at least
I'm not
last and chenry
wins nice holy [\h__\h]
what
finish a new record
Mario is this how you pay me back for
killing your
family unbelievable that was that was
hacks okay out I'm out of here
no talking stre no no no that was in
case I was still feeling um not good but
I am feeling good I'm good I'm good yes
yes I'm uh I'm I'm perfectly
fine yes I would have done uh a Mario
Kart and stream uh where the game ends
if I talk so I would have just quietly
silently played the game if I was still
in pain from the dentist but I'm good
I'm
good H so I will do one
thing
[Music]
okay I'm going to do the the Japanese
Bros a favor and see if they get in if I
tell them the the number first in
Japanese to give them a chance as well
uh
okay don't you be
[Music]
okay can I still try now please try I
have to someone at least one person made
it then I'll tell you
[Music]
then y
go
go non-japanese Bros who speak
Japanese for [\h__\h] sake K guy
he left
though
Nik I like the name though
okay maybe this one is a Japanese one
maybe
o uh 9 11 33 Okay this honestly seems
like a good match
though hi
oh is he being so nice to let someone
Elson but I don't think uh I don't think
they're going to make it I was going to
I was thinking of doing HEI HEI HEI he
oh [\h__\h] back no wait ah game Taco game
Taco this better not be a level 99
player o o let me check I need to
check level one okay let's go why did
you leave you could have stayed
let's do this let's play some games
everybody Mount mini
games oh don't please don't send me
friend requests I will I'm ignoring them
I don't accept
them so
[Music]
thank
you Dy eat
mine guys today is a p Sly new outfit
reveal are you guys aware of that 900
p.m. Japanese Standard
Time
uh that should be before my stream
definitely if it if it overlaps in any
way I will have to move my stream well
not over I but but 900 p.m. Japanese
Center time
is uh
uh at 1:00 p.m. my time oh so I guess my
stream starts when hers ends if she only
does it for 1 hour I
think wel to my mini
games yes P by finally getting her new
outfit 40 games out 100 okay finally a
new number on the horizon
[Music]
finally it I I I am 100% sure that it
will be insanely
cute and perfect
oh I want to play this maybe but these
are the ones of the blue uh one are no
wait which ones are the one I
played why do the Blue Points go
away those are the ones I didn't play
yet right okay let's play uh let's play
Crazy
colors no wait I did play this one
before pretty sure this one I didn't
play Oh Tipsy turny tilt to slide the
shell why is it so laggy oh my God
connection
unstable so Slide the shell and uncover
all the panels
okay uh not
sure how it works but let's try on oh
this is from 64
a wait maybe I did I think I kind of
remember it from my
childhood what a
boomer oh oh man oh God I'm I'm bad at
this oh actually not that bad
yo
yo yo second one to finish wait you can
jump what would that do for me wait wait
what does jumping do what does jumping
do what does jumping do damn it damn it
I didn't test it out but no one was
jumping
start I have to jump over the shell I
guess oh my God I'm doing so
well yeah second one to finish again
let's go game do good job to
oh
winner okay okay easy easy clap you guys
clap for me I can't clap right now and
okay next game next game next game that
was good don't need to practice I'm good
at this
one oh Mario Party
7 uh wait what bring me back oh it's one
versus free okay don't fall into the
holes uh
n um Mario could you maybe fall into a
hole so we can try
again
please it's just practice come on it's
just practice hey come on don't act so
strong and tough
buddy there we go okay
uh oh a moral class see oh
difficult that's tough I guess I should
probably just stop when it stops moving
as
well well I don't think I'll do well
with this oh God oh God oh God oh God oh
God oh God oh God no no no no oh God oh
God oh God oh no
no I think we'll play this one one more
time because
this is one where I do need some
practice I
see
ah yo Wario you're freaking mad
lad really good at that aren't
you even valigi doesn't know how to
overpower
him wow but we I I guess it does mean
that we won but I I want to try try
again to become
better yeah same team oh sorry I could
have at least switched out Waluigi
sorry sorry do you best
then no
[Applause]
[Music]
no yeah that's good Wario I don't know
if you did that on purpose but if you
guys just dip out now you would do me a
favor thank
you win I will do another run but I'll
switch out
uigi course
you Wario is on the wheale
now let's see how good you're now when
you're in control
huh okay what am I doing
wrong wait did they do that on purpose
winner or are they all just that bad or
is or is is he that
good
huh is he just that good at spinning the
wheel they did it on purpose maybe they
did because they know I will I will
continue this until I'm good at
it okay start on the left side I don't
like that I don't like that oh God oh
God okay okay okay okay okay can you go
slower Wario can you ease me into it
please oh oh oh no there was a lag there
was a
[Music]
lag Yoshi good job Yoshi
f waai for us eight seven 6 5 4 3 2 one
good job
Yi I'm so proud of you yashi players are
always nice people I know that this one
is easy it's not it's not easy but I'll
switch this one out again this time
Yoshi can spin the wheel so you guys
don't get bored while I'm repeating the
same game over and over
let's try nice I play Yoshi I know you
do because you're
nice makes sense which where are we
going oh God oh God Yosi thank you are
you're doing this to be nice oh God the
lag oh God oh God oh God oh God Yosi I'm
winning Yosi let's
go I
tried well some things are just the way
they are and you have to accept them
it is what it is I I'll give you guys
one more random game because we play the
same game over and
[Laughter]
over no I already played that one I want
to get out of here no how do I how get
how do I cancel it if I don't want it B
doesn't work for
real okay but
uh
okay I guess I have no choice
oopsy yes you can't damn it damn
it start it would be cool if you could
at least um select to uh
get when you choose random games to only
get random games that um you have not
played before Oh God
worth
[Music]
it they are not getting much money there
oh they will get that one though damn it
I'll get this
one yes I have all the money in the
[Applause]
[Music]
world no sorry that was by accident it
better be a short game and a new
one
a
what ice sking
yay okay not not difficult not very
difficult and yet and yet uh we
lose baby steps asking for options could
K I see that hold on now oh God oh God
oh God oh God God yeah be careful
Ki no the middle is just really
dangerous right now oh okay here we go
oh God oh God oh God oh God here oh God
oh God oh God oh God oh God oh God oh
God did you see
that
yay
wow a skills those are some math gaming
skills that I have just presented to
you level
nine add an extra nine to that and then
that's what I Really
[Music]
Deserve feel like Japanese people didn't
make it in last time so I'll give them
one more one more
offer of a
Japanese uh
help give them a chance to I feel like
they're a little bit slower with typing
in the
numbers I'll give them a chance you guys
be nice too and give them a
chance yes say really
[Music]
quick ah oops it uh create
room okay
[Music]
got gave you a head
start let's
go this person has my name in his uh
name he's my he's my
child 57
41 but I feel like the people who made
it into this team are all kindhearted
Sweet
People
yes did you lay this egg no I only
hatched all of these eggs oh I already
feel the
lag
M no I are you getting kicked
out oh wait no I think we're still we're
still in I think they're still
in let's just have fun together even if
it's super
laggy you know what you do I get
Daisy she is
me okay oh my God already lagging here
oh bero is a rare Choice oh Berto is
very happy and thanks you for choosing
her or him connection is
unstable
uh wow slow motion are we in The Matrix
or
something wow nice
[Music]
job oh
no oh
no let's
[Music]
go let's
go oh my
God I don't even hear music
no
a are we still on the same team we kind
of got kicked out
there am I all
alone all around me
[Music]
finally kind of
sad I was just happy being with you guys
for even even a slight tiny moment I
felt like we had a connection uh it was
it was weak and it was poor but we had a
connection oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh man don't don't blame
[Music]
yourself okay here it is
guys so sorry Japanese Bros nice
[Music]
43 thanks for the membership
welcome s snil welcome
we
America America right he's Amer why did
you live I'm I'm not uh it's okay now
you don't have to help them is that
Spirit
[Music]
snare I think uh this might be Japanese
person if has then Lucky
21 okay we got only losers let's
[Laughter]
go yeah Japanese one in the beginning
said I am
American wow wow wow wow will we have a
good ping or not it looks good so
far it looks
smooth thank you for the membership
message coming aboard everybody and this
time not in slow motion
thank you m
Daisy M
Daisy is this everyone
yes oh look at those
jumps so fast my eyes can almost not
follow them way too quick can you slow
that down a little
bit okay let's play some more new Mario
Party
games learn some new gamer
skills
M hi
toad we want free play the same as
usual can we get to 50 games at least at
least 50 games but if possible even
more I said 2 hours and we're still only
at 1 and a half so we got a lot of time
still let's play I guess this one I
didn't play this one before
mushro mixup from Nintendo 64 hurry and
move to the pattern that matches the
sign I hold up ah sounds
fun let's do this doesn't sound too
difficult uh ground pounding works too
why would I do that no no the water
looks so good it's like we're in in
Super Mario Sunshine even though it's a
Mario Party 6 64 game
wait do
you I need to try this again okay okay
okay I let me in let's me in let's me in
oh there we
go okay this one losers losers losers
losers loser Luigi get out of here get
out of here
Luigi get out of here Lui no no you
sucker
[Applause]
okay this is luig this is why Luigi this
is why Daisy is never going to marry
you because you don't know the real
ladies
first stop sending me friend requests
we're already friends kfb friends
forever K has friends and
portrait Luigi let's go no more practice
time Luigi
please let's move
on Luigi this is not the real game this
is
practice
Luigi
Luigi Lui it might feel like the real
game but it's not okay okay
okay K's friendly p is
no he friendship party oh that makes a
lot more sense uh right okay move Mo
move move move Mo
move ground fing all of them
woo I I could have just stayed and
chilled it's not like they were
attacking me
right
uh why I I want okay now okay this this
is fine this is fine I was I was having
a little bit too much fun uh let me
choose a mini
[Music]
game
yo let's just choose this one this looks
like a Super Smash Brothers map
[Laughter]
bombs away ah I think I remember this
one try your best not to fall off the
island as it rocks and
tilts let's give it a
try okay oh God oh my
God oh my oh what oh my god oh the
headache that that caused
us
all oh oh I went swimming because you
know what it's kind of more dangerous to
be on ground at this
point sh M Senai please stop Min Senai
no
no please don't be so
aggressive oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God help me please oh oh my
God no why am I the best one to go
swimming it's probably the Senpai power
that Min Senpai has over
me oh
[Music]
man oh man winner oh yeah okay that's a
pretty cool winning pose I got to give
you
that I want to play it one more time I
have to practice
but it's good to at least know um how
these mini games work ahead of
time so that if I play it with some
other girls I at least kind of know what
to do that that no that already helps
guys please jump into the water do me a
favor we're going to play again just
jump into the water make it make the
pain go away quicker oh they
listen oh those Chads
they listen they actually
listen one
more
SK okay yeah yeah let's do this
teamwork let's win together
everybody see it's it's time limited we
we we just have to you know all win
together shut
up well that was inevitable who could
have seen that one
[Music]
coming
come okay I choose a different
game oh baby a
triple triple
kill
and shy guy says Ah it's like uh Simon
Says raise the same color of the flag
that shy guy raises he's going to go
faster and faster
okay let's go from top to bottom
now yeah I have a system now organized
ke
oh I'm yeah it's correct right okay
okay oh
sh what
yeah yeah it's not not that
difficult oh sh you little
[\h__\h] why would you do that he faked it
he faked it I didn't know he would do
that okay I don't trust you anymore then
okay yeah yeah yeah
yeah
left
right left oh
okay he faked it but he can't came back
to it oh
[Music]
man
oh I knew he was faking and I thought he
would do
[Music]
right oh
[Laughter]
man I do have to say though this the
like look at the boat textures it looks
nice the water looks nice too so I must
say that the graphics are really nice in
this in the remakes m m okay not really
much to practice here so I will move on
to the next game next one will be last
one for this group and then we switch
out the group
[Music]
again uh play this this one maybe ah
wait this one looks familiar from my
childhood as well Mario Party 2 yeah I
think I played this one fight for the
Disney Dan to grab the cliffs hovering
above the record collect the most Cliffs
to
win how does it
work yesterday I went on Amazon looking
for a very weird specific
thing and this just reminded me of it
what what what why am I not moving why
am I
dizzy what fight through the dis grab
how do I fight through it
how do I how do I fight through it she
just always goes in that
direction do you go
do oh I have to go the try to go the
opposite direction oh and then what ah
then I have to try to oh I are the
controls
reversed jump and punch oh oh God not
reverse controls you know I'm not good
at
that oh
[Music]
no
mine
okay okay I can do this oopsie so I was
saying what I was looking for
was a
gramophone not just a record player I
wanted specifically a gramophone because
that huge golden or brass depending on
which one it is uh a thing on top of it
just looks so
fancy and I thought it would it would
fit into my apartment nicely because I
you guys know I was trying to kind of uh
commit to like a art deco slash um great
the great gasby
style oh God oh God
no for my apartment Dam it Dam it Dam it
Dam it I wasn't starting off so
well no
no oh
triple finish okay well not that bad I
kind of caught up at the end I don't own
a record and honestly all all the
gramophones that I found on Amazon I was
actually surprised to find one to begin
with thank you guys for playing all of
them said in the description that they
do kind of work but not really well so
they're really only um for
decoration they they do play
uh some kind of music um but like with a
slow beat or
so apparently thank you for the
opportunity thank you too thank you for
joining you made it yeah but that's okay
with me I guess at least like it would
look really cool
M and it's it's a decoration element
that not everybody has in their
apartment right so why do you want one
because I need more decoration for my
apartment and because it looks cool
that's really all there is to it and
because the golden color works well with
the color theme that I'm going for uh in
my apartment cuz I wanted like green
gold for my for my green gold black for
my living
room yeah
I don't have many visitors but
still but still but I I didn't purchase
it yet cuz I'm I'm wondering if it's
possible to get a gramophone that
actually works rather than getting a
gramophone just for
decoration I would like to have one that
works to show it off as well but I guess
I wouldn't be getting it on
Amazon maybe maybe I need to go to a
antique Place 994 377 or to a music
Place do music places still sell
gramophones or I guess probably should
go
eBay how did you guys do
that tou
what
it oh the the Ping will be fun here I
think but let's let's give it a
[Music]
[Laughter]
try oh so far wait it might be fine the
Ping might not be that
bad at least it's not like spread all
over the world all all over all
continents just two continents in this
case oh okay oh it seems fine it seems
fine just you got to just despacito you
got to give me Daisy please
Mo let's do it let's hang out together
I'm glad you guys made it in even though
I didn't even uh help you guys
[Music]
I don't know the lyrics you guys know
the lyrics I can't speak Spanish
although I I wish I could it's [\h__\h]
[Music]
hot are you hungry tal uh no not that
much maybe a little bit but not that
much I'm I'm good but a burrito would be
nice
indeed and I think I've only ever eaten
a burrito when I was in Japan uh from
the convenience store
M let's do this one hard rope jump rope
jump yay flaming rope spins and Spins
jump the rope without touching new
Flames oh it's like oh jumping rope but
didn't do that since school
time I remember this one this one is a
classic for me oh Japanese Burr yeah and
the the convenience store in
7eleven 7 noi oh my god oh yay yay a
[\h__\h]
[Music]
damn it this is something that I should
be good at because if I remember back to
school time Elementary School and so on
and Junior High School only the girls
were doing this kind of stuff but we
were doing it in reality maybe you guys
are good at it if it's on a on a screen
and I would be better if it was in
reality let me try
again just die also being on the very
edge of it is not so cool I would like
to be more in the
middle can I change my position please I
had an unfair position yo these guys are
too
good
[\h__\h] can you guys uh thank you
did it became slower again after
speeding up
once oh these trolls I'm ready by the
way I'm ready Luigi when you are okay
okay okay okay
okay okay I got the ribm now I just have
to meow with it start
you little
[\h__\h] my finger was stuck on the
button finish a oh but that's fun that's
fun that's
fun that was fun good game GG and no
ping no lag that's good I think the
other time we did it is because it was
like mixed with someone from Japan
someone from Europe maybe someone from
America and so
on but these people either either have a
better connection or it's because
they're all from a similar region
maybe did you swear much when you were
living in Japan
it no because when speaking in Japanese
I don't swear that as much as I do in
English I'm so sorry this is not because
like it's it's just you know I don't
know when I speak English because
because
um I don't know I don't know why I don't
know why I swear so much I would like to
swear less I would like to be more say
so shoot the Rival tanks get hit twice
and you're out oh this is like a mini
game in Mario Kart part stage one stage
two oh I can even choose the stage here
let's just go with one I guess that's
like the easy
one but but uh at least my vocabulary is
so limited that I really only swear
um uh by saying [\h__\h] and [\h__\h] and [\h__\h]
and that's pretty much about
it mobing is not okay
ow two hits shoot upward wait upward
shooting
upward oh upward is like closer huh no
hey hey give me a chance what is lnr to
stra why is it
German I I did
damn it's going down it's going down oh
I'm yelling
timber you better move you better dance
oh
God lad REM movement what I never heard
of that word before it's not that's
that's
German I'm inan the tank M tank
oh God oh God stop no no no give
me now we're just looking at 3K of
people having fun with each other but
what is this
showdown oh oh
damn there
oh wait oh wait Co King is already dead
too look
at oh my God oh my God oh my my God oh
my
God
[Music]
what thank you guys for showing me that
show that was
entertaining I will not play that again
even though I could probably use some
practice in it but oh
well what was that
struggle H what should we do play this
one slot slot
Derby I played something like this in my
childhood like in real life drive four
laps but watch your speed going too fast
around the curves will make you spin out
so be
careful o look at those oh my the third
stage looks really difficult
is this one in first person though or
from that
angle wait that's so cute yeah yeah I
played that when I was a
[Music]
child oh oh fun
fun
wow
wow oh my God
wo w
w w
w I'm
excited this is my childhood but not
because I played this game on on Mario
Party but because I played it in real
life you guys played it too as a kid do
kids nowadays play this or is the only
thing they're playing with their phones
and their
consoles 3 2
one y ah you got to be careful in the
beginning there too
huh
[Music]
yay
wo oh my God so much
fun
W wo I don't even want to win this is
just I just want to
drive
w
w i had a lot of fun there even though I
was the last
one it's time
see I want to play
again game
start kids now probably think slot cars
was invented by Mario Party no way no
[Music]
way I want to be a car I want to be a
slot car
two
[Music]
one why why do I keep on
stopping o o
o I have a feeling though if I were to
play this against whole life members
that I would I would not be last one I
think you guys are just good at it
to I love that game but let's play a
different
one next up I played this one before
probably this one too this one too oh
God baseball
[Music]
my Japanese Bros they love they love uh
they love the
baseball
yeah oh yeah or do they do they I think
they do golf and baseball is like the
most popular sport in Japan I
think and what oh god and oh
H oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh h
oh oh
baby cool okay uh I never I never played
something like this before in real
life uh I did see like like batting
centers like this before but I never
tried it out before I would no wait I
did before at a convention in
Brazil out of all places who oh my
God the
Ping the
Ping oh oh my God oh my God oh my God
I'm a
natural
totally [\h__\h]
hey
[\h__\h] oh come
on again one
more yeah that convention had like so
many crazy things uh that you could do
so many
attractions and it was kind of
weird they had a like a sword fighting
ring as well which I tried too and and
they had a quiddit area
W [\h__\h]
you come
on ah ah
[Music]
oh
W hey I was doing pretty well but these
guys are just too
good I wasn't playing through
OBS but I'm playing for a game capture
card and these people are probably not
playing play for a game capture card but
I'm not going to blame it on that okay
okay I think we already played enough
games thank you
guys I'll do one more group LEL
10 you C were added hell yeah hell yeah
I'll do one more group of people
okay so you guys try to get into the
last
group one more one
more could I got to end it at a decent
time today to prepare for the cookie
baking
tomorrow and also get some decent sleep
although I feel like I I won't be able
to sleep early tonight because I napped
so much to sleep the pain
away
M well well well let's hope for the
best I hope the cookie baking goes well
I never cooked cookies before baked
cookies before and I gotta be honest
I'm already cheating because I'm not
making the the um the the the the the
thing myself I bought H I bought the the
the the the the the the the batter yeah
I already bought the cookie
dough I have to like roll it out and put
it into shapes but like I bought two
different types um I bought the one that
I need for the uh vanilla Kile um the
vanilla
how would I call them
horns they they are really really good I
love them so much but that one I think
is is better to buy pre-made Dough
because I would definitely [\h__\h] it up
now the other one probably wouldn't even
be that difficult to make myself but I
would need like a mixer like a cooking
machine but I I don't have one yet and I
mean I'm going to cook like buy one
sometime eventually but I didn't feel
like buying one yet so I just bought
pre-made cookie dll you guys are not
even that mad about it thank
you and it will definitely save us a lot
of time and a lot of trouble so the
other one is just normal uh
M and and for that with that I will try
to make linta Alan and also just some
random normal ones that I will decorate
with like um I bought I bought a I
bought um sugar coating and chocolate
coating I don't know if I'll use both of
it um but yeah and I also bought like
some some um some decoration like
chocolate sprinkles and rainbow
sprinkles
uh now one problem that I had was um
I'll talk about it tomorrow never mind D
I'll talk about it tomorrow free 51 free
free free easy code yeah frosting yeah
frosting I have like sugar frosting and
and chocolate
frosting overall it really uh shouldn't
be too difficult I guess I I looked at
um the the guide welcome everybody I
looked at the guide how uhhuh how uh to
make cookies and it didn't seem that
difficult it's really just rolling out
the dough and then putting them into
shape I guess oh all all the beginners
nice I'm the best one out of
[Music]
here yeah it should be super easy so
we'll uh we'll spend most of the time
just really putting the cookies into
shape and then yeah making them look
cute and I think that's good um because
yeah then I can uh also be on the same
table as when we did the pumpkin uh
carving rather than uh on the kitchen
counter and that will be easier for me
cuz I can sit down and work while
sitting and it it will be it will be
easier I think yeah I'm looking forward
to
it I'm excited I hope I hope all goes
well and last group I am
Daisy o
yeah yeah baking temperature now
shouldn't be too difficult to set the
right
temperature I am a little bit worried
about the lensa Alan though I hope uh
it's going to work
well I'm just going to use the jam that
I have in my
fridge eh should should be
fine
um Sky scoop I'm excited I want to eat
cookies
M
cookies next week by the way we'll be
making a gingerbread house if I find the
right things for it I've been having
some trouble finding like gingerbread
building
[Music]
sets but I I'll I'll make it work
somehow worst case I'll make the dough
myself and just make the house make
literally everything from scratch I hope
it will not come to this I would like to
have at
least like a pre-made dough or so
H
anyway yeah I I have literally I've been
looking at the supermarkets recently all
the time and I just cannot find
gingerbread building stuff anything
nothing Co Island Ice a this is like ice
cream building I like that let's try it
out keep an eye on the Shadows to catch
the falling scoops of ice cream catch C
your most Scoops to
win hate to say it but try Amazon I
looked on Amazon 2o and that will also
be my last minute solution I found like
sets that have like um the shapes to to
cut out the the shape of the
house oh my God this reminds me of 31
ice
cream I love 31 I bask and Robins in in
in English I guess they call it uh saan
ice cream oh move
in in
Japan and they have my most favorite ice
cream from all over the world La San is
my favorite ice cream yo no h i love
haing DTS and all those other ice creams
but no other ice cream can beat La
potion sa one start I wonder if you guys
have it in the
American uh Baskin Robins oh God there's
some lag
here give me yeah what is that matcha
matcha
pull oh God the leg oh God no it's mine
no it was supposed to be mine it's
lagy Yoshi No Yes
mine no the
leg oh Yoshi doesn't have a single one
no give Yoshi one give gray one I'll
give that to
you move move no are you guys suffering
because of the lag too is it not only me
oh God no oh God oh
God we try this one
again the laugh potion s s one is a like
a berry taste ice cream with some
chocolate Hearts mixed into it have you
guys seen it before in the American bask
and
rins cuz I think
I think that one time when I was in
America one time only for a very short
time in in San Francisco I think I
checked and they didn't have it I
think I want to try this
again is it for Valentine's Day no they
have it throughout the whole year in
Japan but maybe it's not so popular in
America and they only have it for a
short time or just not at
all that would be
unfortunate okay
H mine yay going well going well that's
also mine wa waa I'm on the road [\h__\h] it
it h Drop it like it's cold oh god oh
yes
M oh it's so heavy w
wow look at my ice cream
yay oh and I mine mine looks the most
delicious too I like I like the fruity
flavors the refreshing I love me some
sherbet as well
M wish she saw maybe I eat some ice
cream today I wonder if it's okay
because of the dentist appointment
should be
fine I have some hag and DS in my fridge
actually okay what next something we
didn't play before
uh Spotlight swim we haven't had a
versus game in a while so side stay out
of the spotlight team side all of you
must shine all three search lights on a
solo player together
o he that sounds really difficult I'll
be the one on the solo side for
now yes H and duts it's called La potion
31 they have it in the US I just checked
white chocolate Ras yes yes yes that's
it yeah
oh I can
die hey I got caught oh wait no I want
to no no no no
oh oh no
no you can't catch me you can't no you
can't catch
me no no no no no
sneaky b no no prison break let's go
start don't tell them where I am don't
tell
them stop following
me I can't die for so
long oh that's tough
tough my moves are probably too
predictable
oh oh I be winning
[Music]
get I think the solo side in this game
might definitely have an
advantage
um I think I want to give it a try on
the other side it seems really
difficult uh just got to keep on diving
and then you're good un unless the diver
is really
predictable it's really not that
difficult okay Wario you'll be the diver
good luck to you I broke out of prison
successfully thank you thank you thank
you you will not get rid of me that
easily
kfp so actually has the greatest disadv
out in this one oh they already already
okay if you think
so AIO seems to have a lot of confidence
in this didn't even feel like
practicing start okay I'll trying to do
my best here oh God that was that the
lag oh oh no oh God oh
God oh God
he's trying to do it without diving oh
but there there he goes there he oh
oh we got him
yo winners we caught him in the
corner
wow we're pretty good at
this okay choose oops no no no not the
course select the course ah uh no no no
we can stay in free play no no that was
by accident that was by accident we're
not done yet
guys go back go
[Music]
back does this mean that I was just
really good at this
game well it's not my first time
escaping from prison you know I found my
way out
a few times
before oh is this stupid or lose
it try to pop your rival St ah team
sides steer steer clear until you reach
the
goal oh I would like to be uh not on the
solo side here Yoshi you can have a
go this reminds me also again uh about
another thing I did in my childhood a
few times um
uh
[Music]
literally this what they're doing
here uh tube tubing in the snow I don't
know what to call it oh God oh God the
lag the lag though oh you can I can stay
back oh damn I didn't
realize like down down the hill have you
guys ever done that it's a lot of
fun it was really addicting
it's sledding but with a tube yeah you
sit in a inside of a I think it was uh
just yeah tube like
this uh okay
break
oh no no
no
yummy I'll give it a
try it's common in the mountains is that
so snow tubing yeah it's called Cuban in
Canada oh I can imagine the
Canadians oh liking to do
that okay we're still alive we're still
alive oh God oh God God
God so
far I'm so good
yum now stay behind a little bit okay is
there a time limit oh God oh God
we won because of
me bow to your
[Music]
queen wow you guys are so impressed by
your potential I don't know why you guys
are surprised was
obvious this was just obvious which one
should we
do something where the lag isn't so much
of a problem oh I love this one I want
to play this
one yes Mario Party 3 jump in the I feel
like we played it
before H wait two people only what do
you mean two people
only did the other people dip why is
this only two
[Music]
people as if they're there couldn't be
it's a Dell
game I want to sorry I will I I who who
will endless who will be the lucky one I
think Donkey
Kong I want to play it I want to play it
sorry you guys have to wait a little bit
only one
moment oh you better be bad at the game
Donkey Kong you I
chose I chose you for a reason you're
the chosen
one don't practice for too long Donkey
Kong yeah
okay but but don't don't fail too early
we want to have a little bit of fun
right okay
it hey boring
boring boring couldn't even show my Pro
skin
it's
boring if I press play again can I
choose the a different person I don't
want to choose the same
person oh I better do it like
this I'll give someone else a chance on
a well with
meel was Donkey Kong a gentleman or was
Donkey K Kong just really really bad at
the game
I'll give you all a try I
guess good job are
you please don't fail too early I mean
very gentlemanlike but no need for
that I don't need that much of a
handicap oh god oh
motion winner what are you
[Music]
doing are you comedian you guys should
join whole life
honestly g
k h no way that you're so bad at
it what is going on you guys
suck and Yoshi didn't get the the turn
yet right what is your excuse for
sucking so
bad it was his pink no
[Laughter]
way y see oh well that was that was just
that was just that was because of a
different
reason but Yos see um I'm I'm counting
on
you you'll be on the inside then I I
would if I had a
choice all
right game on your see
it's not fair though because Yoshi can
in FY um fly a little
bit but I guess at least not in this
game oh
[\h__\h] the moment the moment this comes
in they die like little
flies oh oh losers all of you Los
oh I
feel I feel like I have a big pee PE
energy right
now Pizza Pizza I remember this one yes
yes P up to Goble as much of the Giant
Pizza as you can pepperoni and crust
take longer to jump okay no problem I
ate a lot of pizza yesterday but I still
want to eat the more pizza Donkey Kong
has nice teeth Donkey Kong has the best
teeth let's go with uh Donkey Kong
strong
first let's go let's eat some pizza M so
you guys get something from the good
time that I had
yesterday I want to share with you guys
a little
bit okay I'll go I'll go here
now fun oh yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy
yummy m
[Music]
simum
Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum pineapple pizza
good
chice I I think I said this before but
mostly the people who say they don't
like uh pineapple
pizza it's [\h__\h] most of those people
have not even given it a try
yet eat all the pizza look at my did you
see my strategy I'm not going in a
circle oh God they're fast they're
actually fast oh God I got to eat faster
I was legit just enjoying my pizza here
finish no
[\h__\h] oh damn I'm sorry we actually lost
because I wasn't doing my bestest I
wasn't smashing the buttons that well oh
well that's okay one pizza is enough
actually it was two I guess we ate one
in
practice and
[Music]
next which one is a lot of
fun what was that sound was that you
that's so cute bops this was a Dell game
too
[Music]
right what about speed hawy ah wait oh
that sounds like fun not to Shell until
your Rivals goal the first team to score
fre goals wins okay Switching Partners
uh to
[Music]
Yoshi
okay okay this one is hectic yeah I
probably will not do well in this one uh
uh uh uh oh God because I suck at uh
table uh soccer as well I I'm so bad at
it I'll just stay up here
maybe I'm the worst oh God I'm the worst
at table
soccer Tish fball no no not my
thing or any of these kind of like table
games
what the
[Laughter]
[Music]
[\h__\h] I'm
sorry w
can we change okay we can change teams
like that okay let's give uh Wario a try
Wario Wario there we
go everyone gets a chance to play with
their boss to impress me this is the
moment guys this is the moment your
chance for a promotion oh God I'm in the
back it's like Wario's relying on me
unless Wario is going to oh oh wo wo
wo Warrior is going to protect me right
oh I'm sorry I was so close I'm so
[Music]
sorry I was play so
wild oh my
God
[Applause]
no holy [\h__\h] that's difficult okay but
changing
game last game maybe I want to play more
but we're already over time
[Music]
uh beach volleyball okay another team
game beach volleyball return the ball
with in the fre volleys again I suck at
playing these kind of games but let's do
it we cannot run away from
we cannot hide uh I'll give Donkey Kong
another
chance last
one beach volleyball beach
volleyball played volleyball sometimes
uh
serving in school oh
interesting
jump wait okay jump ah but when you do
this you don't have a
jump oh god oh that's tough oh that's
difficult oh I keep on serving I was
always so scared to serve in school to
serve the the ball in school oh
man cuz I had the weakest Thro ever oh
god oh w w w w okay I mean we tried
Donkey Kong you got the biggest hands
out of all of us you got to rock this
one
how wait
what uh
what do I have to
jump wo
whoo oh nice okay that's the first time
we actually worked as a team that beach
looks amazing though holy
[\h__\h] oh no
wa oh God we're all bad at this one
going to be the first to score seven
points can we do it can we do it
probably not
hey okay one
point and I
ser and two well when we start serving I
think the person is an advantage uh our
team is an
advantage okay okay let's do
this one-sided game
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
no I can't I don't know how to I don't
know I don't
know I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry
[Music]
thank you I don't know how to do
that oh nice nice we're serving again
let's win this
[\h__\h] go Donkey
[Music]
Kong
uh-oh nice nice
nice serving until the end let's go
Donkey Kong make me proud make my no no
no what a scuff volleyball match oh no
oh w w hey hey he we so close to
it oh God oh God oh
[Music]
God oh my God oh my
godu Ren t b
no [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] that
was a great last fight though I think
I'm so Sor I threw it at the
[Music]
end we could have won
it Panic is my worst any
well that was so much
fun see this totally worked out we can
do this more often in the future but now
in the next weeks I have to practice
Mario Kart yeah level
up yeah Mario Party with you guys not a
bad idea hope you do this again in the
future definitely will I want to give
you all a chance to participate
thank you guys we're going to read some
super chats I think and I have no idea
where I left off last time but I'll see
you guys in my office uh let's let's
move on I guess right away and going to
put down Ki I
think thank you guys for trying to get
in and thank you to everyone who made it
in and thank you for always giving me
Daisy I must say respect to the K of
people they know how to read the room
definitely thanks for the stream thank
you too hopefully I can get it next
stream hopefully yeah I got to give it a
try I I always say that people who have
been uh in the game before the same
stream shouldn't try again but next time
we play Mario Party Superstars and I
will um say I will mention that everyone
who was able to come in last time U to
please not try to participate uh in this
time okay yes chat to streamer yeah you
guys have good manners
M yes very reasonable people yeah I like
saying K of people it kind of rolls off
the tongue
well when talking about you guys even
though you guys are not really people
you chimpin but
still okay let's see what does my how's
the office looking like is it cleaned
up
uh it's a big looking like a big man
mess
here looking like a big old mess can I
bring my burp with me I
wonder uh office here we
go oh ho ho ho T the
season all the way
outside are you guys sick of Christmas
music
already I listen to a lot of Christmas
music yesterday at the pizza party and
today at the dentist trying to calm
myself down and and I got nope not yet
not yet oh maybe you guys also don't
have much opportunity to listen to the
uh Christmas music anyway just like me
still in the mood right yeah I agree and
I was able to write down a bunch of
songs uh which existence I forgot
because I'm planning to do a Christmas C
next week um uh you guys might have
heard about this new uh F system that we
have this it's become a bit more
complicated but it seems honestly
manageable at least for me
so I even I even uh looked up if they
have uh in this in this uh service that
um we might be using a lot in the future
called K fun like if it's on kfun then
usually we can uh use it but they had
they had a the Falco song The Rock me
amads they have it on there so I thought
it was like impossible I didn't think
they would have German songs but they
have Falco songs they have the rock Meo
songs so I can sing it for you guys at
some point yeah
the I'm not really a big fan of Falco
but he does have a bunch of uh famous
German songs so that one and and another
one that was really really famous I'll
try to learn from you guys for you
guys yeah yeah so I will try my best to
put up an interesting playlist but but
it won't be in the coming up one because
it will be a Christmas themed Cal all
the tacky Christmas songs all of
them and some some Christmas songs that
you may not have heard before because
they're more on the new side and but a
lot of old ones yeah yeah the the chromy
S maybe I'll sing that one too or or rap
it I think it's like a low key
rap um let's put on a different bgm
unless unless Mario party has anything
good to offer here
uh can I get out of this
menu do you have anything good
[Music]
oh that's too
energetic Silent Night silent night I
sang that one last year I
think oh this is a cute
bgm I think it's a bit too
quiet are you hearing this wouldn't this
be nice as a super chat reading maybe
not also toad is constantly screaming in
the background who wants to hear that
yeah
woohoo
[Music]
W but yeah in case you didn't hear it um
for uncraft streams in the future
um until now we were doing it pretty
carelessly and that was fine but in the
future we will have to be more careful
so um not not as easy as before um but I
I'll still try my best to make my unar k
um not too different from the usual ones
but yeah I think you know the songs that
I sing in Koka are mostly well-known
songs I think so generally shouldn't be
too much of an
issue
yeah but there are some upsides as well
uh I don't know I don't know if you've
seen it yet yet maybe someone else like
Ci did it already but we can we can turn
on super chats from now on and the on
archive streams as
well so I guess that's at least
something I don't know if cie already
did
it yeah that's good right
M yes yes
yes yes yes yes
okay
um uh I should put up different
decoration I said I was going to switch
it out let me close the game I want to
play different music I will redecorate
the
office uh
soon I saw that some new decorations
came in as well thank you guys for using
# Kat balls to uh submit your decor
ation for my Christmas tree and my
office thank you
everybody yeah sorry that I haven't
really been switching them
out and let's see what could we use as
music
[Music]
today audio
stock I want a Chill song i s I'm
getting headache again that is not good
I need to drink more water
Maybe
for that's bad what are the actual
LCS that's
[Music]
B
for something like
that bito was
better
oh uhhuh
you know whatever the new rules are Ki
will will keep on doing what Ki usually
does um keep on breaking the rules like
she usually does let me mute the audio
and try to sing
along
okay oh burrito
[Music]
I
FY
the oh oh no
[Music]
[Applause]
no Daddy
[Music]
the Y who is the
Y
for let's go
[Music]
Dy oh
quoit
fore foree
[Music]
crypto give me those
favorites foree
[Music]
ELO
SP I'm so sorry I sent the whole song
I'm probably going to get the mc8 for
this one for the first time in my
life that was the full song it was so
accurate obviously that's going to get
the mc8 how could it not be that was so
recognizable e my ears excuse me I was
so focused on the lyrics I couldn't read
your reaction
nail it oh thank you thank you can you
repeat all of that shut up I cannot no
no no perf oh thank
you that sounded more like the
incantation for demon summoning than the
actual song so you'll be fine um rude
excuse me I was singing a famous song
called despacito you probably just don't
know it you were living under the ground
for the past 20 years probably
uh boring what a boomer you are English
yeah I guess there's an English version
that would be so easier to
sing El Spanish I don't need an English
version Spanish is
my zero language I learned it before
drumman
yes I learned some Spanish from Rihanna
before yes yes Rihanna mhm
I was not summoning the death of hell
no can you say something in Spanish
then um was I not just saying a lot of
things in Spanish
[Music]
foree
you didn't hear Google santes Now roll
the ARs
am
to wait wait don't
[Laughter]
listening quck
I know it's h but for me it's funny
because it sounds like y
or okay enough of those ja ja uh we have
to read some super chats okay behave
everyone behave chat you know what will
happen if if you don't
[Music]
behave SP
did I finish reading everything that was
in my Excel
[Music]
file I feel like I did because I didn't
ask you guys to remember a number did
I did I tell you guys where I left
off oh [\h__\h] I don't know where I left
off uh
uh what what did I left leave 130 oh oh
really oh
[Music]
okay wait this is wrong though this is
not the right one let me
see thank you graas poor
ESP you're welcome have to save you
you're welcome in in uh
Spanish how do I say you're
welcome
Dada all those Spanish Bros in the chat
oh man
denada
[Laughter]
okay okay 1 140 something around that
okay okay we're still in the new outfit
for real Super Chat y
[Music]
uh3 I'll I guess I'll ah I think this is
where I stopped in front of unity chat's
red super chat I
think oh I found it I
[Music]
think okay
you read mine in like the last five
uhhuh really I don't see yours here
what I don't see yours
here you guys remember which one was the
last one I
read you can now add hea to your desk
yeah now I actually remember what that
means Al I can move the tensal one back
to
the uh back to the middle
oh no no what the [\h__\h] no
no no no no no no no no no uh last
stream you left a flim flammable
really this is what I wanted
all the poy is in the way
now I'm not eating Pokey right now
anyway
flame
flammable really but I don't see a flame
flammable around here oh I no I don't ah
here
ah but Typhon also isn't in the last
five here wait so did I read the unit
unit chat are you here did I read your
super chat you read one I love this
outfit the dress is amazing your legs
are dangerous and H I think I did yeah I
think I did and then I read up to here
SPX Pinky the pinky is the one I'm I
left off where where I didn't read
anymore I think frogy is lagging no
way un need chat is here right un
[Music]
Chad okay I think I know where I am
now SP SPX thank you for the
pinky this is too good thank you did you
just smash your head and roll it on top
of the keyboard or are you were turkey
I heard my name you're the first one
yeah doesn't mean that you're allowed to
leave yet though stay here stay
here thanks for the pinky and the
support I'm glad you like the new
[Music]
outfit and ven Shar thank you for the
red super chat M the outfit the room the
piano version of Sparks everything is
just so perfect and beautiful I'm so so
happy for you thank you yes um I'm glad
I commissioned the the room room for it
um I could have just like put something
together like for the first casual the
the first the first outfit the Casual
one the one I'm wearing right now um I
had a background but I just put it
together with like vector images from a
website um but uh which was fine too um
but for this one I commissioned
something early on to have something
beautiful and impressive for the
occasion now the thing is I'll probably
won't be using it that much uh but
yeah I I hope it was worth it I hope you
guys liked the the ballroom I'll try to
use it some more often maybe for the
coming up Christmas Koke yeah an elegant
Christmas Koke in my Ballroom why not
maybe I can place a tree in
it with with that angle it shouldn't be
too difficult to place a tree in
it please use your Empress outfit often
I am planning on it yeah M the wall
Scrolls when chef's kiss M yeah they're
pretty cool pretty cool references to
the H myth members get a throne and a
static sitting pose made I was thinking
of getting a throne too but I was just
not sure how that was going to work like
um because you know I don't look like I
sit down unless it's a throne that is
covered by a table in the front or oh
it's kind of difficult m
it it's just very difficult also because
of the layering even if I put like a
sitting animation on top of it like how
is that going to combine and and like
transition into my
body yeah I don't know a massive Round
Table oh there is enough space
for a big big big like a like a table
round like for for warriors for Heroes
for
[Music]
nights something would be nice yeah
something something with a throne would
be
nice I'll I'll think about
it it would be so cool if we had sitting
poses like rigged into us our
bodies that would be so
helpful anyway thank you ven Shar M
black rich and thank you for the red
super chat another red super for my
Empress my goddess and most importantly
my Tak breath taken
away You're cutie you're so sweet black
fren you're always so
Charming so kind you always make me
blush thank you so much for your
sweetness m
you're so sweet sometimes I doubt if
you're a chicken maybe you're like a
muffin or something like that or a
chocolate chicken chocolate chocolate
chicken
m yeah sitting on the throne would be so
cool
King HG I'm getting hungry now I'm
getting hungry why now every another
cold thank you for the red super
chat my attention looking super cute and
elegant glass we didn't have any issues
this time around oh you have no idea you
have no idea how glad I was to every
another
cult that was my biggest fear like
something failing again like technical
stuff oh man I can't I cannot imagine
what I would have done if that would
have happened
again thank God at least this time luck
was on my side M thank you every another
cult for praying for me and supporting
me behind the curtains right my chimpin
is always supporting me my from my back
and from my
front counting chickens thank you for
the red super chat that was beautiful
it's not like I'm speechless or anything
a was that after I performed
Sparks thank you as uh mentioned last
time there might be a special version of
it coming up on my channel around
Christmas
too
um yeah let's hope it works out I would
be uh
delighted yeah so for all the people who
enjoyed Sparks uh piano version sad
Sparks please wait a little bit longer I
want to put it up on my channel as like
a piano cover where I sing
along yeah thank you counting chickens
for your
support lost Traveler
[Music]
6493 J
poker what am I saying in Japanese Thank
You shadow Cross y of L thank you for
the pinky how can someone be so pretty
feels good to have such a majestic and
gorgeous oi you're so breathtaking thank
you you're
breathtaking every time I look at at you
Yulia you're so breathtaking that all I
can think of is eating you up you look
so
delicious oh that fried chicken
nness gorgeous you look so
crispy I'm hungry I'm hungry let me look
at the bottom of your bucket please let
me look what's deep down
there please I need to see I need to
check it quality control your T has the
do quality
control please
comply if you
insist I yes quality very good
indeed okay e me
pis
or SK thank you for the red super chat
say h although you have trouble in last
time what last time but you came back
like a phoenix your new outfit is so
elegant and full of surprise love you
kada
you hear that say say here here or
whatever you say via indeed thank you
Skye yeah there was no last time sky you
are a good chicken you know how to play
along you know how to read the air and
the room I'm proud of you sky thank
[Music]
you J swg thank you for the pinky
amazing outfit reveal thank you for
being awesome you divine Exquisite
Phoenix thank you
I try I try to do my best I try to come
up with good content um I'm I'm not the
most uh original person like there's
things that I would like to do but that
are just not possible as long as I'm in
this 2D body um and just other things
that I don't know how to do if I knew I
would probably be way more creative but
yeah
H I want to think of like more projects
though like
like streams that are not game streams
um you know something like the the host
thing that OKO Senpai did for example or
even just solo stuff that doesn't need
other people to call in either um I was
thinking because my brain is just so
empty if we can do like a a
brainstorming threed in the kfb um
members community
board uh sorry
uh if you guys would like to share your
ideas with me I might pick it
up thank
you maybe you guys have some good ideas
you want to share with me something that
I can
recreate
oh yeah if you are willing to cooperate
then I will make a friend on the
community board and then try to make
your idea come
[Music]
true thank you
for solo stream yeah SOLO and collabs
anything anything really that's possible
but but what I would like to uh like
ideas that don't really work is like VR
chat ideas because if it's something
with like a whole new world and a whole
new concept and all that that's going to
take so much time and effort and money
to create
um it's just yeah I would prefer to
First do my thing when it comes to VR
chat my idea that already exists but if
you guys have ideas of what I could do
outside of VR chat just you know like a
normal stream uh yeah relatively small
things really just uh you know
anything no I here some Mar please
no um but I don't know something like
uh uh I one thing that came up in my
mind but I don't know if if it's really
interesting or funny I mean I guess I
could make it funny is maybe like um a
stream
where you guys are the chat is applying
uh for position at kfb I mean you guys
are already hired of course but we're
just going to act as if this chat is
applying you're at a job interview with
kiata and we'll be in this office and I
I will you know interview you guys H and
and you will have to answer questions
collec l h and uh to get the job I guess
I was thinking of how to make it
interactive as well that's the only idea
I could come up with so
far yeah you like that idea oh that has
potential
oh we could
also uh while doing that we could have
you guys fill out job application so we
have more more and more more job
applications that we could work with and
um but I don't know if I want to do that
I just want to interview one chicken I
guess
but that could be a different thing a
separate thing maybe having you guys
fill out job
[Music]
applications potential potential oh Star
Fox yo my handw writing is fresh you
don't have to write it with your
hand H I know you guys don't have hands
you only have wings so just ride it like
with the keyboard or
so interviewing the hive mind
chicken okay let's think more about it
sometime
soon
yeah when you get promoted to shacho I'm
already a chatel but people call me Teno
because we started small I
guess yeah but if you think about it I
am the CEO not just a Tano Tano is like
a store uh manager but I'm definitely
more than just a store manager because
there's more than one stores but still
you can continue calling me Teno because
it's already just so so melted into our
brains yeah we started from the bottom
now we here still remember the day when
we created the kfp menu oh I still want
to do a stream sometime early next year
where I create some stuff from the
stream uh from the kfp manual and also
have you guys send in your
Creations as photos of the Yago burger
and the and the Phoenix burger for
example I definitely need to do that at
some
point yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah we will have to find out what put
in the STA sauce in order to make it huh
I'll leave that up to your
imagination coton thank you for the red
super chat thank you no text with it but
thank you sh sweet sweet cotton M thank
you I Dan David ask you too Dan for the
pinky your new outfit is so elegant and
beautiful just like you
Tanto thank you I mean I don't know if I
would call myself elegant in
general uh I think with the new outfit I
was able to show off an elegant cool
side of myself and I'm really happy I
could but if you look at me normally in
my main outfit or in my casual outfit
let's be honest I don't look very
elegant that's okay though I wasn't
aiming for it yeah but still I'm glad
that we have another look for myself and
as always I rock it
[Music]
M by the
way no let's keep it a secret let's keep
it a secret Jackson sha d as d sub d f
thank you for the red super
chat
sh everything is amazing thank you tel
thank you for watching F thank you for
checking in and supporting me on that
special outfit reveal stream thank you
for being there for me to support
me I appreciate it thank
you
Pono IIA
fov also sorry guys I have barely been
reading the messages from non Reds and
non pinkies but as soon as we are caught
up again I will read them uh every now
and then again I'm sorry about like
skipping on them what was that I feel
like I just heard a
[Music]
voice why did I just feel like I Heard a
Voice am I in Discord I'm not in
[Music]
Discord I'm not in Discord I feel like I
heard the voice
[Laughter]
my
brain H the Ghost of Christmas Past oh
no oh I also need to make a ah I need to
make a wait let me do it now before I
forget it um I mean I feel like I would
eventually remember but uh let me go on
the YouTube community board and make a
members only
post
and
Christmas movie
recomendations for
members watch along here
please uh preferably something that is
available on Netflix or
Disney
plus uh where's the plus whatever Disney
Plus or Amazon
[Music]
Prime
go you're welcome to send me
recommendations uh as a comment in the
community board on YouTube members thank
you a good film this time around please
what do you mean did we watch a
Christmas movie last
year I don't I don't remember did we
watch one last
[Music]
year I feel like we didn't we didn't
right
yeah I also kind of watch want want to
watch one that I haven't watched before
so no uh what was his name Kevin stays
alone at home even if there's newer ones
nowadays I don't care for it no more of
that um I also have watched The
Nightmare Before Christmas about a
million times I love it but no more
please h ah Home Alone ah the German
title is more like the one I
said um and yeah
says
alone that's uh I think yeah yeah I mean
Home
Alone yeah don't don't don't I we
watched good movies together before okay
the Grinch nah maybe not that one either
something that I haven't watched before
would be good but yeah that's about
that's a couple of the movies the
Christmas movies that I've seen already
so
Muppet maybe something
more
legendary
Tokyo Tokyo
Godfathers I feel like I know that one
is really good and famous but I feel
like I did I ah no I think I watched it
before let me see
uh uh I think I did
yeah yeah I did watch that one before
it's a really one though
M yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we'll
find
[Music]
something let's let's find a good movie
to watch if we have some popular demands
then I could later on collect those and
then make a poll for members only so
that you guys can maybe choose from that
unless I see something that looks really
interesting to me
personally okay continue
[Music]
youat Aran thank you for the red super
chat I appreciate it than k your outfit
is absolutely stunning and the whole
reveal was so much fun sad Sparks is sad
but also absolutely beautiful you're
such a great singer and so much fun to
watch you always prove to me while
you're my oi thank you ah that Mak you f
like um I I I was thinking you know
since it's an outfit reveal um that I
should sing something energetic and
something exciting something loud and
you know um
something you know like the original
Sparks H because I felt like if I were
to sing like like a piano slow sad song
uh I felt
like on such a important okay where I
got so many eyes on me that I wouldn't
be able to quite really grasp everyone's
interest but but then I thought about
you know I can't just bring in the OG
Sparks or hinoto whatever into this
Ballroom it must be more elegant so I
prefer to keep it more um according to
the concept rather than going for what
would be the most hype uh for the
audience and I guess in the end this
worked really well so I'm I'm relieved
I'm relieved I mean of course you know
with outfit reveals there's always these
lurkers who the very moment you show
them your head they're all going to
leave like no matter if you still have
options no matter if you still are
hiding your best secret weapon they are
going to leave the moment you show your
head which is so lame
but um for the sad spikes Rend
still so many people stayed so I was
happy about that I'm not mad or anything
because that's just how outfit reveals
work it's always the same
[\h__\h] it's always the same they can't
even wait one more minute to show what
accessories I have or what other
hairstyles or whatever
yeah I mean okay I understand some of
them are busy but I think so many people
really have uh not an urgent task to do
but still immediately
leave come on come on just stay one more
minute two more
[Music]
minutes I was thinking what I could do
to um counter that behavior um I was
almost thinking of like doing the the
the the piano
rendition before revealing the the full
outfit so like kind of making the lights
in the ballroom darker and but then you
would have kind of already even if it's
dark you would have kind of already seen
part of my
face so I was like nah maybe not I don't
know people might still leave just by
seeing
that
M put a big blue dot over your face
until the very
end that would be so triggering oh can
you imagine like like zooming up from
the from the feet to the head and then
the moment it reaches the head the head
is just a mo
Mosaic that would be so fun triggering
those people who immediately leave with
just a bunch of pixels on my head and
I'm like e what's wrong what what's
wrong were you not happy with
this what's the problem what's the
matter what do you got to say huh you
got a problem with my pixels with my
face you better stay until the end to
see my
face I would be tring you guys too but
you guys stay until the end anyway so
yeah that's
fine or I'll give you guys I'll add a
secret function to YouTube I'll give you
guys a secret password that you have to
type in and and you guys will be able to
see the real face already because I know
that you guys are loyal and # woke #
Yol you can see it early on but all the
lurkers will not be able to see it
n it's it's okay it's um it's a bit
disappointing but it it is how it is
it's how it has always kind of
been yeah uh AI D flaming pants D Sal
for his beeds thank you for the red
super
chat h k your performance of sad Sparks
put me into tears oh it is haunting
beautiful in both languages you are so
beautiful in your new outfit bless you
and hooka papa for bringing life to such
a majestic mature outfit thank you yes
big props to hooka Papa of
course and uh yeah I I think I was a
good idea to cuz Sparks is originally an
English song so it was a good idea to
add a little bit of Japanese there
because when there's so many people
working I'm sure there's some Japanese
people in there as well and you guys
already know if you are here last chat
reading you know the reason why I really
put in the Japanese lyrics because of
the looping um looping
[Music]
Melody so it was a good opportunity and
I I wrote that Japanese translation
really
quickly H so it could have been better
if I spent more time with it but it's
okay I guess I tried to like do a direct
translation while still rhyming even
though Japanese
songs I've noticed this after listening
to millions of Japanese idol songs Jpop
songs they usually don't rhyme which I
found so fascinating because German
music and English music they always try
to rhyme but for Japanese music they
don't I don't know how was it with
K-pop I I do not know why it doesn't
feel wrong though when listening to
Japanese
music and it's not like it would be
super difficult to rhyme but it gives
them more freedom I guess it it still
flows nicely while when I would hear an
English or German song without Rhymes it
would feel so
wrong
H that that I think is so
interesting any people who can remember
if K-pop usually rhymes
[Music]
yeah they they do focus a lot on like
the
syllables which is um one thing I think
that maybe holds them back a little bit
in terms of Music
Creation uh because there's like barely
any how to say how to describe it they
don't go off into like belting the notes
like
w w w that much you know what I mean
because they're very focused on fitting
uh fitting the syllables into the
melody which for me has always been fun
I I love singing Jpop songs because it's
I I like the way that the songs are
created but there's just like a really
big difference on how they are written
and how they created
anyway
Mo for the red super chat the new outfit
is so amazing I love it so much thank
you I love you too okay I guess you said
you love my outfit and not me but
whatever I'll tell you how it is because
I know you love me too moose you don't
only love my outfit right yeah yeah yeah
yeah
thank you for your support I'm glad you
like it Jake 33 w d a trash boy D nin
diesel Dan H
Dan great Victory 1510 Dan you guys know
what I noticed not only Korean viewers
influx and Korean Clips influx but also
I've been getting a lot of fan art from
Korean artists as
well yeah and they're really good I want
to say come to all the Korean people for
spreading awareness of kfp all over the
world and recently and especially in
Korea
recently yeah Korean artists very
talented they found me y
[Music]
y please keep on sharing the love for
kfp yes oh my God I'm so hungry my my my
belly just um feels like there's Nails
stinging into
it great Victory 1510 dun die
971 son you you write in uh English
though so I guess you understand English
thank you for the r Super
Chat I love your new outfit I love your
voice I love your streams in general so
many hours of amazing content thank you
for being such an amazing entertaining
Majestic BB much love
thank you you're so sweet you love
everything about me huh
a thank you
mi that is those are some really really
kind words and they touch my heart thank
you I appreciate it so much I work hard
to give you guys good content I'm glad
you see it as amazing
content it seems like my work does pay
off yeah snack break and uh well I have
a problem right now the problem why I'm
not snacking the reason why I'm not
snacking is um dentist told me to for
the next couple days try
to uh what or do not eat um colored
things that stain
much at least for the first 24 hours
like take it very serious and then later
uh do what you want I guess but try to
like not eat like anything stainy like
Curry or drink wine or coffee and you
know chocolate does stain I guess so no
snack yeah I didn't know what to eat for
dinner tonight so I I have one piece of
bread that I will be filling with ham
and cheese I hope the ham is okay I
didn't know what else to put in it I
will read that eat eat that after the
the stream m
yeah ham should be fine yeah well he
said uh you can eat rice and potatoes
and all that yeah but like I'm not going
to just eat raw rice and potatoes maybe
one thing that could probably work is
cabonara
right wait I have ham and I have egg I
could make a cabonara
too I don't have cream but the real
cabonara you make without cream anyway
[Music]
well that would that would
work
H that that shouldn't oh wait the egg
yolk no but does the egg yolk
[Music]
stain not shouldn't be that bad right
not like red wine or something
[Music]
a I don't have any parmesan though I
think yeah I think to for today I'll
just eat uh the bread and hope it fills
me
[Laughter]
up probably not much but oh well yeah
I'll see I'll see or can I eat it
now I think I can go longer if I eat it
now can I I just have to cut my bread
and put put some ham and some cheese in
it would you wait for
me no more Mario Party yeah we're done
already we played for 2 and 1 half hours
it was fun we'll do it again sometime
we're Super Chat reading now and having
a chip chat yeah yeah yeah
okay please wait will be taking care of
you uh in the meantime be nice to KI be
nice to kot he has power over all of you
now
[Music]
M thank you for
waiting um
[Music]
smoothie came up when I was making the
the ham and cheese sandwich and she was
like meow
meow she totally went ham over the ham
so I gave her a tiny piece of the ham
just a tiny
one she went ham over the ham get it get
it get it I thought of that while I was
standing in the kitchen I was like got
to tell him that one
[Music]
maybe maybe I should show off that I'm
eating
this way people
will have a visual to visualize it I'm
not eating what you see but close
[Music]
enough
M hi smoothie you want to H
M
M whose legs are those good
question who's missing legs in the
[Music]
chat congrats on getting fried y
oh no that's where
they my legs really oh no I'm still
intact for
[Music]
now what are you blaming me for I
F I thought chicken legs can
regrow if you water them well
M
no yeah you won't need I just did it to
help you because you guys always talk
about wanting to fly but you keep on
relying on your legs so what did I do I
ripped out your legs so that you don't
have to rely on your legs anymore and
force yourself to fly and now you'll be
so much Freer you have the whole world
ahead of
you since you always want to travel
around the world the whole world see all
the continents and all the oceans how
considerate yeah
right I I I knew that was your dream
guys travel around the world it's not
going to happen with your chicken
legs
yeah you can't get very far with those
you got to fly
[Music]
you're welcome you're
welcome that's the real reason why I was
holding you guys last
night mle
[Music]
mle wow
joh kind of hard to read though
[Music]
cute and you know
what I did that
yesterday
after after finishing that deadline
thing after already being super tired
but I felt inspired I wanted to draw you
guys I was already so
tired and I was in a food coma from that
yummy Pizza H do you guys want to see
Pizza
photos I sent them I told you guys
before that we have a a food uh channel
on Discord right where people don't
really post that much U but yesterday I
spammed it with live documentation of my
pizza
Adventures um and they they were like
like their mouths were watering I got a
lot of reactions out of my pizza
photos JMA was like it's 2:30 a.m. and
now I want
[Laughter]
pizza I'm sorry no I'm not okay so let
me show you some stuff I guess this
should be this should be safe to show
that was
show okay so basically as I told you
very serious pizza
making this is a photo of the
[Music]
dough with some ingredients at the
bottom the best ingredients pineapple
tuna uh corn
parmesan uh and the one on the right is
uh
um
uh what was the word uh I forgot the
word I forgot the
word I forgot the word garlic yes uh but
there were more ingredients like as I
said we also put the pepperoni on the
pizza with the pepperoni the pepperoni
with the pepper Bon
yes
M and then the first pizza the first
pizza already was a big success
surprisingly no there was only one
failure uh on that night of pizza making
now look this was the first one
M this was before before it was put into
the
oven was like this and the tuna
with the onions and the basil and the
mozzarella and the corn M yummy and then
you he really just put it in there for 1
minute and it was done it was so
good
M let me show
[Music]
you mhm m
the first pizza of the
day don't worry no
[Music]
Reflections
mhm
[Music]
T doesn't that look amazing yeah one
made it because the oven is like a
strong the like a TP like a proper Pizza
Oven not just any oven it's a pizza
[Music]
oven so the speed was pretty nice we
kept on like eating the pizza once it
was done and then uh quickly soon after
we had another Pizza it was like a like
eating in a restaurant like you know
like a menu where they give you like
five course is but every course is pizza
but because of the pacing and us only
like cutting it up and then only eating
like one piece of the pizza each it was
um perfect perfect balanced as all
things should
be uh we had a maybe I can show this
one round
two was a a classic margarita for the
margar fans out there look
M that little black crust is not a bad
thing it's a good thing
uhhuh look at that would you look at
that
oh perfect
[Music]
margarita
mhm that was round two
want to see another Raw
[Music]
One
M he had this proper like shovel as well
to put it into the oven like a big
shovel this is the pizza on the shovel
this was round free a pineapple
pizza
m m
[Music]
there lots of
corn and
[Music]
ham have to say the tuna was better in
this case we all I mean it was really
good too but something was missing
[Music]
something was missing but we weren't
sure what maybe more ham I think the
conclusion was it needed some more
ham
[Music]
M
M right
[Music]
round
four you guys don't really say salami
when it's on pizza right you guys say
pepperoni what you I say
again what do you actually
[Music]
say the pepperoni but what about the
pepperoni but the pepperoni is also
called
pepperoni and we
call we call that the greenish thing
feroni feroni and
salami what do you call the pepperoni
then
huh the pepperoni and the
pepperoni what no
way so this was another pie you can't
you can't even see the pepponi the
pepponi is buried underneath but it was
there so pepperoni with the pepperoni
pepperoni yeah you know what it is you
see it right now this was really good
too but nothing can beat a two tuna
pizza so we followed that one up with
another tuna Pizza I think um and
then uh and then and then and
then unbelievable but the dessert was
pizza the dessert was uh dessert
pizza
basically pizza dough put into the oven
without anything on it like naked
and then uh they put like Mar Maro on it
cream uh mixed with
cinnamon as a base and then on top of it
raspberries strawberries and uh a better
version of Nutella actually it was uh
like Nutella but uh it's like a more
healthy version of
Nutella
mhm this one's really good too
I must say I mean okay we did it for the
sake of the pizza but I think it would
have been even better as like a crap
just put the same [\h__\h] on the crap it
would have I think fit better but it's
okay this one's good too the
CP
M yummy
[Music]
yeah and actually I wasn't sure if they
were making dessert so I brought um I I
brought something as a dessert I thought
you know I got my
manners I brought um some really good uh
macarons from a famous um dessert place
in
Austria I did my part two I brought like
a a bunch of different macarons each one
different taste and then at the end I
thought that they wouldn't be hungry
anymore at the end but surprisingly we
still had some space for a little
macaron Mac macaroons and so we started
like doing uh uh uh rock paper scissors
over the macarons because every every ma
macaron was so popular
so uh we did Ro we did rock paper
scissors and then cut it into pieces
also one macaron into four pieces or
three
pieces yeah but it was yummy was yummy
so much food porn yesterday I
swear so good now I didn't play I didn't
participate in rock paper scissors I let
them play and then I was like I'm I'm
choosing this one because I brought them
I don't care and for Sumer was like you
you do you I want you guys to enjoy the
macarons pistachio was like the most
popular but they were all good I got to
get a bunch for myself
someday no more fuit teries and we're
done now but I did bring some pizza
home most of it I ate for breakfast but
I should have one small piece but I
can't eat it tonight because of what the
doctor
said I can't eat
it maybe
tomorrow maybe tomorrow I'll be forgiven
maybe tomorrow it's still
good put it in the blender and drink
no
[Music]
ew e he did say that if I drink it in a
straw it's
[Laughter]
okay no
[Music]
that's
disgusting all right I'm almost
done
sorry smaller in
hole that doesn't
work
yum m
okay back to Super
[Music]
chats you were
snake that's a good
argument well that is still past tense
[Music]
okay
okay sorry for
[Music]
waiting hi smooy I'm not done with
streaming I'm only done with eating
smoothie sorry to disappoint
you if you're going to be a good baby
then I'll give you a tiny piece of ham
later
[Music]
okay Leo how thank you for the pinky
thank you can an amazing way to start of
winter break ah are you a student winter
break that actually is pretty early like
I remember in school winter break
wouldn't start until the
23rd if if Christmas was like on a on a
weekday often we would still have to go
to school on the 23rd by the way we only
celebrate Christmas on the 24th so the
25th doesn't even really
matter yeah I remember being like
Christmas is tomorrow do we really got
to be at school now
what lame
[Music]
but I also got to say I was pretty lucky
for um hi oh smooy I was pretty lucky
for summer
vacation
hi she jumped up to the seat next to me
because our summer vacation was always
like so long I don't know if it was
because of the city I was living in or
so but I remember like when I was
playing em
RPGs um throughout the whole summer
absolutely grinding the [\h__\h] out of it I
remember that like the other mostly
German players they were never Austrian
players it was always the
Germans um like austrians were like a
rare
Pokmon H but the German players were
like you're how long how freaking long
is your summer location cuz it literally
was like three months long I'm not
kidding I had like three months of
summer
vacation and they were like how long is
this kid going to grind in this mm more
pachy this
summer she does not step outside for a
day it's fre moms in America too what
nice nice I just remember we had the
longest the longest summer holidays in
uh within everyone who I was connected
with true gamer yeah three months of not
touching Grand
yes when you grind you got to grind
seriously every day from from noon till
3:00 a.m. 4:00
a.m.
yeah it's serious business
in
a I was some good
times I lowkey miss
it h Pap pry D Anonymous 247 and thank
you for the red super chat I'm also by
the way surprised smoothie is cuddling
with me on the seat next to me good girl
sorry I was distracted by your
Perfection the dress the concert and
your usual inner energy that makes you
into the most amazing streamer I know
much love now and all always
Anonymous that is so
sweet the most amazing streamer you know
that is such an honor there are so many
more Amazing streamers out there who
like are so Innovative every
day like even within myth the most
Innovative streamer I know is within
myth and it's a Amelia Watson but thank
you for appreciating me too I do hard
work too within uh the limits of the
boundaries of my
skills thank you so
much unknown thank you for the pinky for
two pinkies which makes one red I can do
math yes yes you get a kiss for that
what an amazing outfit reveal stream I
was right we were saving the best for
the last you look absolutely gorgeous
this is definitely definitely my number
one favorite in both the outfit itself
and the reveal stream oh you really did
such an incredible job even when you
have to postpone the stream not your
fault at all thank you I agree you still
managed to make this the best outfit
reveal everything about this stream is
just Divine Exquisite I love this so
much my Oshi is seriously the absolute
best I
know unnown you
charmer you the sweetest thank you I
love you than you soon for your
sweetness I
know I don't know what to say you just
always choose the perfect right words
that make me feel relieved and
happy thank
[Music]
you
Kate Fafa thank you for the red super
chat sh so beautiful t oh hook papa is
my God now very enjoy today's party
Viana Viana indeed thank you for coming
to the
party yeah I'm glad you are one of the
invited guests I'm glad you came to the
party thank you
Fafa M Mah Mah Mah get those
kisses thank you so much for your
support very generous of you okay is God
yes indeed
[Music]
yes yes
cat for the red super chat
[Music]
and
for
[Music]
for was to's birthday on my outfit
reveal
happy birthday
[Music]
yes okay let's sing a happy birthday for
to happy birthday to you happy birthday
to you happy belated
birthday for toang happy
birthday to you yay oh I like how the
the party chicken icon still comes in
use
it's good that I didn't take it down and
just kept it there
huh nice and nice and
[Music]
nice C Pony thank you for the red super
chat oh my goodness it's beautiful thank
you thank you I am happy to hear that
you like it so much that you even see me
as a God yes oh my goodness is oh
godness actually you're missing one o so
I guess I guess you're not missing one
you wrote it on purpose oh my godness is
what you actually wrote yes am God in
the new outfit not only am Empress but I
am not surprised you see me as a
god thank you CS ply sh
[Music]
Jim Tracy thank you for the red super
chat this was absolutely amazing k your
new outfit is stunning and that
performance of Sparks was so beautiful
I'm so glad everything worked out today
this was absolutely worth the wait thank
you so much you truly are the greatest
oie thank you yes in in hindsight I'm
glad that um there was a delay because
then that way I was able to like put
together a few more things and and think
about what to say a bit more and all
that so yeah it was
good sometimes things are meant to be
like that even though it really seems
like the whole world is against you at
first that is actually a a good a good
um
philosophy or
so if you ever in a situation where it
seems like the whole world is up against
you and everything
sucks well that might be leading up to
something better yeah a good silver
lighting thank you thank you it happens
for a
reason yeah yeah yeah yeah there's
always Silver
Lining even if it all looks
dark
r k d thank you sigus thank you for the
red super
chat first chat ever oo the beauty of
your outfit reveal as well as the great
effort you put into it is astounding I'm
very proud to have you as my
oi oh it's your first Super Chat and I
am your oi thank
you a good chicken a good loyal #v #
yolk chicken I see thank you so so so so
much via
indeed Sig thank you soon please keep on
enjoying my streams
and supporting me
[Music]
yes H thank you for the red for the
pinky knock knock
wait I'm
done oh my God it's ory
now I did it I would clap if I wouldn't
have one hand on my uh cat's chin scrp
catching her
chin if I clap now she's going to leave
I
think
[Music]
y I'll change the music these these two
tracks sound so similar because they
kind of um belong together so sometimes
you guys probably don't even know when I
switch them
out
yeah okay so now we read the ory super
chats who is this from the last episode
yeah it's from can we beat it Orie And
We Beat It Beat It Beat It Beat It we
did beat it we definitely did
thankfully it was a great
game even though at the very end it
crashed and it didn't want me to finish
it but I I still did it we have proof we
have
proof yeah speaking of finishing game
uh transferring your safe data from PS4
to
PS5 uh is now apparently possible in
Tales of a rise and I'm still not
finished with it so I guess it's good I
I didn't think that it would take me so
long uh uh to like finish it that I
would actually make it in time for the
data transfer to be a possibility but
here we
are uh
yeah so I I guess I'll I'll try
to yeah never Silver Lining yeah I'll
try to transfer it yeah I
guess I'm I'm like I guess super close
to the ending but oh well um it's just
like I'm really [\h__\h] busy I'm not
lying
guys this week I took two days off but
on both days I was really busy I had no
time to play games next week is the
Christmas week which is also [\h__\h]
busy uh and then you know New Year's
there's there's always something going
on man I'm just really looking forward
to uh the end of this year and January
because finally some things
will some a lot of projects will be done
by uh that time
yeah I I will be so Rel
I mean obviously there's always going to
be something going on but at the moment
there's just too many things going on
[Music]
you got this thank you this week I
didn't play anything until I today
played Pokmon so I feel you K thank
you Hing you get that break soon you
deserve it K thank you well I don't
necessarily need like a like a whole
like vacation again I'm I'm feeling fine
in that
regards um and I wouldn't even like mind
like I don't know I don't feel like I
don't feel like a huge urge to um finish
T of R either like I feel like the the
hype inside of myself has calmed
down um because it's already been so
much time so it's not killing
myself uh yeah I'm I'm good I'm I'm
fine but I would like things to calm
down a bit more oh o yeah I have a
direct message oh there
n m
[Music]
M
continuing did you guys know
that actually not continuing did you
guys know that cats can have uh
[Music]
acne like not like these pimples that
humans get but like it's like kind of
different
yeah actually Smoothie
has it but it's not like you can't see
it if you just look at her you can't see
it but if you feel uh her
chin even even normally if you feel her
chin you wouldn't even feel it but if
you're like really close to her mouth
then you feel like there's some dirt
there some it feels like a crust like
tiny tiny pieces of crusts
and I already asked the doctor and she
said yes it's not nothing to worry about
the vet I asked the vet said nothing to
worry about and uh
yeah didn't really like there's there's
nothing you really need to do
but sometimes now this is weird but is
it is this
weird I
uh sometimes when I notice something I
like scratch it away like I help her get
rid of it is it weird is it
[Music]
weird I mean she can't do it
herself
so is it
weird no actually I've been doing it on
the side the whole time while I've been
reading super chats
now her chin feels really clean
now I'm
multitasking I'm doing skin care for my
cat while reading Super Chat
you do that with your birds do birds get
acne too what
what for her wellbeing I mean I guess
it's not so much being concerned about
her well-being but I I don't think it
like bothers her at all or like
influences
her um at
all I don't think she even knows she has
acne acne
acne skin caring
yeah uh for cats it really doesn't seem
to be an issue it's covered by fur
anyways and they look beautiful and cute
so no need to worry about that
acne so
[Music]
someone
P oh wait I read those okay no we're at
or now H for the pinky knock can I
please meet with the CEO of kfp Takashi
Kiara hul on here I've come to reclaim
my breath you took away from during the
alpha reveal as I kind of
needed Smo as
[\h__\h] smooth as
Fu your hair s dress ornaments were all
gorgeous I fell love and new
again and I died again just like the
last outfit were real but this one was
way more powerful now I wait to become
as K to be
reborn
wow wow
yeah that was that was that was smooth H
nice one
dun home is 3w hyp dun I don't know why
you write that now that sounds very
delayed are you Slowpoke
secretly I guess you should always be
hyped because you never know when it's
coming Mr casm St for the pinky
H one of the two uhhuh and Not only was
your new outfit absolutely staring but
the creativity in the reveal stream and
your glorious Sparks performance made
for legendary experience well worth the
extra waiting it has really been
phenomenal watching you go from a great
Phoenix Idol at debut to an even more
powerful one as the months go by as
always I'm proud to support you on this
journey you are awesome don't let any
dor tell you otherwise stay FB thank you
uh recently with the uh you know those
whole livean shorts coming up I've been
reminded of my old self every now and
then um so yeah I I I do think I did
change and improve uh quite a bit it's
almost so much that I don't want them to
upload old
clips it's kind of uh embarrassing but
but the last one was good the one from
among us even though that was I guess
that was an old was why did I sound like
was I using an old microphone there I
think it was the new microphone but no
go XLR maybe because I did sound kind of
different there but I don't think it was
that long
ago was that the old
microphone I thought that moment was not
that old what the
hell but anyway that was one of the best
moments in my streaming history I think
so they chose a good one I don't even
tell them what to choose it just happens
behind the scenes so um for this one I
have to give them props that was a good
moment they made you realize you watch
too much whole life there is no too much
whole life maybe maybe too much whole
life but not too much
kada and Mr has Big Stan detective big
St
dun M frog 1 million let's go
dangun oh yeah M frog reached 1 million
thank you
everybody oh that just really shocked uh
smoovie sorry that was just a frog do
you not like frogs I think smoovie
doesn't like frogs I kind of woke her up
there come chill chill it's all good
it's all good
baby it's all good
[Music]
I lied it's not a frog it was me
movie don't worry don't worry go back to
sleep 3D D and 1 million let's go
[Music]
dfy D so keep satify d m unknown
D it's been 12 hours and I still can't
get over how amazing your outfit R real
stream was and how beautiful you look
everything you do is incredible with how
hard you've worked you really deserve
all the love and support in the world
and so much more oh smoothy left oh no
thank you a unknown is down bad for that
new outfit aren't
[Music]
you kfp in general down bad for for K's
new outfit
[Laughter]
y I'm honestly so so over don't stop I'm
so flattered like for stop
no guys you guys
stop come on
stop
stop thank you you guys are too
sweet I hope I can continue make your
happy with future outfits it always is
something that makes me very nervous
whether or not you like it
um yeah I hope I hope to make you guys
happy with
it if anything that comes in the
future but I think what I do want to see
is Council and Iris in casual
clothes hopefully I mean how long have
they been around 4 months when did we
get our first
one ah I mean if we don't count Wolfie
then the first ones
were o the Casual ones they came
in uh
May that's over half a
year I hope we don't have to wait so
long for Council to get new outfits like
over half a year
damn I want to see some yeah Iris Iris
has been I how long has it been for Iris
I don't remember her doing a half year
anniversary
so not yet half a year 5 months maybe
wasn't she like one month before
Council she's said five oh she soon will
have her half year anniversary then H I
wonder if if she gets like a new outfit
with Council together or if she'll have
it like aone
we will see when the time comes I
honestly have no
idea I have no
idea no
idea but I think Iris Iris uh you know
her OG outfit is already so like um it
it stands out so much it's so so
detailed and so
fancy and also takes a lot of side space
so I'm I'm really looking forward to
seeing her in some more simple casual
clothes I wonder what she would go for
if she would go for something girly or
for something cool and
chill I honestly don't know what type of
uh cloes she would
choose yeah I just can't wait to see
more from Red juice yo red juice
Papa oh
red juice work M ponytail
Iris no I don't want to see her an
opponent toil artist will cry regardless
yeah uh I mean I mean riches can draw
somewhat simple things too I think I've
seen them draw some like the
the what's it called again Guilty
Crown
um doesn't she have like a dress like a
white white dress that's pretty simple
the Guilty Crown
girl
uh guil there's like so million outfits
for that girl is aren't there yeah she
has that dress in at least in Black
doesn't she have it in white
too anyway there's definitely like
although did he design that because I
don't know I don't know that much about
gu the crown I just know that the OG
design is from riches but who knows if
he had all the control of old the
outfits I don't know Inori yeah
Inori
Inori you think around eni the black
dress is simple imagine Iris and
something like that enoi black Inori
black
dress I love that normal um outfit
though the body bodysuit oh my God all
the enoi outfits are just so good
[Music]
oh
man looking at this stuff really makes
me look forward to what Iris will be
wearing in the future oh my god oh good
night thanks for being here
okay let's try to read more Super chats
Manuel Schneider D for the pinky your
outfit is absolutely oh wait I just read
that
stupid oh did I wait no I didn't you
guys all just say my outfit is gorgeous
I didn't read this
one feels like I'm repeating myself your
outfit is absolutely gorgeous I hope
you'll have a great time of ory can
sadly only listen for the first two
hours or so oh that's too bad did you
catch up with the archive by now I
wonder you don't have to but but on that
day I was gaming pretty well so it's
worth it to watch the the archive I
think thank you man by the way me
[Music]
oh you were I thought it was only 2
hours you watched the whole thing in the
end oh wait do you mean you watched the
like after the first two hours you were
able to watch it is that what you meant
the first two hours you only listened
and then you watched well that that
works too I guess J D looking for the
top D black FR and thank you for the
pinky kiar I can't get over how perfect
you and your new outfit look you guys
are so
so
thirsty like Australian royalty also I
know you don't like killing aliens in
games but I think a run through the game
XCOM 2 would be hilarious with you and
chat it's a turn-based strategy game
that I think would be a funny time to
guide you through with Chad
helping what XCOM
2 XCOM
2 ew no I don't want
it ew
[Music]
you know what you guys should do when
you recommend me games you should like
hack into the Google search and make it
so that only cute pictures show up in
the Google search and then you could you
could probably turn my opinion around
honestly the game screenshots look fine
though like everything besides the cover
the promotional images looks fine I
guess
I've never let you I don't know I don't
know I don't know I don't
know let me let me first just you know
get through death Loop and then we'll
see where we
go h four kakas thank you for the pinky
hi tento this is the compensation for
not following the new outfit life
yesterday ah I really like your new
outfit very much thank you for always
bringing us lots of energy thank you
Teno thank you too well I suppose you
watched the archive then then you shall
be forgiven only this once next time you
better be Al Al just kidding it was 6:00
a.m. or something for you probably or
even 500 a.m. so yeah it's okay it's a
bad time I tried to choose a time that
could work somehow for all time zones
and if you're good with waking up early
then it should have been fine but yeah I
understand
it I understand it thank you do for
trying and supporting me nonetheless
motion danus dun da 4289 d d big d j d d
Brandon wood
chulu D
six D I don't know how to say your name
so difficult Mr musclean danan ubub Tax
Collector danen happy
birthday Tai danen
Dan Viv NE D AB danan Big danash C danan
and Sky danash now this was when I I
turned them uh the Ori super chats off
so I'm actually done with my with my
Exel uh
list uh I think I want to try to at
least finish the Orie super
chats let me see squirr
squirrel or super
chats I stopped at Sky big swi Cy Sky
big swi
big Swig cyrex
sky here it is ah there's not that much
afterwards I think cuz I had them turned
off until the end where I turned them
back on I guess where did I go here Sky
okay
uh okay there we go let's see how many
of these are it's not it's manageable
it's manageable yo let's gool
let's go I will continue to read them on
Excel though it's kind of comfy
today yeah I turned them back
on oh I can finally get rid of this list
[Music]
y finally cleared this sorry guys for
taking so much time whenever there's
like a huge stream like that it just
takes a little bit of time to catch up
uh I generally don't want to fall behind
this much so sorry about
[Music]
that understandable yeah thank you I I
do I do want to make sure to read them
all um properly so we got to go for this
you
know we got to go through
it so uh we have
let's see how much do we have oh not
that much 56 okay J Thompson D Daisy D
Dragon SP thank you for the pinky you
did it oh yeah yeah this this is when I
made it I did it thank you for the pinky
Dragon
P thank you for staying until the end g
d Anon M thank you for another
pinky congrats on finishing aie I
discovered the Metroid Vania genre here
too Symphony of the Night was my first
and it was a masterpiece I've tried
other games but sadly none of none of
them surpass Symphony of the Night oh I
guess the first impression was too
strong well let me look it up
Symphony of the
Night is that it
oh a castle Castlevania Oh you mean
Castlevania oh n very old school isn't
it
who looks looks
cool um one that is probably very
different but that I can uh that I can
recommend you actually to
maybe
um uh see I I I'm not good at these kind
of games but I do know a few ones
because uh I know like a few creators
momodora
uh very recommendable and another one
that I also tried playing before that
was actually a lot of
fun is icono classs you guys know that
one it's so
colorful I didn't get very far when I
played it really really not far at
all ional
classs that one I did like a lot too
it was very um colorful and and
uplifting and
cheerful and it has a girl
character with big tools yeah yeah I've
heard about the first one yeah the first
one is really famous M as as far as I
know is really famous in its
genre yes so if you need some some met
Vania to try out then I guess give it a
try maybe I don't know if you like it
though you seem like you have high
standards or like a specific taste it
seem difficult to
please
big Jacob
47 thank you for the red super
chat I had to work a lot the past few
weeks I think your new outfit is one of
the best things that has graced my eyes
oh come on on I hope you're happy with
both the outfit and this game I'll have
to go back and watch the stream series
because this is one of my favorite games
oh well then let me apologize in advance
there are episodes where I mean it's
four streams and there are some streams
where or one stream where I was really
not doing well and not feeling well and
then I think the other three are pretty
decent the the one where I was not doing
well I think was the second
one was it
and the other ones were
actually pretty decent so if if you get
to the one that is not so uh fun to
watch I'm sorry please please don't give
up yet was it the first the first was
rough was it the
first it felt like it was the second I
don't know but yeah please fight through
it I I think it will get
better thank you
elen thank you for catching up on the AR
arives I really appreciate it archive
watches very welcome those are the Chads
coton d aren d Jim Trac D
Eric D J swack D Trevor G thank you for
the
pinky congratulations on completing your
first metania game oh
yeah we did not only just finish another
game we finished like a game in a
complete new genre for my channel
and I think that is quite the
accomplishment because um aie as far as
I know I will say this and be proud of
it is a rather difficult
metania and choosing that as my first
one to play properly and play on my
channel I must
say I am a
gamer
yeah it certainly was yes it is okay
there you go
there you
go it did really need me to focus a lot
and really um it needed me to really
memorize uh the skills and the controls
well yeah it it challenged me and I
accepted and completed that challenge
like
a like a like a like a
gamer the gamer of Yen yes yes
apparently I've been called called The
Gamer of Ian but I don't understand but
every time they say that people laugh a
lot and and and and I don't know it
seems to be kind of it apparently it
kind of has a different
meaning why is it so funny to call
someone a gamer I don't understand why
does it sound so mey why is it why does
it sound like something that I can't
really be proud of I want to be proud of
it I'm I'm proud of being the gamer
okay I don't understand these memes are
something that I'm just not catching up
with I don't get
it it turned into a
meme
why Trevor G thank you
for fellow fed scw no longer
you gave up the anonymous love wow
respect um I I respect
that Dan z
d oh congrats I'm going to read this one
even though it's not a pinky or red one
I got to read more of these sorry I'm
going to try to read more again Congress
also want to say thank you had a rough
weekend but watching you today manag to
cheer me up please give chongus and
smoothie more belly rubs
later of course I will Who do you think
I am I hope your week uh is getting
better that or was that this week or was
that last
week that was that was a Monday no I
think it was a Monday so yeah hopefully
uh your week is going better than the
last weekend Sal P D aren or aren
D Domin Joker
0195 D for the red super chat
[Music]
congrats my oie for finishing Orie for
and for the new beautiful outfit today
is my birthday and I want to celebrate
by supporting my Kam o she forg getting
me for every day your
stream thank you happy valed birthday
did I noticed this during the stream and
actually congratulate you already I hope
I did but uh in case I didn't here it is
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday dear
Joker happy birthday to
[Music]
you with the Clapping the the wind that
I created with the Clapping it it blew a
cat hair into my
mouth well well well thank you for
letting me be your oi I hope you had a
lovely birthday and hopefully the next
year your birthday you will also spend
it with me
hopefully thank
soon please stay
healthy take care of yourself arrest
danan aren Arch alien danan I don't know
how to read your name so I read it twice
for the pinky thank
you um wait what is that a is that a
rainbow Cho that's supposed to be a
rainbow and it's like uh interrupted and
it's it's the other way around that's
why I didn't know
this it started small and it's getting
bigger wait let me try to read it uh
from the beginning then let me try to
find where it started 27th of December
oh your birthday is coming up too oh
[Music]
nice
H okay so it started um uh
it
started here
maybe I find it impressive how your
friendly nature and very sensitive
approach to your fans has created such a
unique community community as kfp no
matter how much where that's two out of
five where's one out of
five shouldn't wouldn't that be a green
one oh I can't see
it I hear here it is today on my
birthday oh what it was your
birthday happy
birthday Arch Ellen
aren today on my birthday I finally have
enough time to tell my OSI that I enjoy
every moment I spent watching her doing
various
[Music]
activities I find it impressive how your
friendly nature and your very sensitive
approach to your fans has created such
an unique Community as kfp no matter how
much my very demanding
work or the now seemingly Eternal
learning has taken a toll and drained me
oh man the positive energy of your
streams has always built me up again a
watching you struggle for games just to
fulfill all the wishes of us chicken
has
and also motivated me to fight my way
for many difficulties now I am even more
proud to say that I have finally
completed my doctorate yo
which would certainly not have been
possible without my the moral support of
my oi oh my God you're so cool I love
you content especially H talk and can't
wait to see what the incredible collabs
you come up with next where everywhere
has fun again your new outfit is the
bomb you look incredibly pretty in it
hot as the sun yo thank you you're not
here in the chat are you thank you for
the rainbow first of all second of all
congratulations on the doctorate that's
so cool you're doctor
now nice that's so cool see that's
something I didn't I was not a able to
accomplish in my life but you did it you
should be so proud of yourself oh you're
here wait how do I say do I say Arch or
do I say Arc if it's Arc then then say a
r
k if it's Arch then
write no a r c h i guess
which one is
it let me try to remember it it's ah
okay so it's Arch okay Arch
Ellen I like how you wrote it as if it's
like a given that you always here some
of you guys just really try to spend
every minute with me and that is so
sweet of you guys thank you anyway let
me sing happy birthday for you Dan it's
a little bit late but but it must be
done
are you by any chance uh German
speaking AR Ellen because you donated in
Euro so I'm assuming you could be one of
the
Germans let me see if I can find you in
the chat
[Music]
y oh one of my
countrymen happy
birthday for
[Music]
no one interesting I'm sure you're
interesting
though
Lum Korean
name Korean
translation you you
[Music]
hey greetings from South Korea first
membership of my life hope you could
always stream with joy comment on
getting the ending be proud thank you
come yosiki thank you for two
pinkies still have a cat hair in my
mouth I got it I got it I got the cat
hair Yoo
[Music]
okay so Yi thank you for two pinkies big
kiss to start it off with hi Mom
congratulations to you new outfit reveal
yesterday originally I decided to share
the joy with my whole family in time but
I just too excited that I played the
whole night the game to calm down myself
ah when the deadline coming out at 1
hour I thought that it's probably okay
to let me take a little nap but I'm
wrong yeah I trust my decision again
even though I understand I always failed
about kind of things sigh oh wait it's
actually longer than that it's five
pinkies sorry get down to the stream
your new outfit is so pretty oh you were
late to my stream does is that what you
mean I don't know how to say and don't
know why my first impression on it
reminded me that you look like a
character walking on a fire emblem
oh a great Lord in fantasy world with
magic and sword and I love the Sparks
version set version you sang the blue
rose pedals falling down while you play
the piano and singing the scene is so
beautiful yes oh wait no uh where's the
last one here thank you for the new
outfit everything you showed yesterday
is so good they reveal the
singing and thank God that dream is
smoothly thank you
too thank you for feel kind words don't
worry we all need a nap we all need
gaming time someday I have a
c where do all the cat hairs come
[Laughter]
from H what was I saying yeah we all
need some time to to cool down and and
you know take time for ourselves so
please don't feel guilty about not being
able to come to my streams but I'm glad
you made it and I'm glad that you were
uh so delighted by my new outfit yeah
and the Fire Emblem comparison is I
think the first time I hear it uh but
interesting interesting I'm not sure if
I can personally see it in the Fire
Emblem
game because my impression from fire
embl games is just the one that we
played on my channel and and then with
that one I can only think of like school
uniforms and and all that and military
uniforms what if if you say it I guess
it is
so M it fits pretty good you think so I
wonder the owner of two fluffy
cats yeah it's
everywhere it's
everywhere anyway thank you yosiki that
was like uh at least two red ones so let
me give you some kisses M MW MW mwah Mah
there you go off of you off you go fly
Chicken F
die Mr
St can't be corn for
phoenixes fro for D FR D wait FR is that
a that's a rainbow FR what's what's with
all these rainbows yo oh my God first of
all congr on beating aie and since it is
very unlikely that there will be
rainbows in the winter is that so I
guess because it's cloudy I will send
you on here for the wonderful and
talented kiaha
H and since I was way too excited and
busy taking screenshots of your
beautiful new outfit yesterday I didn't
get around get around to send any uh
super
chats no to send any an orange super
chat with only we love you because I
need to fill other super chats
too
okay yesterday was a legendary amazing
Divine and exquisite outfit reveal
Majestic Phoenix Tak you blew away
everyone tot totally away once again I
love it so much your new outfit is
really wonderful thank
you the creativity you have to make an
outfit reveal so exciting had left me
speechless you look like a goddess B
your spares piano version performance
gave me goosebumps I didn't work the
first time but we all know as best come
some d
umand out r
[Music]
yeah um
out sorry that was long German I I
decided I will reply to this one in
German he
thank you for the beautiful
rainbow indeed I have not seen a rainbow
in a long time but that might not be
because of winter time that might just
be be because I don't go
outside but I saw a rainbow here in my
super chats I feel inspired thank you
for much love to you Mah booy booy thank
you
what does it say say Korean Super Chat I
want to
[Music]
read
a oh it kind of read out the Emoji too I
think thank you oh
[Music]
n that is the correct way to read it
thank you for your sweet message and the
satisy D congratulations on finishing
your first metro I'm glad you enjoyed it
this is one of my favorite games that
I've played in a while thank you yes yes
I am also glad that we were able to
finish it when I started it out I didn't
quite um 100% plan on like going through
with it I didn't expect me actually
doing well enough with it but yeah you
know when you start something that's
even something that's like especially if
it's something that's not even that long
then you got to pull through okay we're
done with or super chats it's almost
1:00 a.m. so I probably should leave it
here
um we will catch up with the rest of the
super chats soon
[Music]
TM thank you everybody thank
you um
tomorrow I'll be baking cookies um
there's a chance maybe I'll move it to 1
hour earlier at the very latest
maximum uh but yeah I also I bought uh
some new uh like uh plastic gloves that
actually fit did I say earlier I mean
later I mean later me earlier no way
later if anything later but I'll try to
be on time yeah I I I I just don't know
if I can sleep early uh
yeah no no don't worry about it but I do
want the C the the cookie baking stream
to be accessible enough um for sea
viewers I don't want you guys to um you
know be [\h__\h] over just because I'm
moving streams again I do think of you
guys a lot so yeah I want I want this
one to work for you guys and work for as
many Poss people as possible but I mean
the the current starting time would be
uh what was it again in
J the current starting time in jst
is uh 1 p.m. which I guess in Australian
time is like 11:00 p.m. right I mean
it's it's still better than my usual
streams I guess uh I'll I'll I'll do my
best to have everything ready in time
and I wonder how long it will take
though it shouldn't though though but it
shouldn't take too long right we will
see ah you know what it will probably
take long cuz I don't that's my first
time i' be like what should I do what
should I
do I'll have to catch the archive for
that one that's
okay but yeah definitely make sure to
check out the archive M you should you
should you definitely
should okay so I'll go now no more
wasting
time
because tomorrow will be
another tiring day but then I'll have
this week ticked off and we're almost at
the end of this exhausting year oh my
God thank you g for the pinky thank you
we're almost there almost at the Finish
Line guys oh my God originally I kind of
wanted to do this cookie baking stream
next week but I figured next week
will'll already be so packed it's better
to just put it here this week on
Sunday yeah
but oh oh man I hope I hope that was the
right thing to do I'll see you guys
tomorrow wo wo wo let's make some
cookies Christmas cookies
[Music]
thanks for the
pinky yeah thank you
everybody and we say oh F in I was so
glad to see you guys again today my cute
Simpkins I missed you guys totally not
noticeable was it was it noticeable that
I miss you guys nah you guys had no
idea
[Music]
byebye thank you guys my sweet
Jim m [\h__\h]
[Music]
byebye let's see if the stream gets D
mc8
[Music]
byebye oh
smoothie how the [\h__\h] did you
know I think she knows what Al in
means hi
[Music]
she's rolling around on the
ground y
You're So Soft for the
[Music]
baby good baby
ooh