[Music]
do
ch
[Music]
[Applause]
ch
[Music]
[Laughter]
for
[Music]
[Applause]
ch
[Music]
e
I love making you guys go insane with
that it's so good it's so good guys okay
do you want the game to be full screen
or
not tell
me cuz I will do as you
[Music]
wish
yes what you're not using the new frame
anymore the new frame you mean the red
one cuz you mean it because it's it
shows a bit more of the game oh well
okay full screen it is but then I have
to figure out where to put you guys
eventually and where to put
me full screen I guess you want to see
the glory of the
[Music]
game I took a nap because I woke up so
early at like 7
a.m. and I thought oh I'm not going to
make it if this stream is going to be
long
well do I have to make an account for
this or does it immediately like take my
Steam account oh how could you guys
know because you guys don't have Early
Access so I guess you don't
[Music]
know how did that happen right even
yesterday like I took a nap during the
day
[Music]
um and then um
a pretty long one and then uh then yeah
I fell I slept again at like 11:00 p.m.
so pretty amazing mucho sleep mucho Amir
for me uh uh your
he because he was very tired I
guess do you hear this
music orchestra baby he
[Music]
yes so okay okay okay originally I was
already supposed to be in my break but I
thought uh can't leave you guys behind
with like like 10 collab streams before
I go right that would be
cruel that would be so
cruel
I was feeling bad so I decided to do a
super chat raing stream but then pal
world came out at least early access and
we got keys and so it's
like
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] now I have
to
why I told I did not have this on my
radar I did not
realize and
now oh my
God sorry Gemma just sent me a list of
things I should do before I go on my
break oh I did so many things I've been
preparing like shorts other stuff before
the stream and and uh editing my own
shorts yeah I've been doing quite a lot
of editing This Time by myself because I
thought it so
[Music]
much uh but yeah yeah I was like uh a
little bit a little bit annoyed that
this is coming
out while I'm supposed to be on my break
right now and then I've been told cuz I
looked up but like to can you play this
online and so you can invite four
players right but you can also have a
dedicated server for up to 32 players so
I was like
H are they going to make a server and I
asked and so they are making yeah
they're so inconsiderate for releasing
this now but I asked and they answered
me and they said yeah we're actually uh
making like working on a ride now and
you'll have access to it like
in the next few days I'm
like I was hoping you guys were going to
take much longer
because I'm going to miss out on all the
hype I guess it's going to be like rust
in terms of like hype like people
playing it for a
while
uh
ah big oof I feel yeah I feel the
fomo the fomo why why why now why now
why why oh no I don't care about PVP
that's not really how I meant it more
like what to expect in terms of
participation so now I'm hoping it won't
be
popular no but I think it will
be and then when I come back it's
probably it will have died down or I
missed all the exciting
stuff m
[Music]
I'm so
mad Season
Two Season one is always the best hey I
wonder if they have to wipe the server
or if it stays up for a while like
that classic waa
stles going to be honest I don't think
it will be that
high I feel like when a lot of members
play a game they can make any game hype
and I feel like for pal World already
I'm say seeing the hype already in whole
life I've seen which Ian girls asked for
a code as
well
so I see what's going on I see and I
think
it yeah yeah so have fun without me I
guess I was late on so many things in
the past too I'm always late on
everything [\h__\h] [\h__\h] H but okay let me
pour some water in my water jug no from
the water jug to the glass yes yes it's
okay maybe I won't even like the game
right I hope I don't like the
[Music]
game Kyla already 25 hours in
oh okay I'm not surprised will you be
late for Yakuza I don't know when's
Yakuza coming out when's that coming
out like me coming back currently is
kind of like um totally up to me 20 okay
I'll be late to that too so good good
have fun guys [\h__\h] have fun guys playing
that before me and getting to a good
point so that you don't get spoiled from
my streams I guess
[\h__\h] I'm so
[Music]
mad
why
no never never can I have a break
where whatever [\h__\h] fomo is going to
kill me but I'm not going to by the time
that Yakuza comes out I probably I
hopefully would have forgotten about its
release
and I'll be peacefully reading
books with my cats and not thinking
about any of that bye
yeah
so we're going to play a little bit of
this today and then I'm going to read
super chats and then I'll be gone
reading books no I have a book that I
want to read I want to read it shut up I
won't have [\h__\h] to do anyway I mean okay
I do have some [\h__\h] to do uh I I have a
few things to do off stream uh after
like during my break so um just so you
know I'll be busy but just not hopefully
not with work no work no work no work I
refuse I reject go relax woman I will
try shut up I can read you shut
sh I even book like a two stay uh two
night stay at a a hotel
even to extend my vacation my back hurts
so I'll be getting
massages wow yeah muchos relax us yes
I'll relax oh also tomorrow tomorrow
I'll I'll not I won't be streaming and I
won't
be writing anything on Twitter I hope
but I'll be finishing up all my like
preparations like videos that I wanted
to
upload I already uploaded
like five shorts and one or two normal
videos I
think um but those are also short I
think um yeah
so I'm I still have a few more coming up
I I feel like maybe almost every day
there'll be a video almost every day wow
wow wow we're prepared so much for you
guys yeah so I'll be doing that and I
need to sign all the Polaroids and when
I'm done I'll upload them on the
community board and then yeah then I'll
dippy dip
dip she loves us I do I missed you guys
and I think I will miss you when I'm
gone but yeah oh speaking of gone
um I just want to say made sen
[Music]
by I couldn't say goodbye um so I just
want to say m pie you're always so
welcoming and sweet and kind to me and
you even gave me a necklace and you're
so sweet so I will miss you will be
missed she was a great Senai
yeah okay so let's play the
[Music]
game game Let's capture the
game
Pap let's hide the
hashtags I should not say the p word no
no p word the p word is not allowed I
mean I don't know I don't know but I
shouldn't say
it p word there's a chicken guys there's
a freaking chicken there what PW word's
new are area exploring the mystical
Crystal ice cave it looks so good that
looks like straight out of Final Fantasy
what the [\h__\h]
14 damn okay start game Survival Guide
no no need for for such a thing that
game I can make a character right create
new world pagos Islands oh no mes I want
to go back let me go back off yeah can
you still change that
later I mean this is I heard that it
will be all wiped all progress will be
wiped so
Pon so like whatever right oh there's
difficulty hard custom a custom
oh
wow
what I've never seen a game do that
before holy
[\h__\h] well let's do normal I guess that's
a lot of
[Music]
Sliders that's a lot of customiz I've
never seen customization in that regard
finishing finish setting up world and S
game yes I can't read my my brain is I
can't read Leathers
today
[\h__\h] oh I look cute player name
um wait is this like it does it have to
be unique it's not proper mmrpg so no
probably
right JMA wants um has named me so yeah
she she gave me that name before anyway
damn what the [\h__\h] she
buff I
mean no not quite a sixpack but like she
looks like she
buff wow that that hairstyle is cute too
oh my God wait hair is the most
important it's already orange as if they
knew
ah they need more hairstyles because
this is like both
genders so considering that
there's there's not too many
options I'll I'll stay with this I
[\h__\h] love it I'm digging
[Music]
it buffo long hair animation is hard
yeah I guess that's yeah games these
kind of games with character creation
they mostly always only have like
at most like shoulder length
hair sucks do more do longer hair please
oh can I do eye color here eye color
first like a bit
more purple thank you custom my color
saturation
brightness that is really [\h__\h]
saturated oh my
God does that look like
[Music]
mine
something like this looks good oh and
then wait oh
[Music]
G she me but she doesn't look so
shook hearts are cute but like having
them constantly I don't know oh this is
like okay p word don't say it waah cat
cat eyes okay wow what is this what this
supposed to be
Hawkeye let's just do normal
that's kind of crazy
though okay oh [\h__\h] wait sorry the thing
is confusing
me thank you guys for the Super Chat oh
my God I have to read them all so this
is like ooh wait this and this oh my
God okay I mean these are the girly
[Music]
faces oh not bad
oh
no this is pretty
neutral damn this comes with a beard oh
my God that looks
amazing but I can't
no I'll do this I don't care you
probably won't see my face still close
up anyway most of the time color I'm
like really pinkish right now but I've
noticed especially like when I'm like
next to waya for
example and I'm I'm talking like in
Fredy she's incredibly white and has
like a pinkish heel while I have a
yellow H have you guys
noticed SC oh wait you can
[Music]
customize oh did did Callie make herself
shre into a shred
cuz there was there's definitely
potential ogre it's so ogre she
didn't
coward I thought she would W you little
[\h__\h] you I was worried about you you
little [\h__\h] she didn't she's been home
for several many many hours is now and I
thought she would tell me when she's
home as she even told me that I have to
tell her when I'm home just from the
short you know travel back from airport
to my place I told her when I was home
she didn't tell me when when she was
home and I was like what did she make it
cuz like she was worried about some
things I was like oh my God why she
should be she should be home right now
why is she not telling
me I got a little bit worried she
tweeted about it somehow when she had
Twitter hasn't been showing me her
twitteros mostly yeah let me
look when did she tweet 9 hours
ago n hours ago Twitter didn't show me
and Nissa didn't tell me Nissa you
little
[\h__\h] I miss
you miss you n missa I miss you Mara are
you still in the chat or did you just
write one comment and disappear
Mara wa body time oh oh who who I miss
you too yeah but where's your
explanation I mean I saw I saw on I saw
what you wrote to
me so I guess I don't need an
explanation
oh they kind of have
nipples but they're not colored so
what's the [\h__\h]
point why would you do
that what that's like you're not
committing to it where's the
commitment ridiculous
ridiculous
commit who
wait no I
mean uh I was going to say like that
looks good like how it like scales and
all that
but I take it back cuz like it literally
goes into the arm
and wait wait is that supposed to be
muscular
um the arms are kind of
muscular oh my God Arc can Ark do that
too
really that's amazing
that's
amazing could you make could you make no
neck
edit the lengthy six wait this is a
isn't this like a nine pack or eight
pack I don't know but like they could
stretch to the side this is so
unrealistic sorry I'm
I'm
the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] wait that
does I mean I've I've seen this in not
in person but like on TV this kind of
proportion I've seen that
before it's kind of
crazy kind of
crazy yeah yeah like yeah I mean a bit
more Boba but yeah okay okay now let's
be
serious oh dear oh oh
dear the hands are too big if you make
yourself small like
that we need a hand size you don't have
to go too crazy on it C world don't make
them like don't give them the option to
make him like as big as your legs but I
would appreciate
a the [\h__\h] was that sound why do I hear
a [\h__\h] the animal but like at least
give me give me like maybe 10% of of
uh I hear them like I hear footsteps I
hear footsteps
guys no it's okay okay I'm okay I I
guess they they already have the sounds
from like wherever I will
spawn but yeah okay okay whatever uh
here I'll make a bit
more yeah yeah okay cute uh oh wait I
didn't even look at this not hold I
skipped immediately to here okay but I
think we're done
so really that's all I'm going to say
hard to make really a a a an an
impression if that's all I hear but
maybe that's all the voice will ever say
will they never speak a proper
sentence
huh yeah
yeah yeah
yeah
cute
[Laughter]
is this like I know F or what who is
this ho ho wait this sounds like someone
H
wo woohoo
yeah oh that sounded like Iris that
sounded like
Iris okay wow okay stop stop stop stop
stop I'm enjoying this too
much I'm done you cannot edit your
character again after the game is
started okay come but can you please
Implement like a cash shop where I can
put real money in for cuter outfits and
hairstyles like cash shop items
please
please no don't listen to him
no
oh wait someone told me the chicken was
a starter I I thought it was the only
starter so you have threee options oh
those
free you literally get a [\h__\h] starter
okay oh the towers are the
key the tree holds the true dressel or
what
well
mysterious oh I'm not sure I'd call it
that oh okay so it's not really like
that okay tutorial pick up Fallen
branches or hit trees to get some wood
open the options menu check the now they
make me look at the survival
guide pick up Fallen branches Pebbles to
gather wooden Stone you can also collect
wooden Stone by punching bites and build
a workbench and craft an axe and the
pickaxe to gather resources more
efficiently once you've gathered enough
materials choose the location for your
base and build a pal box once you play
what a weird thing to call a house a pal
box wow once you place P box area
becomes your base as your level
increases make weapons in in a pal
sphere that start capturing wild Pals by
weakening them first night time can be
dangerous prepare for your first night
by making a campfire torch or a bed and
a
bed it's funny how everything is in um
rotation marks a bed uh campfire and uh
a what a
torch crazy kind of [\h__\h] whatever the
[\h__\h] that
is okay wait I did
that oh it it just gets rid of it I
thought it would give me a check mark at
the top Shad are you comfortable where
you are wait I'm going to put you here
though cuz I don't like you floating
around like that wait what I don't go I
spawned looking in this direction but
this direction looks cool
too can I oh whoa okay Dash and I can do
the
roll
ow nice oh what is that ooh look at that
look at the scen there's a guy there's a
sheep it's called lamb ball
cute is it randomly generated I have no
idea is it I wouldn't think so although
it would be kind maybe a little bit
boring if all worlds forever are always
the same is it randomly
generated no it's not this one the same
as others uhhuh no call look like this
oh okay look at my oaba cloves I look so
beautiful so is this like a safe point
oh fast
travel
yo okay who are you I thought I was
playing solo get on here you
hacker a cat is this a girl I don't know
Cast Away been a while since someone who
didn't stink of Pals washed up here pals
are the monsters I guess this island is
a living hell the people I came with
aren't with us any longer they died
those damn Pals ate every one of
them they eat
humans holy
[\h__\h] imagine that was thinging in
Pokemon holy [\h__\h] wait I'm in front of
the
text okay I've decided I'll be over
here here take some basic supplies you
need to toughen up if you want to
survive out there oh [\h__\h] I said a p
word what is this look good soup soup oh
I got
wood is there any more around here that
I didn't
see I don't think
so open the build menu with be select
the Primitive workbench and set the
build location wait let me I probably
need a bit more wood for that are they
not going to attack
me hi you're friendly cute do cute cute
cute yeah sheep are [\h__\h] cute why is
the sun going down h a little bit no
what is Shady shady as
[\h__\h]
oh they're dooming what is this like a
cat do they have
Evolutions I peaked a little bit
into Fuki senpai's stream with mik and
Su
Senpai I saw like a flamy cat or Fox
maybe that's the evolution
oh look at that oh a palis
spere yo berries oh [\h__\h] oh I got to
level up for collecting things
okay nice I just kind of like have to
look at it eat this n so many bears can
I eat them am I going to be hungry oh
there's a
stone there's a
going Poke
Ball don't make me say things I don't
know I I feel like I shouldn't save
stuff like
that because it's kind of on the
nose oh I guess you can like smash this
rock if you have like a
pickaxe oh and the p word is pal World
okay that's what it what I
mean no picky
upy this is like oh oh I don't know how
big is this world can I see a map map oh
of course map is on M thank
you like some some parts I already have
on my map but is there also stuff in
between I would hope
so
interesting hey if I'm if we're able to
play this with like everybody that's
amazing a I'll [\h__\h] die from
fomo that's not even going to be fear of
missing out it's like factual missing
out cuz I'm actually going to be missing
out this is a
fact Saks and stones may break my bones
but chains and whips excite me oh oh
this is definitely going to attack me if
I get too close holy [\h__\h] though holy
[\h__\h] though screw ification no I'm still
going I mean I wouldn't mind for example
like
moving it a little bit like one or two
days like cuz like that's really it
doesn't matter I have no like set
specific date that I must uphold it's
really my choice it's my thing I just
want to go on a [\h__\h] break detox I
need it can I open
this yo wow 557 gold coins is that a lot
nice water and this is a note from
another adventure you can check their
journe is from the option screen like an
actual different Adventure or is this
just like placed there oh oh she
climbed she do a climb wow the graphics
yeah I mean I'm happy with them I think
they're good and depending on how big
the world is you know I can
totally say this is
amazing this is really
nice wow look at the water wow it's so
turquoise it's not quite like the mes
though this grass like the the the
the plants are not very um much like
mes what is she
doing why is she crouching down there
can I go down y fall damage o I did get
a little bit of
damage oh but it it heals back
automatically okay
cool wow turquoise a swim she swims
weirdly I wish I could see the whole
body
wait
the wait the water sounds wait first
there was like a everyone's in the world
there was a swoosh sound now it's just
like sprinkling water like a like like
when you have like a really tiny at home
table water well like a cat F cat water
fountain oh there it
is what do that more often do that with
every time I move my arm arms
H why is it
so okay water uh sounds need to be
improved they just come and go whenever
they please
and it's just a little bit
weird not very
immersive it is early access yeah but
full access is on when the 19th
not much time tick tock tick tock
chickens I see
you oh look at you
guys you're looking so
adorable can I have you chicky
be what what is that sound turn it
off oh look at you that's
you you you you so as far as I I can uh
say now from what I've seen you can make
them help you and work for you you can
even ride I guess maybe only the bigger
ones I guess no way I can ride a chicken
right uh so that means we can have the
chickens work for us
yo okay why should I put my my my
base should I put it here or should I go
even further
[Music]
cuz I think I have enough stuff to build
now that's pal looks interesting over
there nice nice nice pal
designs near the statue e the one that
was up there or oh I guess there was a
new one that's where the sound was
coming
from was this is that a
scrap no I can't pick it up okay
zooming with the kativa zoom I'm veling
you catch me outside how about
that wait where was there was where was
that sound coming from is there another
one of these
things it made
a oh my God it's making me oh it's
[\h__\h]
crazy it's screaming like as if it's
being
strangled that's more of like a gobble
gobble
sound oh the sounds are so cute oh my
God I'm excited to hear all of the
animal sounds hi baby girl you're
looking so cute oh sorry how do I can I
crouch oh yeah SE is
crouching you are the cutest
marshmallow whoa Su it's trying to fly
it has hope it thinks maybe maybe maybe
I can fly I just have to believe oh [\h__\h]
okay it's getting pretty dark look at
that one that's sitting over
there a with its feet um BL so adorable
okay it
stopped okay I'm I have to do this now I
have to do this I have to do here here I
guess whatever ah [\h__\h] it's so dark okay
um
maybe I don't know maybe here lots of be
what the
[\h__\h] B uh primitive workbench
uh
here how much did that take me move near
the planed build location for put hold F
oh donk donk
donk
nice can I now build a house craft pal
spere wait we have to probably make an
axxe start
production is that being made now oh I
have to okay okay
okay it's [\h__\h] fortnite no why I mean
I can't judge because I never played
fortnite but still oh now wait so can I
hold several things at
once
wow where does it go if I put uh uh uh
pick up the second thing that I just
built Fork knite now I'm holding no
still the axe okay acquire there we go
we have we have acquired
it ah there you
go okay uh probably a torch would be
nice how do I turn it on though does it
just turn on
automatically it's so dark I want to
sleep I want to sleep in the house open
the technology screen from the menu and
unlock pal
okay does it stop time probably
not unlock pal
sphere yeah but didn't I pick this up
before campfire would be
amazing structures
amazing this is oh wait no we want the
shy bed I would think that's better
C I'm going to die wait where's the fire
didn't I learn how to make a fire M I'm
going to die I'm going to die I'm going
to die wait how do i h okay okay I don't
know would I have
died
[Music]
build inventory how do I open my
inventory e eat e e is not the inventory
I I
mean oh what the [\h__\h] was
that
oh ah now there's the P here
though I don't know why they want me to
make that but I guess I'll make it uhoh
don't attack me don't attack me oh it's
Fox Sparks I was going to read Fox
Sparks is apparently scared of me okay
what a weird way to hold a torch I mean
maybe it's a little bit heavier no craft
a pal sphere I did I've acquired it
build a pal box in an open space attack
Pals to weaken them okay open the
technology unlock P box wait unlock P
box did I do
that I don't see a wait [\h__\h]
blind
okay but it's not here eh why not here I
press
tab oh this is my inventory okay tab is
my inventory so many bears they they
uh they only have like 8 minutes left
but I don't I don't need them oh wait oh
hunger okay good good good good good
good Berry seeds no pal fear an item
that captures Pals when thrown oh mass
produced is only effective on lowlevel
Pals also if I can I catch one now I
mean when they're sleeping I feel like I
could probably catch them so easily B to
build ah oh P box but this is just a
screen I thought that was a
house how's that how does that work
oh build donk donk a Don oh Don I a PC
and I build around it
okay I thought that was a
house a box for a human to be in okay
hbox management menu missions and fast
travel okay then uh BBB
build where can I get a bed
insufficient campfire maybe in
sufficient oh I'm just Laing oh damn
okay bed is going to take a while wood
oh oh okay I will need a bunch more
sticks but maybe do I really need a
whole like building right
now
generally I I wish I could skip the
night wish I could skip the night but I
guess I can't as long as I don't have
some
place to sleep and what is this
line what does that line mean I need a
pickaxe
too you need a bed to skip in that a
chop chop chop chop ah true true but
won't it be [\h__\h] cold maybe I'll do
the I'll I'll put up the
the here the the thing first the
campfire which will hopefully provide
heat close by
oh there you go and then I
can chop chop the wood nearby without
being worried about being too cold right
okay uh here there we go
and yeah I'm doing
fine um am I hurting myself no okay this
tree
wa okay 22
wood 22 wood nice
to ah it's too far okay
whatever oh I get fiber from that too
amazing at what point will it get damage
from being cold 22 okay
nice
okay okay okay okay that's that's a good
amount oh welcome Raiders oh is it is it
a wait look at the time is it Fu raid
you guys are not saying
bbo oh oh well I should probably use a
pickaxe for that that's probably not
good for the axe no it's not
oh I can't see I can't see who it
is
not a h raid okay okay well I mean I'm
not surprised because there's literally
no one else
streaming okay I've got so much stuff
wait I should eat maybe again a little
bit ah ah no did I just waste that
thing that was on accident but I guess
it's probably not that valuable
hopefully oops I
overate okay we got some Fiber we got a
a Cooper Key amazing now I'm weigh down
by caring too many okay let's build
something then I I shall make the house
of my dreams can I make the bed no I
don't have wool so I have to kill one of
the
sheep probably not connected to a
structure well well that's
because we have to start somewhere what
do you mean not connected to a
structure
I then what do I need to put the ground
first wait how do I cancel
this Foundation First okay
but okay but then I wanted
to the box is not going to be on top of
it okay I I'll put it over here are the
trees going to come back
grow back are they going to grow
back doesn't have to pretty in the end
all of this is going to be ah
wiped I'm guessing this is how you deal
with such a mistake and you lose the
wood oh my
God
okay that's fine how much wood do I
still have oh oh plenty plenty I
think wooden
wall
actually wait let
me place the door first here looks
amazing ah see is this assemble mode oh
damn
it it's okay wait can I make some stairs
too I see wooden
stairs
is this oh level up is this like rest
without the apocalypse kind of feeling
like I'm not going to be like shot down
by like
planes that would be
[Music]
amazing let's chop this
wood yeah the windows they wor In Me Is
it okay to be
seen I can get braided the house yeah I
know where I'll make a
roof oh am I so slow because I'm oh
okay maybe I'm getting way too much
wood the door is even pth lock oh
okay wait I literally can't
move okay uh
can I build something nice out a no wait
wait look what I actually can't
move or is my keyboard
broken
uh uh I'll build another campfire right
here increase my range wait I can't
build it up oh really slowly oh really
slowly drop something
no I will not
[Music]
drop wait I'm still slow as [\h__\h] for
real I have that much stuff that's not
true that's not much or is it the wood
that's okay H is that the weight
237 okay that's kind of heavy let me eat
a little bit
and
man the rocks are heavy
too but wait I'll
just I want to build
roof sound is
gone you have skill bones yeah to
to
to it seems a visitor is heading towards
the base
what
wait can I oh technology is there maybe
something else I want to
learn wooden structure set set for
building a base using wood what I
already know that no oh wait these are
these are for the things I don't know
yet a wooden chest repair bench I can
put that outside
now learn how to make cloth oh cute
outfit oh I'll probably need that how
many points do I have
eight stone
spare common Shield old bow
arrow all of these things seem pretty
and uh useful hanging
trap well that's [\h__\h] brutal oh my
god oh feet box is that like oh Pals oh
that's cute Pals can eat from that once
I have oh wait this is this is a bed for
the I was like oh I'm going to go
straight away for the actual bed but
this is for the
animals then
okay okay then we can build why is this
all like in different
tabs the repair bench like here for
example what do you think about
that you see him the
visitor oh 28 M 27 he's coming closer
who do I have to kill him what if I kill
him can I kill
him well it takes so much time 22 m
build a chest next to your empty
inventory next to you oh oh no worries
I'm building this now hopefully that
will take up some materials it's taking
Mighty long time so oh they're coming
over to
me y I can move again
hello oh hello who are
you what if I actually holy
[\h__\h] I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I wanted
to be
funny
please go away please go away oh no oh
no could I have oh he's going to destroy
my oh I'll have to kill
him okay okay I'm coming out I'm coming
out yeah bye yeah run you run you little
[\h__\h] that is amazing that you can do
that I wonder what he would have sold me
Goomba Goomba goba finish him Goomba I
want to play with you but I'm going to
go on a break tomorrow can you [\h__\h]
believe
[Music]
it Goomba come into my game
now would you please come into my game
now just kidding just
kidding I'm so sad I'm so sad I'm going
on my break that I've been planning for
a while and then I'm going to miss out
on all the [\h__\h]
hype I can make it online I just started
I can
restart no it's okay no pressure no
pressure guys was this an important
person I love the the freedom
though okay let's
make let's make a
roof rof was
here oh my God guys tell me if I'm
missing a a message by the way wooden
roof slanted roof let's just do a normal
roof uh you guys said I can do several
what was it right click no was it when
if I want to do several ones there's a
few more Merchants okay okay here was my
favorite NPC how could
[Laughter]
you I use stat no no I will I will use
the stats if I find out how to use them
just priority first need to make
house ah [\h__\h]
wrong wrong thing we need the wooden
roof go I wonder if the ax is actually
stronger than the the other weapon cuz
like if I think logically I would think
the axe is stronger but the axe is meant
to be oh nice meant to be for chopping
wood right so let's put some chest
here this is really like cute anime rust
I love it
cuz one thing about rust or like any
kind of game really any
game is this body ever going to
disappear it's like I want it to be
cuter I wanted rust to be cuter here we
go this is what I
wanted wait campfire no shy B and now
I'm out of right I still don't have wool
okay and I need to finish
this bubble gobble gobble gobble it's
literally not making chicken sounds
chickens sound
like so this body can I actually loot
the body
or what is this body just going to be at
my doorstep it moves when I I I can move
him away I can move him
away
what you can eat him if you want guys
you're
welcome holy [\h__\h] yeah he's got rag do
all
physics
crazy we need these stairs hey
wow nice nice house now let's because we
were able to kill a human killing a
sheep shouldn't be so difficult right
cuz the human literally had a [\h__\h]
gun never going to kill a chicken though
of course not
you know
it oh man it doesn't know what it's
about to
experience well you can also just give
me your wool like voluntarily then I
don't have to kill
you what this is so [\h__\h] bral it
feels so
wrong like I don't know what it is about
wait don't don't roll away wait hey no
no no yes yes okay okay roll actually
into my
base give me a wool wait did I get wool
from
that can I get
it what if I put you into the fire can I
get some lamp chops no select
recipe wait is it because I have the
lamp right
here wait here's the
lamp ah I guess I did get like items
from that because otherwise it's
probably ah
no
wait I forgot how do there you go what
how hey where did the food
go what did I ah
acquire what's
so oh wait I did get wool okay never
mind so what these bodies are just going
to Forever be
here gravite
forever reminder of guilt well yeah that
the Sheep looks kind of still
alive cuz it's also still moving its its
uh hands but this boy he's dead I
absolutely murdered him and his eyes are
open
okay good then now we can make a bed
right or is free not
enough ah [\h__\h]
sorry ah wait build I press B the first
time shy bed hey there we
go uh I would like to have it here
wonderful you can catch the Sheep oh
you're right I could yeah I need to
capture you okay that's the next thing
but maybe first I should use my stat
points cuz we need to figure out what I
can even do with
them that was a
master sphere really
no wow I have a bed I have a house I
have so much cool
stuff
mhm oh wait
ah my berries I have 51 berries and
they're all going to
disappear oh well they were wait wait
they refreshed to 10 because I guess the
only the top one is going
to
uh be affected by that I can do baked
berries cooking enhances their
nutritional value and surprisingly they
quiet filling okay
maybe are they do they you do you use
them for anything else no
okay oh only one at a time amazing
okay
oh wait am I going to be cooking oh wait
can a can a k chicken cook for
me can you cook for me how do I do this
how do
I
oh captur rate 11%
only okay it didn't work and now wants
to kill
me don't attack me I'm your mommy you
should love me ah I'm your boss now it's
higher chance right okay yeah yeah first
you need to show them some
violence so that they understand I'm
sorry oops
guys look awake guys
look nothing happened nothing happened
oh where did that one chicken go where I
only got one where did the other one go
do you guys know
H
anyway yes tii Jimmy where you going
Jimmy Don't Panic Jimmy what the [\h__\h]
where are you going calm down what how
do I make them like me
me is it oh is it just like is it
staying close to me oh I think it is I
think it's following
me
okay yeah okay it's running when I
run can you please like do something for
me wait I need to make a pal b a pal
bed uh did it just go
inside oh wait I didn't I didn't get
[Music]
the the P
ah this one ah [\h__\h] I need uh I need
more points so sorry you're going to
have to like I mean you can sleep in my
bed with me as long as I only have one
pal ah P box you can assign to okay
okay uh what about this
um
cute
oh it likes to gather and farm
maybe egg chiy pea poultry nice
extremely weak and far too
delicious is one of the weakest Pals
alongside lamb ball hey they're not weak
especially not if you make an army out
of them no matter how many are hunted
they just keep appearing amazing that's
great that's great for building an
army
egg oh can I eat this
no oh wait where did all my berries a my
berries are like in here
huh I can acquire some
now and [\h__\h]
sorry [\h__\h] my
[Music]
balls I can feed the chii
amazing so how do I use my stat Points
Pizza H
[Music]
poo
I hear sorry my I didn't
see how do you keep
wasting I don't know how what will I
need maybe or work speed would be nice I
have two more oh or maximum weight yeah
I don't think I need HP right now so
let's just increase this to be efficient
to the
max m
M or you guys are saying wait then I
think that choice was right so
far
uh I
think flap flap
cute look at him go
BL let's see what I can do with you wait
Pal's at the base can I put you here so
what you going to be doing what are you
going to be
doing how do I how do I how do
I how do I assign him to something
huh current task
idle that's it is he just going to
decide on his own what he's going to do
interact with him now okay okay okay
in good
condition lift for to open
menu I can B to come here come here jimy
who's a good who a good yeah you're such
a baby so cute I love you I love you let
me lift
you can I throw them oh my God what
meow wait how do I put him back
down wait how do I put it back down
command Paul pal four command don't
attack command focus on S command uhhuh
uhhuh
[Music]
uh-huh Into the Fire you
go fixed assignment to campfire failed
no work suitability oh I wasn't really
trying to do that but okay
so I have to throw them at
something to assign them to something
well I don't even know what you can do
here I guess if you can't
cook
maybe P about beds get stress not H all
I don't really see what what there is
for you fix the sment to
tree that
worked is it going to chopped
tree
so far it's not doing
anything but good
luck
ow burning hey get rid of that get rid
of
that
yeah
water okay oh my God oh maybe I could
have like rolled
around I shouldn't I should make a
pickaxe I need stuff let me go make a
pickaxe who look at that fancy thing
over there that fancy
pal is that one sleeping sideway no wait
that's the
one I was like oh they sleep sideways
really I don't think they normally
do cat why are you running stop running
I want to capture you
you little
[\h__\h]
ah come
here
[\h__\h] now I don't really want to I don't
want
to yes I don't want too much collateral
damage damn
it
yeah oh [\h__\h] you you might be kind of
strong huh ah
oh oh there we go is that my chicken
helping me so sweet get him get him yay
yay smoothie come to me or chunky
[Music]
wonky we have a cat
now pbox upgrade is uh available
interesting
uh wait why can I not put another I need
to upgrade it
huh wble
probably
missions
oh maximum Pals working at base up to
two maximum number of bases stays
one okay oh I can upgrade it again oh
okay so we can have free
now yeah give cat the axe what I can
give the cat the
X
what that
sign well it's working on its own it's
Gathering all right all right now I
should really make the straw bed but I
couldn't equip it yet could
I
uh oh my God there's so many things to
do I need to build the snow the stone
pickaxe too
I want to learn it I shouldn't have
learned the other things yet you you
finish your cooking cooking okay okay
okay I get exp from that too
right
okay the cooking
sounds sounds like it's been home
recorded
M it is way faster
I love baking in a pan
right all
right wait now I can hopefully get the
straw pal
amazing did I acquire those things too
yeah let's eat that
[Music]
okay uh then
finally here we go maybe outside or
inside is it probably difficult for them
to get inside
so probably is it one
per why does it sound so dangerous is it
is it in in good
condition is it uh
uh dangerous to have them outside and
and and also they probably want one per
pal okay oh oh it's building it for
me hi there you
go thank you for
helping I'll help too the chicken is not
doing anything though why are you guys
just watching what's your
explanation chicken if you don't help
you're not going to get any of these
beds both beds will be for the cat
instead no arms no heads wait for
real is that really the
reason that would be so funny oh just go
to sleep it's okay you can go to
sleep cute maybe it's not tired
yet you're the supervisor okay honestly
I like the idea of that like you guys
are superior to every other single pal
in my
world you're the ones supervising
everybody yeah oh no it's too cold I
guess now we can
oh cute look at you can I cozy up next
to you I'm so cold oh man okay I'll
sleep
here oh
[Music]
spicy
Kitty yeah no go back to supervising
that stupid
cat okay okay okay we can get one more
pal but I let's make the thing that I've
been wanting to
do all this time I need to make a
pickaxe
mhm and then let's
make more balls I
guess oh I can only make one
[\h__\h] wait but that those Stones over
there probably give me uh what I
need for more balls
right hey hey hey palum fragment there
we go that's exactly what I need I
think nice five out of one rock do I
need one fragment or more for one ball
look at what's over there what's over
there
that looks like a single
fragment easy free fragments just lying
on the
floor
shiny we like the shiny
things bad idea to mine it like that
what do you mean you for real also this
is probably Stones although I don't want
Too Many Stones right now because it's
just going to make me unable to
walk
okay pretty good pretty
good that was hidden in the
ground I just found that by
accident put the mats in the
chest I guess oh look at him look at him
cute he what are you doing where did you
find
that what a
cutie oh uh height
maximum
only
two and I wasted so
many oh no let's make a
cloth for whatever I don't know might be
useful okay then let's kill
some
things what's that over there oh it's a
a it's a
cat
oopsie
[Music]
you are a dead
lamp oh wasn't there like something dead
dead Lambs that
Lambs some a movie that is the whisper
of of the Dead Lambs or
so it's crying ding oh my God I feel so
bad do I get something interesting from
you by the way if I kill you I didn't
pay attention last time I silence of the
yeah I silenced
it my weapon is damaged no what all I
got is berries sorry that was not worth
killing you I will never do it again
never
again look at him go look at them go
they're better as workers I would
say okay uh wait I have unused stat
points
okay and then maybe eat
something what's running out soon this
but n Nom
n do they need healing by the way I
guess
not the club might be better to use for
fighting okay
okay build a feed box oh I should make a
feed
box yeah yeah yeah
yeah but they're in good condition now
so I guess um
it's not so urgent right now but I'll
make them the feed
box insufficient I you need wood I have
no wood right now okay
okay what's if all these chickens
they're they're lining up in front of my
base because they want to apply for a
job they want to become part of kfp but
I wish I could take you all at
once but
unfortunately it has to be a bit slower
the application
process have to capture five Lambos
what's the what's the point in capturing
so many Lambos when I can only have
three on working on my
base just exp
or or well I guess I could have them
follow me too my ax is broken I thought
I thought damage just meant you know
like damage to an extent not completely
broken
okay fight and farm exp
M
okay wait so wait
repair do I not know how to repair yet
um yeah
okay thank God I have some points so now
repair kit is that what I need
I have a b ah so the repair kit maybe is
for on the road on the
go I can repair
here
o
oh
interesting
who they're just camping outside of my
home look at them so cute I love when
they sit and their feet they're v-shaped
feet look upwards it's so cute I I see a
lot of you guys have been receiving the
uh kfp plusy so you can have them sit
next to you like that if you
want should I put something in here oh
wait the the they put the stuff into my
into my chest oh no no no no no no
but when I let's say I have nothing left
in my inventory but there's stuff in the
wooden chest if I if I build something
nearby will it automatically take it
from the wooden chest or do I have to
take it out I have mine thank you so
much still waiting M literally arrived
as the stream started
wow all right wait I wanted to build a
feed
box wait wood
more oh yeah righted cuz my axes broke
okay here we
go can't wait to receive mine I also
can't wait to receive mine
ouch but I'll probably pick it up when
I'm in Japan next
time I love the sounds they're making
they're so
cute okay feed box here we go maybe just
like over here
that looks amazing all that beautiful
fruit oh wow can I feed myself from that
as
well and then I have to put stuff in
there is it does it does it matter what
food it
is you can have all the baked berries if
you want wait this is running
out can I eat it
raw I don't want it to run
out
I can upgrade my base what
how why not cook some meat well because
it was running out and I had no
time salmonella let's
go we love a good
salmonella we can make
these radio stay static
ASMR for real ktima is taking a break
that's that's fine good good for you
please take a break chillax a little bit
are you going to go to your bed you can
also have some
food you don't want me to watch you
while you're taking a break or is that
embarrassing to
you no problem
then security settings repair
n let's look at this
again how do I upgrade the base you guys
were saying I can upgrade the
base also I need to catch another I need
to capture all the Lambs okay let's go
let's go let's go let's go let's capture
some
Lambs it was C right for
capturing and this time I'm going to use
the wooden
Club sorry sorry no ah okay and go yeah
move almost killed him cuz she attacks
so fast number
one oh [\h__\h] no oh oh okay okay we're
fine we're fine I thought I was going to
fluffy Shield cute I thought I was going
to uh throw out a ball for nothing
again but it's
okay I brought out my lamp to support me
in my time of
need it needs more heal while can I give
it can I give it
food uh uh no sorry I'm confused
uh
here uh can I oh H but wait I no that's
not really for
that hold
F cute no no I don't want to throw you
it's not
working how do I I'm pressing F oh there
we go I have to press it longer okay
ye yeah I can grab it that's the shield
I
guess wait I'm back in my at my home I
didn't realize I was going that way let
me get that one over
there what is that
fluffy thing over there that looks very
familiar to me from a different
game okay wait there it
is another lamb ball let's
go
cat captur
these lamb
balls wa I have to capture 30 Pals oh my
God
if I capture like 30 pounds in one go
are they just all going to be following
me oh no it's just one following me
now
chest
yo bread gold coin low grade medical SP
let's
go maybe I can heal my fluffy sheep with
that but maybe it's not worth
it so I won't do it only for myself if I
need it I don't care if they die right
it doesn't matter if they die can you
can you resurrect them
though the PALS like if they die within
my care oo look at you can I
accidentally like hurt my own I hope
not don't kill
no you stupid [\h__\h] there's not so many
lives around why would you do
that God damn it I know you're trying to
help but what is this egg egg a colorful
egg it leveled up though yeah that's
good there's some stuff over there oh is
a common egg
okay who laid that there that doesn't
look like a chicken
egg who is the owner of this
egg let's go down
here and
then over there oh oh oh kativa is
slacking
off do I hit it when it's slacking off
or
what don't kill
it
nice oh
pullet
Penguins hey
[Music]
my lamb ball is aqua blood wait what's
that
emote it's exactly like that
banglin
y p
Stone uh let me get this one too this is
so exciting I love I love how they
combine several types of games
into
one level
up let me use my stats right away before
I
forget oh okay just one
okay where' you guys get that emote from
what the
[\h__\h] is that new YouTube emotes cuz they
don't look like like the normal PC
emotes oh
oh
oh does that remind you of
something it's so pretty we're doing
that what do you call it when you when
you're like a shepherd and you you move
animals around like this but we're doing
it with a sheep
ironically right let's let's get one
let's Capture One hey wait you fluffy
little [\h__\h] hurting okay okay same in
German pretty much
yeah uhoh no
[\h__\h] oh you get wool from it though
that's pretty nice where did the other
one go cuz I would like to capture the
other one
[Music]
then it's just
vanished damn it to my right was it to
my right
whatever that's the dead
body oh my
God what how what where's the face oh
those are the feet
oh it's kind of evil what what is that
gumas what are
you you look funny you look like one of
those chocolates oh
dear don't run
there king of the forest level
38 oh my God a Tacko
sapling but it looks like that chocolate
that cookie chocolate from uh the the
from
Japan I can climb the
tree uhoh it's coming this way oh no oh
no the taco sapling told him that
there's a troublemaker in these lands a
human troublemaker you can take him nah
no way I'm not ready that's what I
thought I mean what level am
I
six I don't think I'm ready no you what
do you want you want me to die or what
there's another chest there but let me
get the let me get one of
these oh my God it's so
cute
come
here a [\h__\h] can I pick it up again
what who oh the other one is attacking
me no for [\h__\h] sake my
[Music]
balls
okay what why is not
working my
ball wait that's
[Music]
mine guys confusing
me okay finally please go in please stay
in please stay in that's my last
ball
[Music]
oh oh did did they fend off my
sphere Mama
Mia Mama
Mia oops I didn't need one okay but uh I
guess now would be a time to eat
this no no maybe
not oh my God I'm
dying y too hi to catch Pokedex
update so so many sheeps wait here I
still need two more sheeps yo small
Palo I captured their soul why are you
wet why are you
wet are you crying are you sweating what
there was no
water now it's wet again but you
literally I don't think you entered the
water well okay you look funny when
you're Dr
dripping H I would like to heal but it's
going up slowly so I guess I'm fine I'm
probably
fine let me go find some
more Panic sweat they soak up water it's
like a
sponge go home to heal do I have to
sleep for
that I don't want to
sleep I don't want to go to bed yet
no honestly I could sleep forever but
like IRL
forever let me get that one too
no
okay sleepy yeah I'm already
sleepy already already sleeping but it's
okay I'm having fun
so I'll be fine
it's kind of crazy like this whole
vacation that I had with narissa
throughout the whole vacation uh we
continuously like every
day every night we only slept like four
or five hours maybe except for no every
night
yeah even though I was tired but like I
don't know like there were several
factors I would say that added to it but
wa just wasn't able
to sleep like I would want
to oh my God okay now I'm too
heavy to fing
heavy okay I know I can drop it okay
let's drop
it
how much how do I take half okay drop
there we go oh I think I dropped all of
it I want to build something maybe I
feel like I wanted to build
something yeah but that's like we would
keep on taking naps but I'm going to be
honest I feel
like I feel like Lissa kind of like you
know hurts like taking naps made me take
naps too I like naps but like she made
me take even more naps than I would
normally
do kind of
crazy and then I wouldn't say
necessarily that that added to me not
being able to sleep at the night I I
don't think
so but yeah then we created this whole
cycle of not sleeping properly at night
then getting up really early for
breakfast and all that which was cool
and then yeah napping one to two times
per
day
inconvenient naps are inconvenient
during
vacation I don't know I I also felt a
little bit like yeah I should have I
should have
um spent more time doing stuff but it
was raining a lot first of
all so I don't want to like blame myself
too much for that
cuz it it did rain a lot and it was
stormy like I I was going to go to
another another snorkeling trip but then
the snorkeling trip got cancelled while
I was already there waiting for it
because of the bad
weather and then our Sunset Cruise got
cancelled and this and
that so you
know things weren't super
ideal
don't I feel like you have to make the
most out of your vacation otherwise it
doesn't feel like a vacation true but
yeah I don't know I would have liked
to make a bit
more out of it have a bit
more um
activities but I mean if you think about
it I feel like I kind of did almost more
than oh in my previous vacation in the
mon
Alles cuz I think the only thing I
really
did in my in terms of activities with uh
waya in the previous Mal strip was that
one non-alcoholic
cocktail uh mixing
class where I don't think we even mixed
anything on our own but we were just
watching because they had that going on
because it was raining so that was their
like rainy day um
activity
mhm and we just went snorkeling but like
we didn't go out with a with a boat to
go snorkeling which is like snork close
by but yeah besides that did we really
do anything I feel like even
though uh it wasn't peak season feel
like I chilled more on the
beach during that time the first Mal
strip then I I did this time I was
thinking I was going to chill on the
beach so much but
no actually
didn't massages I wouldn't really count
massages as
activities your short two
beds I mean I can't put them in my
unless I upgrade now I'm I'm going to
upgrade now if I remember how to do
it there we go
okay now I can make another
bed why does it say build campfire two
out of one and it's still grade
out does it just want me to build
another one during the that
mission that's so
weird means you already did
it deploy a work pile to the base oh I
guess so build a berry Plantation
is that a recipe I can
learn oh
yeah these other things I feel like for
now maybe I don't need right now o a
ranch farm for raising sheep and fowl
like Pals raising
them what do you mean is there baby Pals
parachute
ooh wooden living room furniture set a
set was it just a
table palar workbench
structures hot spring let's
go wait I have so many technology
points let me get some things done fire
bow fire arrow
[Music]
she get po e
P gear P gear
where ah this one oh I just had two more
points so
amazing uh oopsie let's see a hanging
trap trap that catches Pals passing
through it Pals caught in the Trap are
easy to catch with spheres only
effective on small Pals okay I guess now
that I have the recipe we shall I'll
make use of it are they really going to
be so stupid to run into
it oh it immediately got created I
didn't even have to build it Go sheep be
curious check it out you I know you want
to but actually I want to catch it
normally though oh wait it's going
there I guess it doesn't it still counts
even if I catch it through that wait I
have no balls I need to make balls
uh balls maximum balls
start damn balls maybe the merchant
could have sold me balls oh thank you
thank
you and
then wait build uh alarm bell bell that
sets the alert status for Pals on base
change pal Behavior Uh to e attack
inting whatever okay I guess I'll build
it should it be
like close
by I don't know where to put
it maybe
here good for
raids ah so you don't have to go one by
one on the pal aha okay thank you for
helping oh so
sweet than soon ding
ding pal gear workbench A Primitive
workbench for producing pal tools make a
saddle to ride Pals make a gun for Pals
to use a gun okay but then I would need
more one more cloth and a lot more wood
okay maybe they put some wood into my
chest yeah a
couple
take
let me put some stuff in too maybe
um
this I no this a this is for the The
Berry Farm is it that was a berry farm
right Ranch uh Berry Plantation also
needs woods and stone oh they just got
rid of a tree oh no it was
Stones okay let me chop a tree
then I don't need to take it out of my
chest
a oh okay okay okay that's nice
then check on your
pal why they should be able to take care
of themselves they're they're in good
condition they're
fine
I wonder if a c with multiple arms can
use multiple guns gun
setion that would be
amazing ah ah I yeah cloth okay wait can
I make another
cloth yes let's just make uh a
few okay okay okay okay
okay yeah this game is kind of funny the
things you can do so
far and the Animals they're so cute but
like having to kill them hurts my
soul but being able to kill like even
Merchants yeah it's pretty
funny I wish I wish they would release
it after my break so I wouldn't have to
miss out on all the fun it's like a new
Minecraft for us
now yo I like this bench cuz it even has
like a pink cloth over it
nice no usable recipes okay so I have to
unlock that in the technology manual
that's
fine I think I think I need a fro candy
because like it's I think too dry in my
room I I slept uh you know after my
after my mold strip the whole mold strip
long the my humidifier in my sleeping
room wasn't on so I came back back and I
didn't immediately turn it back on I
slept two nights without the humidifier
and holy [\h__\h] it is unbearable it is
unbearable I was like drying out like
I'm in a [\h__\h] desert so now I've been
turning it on like crazy in my bedroom
sh humidifying as much as I can but I
don't have it in my work room huh I was
like whatever today's my last stream for
a while so no need
right
what is there to learn oh nothing right
now okay so what do I need what do I
need for a berry
Plantation not that I really feel like I
need so much food but okay we can make
use of
bit must be
[Music]
touching is that really going to look
like that
oh yeah my voice no my voice doesn't
really need a RIS it's it's been
fine generally oh I'm already out of
materials [\h__\h] wasn't there something
else I wanted to build the ranch maybe
wood a [\h__\h] ton of wood bunch of stone
and a little bit of fiber okay the fiber
I got from the trees too
right help her sheep so kute
yes I love being represented so early on
in the game with the chickens like kfb
being represented I can imagine a lot of
whole life members will play the game
and be like Oh Ki
KI K
and
definitely I have to
[Music]
wait ha it's
K every game with a chicken it's K
ha I am a phoenix may I remind
you oh let me take
that 70
stone okay I'll build this uh right here
cuz I can't [\h__\h] move wait I can't I
can't build it here ah I want to please
let me build it here no
no I have to put it down
again can I uh oh I want to take half
take half ah ah with
shift there we go oh still oh
my
[Music]
uh I need to cook some food
shift
drop
okay wait didn't I
have another
one didn't I build two or did I just
like fail I ran out of materials or
so make a chest n it's okay I'll pick it
up
again
yo okay by the
way what can I tell you what can I tell
you that I haven't told you it's it's
hard to recall from my
brain Nissa met my mom my mom cooked
something beforehand and we ate it it
was some Austrian
cooking the first impression of narissa
my first impression uh you know I was
waiting for her her at the airport and
uh
he um I got nervous that I like wouldn't
recognize her right away uh so like she
sent me a
picture and then it was really easy to
recognize her and um
she the moment she saw me like she even
though there were so many people waiting
uh all for narissa of course no even
though there were so many people
waiting she immediately saw me like she
went around the corner and immediately
saw
me and then she ran she had like this
big smile in her face the moment she saw
me she got like really y happy and she
ran she
ran I'm like don't run it's okay I'm
here yeah and then we gave each other a
big
hug so as you could
imagine she saw the two hats yeah the
two hats they stood up out a lot I guess
yes or even in in real life I put on two
hats of
course and let me see the
ranch needs more wood okay did I drop
the wood
here there we go that should be
enough that will that really be
emerged I don't like that I don't like
the risk of it being emerged
in let me test
it no that is absolutely
terrible really
no no it can't really not that's that's
really bad I don't like the looks of
that can I build it
here it's kind of like in the
way maybe
behind do I have some some space here
what if there's tree in the way do I
have to clear them oh oh here's
good Ranch is pretty [\h__\h] big this is
perfect though it's barely touching that
tree
nice Callie asked about my hats too what
did Thea think of Austria well she
already like had this
like at me r
somehow for Austria but more so I guess
for like historical figures and musicals
of Austria I don't know if it's really
for Austria
itself but yeah she she we kept on like
comparing things to America and she was
really happy like for some reason she
really wanted to buy shoes in Austria
because she was like saying that
American
shoes like for normal prices you don't
get the quality that she thinks you
would get
here I don't know if that's true I was
doubting it but so she got shoes here
already end and she was really happy
with them I
think she's right really why like that
makes no sense to me why would it be so
much better why are you guys so
happy why would it be so much
[Music]
better
wait another sheep wait I didn't have a
sheep helping right now
really they cheap out over here yeah
[Music]
really cuz America overprices things
with half of the quality
sadly okay well she did get her shoes
and she was like excited about like uh
like the smothie specifically she said
bread tastes different and and I don't
know so many things tasted different to
her she she was really really excited
about uh but this was in the mold she
was excited about the vanilla ice cream
tasting like proper
vanilla yeah she was excited about so
many things that seemed pretty normal to
me no sugar and European bread yeah
stuff like that like things are not as
sweet but at the same time still
sweet it's just different I
guess
[Music]
what else what else I wonder what else
oh I mean she'll probably hopefully talk
about the things that she witnessed and
experienced and felt cuz she probably
remembers them better than
me but yeah I can say narissa really uh
takes good care of her hair just
really always always touching her her
hair and
trying to get rid of split ends and
she's always got it braided but then she
was saying I thought cuz she always has
her hair braided I thought that she
would know like a lot of different
braids but she said no I can only do
this kind of braid she can't do like a
French braid or whatever I should have
taught her I was like thinking of it but
in the end I forgot so next time I meet
her maybe I'll teach her how to do
different types of braids I mean I don't
know so many either I know the type of
braid I think it's called a French braid
I forgot the one where you braid uh
around your sculpt by like you add on
more hair strands each time it doesn't
have to be at your sculp can also be
like away from the sculp but yeah you
add strands each time go talk braiding
lessons let's go yeah I think that's a
French
braid mhm I feel like if she knew how to
do that wow her repertoire of braids
would be expanded
greatly h
perfect girl talk
topic yeah but kind of need to be in an
off collab for that to really show it
and teach it to
her food oh wait you guys are out of
food oh no you still have food you were
just running to it okay pal beds I need
another bed
okay heuse drawings I guess yeah but
still like I mean if drawings were
helpful enough she probably would have
learned it by
now or maybe she's just too lazy I don't
know oh on oh are you like uh what's it
called dual streaming
now thank you I need to after my break I
want to you know look into dual
streaming on both twitch and YouTube too
I've been too lazy and too brain
occupied until
now so I couldn't think about it yet
properly let me put this bed down here
for our four P there we
go no rush I have to break it is
yeah there's many things I want to do
after my break I also want to get a new
loading and ending screen after my break
like actually commissioned this time is
there someone here by the way no damn
lame m wait we need more lamp balls
[\h__\h] and I'm even considering getting a
new gaming screen commissioned maybe but
first of all the loading screen takes
priority
uh the loading and ending
screen I mean the total M screen is
amazing I love it
but
yeah I can't have that one on
no forever [\h__\h]
hell thanks for helping I
guess and then when I'm back there's so
many games like Yakuza and pal
world and I I need to play the tales of
AR rise DLC eventually
too to could be a BRB yeah I guess like
I I rarely ever use my BRB
screen the Super Chat raing screen that
I have that's not really a a BRB screen
I guess so yeah we could use it as a BRB
screen but generally I'm
like I feel like I don't want to use brv
screens because I know it it is
proven people literally even if you just
like on a BRB screen for like 2 minutes
people will leave
impatient
Fox people see it like as a reason I
mean I would probably do so too people
see this reason you know they see like
oh this is going to be maybe now I
should leave the stream now is a now's a
good point that was a good point to
leave the stream
yeah and I've seen that happen in action
yo yeah attention span ruined yeah for
real in
internet so I'm generally always really
scared to go like on a beer screen or
like go on on on the idle
meeting so I always stall as much as I
can for the idol
meeting is it going to attack
me no seems friendly
relatively until I attack
it
That's not healthy it's okay I generally
have a a good um
bladder yeah I a steal bladder I'm good
I'm
good what's that thing over there we
should check it out the glowy
thingy Nissa is like crazy in terms of
hydration I wrote it in my journal too
but she always has like this big ass
plastic container for
water and she drinks so much kind of
inspiring I should drink more too oh
it's a statue no LIF monk fig offer them
to a statue of power to improve your
ability to capture uhhuh okay
ow did she share he there was no need to
share I usually always had my own things
to
drink rightel oh and oh my god I've
noticed this thing like ever since she
first like her first night over at my
place I have a guest room right so when
she was here uh I let her sleep in the
guest room where's my home face over
there um and the thing is I I I don't
have curtains in my guest room
currently so in the morning the sun
rises and it gets pretty bright so she
also she said like she she really can't
stand it when it's bright even the
tiniest
bit um
so she yeah when it's when it is even a
little bit bright she has an eye mask
that she puts on I I can't sleep with an
eye mask first of all like a little bit
of brightness doesn't bother me and
having an eye mask on that feels more
bothering to me like having the
sensation of having something Li lay on
top of my eyes I could
not I could not I don't like that but I
guess she needs it because
she
um yeah because she can't sleep with the
lights on so I I in the first morning
when I wake her up I see her completely
covered like with an eye mask and also
with the blankets over her face and all
that and I'm like oh I guess the light
really must have bothered
her
but the following night even when it was
dark cuz like in the malds for example
we had like blackout curtains and I
would uh close them for
her yeah and then I I I see her still
completely covered like the her whole
face and I'm like how the [\h__\h] does she
breathe then she told told me number one
she uh one she she likes having the
blanket cover her face cuz of hydration
cuz my room was so dry at least here in
Austria uh when when when it's like on
her face like the uh hum it gets a
little bit more humid I guess which I
think that indeed works so
genius I don't know how she breathes
though I don't know how she can
breathe h
but then the other thing I'm not going
to say it on my stream she has said it
before in her stream and and I know now
too I found out like really really
late um oh
nice she has a certain trauma that makes
her cover herself up
completely and then I before the last
night I I I asked her like
narissa is it is is this true like this
trauma thing is that true like I asked
her about it right before she would go
to sleep but don't worry we joked about
it like being a bad timing to ask but it
was fine she slept perfectly fine she
said it didn't scare her or
anything but
yeah
yeah poor
narissa poor narissa I don't want her to
be
scared but yeah I need I need
uh to put up
curtains in the guest room
but I put I did put up curtains
originally in
theory but I I put them up like
with not proper curtain
thingies rails but like cuz I had to put
it up myself and I because I didn't want
to like always ask people to help
me so
um I bought these things that you
usually would use for curtains in your
kitchen um like pretty weak things but
they're easy
to easy to attach to the uh
walls
mhm so that I could do it
myself but the thing is they're not
really strong so when I move the curtain
sometimes s it falls
down especially cuz the curtains kind of
get stuck a little bit on on that thing
on the
bar yeah the retractable yeah you can
change the size and all
that uh so that's my issue and then they
fell down several times and when they
fell down in the guest room I was like
whatever it's up so high I don't want to
get the stairs now I don't want to fix
that now so I just left it and ever
since
yeah tension rods yes yes yes but
they're not so strong I'm sure maybe
there's like stronger tension rods but
the ones I have are pretty weak because
they're supposed to be temporary but
they've been temporary for a while
now okay what are we going to do we need
still need one [\h__\h] lamb ball can't
believe we still have that going on hi
baby
where is nav Lambo oh look at that bird
flying W
nice it's nice that it flies up so high
you have to shoot it down with an arrow
I
guess oh but it's even is that marked in
the
map that thing cuz I see like bird
markings in on the top but maybe that's
not for that bird maybe that's for
something
else
you you are so
weird Ah that's 37% is still pretty
low oh oh oh yay yeah D we got it anyway
a strange pal of body resembling a tree
sap it gradually loses strength with if
it has nothing to cover its body with
eventually rotting away oh my yeah okay
but that's not a lamp I need a
lamp wow I had a little
lamp little lamp little
lamp how come nothing gets stuck in my
trap they get really close can I get
stuck in the
Trap you killed them all yeah but surely
they respawn thank you for the pinky
Super
Chat thank you can't promise that I can
read a catch up with all the super chats
because I don't I don't even know how
far behind I am but I'll read certainly
a good amount of them at the end of the
stream oh bait does it need bait it
didn't say anything about
bait there's a lamp over there so
far thanks for the
membership
[Music]
there we go should be a certain success
yep
okay all
right finally then the other things are
build up your base until the reaches
level seven challenge the boss increase
your player level to
30 no no by capturing Freddy pal okay
all right maybe I'll go and capture a
[\h__\h] ton of Pals
soon sorry that was an
accident this one's new so let's put
this one out here I wonder what they can
do they're
planting they have a sand blast attack
not
e it's spinning on my
berries
wait I need a new
bed gosh eventually you're going to have
like a million beds for the pals huh you
guys want to build it how fast are you
guys oh pretty fast I'll leave it to you
then Yum Yum Yum Yum Big Bird it's so
close wait I I want to get a bow and
arrow and
also maybe I can get the fire one too no
still no technology points that's okay I
should make a normal one first
maybe so weapons I can make
here you can even make a factory where
your pals work I guess so yeah oh thanks
for helping oh my God
so
nice Okay some
arrows you should put all your lamps PC
and only bring that you need what what
what
ah oh you
mean I should move them over to the box
is it a problem if they're not
there I'm growing more and more into a
good
gameer I have I've always been a good
gameer what do you
mean I don't know what you mean oh I'm
hung oh wait I haven't eaten in a
million years
uh right sometimes h
no sometimes I literally forget cuz the
buttons are so close to each other my
brain like inventory I feel like I want
to change that to the eye button if I
ever play the game again if the hype
isn't dead when I'm back
[Music]
ah what should I eat the
bucket no see eat
this I want to cook some
stuff
wait I can make a fried egg you guys are
told you right that I made breakfast
from the whistle after we came back from
the Mal Dives I I basically witnessed in
the Mal Dives her ideal like breakfast
choices cuz she literally chose from a
huge
buffet and every day she would get like
fried eggs so so so with bacon and all
that so I made her fried eggs with a
bacon and she said the Austrian bacon is
better than the mold bacon H I did try
the moldes bacon that we had there and
it did taste indeed like very Porky
indeed have to agree with
[Music]
that but I made bacon and eggs
and on toast
yeah on buttered
toast I even made it in the oven for
some reason cuz I I wanted the wanted
the butter to
Melt while baking the bread basically m
no beans no it wasn't supposed to be an
English
breakfast more like a then we saw
American
breakfast
yeah oh W wo wo wo I double clicked
everything [\h__\h] oh well we're full now
huh okay let's go Capture wait I don't
have balls
probably can I wood wood is what I need
oh
is there any wood around
here no so you guys said I don't have to
get it out of my box so it really means
I have no wood right
now then let me chop chop chop hope you
have a wonderful Str break thank
[Music]
you she did say the bacon was better but
uh still similar tasting from American
bacon like I don't know how
why if it's really that I wonder if it's
really that
[Music]
different and then on different days we
had like
qu and she had yogurt she bought some
yogurt she left over some yogurt so I'm
going to eat the rest of it she did like
the Y y that we
have and oh I bought um what was it a
whey drink way was it
way M cuz in Austria and I would say
probably also in Germany and other
countries here uh we make like Fruity
whey
drinks yeah w h e y
mhm but she tried it and she was like oh
it's different from America because in
America we drinks I'm more like for
protein right uh but here I mean we
surely have protein way drinks too I
guess I didn't even know that that was
like a
usage but uh here it's more like you
know just like a yogurt drink just a uh
like you know a nice fruity little drink
oh wait she wor she wears it
automatically okay
[Music]
nice yeah okay I think we're good now
build a statue of power wait do I have
the recipe for that
though oh that's the
one sure I'll build that why not where
should it
be you guys should try it I really like
our our way way drinks they're
yummy they're tasty oh what a are you
doing here don't get too close to my
base maybe I should put my no the
hanging thing won't work for for it I
guess no way what no way what no way
you'll drink and then you'll be like no
way this is so
good and usually I feel like the best
one are the the mango flavored one
M what else was I going to do I I was
going to repair the the axe
again
ah what no
wood how am I going to chop wood when my
ax is
broken
what wood did no PW chop some wood for
me what chop some wood for me you little
[\h__\h] what are you
doing oh man what is this egg
wool okay so this thing here is working
on its own by the way didn't really have
to do
anything sorry no hands okay you'll be
forgiven you're here to supervise oh yo
yo what so fast and I I don't know where
my bow
is gosh it's so fast hey
Mela
I
buuck oh it's on the edge of the
world God
hit how much what's the level anyway
[\h__\h] ah oh not level nine don't
run what the [\h__\h] it's almost thr me
down the edge of the
world hey that was
dangerous oh my my Pokemon is f my that
was so
automat leave me
alone
no
no no no no no oh my God what it killed
me is this my
base is it oh yes
okay
what death by Blue death by Ala Z no I
think I can get my things back this said
it dropped everything but I just got to
go there I think oh my God level 9 isn't
even I'm like level
what okay seven
yeah I did not expect that but like the
the the environment where we were
fighting was really unfortunate can I
see where my stuff
is huh
okay is that the same yeah it's the same
one but it's not going to attack me now
right I don't want to I don't want to
get too much fall
damage don't climb like that you look
like an
idiot ah okay we're good we're
good damn it that was out of my league
where's my
stuff ah wait there there there's the
pointer but isn't it like even lower
down this
way
should it be like
here oh it's up there oh I thought I
left it all pretty much
like a couple
of floors
below oh can I take it
all how do I take all nice okay I'm not
going to attempt that again at least not
here
my first death that was kind of Epic
though I got to
say now I I do want to capture some
animals some Pals I only have eight
balls though what the
[\h__\h] can I make any more here's my
bow oh only one
okay we will go and hunt and also on the
way gather some of these beautiful
Stones oh was I just missing wood what
what was I
missing why is my axe broken why do you
say fix your axe is it that
broken just
wood oh oh yeah H that axe I thought you
meant the pickaxe yeah [\h__\h] my my ax is
still
broken surely by now they brought me
some wood
right
right how am I missing one more wood ah
because I used it for the [\h__\h] ball I
can still chop it
right oh
okay just really
painfully chop chop chop this one needs
wood too
now we're
talking if sometimes they were
collecting wood I feel like
but maybe I'm
wrong oh
[Music]
okay are they going to water this I saw
them watering it before I don't have to
do it
right now let's do this
six six
balls you need a water P that that one
was watering it though I think it's
fine okay here we go here we go here we
go here we go 15
balls ah thank you for catching the
stream welcome let's catch one of those
Penguins the Wonder
can I shoot with the
bow oh hey is it going to attack me no
wait you're so fast what the
hell ah stay
here
nice oh my God they're so
strong
oh
wait no no no no
no it's going to shoot it's going to
shoot
no
ice I'm going to capture you now oh no
it fell off okay you're going to get a
little bit more bony
donk that's what you deserve okay now
yeah yeah cute pain go in for me please
please please come to me yay you're so
cute but I still don't know if they have
Evolutions do they have
Evolutions I don't mind if they don't
have Evolutions I want them to stay cute
forever learned air Canam oh let's
go pemo
capture it's a combining Evolution oh
combining different Pals you
mean what else could be captur that
looks like epic I don't know if I can
not level nine maybe nine maybe
not now you breed them for better
attributes combined to be a new one
uhhuh use your p attack I forgot
how yeah okay you help me right
Lambo you'll help me let's let's get
another one of these
ones don't kill
it
dude wake up
[Music]
it's probably good okay why do I keep on
having the mam rest up there isn't it
like pretty [\h__\h] far I think that's a
bug I don't think I should have that up
there command
them I don't know
how
[Music]
ah wait now it's
gone let me sleep let me go back to
sleep oh look at them I need to CT
capture more chickens but I
mean all they can do is like supervise
are they really I feel like they're
really a little bit like in terms of of
game meta they're not really that useful
are
they but it doesn't matter because in
the end I need to farm you know right I
need to farm
some some of these
so I need more of you oh sorry [\h__\h] I
wasted it
stay oh oh my God you killed it you
[\h__\h] killed bu it you're
crazy no don't kill no they too no don't
kill them I want to capture them
no no what have you
done oh my God that one is rolling away
so fast did you guys
see oh my God they're rolling so L they
weren't on the Rampage yeah they wanted
to protect the base I guess cuz I was
fighting so close
by oh man what about you let
me shoot
you wait don't don't flap around so much
wait are you are you you're not one of
mine right you're just a random
one stop
[Music]
running ah
wait that's mine oh okay why is it going
crazy sorry that's why you're flapping
around cuz you're
mine all right all
right
oops that should be
good that was like a critical hit yo
no bird flying up there I want to see
like what level it is but
[Music]
nope
oh pum fragment I'll gladly take
that oh there's the bird what level is
that probably too high cuz if it's just
like single one Nightwing I feel like it
would be kind of high level what about
these ones oh these on should be good I
have I don't have a single one of
them let's get him [\h__\h] aim do hit box
do 44 ooh ooh ah okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
okay h
ah [\h__\h] I just ah
no should have done some more damage but
then it was too much
damage o la la do I see a cute chicken
butt over there
huh no no y I swear to
God I mean I know I can probably stop
them from doing that from killing
everything
but
I don't know it's helpful to have them
help me fight it's running away what
level am I
seven probably since that one is level
10 probably better that
way I'm
hungry okay
CH
uh is anything running up
not
really okay
good fa
[Music]
good you know narissa was like
literally when I was bringing her around
out and about in the streets of Austria
she's like reading every single thing
every German sign or whatever that she
could find she would read it out
loud no but most of the time it was
pretty cute and pretty funny cuz like
her her pronunciation isn't even that
bad but yeah she was I think she was
hoping for me to correct her so I did
correct
her
uh just like cie no Callie was by
far by far not that
[Applause]
bad chicken too fast for
me should I give it a
try I mean my biggest problem was really
just the the location where we were
fighting
oh damn it's barely ah I'm barely doing
damage wait don't chase my my sheep
[Music]
around it's like a boss fight
now yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah pretty good
pretty good oh it's it's zooming it's
zooming where are you
going uh-oh Yoo it's zooming but it
can't turn when it zooms it just goes in
the straight line easy easy
[Music]
easy this will be our our Mount I think
if we can successfully capture it there
we go no it's blocked it are we going to
die
[Music]
again what no you killed my
friend killed my
companion oh oh give me
oh where are you going stay
here
[Music]
uh-oh can I catch it down
maybe okay at least it's going in for a
little bit
30% will it be worth it will that fight
be worth it
yay oh I got a pretty cool one I got a
mount
y oh how do I switch how do I there we
go mm I know I could have gotten it out
earlier is that one going to heal or is
it dead
forever uh wait
[Music]
party this one's
dead put him into the power box okay
okay it will revive in 10 minutes oh
okay I mean I don't really need it I
wouldn't mind if it was
dead no don't
care Oh The Penguin I wonder if the
penguin is strong attack 166 oh it's
stronger stronger h
okay let me let me see can I make some
more you guys need to run away no he's
still good you got a lot I could
cook ow The Fox and the alpaka yeah the
fox
maybe as a fighting companion but the
Ala as a writing or is that like the
same thing
then I I think I still need a saddle
though
right
oo
Yak Yum Yum Yum y yum yum oh even those
like leak leak in between
yummy oh that looks delicious
cushy
yucky yum actually they have food this
this is for
me what is this flame organ material
obtainable from Fire PS oh ah to make
fire arrows oh makes sense makes sense
yo thanks for
that you just took it away in front of
my
nose
this game is so good that you're
starving
now speaking of starving I should eat
some cookies I had some snacks that I
had on Nissa try like milka strawberry
milka
chocolate and um from
Bon those cookies that are called Chini
cookies I really love those because they
have like a a slight
orange uh flavor really slightly and and
little
chocolate um balls in the cookie those
are so good but she said she doesn't
like orange so she did not like
the cookies very much then I had
different more even more cookies I had
um
uh what are they called life nits lifeit
these small liit mini cookies that have
chocolate on one side and she really
loved those she actually took them with
her
yeah the other ones she was like me
about but these ones she liked Nissa is
here oh
[Music]
hi and I taught her to eat two at once
because somehow they are like a million
times yummier if you eat two at once
trust
me I am going to walk over there even if
it takes me
forever I don't care what was she saying
though what was the cookie lady saying
did you finish them already did you did
you eat them all
up it was still good yeah thank you good
I want to give you a snack
box we were kind of like talking about I
wanted to buy her uh like a [\h__\h] ton of
snacks and have her bring them home but
you said in the end your your uh luggage
was full so probably better that
way that I didn't make you a snack box
to bring home h
but make a spare yeah but eventually I
want to make you snack box and and I'll
send it to you
okay please enjoy Austrian snackles
Austrian SL German
snacks oh yeah P only found out this
week yeah I mean it is pretty recent the
announcement I I didn't talk about it at
all yet H I did know about it way longer
so I had a lot of time to mentally
prepare for
that and I mean it's not like we won't
talk anymore you know we will talk off
stream we might even meet you know IRL
you
know so it's fine I guess but no I'm
it's not fine I was really sad cuz I'm
thinking of the
pomes and I'm thinking of her artist
this is one thing that makes me really
sad with these like graduations or
terminations or whatever like I see
the reactions of the artist today also I
saw I watched a bit of the stream from
M's Mama artist mama and she was crying
so
much [\h__\h] breaks my heart man cuz
oh Pomo P's artist too is like really
really
supportive and and and really really
likes her a
lot M's Artist as
well yeah and pule puckle papa of course
was also like an extremely supportive
one so oh man like they they put so much
work into the design you know and then
in future outfits as well
and
uh and they they really love what
they've created because it's not just an
illustration it's a moving illustration
it streams it's a person it's a person
it's more than just one illustration
so it's really painful for them breaks
my heart seeing their reactions and all
that and even though I can talk to
pomu afterwards it's still
like I don't know kind of sad to see a
legend go you know cuz she's first
generation first generation and and
she's
pmer she's pommer like where where will
P be if not there where where is my
fairy going to go she's so she's like oh
a legend she's so funny and she she's so
cute and she always like was a my I from
my observations I would say she's like
one of the
pillars pillars of her branch and it's
just so
devastating I mean just because of like
time difference and me just generally
not having time to watch other people's
streams I didn't watch much of her
content and but I still always enjoyed
her
Antics and her as a person her
personality her ideas for streams her
little attachments that she would put on
herself especially recently I really
liked her
nose and yeah she's just such a
sweet sweet potato I really love her
Metal Gear brain Rod yeah she's a
freaking Legend and the one thing that's
certain is that her Legend will be
written in history books and no one will
forget her and there will definitely be
like a big part
missing no one could ever replace pomu
she left her Mark for sure for real for
real I love her so much I love
Pomo I feel
like
Pomo Pomo is such
a such a sweetheart she I think I
remember she like
first reached out to me I
think or did I reach out to her I don't
know but like she said that she's really
fond of me and that made me so happy to
have someone who says they're fond of me
you know like narissa but back then
hearing it from pomu like I didn't have
that experience before like from from a
from someone who's not like a you know
just a viewer but someone who's in the
industry
basically made me feel very flattered
and
honored
yeah
Pomeranian yeah she messaged me yeah she
every once in a while she would like
message me if she's like worried about
me so uh while no one else
would
so ah such a kind soul she will be
missed I don't know it's it's so weird I
know that I can still talk to her but
it's still heartbreaking but my heart is
mostly breaking for all the fans you
know where is this ah there you
are there you
are oh [\h__\h] Sparks let's let's have you
here
too actually
uh
[Music]
upgrade
P well I hope she won't be happy in her
future
endeavors that is the most important
thing the only important
thing let me repair this breaks really
fast huh also this doesn't update right
away that's kind of weird confusing so I
don't know if it really
worked
I wish the best for me
too me too same for
me I'm going to call in tomorrow to say
goodbye is it tomorrow tomorrow
for my time zone or tomorrow
for if she lets me I will call
in wasn't it the 20th
yeah I thought it was the
20th I
[Music]
mean yeah I I I I'll I might I'll ask
her though cuz I don't know if she will
want like Outsiders to call
in oh colins are tomorrow oh she has a
separate stream for Collins oh okay okay
I'll I'll check with her
H what should I do I need to capture
more more
Pals more Pals need to be
captured also we need to level up and
explore a little bit further what's my
level right
now eight I need to capture
more I need more stamina too I should
get some
stamina so if I spawn this one's going
to attack too
right I can only have one out at
once guess it would be too op to have
too many
out no stamina yeah I need to get
stamina for
real also I need more balls I always
need more balls let me get that that
thing over there is that a teleportation
statue thingy let's go get
it
[Music]
wait let me jump over
there
ice on the Phoenix is really
painful but you can't get me down I got
my PS by my side oh you fended it off
you little
[\h__\h] yo and another one yo nice nice
nice where's my pal there you are I am
actually they have the perfect element
oh
how dare
you is there such a thing as like
elements Elementary
actions
Yahoo yo yo yo
yo
probably I mean would be cool would make
sense to have it in the game there has
to be a I think there
is M do I want more Penguins I don't
really want more Penguins but there's
nothing else interesting around is there
like Pokemon in the
water no but there's a
beach look at that
beach what is this dark
egg what are these
like Easter eggs oh there they are
Pokemon in the water Easter eggs that
are like sprinkled across the is this
like a
collectible
dark egg is this newa
egg pal did I say did I say the p word a
[\h__\h] I need I mean pal
[\h__\h]
ah I said it a lot well sometimes it was
like somewhat consciously but this this
was definitely subconsciously there's an
egg normal egg very normal
egg okay
touch yay oh it gives me a technology
Point
H that looks like they're like uh on top
of each other those chicken looks like a
totem pole chicken
but no probably not there's also a
skilled eylander over there does he want
to fight me too what do you
think
kativa no it happened too
fast how unfortunate what the [\h__\h] is
that another
chest can I open
it ooh
lots of
money think I should go back though I've
come so far but I got to go back I think
can I how do I teleport from here can
I this is my
base can I not go
there do I have to go through uh a
teleportation Point
here like how it jumps like delayed with
me
[Music]
cute w why is it sleeping on top of my
roof
cute is that that's the one that's going
to go k k in the
[Music]
morning you heard it you heard it here
first K KY key indeed
oh wait I can have another pal
here and then I'll make another bed here
how about a
penglin need lots of variety I know I
said I'll make it all kfp but they seem
to pretty be pretty useless I'm sorry so
I got to have
variety it is what it
is having everything wiped afterwards
makes it seem so like meaningless to
build
things I hate when things get wiped in
Games N the [\h__\h] Daydream written with d
AE it's
beautiful he's looking at
me wait uh oh my God he's looking at
me I have to catch it it seems kind of
rare oh so magical
mystical I barely am doing damage I hope
I can get like a better weapon
soon now um before it's too late there
there Go Get It Go Get It and night time
look it's
daytime oh yeah right I have a
spare oh do I have to equip it oh my God
wait there's more oh this one died a
don't play with the dead body oh man I
didn't know there was another one the
hell
H okay
wait uh what was I going to do I yeah
equip
how ah spare I guess just instead of the
stick should be good
right
[Music]
okay what about technology how are we
doing we have seven
points Fox Parks harness harness for
holding Fox Sparks activate its partner
skill to hold Fox SPS and attack using
it as a
flamethrower
what place it at the base oh cool that's
cool what is this
unlocked after certain Palace has been
captured yeah which
one logging lodging logging side can
produce wood at a base oh cool
ah there's the saddle I need the
saddle caller for Dam if dam is in your
team it will stay by your side and
attack enemies in
tandem what why did I need to a collar
for that will it not attack otherwise
why the other ones attack
attack
poison Crusher facility for breaking
down Stone and wood to exchange them for
other
materials
interesting ah to have two at once oh
interesting a bat for close range combat
so this is like a
better Bonk
stick and this is for this is also e is
the bat B better than the stone
Spar I just switched it
out let's learn
this I mean this kind of makes no sense
right now to get like a lot of
decorative
things can't get that huh
okay spare is range it both say close
range though but I can imagine that the
spare has a bit better
range I don't know if
I so does the logging side have to be by
a tree I assume no not
necessarily ah well I need wood
okay check the left purple line left
purple
line you mean in in the technology
tree oh egg
in oh wait a pal egg so does the dark
egg count for
example I can't choose that
though who what the [\h__\h] was that don't
make such weird sounds freaks me
out
z a you're so sweet thank you I did kind
of read it but thank you wait I need
even more wood oh my
God it is for those
eggs the sapling is on the
roof is he stuck there it also one of my
chickens is on the
roof
cute
ow I am overweight but it's okay cuz I'm
going to put this right
here come on my friends let's build it
together
[Music]
yeah he's stuck in his star oh oh okay
I'll try to push him off off of
[Music]
it why don't you put your mats oh I
don't know instincts make me want to
keep it okay move how do I move you if I
if I punch it it won't hate me
right everything looks so painful maybe
punch it oh
no ah wait I can pick it up right uh how
do I pick it up
again what
wasn't there like a prompt to pick it
up F if it's not working if it's not
working maybe from
below a there we
go n what are you
doing does the chicken need help
too what you want to stay up there huh
you so
cute my good morning chicken K
kittyy available in IM switch to
automatic work yeah do whatever you need
to
do it's like oh finally some good
[\h__\h] food I was stuck up there
forever no one was helping me I thought
I was going to die on her roof and she
just wouldn't notice my
cry yeah sorry about
that oh wait the chest just is so small
need to make
more oh
wood always out of
wood actually
fascinating is there a bigger chest
maybe there's a recipe for it but I
haven't seen one
yet how's that would F work I would
assume that it's also working on its
own I mean I can work it but I would
hope that the palace work it cuz like
what else are they here
for master XOne thank you than
you for the
[Music]
pinky
don't you already have a big chest are
you making a
joke so you guys say I can use it even
if it's in the chest
right that better be
true what about the
coins if I don't have them with me can I
buy things on a merchant though I should
I have them with me
well let's test this I have I put the
pium fragments in there let's see if I
can build some more palum
spheres also got to make those eggs into
fried eggs before they go
off this is not going to accidentally
use my dark egg
right I
hope ah thank you for Pinky ah so many
super
[Music]
why it does use those eggs I I would
hope so but can you guys really say for
sure you guys don't even have access to
the game
yet
just
saying educated
guest I mean I I would really assume the
same thing but
yeah just checking just
checking I think I want to switch out
you
guys
it looks so cool so far the designs are
really pretty awesome I mean some seem
rather
familiar oh hey I can't make it but okay
it's because of the
wood but generally I I really like the
designs they look good ride the meaka I
need the saddle for it
no I haven't I think I got the recipe
for it
though it's not in here
right okay we can make it no
problem yeah I need to make the
saddle oh saddle was uh did I get the
[Music]
recipe
I feel like I saw the sadle recipe
somewhere but now I can't see
it I got
it ah from yeah I saw it an AAL Gear
Station ah so many different ways of
building like in like like uh this way
of building has different
things and then that one over there the
workbench and then this one it's a bit
[Music]
confusing makes me think of Digimon more
oh I I uh there's this one Digimon game
Digimon
game that I was watching a friend play a
long time
ago diyon is really not my thing like I
never was really interested going to be
honest but it looked really good looked
fun I think it was
on was it on the switch or was it on the
PlayStation now I'm not
sure diyon yeah everybody in the German
language says
diyon
Whoa there's um M's dad over there and
y'all what who are
you who
cus M would love that name
uh-oh wait don't kill it right away
guys wa uh uhuh I'm going to leave the
damage to them cuz they're going to
Overkill uh
no oh it resisted and it [\h__\h] died
well that's your fault you were pretty
low on
HP so even in this area where first it
seemed that only like weak enemies were
spawning now like the spawn is looking
different like even during the daytime
you guys said nighttime spawn but now I
constantly have Daydream it's literally
a Daydream not a night dream so I'm not
surprised wait is that a oh that's one
that's not dead is it are they fighting
it don't
fight I want to capture it don't kill
it where is the dead
body no I would see it that maybe it
rolled away though wait there's
something new over there
too yeah I think it like must be scaling
oh that's is that thing alive that one's
alive
okay whoa you want to come down maybe no
oh
God
uh-oh quick quick before it does oh the
the pressor wait you really don't want
to get captured
huh come
on yeah what's the M I'm going to waste
all my balls on it come on come on there
we go there we go that's that's how I
like it yo finally newbie Paul T called
10 kinds of Pals let's go oh my God the
the prussel is Brussels why are they
called the prussel oh no you made me
waste the ball you little
[\h__\h] oh o look at these
Majestic deers
gorgeous now I have to find some more
depressed
Pals cuz you killed both of them foxb
and now you're poisoned well I hope you
enjoy
that yeah will it still get poison
damage I wonder if I retract it
I can't believe now they're not around
anymore isn't that one kind of weirdly
big no that's normal
size What's My Level
now
[Music]
eight no you guys are not all depressed
pals are
you don't say that it would break my
heart why are you running so fast level
11 okay I'm not going to attack that
one go for the bird I was thinking about
it but I think it's still two levels
above
me I'd rather capture the the
presso or this Daydream I know I already
have
oh huh where did that go
come on come on come
on 11 more Pals guys am am I going to
even ever reach
that I don't know cuz I don't know how
long I should really stream but let me
eat a cookie how about that I think
that's the best
idea to eat a cookie
now
what's going on who are you fighting
those
cats no no don't no no what's going
on those cats are attacking it
too
[Music]
uhoh
wa yeah I'll save you I'll bring you to
safety just stay in the ball no why
would you choose to be attacked by
them why would you prefer
that no you little
[\h__\h] yes here one last try please
no you're not doing yourself any
favors did I get more exp when
I help in the
[Music]
battle uh-oh
uh-oh
a whoa whoa whoa whoa now my crew is
coming look at
them oh my
God just looks like a
ra Crazy Action oh my
God you guys did it you did it
you Avenged
me thank you only we got some good
venison from
[Music]
that
nice but I would have liked to capture
one they're so pretty I guess you can
probably ride on them too
maybe let me
go are you
stuck
let me try to help
you all right I can't can't pick it up
this is mine
[Music]
right no I can't I can't even it's not
rag doll either I think it's
bug can I reset it
somehow or maybe if I go to
[Music]
theh wait I did capture one I don't
remember that I
did what can you do my
friend M it's going to be working on the
logging it says logging for man up up
up he's really slow
though the chicken is also
bugged you think
so does that do the trick I think so
okay yum these cookies are so good I'm
I'm eating the the slight orange
tasting um chocolate ball
cookies
chinis did you use the statue yet no I
should they're so
[Music]
good
yummy okay what is this oh aha I have
one Li monk fig that I I like found
somewhere W whoo whoa wo what what what
did I
do now my capture power is stronger I
guess so I can
capture Pals
[Music]
easier
okay I'll go to
[Music]
sleep
K does that only happen when you have a
a chicken in your
base the kiky key the morning kiky
key I love it
it's exactly what you need in the
morning unless you actually IRL have
like um chickens that wake you up at
like 5:00 a.m. K the keying then you
probably would be annoyed by
it unless you have it so often like and
so so many like several ones then you
probably get so used to it you don't
even hear it
anymore but if they don't belong to you
but to a neighbor you probably get
really [\h__\h] annoyed by it you have
have to
really show me pictures why have you not
showed me pictures on Twitter yet
H where are the pics show pics or it
didn't
happen at 4:30 yeah they they they yell
quite early don't
they my mom wants to get chickens
probably this summer oh look at that
over there I should go get that
I can make that swim right
Yoo yeah she's she wants to build a
chicken cop
first she used to have chickens
before so you know she's used to
it
yay where am
I
yeah fresh eggs every
morning probably more than you
need what's that over there I saw
something
red oh oh oh fire
egg scorching egg Fenix
egg that's my
egg wow
egg I will personally sit on this egg to
make it
hatch I don't need that
incubator eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs let's
go oh there's an fig in there
too and some other cool stuff do you
think he'll let me take
it you got some cool stuff there I don't
even have to talk to you huh
hey and then what the hell is that poor
NY oh it looks like a like the thing
that I have the the pad the iPad oh
another Journal I see I
see haven't looked at the other one
even oh yeah I guess in my lore Phoenix
don't lay eggs yeah that's true this is
just a fire egg
um but I can still hatch it you know you
guys can hatch eggs too you know
everybody can hatch an egg if they want
to you're a new face don't tell me an
outsider not that it matters to me now
that you're in this island why not try
and catch some PS like you can get extra
XP for capturing up to 10 of the same oh
really you know what they say pal Tam
get stronger the more Pals they capture
here take this I've got high hopes for
you ooh thank you some more fr
I appreciate
that 10 of the same type
h that I don't know how much extra exp
you would get from that generally I
don't like capturing the same pal over
and over again are
those they look fiery why are they in
the water are those the foxes the fox
Sparks
n it's it's really
dumb what are they doing
there
crazy what's that is that a
mushroom oh oh no it's like wool
what randomly lying around
okay what's the pr of fox
Sparks F
Fox well several Sparks probably make a
thunder maybe I don't know you wanted me
to say fox Sparks is or so right what is
this that's something new te Fant a is
it like a like a tea a kettle tea uh not
t Kettle but like the thing that holds
the
T oh that was cl close it almost
died large amounts of water pour from
what is f to be its nose don't some say
it is in fact just not ew This SP has
sparked a fierce debate among pal
schoers
oh oh that's a that's a Mont AKA c c
c yo I saw snowling was so cool when we
went out of the boat in like Depot
Waters we didn't see the
shark but cuz they said we might see
sharks but we saw I'm glad we didn't see
sharks we saw like several different
kind of
rays and the the turtle was so Random in
the beginning we saw a big turtle zo
zooming around but the Rays usually were
like in pairs except for the one so I I
I asked you know uh we saw two Eagle
Rays in they came in in the pair and
then we also saw a stingray and the
stingray looked really interesting to me
because the the Eagle Rays they were
like kind of triangle shaped and the
stingray was so much bigger than the uh
Eagle Rays that I
saw uh the stingray was like round and
looked almost like a taco because the
the edges of it were like moving like a
like a taco like in waves in a wavy
shape you know what I mean where did
that r go no I got I'll get one of
those yeah yeah we talked about the
Steve irvan incident just the other day
huh I think in my was it in my member
stream must have been in my member
Stream So that made me think
yab Stingray sounds dangerous kind of
scary can I shoot the
ball no can I attack somehow here oh
it's going away I have to climb up up
attack it from above just don't provoke
them I guess oh that made me think so
stingrays they have that sting
yeah the
sting that they can kill of or several
like when it attacks I guess it shoots
out millions of stings in an instant so
tell me
please the other Rays I I have I have
seen also
have
ah wait no don't kill
it also have like Tails but they're not
called stingrays but they look the same
like the tails look the same can they
also attack the same
way you can ride those to Glide I would
be too scared you know knowing the story
of Steve Irvin even though that one was
just scared cuz of the Shadow or
whatever from Steve but still like I
would never attempt
that Stingray specifically have a
stinger I'm not talking about monterays
I'm talking about eag eagle ray right e
Ray
yeah eagle
ray eagle ray feet on mollusks and
Crustaceans crushing their shells with
their flattened teeth okay so this one
us it teeth but it also has a tail that
looks the same way as the stingray tail
so does it not is that just decoration
does this one does the eagle ray not
have oh what the
[\h__\h] does the eagle ray not have the
same
[Music]
thing no sting oh all the rays are safe
only stingr have a secondary sting for
real rush rush is like rush hour and
it's rushing y so far a
no God damn it such a
waste at least let me capture
you thank you normal way use it to stare
oh so it doesn't have a sting
home that is very
interesting oh we should get that
FG just stare in the middle of nowhere
what is
this small CLE oh I forgot what that
does what that what that
is I don't have no I have no idea where
the [\h__\h] [\h__\h] we are right now like I
got kind of
lost
sidetracked if you see the stingray
Stinger it's a spike or small
spikes yeah just because we talked about
it in the member stream I afterwards
looked up like a video about uh Steve
Irvin like how it happened and
everything and oh my God that's [\h__\h]
[Music]
terrifying cuz I thought oh like from
what I heard I thought like maybe it
shoots once like he got shot once from
the stingray but no like it shoots
hundreds of of its little little spikes
spikes oh my
[Music]
God and I saw one of those deadly
creatures in
[Music]
person
crazy if you think about it nature is
crazy and
terrifying I mean I was kind of like it
was pretty far but I was like pretty
much directly above it we were in a
group oh
egg but yeah it was pretty far cuz the
waters were pretty deep we were like
swimming around the edge of uh coral
reef [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] and the cor re itself was pretty
normal but it was pretty big pretty
long and we weren't allowed to go over
the the edge of it where it gets like
really dark
blue so what the [\h__\h] are
you oh you're duck a [\h__\h] duck
what I don't know where the name comes
from I'm trying to find out wait why do
I still have the wooden Club did I not
save what where's
the where did my spare
go a
platus it's cute the ear are making it
look like
no I hate you you're going to pay for
that oh but wait you made me find the
treasure
chest nice oh 19
arrows ooh
mushrooms okay you come back now cuz
it's really
annoying although with two enemies it
would kind of be helpful especially cuz
one is level six oh [\h__\h]
what
help me after
all wait I'm out of balls now
no I have to go
back get some balls I
guess where am I though uh oh
no I'm so
far what's that looks like a Tey I'm so
far is it this
way oh my
God and we can't just teleport like that
is that a blue egg up
there I have an eye for
eggs maybe there's a Teleport near bar I
don't see
one didn't see one it's okay we'll
explore a little
more we can pick up eggs on the
way there was
one wait is it this
thing well then maybe I'll run back to
it after I get the
egg what let me
climb you showed me the egg now I want
it oh there it is water egg
okay damp egg
so okay it's like straight
ahead moist
egg a glider
yeah I have the recipe for it but I
didn't build one it's okay it's okay
you know narissa loved my cat so much
which is no surprise because everybody
who meets my cats is like absolutely oh
um in love with
them and she said she wants to
get the same species so like either
either a Cheeto or a radioactive cat I
guess she loves them so much that she
wants to get one of them
yo L tells you how [\h__\h] Charming my
cats are nobody can resist
them yeah my cats are the
best they make everybody fall in love
with them even though they're kind of
weird like they are so shy they love
cuddling but at the same time they're so
shy and run away from
people reliable PF officer that sounds
wait you're an
enemy
oh ever bumped into an extraordinary
strong and big pal just my speculation
but it seems to be some kind of leader
who controls the pal around if you could
make it your ally it would sure be handy
but it's super powerful so be careful
yeah I won't I won't attempt don't
worry this looks like one of these rust
camps where you can like destroy these
things and like get some scraps out of
it what are you cooking
here FX a cave no there's caves I've
heard that caves are home to loads of
unique Pals what's more there there are
even more even treasure TRS created by
Pals with a neck of neck for collecting
stuff give me a shout out if you spot
any caves will you
no the caves will be mine oh look at you
there's a merchant you think he knows
about what I
did got some good items oh really oh
what is this oh oh hats I was wondering
like where where are the hats
the Hat recipes you got them all why why
do you have them
all why are you hogging them pinking
cap unlocks recipe for paning cap can be
what are these caps long your headband
Which hat wait which one should I get I
guess farming hat would give me like a
farming buff or
so they'll never find a body yet cuz it
despawned
I know yeah this sounds
interesting wait I barely have money oh
my
God
okay
H did that count the money that I have
in
my um base
no
right I surely have
more they're not even mad that I woke
them up why why is the ink keeper
sleeping it's like they're advertising
like hey you can sleep here very
[Music]
nice I don't need to rest thank
you
boat
egg you're hiding an egg over here huh
you think you can keep it for me oh
there's a there's a freaking
cave it's a
dungeon level 13
boss well well I don't know where the
[\h__\h] my spare went maybe I I don't want
to go without my
spare wait but I activated the
Waypoint so what's this King
pcka
what
yo ah uh wait I need to go to the
thing
yeah let me go back rare yeah but
there's no way that I can fight it right
level
23 guys that would be
crazy that would be kind of
[Music]
crazy
oh my backpack oh there it is why is it
here though I thought maybe it broke or
something I don't know
M but it's okay we can craft some things
and check up on
everybody nobody's bugged or
so wait so did I never make this did I
really never make it
wait do you guys see a saddle here I
don't see one let's make the saddle so
we can
ride our MPA I made it I did make get
didn't I where' it go is it just
automatically on on the m p car
[Music]
yeah a some key items so how do
I wait Stay
Stay oh ride
oh oh well yeah it doesn't have
to
the the saddle on is that just
like it doesn't appear
visually I guess okay that's pretty cool
though that we can do that now we can
even attack I
guess
nice good to have for sure
[Music]
wait I should make the crusher and the
stone pit really
quickly oh I don't think I have the
recipe for it
though Tech
tree oh wait I have oh wait there's a
saddle for the rusher oh and gloves
gloves for gently holding on to oh it
can be used as a
glider what oh that's it's kind of cool
though that you can basically replace
certain
items with like the we do have a
parachute so I guess it's like you know
instead of that replacing that is pretty
cool so Stone pit and a
Crusher it's getting dark again I want
to put some torches around to oh
we need more wood and more wood okay no
problem uh where is a
axe why are you not with
me anyone working along inside I guess
not I
mean
you thought he meant real life who whoa
whoa what was that about I was talking
about yeah snorkeling and seeing real
live race but I didn't mean a manay we
didn't see
Monteray I was a bit like shocked though
like on on my last day on our departure
day it's like really early
morning and right at the dock where the
planes the sea planes leave and arrive
there's a little bit of a snorkeling
area a little bit of a coral reef there
and I've been uh using
that and I saw I indeed in that very
morning saw like two
small some Eagle Rays probably just
roaming around
casually only on this very last day in
the early morning I saw those rids small
race and like a a t a
turtle basically saying goodbye to me
me but there was like a a couple uh a
pair a pair of British people and they
were like oh yeah um just yesterday we
saw a Monteray here I'm
like
really what what what what do you mean
raid what does that
mean am I being
raided what does that
mean wa that's so sudden I was telling a
story
close wa have to sound the alarm [\h__\h]
I'm so
slow
ah ah where's the
wood what do that
[Music]
mean what does that
mean currently attacking Invaders oh
okay wait where are there oh they're
coming what if I just
sleep can I sleep
oh the
British
what it's real
people
uh what The Syndicate
fog what the [\h__\h] yeah they have guns
what the [\h__\h] is the problem
what's your
problem Oh one's dead already oh they
dropped some cool stuff oh ammo wait
it's already done and I even
slept I was even able to
sleep
what what the hell gold
coin po spere waa let's
go now I have all these dead bodies
right
here can somebody move them get rid of
them what the
hell that was so sudden I was so
confused but I was saying um yeah they
were like boasting that they saw m but I
don't think they they knew what they
were
saying that I don't think they would be
monter R there really close to the land
like they said oh yeah just a small one
but like M do you even know like I don't
know I can't tell the difference they
all look the same to me on the water
like are you sure you saw [\h__\h]
m i don't believe it m are so huge right
normally yeah but surely they also grow
up and are not huge from the get-go but
still I don't quite believe them but
first at first I was kind of gullible
and kind of believed them I was
like I can't believe they saw a [\h__\h]
Monteray and I got kind of jealous but
like immediately after that I looked
into the water and I saw hi KY I saw a
lot of uh cool things like those two
Eagle
Rays saying goodbye to me before I
left KY what did Kyla say is she saying
let's play together or
what I'm scrolling
up oh is it a Kyla
raid
ah let me guess the raid comes from
uh her also playing this the very same
game right
before how fitting one okay one power
word rail to raid to
another I speaking of raid thank you
Kyla for the raid you kind of Shook at
me cuz I got raided in game as well at
right before Oh who who who who you can
definitely tell a monter and other RS
apart even on water although some might
confuse those with with Eagle Rays yeah
I mean the Eagle Rays I saw are really
tiny and I would imagine the M Rays
would be bigger and also like color the
Eagle Rays they have like this pattern
Monta oh the mon yeah the Monteray looks
very different it it has like not such a
weird pattern not like a like the eagle
has like almost like a leopard pattern
at this monay it even has like these
weird ears eyes whatever they look so
funny I don't believe them there's no
way there's no
way Kyla oh did you write something in
chat now let me see let me see let me
see my chat isn't moving my chat isn't
moving oh I can't see oh there it is
have fun P the game is so fun oh yeah
KY yeah yeah I'll I'll have fun only
today and then I'll go on my break and
everybody else will be playing the game
and I'll be I'll be
gone I'm so sad I'm so
sad and then I join the game and
everybody will be like the server
everybody will be overleveled have huge
bases I wonder you guys said there's no
PVP right so at least they can't all
[\h__\h] kill me when I join the server
as a [\h__\h]
[Music]
Noob Alo from Stones I can get or is it
the other way around no it is this way
around
okay they plan to implement it
eventually okay please take your [\h__\h]
time don't implement it until much much
later please for my
sake oh man I have to I'll have I have
to catch up with
[Music]
everybody they keep on adding stuff huh
I don't need to even add
anything but I'm fairly hungry let's see
what's can I
sort anyway I'll eat
this yo how many eggs do I have have
[Music]
crazy
yeah let me break some more berries I
[Music]
guess I wonder if you can build like
really tall
towers like in a
rust like really crazy to remember the
pioda base in the ocean where everybody
attacked her I wonder if he can build
something like that probably right but
there surely is no automatic turrets and
stuff
right oh we could check out the tree
wait I need to acquire do I need to
yeah and let me put the baked berries
into
the into here though I don't need the
baked berries
enjoy
wait uh let me make it only one huh what
do you mean only
one
St I need more Stone oh easy Stone's
easy right Stone surely my pals
eh they have not created any stone
rubbles what the
[\h__\h] also how do I assign them wait who
could who could work on the Stone from
these I need to
check you need kativa pal for okay where
where is
it currently not working huh sorry
chicken oh you want to eat first feel
free what's this
sound n n n n okay we're done with n n n
n let me try to assign you
you ta all right it works and for the
lumber I feel like I
saw that one of you definitely has the
ability to work on
[Music]
it and how do I see it
uh I at this one doesn't loging format
to me sounds like he can do it where is
he
maybe he's bugged
somewhere you come with me work here he
was in front of me didn't see him okay
nice no work
suitability
huh who else you're watering how about
who could maybe like
a a boar
maybe I guess I could check the PEX but
it's okay I'll try the
boore oh don't run so fast oh he wants
to
mine wait all of them are working on at
the stones now are you not capable
of working here though why do they all
have mining cap capability look about
here no
wait ah it doesn't work okay he goes
mining okay well at least they do that
on their own so I would assume that if I
had someone who could be the the Woodman
then they would already do it on their
own okay let's see
pal
farming where would it lumbering
lumbering
oh
handywork handy work
planting Gathering
watering handywork
transporting
mining I might literally not have anyone
yet who can do that that's okay though I
just wanted to build those things so I
can
upgrade Max pounds looking a base oh
wait no uh build hot spring build
primitive
furnace uh wait what did that just say I
already forgot the Primitive furnace and
what was the other
thing I also wanted to build the
Torches I want to build the
torches on oh yeah right I saw the
recipe for that
before h
I thought we can attach them to the
house no okay so they'll just be like
around
here you guys don't have to come over
I'm doing it on my
own
nice maybe I'll put them like even
around
here you guys can build that one I don't
care so that we just had have better
visibility or all over torch you think
it will burn I feel like it probably
won't have that function in in the first
place one
[Music]
here one
here nice be pretty
good okay let's
[Music]
see and hand stats we need maybe some
stamina and what
about technology here's the hot spring
yeah I can
already make
one wait it's not
there probably need needs
Stones where is
it there it is insufficient more wood
and more
Stone well if only they weren't working
so [\h__\h]
slowly give Koreans money power come Mel
star oh did you guys
see
um K is normally on Twitch right but she
has a YouTube channel too where she
uploads uh clips and they're they're
edited quite
nicely H and she uploaded a clip that's
like kind of a compilation of our
interaction so
far I didn't know she was going to do
that I was surprised by it
he but uh at the very end she kind of
teases a
collab um I can say yeah we we will
collab but there's no date or anything
set yet but
a nice teaser got people really excited
too I
think yeah she'll help me set up uh my
things my 3D things I think and then we
can do it because I think we want our
collab to be like kind of
3D
heavy I I want to match with her I want
to be 3D with
[Music]
her that could be one thing that I might
look into my break I don't really want
to because that means I have to go onto
Discord uh because we would communicate
over
Discord I just like squint when I look
at Discord and only look at what G is
writing to me when I squint maybe I
won't see all the other
[Music]
messages I don't
know ideally I don't want to really look
at any of that but the truth is uh I
kind of possibly need to record a dance
choreography on my
break so I'll I I don't want to but uh
there's
like some scheduling for the video the
the music
video for my next
single basically like because of Kana
uu's Avail availability I I kind of need
to do it
early possibly during my
break so I need to learn to dance and
record the Coro but first i'm I'm still
not quite sure with you know using the
exent suit I'm I'm still a little bit
lost right Stones you guys yeah why are
you not working there
now what the
[\h__\h] why did they all stop
working no works are the build with
cooling what do you
mean oh is he on cool down ah he's on a
short break it says never mind
then
sorry I'll do it myself then fine I'll
do it myself do I even is this more
efficient
than ah wait where's my pickaxe though
then hitting normal
stones
what am I
doing need the stone for them focus on
the wood but I want some Stone
now oh this gives me ore and more ore oh
this one doesn't even give me stone
huh
he it wasn't enough Stone to build
the the
on
so shees I'm so oh my God I'm so heavy
oh now we're missing palum
fragments
uh I'll drop this remind me of it I
don't want to
forget what do you mean I have no Stones
no fancy
Stones
uh finally a normal looking Avatar you
mean my
character are are the others all making
them look weird
the ones from the Japanese girls I saw
all looked really cute though the though
sorry had some cookie stuck in my throat
oh look at him he's like you shall not
pass sounds about
right wait P I guess I need pal speres
too but h
both coyote and CI made them
really Mooky Mooky
oh why not why not I mean if you want to
survive in this kind of world you got to
be Mooky
mookie who is whoever is m mie is
definitely definitely has an
advantage
let me put the eggs here since I don't
have the incubator yet oh wait Can I
stack them
no this is uncommon this is common oh
cuz this one's large
[Music]
oo coar
ammo or poison
[Music]
arrow
every day was leg
day oh leg
day I've been skipping leg day and arm
day and every every
day so
sad been
slacking but I I have a running machine
now I just need to you know find some
space for it and unpack it and all that
but the time the time will come don't
worry about it I'm serious about it wait
build oh yeah build hot spring let me
build the hot spring now I have the
fragments but I don't have the stone and
the wood oh my
God what about the one that I dropped
does
that where did I drop it
here
Stone
next year for sure no no this year this
year I just need some time you know I
have some some crazy [\h__\h] going
on IRL you know I'm
busy I'll be taking care of a lot of
things once I am
free from
work I recorded free songs today yo
free free
audioos yeah yeah yeah did some work
today very efficient
yeah free vocal
tracks oh it's like a it's like a kitty
pool nice
everybody will so be be so delighted by
that I wonder if that boosts their moral
not that they need it if they're working
for
[Music]
me it is a candy pool but made out of
proper material so yeah okay now it
doesn't look quite like a kitty
pool what I don't get wet from this I
went a big [\h__\h] boar in there
he's happy oh he's falling asleep in it
oh that's cute is it like a bed does it
count as a
bed wait what was the other thing uh
primitive furnace I don't have the
recipe for that do
I where is
it ah this
one I can't get that one we take a
while uh producing hot climates helps to
fend off the
[Music]
heat damn so much stuff to
get seeing them happy heals me oh he's
still in it he really likes
it let me sleep flame organ is a drop
from the fire fox oh
yeah I'm sure it is
is
get Happy Chicken he's not even like out
here but he's still kiky key so maybe
you don't need a chicken to hear the
kiky
key uh we should should should I go into
that
cave well even if I go I feel like
maybe a few more balls would be nice oh
I can make eight let's
go statue first oh okay
okay true cuz I have all the Fig still
have enough for an
upgrade
no I have I need one
more what are you doing up there are you
okay there's one stuck again why do they
get stuck so
often that's that's an
issue these ones keep on turning
themselves off
huh or is it just my
imagination wait what was I going to do
oh yeah reset the
pal oh oh wait I can also add another
one oh I don't
know what can you do again I
forgot but let's have you around cuz you
look
cool that's The Monto
R yeah oh so
cute ah yeah I need beds for them true
true
true for one
more how
[Music]
about here you guys can build that I'll
leave it to
you get one to work on W I literally
have no one I already checked my palex I
have no one who can work on the
wood may maybe I'll get to capture one
soon actually if that big boy that deer
is around I'd like to capture that one
right
now go go
go they are around in a
pair they appear to be a pair level 10
and level
11 I'll try to get the level 10 one into
a
ball
o wait
wait
oh oh my God why
why
please but do I get it do I get it
though yeah I got
it if I was alive would I have gotten
it that looked like the animation for
getting
it n the [\h__\h]
why are they so strong why do they hate
me so
[Music]
much level 9 Fox
Fox oh they're so low HP no don't run
[Music]
away
yeah that's probably what messed up my
inventory
dying got their attention why is this
one
running come
[Music]
on be one of
kfp you know you want it it that worked
right did it yes I think
so
woohoo it's in danger no it's going to
die
yeah another one another
one no okay you shall
[Music]
die that's what you get for being so
naughty naughty why don't you want to be
with your friend
huh well not my problem oh we should try
to get the bird now
Nightwing o
but
[Music]
oh
cies is it going to come down when I
attack
it oh
yes oh I I'm out of
arrows brand straight into that I might
die
oh
also when you get like really close you
know like this you so close when you
attack that you can't see the HP which
really sucks cuz then I always have to
take a step back to see if I'm not
accidentally
kill what's this dramatic
sound I'm not actually accidentally
killing it you know what I mean y yep
yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep y [\h__\h]
yo
oh quite a
[Music]
challenge oh yeah right I forgot there
was
this
ow um hi at least they don't regain
their HP right away that's pretty
nice
mm wait I do have some more arrows what
the
hell ah the fire bow was the one that
didn't have
anymore will this kill him no
yeah yes that's true no oh really I'll
try again got to try a few times right
how was it able to attack me
oh I forgot how to throw the ball okay
there we
go I got nervous and I forgot how to
throw the ball so I almost killed it oh
yo yo yo
woohoo let's
go
hey carries newborn Pals to its nest and
raises them as a surate parent
[Music]
what that's
cute newborn
Pals
mommy M sorry Mommy oh you're right that
reminded me of
something this hat hat makes you feel
like you can use P what
yeah but I do want better armor but like
there's not really much that I can
do
[Music]
anyway how about we switch a
rule
uh like these for
now I'm going to eat something
too
nice put the deer to work oh what does
it do can that
one do uh
woodwork oopsie what did I
do oh I
can all
right that shall be your destiny
then uh the deer right yeah okay maybe
instead of I have so many working on the
stone so and also watering I don't need
these two I think are watering no this
one too let's get rid of that
one ah
sorry then I actually let me bring let
me bring you you look interesting
finally getting some work done over here
ah it's about time oh look at him
look at him bonking his head against the
tree sharpening his its antlers like in
real
nature
so oh was sappy boy planting the
seeds do I need him do they all like
serve different worlds
here o really oh well for a while this
is okay
oh [\h__\h] we have way too many berries
anyway look at
that oopsie
no I swear to
God I swear to
God every
time
I was going to do
something what was it what was it what
was it what was it what was
it I
forgot ah I was going to put this
away oh because I don't like how it
keeps on being equipped when I don't
want
it what what the [\h__\h] is that
sound
chill sound bug I
think oh my god oh no it's Cris running
around on fire wait were you did you
walk into the fire take gold you think I
need the the
gold cuz it gets full a building for
storage only well yeah but I mean in the
end this is I'm only playing this game
today and then it gets wiped because I'm
going oh no oh no detox so really not
necessary for me
to you know go that hardcore in my
opinion can you make your witch hat I
can
try no but it needs cloth and ingots I
have no idea how to make ingots so
probably
no no points
[Music]
either yeah let me Grill the meat really
quickly roast egg fur deer carefully
roasted venison with delicate flavor
notes oh my
God M
venison
W what am I going to eat
tonight I think I have I still have a
lot of
leftovers I think I still have
leftover
uh was it L not not lamp chops just um
ribs ribs I have leftover ribs from the
food that I ordered for
[Music]
niss I guess you guys get a lamp no this
you're not you're not you're not worth a
lamp chop I take it
back okay so how do
I can I teleport from
here to
there how do I can I use this as a
teleportation Point
somehow sorry I don't
remember oh and my armor true thank you
for reminding me oh I saw
that ordering ribs for Nisa yes she
wanted meat cuz like the whole day I was
feeding her Austrian desserts cuz
there's so many Austrian desserts we
have like
like some main dishes too that are
Austria only like made in
Austria but desserts somehow we have way
more of
those from the screen thingy at this one
think I see thank
you so I I had her eat apple strudel and
I told you already anyway
bton uh with vanilla sauce some
cakes and what was the other thing kaash
man of course my favorite oh wait
there's a different Merchant here you
you sell
Pals
mozina cute a cow that makes mozzarella
huh I already have the deer no no need
for any of this what the [\h__\h] is
that
where the [\h__\h] do you have a wait the
chair the chair
do what the
[\h__\h] let's get out of here he's a
[\h__\h] gillotin no no it's of all is he
trying to kill humans or
Pals or
both probably doesn't matter to
him okay I'll see if
I
wasn't that black last time is it still
open did they close the [\h__\h] cave it
was
here
no D wait it did have some kind of time
on it didn't
it was like a Time Dungeon right oh my
God can't believe
it not going
well
wait okay now that we can ride our horse
wait it's it's not much faster oh when
it's dashing I guess it's
faster probably has more stamina
too ooh there's a like a rain well not
really they're just chilling
there Vixie who the [\h__\h] is
Vixie
uh ah what the
hell was that an a Pokemon that Vixie oh
it is no looks so cute what the
hell hey don't hurt my my my
Ara
what are those
sounds I still made the sounds when I
was not
attacking what are you
doing [\h__\h]
idiot where's my drop you're not going
to drop me anything egg oh man look at
that poor
baby h oh
H wait why are you attacking us I was
just trying to save the
world what are you
doing let me ride you I can't it's kind
of
stuck let me re reset it
[Music]
basically let's go what's going on here
oh wait I don't want I
don't I don't have these monsters
yet
wa oh let me get up let me get
up spark it man everybody's screaming
Sparks
here level three should go in easily
where did the other one go yo what is
this it's green Le I you already won
that I see the Fig is off all the time
time stop
running stop
[Music]
running it it escaped that one did
Escape oh but this one I got and I'm
level 10
finally what was the other thing the
spark it
right
those two battle it
out oh oh oh oh it died electric organ
oh this one died too [\h__\h]
Massacre I wanted to catch
it
h oh hi welcome
back seems like the boar is still
[Music]
mad no more of the Sparky
boys off br oh FG wait
y' that's the last one that I
[Music]
need y
no you killed them I didn't my pal did
it oh oh look at that pretty
[Music]
baby oh that was kind of early I
shouldn't have done that but maybe it
will work cuz it's pretty low
level oh oh I didn't even have to hurt
it much the idol of palo's Island if you
bully a Vixie you best be prepared to
become enemies with the whole world what
is it like a mascot
oh what was that Arrow vas Mega spere
and gold
coins you're kind of dump aren't you
[Music]
oh you're fighting this one oh my God
stop
fighting blues and bors have beef they
definitely do there's something in the
air that makes them very aggressive ooh
ooh a
ball nice pal spere pal bow pal ball I
guess they didn't call it po ball
because it just kind of sounds
stupid you
what the [\h__\h] are those capry they're
kind of On My
Level but still we have to go down to
their level cuz I'm above them
somehow cuz they're too weak to get up
to my
level
[Music]
uhoh well two at once is actually kind
of [\h__\h] stupid of me oh my God I
can't even I changed my mind changed my
mind change my mind
water am I going to die here
though probably this uh uh-oh wait if my
stamina oh oh no no no no where where am
I going to find my clothes then where am
I going to find my ah
no don't say
denos all it's okay everything will be
wiped
anyway what if you die in the
water be floating okay okay okay don't
scare
me we can get back there surprisingly
big amount of uh uh
deaths I am shooked
let me go
here haha no I'll I'll I'll get my
stuff I'll go get it yeah at least my my
pants are still around and I can still
ride it
so
easy oh this bridge I didn't see that
bridge before I see an fig over
there but but it's okay I
think okay let me get
off the
jumps going to be you're going to be
okay over there egg electric
egg yo my eyes are so good yo didn't get
the Sparks pal but at least I'm getting
that and the [\h__\h] Effigy oh it's so
far that's my
stuff need to go into the water anyway
but
ooh a glider would be nice now you think
I'll okay let's get the stuff
first oh I don't have
a it's okay I don't get damaged that
fast when I'm cold from my
experience oh cuz it's night
time it's fcking oh there it is it's not
even in the
water it's not even in the water
guys they just like put it in the
closest nearby spot
look at that that's a red chest red
chest
n that looks spooky
kaai oh okay old bow
schematic
ow
ah oh it's dead okay
wow good job me P I
guess I like the orange chest more wow
wow wow
[Music]
wow
y
you may be a chicken but you're not
scared of flirting
huh nothing intimidating about that for
you all right I'll risk it oh wait I
should
have that's okay I'll I'll recharge my
stamina over
here if I can
stand otherwise that wouldn't have been
so smart
but this swim should be doable but then
I have to climb maybe it's not worth it
maybe that EP is not worth it
because kind of uh think I should like
you know you
know a right I can't go
back
okay okay
okay
WAOW wait look at the night SC wow so
many
stars try to use do I even have the
Manta with
me no but maybe can you Glide with the
Nightwing didn't say anything about it
why does that look like sauron's Tower
over there
huh
no
yeah I need equipment huh probably one
pal to
guys so there's
rumors about possibly a new season can
you hear me a new season for the pon
series Effy to the
right
ow what the [\h__\h] did I
do can be ridden as a flying Mount yeah
but I need the okay flying M hey
y so I was
thinking if that
happens right
before
do you guys want to do it's going to be
[\h__\h] long but we can do a
got all seasons watch
along RTA one full season per day I
think we can do that one season pation
be so
crazy how many seasons are there in
terms of
remember quite
C no I would watch it in release
order yeah cuz like oh my God it's been
ages since I last watched it so I I want
to catch up again and I mean it's such a
legendary anime that I will forever love
and have in my top 10 top five top three
top one
honestly so we should should do a watch
along no no no no 1.5 speed you know
that anime have you ever watched it you
can't watch B in 1.5 speed it's
crazy there's so much going on brain
H so
guys I'm going to say we're going to
read super chats do I save I mean
there's no save button and it doesn't
really matter because I'm going to lose
it all all this
effort I'm guessing it saves on its own
how do I return the
title automatically save oh nice
[Music]
okay I won't be playing this game I
won't be joining in on the hype probably
enjoy it without me I guess I'm so
sad maybe at least to not be completely
behind maybe El secretly when nobody
else is streaming it log in once we have
that server and make myself a base and
all
that so cuz like it will be just the
beginning of the
game I won't go too far just like level
10 or
so just to play a game you know no no
stream and no interaction really with
anyone I I would play when no one's
[Music]
online just going to grind what I lost
in today's
playthrough maybe maybe if I'm bored and
have nothing to
do addiction already kicked in I don't
know it's really chill it's really
relaxing it's like um I know people say
it's like R and all that but like uh for
me this is also kind of like a new
Minecraft
too cuz like I think a lot of people uh
play it also like I don't know if I
understood it correctly but I feel like
it was implied there will be several
servers so maybe they'll be cuz I was
like hi can we make an En ID server
maybe because maximum 32 so I think we
can't have a full all Branch server and
then they answered something like yeah
they they like in plural are in the
works so I think there'll be several
servers I don't know what my point was
with that oh yeah because yeah several
many people will be playing it so for me
you know I don't know this giving me
Minecraft Bobs cuz we're building and
building a base and all that I guess you
did that in rest too but you know for me
it feels more like
Minecraft
don't think there will be yeah 32 is
probably we're not going to get there
anyway I don't think I can transfer
anything cuz like this is even if there
wasn't a wipe I think server and my solo
playthrough are like seen as separate
saves and all
that
probably
mhm with how you want to do weekly
membership streams oh I mean I wouldn't
I would have even been okay with doing
it publicly but now generally I've never
done a public watch long stream I think
and yeah we could probably keep it that
way if you guys don't get tired of it if
I do them all in members
only oh cats cats was of Ena that was
something else that's a collab that was
special ah rings of power was that
public yo I talked with narissa about
Rings rings of
power and I'm so happy she shares my
opinion on it completely like we both of
the opinion yeah sure it may have not
been perfect it may have not been super
accurate
but I said and she agreed
strongly
that I as someone who enjoys Lo of the
Rings and all that I feel like everybody
should be happy to get any kind of
visualization of a lord of the ring
story you know like you
know as long as it has something to do
with that world view and all that I am
happy about it okay and she agreed so
you can be mad about it however you want
but we shared many
opinions yeah we also we also really
liked
gadriel and and a lot of the other
characters I mean there were some things
we criticized too and we we shared both
our positive feedback and our critiques
about it as well which I think is
amazing shut up you guys you're so mean
now even the ISA is on my side and
you're still hating on
me so sad
so sad Nisa you're by my side right
thank
you they're hating on me
Nissa I don't get
it thank you thank you n says Bas you
call her Bas but like what about me what
about me why why is she
based I personal thinking that bad thank
you I mean I don't know why I say thank
you but happy that somebody somebody's
not Bing
around bed thank you yes I am based in
Europe vtuber based in
Europe narissa did you watch Elizabeth
death musical in the airplane
again did you watch it tell me tell me
tell me be honest
no you
didn't what did you actually sleep oh
but you did tell me that there was
someone ramming their elbow into your
body the
[\h__\h] that
sucks see that's maybe one reason why
like for certain airlines I've noticed
the premium economy isn't much better
than economy um in terms of like space
and and and reclining but one thing that
won't happen to you I think is your
neighbor ramming their elbow into you or
really like taking up your
space that at least is pretty much
prevented with premium economy so n Isa
in the future let's do premium
economy I was in reg regreted not
getting premium yeah
yeah damn I tuck my arms in I don't want
to Elbow people yeah me too but I
generally I tuck my arms in because um
like you know all the pain in my body uh
and the tenseness and the weird
fibromyalgia or whatever the [\h__\h] it is
I don't [\h__\h] know it kind of when I I
kind of like tense my whole body up and
like pull my arms into my body and like
I I I Cross My my arms usually when I'm
like sleeping in an
airplane and I kind of like pull one arm
with the other
together you know what I mean like I'm
hugging myself really
tightly uh somehow
that helps me a little bit even though I
make myself more tense somehow it helps
me with the tenseness it's like I
ironic
I need
um uh I don't know how to say I don't
know how to explain it I need the
tension in my body to get rid of
the other
tension it's like when you have pain
somewhere and then you pinch yourself in
a different spot to get rid of the pain
in the other
spot yeah h
but yeah let me tell you something
because I'm going on a break so let me
just bring out more more
tangent the phone phone store tangent
really quickly I think I told you part
of it but not all of it so let me finish
it
incompletion when I uh went to that
phone store with narissa she was like
sitting on the side for most of it um
and I was like I started discussing with
the the staff it was just a a store from
my internet provider cuz I first wanted
to check how much like if I have a a
warranty and if not how much they charge
and all that so I was like hey my
phone's kind of you know not working
anymore it doesn't want to charge
anymore uh it just completely died we
tried charging it the whole
night uh and we also did like the phone
to phone charging in thing because it
did say like wireless charging might
help but I didn't have a wireless
charger right so I did the phone the
phone charging with the Vera's phone but
that didn't work so we thought that
wireless charging is not working but now
I eventually as you know I told you that
part that I put it on the table they
have like a wireless charger in the
table built in and I put it on there
just for fun while we were
discussing uh and it suddenly worked but
up until that
point the like the the staff told me
that oh it will cost like probably like
300 to fix it300 and I'm
like so then we uh discussed if I should
get a new one and then he said yeah so I
have the s22 Ultra Samsung s22 Ultra and
he said how about you get the s20 Free
Ultra and I checked it out and I I like
I was like I asked him like that dude
seemed kind of like he was funny and
like joking around a lot and friendly
but I feel like he didn't know much
about like the phones that they were
selling there and other stuff because I
was asking him like what's different
between the s22 and the s23 and he said
I don't know I'm like don't you have
that somewhere like he was in front of a
PC and you can like choose those
products there and see the details I'm
100% sure but like he was like I don't
know and I'm like don't you have it like
on your PC can you check the details
there and he's like uh no I'm like okay
so I Googled it on my
side and most of it I saw most of it was
same the same thing the same he was he
just said oh probably the probably the
battery and the core and everything is
probably better and like uh probably huh
probably you want to sell me a [\h__\h]
expensive ass phone and you tell me
probably this and that is Maybe be
better uh
okay so I looked it up and yeah most
things were same the size was the same
and the only thing in terms of camera
was like the front camera was 2
megapixels
better uh I pointed it out I told him so
maybe now he can use that knowledge for
other people but yeah we were discussing
that and then I
said um I told him oh the phone's
actually uh working now
it's it's actually charging I think it
might be fine I think I might not need
the
phone
uh and then he starts offering all me
all these things he says y you should
get the phone anywhere or I can give you
the phone you know but like already like
it would cost me
800 plus all of the points several
thousand points that I accumulated at
the provider over the years of the past
years um and also go into minus with
points like 8,000 points I would use up
like 9,000 10,000 points and also go
into the minus 800 8,000 points and then
use
800 uh so he says like this yeah plus
you get uh 10 months of free internet
I'm like 10 months okay that's actually
a pretty good deal but yeah you know but
it's
working he's like yeah you should get it
anyway because your phone's just going
to die again and I'm like how do you
know I literally got the phone from the
very same provider so them kind of like
dunking and [\h__\h] on that very phone
and like being like very pessimistic
about it you know what I mean it just
doesn't give off a good image like
you're not supporting your own products
you know what I
mean and he didn't even know about the
defect at all and then I told him cuz
narissa told me that the
s23 has the same defect sometimes like
it can happen to this to that phone too
it was like yeah you should get it
anyway or I'll give you those 10 months
for free I'm like
H well the 10 months of free internet is
pretty good but you know I don't need
it and then he's like ah yeah actually
sorry it's actually 6 months uh I I I I
made a mistake and then I'm like yeah
well then then of course I'm not going
to get it if you gave me 10 months I
would have gotten it but not six months
I was just joking but yeah and then and
then and then once he understood that I
really don't need those six months of
free internet he said well I can give
you what was it three months maybe of
free
Netflix he kept on trying to sell me
[\h__\h] what and and me and the ISA at this
point Nissa was all like standing next
to me and we kept on saying like it's
working though like we don't need it
anymore
yeah I mean and I said like if it at
least was an upgrade that was worth it
like this phone obviously isn't much
different than my current one in terms
of you know specifications
whatever if it at least was like a s24
that maybe that has more
upgrades s22 to 20 s24 might might make
more sense but s24 doesn't exist J so
yeah
yeah nah it just made no sense so in the
end I said
sorry sorry for making you get your
hopes up that you were going to sell
something my phone works now so go buy I
don't need your fre months of
Netflix the Netflix
yo free ms of Netflix that's not even
that much
money Wild
the S was revealed
today
Samsung Galaxy for real is it much
better does it have better cameras
because the s23 didn't have much better
than the s22 it was just the 2
megapixels in the front camera Samsung
Galaxy s24 Ultra comes with higher price
and loads of AI
okay useful new AI tools a flat screen
and the what do you mean a flat screen
AR old phone spat I guess it's finner
and a higher price come to Samsung's
Kitchen syn phone what do you mean
kitchen sink what does that mean that
some
slang
okay there I can imagine you say it ever
wish you could have the most phone for
several years running Samsung's S Series
Ultra has been that device and the
company is going just as big with the
ultra for
2024 oh wait those numbers that was the
year oh I just realized it
now that makes
sense kitchen sink means it does
everything oh
never heard that
before higher starting price one
1,299 up from an already high
1,199 okay one of the most immediately
noticeable Fe new features of the ultra
is how it's built this year's model has
a titanium titanium frame like Apple's
iPhone 15 Pro which Samsung say allows
for better
durability a titanium frame no
unlike Apple Samsung hasn't used the
material in an attempt to make the phone
lighter titanium is heavier than
aluminum but it's more durable so you
can use less of it in this case Samsung
has just gone for the durability Factor
blah blah
blah makes it slightly heavier than the
iPhone 15 Pro Max the other big change
up front is a
display oh in this picture they have 23
on the the back no they look like very
similar
[Music]
S4 ultra comes with a 6.8 in 1, 1440p
display just like the s23 ultra but it
finally ditches the curved edges
inherited from the note Series in favor
of a flat screen that's what they mean
yeah I mean I guess it's a little bit
curved yeah it doesn't really bother
me Super Chat reading off to a strong
start we I need to read this now there's
much less chance of accidentally running
your S Pen over the side of the display
I never had that I mean I don't even use
the S Pen most of the time sometimes
sometimes sometimes chck you're back
Chow
meow meow meow
meow classic Super Chat rating starts
with a tangent and me getting
interrupted by my cat you love it
there's another Hardware shake up on the
back of the Sam the phone Samsung
swapped oh oh camera runs
Samsung swapped s23 Ultra 10 megapixel
10 times zoom zoom for a 50 megapixel 5
times
Zoom so it zooms less but the five times
Zoom is like really [\h__\h]
good 50 megapixel sounds really good it
it uses a lossless don't scratch my
chair
bigger
picture I like the Zoom though like
literally me and the ISA but like there
was a a restaurant in the malds that we
would go to for lunch like several times
during our trip and thing is they had no
menus on the tables they just had one
menu written on like a big board in the
middle of the restaurant hi chunky
wonky and like you had to walk over
there to see it so we both have the same
phone so we would take our phones and
then zoom in and take a picture of the
menu and then look at it without having
to get up that's one way of taking of
using your Zoom of your
phone we did that all the time then
looking at our phones to look at the
menu technology wow so the 10 times
Zoom I don't really think it's good to
get rid of that completely
it uses a lossless crop Zoom to get to
ah okay a lossless crop Zoom to get the
10 times Zoom even though it's no longer
a native focal length several Samsung
Representatives told me the image
quality at 10 10 times should actually
be improved compared to the est3 field
oh okay to the previous one so okay you
can still Zoom all the way out to 100
times which in very early testing still
appears to be mostly a party trick
okay Hardware on the other four cameras
is unchanged from last year H you're
still working with uh
20 okay well well the the the
the the front camera is still improved
to the s22 and also the portrait camera
I don't think it needs to be changed cuz
it's [\h__\h]
amazing always stick to more optical
zoom I do not trust any digital Zoom
they claim they are lossless yeah
yeah okay what's this about the AI
Samsung has filled its new phone series
with just about every AI feature you've
seen on other Flagship phones to
date um they're loaded with local and
cloud-based AI features and are running
Google's geminy foundational models on
device what what does it me what does
that mean uh has a handful of New Image
and video editing tools powered by
generative AI
noted throughout the UI with an
extremely Google bardes Star icon you
can Circle photo subjects to isolate
them and resize them ah so like okay for
picture editing move them around or
totally remove them from the frame you
can also adjust the Horizon level in
your photo and rather than cropping have
ai fill in the edges of the image okay
so like the new Photoshop where you can
use AI to put on the
phone H they seem about par from the
course sometimes sometimes impressive
sometimes prone to adding wacky stuff to
your image but the coolest feature I saw
demo it wasn't for still photos it was
for videos you can turn any video into
a
oh yeah okay into a 120 FPS slow motion
video after the fact no matter what mode
frame rate or even camera you captured
it with it uses AI to interpolate the
missing frames it was incredibly
convincing on the 60p video shot in the
demo yeah okay that's pretty awesome
because yeah I've seen this before
where like for example older music
videos that were like 25 FPS or so they
would bring it up to 60 FPS and it looks
like wow looks really good that's
cool that's pretty cool cuz like filming
in 60 FPS is uh
yeah takes up a lot of space and usually
comes with
the
the m
loss of
quality in terms of like size like 4K 60
FPS usually doesn't work I
think for a lot of phones you have to do
4K 30 FPS so you can film 4K 30 FPS and
then bring it up back up to 60 or 120
[Music]
FPS or it works is just massive exactly
yeah so okay that's that's fine that's
cool oh there's some AI features
centered on
translation there's a feature that acts
as an interpreter on phone calls
translating your speech in real time
into the other party's language and vice
versa I don't know if I would want to
rely on that it will work with 13
different languages you can also
translate text conversations into
another language a function that's built
into Samson's keyboard app so that works
across any chat
service h
blah blah
blah oh one thing that's curiously
missing from every Galaxy s24 phone the
qi2 wireless
charging uh
but whatever I don't know I don't know
I'm not going to get a new phone until
this one dies for real or or maybe in 2
years or so when there's really
something that's a big step
[Music]
skip ad why I was just interesting let
me be a TCH vtuber for a
moment dony wonky is like on my table in
front of my monitor want she wants she
wants the belly
rubs yeah I think my S2 Ultra is still
pretty up to date in terms of
tech so I'm I'm fine with it foldable
phones I'm not a fan of those new
foldable
[Music]
phones if narissa was still here sitting
next to me she could pet chunky wonky
while I read super chats I can try to do
both
though uh
okay
oh oh let's uh let's let's go to my
office or so
um
yeah wait I have uh the fantasy office I
forgot the Guild
Hall
[Music]
like
this okay
okay Mario
[Music]
odyy okay thank you the peach one okay
so is that the last
one why am I cat so electric can you
guys tell
me you guys even hear it on stream as
I've
heard uh should I keep the bgm on is
kind of
fitting is the fur air is dry
humidity but I feel like I don't
know it is kind of something that
started like a few months ago two months
or so
maybe or maybe before I don't know but I
don't think this has been a thing for
too
long oh she's so Happ
happy she's such a happy
cat a okay I will not pet you now drunky
Wy I have several weeks without a stream
where I can pet you
endlessly but it's kind of nice to have
her on the table while I
talk that's
nice fluffy fluffy thing to look
at they're developing electric powers
they're turning into
Pokmon okay I will look for my Super
Chat can we hear her meow no she's like
she's chilling she doesn't want a
meow
[Music]
W guys are you going to miss me I think
you're you're going to miss me and I'm
going to miss you too
damn it'll probably be like 3 weeks or
so I
think but I have I have
videos many
videos don't forget about me when I'm
gone don't replace
[Music]
me I'm happy you're taking time for
yourself thank you um I have other stuff
to do
[Music]
okay like watching someone else's
streams please get lots of rest thank
you you deserve a great break thank you
I think I do
yeah I think I'll write a
little um notification for my
Twitter um that I'll be on a
break m
I might ask jenma to update my Twitter
whenever a video uh comes up on
YouTube but yeah just know that won
that's not
me also any fan art that will be
uploaded during that time I'll try to
check it all out after my
break I'll
try please don't use
announcement
no
no I did sunglasses on my profile
picture to show I'm on
vacation I
mean no because then I lose my badge my
verification badge it's so stupid that
you lose it each time you change it same
for the name you can use you can change
the banner without losing anything but
nothing else
okay here we go Super Mario
Odyssey I think it was the last
[Music]
stream turkey don't push the mouse away
I have no
space I love you
though mhm the peach one yeah
yeah let me just find is this a
thumbnail says finally was it really the
finale
[Music]
oops
or
what last game stream before the car
began no that was Raina before that yeah
that's one
okay let's go py D Ultimo MK thank you
for the orange
carpet
let me read rolling out the orange
carpet for 2024 KB's very own year of
the
waa
why why why why is is every is every
year year of the
W let's start this year out strong with
a big kiy and now for some not as happy
news I have exams coming up in June and
July which means I have to pull back
yes and cut all social contacts and
completely focus on studying from now
on but only until June July that's okay
that's okay but maybe every once in a
while you still yeah I will of course
continue to watch your streams during
that time just not as active in chat as
before that's fine I'll also send some
occasional super chats as a sign of life
thank you I just want you to know that
while I can't actively show it I'm still
there to support you no matter what and
if you ever need anything from me just
call me and I'll be there thank you well
that sounds great that's not so bad then
you're not completely gone then then I
am I am
satisfied I have no
complaints oh that's a that's a red
super chat in
total
[Music]
than Super
Chat disguised as an orange
one yeah good luck with your
studies
gamb damn I I
couldn't I really can't
imagine but I bet you can do it
easily I believe in
you and come back
smarter and more
evolved until when is your vacation I
don't have an exact date that I can tell
you um but I think I'll be back in the
maybe the end of M yeah possibly the the
middle or the end of the second February
week sometime around
then one wallpaper yeah that's I don't
know it will maybe be uploaded by JMA I
don't
know um but I haven't
seen yeah she'll she'll need to send me
progress and let me check up on it cuz I
don't have the final one
yet I want to H
walk I want to hug her squeeze
her oh [\h__\h] I forgot I should have
washed my face because I just remembered
my nap I was like napping with smoothy's
feet in my face literally on my on my
cheeks and my and on my
lips I just remembered we fell asleep
like
that cuz I had my face towards her
tummy and she was
like she had her feet like pushed
against my face was quite comfortable
I'm not
complaining it felt quite nice to have
the fluff in my
face and the toe beans on my lips but I
was like I gotta wash my face after this
and I
forgot Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum she was
purring so much while I was
like fluffing for her fluff with my face
in her
toes she's so
happy it's quite a blessing yeah cute
and also gross yeah
yeah you can't sleep with an eye mask
but a cat in your face is okay
yeah can you guys sleep with eye masks
though like for me it's like I don't
like to have weight on my eyes it's nice
at a massage to have like a towel over
my eyes cuz first of all it's less
awkward and second of all less blinding
no no no never tried no can't I can't
same yes well most people say no or they
haven't tried
a
well you could try I guess if you ever
need to if it ever bothers you like the
light or
so I wish I liked them because I could
make merch out of it I wish it was a
more popular
thing I could make um um eye mask wish I
mean I still could but I want to make
things people actually want to
use you found some you can
[Music]
tolerate I would take a hair band
really but the
hairband can't really put much of like
kfp design on
that narissa should make this merch yeah
narissa could make it cuz like she
personally likes it and uses
it I need that official kfp Happ
I I am considering making a happy maybe
in
2024 I might make one but I feel kind of
bad because so many people already have
like one of their
own and then I I don't know I feel bad
for because those look so good I feel
bad for replacing
them but maybe I should make one
anyway because the one that exists made
by fans already looks so good
is there really a need for
one I'm not replacing you want
one many k if we don't have one because
we cannot make it in time
oh happies are so nice cuz they're so
Airy so
lightweight for people who don't know
it's like a otaku Idol otaku kind of or
not only only Idol like anime
otaku kind of like like a shirt an open
shirt usually I think it's like
polyester and they're really colorful
and the color of the image of the
idol perhaps with a big image of the
idol on top of
it those are fan the fanmade ones very
limited quantity I I know I know okay
maybe I'll make
one maybe for birthday next birthday
merge maybe I think I
don't have
anything in planning
yet all
right I didn't really want to make it
until now cuz I was still kind of hoping
that maybe one day I'll have an IRL
concert and then it will be part of the
merchandise there anyway but yeah you
know
I guess at this point we can make one
for my birthday
mer for the
[Music]
pink two super chats to far no no what I
know this year had its ups and downs but
you made 2023 extra special with our
made and greet connect the world and
your first album being released looking
forward to more from my came
in 2024 2024 G thank you yeah it was a
big year I liked looking back on it
during uh the member stream was
it with the the the graphic that I
made yeah we're in 2024 now 2023 already
so far behind us I already went on a
vacation this
year yeah on your
[Music]
you made such good content in 2023 thank
you I really tried I always tried to
bring out unique interesting
content um to set myself apart and keep
you guys interested in the content to
not get you guys like bored of
it
and what I already want a return receip
no 2024 is going to be cool too don't
worry h
but yeah yeah I I hope I can continue to
make interesting original content this
year too so far I mean I think it
already started great with you know my
ideas these days these past weeks like
The Sims even the Sims stream like
that's a new challenge that I f up out
of my small small
brain you wouldn't believe it
I'm squeezing chunky
paw so
cute yeah um unknown thanks for the red
super chat happy New Year boss oh yeah
this was on the 1 of
January thank you for making 2023 such
an incredible year thank you so much for
always giving us endless happiness my
life is a lot brighter because of you
you're truly amazing I will always be
here supporting everything you do no
matter what I love you Wawa thank you so
much I love you
too thank you for staying by my side no
matter what in 2023 even when things
looked maybe not so
nice you're always so
supportive
yeah water ASMR
let me pour one for
you chunky wonk is so confused like why
won't you make space for me why do you
put the water jug
there I think no I I
electrocuted my cat a little bit and
then it made the static sound and it
disconnected something isn't that so
funny
boom it happens it happens no the mouse
is still
working but the mouse has no space it's
like half half of the mouse is off of
the table chunky
wonky move
back ah anyway thank you so much
unknown what brings 2024 is also unknown
but I know that you will be there
right wow poetic so
sugy
yeah that is
known I know we know check 47 D Jim
Tracy D isah right thanks for the
binking happy Happy New Year I hope
you've been having a good holiday I have
a question is there any way this CP can
get a motivational gym speech I got 200k
kilogram on squats this morning what
does that
mean like squatting while holding up
weights 200
kilogram I'm training to be strong like
my H lifting friends and there's a whole
Hol lifting
group yeah is that what that means
you're awesome thank
you 200 kg is insane that sounds
crazy you can lift
like like
like 100 chunky wonks
maybe
yo that's so strong you're so strong I
don't think you need a motivational gym
speech you're already doing it like
I don't think you need my my
speech you just need my praise because
you're already [\h__\h] doing it you
already smashing it hey
shees
yo
congratulations that's pretty sick
that's insane you know I can only lift
like 5 kilogram at
most yeah let's go go next 250 kilogram
or I don't know what your next step is
going to be but you can do it get
buff get
strong I give you free
weeks is that realistic cuz I'm gone for
like three weeks I
think my legs yeah my legs are probably
stronger than my arms I don't know maybe
not I don't know can't
say chunky
[Music]
wony you want to say something yeah cuz
they won't hear you for a while cuz Mama
will not be
[Music]
screaming
yes
indeed the Pearl the strong
Pearl strongest purr in the
world I'm so happy they were so happy
when I came back they wanted to cuddle
so much I mean they always do so it's
not a big difference but still I can
tell they'll be confused that I'm not
streaming yeah they'll be like chilling
they'll probably get sick of
me cuz I'll have so much cuddle time
with
them where smoothie love well don't
worry like she gets all the nap love I I
nap so much with my face in her
so oh anyway let's
continue and GD thanks for the pinky
Happy New Year keata hope you achiev
what you set out to do this year have uh
happiness and good health CIA my come
thank you good health yeah I could give
I could give it another girl with like
doctor
appointments maybe I'll even go to one
during my break oh if I can get an
appointment I want to get a new doctor
though I'll see what I can
do I don't even know what to say anymore
at this
point kind of like done at least I can
like w the
static one day I'm going to just [\h__\h]
electrocute myself
here I was going to
say uh at least like these
past months or this past year even maybe
I've been able
to sleep really fast and that is a huge
relief for
me my whole life I was having issues
falling asleep like it would take me 3
to 4 hours you know that I told you
before and that made me go crazy at
times when I was really really tired and
I still like I closed my eyes and I
still need like 3 4
hours you think it's me getting old
I think it's just my body completely
giving
up it's like I give up I waved the white
flag please I just want to
die that's what my body is
saying but yeah maybe it's also I would
hope that maybe it's also like a
mentality thing like me mentally feeling
better but I don't I can't really
clearly feel
that
[Music]
maybe but my shoulder pain and all that
is unchanging
since yeah many years now many many
years since before Hol
live I've had this crazy inexplicable
pain in my shoulders and
neck which I really don't understand
because it's like yeah I have bad
posture and all that and yeah I'm in
front of the PC a lot and all that but I
feel kind of started so suddenly and
even before that I always had bad
posture and it was in front of the PC
all the time but I feel like it just
suddenly got so much
worse well whatever no I didn't do the
the the steroids yet
no cuz I didn't go to the doctor for a
while now cuz I was too busy and I
didn't want to go to that doctor
anyway I forgot where is my doctor I
don't even know do I even have a doctor
right
now I'm not sure so whatever um let's
work on that Health shall we GD I don't
know if you have any issues but let's
work on it together fight all
[Music]
wait sorry that was oh
well preemptive kiss in case you send
the red
sometime h d thank you H H what the
[\h__\h] H H at least you got it right the
first
time
[Music]
choc
n a sports massage I think I've had one
sports massage before I
think it's pretty good but in the end
all
massages really just
are a the like a relief for that moment
honestly I do have to say the massage
though that I had in the
moldes narissa can confirm cuz she heard
heard it cuz she was next to me cuz we
were getting a couple's massages of
course same room um like she started out
it was an oil massage but they start out
by having like a fabric over your body
and then they like press really strongly
into your
body and I've never had such a strong
multiple
culation in my spine she pressed several
times deeply into my spine and I think
three out of those
times per one
press she got my spine to crack so many
times that I can't even count culation
yeah
congratulation like probably like 10
times 10 little cracks in one p push and
then she could she would go a little bit
up higher she did it again it was
insane it was insane I was
like but one thing I wanted to ask
everybody here who gets massages tell me
this cuz it's something I've been
observing and I wonder if if
my maybe some part of like my body is
wrong
when I
lie with my belly
down when they
press around my shoulder blades or so or
also a little bit
below um it cuts off my throat uh
breathing
tube uh all the time every time they
press down
and it makes me
think is everybody incapable of
breathing when they get a
massage or is it something with like my
maybe my spine
being or my neck or some some part being
that's not normal right like I
literally I literally get
choked
H with pretty much all of the massages I
I get and I get a lot of massages I just
kind of like uh like suffer through it
because at the same time I don't want
her to lower the pressure because
otherwise I wouldn't feel it in the
[Music]
muscles I think I think I experienced it
being a little bit bit better sometimes
uh at massages where they don't have a
completely flat surface but have like
the the chest
area uh with a slightly angled pillow
have it like heighten a little bit you
know what I
mean like it goes up a little bit
starting from like around under your
chest up until your the end of the
massage table
basically I think that helped me a
little
bit Yeah but I know they yeah they they
press too hard so obviously you can't
breathe but I feel like that can't be
normal for me personally it feels like
maybe something's wrong with like the
way my body is
shaped maybe my my my I always I always
think my neck um my
jaw is too
short
cuz when I look at my face my profile in
the
mirror I see that there's like barely
any space between my chin and my
neck okay and when I even slightly like
not you know when you like do a double
chin on purpose even when I'm not trying
to do a double chin just very slightly
like
relax in a relaxed way just some times
like put make make my face go a little
bit back I already have like a little
bit of a double
chin you think I have an
underbite
underbite so when the jaw is too far in
the back see I think I might have
that and then maybe that's connected
with my choking
issues no dentist never told me that I
had an underbite or something like that
maybe they think oh she's already
[\h__\h] old Phoenix it makes no sense to
fix it now should have fixed it when she
was a
child can we see an xray of your body
honestly I would love to show you maybe
next time I get an
x-ray must be very minor yeah I mean it
mostly doesn't affect me it's just so
far I guess it's only a aesthetically I
don't know really but maybe there's some
things are affected by it that I don't
know like can can it uh can the underjaw
what can that
be affecting my shoulder pain who knows
okay I shouldn't be asking you those
questions because you guys are going to
say go to a doctor okay but I feel
stupid asking these questions because
they don't care they don't seem to care
at all
[Music]
they don't
even like trying to help me you
know go to the doctor but they're not
trying to help me whatever okay let me
go to Super Chat I have to read super
chats okay so daddy issues yeah I have
Daddy Issues that's the problem yeah
that's why my shoulders
hurt oh
sorry I was reading Discord
DMS no I don't want you to roast
Austrian uh do like no Austrian
Health
stuff I do want you to think that we are
superior
Ah that's
[\h__\h] fiber mialgia there's like not
not enough proper studies to determine
why it exists and how to fix it so I
don't think you can say it's caused by
extremely low self-esteem apparently nah
like who can say for sure fibromyalgia
is like a [\h__\h] mystery and I don't
even know if I really have it so
whatever
I don't even really believe in a neor
so can I waste Austrian taxes instead
yes that you can loud and
clear a kidney stone from the pain she
was experiencing you just have to keep
trying the different dogs yeah yeah no
[\h__\h] okay H chocolate
insia the game mental Jett thank you for
two pinkies Happy New Year I'm back from
my East Asia travels great to catch you
live again after so many months away yo
how long were you gone East Asia travels
managed to catch some of the key events
including the Advent calendar and 3d
concert nice I appreciate that I also
bought lots of Hol merge I miss Japan
already especially the food you're so
amazing 2023 was a hard one but also
very productive of some of my favorite
streams collabs and releasing a great
album oh we were busy let's go 2024
can't wait to see what you cook this
year oh I'll cook you
aitel are you in the chat you are four
months wa that was long welcome back to
England Brit British land pound
land as you are donating in pounds I
assume
so wait you say you you you catch the
highlights wait wait this was January 1
first you came back you you must have
seen the aura collab right back in
London oh you're in London
London
what so you you surely watched the Ora
collab and heard me talk talk in my most
beautiful English accent I worked on it
while you were
gone no I didn't no I really didn't it
hurt my soul no
were you not feeling like loved and
depreciated because of my love for this
acent please tell me that me trying to
speak your beautiful accent made you
feel like I'm trying to connect with you
sure boss
okay
[Music]
I mean no
harm I
swear I solemnly
swear
football here's a kiss a welcome back
kiss nice to have you back now you
better stay but I'm going on a break now
so I'll see you soon you'll be there
when I come back right cuz I waited for
you now you wait for me Roa dear SRA
oh D for the pinky let's say that you
switch places of an alternate Ki for you
and learn that this Ki treats am and
gura like cats doing to them all things
you do to your cats like make them go
into my robot toilet are you worried
this K will hurt your relationship with
them
so I treat them like cats but it's not
like they're any different from like you
know them they're actually still like
what they
are something like
humans oh that is uh they must weird be
weed out by me they must be so freaked
out and be like what the [\h__\h] is wrong
with kada
I
I I I can't deal with this be there
going to hate
[Music]
me yeah it's definitely concerning Rocka
dear sja definitely very concerning I
don't want that because I don't want to
be disliked by am guro I worked so hard
on our friendship over the years I
really worked so hard I can't have it be
ruined like that by such a stupid
[Music]
thing
maybe they're made by AI
yeah it was uh it was I was quite happy
to see gai in the chat
[Music]
today maybe she wants to play pal
World maybe she's excited to play pal
world you
[Music]
know also should just sent me a little
recording for a a little meme video that
I was hoping to upload during my break
so big
Tas I have so many videos holy [\h__\h]
let's go I still have to finish some um
editing on them too I have a couple a
[Music]
couple
I'm just sad I'm going to miss out on
all of that I would love to have an
alliance with
[Music]
GAA you edit well like your hyperx at
thank you actually I did some of those
editing of that editing of those clips
that I made um in the
airplane actually used my time in the
air
efficiently bottom of sh's boots thank
you for the big red Super Chat
D wow well her boots are
amazing so you're amazing thank you so
much MW mwah mwah very very very
generous of you thank you and happy New
Year
[Music]
Ain I for thanks for the pinky happy New
Year Tel looking forward to the great
streams and events that await us this
year wish you having great time on
streams lots of fun and interesting
collabs of amazing people lots of new
chickens and much more I hope so I hope
we'll get a lot of new
chickens I hope we can make kfp
grow I really hope so because Grove has
been really [\h__\h]
dead
depressingly dead
so I'll continue working hard to make KB
bigger and dominate the fast food
world
yeah more chickens more
chickens No 2 million is realistically
not going to happen
if it would happen then that means
something
crazy would happen this year like
something insane would have to happen
for that kind of
growth some kind
of
Miracle yeah but thank you so much
AF let's have lots of fun together in
this year um I'll be on a break for a
little bit but after that we can get
into it for real for real
okay Nate zinski D soon
a Darkness d m linkx c d jelly red D
thank
you oh you wore earrings that had me on
them oh thank you Elite Lea than super
bear hero thank you so much than Nathan
cotton thanks for the red Super Chat
happy New Year tal looking forward to
another year of kfb with my favorite
streamer
wow I love hearing that thank you so
much yeah let's make it a great year
2024 my fourth year this year we'll have
fourth anniversary
so got to keep on going strong with you
guys By My Side Y Ru
Nathan black d red diamond d g d Brandon
d tyen d thanks for Pinky spending New
Year's the way it was meant to be spent
watching wa on my TV while marathoning
Lord of the Rings on my computer
what you were
watching lower the Rings while watching
me that's disrespectful to Lord of
durings you should pay full attention to
Lord of the
Rings and also full attention to me
though
so don't doing at the same time
tyon
[Music]
hey can't believe it why would you do
that I mean what here's another year of
cheering on a phenomenal Phoenix as she
reaches even greater Heights than ever
before well thank you so much but you
shocked me with
that you have to rewatch the full movie
and that
stream separately
please just kidding you don't have to
but ah how can you how can you what
M I'm going to sue you Mr
[Music]
tyen that is what you call it
impractical
practice illegal practice should be
illegal Mal
practice Yeah Mal practice that's
it that's the word I knew it Al
along totally didn't read it from the
chat yeah happy New Year
though
maybe sometime this year we can watch L
of rings again who knows they they did
give some news
that was it was it how am I mixing
things up didn't wasn't there some news
that there's new Lord of the Rings
things in the
works
right like two things two shows or
whatever yeah I hope that will be
good cuz people were disappointed with
rings of power not me but you know so
hopefully the next things will be good
War of the
RO Rohan film okay cool cool cool
cool okay well probably going to take
ages probably not going to come out in
right Richard
G for red Super
Chat
good I spent my New Year with my father
and we actually sang some okay oo I
wasn't brave enough to try some of your
songs yet but maybe in the future anyway
I'm excited for this new year with kfp
thank you me too I'm excited too well k
for New Year sounds amazing I actually
was kind of planning on setting up K in
my living room with kfun I mean having a
subscription to KFAN is kind of
op but then
I just kind of canceled the idea of
setting it up because first of all it
seemed too complicated I didn't know if
it if the sound was going to be fine um
in terms of like if it goes through the
speakers is there going to be like uh
howling back and forth whatever and I
was kind of too lazy to set it up so I
give up cuz probably the only people who
would have used it was me and one one
more person so yeah instead we played
Monopoly for 5 hours yeah through the
[\h__\h] night which was honestly I love
that way did that everybody was like in
the end they were like everybody was
[\h__\h] tired and they also kind of said
never again and I'm like why you enjoyed
it we were all passionate about
it yeah but stuff like that like playing
[\h__\h] Monopoly through the night I
wish I could do more stuff like that
with my friends just like General
generally hanging out and making
memories like that but I've been
definitely
neglecting all of my friendships ever
since I joined home
life yeah 100%
but well they've been um not complaining
they they they're fine with it and
they're
supportive and and I'm mostly fine with
it too like I don't feel like I'm
lacking social
interactions or anything like
that but when I think about it it is
kind of sad but I mean we're still
friends and all that and we still got
many many years to be friends
so for now I want to focus on my career
so that's that oh but yeah sounds
exciting Tassimo thank you so much for
the generous donations always throughout
2023 and also already this year so thank
you for supporting me like that you're
amazing Happy New Year I wish you all
the best
Asimo npe thank you for the
pinky focus on your friends I don't know
if they really have time um probably
going to meet yeah some of them maybe
once or twice yeah npe come for the
pinky happy new Year
yay oh I forgot uh wait
uh what was it I already learned and now
I forgot uh Korean happy new year was
something
um
help somebody's going to tell me
somebody's going to tell
me
[Music]
sing I'm glad to hear that we can spend
this year with t again I look forward to
a great 2024 I hope you continue to be
happy this year we're happy because of
[Music]
you n one of my Korean Bros who has been
around even when the like the big Korean
hype kind of died down a little bit yeah
you're still here you have no
idea you have let me write that in
papao
you
does that properly translated I
wonder
okay yeah it's way a board
it's so hard to type with it cuz I'm not
used to big big
keys and I keep on missing the keys that
I want to
type wow wow
wow
[Music]
and I will do my best to practice Korean
again okay okay I promise I
promise thanks for the pink Super Chat
GS k your New Year's performance was
brilliant also happy New Year thank you
yeah New Year's New Year's countdown
life is always very exciting I'm happy
to be part of
it yay maybe next here maybe I can be in
the
shuffle but yeah I'm honestly for me by
the way do you I think or was it Sparks
I think it was do you reached 5
million views on YouTube
recently and I'm really really happy
that my songs even if not all of them
some of them you know it's just an
algorithm thing some do better some do
some do worse that's just how it is but
I'm happy that my songs are you know
recognized by also the Japanese fans
even though they're English my
songs
yeah I I'm really happy about that so I
hope I can release some bangers that
will stay in everybody's Minds in 2024
as
well so thank you so much Ricky DOA
please continue supporting me this year
I'd love to have you around your
cool yeah Korean do you maybe this year
for do you anniversary maybe I'll
release a Japanese
version
yeah maybe it's time Brandon
than
Bruce
MK oh yeah that's super CH clear R oh
wait m okay happy
birthday
congratulations sorry I'm a bit late
rro and J thank you for the pinky
finishing a whole game one day into 2024
wow happy New Year Odyssey was really
fun to watch over the winter holidays
yeah really it was fun for me too thanks
for more fun streams in 2024 yeah I'll
do my
best I'll try to deliver pressure is on
me pressure is strong
[Music]
but you guys are always welcome by the
way to give me some fresh new ideas if
you think you have a genius idea for a
stream let me
know but actually I'm impressed with
myself still thinking of new
things even
nowadays good job me good job waa
brain yeah so
jayber hope to see you again after my
break I know you'll be around I Know I
Can Count On You hi chuny Monkey she
saying hi
too did a big stretch right in front of
me
yel Jim Tracy Don mapine thanks for the
[Music]
pinky
and congratulations on yet another game
completed the game finisher of Ian
strikes again great work tal great start
to 2024 oh yeah I
mean compared to like
one we didn't finish as many games but
that's only because we finished like a
lot of very long
games lots of very long long
streams long
games but I I think we did a lot we
finished so many games holy
moly yeah and there I go on the first
day of
January already finishing another game
ha sugy
sasuga vertical Super Chat reading
streams on the treadmill
oh that's that's a way of using vertical
yeah but I don't know vertical stream
hype is also already
dead can't believe that it wasn't even a
game it was a flavor of the
month stream
aspect aspect can you believe it one day
there'll be like round shape streams
that you can watch on your clock on your
wrist watch your I watch or whatever
they're
called round
streams I'll film my my face will fill
the whole
screen fish I streams oh yeah I love
that yeah but now the the the hype is
already dead that was only like a two
day
hype and I did not join it because I am
too lazy to change my settings in OBS
number one and second of all I didn't
think it was such a big
deal oh well my fault for missing out on
the flavor of the month I
guess but yeah I'm too cool for the hype
[Music]
yeah it's perfect for you cuz you're a
mobile
watcher
[Music]
well
well anyway thank you so much may
believe hopefully you'll be
around this year a lot too I would be
happy to see
you
YX Kenny
stamps
D wrench me cool
d f FX D EV D M8 thanks for the pinky
first stream of 2024 and you beat
another Mario game still a lot more
moons to find and there's special levels
at 250 and 500 oh and if you find Peach
maybe she'll look a bit different don't
forget to grab the N64 outfit special
door for that too wait the N64 outfit I
think I did end up grabbing right
right what what if Peach is also you
said she looks different what if she's
also in in like N64 Graphics maybe
that's the the
thing by the way I did say that maybe
I'll
record uh a Mario Odyssey
stream but I didn't have time so it will
only be short videos I'm
sorry ah she dresses based on the
kingdom oh what you make me
curious well wait wait wait I scrolled
weirdly thank you m
always for sharing your brain with me
always thank you so much it's been a Del
light D Domin Lou Mo
D damn it I forgot to give you a a
task I said okay I'll keep my coupon for
after my break I think I have
like enough videos almost to fill every
day almost maybe I don't know maybe
maybe maybe I'm still here do you think
you could make one until tomorrow though
cuz I want to put up
everything tomorrow and then never look
at YouTube
again every for 3 weeks
maybe
almost oh she's rolling
around something she wants something
from
me I mean maybe I
don't well I don't know now I'm doubting
myself maybe I don't I have the night
off and five cans of coffee I'm ready
but I know you sent me ideas
already um but I'm not sure
H
[Music]
maybe maybe something moldes related
would be good
though although Kiana's that that second
idea you wrote it sounds like it's a lot
of
work that's s like a lot of work you
think you can do that in one
night actually no I think I would prefer
the third
idea yeah cuz then we don't have to
worry about game
for the third idea is
good let's do the third idea Elsie
Lain
y coupon exchanged
Yahoo Yahoo I'm excited to see what
you'll make um I have a [\h__\h] ton of
shorts so if you could make this in a
non-short way uh like uh normal
video doesn't have to be a short like I
want to have some known shorts
too yeah also you could probably not fit
it into a short
anyway I
suppose still at the first stream yeah
well okay
I'm almost done yeah maybe
almost
and I am a
chicken soon Che Channel you soon Unity
CH you soon thanks for the
pinky happy New Year LA and wishing the
new year brings us a good health and
happy moments even if couple of curve
balls come our way we're going to do a
best right right let's go oh you're so
motivated let's go
curveballs I had a lot of curveballs in
2024 three so I think less curve balls
this year I think I have a good feeling
I have a good feeling but I don't want
to get my hopes
up yeah no beep I'm too lazy for the
beep now I'm
[Music]
done I don't think I'll read everything
I said that already I don't read it all
but it's good to at least catch up a
little bit it's not like you guys can
bombard me with super chats while I'm
gone those fre weeks I won't be
streaming I mean you can send some super
chats uh no actually not because they
they won't be
premieres so it's not like I'm going to
build up a huge
backlog no you literally can't send me
anything I don't have a waiting room
open either no no no
you'll have to talk to yourself or talk
on Twitter or talk on kfb
Discord oh my God thank
you have fun on your
break I'll have fun not sending you
money thank you that's that's indeed
probably
fun waiting room free chat no
no
no that's too long and I can't take care
of
it oh my God yeah guys but
yo I'll ignore you guys I will be
ignoring you
now
zly happy New Year for let's go let's
[\h__\h] go space one for D looking for
the top
tun thank you and dragon dun Wiki too D
Santiago Martin thanks for the redet
Happy New Year I seen a lot of people
doing this everyone is confessing their
feelings with their favorite YouTubers
and inspiration so I have to do it too
ah I love you a lot cie yeah this is a
troll right you're trolling me right I
know you love me too cuz you're a member
you're just messing around with
me you little [\h__\h] m
did you send the same one to cie with my
name at the end you
better uh wait there's one name that I
can't
[Music]
read what why is chunky wony just
sitting down there looking like a pair
like a fluffy
pair staring at
me I think she has
cables don't know what the what the
issue
[Music]
is dinging Aban thank you for the pinky
and some extra
ones I went for a very difficult year
last year for my body and mind but in
fact these things are still bothering me
I once felt hopeless about life and
wanted to end myself I started watching
a live stream in October last year the
stream often accomp accompanied me for
many sleepless nights and also gave me a
lot of energy so that I can continue to
face a bunch of bad things in life thank
you tel for the smile you brought me uh
I will work hard to survive and wish you
the best in a New Year everything will
go well in the new year
kiky yeah it will there's ups and downs
in l
life but it's always worth it's always
worth it to fight through the Downs even
when they
are lower than
ever eventually it's so low that all
that can happen is it's going back up
again so you just got to push push that
roller coaster cart to go back up to the
top
eventually there
is an upwards
again so I believeing you and I'm glad I
could help you when you weren't feeling
well so take care of yourself I wish you
all the best and good luck thank you
soon car Absolut D
meow and py D
[Applause]
Yahoo yo next is pavi off
[Music]
collab was there no super Chats on the
members I guess it doesn't show on H Lin
I'll read it another time or didn't I
finish [\h__\h] though I don't
know I don't know it's really hard for
me to breathe you know right
now yeah I'm going to keep going a
little bit you Jim try thanks for the
pinky Pabi off collab
K
yay I'll almost assuredly have to watch
the replay of this D to work oh wait at
this point it was still planned to be in
K but I know it's going to be awesome
for sure ah oh well we have we had off
collab Koka before so surely you guys
didn't feel like it was so bad
to uh not do a Koka right you you
enjoyed the Kirby the Kirby
okay what is she
doing pick you
up
[Music]
hi Kirby was
better I'm happy to hear
that yo she Pur so much so
loudly you want more maybe some
sometime okay yeah thank you Jac monkey
happy New Year Ki I need to get I go get
a new book of Praises so I don't sound
like a broken record so for now I'll
just say thanks thanks for always being
here for us k for trying your best for
making us smile here's to a great 2024
thank you so much well I think you can
relate to me then like I or I I can
understand
so let's say you guys sent me
one uh Super Chat full of Praises per
week or maybe even more
often uh I can totally understand you
running out of things to say just as
much as how I also run out of ways to
thank you
guys yeah and I I don't want to sound in
genuine so I want to like thank you guys
in different ways I don't I don't always
want to like repeat the same things but
also no English non
Eng so it's hard for me to find
different ways of saying thank
you and like yeah reply to you guys in
unique ways no
English so
yeah
that's one one big concern that I have
that probably I worry more way more than
you guys worry about it but
still well thank you so much take it chy
don't worry about it honestly from my
perspective it uh it's not noticeable to
me that you guys maybe repeat yourself
or run out of things to say uh it's
still honestly it doesn't feel like oh
they're all saying this same things
no like even if I get told like oh great
year great
streams a million
times it actually doesn't really lose
weight to
me that's from my perspective so feel
free to continue telling me how much you
love
me and how much you enjoy my content yes
electric
cats
yeah you may feel like you're repeating
yourself and that may be true but to me
it doesn't feel really weird or anything
doesn't feel repetitive I'm still
flattered each time I just don't know
how to say thank you
anymore doesn't mean I'm not really
happy and grateful about it I just don't
know how to say it anymore I'm so so
sorry yeah no ziply you little [\h__\h]
stop
crazy yeah every word of pra still means
so much do you really touch me it really
does I it's actually surprising to me
too cuz you guys are right like it it is
like if you think about it what the
super chats that I'm reading they're
usually very repetitive but
still it doesn't feel like it so all is
good in this neighborhood jaob 47 d y
mik d yay thank you for receiving my
album Psy D Wing CB D SL of Shadows D
thank
you Daniel KS D Eugene d v d g d Slavic
fellow D for the pinky
beloved cute dorky Birds future ID
vacation fun thank you yeah we've been
slowly making slow slow slow slow slow
slow progress not really though no
progress so far but we've been talking
I've made a group I made a Discord
group we've been discussing
lodging but we don't really have a date
yet but I think it it will happen just
need to uh maybe after my break
I'll um cuz some somebody needs
to take the lead in planning this it
seems Callie's kind of too busy for it I
think
yeah so maybe after my break I'll try to
plan it with
them yeah and I I really I really want
to go I really want to see all the ID
Girls not probably not going to be all
of them most likely but I I will not say
no to an
opportunity to meet a lot of ID girls in
one spot because they're amazing I love
them Brandon I am
aicken thank
you thank you for the red chat zly yo
are you
okay p my beloved I hope you can meet
again soon it's always nice H hearing
your shenanigans here ID flight ticket
fund thank you yeah I want to fly
premium economy
please last time I went to ID I flew
from Japan and even from Japan it it
took so much
time damn but I think from here from
Austria it will take a little bit more
even let me see
definitely not something I want to go
through with economy oh my
God is there no direct
[Music]
lights surely there's some direct
flights
right oh these plats are really
shitty wait what about
Bali okay flights look really difficult
maybe I'll go by
boat maybe I'll go by boat or I'll just
walk oh cuz I could walk a thousand
miles or something like
that
[Music]
I'll have to look a little bit deeper
into flights cuz right now it's not
really showing me
anything maybe there's specific dates
they like specific Seasons cuz like for
Japan austan Airlines only does direct
flights during
uh
[Music]
summer no
even even for part right now it was
showing
me only connected flights which is like
what the
[\h__\h] no
way thank you
guys H oh well oh well I'll look at it
another
time oh thank you so sweet of
you Brandon D I am a Chien
D thanks wait I just read
that oopsy
oopsa oopsa oopsa thank you dipply
here's your kiss I think I forgot that
kiss with some germs because I just
sneezed take my germs take them h d out
run the wind D SL of Shadows D and fried
screw
[Music]
D did I did I good question I wouldn't
know where it is though the iron beat
keychain
I need to make more iron bead
thingies I have
to yo yo yo lethal
myth ah guys while I was in the males
the song came out
finally it was so delayed oh my God I'm
so sorry I'm so sorry I'm to sorry but
finally it's out I am I know that you
know it's more like Idol like so maybe
it doesn't um suit everybody's taste but
I really [\h__\h] love it it's so
like the speed the Speedy Parts I really
like them cuz they keep
me like this and really exciting and I
can like already imagine it being
performed like in in a concert someday
maybe I can imagine it I can I have a
vision and I think it will be super hype
and exciting and spread yeah energetic
energy meow meow
meow what's wrong what's wrong she's so
cute and yeah and you know because our
songs so far were all more like on the
mythical side I think uh for me
personally when I first heard this I was
like honestly I think that's exactly
what we need
we don't have like a like a fun Idol
song yet for myth
only um and I really thought this is
what we need you know have some
different Vibes our mythical songs are
really cool and
all but I wanted something different and
basically
basically this this was like the song
was apparently lying around in
the storage for like several years and I
remember I think
in during the 3D showcase
recordings we were like sitting around
and and they like reminded us like hey
by the way you guys know we have like
the
song that we were like I guess going to
have for you guys maybe but I don't know
somehow it was dropped because I don't
know I think it was maybe because
because of management changes and this
and
that and it was forgotten and I never
heard it before and then they played it
I was like oh
interesting and since it was already
like basically created I was like well
if you guys want to release it it's like
basically like the song is like paid off
now
so you want it and we're like I mean
yeah we can use it for next any
iary so that was planned for a
while but it may have been you know like
an old song that was like lying around
somewhere in the the dark dark uh Dusty
corner
but that doesn't change that is [\h__\h]
awesome I love it yeah yeah I think
having different uh Vibes different
atmospheres that's
good we brought it to life yeah we
revived it it was like in a coma the
song was in a
coma I think it would have been a waste
to just throw it
away so please enjoy it and watch the
music video on the YouTube uh give it
some views on my break perhaps yeah will
you do that for me
give my other mvs also some views thank
you I am Minecraft uh the thing that BS
was working
on true true
true that's coming out she had to delay
it a little bit but it's coming
out soon TM I'll be in that as well so
uh check it out for waa
voice anyway I'll read those super chats
now Jack 47 d py d The Gamer cre D don't
look at my profile picture D wait it
says don't look at my channel Banner but
I I can't go to your profile from Hyer
so sad Wing CB person tempor D for the
pinky I know today was not a good day
that's okay and you don't need to blame
yourself ah that was the day where pomu
yeah P's graduation was announced y I
know but
I I was really sad but I already knew it
so I had no right to be
sad oh man I was still emotional mostly
As I said not for myself but for the
fans and the artist and for
pumu that made me
emotional uh I'm sure we all understand
so don't worry but I need to say thank
you so much for bringing gooa for at
least one collab I really enjoyed it oh
yeah he's so good uh I'm glad she was
able to make it I'm glad we were able to
be full myth for this
collab and I hope we can do a few more
full myth collabs that are maybe not uh
to um advertise something I know I know
you know I know that most of our collabs
these past months or two years have been
too advertise something I'm so sorry but
it's just hard to get everybody
together um you know it's really hard to
get everybody
together maybe maybe we can do more
normal streams I'm so
sorry I'm so
sorry you know a lot of time has passed
I know Advent is doing like weekly
collabs and we used to do collabs after
after our debut more um often too you
know but it's been 3 and a half years
so everybody's like doing their own
stuff focused on their own path and has
everybody has their own issues in life
and
whatever I'm going on a break now others
have been on breaks
so
yeah yeah but I I'll I'll try to get
something
going
uh mod AR G long time
no
mop
also wait GD you thank me for organizing
this collab I don't know I don't think I
organized it did I organize it I
definitely didn't choose the
game I was like helping with like time
organizing and all that but uh it wasn't
really something that needed to be
organized for most of the part
yeah yeah I think like Ci wanted to play
lethal
company yeah I don't think I did any but
there wasn't much to do anyway like we
had our own
thumbnails yeah
but then everybody like freaking forgets
what we did the stream for it was to
remind people of the song release and I
think I was the only one who had the
graphics Ready the song release and the
uh the sales of the merchandise the
small merchandise they all forgot about
it so I made may not have organized the
collab but I may have still been the
most organized oh word
play yeah number one sales bird I am a
saleswoman I'm the
businesswoman that's me that's me that's
why wa gets amazing sponsorships with my
favorite ever games like taals of a rise
let's
go and where was I are you got Mike D
crusty D here another person thanking me
for organizing I didn't really organize
I was just organized I was organized but
I didn't organize there you
go ptic Sky I am a chicken Papa d g Trac
D salus beats D Cru D thank you
a huh do I have to say it again I was
organized but I did not
organize the
stream I see that all the other streams
like the Sims 4 and all the like the
malds collabs they barely have super
chats the only one really with a lot of
super chats this one so I think we're
not in
trouble I'll quickly read these ones
though okay okay
okay good deal take a 47
[Music]
monkey this is where I showed you guys
huh P eating my as spankenheimer
chat a free person off collab with two
vtubers and my
oi chuny wonky ah I was like what what
do you mean Free
People yeah it was kind of weird like
when when Nissa was here sitting next to
me the cats actually joined us when we
were streaming that's that was so weird
it's like they thought we were just
hanging out and they
literally like differentiated between me
talking alone to the computer to the
glowing
screens versus
me from their POV probably just talking
to a
friend they're smart I mean they they
got it wrong but they're still so smart
wow no I was fascinated
like even today when I wasn't streaming
but like recording some
singing like CH uh smoothie would come
in when I didn't sing for a moment then
I sing and she immediately leaves the
room then I stop singing for like 1
minute she comes back in thinking I'm
done I I start singing again she leaves
the room
immediately well that's probably also
because when I sing I'm kind of
loud and she doesn't like the
noise but yeah that just tells you they
normally when I'm loud here they go
away when I'm quiet in front of my
computer they join
me singing adios vamos vamos vamos
[Music]
c
fuos o stretch okay I'm I'm melting in
my
chair what's
fos did said she really likes your
singing as oh yeah yeah she kind of did
she did a English phrases kind of thing
right yeah yeah I said you little [\h__\h] I
don't think what she was trying to come
up
with I I would not put my approval stamp
on that
though that sounds not good the the
the sound the ring it doesn't ring
well hi tky wony how many times are you
going to say
hi you want you want my
attention I'm almost done baby
girl
and SP thank
you the I just Peter dinglish only
agreed to be an elf if he didn't play
elf which I feel adds another layer of
Comedy to a scene in elf I never watched
it I have literally no idea what you're
talking about but it sounds like there's
a lot
of
funny facts to this chunky wony jumped
up on the table by the way and she is
now lying down
again H tratore dun what the [\h__\h] is a
tratore fact there are secret eras in
the game such as hidden volcano wait oh
yeah yeah I didn't realize until you
guys several people pointed out that
this game was nostalgic to them so I
realized this is support
huh and so many of you guys already knew
the game from before I like that it had
a nostalgic side effect for you guys H I
didn't know this one it's a we game oh I
can see how it would be a wi game they
they probably did a lot of motion for
these sports activities
yeah motion
mention
before it seemed like a really neat
party game yeah I'm glad cuz it wasn't
even it wasn't even in our like approved
games
list so people wouldn't Pro probably
wouldn't find it in
there um
but it was pointed out to me that this
game might be good for an off collab and
then I was like well well it might not
be in our list but it's Nintendo
publisher so I think it should be okay
and I confirmed with jenma and it was
okay
[Music]
so just because something's not in our
list doesn't mean that we can't play it
I know we generally have Nintendo perms
so so I believe in my guts
[Music]
yeah always good to double check yeah
cuz like narissa made me doubt
myself she made me lose confidence cuz I
didn't want to get her or us in
trouble Psy D Lou Moonlight thanks for
the pinky Kiwa tell n about the time you
went backpacking in Wern Europe I know
she'll love that
story
huh I told her about my brother going on
the
pilgrimage
but I went
[Music]
backpacking oh I did are you trying to
like rise me up to narissa like make me
seem more impressive she didn't get
it Western Europe backpacking and West
she'll love the story is it is it a jerk
that I'm not
getting time I went backpacking
[Music]
it's a friends
rence
what I don't remember
that what was that who said that to
who it's a friend's pickup
line what from Joey or
Chandler h ah Joey
Joey Joey how you doing I love him
thanks for the red super chat Mr Egg
there's someone with an egg I I egg name
the egg emote in his name no name
besides the egg so thank you for the red
super chat kisses for red super chats
you say wa yeah you know
it choo choo Cho Little Egg you're so
round your surface is so smooth
such a nice egg would be such a shame to
crack you to drop you on the floor or
drop you in a frying
pan make you Sizzle Sizzle next to some
some bacon Stripes strips whatever and
then serve
you together with some orange
juice by the
beach would be such a shame to see you
go that way sprinkle some some rock salt
and a little bit of pepper and then I
poke you I poke your
yolk you yolk with my fork and then you
go all
over the Yol all over everything
spreading making everything
orange yum
huh sorry fried egg Good
Egg runny yolk yum
[Music]
[Laughter]
sexy that's exactly how I made the
breakfast for
narissa and Miss Lulu beff thank you for
the red chat K you are my you are my oi
I especially love all of me but you by
far my super
favorite Nara is awesome as well I love
that you are her oie have a fun trip
together it's crazy to me I thought that
would never happen I was always hoping
for it someone joining to not
necessarily say I'm their oi but to at
least say I'm I would I'm like one of
their Inspirations one of them not not
even the top one anything like that
would have made me happy one of their
favorite Senpai or
so but Nissa came in here and she went
immediately really hard she's my o I
love her
so
honestly I said it so many times before
but I really needed it I really [\h__\h]
needed it because I just generally often
feel um not so desirable
and yeah kind of
like a bit lonely perhaps so someone
like
narissa she changed she changed my life
here my work
life yeah unseen yes
yes she made it more
bearable
it's nice to have someone like narissa
around
really
so for her giving me so
much so
much love and how to
say I don't know how to
say I just felt like the least I could
do
is yeah appreciation affection all of
that the least I could do
is be friends of her be friendly to her
be welcoming to
her thank her for all the love that she
gives
me she keep kept on kept on saying that
she's like really worried that I would
be creeped out or freaked out and like
uh be really dismissive or like be like
e like keep a safe distance or so but no
if
someone comes in here and is like you
are my
favorite duh I'm I'm I'm I'm over the
moon
you you're my
savior for appreciating me you have no
idea how much that means to me
so you are automatically my best
friend in that
case thank you for giving me a little
bit of confidence back
[Music]
Louisa you guys also always give me some
much much uh appreciation and love and
support and that also means so much to
me but I think you understand right that
what I'm trying to say and what what
effect she has on me and why why I
needed
that so
yeah it's two different things
basically two different ways of support
and
affection that have different effects on
[Music]
me where was I I here thank you little B
yeah you made me go on a little bit of
an emotional tangent thank you so much
for supporting me I am happy to be in
your favorite as
well really Eternal D Ty D I am a d
Al try d z d Cruz d g d and a d wait GD
do you change you changed your picture
right actually
me once I saw that fan art I I DM jenma
I was like hey you me we're going to do
partner Discord
pictures every once in a while I think
you guys may have seen like some
screenshots or something of Discord what
you saw oh Kiwa has been using the same
Discord profile picture for a long time
now the Sparks one but recently I
changed it for the first time me and JMA
have matching profile pictures
now
yeah people probably didn't recognize me
like who the [\h__\h] is this in my
DMs who this new profile pick who this
it is me I'm just twinning with
JMA
yeah
new pfp
H yeah yeah we're looking cute together
so production and that's it uh for today
oh my God no wait that's oh my God you
know what that means that's I'm getting
an existential crisis now
oh thank you for the poy partty for the
clap
Club oh God you know what that
means okay
bye that means I'm going on on my break
that feels so so real I don't know if I
can make it I don't know if I can
actually like do what I'm trying to
do I mean tomorrow I'll still be getting
some work done so I'll I it doesn't
start right away more like the day after
tomorrow I'll still be Ed editing some
videos and organizing some stuff
and uh getting a last few little itty
bitty bits of work done so that I can
then properly take my break
mhm
yeah
e no I I will
not if a live stream pops up I won't be
watching until break ends well I won't
stream don't worry I will not stream
[Music]
I will try my best to keep
my keep my eyes off of Discord and
Twitter I
don't that help be so difficult because
Twitter like whole life made me kind of
like look at work stuff every
day um since I joined even during
Vacations so that's kind of what I'm
trying to avoid like people may think oh
she's going on a break again she was
just in the mes but you know I streamed
in the mes you know I was making content
in the
males so with all my vacations in these
three and a half years I've always been
making content and even if you guys
don't see the content I'm like behind
the scenes I'm like doing correspondence
on Discord uh working social media on
Twitter and this and that um so it's
always work there it's always work
there always
is and so this little break I'll be gone
for like uh is it really 3 weeks let me
see let me count one two three yeah
probably 3
weeks I'll be gone for 3 weeks it'll be
tough for me and you but you got to stay
strong you got to stay strong for a
bigger brighter future this is like a
motivation speech when we go to
[Music]
war just when you're when you're lonely
when you miss me watch some older
streams watch some streams that maybe
you haven't seen and also you know I'll
be uploading a a lot of little videos so
make sure to watch them that's your
little uh Wawa video per day keeps the
doctor
away
doses
I don't know this feels really surreal
to me it's kind of dramatic to me now
too with that music welcome back chy
wony it's so
dramatic it's like I'm doing something
big something
huge I'm doing something epic I'm going
to take a break
yo I'm on the big Quest and that Quest
is taking a [\h__\h] epic
break a break like you've never seen
before an actual break but yeah I was
going to say like Twitter I'm actually
addicted to
Twitter because like obviously I've
been it to Twitter way before H life so
um
yeah [\h__\h] how do I I mean I don't I I'm
not going to
like um ban Twitter for my
myself I'm just going to ban whole life
Twitter for myself like anything that
has to do with whole life I do not want
to
see so yeah delete the app no
no
[Music]
no no I can't
Twitter I'll I'll try to not be on it as
much but I still probably have to look
at Twitter a little bit
otherwise I'm going to go
crazy it's okay at least I don't go on
Discord that's the most important thing
like really me just like being able to
not do any work for more than a
day that's going to be the biggest
Miracle that's the point of this break
really and not
streaming I'm detoxing don't worry
that's that's a big detox all ready
that's like the detox of the century for
me holy moly I'm so scared guys I am
shaking I'm
shaking I'm scared can you take my
hand I don't even have the kfp plushy
yet how am I going
to hug you and take your
wing to calm me
down just kidding I don't need it I'll
have my
cats yeah but yeah thank you for letting
me do this thank you
for surely being patient in the coming
weeks um I I hope you guys don't
completely uh forget about me or get
used to me not being around and then
you're like oh this is actually kind of
fine actually I think I'm okay without
her oh she's back streaming oh yeah but
I don't really care about her anymore
unsubscribe be no don't do that
please this [\h__\h] pal W music is
making me so dramatic this RPG office
RPG
clothes feel like I'm about to go on a
big ass ship and go over the big ass
ocean and I'll I'll
Stand in in the very front the beak of
the ship and I'll be like I'm on top of
the
world the really big cut scene before
the final boss
fight what's the final boss
fight what am I
[Music]
fighting before before I go on this epic
travel to the final big boss fight I
have to have one last talk with all the
NPCs know all the team members
no like a uh emotional oneon-one with
every single one of them but I guess
that was the Super Chat
reading that was the Super Chat
reading press the button you mean to
stop streaming
button I'm
scared you're stalling yeah it's like
what the [\h__\h] this feels almost like a
graduation
stream
[\h__\h] I'll be back as another Austrian
has said before dramatically while I
think with a fump in the air I
think I'll be
back
yeah remember that 3 weeks
okay don't don't again I'll tweet uh
something tomorrow I think that I am
going on a break and uh hopefully I'll
get at least some of the Polar words
I'll try to get all of them but if it's
too much then I'll just upload part of
it
okay the polar wa from
Christmas I already miss her I miss
myself too where did I go where am I
where where I'm alone I'm all
alone make sure to relax a lot y I mean
it's not even mostly about relaxing but
I'll I'll be relaxing too it's more
about just being away from work and also
getting some stuff done IRL stuff done
that I've been like pushing away and
ignoring
[Music]
mhm I'm going senile seile yeah
H the accident was two years ago we need
to let go no no what
accident honestly I'd rather you not
stress over Po and do them when you
return from break no it's
okay I'll try to do them tomorrow I
don't want you guys to wait too long
they're Christmas themed after
all Chinese New Year with kiaha you'll
miss it oh we can celebrate it
afterwards
[Music]
I need to let go get back to swimming
and exercise no maybe in
summer I don't mind waiting thank
you Samantha no I'm
Kiwa not Sam Mana fly you fool
oh I guess I'll go
oh
okay are you going to miss
me
wait are you going to miss me
yes
[Music]
maybe
goodbye
farewell I'll be do in see you in the
Far Far
Future will will maybe have changed you
might not recognize
me but I'll still be the same person
that you once loved the same Phoenix
that you always looked up to as a little
chicken trying to to become as big and
and graceful as
me with
flames and big
wings I'll still be the
same and I won't forget you even if you
forget me cuz you have less brain cells
than
me little chicken
bread oh always think of
you every night I'll touch that portrait
that picture
frame in
bed and think of
you when I see you
again I'll
have as
[Music]
many
uh what's the
word
I'll have as many
creases in my crinkles
wrinkles in my face as it dressle the
big tree
has in his bark bark bark
bark
B I will become a
raisin the raisin that you hate so much
in your apple strudel that I make for
you every other day because you love it
so
much because I love
you yeah
um words can't describe my love for you
but not even this big distance or
time can get between my love for
you oh my God love
forever
no it
shall say my
farewell
cuz I'm
leaving on the dead
plane I don't know when I'll be back
again oh
no I hate to
go cuz I'm
leing on the Jet Plane I don't know when
I'll be back again oh oh babe I hate to
go oh so that gets you huh my whole
emotional speech you were like oh shut
up stop stalling and I sing a little bit
of that one song and suddenly suddenly
you care suddenly The Tears start
flowing suddenly you're like no this is
so
depressing
[Music]
wow okay I'm going going to go what it's
so weird what how can I not stream for
free oh God I'm going to get like a like
a [\h__\h] mental breakdown from not
streaming
oh okay I'll go fine I'll go I'm going
to lose my mind but I'll go please keep
me in your prayers um I don't really
believe in that but please keep me in
your prayers because I think uh I I will
lose my
mind okay keep it
together
woman
H oh yeah I mean we could do seven no I
don't I don't care I I also don't feel
so well so I'm going to
go you will pray for me thank you thank
you that means a lot to
me all
right
it's so
dramatic
goodbye
chickens when I'll be back you'll be so
grown
up I'll be missing out on so much of
your
growth I hope
I hope I don't miss too much I hope I
don't miss your first baby
steps and your first words or your last
words okay I'll
go goodbye my loved
ones farewell Sal
now is the
time it is
over until it
isn't
anymore well I'm
dark
goodbye I love you [\h__\h]
Amigos and in German we
say I won't
forget I won't
forget
[Music]
you
okay I'll [\h__\h] die
[Music]
I
why the [\h__\h] is it only
[Music]
77%
man bye
[Music]
bye