[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
meow
meow meow meow
[Music]
Kitty
hello Mama let's watch your finishes
hell yeah we're gonna finish it today
um I haven't seen you guys in a while we
thought he uh missed you guys
it's nice to be back hello I'll I will I
will oh the purring sounds so good man
hear my headphones oh man I will tell
you about my weekend today uh
but I mean there are a lot of I did a
lot of things in the weekend so
might not even be able to finish
my whole story always I I should have I
should have done you know a whole stream
about this trip too like I usually do I
guess but oh well
is your foot healed up now
depends on what you um what healed up
means for you because
I mean it's it's not completely healed
but it's all right uh yeah no longer the
fire yeah
yeah
you can still definitely see it but I
feel like
it's dried up well enough that
you know skin has been starting to grow
back but like in really really thin
layers it's still like red but yeah it's
okay hello
hello yeah and also it's just a tiny
thing usually I I made a big deal out of
the tiny but it's not really I mean you
know it's not really convenient when you
have
an open wound on your toe that you walk
on and your whole weekend is going to be
spent on sand that's the detail I didn't
tell you guys because I didn't want to
tell you until afterwards but I was just
you know if I was if I could have spent
the whole weekend on normal ground then
it wouldn't have been so much of a
problem but I spent my whole weekend on
sand
yeah
so yeah especially if you weren't yeah
exactly like the like the original
reason why that happened was because I
was wearing flip-flops
and then you know the ideal Footwear for
Beach would be flip-flops but I couldn't
even wear those anymore because it would
just make it worse so didn't even wear
my flip-flops on the beach anyway I'll
tell you all about it or like partially
all about it
and we're going to
uh play this game until the end killed
on it
[Music]
sand gets everywhere yeah it does oh my
God controller controller do be
vibrating
um let me put the water here if that
works that works amazing you know I have
I have like a like a like a planter like
a stand for a plant for plants next to
me that has like several levels like
three different levels of heights it's
like connected and I only have one plant
on it though so now it has the perfect
size the perfect height for me to place
my water on it my water jug nice yeah
uh also all my
um probably not not because of not being
uh watered but just because of other
reasons my plants are completely dead
now I mean the the balcony plants are
now
completely
completely lost
[Laughter]
like you know as if the the heat wasn't
enough to kill them and now the wind has
killed them even further and they're
dead they [\h__\h] did
you know my berries died long ago yeah
and they never really stood a chance it
seems
but you know I still had like cherry
tomatoes there that were still going
strong
um but even my cherry tomatoes have now
been completely destroyed it seems
hey thanks for the super chats guys by
the way I'll read them later yeah yeah
yeah
um yeah so sad man because like even if
I get restarted now like if I start all
over now
it's too late like I won't get any
plants any any
produce out of it anymore this year I
think so sad unless there's something
that if I plant it now it will grow like
I don't know in October or so I don't
know if there's anything there I don't
think so I don't think so I'm so [\h__\h]
sad
French raspberries every day it wasn't
that easy man there's too many natural
circumstances that
just [\h__\h] you over tomorrow
bean sprouts
if your balcony is covered you could
work as a greenhouse I don't think it
could work as a greenhouse no ah
however my mom sent me a picture
flexing her produce from her garden like
a million tomatoes and oversized
zucchinis and [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] she has
like she could make like
tomato sauce for
to cover one week for a hundred
humans
pretty much
it's crazy crazy okay so uh let's let's
get started I'm already tangenting
through a million things already but we
want to play the game how do I
mean
yeah you guys hear the sound yeah I
think I mean
there's not much to hear right now let
me
go oh I only hear it on one ear that's
interesting
oh yeah yeah tell me what I was supposed
to do thank you for all that have a
great position now oh yeah I don't want
to talk to you
we're 1080p today
oh yeah I graded it down again
I don't know whatever uh it's good
enough why do I only hear it on one ear
whatever that's okay I'll I'll accept it
oh wait I totally forgot about the light
how did I just turn it on
I just turned it on by accident
how did I turn that on
oh I want to talk to the lady was it
this stop me okay now that we'll fix
that tracker let's find Seamus and track
down his papa no time to lose oh man
okay so where the hell was that dude
somewhere in the city right you guys
have a hint because like I don't really
remember much
I mean I do remember but like you know
uh give can you give me like a
Kickstarter and where do I need to go
where I dropped the white paint ah okay
where the dudes cleaning okay okay
I think that's like somewhere
somewhere I know it can't be there
there's just yeah dead ends that's what
I thought
uh wait
wait let me do that again I was sick
oh it Ducks automatically when going
through that I love that why why am I so
fascinated
you see that it talks automatically cool
see
okay wait let me find the white paint
place
[Music]
I have to talk about
what what wow
I didn't realize the cat could move that
flexibly
foreign
[Music]
washing place
nice jumps
was he like up there
you mean that you mean at the top
well I was here at the top
has the white paint on your right across
the street to the left one pass the
light paint on your right on my right
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
here
yeah thank you that was a nice
explanation easy easy to understand for
stupid cats like me you manage to fix
that tracker uh yeah I think I did yeah
as far as I remember
fix tracker you did it you fixed it well
done yeah give it here oh yeah yeah you
can have it
[Music]
should I turned out audio up guys
oh
advice
that's too loud
whenever I do it it's too loud
oh we got a pig oh no
is Papa really alive I can't believe it
let's follow the track and maybe we'll
find where my papa went
ah he just went out to buy milk right
the usual stuff
[\h__\h] ping yeah oh yeah good okay
tell me when there's a problem meow I
love you
I love you guys too
the music is nice for me yeah
do robots drink milk
yeah I don't think so
but robots have evolved a lot in this
day and age so
maybe they do it's so slow we'll see
[Music]
all right this guy was incredible way of
the way thank you I'm glad you guys like
the director's cut there were a lot of
changes made
uh
uh so I'm happy with it
this must be it he really left the slums
it's dangerous out there but I must be
sure I need to know let's do this
yeah
it was 4K
um I think it didn't Premiere in 4k but
uh it's actually 4K so if you didn't if
you only watched your Premiere check it
again
for like the 10th time because now it's
4K
capital
[Music]
don't close the door behind me please
can you leave it open so I can get back
is he joining me
oh my God yes
he is
let's see if I remember how to play this
game
I mean there wasn't much to you besides
jumping right and running look at all
these jerk jerk eggs they will eat us I
can't I can't I can't do this I'm not as
fast as you the xerx will get me for
sure
here it took it takes his bed my papa
will recognize it he will know that your
friend
oh okay
wait wasn't it normally the the mouth
was the out the other one was it a happy
mouth
why is that outside of badge with like a
sad one was it always like this
are you sleepy
not not like really I don't know it's my
body just wants to yawn a lot foreign
it was always like this oh
oh
wait is it
okay well he left me alone for real and
he closed the door
she haha he's watching me
watching me dude don't watch me like
that that's scary with that face as if
he looks like his face
why is it
wait the music scares me
okay I'm [\h__\h] scared
um
when he looks at me like that I feel
like he's
she has something planned
hey okay okay can we not do that music
it's freaking me out it's like a horror
movie now hey quiet
you know
oh don't do that what is this soundtrack
freaks freaks me out
like like what
then
music is a [\h__\h] jumpscare
thank you taco mom
wait I was so scared I'm so scared I'm
so scared why am I so scared
oh
meow meow to feel better
memory
remember
look at how he was his wall is oh yeah
I'm liking Game of Thrones
I remember it was a symbol of the
division between those and the slums in
Midtown
and that and the fact that they kept
throwing the garbage down here hmm what
a horrible thing to do maybe that's why
they failed
okay I don't want to go there
it's okay it's okay it's okay it's
I would be a stupid cat to go there that
end literally tells you you'll die there
let that end
it's a dead end guys
[Music]
I would be stupid to go there
oh
[Music]
you got a dead end in English in English
it has such a
weird name though because like in German
it's not like dead end it's like a
soccer cassette
which is a bag
back path I don't know
it's it doesn't it's not so scary it's
not such a scary name and I think in
Japanese I forgot now but I don't think
it was something so scary either or
intimidating
yeah back
and yeah I don't know what's it called
that
cul-de-sac oh
is that the French word for it
and people say German sounds right it's
not
um
Japanese is just
ghost up going stops that's the word for
a dead end in Japanese it's that simple
have you noticed I've been stalling
because like I'm really scared to go
ah
okay
rad just run I'll just run oh no
um
okay
do I keep on going straight
[Music]
you can't jump in you can't
change
is still there chilling
chunky wonky oh cute
why didn't that looked like it could go
there
look totally looked like it could jump
up there don't you think
like it's if you don't know
but you decide to go there so determined
you'll end up being so [\h__\h] that's
kind of sad
oh my God okay
okay so left here and then right
even though all the monsters are there
uh like how they're like right there
okay keep on going my nose is
[Music]
okay oh pretty good pretty good pretty
good
[Music]
where do I go where do I go from here
where do I go from here oh I guess not
up I guess we're going down
foreign
it's kind of hard to know without trying
a few times
um
it looked like I could maybe go up too
sometimes there's things you can climb
up and sometimes you can't
and it's like uh almost impossible it's
not sometimes
get attacked by this
just have to while still maintaining to
run I want it
I can hard to like
get them off of you while also jumping
oh look at that
oh spin
[Music]
okay okay
oh pretty good they can they barely are
getting me what how do I do this
okay
and up and up nice and uh I don't know I
hear
okay we're chilling for a while
but uh
that went okay ish
no that won't work or maybe I have to go
there
can you can you
no okay don't fall into that
melon soda juice
uh I don't I don't feel like I have to
go there I
gotta go here and then I go there
to give it some momentum I need a bit
more momentum Maybe
or
I need a little bit more momentum
maybe I
know okay now we're good
have you guys drunken met on soda before
like I feel like outside of like Asian
countries you don't uh
[Applause]
get up
well that was fun
could have made it a little bit of a
longer segment I wouldn't have minded
It's like snowboarding
are you okay that was a huge fault yeah
I'm fine
oh yes me
foreign
a dog should be nearby we must be close
okay
oh no I'm hurt again
oh but cats recover fast
and conveniently there's no monsters
around so oh yeah clean yourself now I
feel better
that was fast
yeah yeah all right recover fast
food
oh shh
independent yeah there are so many other
members also play this game seems like
it turned out to be a
everybody's favorite game this month
I hope you guys don't don't uh mind me
finishing it up too I wanted to you know
play it there right the next day after
but I needed to do you know super
chattels and all that and yeah I knew
that it was gonna be a problem because I
was gonna be gone for a few days so yeah
circumstances somehow sometimes not
always are the best
oh
well
oh no everybody loves cats I'm not
surprised
this is like a market
this this thing in the middle
I'm scared I'm scared but there's no
monsters I'm fine wow
[Music]
what do we want to check out oh bananas
No No Bananas
cool place
watch only you watch only me hey did you
like the hashtag workout cow carrot
video
I'm glad we got that one out of the way
[Music]
yeah
newcomers
can check those videos out to
understand the kfp history I think it's
really useful
oh
I don't have an item for this I wonder
what it needs I guess it would be close
by
it's an electric generator but it seems
to require some other part to function
which I don't seem to have unless it
uses energy drinks okay something about
that size is probably somewhere around
here
um
probably over there
um oh God
oh it's really dirty and red
scary okay I'm guessing it's pretty deep
in oh wait what is that no that's not it
why
as long as there's no monsters
I can chillax
hello
meow
what is this ew it's so disgusting
it's like the inside of a human body
ew
oh oh oh what is this place oh
the monsters in here but in the cage
doctor is this you
know nice music safe Zone
hi is it really safe it seems safe
they're trying to attack me wait this
isn't knife on top
step stability stab
[Music]
so it's the electric thing maybe here
no I don't see anything in particular
I have them trapped yeah good job maybe
there's someone downstairs Mia
oh hello
is this dog
what's up
oh
[Music]
wait you know who are you that's my bed
you're wearing how did you find it did
my son send you oh see Miss You clever
boy I've been alone here for ages I came
here to to test my deflector but I
didn't go as planned
I wish I could go back home I miss my
son dearly
you cannot it's not even that far like I
can help you go back probably
I mean yeah there was this whole like
jumping run section but besides that
it's not that far
I have no idea how to escape this place
okay
oh there's a memory here also what is he
doing though
he's just looking outside
can I can I take the memory that you got
here oh well
and when you forget something
well with a bucket
buses wear costumes like this
they were small and running around
making a lot of noise
oh yeah I remember now they were
chilling and he's talking about
Halloween
streets felt much more alive with them
even though the difficulty they brought
the adults seem to love them very much
doc says he misses Siemens is that the
same thing
[Music]
I don't know I'm just missing something
Halloween Halloween is fun where's this
thing oh look at that that's like a gun
NY
hello tell me about this
I think yeah that's how we kill those
those monsters oh yeah the flexor at
full charge you can explode jerk and
full charge you can explode jerks like
confetti this baby needs 1.21 gigawatts
to work and the only thing around here
what that with that kind of juice is the
generator outside the house
the problem is that it won't start I
think a few is blue and with all the
xerx around it's too dangerous for me to
go out and fix it
I'm not fast enough but you just might
be if you can catch the generator it
reach the generator and replace the fuse
I should be able to get the flux
recharged come on follow me I'll show
you what to do okay
well is it a reference why does
everybody
I know nothing
foreign
wow
sick
noise
back to the feet oh
oh we oh we watched that
oh wait why did you go did you go for a
year on it no you did he go up
where's up
yeah
dunk
no we did we didn't
what
what did we watch okay
oh
maybe we should watch it
one time
huh oh yeah hitchhikers thank you that
was that's what I was thinking about
hitchhikers is a Galaxy
[Laughter]
[Music]
maybe you guys like me
here take this fuse it's brand new
oh thank you
oh thank you easy
turning on the generator will be loud so
expect
[Music]
once you fix the generator I should be
able to charge and Kickstart and flux
you just need to follow this cable
change the fuse and meet me back oh
okay
[Music]
um
cable
this now
oh well that will be a good help for
running back here
to keep my eyes on the cable yellow
cable
okay
I've got it
I will probably fail at least once
can you go faster kitty cats you already
know what's coming don't you
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah wait shoot them
oh yeah
okay can I go I'm coming
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
uh uh oh yeah oh yeah thank you thank
you bye thank you
[Music]
pricing so hard am I should I like stay
in the light for a little bit
literally a UV lamp no hold on
should I stay there like is it like a
tactical
thing to just like stay in the light for
a little while yeah
for a bit until he like does he adjust
where he does it according to where I am
oh no he just gets rid of all of them
once and then he follows me
okay
hey it's just you still see me hello
I guess that's it
unless oh that's it that's it
ah okay easy I thought it would be just
like me running fast but I can stand
yeah
[Music]
you got the generator back on it wasn't
that much work
have you seen how powerful it is
luxuries it's definitely our way out of
here yeah but how do I if I can replace
my headlight with this that would be
nice thank you
oh yeah okay he's mounting into my drone
Coolio
[Music]
nice dog
cute
oh
so now you have to remind me how to use
then
and so instead of my fancy drone it's
not meant to run off such a small power
source if you use it too much it could
malfunction
just remember it's dangerous now let's
go back to the Village I'm coming home
okay so we bring him home once let's go
uh I'm gonna turn it on again
it has a meter what
me too
oh like how much I can use it yeah yeah
okay Allen
ah but it like goes back down okay
take out all the desserts so we can get
fruit I did
but wow it's working great but as I
suspected it can overheat
cool down for a bit when it happens I
hope it would last until we reached a
village
easy peasy lemon squeezy or jerk squeezy
because
it seems to be some juice coming out of
them we can make a cocktail out of them
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
where where oh God they're probably
right behind us
our day
I can't move
switch doesn't work
um yeah electricity was cut let's eat
so you're just gonna stand there
how about trying to lift it huh
you're thinking
really
come on you're a doctor
you've got more brains than I do I think
must be a way to open the door okay it's
on me of course it is I knew it
I'll I'll open it
so straight a second out and I'm gonna
figure out something
wait maybe it wants my lights too do you
think it went by UV light
okay it doesn't
ah then that puts you in a cool down
okay
good to know when when I
uh do I have to roll them somewhere
huh
overheat mm-hmm
cool
I don't know
huh
only one out of the day well I don't
know what no way Leon out of the way
okay okay and this one all the way to
the other side what what is there on the
other side wait it's not quite
[Music]
we're going there up on up on that tube
Maybe
how far
should I go
I know there oh
oh there's something there
is
up and uh
up
and up
I'm scared
I did zerk's there no
oh okay
yeah no
I wanted to go
out there maybe that wasn't maybe that
wasn't even possible it looked like it
could have been possible
like a swing but it wasn't necessary
because ta-da
uh is that opening the door right now
[Music]
okay normal lives it doesn't mean I died
nine times
scary did we already open no
scary
come here
[Music]
come here [\h__\h]
try me
[Music]
okay
I had it okay okay
there's more
but wait there's more
okay let's kill him
okay beautiful beautiful beautiful
beautiful
so ah we have to open it from the other
side okay
okay oh
yeah you're not gonna die oh I'm gonna
help you
I'm gonna I'm gonna uh
[Music]
what's the best way to do this
okay I'm okay
that was close let's go back home
no no what's the sound from behind the
door
to be careful doctor
a certain scientific UV light is what I
have with me
I [\h__\h] love railgun
hello
where are the monsters
where are the monsters although they'll
come from above herself
right behind us
where where are they where are they
where are they
crew
are we good have a good I'm good
oh
three onions
[Music]
oh
oh oh
[Music]
thanks for saving duck little friend
it's great to see that Steamers is no
longer alone now we know that we can
fight back against the jerks Momo has
been waiting for you by the sewers
how can see must look happy I think we
did a good thing together
oh it's so nice to see family reunions
nah
oh man oh this place wasn't open before
right
meat
woman's waiting for you in his boat you
can join him but have you done
everything oh
just like a
can't go back anymore I'll close the
door behind you don't want any zerk's
comfort understandable
I know I think I mean we did all the
songs
is there anything in particular I should
do
before guys
foreign
did I like finish
[Music]
um
you cans
[Music]
I'm missing one right
oh but I I if I understand correctly the
last one is kind of tricky to find
[Music]
the memories are they all if not you can
play a chapter over again oh it I mean
I'm definitely missing memories but I
don't know if they're all like here
how many I'm missing
[Music]
[Laughter]
I have one memory from the slums left
vending machine last time machine is in
the corner at the balcony level
what
corner of the balcony
Corner when
corn Arrow balcony level
go up
okay oh I'll try to first of all
higher up
and the roofs the corner what corner
though
good morning
corner
okay let's see Corner where's the corner
where is the corner uh
vending machine
above Grandma I don't remember what
grandma was
Vanishing top of the TV
top of the TV TV
it's a
no that's just a AC
unit
hmm
[Music]
find Hector it's below him
who's Hector again
God damn it I don't I don't remember
foreign
are we trying to find the last one
oh
one of my
dad song that's new
that's new
I don't remember that
how do we get in here in the top most
likely I want to get in there
um
[Music]
but there's like spikes on there
it won't let me it won't let me
TV is on the ground level huh okay well
one second I want to get up there
I can't get into all doors oh okay is
this one where I can't go in but it
makes me so curious with the singing
well there's literally everything it was
sorry
yeah so now somebody says I should go
down because the TV is down um
maybe I'll find it by accident if I just
if I just walk around who is this guy
again
my friend and I love love touching
buckets at each other good Queen fun our
downstairs neighbor disagrees so we're
taking a break right now
why would I give him something
what would I give to you
know the paint people
hmm
you're just chilling now are you guys
help him
just watching him clean everything up
and don't do [\h__\h]
why am I going it gives you a clue in
the memory bar
in memory bar
okay we're probably not gonna 100 this
but at least I want to get the energy
drink
[Music]
um
am I like even close to where that
machine is
or am I like at the very
ah other side of the
City
no yes other side go opposite side from
elevator
with elevator you mean the bucket
I think you are go to the ground I think
you are oh I'm close
go to ground level okay
no down
so and where the paint is
okay
um what is that
um
is that a bug
that's a common bug okay because that's
[\h__\h] creepy
is that like the end boss
why quite good
[\h__\h] scary
oh my go away it's creepy
ripe humans on you where was the TV
I'll just explore the whole ground again
I'll find the TV eventually
could be an Easter egg no I don't think
it's it's an Easter egg it's a it's a
bug
and what's up
talk with Grandma
you're liking your outfit yeah I love it
thank you oh [\h__\h]
wrong way close to here
start start from Guardian then go
opposite side
okay you know for once I actually know
what you're talking about I know who the
guardian is but
what
[Music]
I wasn't able to run for a moment I
wonder why
ah
[Music]
why is it so loud here
[\h__\h]
is it a is that a sound bug
sound bug yeah I thought it was like the
buckets bucket moving
oh
my God
cursed
[\h__\h] cursed mate okay
uh so a guardian this dude right that's
the guardian yeah opposite side so first
I went that way so now I go that way
but that's just uh
that's just bad
maybe maybe just not this way but
um
what about this one
this way
in a tight hallway
okay what is that TV this is a TV
[Applause]
but that's not a tight hallway
there
that's that's a tight hallway
path
real TV is it inside a building or
outside
a vending machine I already used
TVs are in there
outside
it can't be so difficult to find it
what about here
to me
and then Above This
okay how do I get up
here
there it is
yay
thank you
[Music]
energy drink this
let's go
to the shop we go right to the shop
shop doco here is the painter up there
thank you very much it's really hard to
read you're like what there's like a
fence right in front of it
okay what were we going to buy with the
drinks this thing
I want to buy this
yeah okay that's that's what it was
show this one I only showed him one but
I guess he's taking all them oh
yeah is that the last one I had left
here
this is an early model of a companion
back then they didn't have any
personality they were just glorified
autonomous cleaners find the memory fine
fine
meow Marie
I think in science that thing eventually
mimics humans
it's like they missed them and in a way
they kind of kept them from going
extinct yeah
they're good robots Nia
oh
48 of memories yeah okay I guess so
that's it then I bought everything here
then I can leave now
[Music]
you can leave meow
meow Marie
missed one and Dead End
okay whatever
oh
hi ghosted
said
well I like this place interesting
hi yeah
oh my God
freaking me out are we gonna go on a
boat
like invented Venice wait this is the
boat oh my God how fun wait let me
explore
before I talk to you
washing machine
oh
I'm gonna go for that hole
[Music]
smart gotta loot yeah but I don't really
see anything to loot unless in here
no no
no okay
hello pay attention to me again please
hello look at me I think his head is
glitched why is everything glitching
today I'll go to this side and you can
look at me on this side
jump on the boat when you're ready let's
get out of here I'll go right Mama let's
[\h__\h] go okay
I can't believe you found that
what was it
that sounds like a Yoshi
at the defluxer deflexer with this now
we can go to find the balthaza let's go
okay
did you hear Yoshi I heard Yoshi
[Applause]
[Music]
bass boosted me oh it wasn't meow oh
AKA Venice
let's go City technical Network nice
graffiti
oh oh are we gonna fall out of there
eventually
cool oh
am I dirty or why is that like stuff
falling off of me like I have fleas or
something
you sit acute
sit and doing a seat
is he singing
keep your eyes open oh okay
okay I'm keeping
or is there something attacking me soon
but there's a dead end there bunny
do they have to open it there's like
some platform over there for me to open
it up
nanny
yummy
yeah
I don't see a way to open this guy can
you take a look at the other side
me
why is it always me but like I can't ah
jump right here
oh no
Kawaii alkaline
yeah a little scary I'm scary I'm scared
I'm so scared I can't speak English
anymore let's speak Deutsch
uh uh uh Sofia Sofia the lizard side yo
come on
foreign
hinta minor deadlines
also sad life
[Music]
um
struggle yeah um is it gonna like pop
out of there
What if I preemptively
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
what what would they have like jumped
out eventually without me like popping
them
Wonder
Ed
okay okay
then I like it this way
what if I missed jumping on this thing
I've never been this far out of the
slums with you here I'm not even scared
that's good
um I'm not scared
either totally
oh let's turn on the lights
okay I'm keeping my eyes open it's
probably all I see you guys do I how far
does the light even go
not very far I think
they're gonna they're gonna jump down
they're gonna jump down
when we pass through they're gonna jump
down
see ya
[Music]
what's your number
are you coming
I'm ready
they didn't they didn't they didn't
they didn't
[Laughter]
huh what am I keeping my eyes open for
[Music]
Bamboozled those cowards
oh should I have attracted them
I'm naturally attractive I don't have to
meow
foreign
[Music]
did you break it
[\h__\h] idiot
Ana
all this old Machinery is broken now I
think we can only open it manually
Aha and um me the cat I'm the one to
figure it out got you got you got you
got you gotcha
I got you I got you fam leave it to me
okay it's not here
why are
oh oh wait oh he is opening it up I was
like is it is this an earthquake
okay he's up there
you're
that's that's gonna take a while I guess
I'm gonna do it on the other side
no
your wine
do I go to the other side how how would
I if you if you're too weak to pull it
up how would I be stronger than you
how do I go over there
cool won't I pass under oh wait I fought
really I'm alone now
sorry yeah
I can't go in with you but uh I want to
stop looking for a way okay so you tell
me you're gonna come at a moment where
I'm fighting for my life probably and
you're gonna rescue me when you find
somebody in clementine tell them I was
Brave
I'll tell them I was Brave
bye bye oh God
oh my God
[Music]
okay so the bottle size Dead
Clementine also dead
okay cool
um let's not tell him let's not crush
his spirits
okay I'm terrified
I'm terrified
why is he hanging
oh big eggs there's big eggs over there
okay okay
I will have to crush them
what about all those
maybe those those are just decoration
but those over there they look like
they're gonna
after was cursing filth I thought I
thought I can't touch it
oh it looks like I'm fine
okay let's
[Music]
see
where did the other go let's just
chilling here
okay
um I wonder if I can get upgrades or
something
I guess okay I just I I can like only do
it for a short second and that already
works okay okay I have to just be more
more energy saving and effective but I
do Wonder
those those don't even die okay good
some of them glitch into the walls that
makes me happy because I have less to
deal with
would have been a nice feature though
oh God
come back to me
no no no no no [\h__\h] no [\h__\h] hell
[\h__\h] out [\h__\h] out [\h__\h] out no
no no
no no no
okay come at me I hate it I hate it
get back
I'm alive as long as I'm alive
all is good ah look at them waiting over
there
like a distance upgrade and a a radio
right radio right righty oh radius
upgrade and a a battery upgrade those
three things would be nice
oh okay these ones don't
don't come out of their shell
this ain't no RPG no even
Jake if how I could still see it doing
that oh hello memory
remember
Chihuahua deep in your heart to remember
the story system yes I remember now
clean water was scarce
he was supplied by huge Machinery that
dug deep into the Earth
just like everything else it was racial
race rationed
to sustain people during times of drunk
drought drought
the scientists showed me the blueprint
of the one tanks they were huge and
could contain a whole building in them
huh
51 okay now yeah it seems like we've
missed one but now we're halfway through
the memories
ratio
I want to tell you my story my story
from the weekend but
I feel like I'll take a million breaks
telling you the story uh so time to rely
on Kyle carrot
uh
what
story time when I figure out where to go
first
um
wait is it just a dead end here
the ones that are stuck in the wall I'm
making noises
no but this is uh not it either
maybe that way because I came from there
is it that way oh
looks like it okay so that was like a oh
that looks like a secret spot to get the
memory okay okay guys wow wow wow wow
so let me tell you where I went
um I surprise surprise I actually was in
Italy
from Thursday to yesterday late evening
[Music]
what what mama
mommy guess how many times I used the
words Mamma Mia on my trip
oh
real traveler yeah they just show them
your accent I spoke
to a couple of friends with my friend
Circle and I mean that was the only one
who even spoke like at least a few words
of Italian so I did I did Flex my
um Italian a little bit
is ice cubes guys and I ordered ice
creams for example one time at dinner
and everybody was like holy [\h__\h] kiwawa
you are a genius I'm like thank you yeah
I am and it was that was actually on the
last day last dinner
um well I was wow I ordered the cube
and I kept on like trying to impress the
waitress because she was really cute and
like I I was like uh for Keta when she
laid down the the fork next to me I was
like forget that and she looks at me and
gives me this really happy smile
and then I was like I picked up the the
knife and I was like I don't remember I
don't remember it's what I said in
English and she she barely spoke like
not no English at all but um she
understood that I was trying to figure
it out so she was like and I was like
that's what it was and she looks at me
like really and she grins and this is
really happy again she looks so cute I
kept on trying to you know impress her
oh it was really
exciting
oh
okay
uh yeah yeah yeah yeah
nah she didn't think I was a child she
just felt I was cute because of my
Italian skills
hell yeah okay
step by step one by one
[Music]
okay
it just needs a tiny bit really just a
tiny bit
um so I actually
um oh
there's there's this whole story about
why I went to Italy uh I will tell you
um so you know how my birthday was on
the 6th of July
right guys you remember because I had a
concert
I know you remember
but
um because I was doing that concert
um and because my friends were like
partially not available
uh we couldn't really you know do
anything together oh my God
uh-huh
okay yeah so I didn't do a birthday
party or anything with my friends
yeah
I'm in this [\h__\h] mess up
and uh you know
[Music]
I hmm I my friends
you know they always wanted to go to
this convention before Oh my God
[Music]
Comics are so in three minutes yeah and
I I heard a lot about it too for a long
time because it's a it's like a
convention at the beach
in Italy in a city called telemini which
is really just a like a random
city city I mean it was it was not nice
but like it's not like it was like as
special as Rome or whatever
[Music]
pretty famous at Columbus yeah I would
say it's like out of like in Italy
there's like two conventions that I
always wanted to go to like Luca Luca is
like insanely big and
um oh
uh it's really big and it's like through
like taking place in the whole city
outside in the evening like afternoon is
that it doesn't even start in afternoon
it starts like after like 4 pm or so I
think I don't know from what I've heard
and then there was Rimini which is a
Beach Convention which also kind of cool
because yeah it's like it's like a mix
of a convention with a vacations doesn't
that sound fun
like I know like America for example has
most of their conventions in like hotels
yeah imagine just going to uh going to a
beach to like see all all the peeps all
your friends and all that and hang out
there
um
yeah it's in it's in the summer and I I
always heard about it and I always
wanted to like go there someday where
did I come from
I came from there
wait I lost orientation
I guess I have to look at this
oh big door
big door
there's no level pull it level it's kind
of hard to see right ah there it is oh
foreign
[Music]
okay
go left or right guys
run
no I'm fine that was easy
are there more coming
and on the ceiling right
[Music]
quiet
foreign
I feel like the obvious path would be
the middle but is there like a memory or
something hidden here
I can't I can't go down okay
paranoid chill I mean I wouldn't be
surprised they'll probably do it
eventually what was that okay hi
okay
nice it's so much I feel so much more
powerful now that I can actually take
care of them
foreign
[Music]
why did they react like that just now
okay I'm terrified I'm terrified
um
why do you know that oh my god oh okay
it sounds like
is that what it does oh my God it's the
same one conceives me
once it sees me it sends me like
these [\h__\h]
no okay but like how do I not get seen
um
is that even an option not being seen
it already sees me from the moment I
enter this place
oh it sends them to me in a in a
ribbon
[Music]
I
don't know
[Music]
what was that
so anyway
[Music]
um
I want something with my friends like I
was like you know I was I was talking to
my friends like I uh remember Remini
wouldn't it be nice to go there since
like we couldn't meet on my birthday I
hope or like weekends meet on my
birthday let's let's uh hang out uh
there and Lincoln you know see it as a
mix of vacation and Convention
and also uh
uh birthday a birthday party [\h__\h]
house
I can run through really okay
uh but then a [\h__\h] ton of them will
attack me now
okay we'll see what does happen when I
just run through is that a stupid thing
to do
Maybe
no no no no
I mean
oh some of them exploded but not all of
them
and I have control over the situation
okay it didn't explode them either
we could
so my friends were like yeah it sounds
like a good idea and then I quickly
really quickly because I was so
motivated I booked oh
I booked the flight at the hotel like
super fast you know
yeah yeah yeah
because I Googled the mini
Comics whatever and then it gave me
these days you know from this last
weekend
and
and yeah I thought like okay cool
let's go it's perfect
yeah
my friend said oh so they have time so
let's go I booked it go left for memory
oh yeah
here
[\h__\h] can I go back
I can't go back did I miss it
oh wait maybe here maybe you did mean
here
oh
nice timing nice timing
[Music]
thank you for telling me
dangerous
this substance grows in all places where
there are jerks
what is it made out of it seems to pulse
as though alive
do you think we're inside a giant
organism
and that's what it feels like that's why
I keep on saying it looks like the
inside of a human it's frame chilling
Hawaiian name
[Music]
okay
thanks thanks thanks
so I booked it and then my friends uh
pretty soon after also booked their
flights and hotels
and
it's nice because you know it's a short
flight really short flight and cheap
flight with like a
um Budget Airline
normally
normally my friends usually don't fly to
conventions me neither though in the
past like we were just uh
[Music]
usually in like bus or a train or going
by car yeah but flying usually
wasn't something we would do
excellent and then
[Music]
realized that there's apparently
now too Remini Comics conventions
uh
uh very interesting
[Music]
but not not really two
um you would think it's two because like
originally there was only one but then
like apparently the organizers had a
fight or something
and they split into two different
organizations
uh the problem is that like
they made it like one week after the
other like one week before was one of a
mini and this week was the other Remini
Comics convention uh run tickets no no
there were no tickets to begin with like
convention tickets but yeah
so if I look at not so bad probably I
mean
there's gonna be people right still
still gonna be a convention right but it
turns out that the one that we chose
even though it's like the first date
that came up when you Google it is kind
one oh there's a memory there
okay I gotta go to the other side
it's kind of the wrong one because
apparently that one didn't even like
manage to get like permission from the
city and all that to hold it at the date
and like they don't have they didn't
have any guests like performance or
whatever
nothing nothing
they just had like one post on Instagram
or so announcing that the tap oh no no
no no no no no no no that is happening
oh God
okay
and that's it but like if you're not the
problem is if you don't speak Italian
then it's kind of something that you
would not really uh up like notice
because like in the in the comments of
that Instagram announcement apparently
they were like Italian like convention
visitors discussing how that's not the
real or early mini
convention and yeah that like it's all
[\h__\h] up and all that but I couldn't
know wait where was the memory I thought
did I see it wrong
I thought I saw a memory here
it looked uh it was I think it was just
those screens over there
okay I was wrong
okay open door lock
there's no memory yeah and as as an
English-speaking person
oh the eyes are looking at me did they
just were they always open
do I have to open uh go there too I
think so
uh-oh why is the music like this okay I
see I see I see
he wants me to hurry up don't you
[Music]
I'm hurrying I'm hurrying
okay well I'm trying to run but then
okay you coming over
I thought so
okay opening this one up too okay
it's like those satisfying people
popping me just eat a disgusting
I don't find those that satisfying I
don't like to watch them I like if it's
only it's only satisfying if I paint my
own Popple like pop on my own pip what
people poopity pop you know what I mean
but watching others do it no thank you
[Music]
yeah it's gross it's gross shut up it's
not like you have never pimped your own
Papa before
foreign
[Music]
anyone
p.m no
oh
um there's one even bigger one
no piano
that face expression even though it's
not a face expression says everything hi
hi nice to meet you
oh no oh poor kitty candy
dude I need you I need you
[Applause]
yeah help me out here
I'm gonna die
it never went that long before I feel
like
[Music]
can't use it right now
great you destroyed it
you have to even it out
[Music]
oh yeah
cutscene got rid of your upgrade [\h__\h]
hell mate
give it back
can I not run I'm not running am I
wait wait how do you what no I'm running
that's running wasn't that fast on the
floor
I feel like that was faster before all
right now I'm totally fine
I'm not getting attacked at all
I I I
uh
am I taking the right path and it seems
so
[Music]
for this now
oh oh there's a timer oh so if you run
around too much then the door will close
before you reach it
pretty good for a second try
wake up
oh there you go hi
hi you good now
you were dead in the worst possible
moments
it was dark I was alone I felt like I
was back in the network but you saved me
thank you friend drawing that much power
was rough on my core but the flexors
completely destroyed
gots it
yeah
I gave you the control once and you
destroyed completely
oh my God
what friend
why'd you say friend
can we fix it
pack ventilation system at least
something you can still do
uh the robot said thanks friend okay wow
that's a stretch guys that's quite the
stretch on it
oh you only hacked one okay
yeah okay back to my story
um uh so yeah we found out that we kind
of chose the the wrong convention that
actually nobody went to
the one the week before
you know all the usual Italian
convention visitors
went to it seems
all the people all the cool peeps but
you know I was like still trying to be
positive and like oh I'm sure I'm sure
there will be people there right like
some people will go there and I'm sure
we're not the only ones who made the
mistake right and
I'm not sure that will be others
ah well Well turns out that like on the
uh like wait it's a convention that goes
from Thursday to Sunday
and um
we arrived on Thursday uh kind of late
so we couldn't even have seen anything
but I think we saw like a few like maybe
five five cosplayers or so
uh in the late evening and then on
Friday I think we saw like maybe seven
at maximum
and yeah it was only only for brief
moments at the very end of the day
because yeah it's usually an evening
convention so that's that and then on on
Saturday it was
it was like five
and then on Sunday none
so
that's that
um
the one
no one there pretty much
but you know before I went there I
didn't I didn't quite know yet I thought
you know I'm sure I'm sure there'll be
some people there I'm sure it'll be like
a convention somehow I'm sure it would
be worth the experience
um
and the thing is like you know
uh when we found out about that it was
it was like I think like maybe a week or
so before the flight
and I was like okay I guess I could I
could probably
still
um cancel it I would lose some money on
the flight but the hotel I could still
cancel what about you guys is what I
asked my friends but they were all like
nah like we're gonna lose a lot of money
if we do that like we can't cancel our
[\h__\h] anymore
um
and they were like I was like hey well
you know I'm actually currently in a
very stressful time anyway so I
in terms of how busy I am I would
actually be better off not going
especially if it's if it's not a
convention in the end anyway
um
but how would you feel if I wouldn't go
and then my friends were like yeah we
would be very sad and we do think that
you being there would be like a big plus
for us and like basically you're the
reason why we wanted to
eat like we wanted to go there anyway
so I kind of felt bad you know I didn't
want to leave them hanging at a
convention that's not a convention
when I'm kind of the one that started
bringing it up and all that
um yeah I I I didn't want them to be
like alone there
um
yeah and and maybe in some way I'm the
glue that sticks us together
but that's how you say it right
kind of no it's not social pressure you
know I also felt happy hearing that that
they feel like I
um what was the word
um
I am
enhance the experience yeah they said so
yeah so I was like okay I guess I'll go
and even though I'm super busy it would
be nice to take my mind off of some
things anyway I guess so yeah but then
you know I was also like really worried
about
you know not streaming and all that I
felt bad about that too so I was I
wasn't quite the conundrum yeah
so that's that for now let's continue
with the story and then I'll continue
with my tangent oh
Julio
and then a tarantula from the sewers we
haven't seen one of you in ages
are you the one who contacted us earlier
the little Outsider yes
it has been expecting you
he's meditating at the top of our
village cool
oh my God this is so cool this place
it's like a tree house but it's not
really a tree house but also it reminds
me again of near
ants Village
are we the ants
oh nice train
oh cool wow it will be a whole nother
Village to explore
are there side quests too
cool
yeah it reminds me of that one round
play said I really had troubles getting
around on and
you know what I mean where the guy with
the
um
I don't know there were like several
of that
um
yeah yeah this machine the scientist I
assisted used one of these
he was sick this was his last help he
walked into the machine but I wasn't
with him he was alone what was he doing
he uploaded himself into the computer
and then everything was different
whoa
what the upload something went wrong he
was stuck for hundreds of years
until a little cat appeared
mind explosion
was it it was me yeah
yourself until like this thing oh
I was human oh
foreign
I I need a moment yeah okay
take your time think about it
that was an important memory
oh oh sorry my sorry
seems like I have a problem with buckets
now
hello
I'm sorry I
oh okay I don't feel like talking okay
you don't want to translate for me now
okay okay okay okay
so I'm not allowed to talk to NPCs now
but this one looks so funny
damn it we'll talk to them later I guess
I guess it forces me to go straight to
the one dude it's about as well
but it's so interesting I wanna
see everything now what meow
is that him he's not meditating
what else have I forgotten
um
I must have had Parents friends what
happened to everyone
um
I want to open the city what is there
every even anyone left to say it
uh
um
it probably not
and
is it gonna be depressing ending I mean
how do I get up
ah from here
oh
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
is this a cult
[Music]
what is this
what the [\h__\h]
what
the [\h__\h]
that is
that is a cult
I mean
don't you know not to interrupt the
fella during his Transcendental
Meditation
ah it's still you wear with Mama when we
received that call earlier I'm glad to
meet you at last little outsider
so you're already familiar with us
Outsiders I'm still the memory brings me
peace Momo stayed in the slums I heard
you helped find duck and Clementine
she's in Midtown now if you still want
to see the outside she's the one who can
get you there apparently she had some
kind of plan to leave the city here take
this I wrote her address
on the back of this picture
Clementine's picture
oh
okay wait wait wasn't she saying uh
there on the bottom
to Richmond Town climbed up by a little
village it should be easy for dexterous
one like you
if you manage to reach the outside you
will be very first the very first I'd
wish you good luck but you don't need it
I Believe In You cats are gonna save the
world holy [\h__\h] there's a telescope
picture on the TVs I'm sorry for
shutting down earlier I'm feeling
probably the last in the world now look
what's left of me
I'm not sure if I would still call you
human but I don't know
someone just come back to me how much
have I forgotten
maybe if we find Clementine we can
restore my memories and get you back
home at the same time we can go back
down and find out more from the
companions or head onward to Midtown or
no we'll find out everything we'll talk
to everybody maybe we'll get some more
memories on the way
let me go
is this the way to go all the way up
[Music]
or is there something
interesting there to check out first
I like the soundtrack here too
and I guess I'll tell you a little bit
more about my story
my weekend story so we decided to go
there
after all because I felt bad and um
yeah I I couldn't make up my mind either
so I could basically let my friends
choose for me
but you know at that point I still had
hope that it could still be a little bit
like a convention
yeah oh hello
one second this food is actually
horrible
but it's the only thing around
I love your hat
great yeah I should try a hat like that
I'll have to unscrew my front casing if
I keep eating this trash
what do you mean what do you make him is
this like a direct insult to you
people call me the tin Chef I specialize
in upcycling leftovers
special
j45 with my secret ingredient what is
what is that secret ingredient I feel
like that's what [\h__\h] up everything
how about stop putting that secret
ingredient and then just cook something
properly
instead of poisoning everybody
gonna destroyed this
yeah that's my aggression out yeah
[Music]
I'm an educate it's not a phase mom
and you catch
okay
so
where was I
oh yeah oh yeah so on the first day uh I
left
and uh actually okay we all took the
same flight so that was also kind of
cool I never I never took a flight
before with like all my friends
that was kind of fun
I mean we didn't sit next to each other
but still was fun
and I'm meeting up at the airport going
for a security check together like for
example
like I had I realized oopsie oopsie
Doodles I had a scissor in my way
in my um my hand luggage thingy in my
bag and then I was like okay I hope they
don't notice because I like the scissor
I don't want to get rid of it and then I
went through with no problem and then
right after me uh one of my friends goes
through
and I also had a scissor
and they did stop my friend
like the scissor they took the sizzle
away I was like
I still have my scissor I don't know why
I got to keep my scissor
yeah
lucky me
so yeah we went for a security check
together and then we went to the plane
and we you know checked checked if our
bags are small enough to
fit into the airplane if all is good
because it's a Budget Airline so they're
really strict about that
um
but
flight was nice one one thing that
pissed me off
it is
I mean
some of you guys might not be able to
relate but
airplane lands okay
and everybody he [\h__\h] collapse even
though the landing was first of all not
even small second of all it was just a
short one-hour flight what is there to
clap about huh The Landing wasn't even
good and everybody's like
clap clap clap clap clap and I'm like
guys guys it's so embarrassing why are
you clapping and then
my friends were actually also clapping
very disappointed in them and then after
a while uh like you know you drive
around the airport a little bit uh with
the airplane and then it stopped
somewhere and then they clapped again
they clapped again why did they need to
clap a second time
oh no wait they collapsed after we
stopped and the dude made an
announcement the the flight attendant
made an announcement and then they
clapped again and then he was like oh
thank you
that took me too long yeah it was it was
shy and happy and good for him but there
was nothing in particular to clap about
good job for landing near the plane and
not killing us I guess but I don't know
I don't think they needed to clap not at
least not twice okay
yeah I mean if it's a long distance
flight that had turbulences and still
got us safely on the ground
behind clapping maybe because yeah that
was a long flight and I almost died and
used a little good job so thank you for
keeping me alive but it was just a short
[\h__\h] flight why why how can they be
Americans do you guys like clapping uh
American flights a lot
I don't think I
I don't think I remember people clapping
there when I arrived in
America and even when I left when they
arrived again no no
I do have that like it happens sometimes
but I don't know what what kind of
people have to be in the plane for that
to happen because only a sometimes thing
anyway let's talk to them
oh there it has been so long since we
had a visitor we'll accept those damn
zerks of course imagine if we could
harness their power having them run in a
wheel or something ah it's a trace of
potential
you're like hamsters and maybe make
electricity through that
[Applause]
when I grew up I wanted to be great like
the aunt Clementine right Clementine
Clementine
old people
really
I think if you clap on a flight in the
UK they would think you're a loon
there's really another herd of people
clapping the plane really I've had it
happen several times but like
I don't know I don't know I I have yet
to discover a pattern like oh it happens
in this continent or this country
celebrating that you don't live for the
flight yeah but it's not
installers or anything except for the
landing which was kind of like what the
[\h__\h] could have gone smoother
I wanted to explore like she did but the
grown-ups for Betas to leave and Village
yeah you should not leave at the moment
unless you have platforming skills like
Me Maybe practice with you know playing
Super Mario 64. how about that
the electric jerk everywhere
okay he's sleeping he probably will wake
up at some point
if it was anything like the other
Village oh
remember
um
foreign
was made up from scratch how impressive
I remember it happening when I was in
the network
who won exactly but at one time all the
communication started to switch to these
symbols
oh I was stuck in a computer alone for a
long time so I translated every symbol
and word one by one until I was able to
understand everything none of them out
and I know their language I'm curious to
hear all they have to say
they made up a whole new language
[Music]
wasn't always his language in this world
oh wait are you
what
9536 games one to six
don't tell anybody I'm actually
programmed to win at this game
well what about the six games you lost
is that like some glitch in The Matrix
statistically I should have won at least
eight times
really
I should tell him that he's Pro What if
I
you win hey you should be because at
least you can't lose anymore
sorry
oh they're picking them up they're
picking them up
I'll come back to destroy it again
because what you're doing guys is
absolutely useless you're wasting your
lifetime
what the hell
let's talk to you first
May is I love the music right now holy
[\h__\h]
amazing
deconstructed this period so she says
I'm sure she'll become a great artist
if only she could practice elsewhere
expecting on you
on your bed is that you
me
yeah there are more than 900 shades of
white paint
well I guess so yeah I mean yeah I guess
there are a lot of but I didn't think
there would be 900.
don't tell anyone but I'm creating my
own shade of paint
okay good luck with that I'm coming at
garbage Brown
yeah that already exists I think
look at your pants
anyway
I thought you were ah I guess not much
I don't love the smell of fresh paint it
reminds me of always you can't smell
anything how sad
oh no no there's Sun I need to I need to
program a nose into their face
can somebody do that
maybe I asked Kobo she knows how to
program some stuff like code she knows
how to code right like some stuff at
least
maybe she can make her a nose
okay where is uh Clementine Clementine
[Music]
everybody I walked past
right I talked to them
is that uh can I go down
meow
ah no wait that's just there again okay
side quest is on the top floor oh okay
let's try to go to the top corn
wait what about the tree oh wow
okay now take purple blend oh that's
probably for a side quests
right
maybe maybe to create some paint color
I don't know or to impress some girl or
to make that that robot uh try to smell
the flower I don't know
could be any of these things that's up
to you oh the soothing sound of the
trash falling shimmering waterfalls no
dangers it's a blissful place to work on
my poetry here listen
the mighty concrete shielding me in its
womb shall you also be my tune
you think it's too solemn
[Music]
um
my kfp chickens can make better poems
than you
and they have
I guess I guess you guys have more of a
brain than they do
robots have a brain I guess not
but they could be programmed
to make poems did I talk to this dude
yeah
if they're programmed to do that then
that's just cheating and that's not fair
I should talk to no
when you talk to him how did I get up so
high before
nobody time
here
we go
yeah the soul of a champion
you know timkins go for a lot of [\h__\h] in
their lap times
so they have so much to share so much to
give
in poems
um this I'm just going down right
and now if you guys are talked
how do I get even higher
[Music]
there we go
but this one I can't use
this one I can use
hey hello oh
I don't want that flower
love your hats too oh my God hello buddy
how are you did you know that on
Clementine taught us how to grow special
plants that can live with us online
oh tell me about it because
I need some of those plants
am I am my apartment I have a huge
collection of them do you want to see
it's still missing some colors are you
missing purple
yeah you're missing purple and yellow
and red okay only someone small and
agile could get them for me here you get
this one first
I heard it's a real plant thank you are
you gonna oh wait it was already added
that thing that purple thing there
find another one please please uh okay
wait I only saw the purple one I wonder
where the others are
maybe up really high
I guess that's a side quest let's try to
take care of it show me
yellow behind the bar ah okay
thanks for the help I didn't ask about
it just yet
I feel like I'm going too high yeah I'm
leaving the I thought so I thought I was
wondering like at what point am I
leaving the village
that is the point
s okay
thank you
this is such a lovely cat's tree in the
end it's a cat's world so
oh no now I'm the culprit
sorry that was totally not me but what I
was saying is it's a cat world and
therefore this is not somebody's
building not somebody's Village it's a
cat tree a huge catch right for me to
have fun in I didn't talk to you did I
can I talk to you
I'm born on Clementine you lose the
whole class is here we learned a lot of
cool stuff
I can teach you something
um
I'm gonna try to teach you something
what do you want to learn what are you
interested in
I thought I can teach you that this is a
color that's called Purple and this is
kiwaba green because
it's that beautiful green that I have in
my outfits in my hair as well
right
you're going to see on Clementine can
you tell me that everyone misses her
yeah but I will I will monopolize her
and she'll belong to me so she's not
coming back don't get your hopes up
she's gonna be mad
no she doesn't give a [\h__\h] okay
uh behind the bar bar was like below
close by
[Music]
um
lets me down no let me down
that was uh you
uh keep an eye out for flowers flowers
I saw a clip of cayenne talking with in
like a Minecraft collab thingy
where yeah she was talking and sounding
like crony
the holy [\h__\h] she really does like I
guess like I never realized
maybe she only sounds like her sometimes
but In that clip she sounded like her
the whole time
never noticed right
now
um
we should we need a collab of Canada and
crony now
maybe I should take the bucket
wait where's the flower
maybe I can't get it yet
maybe behind as in like literally behind
on the other side ah no wait ah
okay what was the other color I'm
missing
yeah no that was like around the middle
maybe the next color is at the very
bottom
thank you
red
[Music]
look I saw red flowers somewhere
that's where the purple ones were
[Music]
um
are they playing the takes two together
oh
I didn't realize oh
[Music]
I'm coming
wait how do I get over there
what
um
oh this way what the [\h__\h] it yeah
yay fun maybe there's some some dead
fish here that I can eat some rotten
fish for this kitty cats
now
just just normal trash okay
tell me when you find
or some salmon
all right we got all the flowers
uh any salmon yet
I may call this junk me I call them
Treasures Jenkins
I was about many cycles ago but I've
repurposed myself into a treasure hunter
bellbot like a bell boy like in a hotel
I guess so don't be fooled by the sound
of it it can be hard to hard and
gruesome just like this arm I just
thought
poor fellow may he rest in peace I like
that
it's funny
that is funny let me take a throat candy
modeling
[Music]
come on
rest in peace
okay
okay let's go to the side Place lady
again
The Flower Lady
and bring her some
flowers
[Music]
not flowers
totally
sounding like crony now 100
uh buckets
[Music]
is
squeeze
good
good good
you're welcome you're welcome for this
beautiful image of two beans oh
your pink they're pink
you guys must be so jealous about the
fact that I
have blanket perms
to touch my cat's toe beans anytime I
want
they're used to it because I raised them
to accept their fate
Tennessee
[Music]
foreign
holding each other's hands or pause
sometimes
um
it's so sweet
yeah anyway let me tell you a bit more
about Italy where was I
um
let me check my notes I took notes again
of course
uh uh Francis are taken away
one thing about the flag one more thing
about the flight
you know we flew with Ryanair I don't
know if you know and if you're from
Europe then you probably know it the
thing is with Ryanair it's a Budget
Airline and it likes to like
um get as much money out of you as
possible pop pause
cat possible yeah you know what I'm
saying
um yeah they like to take your money
so uh like you can get priority
um if you I don't know what was it
because I didn't do it like my friends
so I didn't have priority they had
priority
because they had a hand luggage
and I didn't have priority I guess I
could have booked it additionally but I
didn't need it I was like whatever I'll
need it
so they had priority
but hey
when it came to like boarding the plane
you know they they uh lined up pretty
early you know they were right in the
front right in the front
and then they they started boarding and
I was just chilling you know I was like
oh I'm not gonna I'm no priority anyway
it's gonna take a while until I'm in so
I'm just gonna hang here I'm just gonna
chillax and watch some more uh shows on
my tablet it's gonna take my time this
time normally actually I am the type of
person who lines up really fast
um yeah I'm one of those [\h__\h]
uh but
yeah this time I was like I don't care I
don't care everybody gets in the plane
eventually so [\h__\h] it no need to stress
myself out
and then after like 20 minutes or so
I finally
make my way
like I line up and try to get into the
plane
and so the thing is like they they
bought they were gonna board like from
the front of the plane and I was gonna
board from the back
and then
I answered the plane
so much later than them but I got to my
seat
earlier than them
and I find that very ironic because I
did not have priority
and in the end
of them and I even gave them a head
start
yeah it's because like they all like
like even after you know you go through
you you show your ticket one last time
and then you go through this kind of
tube thingy but then you know it gets
crowded and people take time to
like sometimes they let you in before
they even actually let people in so they
just like let people into into the tube
first but then still make you waiting
right in front of the door of the plane
I guess that that maybe that was what
happened first and that's why there like
a line was built inside the tube
and they had to just stand and wait a
bit more but I waited and waited and
waited and waited and I had to board by
going
um outside like I went down the stairs
to go on the ground like they went for
the tube but I went on the ground into
the back of the plane and then I went up
the stairs and I was in the plane and
then I sat down before else
yay
yeah yeah yeah this this trip was just
Kiana one up being her friend how do you
know this
no this plane ride
but I felt pretty Superior with my life
choices at that moment
um
[Laughter]
smug joke
like I've said if only someone could
snatch a yellow plant I got I got
yourself
yellow
and
red ah they planted immediately nice
where's the yellow one where'd you put
the yellow one
I can't see the yellow one I only see
purple and
I see purple oh there oh there's a
yellow one on the right side okay oh wow
so pretty
pretty cute
you found them all thank you so much
here is where you want to take my badge
badge
oh oh it's cute
uh what am I supposed to do with this
so good with it well take care now see
ya friend
uh okay what who wants this badge
what I need this bachelor
not you
definitely on you hmm
who wants this badge
on the backpack wait am I just done with
this uh side quest now
oh it was a pretty short one I thought
it would be like a long one like the the
one in the other Village
so am I supposed to just go to the main
quest now
I I guess so
Tyler question already
yeah I saw it as I was on the right side
that's what the other badge went to
um
next one much more complicated
I can go up now okay
yes I did get the memory I did
[Music]
um
is it this way
I thought we would go up there okay
Clementine
you in here
why are you in such a Dark Lonely place
what here
[Music]
how far am I into the game I feel like
I've been um going slow today
because of the tangents sometimes they
make me stop
bulk
very close 75 that doesn't sound so
close but okay 75 70 to 80. okay
cool old Subway oh can we like make it
usable
look this is the subway station I had
completely forgotten this kind of
Transportation existed yeah me too
you could write to anywhere in the city
people used to take it to go to work I
used to take to I used to take it too
every morning after saying goodbye to my
family at home
ah don't be sad I remember I was doing
this for them but they're gone now
it was so long ago
maybe not gone maybe maybe there's still
hope I don't know maybe they uploaded
their minds too maybe you uploaded their
minds onto something
they wanted to see the outside but does
that even matter anymore
no man's sad life
what happened to them what happened to
everyone
don't worry it won't I mean my quest is
to fight my other kitty cats but I guess
I'll I'll help you find your your family
too
anyway we're near Midtown now let's find
this Clementine
we have a picture of her we can show it
to some of the companions around her
here maybe they'll point us around here
you don't mean in the village
huh
around here
there's no companions here
does she mean in the village why didn't
you tell me earlier
oh wait there's only three stops
yeah
wait and we are in the upper town ah
exit is the control room
speed Speedline service line
oh it's glitching
what does that say in the bottom do not
hesitate to ask for any kind of
information to the machines named helper
they're they their art was so bright
they they are here to end you stay in
the world city 99 for any other specific
inquiries please contact to this
customer service at zero zero zero four
six five seven eight five nine nine zero
zero one nine eight seven does that lead
to anywhere
oh
nice
I'll I'll take this path because I'm
fancy
oh
oh memory
are you Clement hi
nah
remember nice place you got there I
liked it
comfy there's so many books here
the Turing test Legacy the ethics of
artificial intelligence
now some of these did I have a library
you have a library I don't know you
maybe just went to a library
I remember nothing was quite like the
smell of books and the turn of the page
a bookworm huh
actually I find it funny in German we
also say Bookworm like directly
translated
oh
I think we do
now that I say it out loud it feels
weird it was a feeling almost like
Comfort Comfort comfort
a book was like spending time with
someone
uh
[Music]
thank you love books a little bit too
much because then that seems like a very
lonely statement I don't know okay maybe
not I don't know I feel like
um
like when you read a book you like dive
into another world and all that but I
feel like that goes a little bit too far
I don't know I never felt that way about
the book before
books better than people
no
V2 was better than people maybe
anime Better Than People Maybe
books
okay okay maybe
yeah maybe it's like a point of view
thing yeah the way I I say like although
I'm not even that much into anime
anymore either I wouldn't personally say
anime is better than people
bookworms triggered oh no yeah I I can
see it though I guess it's a subjective
topic
okay books
what is this what are you playing
play something
play the Boogie
I'm gonna be jam is too loud for me to
listen properly but wait it's just
pictures again
everybody wants to go to the same ocean
same vacation destination
oh
okay
I know it's such a happy feeling I'm
always so happy when likes movie
um does this
to like visitors that I have at home
because they get like really happy and
I'm like oh yeah oh yeah good job
smoothie
good job make them feel loved and happy
and warm and fuzzy Make Them Fall in
Love with You ghost movie
this movie is so friendly to strangers
hello talk to me oh the dog
the dog wow woof
doesn't talk to me okay what a waste of
time rubbing on to you
smell like me now you're gonna think of
me every day you'll never forget me oh
wait I was supposed to show you the
picture
now
yeah yeah yeah
really okay
he still doesn't talk to me
okay
oh wow there's still other people here
hi can I talk to you no
that's what you get for ignoring me
yeah
look down there's small people too yeah
they deserve attention too
[\h__\h] tall people
they never looked down
I already told you five times Josh you
can't run around like that is dangerous
and it's the first time I've seen this
kind of rubber you look so fluffy
eyes the girl that's playing on this
wanted screen right it wanted
a bad way or in a good way are they
looking for her to rescue her she's
asking somebody else I'm too busy if
you're scared to know anything yes have
you been running around it's so
dangerous you need to be careful listen
to your daddy
nickel Corporation
enjoy the world's safest city
there's literally no no safe place in
the whole earth
are you growing up
are you about to throw up
or are you oh it's a police car
oh where I thought you were throwing up
and you were like mentally supporting
him to be like yeah it's okay it's okay
buddy you drank too much alcohol it's
all good you're gonna be okay just let
it all out and then and then you'll feel
much better I'm behind you I'm I'm gonna
support you
okay that was not it
please State your identity
cooperate or we will have to transfer
you to jail and reboot you
there's like this is the first time we
see police acting around
what
what did you do please leave me alone
I'm not the one you're looking for are
you looking for The Wanted girl huh
I'm sure she's hiding in the residence
the police guy why are they looking for
her in the village they were like
Network there were no like like I don't
know it didn't seem like she was a bad
person or did anything bad or you know
oh sorry I I thought I was gonna rub
against you like
can I talk to you
hi vladi
it's tomorrow if I replace my arm with
another robotic arm and then the next
day my other arm too
and then my body and so on until I've
replaced all my parts and upgraded my
software will I be the same robot you're
talking to now
I know but you know this robot
oh hey what are you showing me right now
a bunch of people I don't know my guess
is that they probably live in the
massive house building products
you do know don't you
do what you want with that massive
building
further what down
okay okay
let me check out your Play Store whoops
whoops sorry I didn't want nothing
totally didn't want to throw that over
I'm sorry
nice computer there
kind of a boomer computer but okay
oh look at that jacket look at the drip
yeah
this Merchant crook sold me a faulty
battery the other day now he just
pretends not to hear me every time I
tried to confront him
are you Karen if it wasn't for the
Sentinels on patrol he'd end up a spare
parts oh
stinking on the Flies are surrounding
you
[Music]
found the Karen
he's like always he's out of battery
[Laughter]
but even if you wanted to help he
couldn't
a cold two four five eight but it's the
other way around probably eight five
four two to turn him back on
eight five four two remember that guys
oh
uh eight five four two
eight five four two
hey guys
a badge oh we got a new
that's it
okay I have a new badge I thought this
would be maybe something side questish
never mind
well I want to help him though I want to
charge him
I guess I can't
okay
yeah it would be cool to can to like
um charge him and then resolve the whole
issue
I guess we're not doing that
okay wow there's there's so much going
on I didn't expect like there to be two
more villages
there's so much to explore again
Monty how is that that feels like I
still have like 50 of the game but
you guys say I'm already so close to the
end but I've just reached another huge
[\h__\h] City and this one this one just
looks so much more like you know look at
like a city that actually used to like
be lived in before and I mean I guess I
still live in it about
go the bouncer
clubs close get lost
are you also wearing that jacket it's so
in fashion
trip
uh in a trip I'll make him trip with the
[\h__\h]
doesn't trip I guess whoa what
what this place is so sci-fi
foreign
I saw
[Music]
it on Twitter I think I was wondering
where you can do that and how I missed
out on that
I I wish my cats would do that I will
tell you my cats are [\h__\h] angels and
they sleep next to me every night but
they don't sleep on top of me I only did
it when they were babies
I wish they would do this now
um
no God came out good at it
foreign
[Music]
what are you selling some more parts
even if this guy bums me out he's my
only customer try not to scare him away
please
uh I I could be I could be your second
customer
be nice to me too maybe
[Music]
whose sorts you don't it's a Japanese
Sam I used to own a bar it was the
coziest place around here until I took a
screwdriver in the knee and it's closed
now oh [\h__\h]
how did that happen
who did that to you you did it to
yourself
[Music]
I love that
I love it
you've been in the city below I have a
friend girl what are you free I haven't
seen him in ages
Albert Fifi did we meet the Fifi I don't
remember seeing a fifi
okay no more no more vending machine
games
surgery
yeah
oh they did is that like a hospital they
did surgery on robots here
yeah
like an oil change
are there rooftops here too can I get on
the top
looks like I could
back from Doctor it says
I talked to you right yeah yeah okay
Michael makes
spam
thank you very much for the stick on the
pinky
I didn't talk to you
we work all day long to gather the waste
and send it downstairs where they're
recycling repurpose it
oh
it's picking up downstairs it has been a
while since we had news from them
well I'm I'm bringing the news I'm the
news bringer now cool picture that one
hey is that an address on the back
first symbol is the street and then
there is a floor in the door number
super pretty easy
what what there was an address on there
on this time
good that we didn't show it to the
police
Clementine troublemaker
outside of rebellious please report to
any Sidekicks no I will not no I will
not
I just want to talk to everybody
sorry you can't play over here the
nickel Club Factory is no place for a
little fuzz ball like you
I think he likes me just the fact that
he calls me a fuzzball feels like he
thinks I'm cute axes is restricted but
only for a little while if you can wait
a few years we'll open it right back up
okay
a few years in cat life
[Music]
I don't know if I can wait so long
that's like my whole life man
[Music]
I'm in the box
and we're getting the moon the bugs
cat in the Box
just about no it's not just the Box not
to a cat it's way more than just the
books it could be anything it could be a
house it could be a car it could be a
microwave it could be so many things but
now now it's my Heidi Place my bed cozy
um I love boxes ah it feels so good that
cardboard feeling and now I'm so hidden
that nobody could possibly see me nobody
sees me and that nickel logo on it
totally doesn't give away what's inside
either
[Music]
you I am in a secret box
I'm in the secret box
nobody will ever know
nobody will ever open this box
but secretly I'm hoping for someone to
open this box
so I can go back
[Music]
fun I love bugs
amazing what do you want
I don't know I guess I'll show you this
even though I already kind of know where
she is but yeah go away huh
are you a friend oil
or an enemy
but anime
my enemy
[Music]
I want to meet my enemy
Elementary
[Music]
I don't know the song very well in case
you haven't noticed
okay well I want to try finding
Clementine commentine now
what about here
oh
what's that what's that
due to organic life hazards please keep
out of this area but that's why
Clementine is no
commenting sometime
everybody wants to be my enemy
my
Yahoo
boys
[Music]
my whole
my
hair
why are you
oh my
my
heart okay I wanna know where to go
who is you
bonobot do you hear that down below that
app that flow are you rapping the city
haunts me it taunts me you're sick rap
sick flow you got there oh Clementine I
used to hang out with her but she wanted
to leave
she was a breeze and then she flew she's
a wanted person now and too heavy for me
hear that that flow
say cramps
what you don't like it I'm sure you like
it why you look sad you have looks
literally a cat waving at me next to you
telling me you don't like cats
[\h__\h] everybody likes cats everybody
loves cats even if they say they're a
dog person in reality it really
they had a cat
okay
Bang
that's right 70 Bang
bang okay we're gonna make our way to
Clementine Clementine
like a big building they said wait
there's so I didn't check out this place
yet can I get some sick fashion
that's the tiniest top in Midtown but
the shopkeeper is pretty grumpy
okay
whoa
whoa what if gets us sandals
oh are you dressing up you should close
the curtain
I can Sail
insert item
I don't have anything
you can play like a sick mixtape here
if anyone would ever make a mixtape for
me
I didn't even talk to the shopkeeper now
oh well
should I have talked to the shopkeeper
but now I feel like
I'm I'm on a better path
um
I can go on the roof now
not really okay
wait not really as in I shouldn't I
don't need to talk to the shopkeeper or
not really as and I'm not on a better
path
because I feel like um
I'm getting somewhere
[Music]
you're rapping candy strong during the
off collab was pretty fire yeah
that was the first time that I like
tried it in a long time though could
have done better okay this is a dead end
dad and
oh nice
could have done better definitely yeah
if I had some more practice
was a good start though do I need to go
down again
still fire thanks
Cali praised me
Rap God Kelly praised me for my rapping
she must be intimidated puppy
[Laughter]
she must be scared that I'll take over a
rap Queen title
she's playing it cool but in reality
she's trembling In Fear
And I'm just out of Mercy
I see I'm not taking that Crown let me
tell you that
I totally could steal that clown that
clown crown
where where are the clowns clowns are
scary
okay I don't know where to go help me
help me chat
a cat can read an address like there's
no way
I've been on here anyway
you can polka isn't scary yeah okay
that's true polka's [\h__\h] cute she's
amazing
oh
follow the street which one
open up hey I'm off to work see you
later okay honey be conscious of the
Sentinels are quick to make a Rest For
No Good Reason oh
don't worry about me babe I'm good babe
babe
robot says babe
[Music]
the main road okay I guess this was the
main road
I kept on going to a lot of paths
okay I'll just follow follow follow
[Music]
uh what about this way this path
meat
do not proceed further the access to the
outside is fully restricted and the
elevator has been disabled
the series is unsafe do not proceed
further
all right it was right okay
this way
um
this place is huge
isn't it like so cool right now so chill
I think that nothing bad could happen to
us
[Music]
why are you whistling who are you
whistling at this beautiful sexy cat
understandable
do the cat look oh we found another bar
her
so many people to meet sorry guys I have
to talk to everyone
I don't know Tony I like pretty much
everything what
[Music]
um
what will it be today
from you little us
wish I could be 10 years used to work
and explore new hidden places
so small
I already talked to you
his face is so small you have a funny
face do you know that
my favorite drink is oil what's yours
noodles ah what are you drinking what is
that
okay wait let me try it let me take a
step
when you try oh
what is wait
oh come on
it's literally the next the same
pictures next to each other
be more original
it's like
no other place exists is that some lore
today so what
I'm really curious about this
same picture everywhere
they only had money for two photos
ah
is coming
should I give them I can give them some
free photos from my Maldives trip
you
meet
I try on downloading an Aimbot to be the
best at this game but we ended up with a
malware
I'm not sure why but everything seems
odd now
ah your face is upside down you
Australian now
good luck with that a master and every
game never existed but I can't figure
out how this one works I'm not am I not
seeing the whole picture here
I don't know what your problem is you
have like two faces
I guess that's the problem
it's tiny fidget he has a tiny know
mid-scale face I don't know
I guess he's a camera oh
okay
uh now where did I come from
ah okay I think I go this way
hello why is this place so big
he don't know
exploration let's go grab
tape I have to put that in somewhere I
you know the place where I said we still
had to mix it and it saves our hours
don't you know how no not to steal can I
take it anyway I could give you one
but you'll have to do something for Jen
ma Miku said bye and me
huh
what a gen mine Mikko stand by doing in
this game and who are you why do I not
know you
I thought I know everybody who knows
General
the Santa's haven't sell free security
cameras to watch over ah do you want me
to knock them over
ah huh I can do something about that
you you
skirts
we can see you too wait Miko Miku Senpai
actually is wearing something pink
that's so in character right then you're
Gemma go Gemma
yo Gemma you've got Style
a different style than normally but life
is boring this is something else put
cameras in our residence
okay okay I'll help you out and get
those cameras
get those [\h__\h]
what are you
what do you mean you forgot your
character sheet aspect don't wait for
her in this session or are they
preparing for your YouTuber debut
hey you character sheet I'm sorry I
forgot where I put it well let's play
anyway I will go in that cave let's go
why you need your characters ah wait are
they oh is it for like an um ttrpg
session oh yeah yeah yeah okay
go
nobody can see me ah
[Music]
you can't see me can you
I wonder where I went
oh I'm not gonna come out until you find
me
where where you are huh
[Music]
where is
you're worried now it's okay
please
I'm here
I know it was a good idea
again finally
yeah I'm gonna be quiet gotta be quiet
so they don't find me
I'm too good at this game surprise
oh my God there's so many boxes
box the box and they'll never find me
it's a surprise bamboozle
all right let's play again let's play
again sometime
Chad oh no box okay I'm gonna I'm gonna
hold back then we have to destroy the
cameras
how do I reach them I have to go one
more level higher
am I already
how was I 80 percent in
a while ago
that would mean I'm 90 in now
impossible
why don't you exactly I'm a cat I'm a
kitty cat meow meow
a quadrup making cute sounds I like the
concept
yeah it's me it's a mama can't I'm a
kitty cat meow
okay have you never seen a cat before
oh oh oh
wow wow
you have to stop it you have to rip it
out
wait let me I want you to the camera
oh here
wait don't jump on it again
oh one down on two to go
tell it
was there one here
no no not reachable
oh is there one here
yeah
what a vandal no I'm just helping uh
I'm saving lives
I'm letting them live their life freely
again
and there we go
what do you say about that no more
camera camera is no more
what's that noise that hold up
oh my God Michael weeks again thank you
do you like cats
I hope you do
I hope you do where's the third one
where's the third one
behind behind you top of door
ah
noise chat noise okay
thank you
from here to here from here to
here there we go Quest
mission accomplished
everybody in the USA
I'm coming down
can I come down from here
I want to I won't let me okay the stairs
it is
[Music]
a preview for her dance
live concert thingies
I could do that too totally
go let's go
let's go
me go save my skin
sick
sick let's let's I wanna dance with you
I wanna dance with me
I'm a break dancer see I'm a prank
dancer I'm a break dancer yeah yeah wow
I'm gonna get dizzy
sick now where's my thanks
well done I didn't think you could do it
you think you're brand new and then
let's go cassette tab
thanks do that and dudes
oh yeah I wanna bring that to the
cassette player where was it was close
by
it was not that far away uh was it done
in the shop
in here
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah fast
progress
[Music]
he turned it and then he gets
distraction when was that for I saw that
I can take something
[Music]
[\h__\h] what was I supposed to do what am I
supposed to use this time for
uh get the money from the cash register
what
[Music]
it's so loud
I don't know
I don't know the purpose the money
check
[Music]
hahaha
to take you to get the added he like
purposefully wait
long enough
for aha
wait who needs the work jacket did I
talk to someone who needs to work jacket
I maybe maybe our upcoming friend
Clementine needs it
because uh so that she doesn't stand out
when I go somewhere with her I assume
right
there you go I'm so smart
hi
yeah I feel like that's it
okay now it's about [\h__\h] time that we
find Clementine
[Music]
so you guys were like go right here I
think
right and then oh I guess maybe here
so we already went straight
um but we talked to you
[Music]
preschool inspected uh
um
rotate
[Music]
um
okay
yeah
what about this
you say the same stuff
no
oh
I already showed the picture to like a
million people and they said she's in
the big
that's the same sign that is the same
sign
wait and then okay okay so somewhere in
here and then it was like some dots
um
free green dots and five red dots
three Green Dots five ah
there are two and there's one
if you count them together it's three
and there's two and then one
um
[Music]
she's actually doing it yeah I don't
know
Korean one
three three and one
all right before there was two and one
now there's actually free and one
for three and five no friend four is
that three and four ah it's like a
apartment number huh okay that is three
and four we need three and five
friend bye bye I found it
means
so that was like apartment number
[Music]
oh nice place
oh
she's got a chip oh
what a chill place oh can you help me
put Furniture in my apartment I am
a friend no four meow
I thought you were sent Ascent never
mind who are you what do you want
I'll show you a picture of you to tell
you how beautiful you are wait so it's
about the south finally decided to send
someone I guess you're my new recruit
you're not very big how did you even
manage to do it I guess you must be
pretty resourceful yeah hell yeah I am
I've been looking for a way to the
outside ever since I left and Village
but this sentence are always watching
not if you're here you can help follow
me
wait can I turn on the lights of my room
one second
[Music]
wow and let's drink some more water
hydrate
[Music]
only since I see of this game are intro
on this part how why
oh yeah
what the [\h__\h]
okay okay okay
I should do it
why did I not why did I not schedule a
stream where I talk about my trip
I really should have
I really should remember so much to talk
about put on my other streams
foreign
[Music]
for tomorrow
uh
what are my other streams
Korean members gaming else fiction okay
it's not really not really much
space to talk about it
after the Nabi collab
[Music]
wait a second
I guess so
Maybe
[Music]
if I might have time after that one yeah
I might have time after that
um Sims I don't know
I don't know I want to get it all out in
one go you know
[Music]
The Vibes
oh
she's not looking she's not looking I
need to let it out oh
Secret
Gateway
whoa oh my God
it's like a loft oh
wow sick stuff you got there
oh my God that's so chill
I mean
quite like my style I guess but I mean I
would love living in a place like this
anyway
she even got one of those things you
know remember when I said I wanted to
get one of those
those things
I still want one
cool there was nothing else up there
though
whoa
oh hi oh there you are oh oh
Sperrys oh let's go
a gramophone yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Grandma phone
literally
hello
I've been working on a plan to use this
old Subway for a while now I even have
the keys to start what
all we need is an atomic battery to
power it okay that sounds tough
I know nickel Corporation has One
Secured inside the factory I have a
contact who can help us infiltrate them
I don't know his name he's a robot with
a Bombay jacket and a gold chain take
this message to him
okay maybe he will use jacket then
someone small and Swift like you should
have no trouble sneaking inside the
factory one last thing don't hesitate to
ask around for help the city is full of
information yeah I already talked to
like a thousand people
ah
oh yeah okay no no Sentinels all right
all right all right
[Music]
[Applause]
can I sit on your keyboard
yeah yeah how can you work when I'm here
usually people pet me when I'm right in
front of them come in town
I have no heart
you have no soul No Love in Your Body
huh
pet me [\h__\h] pet me
feed me too while you're at it
come on
she's ignoring me I don't know if I want
to help you anymore
you don't respect cats
wow
Coolio
cool stuff
[Music]
I need to get overload
and being a threat
this is an order
instead of the knife it's just my claws
okay where the [\h__\h] how do I get out of
this place
here what's here though
okay
I'm leaving
uh so she's wait is the guy that I'm
looking for in the factory or outside
the bomber jacket guy
wait what about him
do I have a gold jacket
a Golden Ticket a gold chain no
okay I guess we're gonna leave this
place I saw like a couple people of uh
bomber jackets
outside but close okay
um
okay
outside the factory
well then uh if I tell you tell me more
about my Italy trip in an extra stream
perhaps I'm not promising it yet but I
will try
I can tell you something else did you
see
I was announced to be a guest with Bales
and
salt popcorn sounds like popcorn yum yum
yum yum yum yum
yeah it's it takes place in Korea and
Seoul
hey
it's like like you know this timing is
really good because of the cafe going on
and my trip but my trip doesn't overlay
with the convention so I won't actually
be there during it
but yeah I'm I'm excited
and then for crunching world uh Expo
there's also something exciting I've
been told today
that I'm looking forward to
a small surprise
for y'all
not here not here
so the one guy that I just looked at he
did not have a this one does not have a
golden necklace so
it's really exciting I don't I don't
know yet how exciting it is depends on
on the execution uh but
let's see let's see we'll see
we'll see I wish I could check out like
Crunchyroll Expo in person
oh wait there's soap is it it must be on
purpose that so many of them have the
white bumper jacket
it must be on purpose so that I get
confused
did I look at you already I did
damn it
that's two of them
that was him
this one
nah can't even talk to him I mean the
other one
but this one's fighting
the that dude
Brown
Obama leather jacket of the foot I
passed him
okay
wait a bomber what is a bomb attack I
thought that's a bomber chicken
is that a bomber chicken with a bomber
jacket
and go here
okay an army jacket Oh I thought I was
thinking
of white eyes you
that's why you were so weird I thought
you were says it
once you get that
um
my contact Let Me Brave you about the
atomic battery
oh
stealth South Mission
the battery is powering an echo cord
Factory right there but it's hilarious
restricted in heavily guarded they check
every person who enters and turns away
anyone who's not a worker
here's an idea yeah
what do you need uh but at least I
already got
the helmet the jacket where's the helmet
let me explore
um
can I take someone else's comments Maybe
by trading it for something else
let me see there was um wait does it
have
[Music]
why yeah
do you isn't this cat's discrimination
do you think that I can't wear hats
I can perfectly fine wear hats I look
gorgeous in hats
nobody can answer the shop while it's
being restocked and seeing how
incompetent those two are it might be a
while do I have to help them
you're already stunning
[Music]
you
I've been waiting for answers for stupid
to get back and help me restart these
hats the boss is not happy
the guy slacking off at the bar again he
has an okay bar
was
not here I think it was a little bit
further out
a bar
um bar
fight a bar but I didn't go in here
before so I'll talk to you
can I do for you tonight Jeff
oh finally finally someone who respects
me
you got what do you got
how about some carbonara
oh what are you guys doing
what's happening
crowd
you know what my friend how do I sound
like you know you know you know what my
friend no you know what my friend stay
away from the Sentinels I don't know
it's a typo though it should be double I
not double O the their their wishes and
they got my body
their wishes and they got my butts
Crow
he's in for 350 years so be careful I
don't know how to talk like her mouth
kundi
I just walked you the elevator and I got
yellowed by Sentinels for years I have
been told that the surface is
uninhabitable we just accept it as a
fact but why
so many whole life members here what's
up
is this Crunchyroll Expo
let's go
let's go it's was this the bar yeah okay
I'm looking for it
ah just down
what was the name again memo
toning
[Music]
this dude
after this one
wait I forgot the name
just one dude I can't talk to
it's too flat there's just two plants
was our second floor
look
and I like to disturb him
no
I don't know
[Laughter]
you
he was not here before
I like you know I like that they change
things in the game
wake up hello
hello let me just surprise him or
something
by dropping something
I'm trying
what okay how can I wake I'm sure that's
him he was here before you just me
you're telling me that I went to this
room looked at the pictures and did not
notice this guy I'm pretty sure I
noticed him if he was there before
can I jump on him
how is he not waking up
yeah he was not thank you thank you
oh my God I'm gonna
masaka
kill him
so
um that was not me that fell down uh but
that's really oh you wake me up oh you
oh you're awake now wait what's that
Skyrim mean
you're awake now
what the [\h__\h] up all right he's going to
work automatically now oh that's good I
thought I had to tell him go go go go
ah you're finally awake yeah I I did say
that Meme in the Kyle carrot video but
guess what it wasn't my idea cow carrots
who told me to say that
before helping me look cool in front of
the cool kids
by making me say memes that I wouldn't
have thought of myself
how did you know did he tell you did he
rat me out is that the right word
do that
let me be cool in front of them
it's pretty obvious why would why why
you missed you have missed all the
Skyrim references Skyrim references
[Music]
I told you okay
don't rat me out
oh I should have gotten up
that's why they keep on showing me that
I'm happy are you saying I'm heavy
like I keep on showing me that I can get
into the box oh
wait are they gonna keep on like
stapling them
people escape not safe please stop
because it's in German it's shopping
I mean uh you're putting one and one on
top of each other
wait I'm here to buy hats right
master
uh so what's what's the the most popular
model in this season uh sir
uh I would like it in
cat size
what was that sound
oh this is the helmet oh my God I made a
shortcut
noise but that's still the work ahead
thank you
[Music]
that reminded me of the Pink Panther
sound for some reason
was that even a pink panther sound
anyway I got all I needed
this is fun I like this game very much
I really like it
hey I really have to say I really
[\h__\h] like it
like it could be like one of my favorite
games this year
one of my favorite games is yeah
[Music]
I like it
okay
yeah I gotta put it on and don't worry I
got it too
put it on
I can dress down by turning around okay
does that mean you'll play more sci-fi
games I mean it's not why I chose this
game but if it has a cute cat in it then
there's a high chance and I would play
it
they're so great a little snug around
the waistline but I'll do
okay hop in this box I'll sneak you
across the checkpoint yeah
I will gladly get into the box but then
you won't see me and you'll forget where
I am
it's blessing too
are you sure just remember that I'm in
here okay because you won't see me
anymore and then you might be wondering
where I am I'm in here okay I'm in this
box okay
oh he probably already forgot now he's
probably wondering where where is kiwawa
I'm here I'm here
foreign
you know it makes me invisible when I'm
in the box so
oh yeah don't be suspicious just blend
in
[Music]
wait I'm here I'm here
oh I have been approved a proud I am
proud
[Music]
I'm guessing it's not the right now can
I jump up now because he seems to be
distracted or do I wait longer
okay I think they're distracted enough
okay
oh so distracting
hey
[Music]
this is really just just a box
this really
oh my God I only saw that game
because
we played it but
this is literally it
can I move it I wish I could move it I
wish I could move with the Box
[Music]
okay okay okay
come over
I see I say I say fun
more
uh observing okay
[Music]
Mr Box just a cat
oh okay
we'll go back
that's a little bit complicated pattern
but oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] get in the Box get
in the Box
oh that's a box that's the Box
uh
uh when do I oh [\h__\h] okay okay after
that maybe
next box
[Music]
um
I'm doing fine I'm so far I think but
now it's kind of hard to see it
uh wait where do I go from there can I
go up
probably
should
no no okay
I guess I can't go up but they don't
seem to see me I'll be ah
okay Sam this one doesn't move at all
yeah
what do we have here oh
does he move
d
online
it does not seem to move
besides that just uh but does he know
this when I walk by
I can meet him
I don't think I want to
oh yeah yeah yeah oh okay ah okay
does it only detect the ground because I
don't see the pattern on top of the wood
for example I don't know if it's wooded
whatever
stealth job
ah talk to him he's a friend
I do want to oh okay
you better be right
hey good thing you're here you can help
me I lost the keys to my place in this
dark huge Factory
uh
uh Sentinels refused to help me they
told me if no place to go mom work here
we find a chance you could help me find
that I'll be eternally grateful wait
wasn't I already down there no
am I going in there now
no that looks new yeah
down there you lost it
well if it's on my on my path I guess
where is it
is it though
they're they're what's diaper no they're
further somewhere else
they are not that where then why is he
looking there
okay uh
do I want to
wait which way am I going
left right straight
I'm cat and box huh
I'm a shape-shifter yeah
uh
[Music]
all right
interesting how he doesn't see me that
because like the camera isn't even faced
like downwards his face like straight
but okay I'll take it
move
okay I'm going here
[Music]
hmm oh
this one
no no
aren't we just going through here can we
no I
don't know
what's that doing uh
but I can't go back the same way I came
here so I gotta go this way
blind joke no I found it very fast okay
there's a dude there
[Music]
is he cleaning the ground where's the uh
the camera thing is there
I gotta go when ah
we're about to do though do I have to
walk behind him
he probably doesn't care does he only
the cameras here maybe
I can go up right wait I can't can't go
up the boxes
how do I
how
is that really enough time
[Music]
[Laughter]
huh
laser pointer not friend Lisa evil
yummy
ah no way we start from the beginning
oh my God
[Music]
unbelievable do I have to take the quest
again
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] I don't know I'm too I'm too
late uh do it again
I don't know I don't know I don't know I
don't know
I have to go next to the boxes
Speed Run yeah that's my plan
oh okay
[Music]
okay once you do it once
shouldn't be so bad anymore
Sprint for the whole thing yeah
so talk to you again
I got you
and now
cat
cat platforming let's go
pull this trigger
and get up here hello here go here
run around oh yo yo you don't get caught
speed runs make it very very dangerous
though
[Music]
if I could only jump on top of the boxes
that would be nice
[Music]
I'm gonna walk with this thing
oh my God
oh my God oh my God hallelujah
what's next don't want to get caught is
there no safe point in this I wonder
there's light get in the Box
okay I guess that I I will open this up
but then yeah
hide
I didn't even look what's up there in
the front do I just go left now
[Music]
here for a better view okay I could
continue following it
oh keys are here
which one back on the right
[Music]
yeah I have to go back
yes
let me see it
yo
over there
Ah that's hard to
talk again and do I have to go back to
him or realize just meet him again
somewhere else
question mark
a short and there's a shortcut that was
a shortcut oh
into the open door this one
oh
okay I recognize it now oh
[Music]
please tell me I got a safe point
what's up monkey
s
[Music]
oh
wait you can't be found on on the you
can't be found on those I thought I
[\h__\h] up for a second
thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's take a little stop
okay
[Music]
[\h__\h] ticklers
damn
oh my God
stop
yeah I wanted to jump into it but you
know the ex made me go on the Box on top
of the box instead and so instead of
inside
oh wait no it covers some of the barrels
but not this one
[Laughter]
um okay
it's okay it's okay it's okay I'm only
angry angry if I'm like already like
really far this is just the beginning so
it's okay
I want to go in there faster
[Music]
is it good to go
I forgot how I went there
[Music]
um am I safe here
yeah
[Music]
oh can I go
oh
[Music]
jump on jump on barrel
talk to the dude
I wish I had a safe point
it mostly looks like I'm safe on
anything elevated yeah
mostly
I wonder how much further it goes
speed
I'm getting hungry a little bit
okay this one I know like by my pocket
my my jeans pocket
my butt pocket
okay this one I also I think I can do
fine now
it didn't it didn't it didn't see me
right yeah okay
um yellow is still okay
[Music]
okay pick up the keys again I suppose
where is there a safe point though
like usually this game was like really
really
gracious with safe points
not now I guess
I never fell behind that far okay okay
now chillax
and observe
I have to go
left
[Music]
right
[Applause]
[Music]
was he left or was he right
that one cornered me
[Music]
slow barrels on the left
left okay
I'm scared I'm scared uh can I jump up
here okay I'm Gonna Save You
[Music]
see
oh holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
oh my I'm shaking
how did you make that well I was fast I
was I was Sanic
yo was it worth it though
I was not worth it
[Music]
oh my God
if I die again and I am back at the
beginning I'm not doing this again
because we already complain it once even
if it doesn't save it I don't care
that was speed running level moves
yeah right
impressive
[Music]
I'm not gonna accept another setback
my heartbeat man
my heartbeat okay now we go straight
it's so close man close the door again
okay okay uh what we go behind it
there's not much space there
okay
I feel it's the same speed as my walking
speed
[Music]
but I'm not quite sure oh oh this one is
the other side
okay
it's getting tricky and complicated yo
but no match for me
[Music]
okay
okay is this a friend no we can't meet
him so I guess he's not a friend
I'm gonna just go this way
ready
place a barrel
feel like we're done a little bit
this is the goal isn't it yeah that's
the thing that I need probably
nobody's in this
the wind right just the wind just the
barrel just the wind
one of these platforms
oh there's a green one
uh-huh because I guess it's pressure
pressure platforms
there's one already pressured if I walk
on one it's turning green okay I
understand so I need a third thing how
about the barrel
I can't move it sideways
I need this thing
oh my God my my brain is like
super power mode
I mean a chair would work too probably
if my little cat paws worked and the
chair would work too but no we gotta
make it complicated
brain expanding yeah the question is oh
it's broken I can't open it up I need to
go from the top
tried
it's right from here foreign
doesn't let me
I guess I'm from there no don't jump
into the laser don't run into the laser
let me oh
wait I use this thing first
um can I move it
can I move it so I use it as a platform
you know or or I use a gnome can I use
the barrel answer platform no it's too
far
what happens when I
okay I can't move it sideways
I think
I feel like I can move this finger
oh
wait is it moving according to me
okay yeah
wait what's happening
what's happening what oh it just closed
down completely
that thing in the middle [\h__\h]
uh what
go straight
maybe a little bit faster
Jump On It
but then it doesn't move
does it follow me
Oh Oh I thought okay I kind of thought
about it in a different way come on
and off maybe here is good enough
yeah
I think it is
I think it is it just needs fingers
Pizza
hello wow we gotta open the door right
yeah
sorry turkey tan
cute
this reminds me of
um a wind waker
when those robots were following me
for sure okay at least they don't have
to be perfectly on top of it just like a
tiny bit is enough
[Music]
smart Kitty
I wrote and last but not least me
it's all green can I take oh
ah now I put the barrel there it's it
fits just perfectly oh
nice
now I can take it
oh [\h__\h]
ocean
uh hide in box and forget about the
world and just sleep there for a million
years
we got it
[Music]
so please tell me that was a safe point
at least
cat feet
fast run stage I must have been a safer
it must have been a hundred percent
okay let's get out of here before the
Sentinels show up gotta get this battery
back to Clementine and are we still
gonna have to dodge cam those camera
thingies
oh okay oh wait is it
wait is that easy
I thought it would
hmm
and I thought it would be more difficult
to get out of there we're right there
that's it that's it
masterful Escape
okay wait we're going to uh Clementine
Clementine right
okay wow that was fun
oh yeah that that wasn't there before oh
they kicked them out oh but Clementine
is in there
oh yeah
but you can't steal our moves me yeah
Elite English
you know and [\h__\h]
let me in hey I think you're gonna stop
us from raining our digs
I guess we gotta go from the side or so
is she even still in there let me talk
to French
we have the battery let's give it to
Clementine
well uh well uh well dude uh
you realize what's happening here maybe
I can go through maybe there's a secret
connection somewhere
it's our secret connection somewhere I
didn't really open like a
oh I can just look through it
oh
the camera
okay that's new cameras
[\h__\h]
okay more stealth
more stealth that's now
can I go here
yeah okay
[Music]
sip sip sip
up the stairs now okay
okay next time
priority boarding for cats okay this
time priority boarding is actually
effective
amazing oh what is that
um
but there's one over there
we're gonna look at the
one floor higher anyway
[Music]
oh
okay that one never moves I'm gonna go
from the side yeah
oh that one moves
oh I hide here maybe yeah
here here yeah
yeah yeah yeah okay okay
this one doesn't move so I can go up all
right
first try baby
[Music]
this one also died your boo
[Applause]
the [\h__\h]
[Music]
what just happened
I thought I could run away again
I almost made it what I made sounds yeah
right
from here are you [\h__\h] kidding me
huh
from here
what happened to all the nice safe
points huh
nandi why do I need to run so far
do the
seems like they forgot to add some safe
points
[Music]
okay they just realized I'm way too much
of a Pro Gamer
and they need to make it a bit more
difficult
I know the way now
[Music]
Hey Ron
foreign
[Music]
if you're running curves then you could
make it for a while
and the first time I didn't have any
problems of sounds I didn't realize they
would be like such an issue okay because
also ha did they even have like a sound
sensor in the factory
because I feel like I made sounds and
they didn't give a [\h__\h]
I'm pretty sure I made sounds
it's loud in the factory hmm
okay hi I'm back
this time first time's the charm
three times strong
[Music]
no sounds just done
we just walked by
and then
oh yeah
this one go like this and then oh okay
we just go back up there what was there
I didn't is there like a secret memory
there because I didn't go there last
time
I'm curious
[Music]
there must be something there
but I don't see anything in particular
another puff around and I'm supposed to
go around the corner
I'm not sure I'll just I'm going not the
other way
it's a dead end okay yeah it looked like
a dead end to me from my perspective
over it uh
for example also made a sound but it
didn't care about this sound
up the stairs can I go yeah
[Music]
okay
okay here we are again I think this is
where I made the Sound by accident
uh-huh okay we're not jumping on there
if we just
maybe walk around ah we have to I think
we have to
[Music]
okay
um oh we're right there we have arrived
but wait don't ruin it now
okay
awesome
are you still here girl
I think like she's gone
no
and I was like oh my God we have to find
her where did she go
[Music]
she must have escaped
ah
look at club uh huh she went already
before me I guess and we have to catch
up Clem
hmm
no sign of Clementine Clementine oh
what's that it looks like some kind of
coded message we're going to have to
play detective to figure out what
happened let's go tin foil hat on
she's full of gaming today yeah yeah it
was fun
for B12 for the cat the answer lies in
my stuff and then there's four symbols
it's signed Clementine take a look
uh-huh okay I already saw um some of
these things yeah
the clue is there wait okay one one
thing is this one
and one one yeah
you found something I guess no I don't
mean the PC you have to look at it from
the bottom
focuses on the PC
oh there's several ones of them
all right
also uh
was it
um
what about this lava lamp
that one says
[Music]
inspect
his clothes mesmerizing yeah it's hard I
guess that's not quite a lava lamp I
didn't notice this message here it reads
oh wait oh okay but that's the most
important one it's probably meet me in
the nightclub
yeah meet me after the coma is probably
meet me in the nightclub
what could they what could the recipe
we'll figure it out but I got the most
important clue right away
maybe it's something like I had to go
what's this
no I don't think I found anything sorry
I don't think I did
[Music]
okay I know that in the loft there was
the stone
oh what about this thing that that looks
like something that was on one of the
symbols
harmless chemicals in a geisha State
they can't recruit
ing that was not one of them uh oh this
is okay I'm with oh somebody meet me in
the barcata
[Music]
oh now now this place actually has a use
because this is the thing we're looking
for
she made spaghetti meet me in the club
we head into the nightclub stream fever
night oh yeah one of the most obvious
changes in the directors cut was the
favorite night though the Disco floor
which was already supposed to be in
there originally but for some reason
yeah after rendering it it was gone and
then we didn't have time to even look at
it before streaming it yeah but the
Disco Vlog yeah gave it some more disco
vibes
also I think um Sparks
for Sparks you know for some reason like
I don't really understand this kind of
stuff so I can't really explain it but
like body parts are like
like the motion capture for the body
parts it's like different data and for
some reason like my hand was like
straight but uh the rest of the body was
like sideways and that's what bothered
me so much for Sparks I don't know why
that happened but then for the new
sparks it got fixed did you guys notice
I feel like like for me it was so
obvious
the whole if you compare the
um and the where my body is facing for
the first Sparks it was constantly
facing a little bit sideless and then in
the new sparks it was fixed yeah I I
figured that
yeah if you if you see the dance for the
first time then you don't know how it's
supposed to look originally so you
probably wouldn't know but this was like
really important for me yeah
so now it looks much better
[Music]
um
yeah you don't know there's a lot of
things until you look at them side by
side yeah you guys are so much to look
at um
yeah and a glitch
um
yeah you can compare now and see what's
different Kyle carrot did like a whole
comparison thread on Twitter
yeah she beat the stuff yeah I did
Welcome Back looks spectacular thank you
now now that that's done we can finally
work
um on the music video like continue
working on the music video for my music
[Music]
I it seems very impossible now but uh
August I think
before the end of August somewhere
around the middle should be possible
yeah I'm so excited because
it's
you know there's differences in tastes
of music
but
personally I think it's my biggest
banger but that's just my own Taste of
music maybe I don't know about you guys
but
I think even if if that's not the genre
that you normally like to listen to I
think you would still say it's a banger
um it's a [\h__\h] banger
it's yeah high quality
um
you said it was kind of similar to
Sparks no did I say that it could be
similar to Sparks it could be
Kiana pump
yeah
[Music]
music videos
it will be another English song of
course so
and I think I think you'll like it
so far I've never been disappointed with
your music thank you very much I'm glad
to hear that
I'm very passionate about this song
because I I was so
addicted to it for a long time I still I
still like even when I don't listen to
it for a long time
I still get the
um song stuck in my head
every now and then yeah it's really
catchy
really really catchy feels like it must
be my most catchiest song
so far
quite the earworm yeah
it must be hard to not accidentally
helmet yeah yeah yeah yeah sometimes
sometimes I'm worried about that
[Music]
my gonna be my fifth right my fifth
single let's go
yeah so look forward to it I'm excited
I'm excited I'm excited I'm excited
this gem is of medium value and low
Purity this glow seems to have been
added artificial why does this B12 [\h__\h]
talk all of Clementine's items
maybe an ass is a beacon for us to find
something in yellow
laser Europe Blazer I mean do I really
have to get all messages when I already
know what I need to do I wonder
foreign
hahaha I always knew that that was uh no
no not at the bar did I say bar I mean
the yeah the nightclub but I always knew
that that nightclub
sounds
anyway time to sleep
I have to find them all okay
you came at the right time
you're taking oh she just walked in and
flopped over while she was stretching oh
okay I'll be I'll be there with you soon
I think I'm finishing the game soon
if what people say is right
oh she's just chilling now
uh what was the last piece what what
looks us um I don't remember let me see
uh a plant the one on the very left
a plant
this thing
no it won't let me inspect
if it's too close could be here
there was nothing in this room so far
so far besides the sofa
probably in here
something to inspect a toilet oh wait
yeah
huh enough
can never get enough of kiwawa
I can't I can see what you're saying
there well what an offering to have in
an apartment yeah is this the way that
companions here see humans it's kind of
funny
look something's been left
okay now I got it all but that doesn't
look like the clue huh
okay what what what
I'm a Blazer come to the nightclub um
that's it Well Done Lord tenant cat what
it's calling me Lily tenant's cat I got
a nickname let's go find it we don't
have much time okay yeah
[Music]
oh the BTM changed and it's just saved
uh I wasn't there like a
like a shortcut
you get outside
didn't I open a shortcut
I don't want to go through
a lot I'm saying it in a very German way
I guess
sneak out again
imagining things
I'm not gonna do this [\h__\h] again
foreign
[Music]
okay maybe going outside is faster
turning around that one
no
right
here we go what if I get caught no I
just die right okay I thought that maybe
they kicked me out to the beginning
again oh thank you hi we're having a cat
party here four cats in the house
let's go
huh
where is this it's confusing to go
backwards
oh wait that's not a dead end they look
like a dead end but it's not it wasn't
but I'm not gonna take that path
um
oh
I can jump down from the railings really
honey well I'm almost there
here I go
I can't jump down here
sneaky cat
everything so quiet now
I'm scared scared
baby
okay Michael
turn time to put on my sick trip my
dance shoes and get on the Dance Floor
Boogie Woogie hi
um
bouncer son I know I'm a cat but please
let me in
I I'm just gonna show him I have nothing
to show him
okay it's sneaking in time again or
maybe my friends can bring me in
they would bring me in
[Laughter]
[Music]
so addicted to dancing Simon what about
you can I like hide in your hoodie I
don't think the bounce is going to let
us in
even though you got those sick moves
here hey guys I think we're going to
have to climb at the back again all
right I'm gonna do the same
I'm going to do this thing back
back
the back
not a hotel no no no from where I'll
come back here
thank you for welcoming me back yeah oh
potatoes
I never sleep sneaked in a club before
why would I want to do that
but then again I can also say I've never
been bounced off of a oh hello out of a
club or yeah you know what I'm saying
uh you're fancy I'm bad if I had your
clothes
uh they would let me in
you got style late Kila tequila what
honey how are you doing today
what's with this dude
it's got this aura about him
oh hello
you want a party bus and jump in go get
a drink yeah
let's go
ah finally no cat discrimination let me
check this place out oh my God
Zach what's that dude with the fish face
with the magic card on his face
oh but there's like nothing going on
there they should let more people in
what
very cool how come this dude can go in
but Mikko can't
yo
Viv you like my mask I made it myself
the gems The Sentinel scans and it looks
cool it jams well that sounds like a
hint for something I would need
to make my story
you know my girl have you seen my girl
got some access to the VIP balcony is
closed some private business going okay
I guess that's where I need to go it has
been reserved by some Blazer guy
um
[Laughter]
for life oh
wait what happens if I take the strange
drink it doesn't mean I'm drinking it
I'm just taking it with me
what is this
did I just find the secret pathway that
I have to take anyway
it's a deadly
yeah maybe I just found a memory okay
nice
a dumb waiter
what is that
what is that is that something that
brings down the
or is that a meme
I didn't even know this was here
oh that's the name of that
what did you say why can't I not scroll
back up
what what how do
oh there we go when I was a human my
friends and I would gather and pining
along into the night even if we had to
suffer the annoying consequences next
morning
I forgot to find Joy despite the
unlivable surface at the underground
living conditions becoming more and more
squallied
what does that mean and the capitalistic
greed of companies like nickel Corp and
the police state
wait a second
wait is that
is the ending gonna be that like I find
out
that the reason everybody ended up down
here is because of the cats and we're in
control
where the evil
okay don't tell me Chad
what the [\h__\h]
that's why it's called nickelcorp We're
the evil ones uh we're the overlord
that's what happens when cats take over
the world
wait
wait no I don't like that ending if
that's
no no
um
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm gonna slice someone's buys with this
no I can't can I like play a different
track with maybe that's what I need to
do let me go up here
maybe if I play something else they're
gonna get confused and oh I take
[Music]
me oh my God they're microphone heads
hey everybody
[Music]
wait is he saying that because I just
put that song in there
oh would he have said that anyway use
lever base
what
[Music]
oh there's another laptop
uh do I have to find another level
why do I have to hide these
scrunch
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
ah
fun yeah just cat things you know
okay I feel like I need to
no that was just for fun right that was
just a gimmick
I suppose I need to go to the VIP thingy
tell me how to get there Alex
enjoy yourself level one
yeah everything's Gucci
everything's Gucci
wanna drink with me no oh everybody left
you all these drinks but no friends for
you
so sad
yo sir
wait he has the thing the trigger
we're not trying to go to that stupid
BMP run to kick me out me can you
believe it
I still just love it Just for kicks
specifically if you get me a drink I'll
give you this I have a drink yeah baby
next thank you
so I guess it was not just a gimmick I
actually do have to
shut these things down
and I turned the other one off too wait
um
and then the other one
there we go
ah you already put it up the other one
does it have to be like at the same time
and now they're broke down what does
that do
Wait nothing
oh jump on top of it
and then
he can't can he oh wait he'll fix it and
then he'll transport me back up but then
why did I need two of them because only
that one is actually gonna do the trick
oh
um
[Music]
that one
huh
I need to make myself a path this now
[Music]
that looks like it could work because it
also lit up didn't do that before wait
what did we do this one
oh wait ah oh that's fine
wait was it supposed to be a puzzle
[Laughter]
I like one of those you know those
moving puzzles that I always struggle
with
oh
I love that
um
rap I have a very good relationship with
the Sentinels I don't understand why
people complain so much about them
[Music]
they suck
you're manipulated you're brainwashed by
them
hey yo
it's another 10 attention moment it took
me five minutes you didn't do mean
[Laughter]
wait I didn't see until now I was
looking at chat
I guess not because that dude was like
he likes the sentence so he's with them
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh that was a that was a trap she didn't
write the note
he did
hey now you're making me very very angry
yeah
two birds with one stone you're not as
clever as your local cat anyone nothing
personal business is business
but his face is so cute how dare he look
at those little blushes
business is money you want money
I don't have money
I only only have Kibbles
and I value money way more than
friendship or camaraderie
they're all yours
I'm thinking
that means the cuddles aren't mine too
oh no no
[Music]
the deadly laser pointers I will throw
out Monday my laser pointer into the
trash now after the stream because I
don't trust it anymore
[Music]
no
no you can't cage a cat
no I'm so cute though look at me looking
cute where's my backpack
they stole it I see what I'm doing I see
what I'm doing
[Music]
yeah yeah oh yeah baby
nice momentum
oh I don't like to see my animal being
caged evil
[Music]
no no no no
no no no no no no no no
no
oh there we go
stream animal
English version
have we been in here before no it's jail
great
jailbird becomes jail cat
ah
magical
one more
no
ah wait from the ah okay aha I first
have to prepare this one anyway I guess
to get there from the other side all
right
jail time it's a good cover thank you
I already uh decided with Cobble what
song to come up with her by the way but
I think it might take a while come on
probably never did like a
not probably in fact never did a collab
with someone before so I don't think she
knows how how it works normally
I'll teach you I'll teach you how these
things get organized oh my God
holy [\h__\h]
that's scary
no
um scary world yeah
can I open this
okay time
but maybe he's really an evil criminal I
don't know who knows oh my God it's like
Outlast
oh please tell me there's no Outlast
reference in this game because I would
not
[Music]
I would not really appreciate that
beautiful people
I have to go down here huh
oh it turns around so fast holy [\h__\h]
I'm going in here what is this just a
little fancy place to take a break in
you died a while
throwing up in the toilet
that is very unfortunate oh there's a
box there too
and where is it the camera right now
it's hard to see oh oh oh okay
I want to get into the box
and observe where are we going there so
we're going up the stairs okay
Step Up
gonna go up already
does this one move also what is that a
glitch up there
or is that a screen
a TV screen you know those windows up
there
I think it was glitching or no it's it's
probably a screen that's supposed to
show you the sky
to not make you go like
too crazy
because that looks like a sky but first
it was glitching it's a fake outside
yeah but the glitching might be on
purpose
why
with my elf now it's gonna I'm gonna
make a mistake and then it's gonna
kick me out again very to the beginning
I can't go straight uh
we are therefore
going where I have to go up the dumpster
and then up to that platform I guess
what I'm scared to go now [\h__\h]
like what
okay after that I'm going
I like stealth and games and so far I
mean
I mean it's all right
yeah here we go
scary
[\h__\h] out west
[Music]
I don't know how to help you I I mean I
I I can literally fit through that door
I'll help you okay okay
[Music]
I'll have to help me too though
um
you help me I help you or the other way
around
oh easy busy
the [\h__\h] picture will haunt me for
life
[Music]
ah
I always jump scare myself
you're blaming me now
why isn't my phone the game's fault for
making it scary
okay I got the keys
wait what was that Sparks legs crap
let's take the kids and never what what
was it
like because you got the keys because
you got the keys never throw it away or
something like that
yeah welcome to Korea okay I'm not in
Korea yet but
and I'm looking forward to it I need to
I still didn't book my my trip though
I'm still very flexible about it but
what are you gonna do dude
do I follow him
is he gonna open the door for me
because I have no thumbs here thanks for
opening the door
[Music]
[Applause]
you're trying to tell me something
no no
no no no no no no
you know I do prefer this stealth stuff
over
um you know running away from the
monsters
because that one's stressful for me I
like taking it slow
and having time to think oh [\h__\h]
something's happening
oh
there's this this reminds me of
handmaid's tale
um
[Music]
no it's B12 not an evil robot it's B12
captured
help please meow
basket dance
thank you I follow
thank you
literally yeah I hated that so much and
hand means tell us oh by the way
I think I saw something about uh season
five either already yeah I think they
already put out a teaser I didn't watch
it though but they have a new teaser
from the new season which means that I
think they're gonna I don't know do they
have a release date but it feels like
then maybe end of end of 2022 release
could be possible
I am gonna get so mentally [\h__\h] again
by that show nania
[Music]
oh that's bad opening
handmade still
except there's oh [\h__\h] Skye you know it
all you know everything you know all the
release dates the shows that I watch
September
holy [\h__\h]
if you finally watched episode no but
you know what I will watch it uh before
season five which will actually become
be kind of like a good refresher to ease
back into the show you know
people watch like the previous season
before the new season comes out just to
refresh I just watched the last episode
because I haven't watched it anyway
because I I was too you know worried
about it too scared to being more
mentally [\h__\h] and drained afterwards
oh [\h__\h] oh there we go nice
easy
I like the melancholic music mixing into
the kind of
um
threatening stealth music
wait let me see
I could have probably already gone but
yeah
taking it slow to see how far it goes
okay
if I can stop here
nickel box
very atmospheric yeah
okay well I can jump up here too right
and then just go there
[Music]
okay okay
we jump on the fence oh interesting
you're already like really Mission
Impossible
impossible but not really nothing
[Music]
simple aha
we have to jump above it
like meow
real baby
the fruit baby
I didn't see that one coming even
okay okay okay
it goes back very fast
[Music]
uh wait which way are we going anywhere
I mean that's that area seems safe ah
unless when he turns around like that
to see but I guess I'll just go into
that left area behind the windows
um
I went under instead oh
I'm gonna go here
[Music]
oh what does that do open something up
oh
yeah
what are they gonna do
wait are they occupied they're Rocky
they're occupied but they're also yellow
now what's that mean
they're like I guess like immediate kill
then
because they're already at yellow so
there's no blue to Yellow to red but
it's yellow too red immediately they're
on alert yeah
education
at least they're like uh
they moved positions do I just get B12 I
guess go get B12
okay I'm scared to [\h__\h] up now
um
am I safe here I think I'm
possibly safe but I'm not sure
okay I'm safe I'm safe yeah table is
safe
table is safe
and then we go from
when he yeah when he goes when he's past
the table I can follow him I can
when he's past the table can I just jump
onto the middle platform but
let me see the timing when he goes out
there he turns around yeah yeah okay
once he's past me the other one turns
around too
impossible call me baby
how about you jump off when I [\h__\h]
need you to jump off
Call Me Maybe wanna meet me it's okay
whenever you need me baby call me baby
if you wanna
[Music]
oh don't get oh you're asking me to not
get called now I thought we're gonna
like you know attach you to me again and
immediately gonna blast everyone's asses
like you know like this
[Music]
oh it's like one of those dead corners
oh [\h__\h] I'm so glad I I'm so glad I I
waited here I'm so glad I'm so glad
you could die
ah thank God
okay I'm guessing I need to go into that
room over there
maybe oh wait I can go for that hole
okay I don't have to go all the way to
the door
ah but there's a there's a drone there I
gotta be careful okay
once the Drone right now it's on the
right I can see it
the pattern on the floor once it's on
the right like once it's on the way to
the right it's safe to go there
um am I safe here
hey
oh no no no okay
[Laughter]
top spot man top spot
wait go away dude
stalkers
can I go now
am I safe here
okay
oh my God this is really tough hey
what okay it didn't see me even though
even though it should have kind of seen
me
can I am I going left after that I hope
I'm going up
okay
or is it gonna come in here
rather hide here oh yeah it does come in
here partially okay okay okay okay what
now
I'm so
I'm so tense
but it's it's fun it's fun it's fun
oh is that
oh girl
oh dude I did it
my friend thank you so much for waiting
for me please put it on me or no I'm
fine
sweet time there
oh finally you know now I really like
the last feeling I missed it I felt like
I was trapped in my laps computer system
again all alone
but you came back for me I can't believe
it you're a good friend
I know I'm so glad that we're all
together again but we're not safe yet
we need to find a way out of here can
you open that door just there
oh wait that was Clementine
yeah okay
damn okay at least this time we didn't
die I saved myself twice from death
I probably shouldn't knock those over
should I
is there nothing here to check on
uh you can't get through man this light
freaks me out
it's like there's a camera right there
but no
we'll throw the brakes at
something
yeah hey here's brakes use them somehow
vandalism let's
go
or are there bricks she holds it so
lightly
yeah
it's top oh yeah
oh
and now you're gonna lift me
cute
with me
[Music]
okay I will open from here
hopefully
I was titty action
Daniel
see she you know in stealth missions
where you have to like lead for someone
through some section usually that person
is usually very useless but in this case
you know
this robot is being pretty useful to me
so I'm not mad
those Sentinels are blocking away again
they will spot me instantly if you can
try to bait them into those cells and
lock them in
that sounds
very difficult
you for real
okay we saved it's saved okay
how would I do that
until okay one of those cells
what does dude doing there
hello
are you Pablo
do you see that guy on the ground over
there he was rebooted I don't want to
lose my memory I'm so scared
what's that what does that remind me of
also music loud
what does that remind me of
near I guess so
the memory wipe yeah
mama
then
oh this dude oh no
I don't think I can still meet him oh
this Recovery Center has done me the
greatest good my mind is clear and Lucid
I'm an exemplary citizen now
get back to you senses
a [\h__\h] brainwashed you
a dark dark world man I did not think
this game would be so ah dark
okay I locked myself in I guess because
it's so dark I just want to stay in here
I lock it in and then I'll be able to
get out through the
things okay well hi
um I guess we're doing this
really
um
that was not quieted
come with me
[Laughter]
what
ah that must be a different way to do
this
mm-hmm
[Music]
[Laughter]
koala is in control all right you can
come now
like a pro
totally didn't die there
[Music]
do we have to do that again it looks
like it yeah
let me get this memory though
this poor fellow it seems that the
Sentinels are ruthless when it comes to
Defying them
that's what I feared they have
completely erased him no more emotions
no more self-awareness no more memories
please let's not get caught
oof
okay I'll do it again even though that
was really [\h__\h] difficult
wait there's two
I have to get both of them in one cell
or can I open this one up too
I mean I think it's possible
wait yeah I think it's possible
I'll try
[Music]
um
if I just go in first
and then meow oh it's connected oh and I
wouldn't really want uh I mean I can get
them through this door and then run out
of
[Music]
I know I should already close it no
because I can I can get out either way
and then I'm running they'll follow me
probably
and I'll I'll run out here and then
close the other one from the outside
maybe
Maybe
or I don't know is that the best way of
doing it
[Music]
I'll try
will both of them come though oh
only one came
yeah I'm closing it but I only got one
when I open it again will it like
immediately leave
yeah it's waiting it's camping there now
so what if I open uh okay
come here uh hello please enter
come here
did you what
no no
[Laughter]
[Music]
hmm
that was fun though
difficult difficult situation now we
find ourselves in
so I guess getting them both in with
just one meow does not quite work
What if I
you know run past him or or I really
have to get this one in first but when I
not difficult yeah I want to do both at
the same time because once one is
already in it's difficult to get the
other one in without you know
having it disturbing me [\h__\h] how I'm
gonna do this
it's gonna make them run after me
when he comes
um this way
yeah okay follow
please no kill please
oh that was close he was right there
I was close yeah yeah
oh you want to play some hoops
look at this recently I watched that The
Office episode
where they were playing Hoops oh what's
with you
when he stopped moving
you're not gonna
open it we're just gonna laugh at them
right
[Music]
well done locking up that Sentinel we
gotta take the power back yeah he's on
my side okay okay thank God
what if he was like brainwashed enough
to you know open it up on it
[Laughter]
the essentials deserve it I want them to
know what it feels like to be jailed oh
Pablo Pablo
Pablo My Sweet Summer child
ah that was funny huh Lupine you're kind
of broken but he's still he still kind
of gets what's happening
stands it's like he's in a half coma
what's this
okay I already understand you can't get
through so I go through here
I'm thinking like a cat
what am I hearing
Loop in his loopy this doll is the only
way to only way out of this jail
um I think we can open it from that
control room over there we have to find
a way to get access to the room though
let's look around
easy
I'm looking I'm looking I'm looking
there must be a hole somewhere
where
I'm going to the car and I will just oh
well you pay attention to it when I do
yeah okay okay well I was just saying it
as a joke I didn't think oh wait well
we're not we're not driving the car
oh we are driving the car yeah what's
just a joke to be honest but okay
Works we're doing it
hold on
thanks although to be honest
if a cat was willing enough I'm sure it
could do the jump from the bottom up to
here
I've seen my cats do some sick jumps and
I believe in them
foreign
[Music]
wait [\h__\h] help what okay I can't no
no wait I found
a loophole
will you ever stop looking for me though
when I'm here because they definitely
see me
but I can't jump up the thing from here
my destiny
uh can I tap and jump during reload ah
reload
[Music]
the [\h__\h] it wait for me
let me up
yeah yeah
[Music]
Escape Mission
I'm not driving right I don't have to
drive right
[Applause]
nice nice cutscene
yo I like it gives me like Loki
cyberpunk Vibes the whole lights and all
that let's go let's go
oh you want me to do it alone but
they're gonna kill you probably
oh
[Music]
there's no way we'll all make it was the
Sentinels on our tail
I can distract him for a little while
but you have to go
The Outsider Manifesto says we must go
outside at any cost I wrote that
could be cuter
you're one of us now
it's not that everyone has to get to the
outside but one of us has to
oh my God
wait am I at the end of the game
go now I'll keep you in my Ram little
Outsider oh no oh
it's sad to say goodbye
no
you have to live
you were one of the few useful NPCs that
I've met in my lifetime
the world needs more like you
oh we're back here
let's see Daniel
children
where do I put the key in yeah
was it inside yeah
it's not here now
the other side yeah
no it's not here now
a battery first oh
no
is it at the top
making some control then
on there probably
no
am I blind now
is it down here it wasn't that far right
I followed the cable oh wait this cable
this big thing
oh it was that far ah
okay
let's go
let's go to the outside
oh the subway is working again
we did it but
we did it and yet I'm melancholic about
it
[Music]
feel bad for leaving my new friends
behind but I'm taking B12 with me
at least that's something
[Music]
I have to
for the sake of the robots
for the sake of their future
not only for my own sake
for everybody
sure there's a happy ending right
[Music]
should come
on
just hold on to the handrails
down
receipt
let's go
around
Mia
I can't sit on top of it anymore
are we arriving or we're arriving
I'm scared are they gonna be people
are there gonna be cats are they gonna
be overlords
they're coin
oh hi
the first person I meet you you're
Orange
Apple 477 hello how may I help you
oh you seem like you know like the
companion kind of robot
it looks so fresh
oh what what are those
companions no more companions but no
no humans
greetings inhabitant of world city 99
foreign
I am currently painting this area please
be careful of the wet paint have a nice
day
maybe the outside looks like
oh
maybe that's why they have those
pictures everywhere taking the stairs
this time
um I'm sporty
I'm a sporty cat
oh he's falling to me so Japanese
greetings inhabitant of 130.99 this door
is leading to the surface is currently
locked due to confinement procedure
please refer to any certified engineer
inside the control room if you have any
requests have a nice day
it's beautiful it looks so clean in here
but still perfect
I don't want to look outside yet
hey Bobby Bob hello how may I help you
space
whoa
sick
whoa sick
hello my current task is clean the
window please refer to any certified
engineer inside the control room if you
have any requests have a nice day
hello the city has been sealed for your
safety please refer to any sort of okay
I'm repeating what everybody else says
don't mind me please
those chairs are beautiful I have a
chair like this
in my apartment not really like this but
in that green it's a beautiful emerald
green
it suits your mind
inspector
and robot the control room is close by
its own a controller almost comes by
some sort of security protocol and says
that only humans are forced to enter but
according to you you're still somehow
human right
audio crackling
so maybe you're a little too it also
says that oh there we go
I guess not maybe if we work together we
can open this position
[Music]
yeah a robot combined with a cat totally
could go for a human
well then
oh wait did you stay up all night for me
and now you gotta work
good luck fighting oh please don't do
that too often you're gonna suffer but
this week we have two streams that are
good for sea times
oh wait this thing
get muted oh Noni
okay
now it should be back
I think oh wait ah it's not here but
over here
perfectly in position noise we can hack
the system
okay
still won't let me don't do it
what what am I missing I'm not close
enough now
[Music]
your other panel oh okay okay
come here friend
[Music]
oh wait is there another one or can I
just oh I can't just do it from here
okay never mind squeezing
we've been playing this for a while now
brain is starting to lose battery
what
oh
where's my scratch scratch you think I
can do [\h__\h]
[Music]
well I doubt it but okay
I guess I just destroyed it while you're
hacking it okay I just break it I
thought we were hacking into it I guess
okay oh do I need ah
[\h__\h] I did
can I can I take it with me
I think I need it what if
I can't activate it anymore oh the
second one will open okay
this is the controller for the entire
city they controlled everything from
here and it's empty
oh no one is in control
how about over then I'm really good at
being in control I remember hating them
so much they had everything clean space
Limitless power freedom to move little
good it did them
oh
the plague I remember now
wow everyone was dying and they thought
they were above it all they did nothing
to help us
and once my family died I felt helpless
I couldn't do anything to save them
but I can still help you we can still go
outside together I will carry the
memories of humanity and the people I
loved
okay oh oh so close
yeah I'm okay again let's play some
music
what is that
this sounds
broken myself
be more like you know a song that fits
the move mood right now
but okay
okay
what is there to see
where do I go
here
inspect
this is it the main computer
according to the Mainframe no one has
been here for years
the whole city is stuck in a lockdown
cycle from long ago if we disable it we
should be able to leave
we'll need to bring the rest of these
systems online
these computers hold the data we need
we need to turn them on
why do you do that I look for passwords
and encrypted keys to get into the
system
okay
I'll just turn everything on
[Music]
oh I see I see okay don't step on those
because that will turn them off again
no no I mean yeah
no no no
[\h__\h] we're good
be careful we need a finger fingers
Pizza food what's that in English again
fingertips feeling
be careful
Harry now I feel like I'm doing
something bad
finesse yeah it worked good job my
friend
I found it
I know how to open the city
something's off here
wait maybe there's a way around it
roof control station unlocked system is
locked
there that's the workstation to open the
city but there are several layers of
security preventing us from using it
this is longer than I thought it would
be now we need to do what we do best me
I'll have the machines and you destroy
those stuff
huh
okay wait you're not going anywhere
though
why are you not doing your job okay
[Music]
really
how long did I just knock over
everything
like is the actual mission to knock over
every single thing
right now it's kind of difficult too
get down out and
okay boss oh that was not what I was
supposed to do oh
what
oh how about this
I love when the cats jump back like that
yeah
okay is there more
can I unplug it no let's see
anyone else is there
[Music]
there's there's more cables but I can't
do
I feel like I did what was necessary
unless I bumped this over
yeah
and then I got access to it
[Music]
um
what else maybe and some free free
things I have to destroy
true cat
yeah it's just a normal cat life no more
absolutely normal everything's normal
although I really have to say my cats
never destroy things
they're really really good kitties
I can't turn these off anymore right
there
I saw yeah okay you can do this now I
guess because I think I'm done I raised
them well but the thing is like I I
didn't do anything in particular I never
even like scolded them because there was
never need to sculpt them
the system is taking more time more than
I expected and why are you stuttering
[Music]
huh
no
[Music]
oh no we gotta keep them keep going
why are you slowing me down
wait what do you mean keep going what
are you gonna do
attack other PCS maybe are they gonna
come is this like a Time
pressure kind of thing
two more PCS this one
on it
I have to jump high
huh
why won't it let me
it won't let me hack this one
I did not destroy the wire
oh
hi
hi stop looking at me it's embarrassing
I'm shy
okay we can hack this one
keyboard smash
don't worry I can recharge once we open
up the workstation I'm gonna kill it I'm
gonna kill it by doing this no
no
[Music]
and uh
he's falling apart yeah he's smoking
what about this one
I don't see how I can do the cables
what about this
oh
[Music]
that's what you meant look at up on it
okay
now we're ready to hack this is the last
one
I want to eat food
this game is longer than I expected I
mean no complaints but I thought it was
shorter I think
body is done for no
no no no
don't leave me that's okay I'll be all
right just carry me to the workstation
we can disable that alarm
Harry
let me carry you
okay
we can do it together
you mean this one right
should wait
oh [\h__\h] wait
no
[Music]
of course I have to lose someone
important
to rescue the others but that was your
purpose then you know the reason why you
stayed alive for so long the only the
only one that had some kind of human
left in themselves
it was necessary
I couldn't have done this with robots
only you know I needed your brains
hmm
it was your destiny and you fulfilled it
listen I have something to tell you
I knew the power required to disable the
city's central control system would be
immense More Than This drone body could
handle
but with the security Now disabled I can
take control of the system and open the
city
overriding it could destroy my software
when I made that choice when I looked
hooked into that first computer and the
consequences you could bring
I'm sorry we won't see the outside today
you know
I thought I needed to carry on to the
memories of humanity to hold on to the
Past
but I see your future in the Companions
and you
know here let me take that off of you
[Music]
were my friend the very best I could
have asked for oh yeah see cats are the
best friends people say they're evil but
I'm a good friend thank you
[Music]
oh
machine
look at look it is gonna help
yeah yeah healing purse as well
make it vibrate so then I don't know it
comes back to life somewhere you curl up
around it yeah yeah yeah yeah it is
right new
that's exactly what a cat would do
um
oh it would play around by tossing it
around
oh
[Music]
it's happening
the light
[Music]
[\h__\h] time
yeah oh my God it's so nice to see it in
light
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
friends
we did it it was one little cat and one
half human half rubber
Clementine
[Music]
ah it's the real sky
and and wake up now
[Music]
no I mean not me I mean friend
um
oh I can chill again
oh I can always lay down here
I don't want to leave
I'm fine here doors aren't completely
open yet anyway
let it all in Let It All In
you
oh it's so so sweet but so bittersweet
oh wow we can watch the whole thing
happening here
it's so sad
but also happy but not only son
meet cat friends again
it keeps on opening it's almost done I
think
holy [\h__\h]
oh
but
can't perish heal people
heal everything I believe
maybe I can fix it
oh
it's done
thank you Brandon
the entire game was another cat that
went inside I want to go outside
we have a [\h__\h] indecisive cats yo it
looks so cool
oh my God I want to see like more of
their reactions I want them to throw a
party for me
now I want to go outside too though
when do I just go here
companions gonna say
hey
um
oh I can't talk to him
oh
I'm I'm out
and it's
beautiful
just like the day when I lost it
words
I have birds that I can hunt down again
oh [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] I'm gonna eat you
later
I'm I'm happy
oh sniff sniff happy cat makes me happy
oh [\h__\h] robots I only care about cats oh
cute
[Music]
pretty cat free again just enjoying
nature
chasing butterflies
[Music]
pooping everywhere because the world is
a cat's toilet
almond
what did that mean at the end
eye opener after credits scene
yeah it means he lives right but what
about my cat friends
[Music]
after credit scene
by me
Maybe
holy [\h__\h] how's it already midnight I
thought I didn't have so much left
I played for five and a half hours
Nani
oh my God but that was amazing
I really really
really did
I'm gonna give the game nine out of ten
what do you mean I'm slow I was pretty
fast in a lot of just these parts today
I don't think
zooming through it partially
um
wow
I like the ending track too I like the
soundtrack overall
[Music]
I feel like what what could have been
improved uh is some of the same points
and I think well I thought the graphics
overall were really nice I thought you
know
what should be the focus the cat could
have been more polished
but maybe I did turn off some blur in
the beginning of the stream last time
maybe it would have looked different but
no that was just general blur I don't
think it would have improved the cat
itself
um yeah more polished yeah because they
were like close-ups and then I felt like
what this cat looks kind of really low
quality
um could have been
a bit improved
um but yeah I thought the cat cut scenes
were cool I thought the you know the I
found all the NPCs were really
interesting to talk to I liked talking
to them a lot normally normally I don't
like going around to talk to
um NPCs that much like at least about
every single [\h__\h] NPC but in this
game I enjoyed going around to talk to
every NPC
yeah I wanted to know more about them I
wanted to know okay Lauren I wanted to
know if they give me something for my
side quests and all that yeah
I know there's something about the pets
there it's a white
[Music]
I was fun zooming around I like the cats
things like scratching things like
purring things appearing at things
meowing at things and sleeping on people
rubbing yourself against people's legs
making people trip you know those kind
of things and you know the happy
reactions from the people were also
really cute to see how they react when
you know a cat
you know comes up to them
I like my boxes yeah and my barrels
barrels were nice too
the monsters were disgusting and the
worlds they created were disgusting too
uh but now it's all gone so it's all
good
oh
the light shines through
ah but why not I know French reunion
also wait you guys really made me think
that my idea might have been correct
maybe it's up to interpretation
that you know the whole thing about cats
being the evil ones cats having taken
over the world and cats being the evil
one maybe maybe it's just you know the
reason why I didn't show much afterwards
is because they want you to make up your
own ending
well I think they could make a sequel
yeah
something where this cat has an
adventure in the Overworld oh
yeah reposition yourself yeah
you gotta lick yourself that's creepy
sorry I just meant not trying to tell
you what to do but you know usually cats
after a nap they wake up and they clean
themselves
sorry I'm just I'm not trying to back
seat you
sorry
no that was a lot of fun I really like
this so much
big props to the developers I I really
like this game not just because I'm a
cat lover I think it really was a great
game
um
[Music]
foreign
scary stuff I could get by or passed
because of the cute elements
a motivated me to get through
yeah I'm glad you
can join it too
oh it got 90 plus ratings in nearly
every review oh that's great to hear and
let other people enjoyed it too
um
I'm so glad it was a pleasure to play it
I will not forget this for a while
poor cat's getting laser pointed yeah
what the [\h__\h] if they wanted to make cat
lore a little bit more accurate they
should have made the cats immune to the
laser and make it play with the laser
cat
is attracted by laser like chunkers
ignores it completely
while a smoothie loves loves the laser
so much
yeah the moment you know my my laser
pointer has like a little keychain on it
so it makes a sound when I pick it up
and even when she's like really far away
in a different room
the moment I pick up the laser pointer
or even slightly touch it she recognizes
the sound immediately and runs over
really excitedly yeah
[Laughter]
it's so cute
but sometimes you know I just move it
because I want to clean the room or so
and then I feel bad because I got her
excited but then I have to I have to
play with her
yeah ah thank you guys for watching
today I think it's really
um it got way later than I expected I
thought we only needed like maybe three
more hours to finish the game and then I
would rate super chats so sorry uh sorry
about that but
um
I might be adding another stream to this
week's schedule
and to um
talk about my tangency
yeah
and I think yeah we just recently called
up on the super chats anyway so it
shouldn't be too bad
um
[Music]
thanks for a good time thank you for
watching
[Music]
thank you for watching
thanks for streaming in Congress for
finishing his game yeah another game
finished
um
you missed the ending ah come on you
should have known that that felt like
the ending was super close
but I also felt like
um
the ending like for some games I feel
like the ending is way too much dragged
out
but I actually felt it was fine here the
only reason I was like oh this is longer
than I thought it was really just
because I thought the whole game was a
bit shorter
and I I didn't think we needed that long
so just from like a streaming aspect
because I wanted to read super chats
that's why why I was saying that but in
general I feel like it had it had a good
length what the [\h__\h] you
even young you're still here
didn't you go to work or are you are you
hiding in the toilet now
let's get a sneak peek
getting a sneak peek
um fighting
those stealth missions dragged on no
I think they were a fine length
at least they didn't make me like
run for my life again in the end
with the with the alarm going on at the
end I thought we're gonna have a really
annoying running
um part again but thankfully it wasn't
the case
um
okay I think the next stream is the day
after tomorrow uh with with Nabi Mama
already
the next stream
oh yeah it is but before I go if you
guys are not on Twitter you may have
missed it but um I guess I should maybe
uh put it on the community board but the
information about the meet and greet for
the birthday merch raffle is out
and it's been tweeted out and I I
retweeted it today so you can check it
on my Twitter
um
or let me post the link
for the campaign information in the chat
right now
yeah
is it for Geek Jack buyers as well uh I
think so it says everyone who has
purchased a total of more
of or more than 5000 Yen shipping fee
excluded
of the merch is eligible
uh customers who made the purchase
priority event announcement are of
course also able to participate
yeah it should be it doesn't say
anything about where you have to buy it
uh so I'm pretty sure it's fine
if uh Gemma is around I can ask right
now
but I think she's uh offline yeah
okay okay uh
yeah
um
I don't know how you're gonna be
contacted but you will see when will I
get notified for the event we will be
sending you event details via email if
you have chosen us if you haven't chosen
as the winner for the raffle email will
be sent by the middle of September
because the meet and greets are going to
happen in September and and yeah there
will be like two different dates or so
um
five whole minutes yeah they asked me
how long I want to do it and I thought
you know normally the meet and greets
before I have been like two minutes and
I thought it was a little bit too little
but for some people it was actually
enough but then mostly the most people
were like it's too little and since I
can
um you know split it into two days
uh I think
[Music]
it's fine to do five minutes I think
will be fine
um
yeah
I think um
I think it it should be fine now I'm
gonna take
as much time as possible for you guys
there will be a lot of winners yeah it
says here at I said I want to do a lot
so I'm doing two anti-winners
and for a five minute long one-on-one
meet and greet session yeah
um
[Music]
foreign
once the emails are out I'm probably
going to be notified by management so I
will notify you guys as well so you can
check in your spam folder as well just
in case you think you missed something
um
yeah yeah and it's fine German English
or Japanese I will be able to talk to
you any other language please know
please try to communicate and prepare
what you want to say
um
anyway
yeah that's uh that's so important sorry
that it took a little while to get out
there but it takes a while anyway until
the winners are decided uh it will be
for the whole period of one month you
can you know buy the merchandise and get
a chance to enter the raffle yeah
how about a chicken book The Chicken
book is fine too but isn't that what you
guys always talk
would be great if I could actually be
there good luck to others what do you
mean if you could actually be there it's
via Zoom it's online you can do it from
anywhere oh
hmm
uh well actually let me try
are you there
is geek Jack okay true for me and great
I think I think she's sleeping but
it should be that job
[Music]
wow
yeah sleeping now
well I'm pretty sure yeah I it would be
stupid yeah not to be eligible it would
say that somewhere
um
okay I'm so hungry now Yum Yum Yum Yum
Yum Yum gotta eat some gotta eat some
Kibbles
oh yeah she needs her rest yeah she
really deserves it yeah
all right
she was just dancing earlier with
Michael
yeah she was she's exhausted now
yeah She fainted from all the fun that
she had in the disco disco party party
okay thank you for the fun time today
and yeah I'll see you with nami Mama on
my channel she's gonna teach me some
Korean uh I'll I'll do my homework
tomorrow
do some preparation yeah
thank you guys so much I hope you
enjoyed this sorry for being gone for
the weekend uh I'll tell you more
stories about it in an additional stream
I think that's the best and I don't get
so distracted at least
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
that's so creepy right like often I want
to take a cute picture of my cat and
like in the reality looks fine but on
the picture they have like really scary
eyes for some reason reflective eyes
freaking me out
[Laughter]
bye-bye
it's so nice to be a cat isn't it
ah
foreign
[Music]
nice
oh thank you thank you
thank you thank you for the red super
chat good night
[Music]
foreign