[Music]
T
H
[Music]
Come
on he
[Music]
he
[Music] Hey
hey hey, ...
Genius,
this is Lyrica from Hololive Device Regro. Hello
Lyrica, she's so cute, so positive.
[Music]
Oh, I'm back. Yes, I'm back. Yep, I'm so happy.
Ukambae. Hello,
everyone. Guten
Morgen and
Dankishespa. Dankesupa. I'm Lyrica. Nice to
meet you.  Did they do it? Only Super,
only Super, only Kisspa, I don't
know, I don't know,
yeah, in this stream, I want to
talk a lot about when those two came to see me.
We will talk about
both English and Japanese.  Yes, I'll try my best.
Yes, I think Doi is a little bit, but Laden-
chan is really amazing.
That's right, even though I was originally
not that good at English, I
think, but
this time while traveling, I felt that Laden really
understood it, and he really
understood what I was saying.  I was thinking, "
Why did you
say you studied?" I thought. "
Yes, I studied. I studied.
Stop acting like you've awakened to special abilities."  I
was watching the streams of the members of that house, and somehow, somehow, somehow, I
started to understand what they were saying. Who are you
watching? Who are you watching? Who are you
watching? Um, it's me, senior.
So
that's the end of this story. No, no, it's okay. I don't watch my books in the first place. That's why I do
n't watch them.
Turnwatches
of English people
have been picking up
English
PRal. I mean, La-chan understood the last collaboration pretty well,
right?  Bitin
Ieri is right
Lil' bit English Ladenki Suki
Ah, it's right, it's a little bit right, it's understandable, it's understandable, it's understandable, it's understandable, but I think that katakana English is a bit hard to understand for people who don't understand Japanese at all. Ah, I see, I
see, it's lil' bit
English.  If you say it to a stray person,
most people will say "hete", but what do you mean
? They say "[ __ ]". Super Daki, Super Daki, that's right. Super Daki is first. Yes, yes, yes,
yes, well,
these girls were eating at
my home for Couple Days
last week and  Basically, we
only did something like
that for three days.  Even though we
didn't have much time, we still
enjoyed it.
Thanks to my senior who made a great schedule, we didn't have any time to spare.  I
had a little bit left, but for example, on the 1st I
took a little nap and was too sleepy, so that's
right. Well, right after I arrived I
slept a little bit. So, let's begin with a day.
I
put some notes, I really like notes.
Yes, on the first day, my senior came to pick me up at the airport. He
was a little late, but he
was too early. He was too late, so I couldn't make it. Yes, yes,
probably. Ririka
-chan, I know, if it's my eyes, you don't want to see me, right?
No, my senior's  If it's for our sake, I guess it can't be helped.
For Raden-chan's sake, let's
try our best too, I think. So sweet.
[Music]
Well, I don't think it makes sense, don't say it, do
n't say it, right? At the
airport in the morning, we came together with the morning sun,
right? Yes, we arrived first
Did you have any impression right away? It was
so cold that
even the sun rose early in Japan.  It was
colder than  It was
really cold, it
was incomparably colder than I thought it would be. Oh,
wasin Japan, but
Austria also had that season,
so there were three, four, three, three
, one disappeared, I was surprised, that's
how it was.  Well, one by one,
when summer turns to winter, it gets a little cold so
quickly that I wonder where autumn is, but,
well, there is still autumn, there is still autumn,
right ...  It's already been
this cold since October or November.
No, it seems a little hotter. I'm
just exaggerating. Yes,
autumn is gone in Japan too. I wonder.  Autumn is
disappearing. I feel like autumn is getting shorter. That's
right, why does it get cold so quickly? I feel like I'm getting colder
earlier. Ah, there's a chance that autumn will no longer exist in 30 years.
That
might be confusing, or
maybe it's just that the winter is just getting more and more out of sync.
Yeah, yeah, from February to May, yeah, yeah,
yeah, it might be off, it's too soon,
I feel like it's already off, in Austria,
yeah, I mean, at the airport, yeah, at the airport, yeah, I
arrived, in the airport  Well, that was made of
walnut wood. There was some kind of chair that came
out. I was like, wow, that's amazing. It was a
walnut wood chair. It was made of walnut wood. It was
n't really a chair, it was a bench. It was round and
shaped a bit like a gourd.  I was so
happy to see a bench there that I sat down. I
thought there was a bench, and I was so happy to see something like this in the airport. I
sat down.  It's
a bench that I
found in a place other than the airport,
so I guess it's a
fairly common bench. I see, it's a pretty normal bench, so I'm
happy. It's normal, after all, and you see it
in a lot of different places.  I thought I wouldn't watch it
but it was so happy, happy, happy, amazing, it was
amazing, I was laughing the whole time, especially
on the 1st, I felt like Mere-chan was happy, happy, happy, it was the
first time, I was happy, I was happy,  I was
really
happy when I heard that there was a meeting. I was driving along this road and I was like, "
What is this, what is this, what is this, it's amazing," and the
taxi driver laughed at me.
OnAll
Things Japan doesn't have
them at all, so
there are a lot of beautiful shrines, so there aren't any in Japan.
Well, I guess there are shrines. Well, I guess there are ...  Was it
that early? It was
n't around 1pm. Did you have to wait that long? That
might be true. But why did you say around 10pm at first? It
seemed like everyone at the station was asleep.
Hey, hey, expose
me,
Lyrica, it seems embarrassing, but that
Thank you for
Let me sleep thank you
for Laden and the others wanted to lie down too,
so we did, but
was Half A
SLEEP and I
had over [laughs] and  I was
watching the whole time,
but I couldn't help anything.
Hey, Japanese Shirara-chan, maybe now, I'll
explain it to you. That's right,
Shittsu.  Well, Kihara-senpai
made everything new, right?
And when it came to putting the sheets on the space that was given to Laden-chan to sleep in, Kia-senpai
couldn't put the sheets on properly about four times, and  It's Lyrica,
not Laden. Oh, oh,
oh, Laden was already playing with the cat at that time.
There was a cute cat there. Please pay attention to me.
Lady, yes, the cat is talking about Lyrica and Laden. He's
been saying something all this time. Mya mya.
Yamyaaah, I'm so happy, it's so cute,
is that a lie? Is that a lie? It's so cute
in my suitcase, it's my
favorite and it's been tucked in there for a long time, is
n't it? I should have taken a picture of it in my suitcase, I guess.  I
'll be here forever and ever, Re-chan
FluffyIt was fluffy, so I
wonder if it was the contents. Oh, I see.RsuitWasAlwayswassleepinglivingputDownRandhadHer suitcaseOpenandstilllikeleftHEROESinitwasreallyFluffysoMyCatslikebothofthemThey took Turn MIDIt looked really comfortable, but I feel like it was my own cushion. I see.
TurnErika was quite lunch  I thought I
was ordering something for lunch, but that's not right. I
had a breakfast burger.
That's already lunch. I
had a breakfast burger for lunch.
Yes,
yes, yes. It
's One Apple.  Apple, apple
like apple ginger,
like ginger juice, I see, I
see, it was delicious, what did I eat that morning? I have a terrible memory,
eh, not that one, salmon,
salmon on top, that's right, yeah, there was a photo,
salmon and cream cheese yeah
sandwich  So I made it like this.
Oh, I was so hungry that I ate a lot.
Raden got hungry soon after taking the photo. It
looked delicious. I ate a burger with plenty of avocado and egg. It was
delicious. You ate a lot. That's right. You ate a
lot. I ate a lot
.  We had Kaiserschmann, a famous Austrian dessert that was
like a crumbled pancake,
and we both
thought it was super delicious and we were really moved. It was so
beautiful, so beautiful. It was hair. But, you know,
Rika was a bit
surprised.  I do
n't know, maybe it's just Lyrica, but I don't know,
but I don't really eat sweets for lunch or breakfast,
so I guess
that's what it's like in Austria. I'd be surprised,
but it's true.  No, I just love sweet things. That
jam was delicious. It was
apricot jam. That time it
was apricot but I changed the base and made it more like an apple mousse
than apricot. It was
like a plum jam.  Together  I guess it's
normal to eat them, yeah, yeah,
but you can have apricots and jams, you know,
yeah, yeah, I've tried a lot of different jams,
but every jam was delicious and I was impressed,
thank you, it was super delicious, I'm so happy, I wonder
if the jam is famous, Austria Rica fruit
is a souvenir  But I bought quite a bit of jam and went home. But
yeah, what did you end up buying? I do
n't know. Did you buy it?
The two of us, listen, listen, listen, listen,
take it, take it, buy it.  I thought, "Yes, yes, I
didn't have enough money so I couldn't buy it." I'm sorry, but I wish you
had told me. I have
n't eaten it yet, and it's in the fridge right now, so
Let's eat it, no wait wait wait wait wait
wait no no no You two
have already eaten it so give it to someone else It's just a
souvenir but I can't
eat it This is the real thing I want to eat it  I
ate it anyway, but it was the real thing. I
told you it was the same. Oh,
there are three little ones.  Which
one did I buy? I bought it. I bought it with three little ones.
Nice, nice, nice,
nice. I always win too. Yes, yes. Let me suddenly won the to of souvenir. Because I told them from Day one onwards that. When they are at the airport. They should look for the Little SAA Hotel. And Sweets boof. Because they sell SA cakes that really tastreally good Home over and over and for did buy One Of These
Little
Pages.
Sawanted to BU had no oney. Silently
suffnow.
And also,  I didn't have 50 yen so I bought a
bag, but Racha said he had money and gave me 50 yen.
[Laughs] I
couldn't buy it, I couldn't buy it, I couldn't buy it, I could
n't buy it. I was buying souvenirs for everyone, and then I couldn't buy it at Zahar. We
ate together.  Well, I have to eat this,
but I'm going to buy it as a souvenir and give it to someone else. I'm going to buy it
at a Japanese department store, Demel, and
buy it for myself. I
bought it in Australia.  I want to eat it
Well, why? Then I'll give it to someone else. I'll
buy it in Japan. Oh, but it's already the
real thing, so it's all real. I see. I
want everyone to taste it. No,
wait, wait, then, then, then, that Liliko.
Chan gave the one she has now to someone else and
I'll bring it back the next time I come to Japan. We're both
happy about that, aren't we? We're happy about that.
Yes, we're happy about that. Yes, we're
happy about that, but we're not going to eat our own.  No,
no, it's fine. I thought that it was more that
Laden wanted to eat it than that I wanted to eat it.
But I'm glad that you liked it.
Let's see. Yes, let's do
that. Let's discuss
it. Let's discuss it.  That's right, yeah,
yeah, thenAFTER
breastsWe really
about the cakeshere
ikeponTry convince
them to give their
cakesASVbut anywayWe
went to amuseumAfter
the
breakfastthe museum
wasaBIGfamousmuseum
thatIactuallygoto
yetIt was like an art
History museum
was so Big and They
[Music]
even in the Special
Collection But The Special Collection
was also I think like a
BIG Plus because seems like I
already like it I like it I was happy Ah, right
here, right, right, right, the artist, the sense of art, in Japanese, right, right, the
technique, I wanted to
go to the book I've always wanted to see, so I
was glad  The reason I wanted to go was because I
was really interested in the architecture of the museum itself.
That's right. I
didn't really look into what was on display, but I
thought it would be nice to see Bruegel because he's famous. I also enjoyed the architecture
and saw a lot of Rigel.  I'm
so
happy, I'm so happy. I got to
see the painting of the middle of the painting. I'm so happy that I got to see the painting of the middle of the painting. I'm so happy that I got to see Bruegel's painting. That's
right, that winter one. That's right,
that snow one. I have a photo of that.  I got it
I don't have any pictures, so please send them to
me later. I got it. I'm so
into the images that I want to see. I think it's good. I think
on the first day,
All of Ustaketoo many Pictures, so you have to
IMAGINE,
I only took a picture of this one at the museum. I only took this one.  The
reason is,
I have been really
interested in the Loire family from England.  I've been
doing a lot of research and
enjoying a lot of different media, and
Tiz has a lot of money, and
he's a bit of a strange guy, but he really
wants a boy, and his first
wife won't give birth to him.
So one day, I met a really beautiful
new woman named Evelyn,
and
I was so stubborn that I thought, "I'm going to get divorced."
So, I changed, and my head was so
stubborn that I thought it was normal to force a divorce,
and then I got divorced, and it became a great drama, and I thought I would be
happy with Evelyn, and I would bury that man, but I
also bury that.  In the
end, he cut off Evelyn's head and
then he continued to drag in various women
to give birth to boys, but it
always failed and in the end he
ended up with six of them.  That guy, happy or unhappy,
couldn't give birth to a boy after all. He was
with that woman. That
woman was the third woman. The
third woman.  Yes, the third one is a
really interesting story, so check it out.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Please.
No,
My, yeah, yeah
, I won one more, and this one. I ended up winning, but I haven't heard from them yet.
This picture says I haven't heard from them yet.  It hasn't
come yet. I wonder why. I want it. I really like
it.
I was drawn in.
There were all kinds of versions, and I
made it like a game, and in the end,
I thought, "This is it, this is it." It
was really big, but just like that, this is
it.  I was told that I couldn't take it home because there was only one. I
ordered it. This picture is so real.
This print was really good too. Yes, it was
really impressive. I wanted it.
Where is it? I'm
waiting. Where is it?  It
takes time, I guess. It's not just a matter of getting close. Yes, yes, yes, probably.
Our
SHOWthere
[music] I
thought it was really important to see the real thing in front of the museum.
How long were we there? 2 hours or 3 hours. Yes,
quite a bit.  I feel like I've been there for a long time. I feel like I've been there until the end.
I love ART from AR over and he
goes to all of the collections in Europe from this Artist like Wherever this Artist has AR The Goes there
because he needs to
Follow HIS
oshi HIS oshi ART He has oshi of
Piece of AR Theme all
about
[Laughter]
Lyrica-chan, I want to translate that into Japanese, something
like "o" in Japanese. There was a painting or something of a work of art at the museum, I
think it was a woman,
yes, a woman.
In front of it, there
was an old man sitting in a wheelchair, and we were
looking at it, and the
old man started talking to us and said, "It's the best," and he was really talkative and
said to my senior, "
Which one?"  I don't know if you like that work,
but I haven't finished writing here,
so I'm talking about the details.
Yes, but I met that old man again,
somewhere else, or something, about three times.
But I went back to the merchandise section. If something
came out at the merchandise section, that's right. Yes,
yes, yes, no, that wasgood
GoodMan
was so passionate, so yes, it was
cute, I think it was cute, it was cute, and I
really liked that painting.
So, that Esi-san is showing off his
collection in museums and all over Europe,
and he's chasing something.
So, he
was a big fan of Rembrandt. That's right, it was
Rembrandt-san,
right? That's right, it was Rembrandt's art.
That exhibition was an exhibition of Rembrandt and his disciples, but it was
by other artists.  There were paintings, too,
so it
felt like an exhibition of Rembrandt's work as a teacher.
Yes, as expected, the biology
section was by Hogstraten, I think that's how it was translated into Japanese.
Yes, yes, yes.  That's
right, it looks like Hoss and Laden,
but it
looks like Latte. Yes, it looks a bit like Laraten. I
liked this Cost
Laraten. Oh, that's right. Laden bought a lot of
souvenirs too,
bought a lot too.  Yes, I was happy. So I ca
n't buy Sacher anymore. That's
good.
By the way, I
went to the art museum and
saw the exhibition of Rembrandt and Hochstler, and I
said I was going to see Bruegel after that.  But
Laden bought a lot of books and it was heavy. I
bought a lot of books and it was heavy. I
thought that, but I saw the number of times. Be
careful about the timing of when you buy books. It's
heavy, so be careful. Yeah,
yeah, yeah.  I thought it was good, I was thinking about muscle training,
so I went to the museum, the museum, please go ahead, sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but
there was something I was curious about at the museum, so if you
know anything about it, I'd like you to tell me.  But, yeah, I haven't
been to many art museums in Japan,
so I've only ever been to small ones, so I
don't know, but
big art museums overseas have a lot of
places to sit, right? Yes, they do. They're
big and beautiful.  It's like a king, or something. I
wonder if a king would sit there. The bright red things on the river are lined up like this.
There are things like that in Japan too.
It's like sitting and looking at artworks, enjoying the time.  Well,
I guess it's true, but I actually
went to Austria and passed it.
Japanese art museums are a bit small, aren't
they? It's a simple matter of the size of the space,
but if you want to sit down, you
need a lot of space,
so it's too close.  I
thought maybe it was a little hard to put a chair there, but I see.
But it's a relief. If you can sit there
for such a long time, it's good to
sit down and
relax.  Moreover, if it was a big painting, I would
sit a little further away.
If it was big, it would be helpful. I was very
happy that there were so many chairs. I was able to take
my time to look at it. It was a naturalist museum. It was not a naturalist, it was an
artist. It had a good artistic feel.  It
was really good. It was like a dream. I was so happy to
think that there were so many paintings in one place. I almost skipped. I was so happy
...
When someone seems to have gone somewhere, it just
happens, but I think, "
Yeah, there's this and that, too." Once I
started thinking about it, it got pretty fast.
Oh, I got so much fun with that and that and that, so cute, so cute, sometimes I was like, "Where are you going?", it's dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, I'm not going to get lost even just a little bit, yeah, I'm not lost, yeah, yeah, okay,
okay, after that, we went
thefirstCHmaret That was the
first time I went to a Christmas market on this trip,
and after that, it was fun, but I
got drunk and had some mulled wine. Yes, that's right,
mulled wine. It
was really delicious mulled wine,
and it was really easy to drink.  It
was like hot wine, but
the moment I put it in my mouth, I
was like, "Wow!" and it made me feel really good. I
thought I was feeling good, but Lyrica was already
drunk.  The seed punch
was so delicious, I could
drink it. By the way, it
's not my photo, but I'll
show it to you because it's easier to imagine.
Right in front of the museum we went to.
There is another kind of artistic sense, isn't
there? Yes, there is natural art.
And then in between there is a Christmas market. If you
look at it a little, it looks like this. It's
wonderful. It's amazing when you look at it like this. Yes, it's
wonderful. This is a Christmas market.
So while drinking this delicious wine, you can enjoy the
architecture.  You can enjoy a heavenly place.
I was so
happy to think that it was okay to have such a happy place. I think it's good to see the view
from one of the museums and
other museums, ART, HIS,
Nature, HIS, etc. It's
beautiful.
Yes, yes, I definitely want everyone to go.
No, I hope you all go.  It's fun no matter how many times you do it,
no, good,
good, no, I erased it, the desk disappeared, I
fixed it, athestuffWedrankthe
mneandthePUNCHfor
theandateCheeseaust
foodenoodThingsand
POTATO
stu
soshita, aye, it's
not really street food in Austria, but it's
something that's often sold at Christmas markets.  There
are many types of rice that are easy to eat, and
this is a mix of the two.  It
's not cheese noodles,
but it's not pasta, but something like that,
and on top of that, the grilled potatoes, they were
delicious.
The One Time When We
drank something and the One Time When Weate something we were because really busy we were standing at a table next to strangers and the strangers we real ways really nice and friendly and talked to a little bit with us.
ThenEverybody was
asking me Why do you
knowJapanesesomuch
Yes, yes, you were asked some really great questions, right? Senior Yes,
seven people were like, "That's amazing!" The
Christmas market was really crowded, so
when I went to eat or drink, I
usually went to that desk.  I
ended up sitting next to people I didn't know, but everyone was so
friendly and kind and interested and
asked me all sorts of questions. I had a
little chat with them and they were so kind and the
atmosphere was so nice.  I was able to
see a lot of things on the first day, so I was
really happy. I was really happy.  After
that, we
didn't have a meal together, but I thought it would be
fun to eat together while streaming,
so I did it. It
was delicious, wasn't it? It was really delicious. I
wanted cheese cheese. We love cheese. Ah cheese,
cheese,
cheese. Speaking of cheese, did you
eat it?  Lyrica did you eat
your I haven't eaten yet I haven't eaten yet That
expensive cheese That was expensive I
'm warming it up But I
bought sliced cheese separately
To put in my sandwich Yes I
brought that home  Oh, it's open, so that's what
they're eating. Oh, right, that's right, that's
what it is. Oh, that's the original powdered cheese. Oh, that's right, it's
Parmaison cheese.
AndisbutinBIGchunksBIGfinchunksandReallyWanttohavethatsaysyoucanonlyGetPARMlikegredin
JapanmostlysoboughtthesomeTHEflakyparanTHEshavedOneandtheotheronethat
boughtatthe
ChristmasMarketthat
weshowedyoubeforeofcourselovesCheese
I love you so much, yeah I love you I'm so happy I love you Please
give me some chicken cheese too someday Yeah, that
's right Let's eat that together too There's so much So
much, so much It ended up being so much that I didn't even measure it
Without even measuring,
it's 300g,
it's fine, it's fine, there's lots of happiness, there's still a
house left, yeah,
LAT Day, after that I'll do a copycat stream, eat, and
sleep, so I'll go the next day
[Music]
though
problem Was that
There was Like a BIG BIG GAPin
time between like US
leaving the museum and then going to the dinner which was closed by just because like there was nothing else to do beside the Christmas Market so we were at the Christmas Market for TH to Four hours no joke to really enjoy much as we could do it every day. When I was planning that, I thought a lot about
that
place and wanted to do as many things as possible around that place in
that one day.
So on this day, around the Simbo Palace
There were a lot of people there,
but we also went to an art museum,
and the closing time of the museum and all the other places was the
same, so we
had about four hours until dinner time, and we spent the whole time
going around the Christmas market.  But it
seems like it was fun. Christmas markets have spectators. Did you know? There are spectators. It's rare.
But it was fun.  We were Still like so Emotional and Happy This is Where All The
Emotional stuff
happened We All Got like
overwhelmed
with First of all, on that day,
I was originally thinking of taking her somewhere,
but that morning, Chiara was
able to buy it so that she could eat it after dinner.  I was
just thinking about it, but the two of them
said they wanted to go together, so I ended up buying some bread for breakfast. That's
right, I was
planning to go alone at first.
Yes, I
want for
BREbefanand  I just wanted to go out and have cakes for
eating later in the evening, a dessert and just prepare it, but then they were like, oh, I will come with you, so I ended up buying just breakfast, from the bakery, which is also like, kind of experience, you know, we always have to go to the fancy place, I think tourists like to experience like, how normal people, who live there, go about their days, right, so you, would you just go to the bakery and get something fresh from the bakery, well, Korean customers, well, it's not like they go to a cafe
every day, but people who live there, that's
normal, everyday  I think you
want to do the same thing so you can enjoy a life like
that. So that was good, right? Bakery
food. Right, right? You
know how to buy it properly. You can live there now. Oh,
live just a day. Breakfast at home.
And went to my house.
Music]
glor No, Lale-chan, you took a picture, right? You
took the picture, took the outside, took the outside, did you take Licca-chan too
?
I didn't take any pictures,
but I took them from Google. The
Gloriette in the palace, well,
how should I explain it? The Gloriette,
Schnburg Palace, yeah, yeah, yeah, um, the
ghost of that palace.  In the garden area,
there is a huge building called the Gloriette. Yes,
this is it. This is the Gloriette.
This
is the summer scenery. Inside
There is and is
up on B Hill. When on there and you turn around you can see like All of the City all the betiscen. Here is the person who took me.  The
reason I wanted to go was because there was a cafe inside
and it was a really nice piece of architecture, and
it was a pretty big
place, not a big mountain, but it
was on top of that and you could see the view from behind.
If you look at the back of this building, not just this building, you
can see the whole cityscape. Right, right, right, right, right, right, right, you can see the whole cityscape from the
location of this building.  I
thought that the reason why they made this into a garden and
placed this building here was to see this view,
and that's what I thought.
ACTISgoodingALL
fromGoogleI I think this makes
sense too, but if you look at this, you can see
that hill.  I can see that they're putting it there,
right, if you look at this, yeah, we had this together, yeah, we had it, we had it, F of H cocoa, yeah, hot cocoa, H My Itook, nice photo, very tasteful, I took it with the wall, this, this, this, this is amazing  The decorations inside are
really stylish, I
thought this was the Baroque style, it was really nice, and the
Baroque style is, to put it simply,
something with a lot of decoration,
and things like dents and bumps.  There are a lot of
things that stand out, and the pillars and such are quite classical, so it
was fun to look at each and every decoration, and it
was nice to be able to have tea here at my leisure.  It was the most luxurious thing ever.  I
felt like a princess, it was so good. Yes,
yes, yes, yes, yeah, that's it.
That alone gets the point across.
Mangan, I went
through this park and then
hurried off to an art museum.
Art, art. Yes, the art
museum this time was
something,
something.  It
was interesting to see how someone important used to live like this. It
was interesting, I loved it. This time, I
borrowed a guidebook.
There was Japanese in it.  I
really wanted you to listen to it,
so I said it a lot.
Listen, listen ...
So I asked her, "
Why? No, that's
German.
" "Have an epiphany in this museum?" "Ririka, I had an epiphany." "What did you
have an epiphany for?" "Ririka, I
wanted to be a princess."
There is a princess, there is a princess, Ririka, behind you, she is
becoming a princess, no, no, this is already, you know, I
'm on the phone, I
want to buy this chandelier, but what should I do? I'm
already on the phone, I'm on the phone,
no, I
really want it,
Shide  wasOne
usceAllThatbutwas
fascinatedbyallthe
chandeliersandfrom
thisdayonwardsShe
lookedatlikeeverywhereShelookedforchandelierseverywhereandthenShereallyWANTEDONE SOWediscussedthewholedaythewholeeveninglikeohIwantHowmuchthisonecostandShewaslikeohI wonderHowcanIgetmyhomeINJAPANTolooklikethishowcanigeta
chandelierlikethisforNot
just chandeliers, but also doors and
things like that, you said,
andPCYWhat was it called again?YeahShiki and things like that,
yeahTableware  When I saw all the tableware, it
was so cute and beautiful and gorgeous,
and I really wanted to live here.
This place is like a dream, it's really nice, I
can see Baroque architecture, I was so
happy, but after Baroque architecture
comes Rococo style,
and there are some plant patterns in Rococo.  There were
also a lot of furniture from the Rococo period. I've
always seen things in textbooks that were like, "This style is like this, and this is what's on display,"
but this is not the case.  I was
really happy to see it in front of me. There was
furniture and paintings here and there,
but it was nice, I wanted to sit
there. The legs of the table were curved.  This
is a characteristic of Rococo furniture, but I was
really impressed to see it in person.
So, this is where some
very famous and important people in Austrian history
lived. Do you remember?  Yes,
Maria Theresa van Josef, the
emperor lived there, and
many people lived there, and there was a woman with long hair.
That's right, that's right, Elizabeth,
Elizabeth, famous, famous, Hass
Franz, yeah, I remember a lot of recipes too, and this
woman, that woman, you know, her personality
was interesting, you know, I heard something about it
on the audio guide, do you remember, right, right,
right, do you remember?  I
didn't want to get married. Marriage
is hell. I have to be with a man I don't love. It's the
worst. I
remember it. I remember it. Whenever we met, he would complain about it.  It's
like living a suffocating life.
Yes, it's the same. Yes, it was real. It
was real. I was telling you my true feelings.
So, I guess that's how it is. I
thought I understood. Yes, yes, yes,
was EXPLifestyle and
of history of people Who live there and
actually pretty interpersonal
becausethe
personality of them
was explainedand
reallyLeaves a good image of what they were like and was just
like
quotingthestuffthat
heardintherereally
interestingSoI like
this
museumAfter that, we
went to the Christmas market.  It
was big, and there was a skating rink or
something. Yes, there was skating, and there was a merry-go-round and a skate park. Yes, it was fun. [Music] I went there many times, and there were probably several.  I
think there were about 3040 of them. I
bought a snow globe here. Oh, that's right. We
also rode the snow globe. It was fun. It
was fun.
[Music]
What was it again?  I
know what you mean by "spectator" in English, but it's a
round and round merry-go-round and a
jet
course. It's a round and round fly, or a round and
round fly, or
a Fris is difficult. Ferris is a
wheel, right?
[Music]
Being was
When I went to that Christmas market a few times, I got
a little emotional,
but I remember one word that Chiara said, and when I
saw the two of them, the light, the
way the light hit them, the atmosphere, and
All the memories up until that moment  I
felt it for a moment and my eyes almost started to tear up. I really
love both of you. I'm so
happy to be here and that you're having fun. I
think today is the best day ever.  I
felt like I had become close with those two, and I was happy. I felt like I had friends. I
was happy. We
were walking with our arms around each other the whole time.  Die, keep
walking
around like this,
CROSS other ARM,
know me, just say that,
when La-chan left the Christmas market,
when she headed for dinner, say that, it's
so embarrassing
Until now, I've
been living for someone or something, but now, I'm
living for that person. Let's
go full out.
[Music]
Sweet that SA that
Me Scream We Walking from
Marfin hours
like up until Now I
lived my life for other people
people or for other things and ifeel like I have been really
living my life properly but right now being here ifeel like for the first time I actually living my own life something like that and I was like w really am I'm so happy I'm so happy it was so intense yeah yeah but really I
think it's better to be good yeah yeah because of that experience yeah  I just ca
n't say it anymore, what can I say?
The world was so terrible,
there are so many different people, there are so many
different places. I looked
around thinking, "Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, explain it to me."  I
guess that's how I feel. I mean, when I
look at the world in textbooks or on world maps,  I
don't think it's that big, but it feels like I'm slowly expanding the world on my own two feet,
like I'm exploring the world. I think
going beyond the ocean is the kind of experience you
can have.  I think it's a journey that I think of. Yes, I
think Ririka-chan understands that too. Especially Ririka-chan. Ririka-chan has
been going abroad since she was a child, so she can't really think of it as
something amazing or foreign like Laden-chan.  I do
feel like
it's a waste, but really, Japan is an island nation,
so it's hard to go outside, or I
think it's a little stressful, but I think we
're all the same human beings,
and it's really warm, and I think that, you know, where we were born,  I
want people to know that we can share our hearts like this regardless of the relationship. We're
already really good friends, you
know? We've
even talked about where we should go next time.
aboutheartionabout
being
HereIfeellikeifyou
arelikenever
travelingIftheType
ofpersonWhoeverLeavesYourCountryWhichisverycommonforJapanesepeopleandeveniftheyleaveTheyjustgotolikePrettyCloseCountriesmostofthetimeslikeIthinktotravelovertheworldifyoubecauseitOP
[Music]
[Laughter]
Change
Explain
[Music]
Something diedWhen I was having funAhh,
I can explain itIt became like a Resident EvilIt was
like a Resident Evil
When we walked together it
felt like a horror game. It was
fine, but it was called a horror game,
but it was fine in its own way
. It had a nice atmosphere.  It was
really an adventure.
[Music]
DARK mum Weber
surrounding his
Palace and Gardens there Still like many things that I wanted to see for the mand Show them but Everything was DARK the only thing that was lit up was the big gloron top of the
hill and the Palace but there is actually
so much more around and  waslikehingthatwecouldStillkindmoretheywecouldIRwouldtakepictureandlookbrighterthereWewouldoutATTwasDARKWell, it
was too dark, but there were still a lot of things I hadn't seen yet, so I
wanted to show them to you, so I tried to shine a light on my phone to look at them,
but instead, I saw Ririka-chan and Rane-chan
But the photos I took with my phone were
brighter than when I saw it with my own eyes. I
looked at it a little bit. Yes,
yes, that's right. It
was much easier to see with the camera.
It was so dark that I couldn't see anything with my own eyes.  But we
all walked together in the dark with our arms folded and it
was really
fun. We
talked about all sorts of things. That's right.
Food.
Food. Japanese.
But also for people who weren't Korean.  I know it's popular and they
serve delicious food,
so I
haven't been there much, but I wanted to take my daughter there and
eat Australian food there.
Tae is the Pi photo photo photo At that time,
I was sick and couldn't eat. That's
right, that's
right. I came to eat with everyone, but
I got sick and had to stay outside for a while.  I took it
off for a while and
asked if it was okay because it hadn't come back at all. I
thought it was because it was a walk outside and it was a senior.  I was
crying a little bit outside and
said I wanted to eat dinner with everyone, so I
'm sad. But I'll show you.
Um, this is okay. I've
put a mosaic over the dishes and tableware,
so I think it's okay.  The
hands are different,
so this is the waiter's hand. The
waiter did that
for me. But I drank this soup. The
soup was super delicious. It was really delicious.
Let me explain from left to right.
leftisfamous
austrianfoodthat  It's like boiled along a good chunk of beef meat with some vegetables and soup and
stuffed with a piece of meat that you eat with greens. It's rice and soup, and that high quality meat is cooked for a long time and comes in soup, but you take the soup out of the soup and leave the meat.  Yes, take the meat separately and put it on a plate
and eat it with the potatoes.
And then there's this green sauce, but
this time it wasn't grass. In the first place, the
sauce didn't come, so I
wonder why.  I wanted to eat that sauce. Yes, I was
interested in it, but I forgot about the sauce.
But it was fine without it. The
potatoes next to the POThat are rightNext to the PITareACTfor theTurbspitz are
actually potatoes for cinnabar.  It
was called "Passley, a potato with lots of butter on it." It was called "Kenoma Gras." It's
not the "grapas" type of "pasa," but it's not that kind of noodle. It's
from Austria.  It's
next to something like small noodles that you eat with it.
Yes, Shinil is Rurika-
chan. What do you eat it with? Yes,
this jam is here. Um, hey, hey, what was it again?
Wait a minute, I remember, Ririka-chan.  The
name of the jam is
Lejamuugaberry. It's very
important, so it's decided. It's a
berry, right? Lingonberry. I saw the memo. You found out. You
saw the memo too. And you just told me.
Kiririka-chan, that Lal-chan ate it on this day.  I
didn't have any, but I ate it the next day too, so
please tell me what you both thought. It
was super delicious. Have you ever eaten something this
big? It's made with meat and you eat it with jam. This one on the left. Yes, yes,
this is what I thought at first.  I thought meat and
jam would be good, but no, it's a bit... I want you to
try it even if you think you've been tricked.
Yes, this is really delicious, the meat's
juiciness and the sweetness of the jam... It's a
miraculous marriage that
shows up in your mouth.
Then,
please tell me the difference between winning and not winning.
This is really thin, you said you hit it like this and
flatten it out, right? That's
right, at first I
thought it was fine or something, so I
ate it without putting any jam on it.  So I started making
jam, and the jam business started. They said it was
okay to make it
just the first time, and I thought, well, I want to
try it out and see what it tastes like, and I
did that.  I tried it and it was
really crispy and
had the right meat flavor and was delicious. I was
thinking, "I wonder if it's good with jam on it?
" but when I put it on top, it tastes completely different from pork cutlet. It's completely different.  Yes,
yes, but it's not just the size of the meat, the
batter is also completely different, the
batter is that fluffy type, it's different, the
bread around it, right, right, right, right, right, right, the
panko is different, right.
It's so fluffy and soft.  I
think it's light and fluffy, and I think lemon goes really well with it. I
like Rika and go to a lot of
tonkatsu restaurants, but I
don't think I've ever put lemon on it.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I
was thinking about whether this would go well together, but
yeah, the sourness of the lemon, the
sweetness of the jam, and the juiciness of the meat all
go together really well. That's a
good explanation. That's a good explanation. It really helps both of us.
Surprisingly, Licca-chan also liked the one next to it,
Gracie. Oh, I liked it.
But it had a unique flavor, and you said it was paprika.
Right, right, paprika. Right, right, I
thought it was tomato at first, but then I
thought  When I put it in my mouth, I
didn't taste any tomato at all, it
was quite a mild taste. Yes,
yes ...
timeate
on enI
enjoyed it the next day. That's right. Oh, I'm
getting really hungry. This is not
good. I
said I haven't eaten yet. Yes, I
haven't eaten yet. Is it okay? What time is it in Japan now? It's night, isn't it? It's
23 now.  What
happened at that time
? I couldn't finish cleaning. I was
in the middle of cleaning and I thought, "I don't want to do this anymore,"
and I rolled around on my bed.
[Laughs] I
wish I knew. I
could just get some cheese from the fridge. I'm eating it now.
Okay, let's eat the cheese from the fridge, right?
TheCheesegetthe
CheeseafterthatWeGotHomeIhadtreswiththeUbermessingaroundwithmestupidUbernotComingUberWetooktrainsbutthenWejumpedOUTBecauseYouKnowickUwiitminutforSTUandjustdrivesmeandWRtomeIdrovepastyoucanyoulikeWalkToMeAndI
saidYeahButthetodriveawayandcancelOnMeI
screamed so much, didn't I? I got mad, didn't I? I
was at a station where there were no people
Seriously, I waited for 10 minutes and the car
passed by where I was,
so Meji came and asked me if I could walk over to him. I replied, "Okay, I'll walk," and
the car just kept going.  Then he
cancelled me for 10 minutes in a row.
That happened again. Uba
, seriously. I
was really angry. And Rade-chan was feeling
sick so she went home early. That's
right.  Yes, I was still feeling
groggy and
so I was feeling sick just wanted to get US Home I Bad just messing with me finally I gota new
ONE but
that yeah it was delicious it had a gentle taste it was delicious
no no no no I don't need
osechi it wasn't delicious but it
tasted like herbs and I liked it  I actually
have some herbal tea that I bought at the pharmacy at home for when I get an upset stomach,
and I don't think it's particularly tasty,
but I thought it might be okay to make it for Raden.  You
drank a little bit, yeah I listened to it, I listened to it
a lot, the next day I was full throttle, I was
like, yeah, it was good, I listened to that tea,
yeah, thank you, at that time,
no, I was exhausted, exhausted, yeah,
THENEXT Day feel
better, the end  That day was good, that La-
chan got better,
and when I wrote this note, I realized that there was no bad place,
so I
wrote a lot of things. Yeah, that's right.
OK,
let me, my alled right, I had a lot of things
on Day, we
started out with
breakfast at
a
just, but it was really beautiful. Yeah, it was
bad. Mia  What was it called? It had chives or leeks
or something on it. Yes, there
is a photo. It's a good photo, isn't it? This, this, this, this, this,
this, this, on top of the bread. It
looks like a lot of stuff on top, but it's actually a proper photo.  There was a name, right
? What was it again? What was it again? There was something, I
looked it up. Yes, it's
chives. Chives, sweet chives,
chives. Yes, it's the name of this dish, right? Sweet.
No, the name of this herb is the name of chives.  Is it the
name of a herb? Yes, I'm
not wrong.
I know have
bread, goodie with butter and lots of simple wanty gentle flax. It's not my favorite breakfast, but it
's a simple way of eating raw bread that Austrians like.  It's delicious with that batter
and a mountain of chives on top. You
can try it at home, but the bread is important. I wonder if you can make it. There is
n't much of this type of hard bread in Japan,
but it's quite common.  Well, if you go to a place like Paya-san, you know, there are
probably bakeries in Austria or Austria-Germany in Japan, I
think, I think they were crazy or something, I'm not sure,
but yeah, yeah, yeah, it's crazy, somewhere, you know,
here and there  There is one, but it seems like there is one.
Yes, yes, yes, so look for that dark black Schwarzbrot there. It's there, so hohohoho, let's look for it. It
was really delicious so I want to eat it again.
What is that cream cheese-like thing on top?
This is butter!  It was
like margarine or butter. In this
case it was butter. Yes, yes, it was delicious.
Fu, yes, Piof, I think this was Ririka-chan. I
also took a picture of this Ririka-chan thing.
Eggs Benedict. Yes, eggs Benedict were really good.
Also, this is usually served on bread.  I do
n't think it's the same in this world, but I
think it's probably what it was, usually it's a bit more
toast, I
think it can be put on the British bread, but I
think
it
has an Austrian version,
and that black bread  It's on top of a
muffin. Eddie, it's delicious. The normal one is ah,
that muffin bread. Right, right. Right, right. The round one.
Right, right. So, in a
way, this is the Austrian version.
[Music] It
was delicious, but I've had two eggs since this morning.  I
couldn't eat a single serving. It was delicious and had a lot of
volume.
Rade-chan had been saying over and over again that she
wanted someone to eat that
simple meal. Yes, we
ate it together.  Bread, jam, butter,
Those are poached eggs.
There are many different kinds of poached eggs,
but most of them are put on bread with jam or something.
The bread we have here is called
bread.
[Music]
In Austria, there is something called A.  Yes,
yes, yes, yes, I eat it at home too, no ...
Put it on
top and put the jam on top and then again, yeah,
yeah, I was thinking of how Rade-chan was
doing it and I
tried to cut the bread in half, but it did
n't work at all.  The
bread was already falling apart
so I just tore off that piece of bread and
ate it. Yes, it was good, it was good, it was good, I cut it from the middle,
what, what, right in the middle, what
did I try, I tried but I couldn't do it.
IFIT was a bit clumsy
quitefunnyWhenIWaslikestartingtoeatwasalittlebitfastershealreadystartedlikerippingTHEBREADapartandthenkindoflikeEatingEverythinglikedifferentlyfromHowIwouldeatitandIDAMitIshouldhaveexplainedittoherbeforeShemessedUPTHEBREADsothenIstartedIwaslikeLLlookThisisshowyoudoitandICUTThroughofBreadinthemiddlelikeNicetoputitintoTwotwopiecesrightTRstruggledHardCuttingfortheBREandintereshowyouknowculturesarediffweatBreaddiffNo, it
was difficultIt was difficultIt was deliciousOhI want to
eat thisRiThis is
not itBut I made itEhThis simple thing  I
wanted to try the simple one too. I'll
try it next time I go. I think it's
good. I think it's good.
In Australia,
there is something called a neck disc.  There are
2nd and 3rd districts, and
in the middle there is 1st district.  The
next place after the 1st district is the 23rd district,
but it's not in that order, but there is always the 1st district in the middle. There
are already mountains of great buildings and important buildings in the 1st district,
so for now, while walking,  I saw a lot of things
from the outside, like City Hall, the city
hall, Parliament Hill, and other places,
and the photos were really amazing. The
government office, the government office, the government office, and then there were the members of
parliament, weren't
they?  Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, the first place I went to
was the city hall, right? Yes ...  I
went. I
only saw it from the outside. I couldn't go inside.
Oh, I see, I see, I see, that gold color
was a little bit.
[Laughs]
That's right, only one part was decorated with gold,
but for some reason  That place was
n't decorated in the same way, so I asked why, and they
said maybe the ink had run out.  I
wonder if they ran out of money. It was interesting. It was interesting. We just went.
All Things reach by
Walk middle District there. Some things like the PARLIAMENT this is the PARLIAMENT and When Wereach edit I pointed out that There is some parts where they They I think they just like renovated it For The Longest Time and They finished now but there is a part where you see Golden Elements and then IT just stops and you Wonder did They run out of ink or the color The Golden COLOR or did They just have no name anymore or did They try it and WELIKEN We Need This does look good inter Ian All like up there Around the ceiling and stu like that you see it to understand it I understand We to of buildings and there also like museums some of them Oh, that's right, shops  I think I
entered the
museum. ...  It
was a museum store, but we
didn't see the museum.
[Music] We
bought that cheese on the last day. We wanted to buy it,
not everyone. We just wanted to buy it.
But
I was taking the exam, so I thought I'd buy it on the last day, so it's
not helpful, but if you look at it when you're in Japan now, you'll
remember it. It's here, it's
here, you can
hear it, it's in my hand, it's in my hand, it's on the microphone.  I
won!
It says that I
saw a lot of Christmas markets on this day. I saw a lot of them. They're
in all kinds of places. Christmas
markets are everywhere. That's right. My
favorite place is
But it was in front of the city hall, and
they
said that it would become a huge, huge ice skating rink in January or February.
Yes, yes, yes, they've already done it twice.  Yes, it
was alreadyThere was
like ICE skating Ring
therethat becomes
even bigger lateron
like mostly Christmas
Market Now and just
a Tiny ICE Ring and later  The Christmas
Market is like
downsized to like 10% and allofit the whole ICE drinking place ICE drinking ICE skating
place takes Over Amazing
you
understand You have to betheres of unbecause I do
n't think you can understand how much fun it is
even if I explain it, but I can tell that it's fun.
And I'll wait and show you the photos. Wow, I wonder if they'll be good photos.
No,
everyone, ice skating,
can you do it, can you not do it,
have you ever tried it a little, oh, this, this, this,
it's good, um, okay, I'll
show you, um, I do
n't think you understand, but I'll make it bigger once, it's huge, when you
see it from above  This is also
amazing.
[Music]
Ah, it seems like the second part hasn't been done yet in the old version,
but on the right side, next to the government office,
there is a big skating rink, and there is only one part there now,
but it should be two.  You can go up to the upper floors
and everything is connected, so there are
a lot of narrow paths in the back, and skating paths,
so you can go all over the place.  It's
fun, yeah, it looks fun, yeah, so
cool,
isur, yeah, oh, and then next is, yeah,
Stefan Fischin went to that
famous church in Australia,
yeah, it's a really conspicuous church, Rane-chan said, it's really huge, it's
really amazing, and then Stefanji, yeah, it's easy to understand,
Tenji  But this is an amazing building. The
exterior is colorful, and it looks like something I've never seen before. There's a
barrel on the roof.  It was
decorated with amazing colorful ornaments,
and I thought that was really impressive. And I
also thought it was the first time I'd ever seen something like a scientific design on the outside.  I
thought it was amazing, and the Gothic architecture inside
was amazing, really amazing, so high.
What's so high about it is that it's so high, so high up to the very top,
but when you look up, you see
this ball, it's pointing upwards.  When you look at it, I
think there are some places where the roofs intersect like this.  The
vault goes down and is connected to a pillar, and
the pillar extends all the way to the ground. The
architecture from the vault to the pillar is so beautiful, so beautiful, so
beautiful.
But, yeah, I like it, and it
was really detailed, and there are all kinds of pillars,
and they look like thin pillars bundled together like this, so they're
called bundle pillars, and I
think it was the first time I'd ever seen a bundle pillar.  I was so happy I
thought this was it and it was super fun It
was a pillar of Ota Machine
Gun
Architecture Otaku
PfromGoogle is seriously amazing is
n't it I could look at it forever Beautiful Yeah it was really amazing nyan Thank you
Lare-chan is doing a great job That's
right later  I can talk for about an hour.
Damn, I might fall
asleep after talking for an hour. It's
okay, I
won't fall asleep, I'm just getting started. I
think it's okay to talk about architecture within my own framework. I
want to hear it.
[Music]
Want to
America, yeah, this was crazy, right? It was
amazing, the priceless synergies lined up in a row. Oh no, if we
break this glass, how much will it cost
? We all went in trembling, saying,
What is that glass over there?  There was also a glass shop, and
there were various vessels and things like that,
but
Stand
was
has Ririka-chan, I didn't want to go in at first,
I was pushing for it, let's go, I
got some good information, right, yeah,
yeah, the price is  I
was surprised because it was so expensive, but there are times when they do half-price sales
and there are even deaths in Japan. I
guess you should try it out. I
guess you can't buy it even if it's in Japan.
Half-price sales.  So let's buy it. If it's half price, it'll
be about 2.5 million yen. Let's
get the electric Lilica-chan Lilica-chan bed. Next, let's get the chandelier deal.
Ah, that's right, let's get the Syria deal.
[Applause]
Wait a minute.
There are also some in Japan.  I
went to the Swarovski store. Yes,
Swarovski is a store in Austria. Yes, yes, I
learned about it for the first time. Yes, I saw a lot of them. They were
cute. Uchiuchi It was cute. Yes, it
was really good. And finally I reserved
USperfIfound
Japaneseguidedtours
with
persontheStateOpera
wehavereallyBeautifulOperaand
neverJapanesebooked
allan
people
WRgroupsattimeThey
havelikethink
SpanishGroupEnglish
Group French Group Japanese Group All kind of languages and They All Start the same time at the time and I wasting All Japanese E
PEOPLE are
wondering this White
Girl
Is That
found that Australian opera house,
and I
found a Japanese guided tour of that opera house,
right, that's right, that's right, so I made a reservation,
but at the same time  The
guided tour started in various languages, Spanish, English,
French, and French all started at the same time,
but I was the only one in the Japanese group.  I
guess not. Well, I guess I
might be a white person born in Japan.
There are people like that, too. How was it? It was fun. I participated in a Japanese tour of the Burgburg Theater, and when you go on a tour,
I do
n't have any knowledge of opera, so I didn't understand that. I was
told that this painting is based on magic, and that this painting is based on Mate, and
the architectural style was also
explained.  And so, you know, I
sat in a chair in this opera house, I sat in a really high seat,
right? I sat in the highest seat, and I was like, "Waah!"  The
view from there is
really something there,
wait, it's really far away, wait,
look, turn it up, yes, I found it, I
found a photo of Ririka and Laden, oh, Laden-chan, oh,
Laden-chan
is there too,
sit down there  I heard that
it was really fun. I
'll send you a picture of it later.
This is it.
There's a room where you can eat, a cafe, etc. Right,
right, there was a room.
This is the ceiling. The ceiling of the room where you eat. The rest area. It was
really beautiful. It was really amazing.
Each and every painting.  But the story of that opera, I guess you
could
call it a story, is it a scene from a story
? I thought it would be nice to have coffee in such a wonderful place.
tolikeoldstyle
Beautifulpiecesfor
EXyouknow
mozFLIknowEnglish
is
yeah, it's in Japanese, remember that famous one by Malt?
Not Majikumate, but Asouma.
yeah, yeah, that's right, yeah, yeah, yeah, Malt is Austrian. By the way, yeah, I didn't
know that. I want to be surprised.  Yes, he
was my best friend.
He's lived for thousands of years. I
thought he was really good at Japanese.  The
Japanese that foreigners use is the
same as the English that Japanese people use,
and the pronunciation, or the
intonation, of the sounds is always
different.
But Hara-senpai really
does speak with the same intonation as a Japanese person, which I
think is amazing. I've
had to speak to him in Japanese for a while,
but I'm not sure if I'd be able to.  The
two of us are so
happy. Thank you. But the like had I had
better
pronunciation but I think
HIS Vocabulary was
atleast this topic I learned well Better Vocabulary would say I thought so. Thank you. Ah, there were also some photos of shopping. Well, um, I think this will be good too. Ah,
this is the thumbnail photo.  Yes, yes, it
was beautiful, it was super beautiful, this is it, seriously, it
was beautiful, wor, cute, it was beautiful, the night scenery,
yes, it was like snow, it was really really
tiny, fluffy, lots of them, yes,
this is light, right?  It's not a  It's
not a chandelier, but it looks like it's waiting for
you. That's the DIY Sharia.
Just like that, you can decorate a Christmas
tree or something. If you
DIY it, it'll be
fine. So it's small and pretty, but
if you hang it on the ceiling of your house,  It's so weird.
No, no, no, if you have a sense, you can make it beautifully.
I see. Seriously,
someone please help me with that chandelier project. And also,
Sowenton Day I
went to Mima on that day, and every
day was like a completely different art.
That's right.  Yes, that's right, this one
was pretty good, yes, this is the
Artinamim, this one was a little more
modern, please explain a little,
Lare-chan, it's modern art,
it's a museum that collects art from after the invention of photography,
mocon
ARTNeverBeenmumlike
actually
sosoWe would
know
placeIt was nice to
seeI saw some nice photosYeahYeahYeahYeahWell,
how was it?
Well, this museum
has a lot of things, a lot of paintings, it was
amazing, but it took a long time.  I didn't
have time, so I was in a hurry,
but there was Momo, Picasso, and I love Laden.
There's a guy called Gian Miro Miro,
but I didn't know that at all.  I
was really happy to see the works of Milo. I was really happy. I bought a card. I was
really looking for one of his works.  I
didn't have a post card so I was looking around and
then I saw the magnet corner and I
won the magnet I wanted. Yes, that's right.
All
have much time much see and wasting time. How many hours was it? One hour, two hours. Yes, but I
think I was there for about two hours.  So, even if it was 2 hours, it was
already running,
right? Yes, the shop is closed, right
? Ring wen thour Butit
was Cling Time after
hours So we RUSH
Through We alsowent to
the shop the girls
really wanted to buy
stuff We
See, I'll show you one that I like. Chiara said, "It's good." So this is the Shah-Shah-Shagall that came out. As soon as I saw this, I said "Shah-Shah-Shah." There was also an exhibition of Chagall's work.
Yes, this is the one I saw there.  Well, at
this point, I realized that I didn't have much time, so I
rushed through it. I
couldn't buy any goods, so I ended up spending the whole
day there.  We
went early saying "Let's go" That's right That's
right It's important We definitely wanted the goods
The two of us Yes Memories
After
we went We
both had fun That's right Yeah It was the
last one so we went again  I wanted to eat it, I
forgot to mention it,
but I wanted to
show you the delicious things I picked up at the Christmas market the other day, so
this is a dessert, right? Oh, right,
these were really beautiful dumplings.  In it,
what was it called? Was it apricot?  I
think it was apricots growing there.
Yes, that's right. It was like
breadcrumbs. It was like panko. It was
delicious. It was fried in butter
and the sauce was something like plum sauce. It was
like this.
Seriously, it's my favorite store dessert and it
has all kinds of fruits inside, but it was
delicious. It was delicious. It was delicious. It was
really
delicious. It had some kind of big cinchona seeds in it.  I
know, I know, it's delicious, it's
sad if it's not a large serving, right? It was
delicious, it was sweet, and it was the best.
from
apride and I Really
Love
breads really THE BREAD crumbs and I was like Y This is I think every a an that eats this always Wants a lot of Breadcrumbs with this se some how They
Amazing you
kind of like GRILL them with
somebutterandmakethemevenyummandthenthereplumlikesaucethereontheSideToso
good
EnjoyIt's getting betterOh, this and this, I
forgot to show you the
drinksOh, this, this is the drinkIt's the
drink at the Christmas market, this is
itYes, this cup, like a mug, is also
very cuteThis,
at each location in the Christmas market, this  It's not like
that. I remember the design.
Yes, I can take this home with me. I think you
can take it home with you. So I gave it
back and the money was  But it
's a bit back about 5 That's right Yes
Yes Yes Wedranksoone
ofthiswasItriedToFindlikedifferent
variationsalwaysSo thatthegirlscouldalwaysTrytherelikesimilaronesalwaysbutORIGINALUNonesSo
we
hadChry
punCherry bounboCherry bounboIt was, wasn't it
Hot Cherry's A
Ga one [ __ ], wasn't it Bo, it was
delicious  What was the analogy? Ririka-
chan is caramel Ririka's wings
Caramel Yeah yeah yeah
Kirapan
WHhave
that I drink the one without alcohol every time
But I didn't really have any alcohol,
but there
were a lot of other varieties, so I was looking for something a little different to drink every day.
Yes,
caramel punch and
cherry punch hot.  Wine, right?
We drank it. Yes, yes, bebe, it
was delicious, it warmed us up, and it was the best.
Yes, it was good. Yes, the atmosphere was also very important.
Going back a little, the conversation was, yeah, and then Yeah, It was
Lovely, we had like
on each Day, we had So Much To Do, especially on
this day, was packed, and
Ifeel like, We bonded so much, We had very DEEP conversations,
especially in the last
dinner, DEEP
conversations, Where I
thought, I was
surprised by
the Things that Connected
with two people, me  I don't know if you know what we're talking about,
but especially
during our last meal, I feel like we found a lot of common ground between the two of us.
You get it, I get it, I get it, I get
it, I get it, I get it  I
get it, I get it, I'm glad to hear that. I
think we're surprisingly alike.  I
was a little happy, wasn't I? There were a lot of surprising similarities
.
Went home after that and packed my luggage.
Yes, and then, on the same day, I got the Sachertorte and ate it.
Yes, lastly, it was delicious at night. It was delicious because it
's the home of Sachertorte.  I
thought I couldn't go home without eating it.
Yes, yes, it was delicious, it was the best. It wasn't just a chocolate cake. By the way,
Rane-chan understood. I
think she was the happiest. Ririka-chan  That
's true too, but I think that
Austrian desserts in general are
n't too sweet, or
rather, they're not too sweet, and
I'm not really a big fan of sweet things.
But even so, it was really
delicious and I ate it all up. It was so beautiful and delicious. There was a little bit of
apricot jam in the middle
and a little thick chocolate on top.
What was it called? It had a name.  It's not
just chocolate, it's
coated with chocolate, and the
chocolate isn't just coated with chocolate, it's
a bit crunchy. It
has a nice texture. The
perfect amount of crunchiness.  Ah, I
thought this was a real Sachertorte. It was
n't explained first, but it was
like it was somewhere between crunchy and crunchy. Yes, that's right.
This
was good. Glaage. Ah, it's
glacage. That's right. It's called glacier's.
Glacier's. Yes, glacier's. Glacier ...
Names like Shahs, you know a lot about it
, you've really researched it, you know, the texture is
really different, yeah yeah yeah, the jam is
like a delicious plum, this cake is
exquisite, I'm so happy, I ate it,
Laren-chan otaku talk
It's really good, I did it, the All Love report is amazing, oh, oh, I'm waiting for the Zahar project, no, no, no, I'll accept it, oh, I saw Think All, I saw it, right, so, it was such a wonderful three days, but in the end  Like
What are your thoughts, both of you? Really, really, I do
n't know, I
've talked a little about Europe before,
but it's even more intense than it was then. I've
had such a quality experience.  It
was the best experience ever, and Chiara-senpai and Ririka
really helped with the translation, and it was so much fun
that I wondered if it was okay to have so much fun.
Thank you for making the plan.
Thank you to Kia-senpai for helping me and to Ririka for translating. I
was really happy.
Thank you for setting up that forgotten item. I
forgot something. I didn't forget anything. I did
n't forget anything.
Ririka-chan, what do you think?  Ririka
has been abroad a few times with her family and friends, but
this time she went to visit Kia-senpai's place,
and it was like she had never been to a
foreign country before.  This was my
first experience of being
guided by someone like that.  I
really took every mode of transportation, like the
bus, yeah, I took every one,
yeah, I took every one. That's right, I guess you can't just
look it up in books or on the internet, but there are
parts that you can't get to know, really,
these past three days.  Even in such a short time, they
managed to condense everything
so that everyone could enjoy themselves to the fullest,
and I really felt that Laden-chan was really
amazing in all sorts of ways.  I was really
touched and it was fun, but Ririka-chan also loved chandeliers. She
became a chandelier girl, and Ririka-chan
is a chandelier girl. She's a chandelier girl, so it
was really fun to walk together and we were all
really friends.  I was
so happy to be able to go to so many different places,
so I'm really
grateful. I was born in Austria and have
always lived there, so surprisingly,
this time I went to a few places for the first time, like the Martial Arts Museum, and the
opera.  I had fun too, but  What
made me happiest was that after those two
said they were going, they actually came this year, which
was a miracle. I
got along well with them and it was the
first time I'd had a friend in a long time, and they were really great
friends.  I'm happy that we were able to do it, and I hope that from now on, the
three of us
can do lots of fun things together in Hololive, and I hope that we
can do good deeds together in another place,
and I wonder what that story is all about.
I've got juniors who listen to me about all the hardships of work and stuff, and I'm
really happy about that. I'm a senior, so I
get along with everyone, but I
get along with everyone in Hololive, but there's something
deeper.  I'm so happy that I was able to make it. I
love it. I
was just saying
really happy like I
enjoyed The Trip of
the course to but I was born
here I was raised here
So I know Most Of These
Things even though I Saw some Things from
the first time too but
more than that more
than anything just
Happy that I was able to
GROW
so close to them and Find New Friends that I can talk to and you know We can also continue
traveling to other places Perhaps in the future so looking forward to that These Two Girls are so Precious and They so of unto be with They bring so much like JOY and PASS to we go and what we do So Ifeel like our Yes our harmoursyy was really good I guess it was the synergy between the three of us The trip of the three of us
was fun I think it
was fun Thank you See you again  Let
's go, let's go to all sorts of places and
thank you for everything. Let's go to Super Super
Dapa. You're imitating me.
[Laughs] It
's so cute. Next time, how about going to the Maldives
or a trip to Europe? If you ever want to go on a trip to Europe,
I'll come with you anytime.
Call me, yeah, of course, yeah, anytime,
shouldcallmewhenwck
morePER I
hope you all and the people in the chat enjoyed our talk, and I hope you feel like going to Suria, that's
great, I want to go, come, it's a
really nice place, yeah, Australia  Please
love me more, more, more. Yes,
yes, that for
today. Let's
end it here. Yes, yes, yes.
At the end, Chiara always says the German greeting,
but can you say it? Can you say it? No, it's
not that.  It's difficult, right? I can
say it, but I'm Avidin,
so leave it to me. I'll tell you the performance. Yes, I'm confident. We
say,
okay, perfect,
super ...
]
[Music]
N