[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
hello everyone can you hear us okay
hello hello my friends are here
[Music]
thank you
with me in comparison to the others yes
[Music]
mike deck one can i have some food
please
give you some steak oh thank you oh
thank you thank you
sounds good
hello hello hello
thank you for the steaks i was waiting
for those
huh yeah all right put him away i don't
i don't need him anymore i'm making a
weapon
oh wait where is this girl dudes in her
house
my house if you guys have weapons we
and you have like any xp i have some
stones here you guys can use and you go
into this basement and you can enchant
your weapons
if you guys haven't done it yet hang on
a sec
i tried it earlier today
whoa wait did you enchant your uh
irons my what your iron sword
oh yeah yeah yeah no my iron sword i
didn't
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
girls do you maybe first of all want to
tell the viewers what the hell we're
doing today
yeah what's happening today even i don't
know even i have no idea
we're going to the another yes yeah
we're first making another portal
and creating some weapons and then we're
going to the never
together and all going to die yay
[Music]
i'm trying to adjust my i've never been
there before what's it what's it like
what kind of things happen it's very red
with lava
cali cali bring a bed
and then sleep in the never because it
gives you like a buff
it gives you a it gives you a buff that
makes you stronger for like uh 20
minutes
really yep yeah okay cool yeah i'll do
that
i'm level one i can't enchant anything
now where is my bed it must be in the
house huh
i make one do you want to chat something
girl i can do it for you
uh yeah wait wow
27. laura it doesn't take away it takes
away your level though
you know it just takes a little bit oh
okay
eight nine twenty seven yes you enchant
my bow for me
of course is that
so everything is pirate language so um
that's cool i want that
okay girls they're both unbreaking oh
i thought i thought it had never ending
bolts i thought that was another
it's random i think
or maybe
all right i'm gonna give you guys a
piece of gold armor because
yes it depends on the person yeah it's
per player it changes on purple air okay
that's cool please
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i
have a little bit you can't have the
boots because it has a curse of binding
and i don't want okay i should wear them
because i don't know i don't know if you
can take them off to your pants or a hat
a hat
[Music]
oh wait wrong way i'm just pretending
this game is all about pretending so i'm
pretending it's the golden snapback
oh i know this channel nick oh my gosh
you know i want a gold pad oh got the
curse of vanishing i don't know what
that is
this is vanishing it's like harry potter
right
yeah yeah i thought you were still
enchanted where are you
does anybody want shiny pants ooh i do
are they free
yeah i'll take that shiny pants yes i'm
very behind in this game because i don't
have time to play games
yeah it's also been a while for me fine
haven't we got
you know people like the hat
the hat will disappear on desktop
[Music]
is everyone okay what's going on she's
having a
crisis over there uh-oh i don't know
what she's called for hello
hello i don't know i hear screaming
there's a skeleton over there he's just
kind of oh he has an enchanted bow he
might start shooting at us
it's like
yeah really get it hey you mother f word
oh my god
no more cursing guys no more cursing
from me oh yeah
[Music]
he doesn't like being called stinky no
he doesn't i'll get him oh no i'm using
the wrong weapon hang on i don't mean to
use uh oh oh no i just threw with my
pickaxe away hang on
where'd it go it's gone i lost it it's
gone forever i got him i killed it smoke
yeah okay and i just killed a bunch of
those
crazy horses i need a pickaxe
what the [\h__\h] is that okay i just
you have an arrow in your head watson
you have an arrow in your knee and in
your hand i hate that wait why do we
need pickaxes
traveling what's in my hand
we're mining again the nether apparently
there's a lot of gold
ah okay never okay
i have a question um so
i had how do i hold things in two hands
and how do i switch
between there's an enderman right there
what's the button you wanna
you can scroll through your your hot bar
like the stuff on the bottom
is that what you mean yeah but i uh you
guys are holding things in two hands
right
oh yeah yeah so if you if you press e
and then you see there's like a little
square on the right side next to your
feet
that's like a equip you can hold it
together
again hand i like the way you were
saying it before you like hand
oh really i didn't notice my left hand
um oh my left hand apparently you can
just press f
to switch them okay between the two
hands
okay um i only have one slot and it has
a sword in it
um yeah and then you can you can use
your hot bar on the bottom and you can
scroll through other stuff okay yeah you
got it sorry i pressed what
i have no memory you're doing it you got
it but i
hang on oh the idiot idiot i got you
want to switch your hands
you can press f oh sick okay
understood understood
i was i wanted to say an announcement
really quick yes yeah
the apollo rail is now complete
[Music]
oh nice it took so long i'm at the
thing on your roof the thing on your
roof looks amazing
oh i see it now i see it now that you
said it i
[Music]
how do we build this portal i have
obsidian in my hand do i just complete
it
uh i think yeah yeah where did you get
the obsidian
from i mined it with a diamond pickaxe
that i made
damn what is this how we will access the
nether
yeah what is that is that okay if we
leave it there
well if it doesn't complete itself then
we can get rid of it
do i make it one block taller i'm making
baby cows hold on
i think okay i got i got the music
yes are we going right in i
think
look at everybody glowing over here
wait are we guessing how we went five
tall four we're breaking out the weekend
okay yeah one more what
i saw i need one more thing
uh this and this is this
okay stop volume
need a weapon i need a weapon okay now
maybe
oh i gotta remove that block i think
okay wait so
thanks guys so now i just do this
yeah and then just remove that
pickaxe i don't want to go get okay oh
my my clothes my house is right here
okay ooh
bgm off yeah bgm is off i'm playing um
i'm playing the minecraft soundtrack
from
the internet because
i forgot about music i think we're
talking so much we don't even
we don't even need music i think my
minecraft doesn't even play music
though i guess it'd be best to play what
do you guys think that's what i've been
doing
hey where do you guys hit your shields
iron and wood oh okay cool i'm gonna do
that real quick
do i even have a house i guess it's over
here
i don't really think i have a house you
gotta build one
yeah i guess so huh i was thinking about
i was thinking about flying
down this mountain
what do you guys think should i flatten
it out so we have more room to build
yeah right here wait what not
i'm gonna flatten this out this big
mountain what are you doing kelly
i'm looking for my chest i know i had
one i mean yeah it
no you only have a crappy table okay i
mean
i guess it was over by the netherlands
okay
it's
[Music]
no problem thank you yes you need a
shield
yes i will create the shield where was
my house again um
it's i think it's gone oh yes my chest
is here but i have no house because the
creeper blew it up and then i got tired
build a new one i'm gonna build you a
temporary house
just live with me i would keep you safe
i'm good i'm gonna i'm gonna throw this
iron i know that i have iron
iron
[Music]
can i make shields out of anything else
by chance oh i need
i need arrows for my bow i got some
arrows
oh i have feathers you can use too oh
wow you know you made it like a farm
down
wait how do you make it
i'll make a chicken find that carrot
leave the chicken time today
and iron something maybe iron nugget i
don't know
i give up this is too much i can't this
looks so cool
you need assistance help
[Music]
gosh back in the day
i'm a nice tennis racket oh no i took it
again it's not a tennis race
drock look behind you yeah
okay thank you sorry you had to make
that for me
in your hand and your sword and the
other yeah okay
besides big axes and swords what do we
need and food
sword pickaxe food uh callie needs a bed
um
i have one i have a bed i have it i tell
you wonderful
first okay okay okay yeah
don't don't forget your bed okay you
want
you want feather i i have 10 shots and
then i'm
screwed that's not a lot that's fine
whoa
there you go you have sticks yeah
one second when you get the feathers i
forget how you get feathers
skeletons chickens did you kill chicken
oh chicken okay i need to kill chicken
i need to kill chicken uh do you have um
pointy rock
pointy rock yard is that an actual
item because that sounds like pointy
rock i don't know what that is
it's a flint oh oh yeah i have a bunch
of flint
here poised mr peters
have you seen bradley and his family
callie
no i haven't can you introduce me yes
come come this way
thank you i want to meet them
is that your voice you have
dogs how do you get that
what hang on hello thank you
it's interesting actually because every
every time that i call an
animal or for example a dog or a cat a
default name i always call them bubba
but because because watson has a dog
named bubba everyone will have bubba
everyone will think that i'm talking i'm
talking about that bubba
hello bubba oh cute
they look at you like you're the mom i
want someone i want kelly
to look at me like that
kelly why won't she
[Music]
i love your dogs i think i can kill him
uh he can't get in the three-way he
can't get in the the door so if you uh
i don't know he's gone no he's right
here but he can't get
we gotta get him to stand in front of
the door because he's only he's three
blocks tall so he can't pass under a two
block
oh you're good
i feel like it is gonna die no no no no
no no no no i got this
listen oh wait you guys are in line
aren't you
now we're at my house right now gude is
trying to kill the enderman i think
sounds really odd yeah something sounds
strange
there is water on the wall over there
why is that how do i harvest my
my my crops oh just left
my hand you just touched it which
reminds me i need to
put the weed this is my home from now on
this is my home hang on i'm just gonna
come out
you have an extra carrot i could have i
have some dirt yeah
for my carrot form oh okay thank you
put some dirt on them awesome i also
have beets if you don't have any beets
or melon i have melon
i have beer roots oh wait what
beef roots beer roots fun
someone's playing this this is my
swimming pool this is my swimming pool
now
has someone claimed this area i think
it's mine now
okay this is a swimming pool yeah it's
it's in here already for me
nice i think he's gone ready
scared him off i think i did huh
my home is perfect well not yet but it
will be
sorry i'm just very excited let me know
when you guys are ready to go by the way
i don't want to hold us back oh i think
i just have to
let me open the uh open lookie africa uh
no
not yet i have the rest okay okay okay
oh wait it's just the one block right
yeah well done yeah yeah i'm just gonna
step away
get prepared probably should make a
couple pickaxes huh
oh yeah we need that um maybe we should
craft some materials yeah
i will help shortly in just a moment it
is dummy
yeah it is dummy oh
there's a gap in the wall what's on this
side that goes outside
evil witchery of disappearing my house
is big
oh it will be big uh let's bring in
hey do i have iron nope what do i need
flint and steel for i've never used that
for anything
um
i thought i knew that but i i don't
remember something
something another is there water in the
nether no
no no no lava lots of lava
[Music]
you write them
you can walk on uh lava with striders
what my renovation is done for today
yeah so if you see striders we can uh we
gotta get some stuff but then we'll be
able to ride them they're funny-looking
and then look at my pool everyone isn't
my pool wonderful
anyway this is my house congrats on the
new home thank you
whose house is this what is this is this
a farm this is not very safe
very cute not very safe house
it will be i'll i will format it later
when we're not visiting the nether i
don't want to hold us all back from
visiting the nether
you need a big guy i do
but uh
[Music]
yes i just need to put him i'm just
gonna drop these rocks who has a llama
what yeah i still someone has a lot
from the merchant no i
borrowed sounds like you stole it
[Music]
yeah that's fine i i don't have a
problem with it
i want a donkey hmm yes
okay okay i will go to the gates okay
what is this tall building
it's my farm the farm what is this what
is
a blast oven
wait wait i need to make a does anybody
have a pickaxe lying around that i can
have
[Music]
anyway uh yes now my chest is protected
thank you for whoever put
a lot of protection around my chest you
know i think i stole your llama
huh i think people are saying that i
accidentally came
to your llamas my llama
okay
it no a little tap on the butt a little
tap on the ball
all right are we ready to completely
ready now
let's go ghost riders ready to do put in
the last block
hopefully this is where i've en history
here yay
let's fix this up it's happening it's
happening
here we go
[Music]
i think i know what you need you need
that little thing that makes dip
and then it's there what uh what
what zip blended steel anybody have
flint and steel
i do oh okay here let me drop it oh i
will
oh it's in my box what do we what do we
like right click with it and then it
like does like a challenge
we're gonna light it on fire yeah thank
you pretty much somewhere
i'm useful for something here i am here
hold on there you go
okay pointy rock yeah
you got it
i shall make us our first ever
never portal are you ready
[Music]
what happens in here the fun
all the fun i'll put it okay in one of
your chests i'll put it in one of your
chests okay
okay how do you hold up a shield by the
way
right click oh okay you gotta do that
like if somebody's shooting arrows at
you you have to you can't you have to
block it and you walk really slow with
it up
yeah okay it's not just like a passive
thing you have to be yeah
okay gotcha
oh don't leave the flint chad says do
not leave the flint because we might
need it to get back
oh okay and wait i get it again i'll get
it okay okay okay
can i imagine if we could never return
i'm gonna bring the rest of the obsidian
with me just in case we need to make
like another portal or something
we can do that right it'll like lead out
to somewhere else um
does someone have shoes shoes
yeah shoes yeah
i notice they're missing shoes i can
make issues
[Music]
yeah i have one okay perfect are we
supposed to
sleep in the nether really yep yeah we
have to save it just
in case uh we die oh okay
that doesn't sound right in my brain
well what do you know about
minecraft i don't know that much about
minecraft but that's something someone's
telling me that
there might be a little bit of trickery
going on yeah i have a weird
feeling right now i don't like the way
that you guys are saying
like awesome thank you
today are you guys trying to mess with
us
why would we i just
we just wanted to go well just want to
have fun
yep yeah i like that i don't think
i'm only sleeping in the nether if if
you guys are sleeping in the morning
i'm totally sleeping in the never i
brought my bed
see it's another slumber party okay
all right who wants to go first you can
do the honors
no no no all right i got this
let's go all right
[Music]
what is that i've never seen that before
no no do you see
[Music]
it looks so fun down there look at all
the friends with weapons
is that is that good basalt can we use
that for something
bath salt basalt
coordinates in it
i think like one block of another is
like eight in the world or something
like that it's like multiplied yet oh
that's not great
i don't like that gold i'm go up there
um i think something to
just to keep in mind i i'm not a
minecraft uh encyclopedia but you see
these pig people down here
uh-huh they uh don't touch them they
won't hurt you if you don't hurt them
okay
okay oh okay yeah just like in my home
they'll see me and nobody's fine
i want this goal oh my god
what it's fine huh be careful
[Music]
i think we're up pretty high there wait
who is up there
ahmet what is that you justin what are
you doing
i want to get the gold and the ceiling
here's gold oh that's
i guess that is gold huh you guys we'll
go pick it up
so there's pig people right that won't
hurt you but there are other types of
characters that will hurt you
yes
but the pig people will hurt you if you
are close to them
and mine some gold i think
i think that really if you're far away
then they don't care but if you do it
like somewhere close to them they will
follow you until you
die there's more gold we should go down
this way
okay just lead the way okay
wait i'm tired hi
you're making friends with the lava boy
he's cute and he is cute i wonder what
happens
i like him i want him as a pet can we
bring him back
yeah how do we get it down there
oh wait we need this and a mushroom
maybe build a stairway it's hard
build the stairway down it's okay we'll
figure it out
um
[Music]
look at him the white oh
what is that okay maybe we should go the
other way
oh yeah i think so maybe
i knew this would be happening i knew it
when i saw him i knew it it's a guest
apparently they're called just
yes i want to see it
and what music is nice is anybody else
here no i have uh
i had my music oh yeah
lava slime
oh we're still high up should be
somewhere
what is that huh should we set a scoring
point
how do we get anywhere everything's so
vertically okay parkour everybody yeah
yeah that should be easy where the
the red rock is what
oh oh there's a guy up there with a
sword why do we need
yeah you guys be careful it's going the
other way you guys
wanna come
say we can all dig down on this but is
there going to be like a gap underneath
if we go down
straight down does everybody know to
hold shift
be careful stay on the block oh no i
didn't know that thank you
yeah yeah prevent you from falling yeah
i'm gonna i'm gonna dig it down over
here okay
digging down oh boy okay i'm gonna go
i'm doing two blocks at a time
yeah two block it's good two block is
good
not that you suddenly fall down that is
very possible
oh see there's one i have fellas well
this music is amazing
wow hey guys how are you doing where'd
you guys go
like inside here oh
did you make it here oh yeah right here
hello i'll put a light here so we know
where we're some gold
lava
[Laughter]
uh-oh
[Music]
okay i'm fine i'm fine
i have food does anybody need food water
is useless
well that makes sense doesn't it how do
we put out fire if we get caught up
caught on fire
don't get caught on fire oh no they're
friendly right they're fine
yes friendly oh they're friendly until
they're not
exactly this gold is far enough away
from them no
no don't take it don't take it but
they're not even that close
they're coming up hello don't let them
leave we'll trap them in
here they don't want any trouble
listen
oh yeah we'll find enough gold somewhere
else don't worry
there's nothing yeah we should set us
one point guys
well this this area is kind of nice if
we if we want to just
make this the the place no beds
that says no bed why i have one
yeah be my guest they said don't
okay play they want you to not get the
the buff
you know that's crucial what happens
what happens when you sleep
you get a 20 uh armor buff
yes you're lying speed boost
you're lying no what happens
get out of here no no don't try it go
what are we looking for in another what
do you do here
yeah well i think we're looking for
materials
what kind of materials i want soul sand
oh oh [\h__\h] she's doing it yeah i do
wonder what the um oh man
i mean wait where which way are we going
angry oh wait strider okay this is the
way we came from
oh there's the bed no don't don't let
them out don't let them
oh oh oh i'm sorry i didn't know i
didn't know
wait okay this is the way we came from
yeah look for the little lava board i
put a lantern here so that we know
oh yeah
[Music]
so what are we going to do oh i got gold
nuggets uh-huh
you want to go down here stop down here
if you want sleep
no who's going to be the uh
i mean who's going to be the uh i mean
who's going to
kiosk
we'll pick you up from home but you
should maybe take my stuff and then give
it back to me
okay wait let me get a good angle ina i
only trust you with my stuff
i don't like what i'm hearing from chad
please thank you for watching
phoenix two swords your phoenix five
pick axes
set a spawn point okay that makes sense
they want us all to die all right
bread and uh potatoes and it's not gonna
happen one mushroom number two
fourteen quarts oh yeah take take this
take that take this take that
take this a shield take the flint steel
and this is whatever what's up here
whoa do you have it done yes hello thank
you ina
are you guys ready to watch this he's
blocking my kid out of the way oh god
this isn't gonna be good
yeah he's ready i'm ready
i'm doing it i'm doing it okay
hey it was nice knowing you all
bye-bye alligator
wow fireworks
intentional
[Music]
even the pigs are like what is happening
what a wonderful day
just blow up a path for us
[Music]
exactly really death does not scare me
so
i'm i can do i can do it again and again
gotta stamp out the flames oh [\h__\h] i
have no gold armor
quick give it to me give it to me give
it to me oh wait where are you
get here uh here oh wait they don't even
think they're really good
boy they're supposed to attack me oh
thank you oh wait in here yeah yeah
there you go
oh yeah
there's a path down this way
[Music]
i think that was worth it right that was
totally worth it thank you yeah we we
got an easy way down
i needed to see the path over here guys
it's another my swords you know
i have two sores and a bread
uh bread yeah thank you
i think it's yours oh
[Music]
do you have my shield inna oh yes
uh oh yes what's that noise noise yeah
well what is that it's the guest it's
the the big floaty
thing oh hey this is
[Music]
thank you chad what is it
i want this for my home
my new home in the cave a fortress a
biome
you die for the sake of the people and
they just disappeared
[Music]
no it sounds so cute go go go can we
fight it okay
yeah i don't have a bow
is it is it is i think it's just
randomly shooting or is it oh
i think that it knows that we're here so
it's going to try and actively
come out oh yeah
well we can go this way uh maybe we can
come i'm not close enough
yeah do your worst yeah let's go this
way
up the stairs okay i'll go i got yours
like a pig
hut hey guys our friends
because you might catch on fire i'm in
full health
all right okay there's a lot of fun to
go
i'm on fire now no what
well oh well if i'm gonna die anyway i
might as well give it a try
[Music]
intimidating nice yeah yeah they're our
dominant
yeah you guys see this i don't know
what's going on
oh oh and are those the glowstone
thingies
there's gold here but there's a pikmin
oh yeah there's a forest over there
let's go that way i think we can build a
bridge
forest a forest there's a yeah we can
build a bridge here
a bridge yeah
another rack
i'll leave this to you girls um i don't
want to fall down guys are good at that
team seriously wow i'm impressed
it comes apart so easily you have to
have so much gold
yeah you'll be okay
so what happens can we make another
nether portal does it exit out somewhere
on the other side
but it will probably be really far away
from where we came from
like super far really
in the outer world right
beautiful now what how do we get down
uh if we hold shift we can't fall right
right that's what i thought that's what
i thought callie
were you wrong uh i don't know maybe my
finger's slipped
get more rock here look this is it's
possible see
hold on no no no
is this far away enough from the piglets
to to get the gold
guys chad it's the btf the music is so
loud for me there's like music in game
and it's like wow
that's like special special another
music oh my gosh
yes please minecraft
go go
what's this red rock is it different
bush wait what is this
hell's wart
red grass oh [\h__\h] oh wait i have pirate
game hold on don't listen to what i'm
saying
what pirate game i like i like can i if
i take this stone
and i take it back to the to the real
world i want my walls to be
we should we should probably try to go
back after we collect some of this stuff
because like
uh if we collect too much and die it'll
just be like
pain no big waste it will be a pain
pickle
so collect as much stuff now and then
we'll go back for like a few minutes
there's another another party
what is that is that a light stone or a
hair oh
yeah where are you shooting down where
is he
shroom light what's that sound you hear
that literally yeah
that shine oh
i heard something ah i heard something
explosion that was right behind me
fight me on the open yeah yeah don't be
a coward
i say as i run away
[Music]
i want to garden with these plants
here like these ones
wait i thought they saw a fortress i
want to go to the fortress wait this is
wood
trees oh what a cutie hello who are you
oh are these villagers oh
is that pumbaa
it looks like there are other people
here they don't look uh nefarious or
mean
maybe they're very smart i i have a
sneaking suspicion that the pumbaa is
not so friendly
but we shall see
ah i kicked
chat says they are hostile so maybe we
shouldn't go say hi oh
we just take over a little one dominance
all right cool i'll help i'm behind you
there's so many of them it's fine we'll
be okay
well it's easy see they're all equipped
with swords so if we taunt them
and we get them to come at us then we
just knock out the bridge and they fall
hey
[\h__\h] boys
[Laughter]
come over and fight us and you want to
fight them oh
we can give gold to them and maybe
they'll be friendly let's try i have a
bunch of gold oh yeah right oh
all right i'll go wait what's up
huh i was i was ready that i was ready
to shoot the title
all right
okay yeah we're here to help i don't
have a i don't have a bow and arrow
though so i'm gonna have to
wait that's really far hold on i'm not
prepared do you believe
i don't how do i give it
[Music]
they're not aggressive actually if you
give them gold they give you some items
back i think
and one of those items could be another
girl
you could you could get another pearl
from them but the i don't know how high
the possibility
are and he looks at it and wow legit
oh what did he give you i got i got iron
boots
damn i can't wear them because i put on
the binding
boots by the way we want iron
[Music]
oh
well i'm glad that things ended
peacefully but
i'm warning you only don't mess around
with us i'm ready to start swimming
thanks chad i'm no coward
i also want to try the katja i want to
do the kacha the cold kacha
all right here's your hair who wants
here
guys come back
oh thank you yeah you better
do i just throw it at him thank you what
do we do with it
give it to him but right click on him
right now crying
right here right click where's chiara
here oh
no wait wait here we go thank you
wait come back oh wait come back sir he
took it away from me
i hit him with it oh my god oh he
dropped his gold sword
why did you kill him i can't take it oh
another one
okay all right
hey i'm gonna try this guide to machine
i want to try two but
right are they the best when i did the
right one
up a shield instead when i right clicked
so i left clicked and it hit him with it
i wanna do gold captain i didn't give
you one here
yeah the the piglet took it right away
from me
thank you can we kill this thing they
try to pick it up
okay so how do i give it right here take
this uh hold it in your right hand
and right click on them okay now give me
something good
now i'll kill you i'm going to guess he
gave me a meatball
i have something too it gave me [\h__\h]
come back
maybe we should build a portal here i
got crap
he gave me a meatball what am i supposed
to do with amiibo
what did he give me oh look at the
cuteness
[Music]
i don't know i got something ah is it
he's running away
water bottle yeah
thank you i need to put my he's dead
okay wait did not drop the harpoon
though
or what is it the crosstalk water bottle
i got a water bottle what does it do
gotcha don't you run away oh wait
you little wait what does this do wait
hold on
that's right
thank you chad thank you wait do we know
how to get back i can throw this spicy
meatball uh
oh yeah here's our bridge okay our
bridge is here
[Music]
hey so the meatballs uh it's like
throwing heartburn
when you throw the the the the the spicy
meatball they give you it makes fire
uh oh oh what what's that
it's fine i got it hey flying split come
here let's play
i'm ready to party look at this wide
open terrain i will fight you
in hand-to-hand combat come here coward
bring it squid
well you dodged my bullets
up bring it squid
i'm just getting the way back for us
really quick securing it
okay it's coming back yeah bring it
that way what's one this
one oh nice
that's mine that's mine i gave it to him
i gave it to him
give me something good what
what hello oh little one hello little
one
the noises they make are so interesting
hey come back
it's so cute hello a quartz okay what
are you doing
you're too young to hold a weapon
hello where do i get the soul sand
maybe it's a different biome i got soul
sand
is it something good oh you got some
yeah i got it uh for gold i don't think
that was
sorry i did go look for more gold i
don't think we could take the gold
from here what are special errors is
that good
what are specialties my site's swinging
twitter instincts were kicking in i got
something really great apparently
i got something amazing what did you get
i got
ten ten spectral arrows and the chat is
going like pog pog
pog wow what do those do
i don't know arrows you can't see the
person you shot that's all it was
oh there's like walls oh we can't we
probably can't mine these gold darn it
yeah we can um i'm addicted
and then we can find gold on the way
back i'm addicted
give me something just build gold yeah
are we gonna go
here you guys want obsidian
my house
crimson roots i like them this is like
eyebrows
this is playing like this what is it
worth the world stuff
i like it yeah
okay i wanted to save my actually i
guess i don't have to say my gold if
anybody say anybody want to go again i
have three left
i have some i wanna i'm gonna milk them
for what they got let's see what you get
give me some stuff wait gotta jump kyle
you wanna go again
yeah ender pearl you're dropping here
okay why is he running away from me
trying to pick it up
what's that give me your pig wait that's
a bow
okay give me your head and your crossbow
yara i got another piece of gold but you
gotta come over here
thank you no wait wait no over here okay
over here
thank you gold dealer did you just
amma is the dealer for everything he
robbed me
[Music]
yes i think so yep oh okay let's not do
that
what did he give me yeah enough did you
take my item that he gave me
oh do you guys see this huh you guys
gotta come see us
you guys gotta go see this where are you
where are you how's that go down
[Music]
what what does a chicken do in the
nether
i got a dead chicken he's riding her
i got crying obsidian what is that
chicken doing here
look at that
[Music]
look at him riding on the chicken are
they
chickens in the neighborhood it's so
cute
it's very rare
[Music]
you guys want to build a portal here and
see where it goes yeah yeah
yeah i have one obsidian by the way give
me something good
come on how much two three four
one two three four four friends
i like your gold storage little one oh
me next one
sweet stride
[Music]
yes i will do let's
oops
sorry my bird brain is uh not being
activated three two one go
[Music]
oh
we're in some sort of cave oh
funny
[Music]
outside area that we never saw before
like a nice
new biome oh wait wow why are they
totally really far in
oh i put it i put it yeah i haven't been
here oh we are
deep oh i need that
[Music]
i mean just really far in the
z direction exactly keeping the ground
hey guys should we sleep now
we might be might be underwater
everybody get ready to uh
swim no this is like a scent or just in
case you bring your floaties
[Music]
[Laughter]
suffocating biceps something i have
experienced before
oh sorry i took here where's the face oh
there's watson it's gonna be the ocean
sandstones making me feel like it's
gonna be ocean
yes okay thank you thank you
what could possibly go wrong no it can
also be a
pyramid or something like that i died in
one before
whiskey experiments clean tuck
we should build a pyramid how cool would
that be yeah we're not going
down we should be pretty close to the
surface actually right now
yeah yeah yeah i'm struggling hold on a
minute
i didn't know where's him i'm okay i
just can't i can't climb i can't play
this game
um it's okay
no i'm sorry i was trying to find the
stairs all right it's just a scratch
it's fine sorry all right i'll be the
caboose
i'll be yeah just
i think we're close to getting out the
sand is usually
light oh yeah oh
no no no this happened to me before this
happened to me before okay
okay we're okay we're okay no one is
dying right yeah yeah yeah
okay we're fine it definitely wasn't my
fault
okay ah we did it
whoa where are we ah
[Music]
i need to i need to keep mining so i hit
you okay oh the desert
oh hey hello
oh we are really high up whoa yeah no
wonder it took us so long
looks like dystopia like we came out
into the store oh
oh good here
[Music]
a gold can we take it yeah i should have
brought my diamond pickaxe
fireman stick oh gold hey
i only have can we get can we go in this
portal is it like continue in the lava
right
what's in the chest i took it there was
a shovel and a hole
yeah yeah yeah yeah give me the gold
i can't it's too high up hold on i'll
build a way uh
oh what is a village
but this one is too long i think we got
a oh yeah
oh no no it's fine it should be wait a
second no it has to be and i'll see you
once yeah
yeah we just have to get rid of these
two blocks we're not going to be able to
save it but we can remove it and then
replace it
does anybody else have an opinion
apparently we screwed it up oh really oh
there is yeah
we can no we can still we just have to
get rid of this it takes a while
i don't think so is this one that i have
in my hand different
amelia you can't mine it oops
no no no but maybe we can make a new one
with the obsidian we have it works
we don't have enough obsidian to make a
new one i have three i have three three
oh okay i have okay guys uh three
three six eleven wait how much do we
need in total it's
four by what is it
right one two three four five six seven
eight nine
ten eleven twelve thirds
some people are saying it doesn't work
the one that i have yeah
oh the bright obsidian doesn't work
which way did you guys go
uh i know that way
the way you do it hello let's just leave
this place
yeah yeah wait okay we can come back to
it to retrieve it
which way did you go yeah there's a
temple over here
a temple hold on did you guys enter the
chest yet
no i'm gonna empty it what i'm doing
here guys
dude mine the what where are you guys
you don't need the corners oh oh
oh yeah but i only have five blocks and
kiara here how many did you have three
three oh uh but they're not the glowy
ones right it's just regular obsidian
it says obsidian okay is it trap you
might be able to build it then
let me try where are we all right we
already have them here in the floor so
if we do
you guys said we don't need the corners
so does anybody have tv
i'm lost why are you in the desert dude
oh i see what you okay come here come
here
okay i can just do it here then
okay so like this
no i have to oh okay i see i see
i'll replace this with sand
[Music]
no yes this is right that's right
this seems like a difficult problem
it's like a puzzle well then
it's okay i'll i'll do a mock one okay
this is one two
three oh and then we don't do the
corners so we do
not the middle mine is then people say
orange and then
all right now just replace
the sides so one two three four five six
seven eight right guys it should be the
one this isn't this is long enough
he's fine they said chad says yes yeah
this looks great
imagine if this was one higher on the
ground then it would make sense
yeah i have to coordinate somewhere i
took a screenshot i have the right
amount
all right kyra i'm waiting for you ah i
think i see it i'm coming home
i got lost a little bit but i'm i'm back
almost
i think it's like a real i'm i'm there
i'm there
i think i see it are you
wait um uh
what do you guys need the cornell see
you i have the coordinates i have the
coordinates
no we already tried to use this one that
we built but we can't mine the obsidian
so we have to try again because it's not
tall enough
um uh yeah
and we don't have a diamond pickaxe with
this because i didn't bring one because
i was scared i was gonna lose it
yeah see him good i'll bring it with us
if we get back home
because like uh i have more diamonds
it's fine yeah see him
[Music]
oh wait that's just the bunny and give
us your coordinates get uh
i've been trying to say i'm in a pyramid
could you hear me yeah i was trying to
look for guda but then i got lost
a cat yeah oh yeah there are cats yeah
oh but that's a bunny that's a bunny
there are cats though in the desert i've
seen cats i
am a paleontologist
that's a dinosaur person though right
yes
oh my god the desert is like endless
what discovers mummies what are they
called historian mummy mummy tissue
i'm an excavator that's a truck didn't
it what
probably i mean they stole it though
okay
um what should we do we gotta wait for
[Music]
i was trying once i heard there's a
pyramid i just had to run for it
please yes of course i love you very
much
[Music]
now let's try with the flint yay
me too me too let me in okay looks good
okay we're going back in yeah or last
time
the little one is still here yeah we
didn't really go five before
we didn't really go that far
yeah we only went up i just didn't want
to go back down i mean we had
[\h__\h]
but we came back in from the same same
gate because we put
look at these guys jumping oh ah oh this
is the same
ah if it's too close if it's too close
and it ends up being the same gate
oh that's what cali's looking at hello
okay
all right well you know the way back to
the home in the world in the cave
okay what cave what the cave we uh
we uh we started what
are these all right i know the way home
[Music]
yeah this is right this is right this is
right yes yeah how's my crafting
toy hi guys thanks for being so chill
ah they weren't bad dudes all right i'm
ready to fight
there's another i'm ready too yeah
he's running away all right i'll let you
freak out
cowards cowards
got him all right
i'm gonna make burgers out of that pig
nice okay all right there's a bridge
here we'll follow this bridge
smart anime ammo is so reliable honestly
out
it's like oh such a wait we go back up
this way
she is the detective yeah
i attention to detail watson yeah
and be careful on these stairs easy to
fall
wow okay one at a time just take notes
that's good care of
us bridge
like we're like following the mother
bird
so amma is a bird too nice
i'm not the only one eagle
oh yeah this is where kiara blew up
sorry yay
let's do this still burning wait
[Music]
there you go
i did not get any gold because i gave it
all to the gata
that's okay i think it's fun too i was
going to get more gold to give to them
what i found this one
doesn't make friend goodbye friend i
hope i'll see you again soon
bye but i'd probably hurt you
we did not i mean the only person who
died is me right
and i died on purpose yeah exactly
wow we're making like progress how many
times have we died
last time too many and there's another
man
golden sword benjamin
it's not the one that's mad at me right
i don't think so
enemies here don't seem as big of a deal
after coming back from the nether
i hope i'm dying right now i gotta smell
my chicken no you leave inna alone i'll
kill you
i got him oh no down you go
thank you
how are you getting that sweet mushroom
i did it i'm so unorganized
[Music]
oh did you kill them nope they're just
walking around they're chilling can you
make me
hurt anyone yeah you should be able to
stem oh whatever that is sorry i'm like
a door or pull door
i'm working on my house now no you can
oh
yes you can okay oh i see
dragons in the sky there's those guys
there's there's no phantom sleeve yeah
phantoms
what mushroom wait
maybe we should sleep one night just now
yeah okay
goodbye let me find my dad all right i'm
in my bed
just a moment here for now here
i'll sleep i'm
okay guys i'm gonna take the i'm gonna
go get us that strider i'm gonna go
bring him home
oh yeah yeah bring stuff to like capture
those dudes
it's a good idea saddle and the mushroom
and stick
what flavor mushroom does he eat though
oh
i have a bunch of mushrooms i have got a
blue one
a brown one and a red one
depends on what flavor they use red
these the blue
mushrooms ah you got a blue one
the one don't yes do you have one of
them
i have one yeah yeah that's what he eats
apparently
okay so i don't i don't know who
i guess he dies if he's outside of the
lava oh i don't know
in there i mean that's still pretty good
can you i wonder if you can make a
little pen
hold on right or something all right i
brought some fence
wait well would catch on fire in there
you put it down
uh i don't know
interesting gardening setup whoa
only this is in your lava okay i'll
bring it i see you damn you're a
professional
we should make a little house in the
nether outside of the
portal oh yeah that's good yeah i'm
impressed with some materials
no no beds no beds you know
just like furnaces and crafting tables
everything's so fancy damn your
ah no i didn't mean to do that i can't
oh i can't stand hang on
high ceiling because i am tall oh cali's
house to be
yes i'm working on my house
welcome ina i'm still in there yes my
pool
do you like it it was here when i found
it this is for your organ not you
[Music]
well we can just build a house in there
and then like
okay yeah it's it's just like a square
house
okie dokie cool yeah in another yeah
yeah a safe house safe zone
yeah wait i mean do you have that
mushroom wait oh yeah i got it like that
night yeah i got no blocks
yeah three hits all right three shots
easy
[Music]
is
in has got a crafting table i can use
this one okay here
uh i want to use these blocks hold on
there you go i want to help
you guys polish fire
[Music]
can we put gold armor on the strider
uh is it the usual
what'd you call it the usual like horse
armor
it should be different armor isn't it uh
okay
i guess yeah hi everybody
are they standing in the lava what are
you looking at
yeah they're having a nice little bath
it's like an onsen for them
yeah they're just chilling at the
hospital
later losers we should make a hug
[Laughter]
[Music]
what did you do to him he he's just a
little anemic that's all he
just needs a nap and he looks cold ah he
needs lavender maybe he needs lava
oh he's cold he needs lavender take him
to the lava he's fine
he's fine oh my goodness he'll be good
he'll be good oh he's probably oh he's
faster
he's faster now i see okay i get i
understand why
you're standing there i have an offense
if you want to build him a little
paddock
maybe we can build him a path hey girl a
lava path
yeah look huh
can you walk on magma rock because that
might be
we can perfect it later but for now yeah
thanks for your service buddy he's cute
i know right maybe we can connect over
here too
oh
[Music]
that looks like a nice house damn did he
leave where'd he go where did the spider
go
oh he fell he fell
oh i know is it my fault he did dead
i hope not he died rescue him
i'll go all down where is he
rest in peace
and we're going this second oh dear oh
god no not look
[Music]
sorry my my keyboard is in japanese okay
hold on back to the game
okay the eagle has landed
it's okay okay okay we'll find him oh
he's alive
okay yeah he's as long as he's alive
it's okay
wait but how are we going to get him up
here i'm i'm making an oh fancy
wow yeah well i have all the material
when
[Music]
nice door hang on
uh our neighbors are here neighbors say
hi
oh i haven't gone i'm out of uh
oh um i have a pickaxe do you want mine
okay oh yes thank you uh yeah
is it okay thanks
chest okay i'll probably save her friend
from
my house i'll be amazed thanks
we'll get them we'll get them done
oh yeah you do the same yeah
[Music]
right below okay so as long as you make
your way down nice and easy you'll be
fine
all right i'll go save our friend oh
that looks cool
hang on okay
um this is gonna take some brain power
but i got it
done
oh i think we can only give the gold to
the villagers i guess not these random
pigs yeah
i tried
there's probably a roundabout way to go
let's just keep moving this way
maybe i can make some stairs wait hold
on just kidding
okay no i can't there are no stairs that
will be made here uh it's okay
i'm gonna move to i'm gonna move this
way until hang on
it's fine we got it what if i can build
actual stairs after this
is that soul sand nice
no way way way beautiful house ame
thank you beautiful you've got some good
taste
we're making progress you could be a
architect
oh thank you architect watson
no i didn't die i just came out to get
some wood
[Music]
are making their way to save strider yes
is that his name that's what he's called
you can name him if you want though
i like that it's okay
you don't know light up the rings wait
let me get it on camera
okay um
getting getting closer i bet i can put
uh you made that jump
yeah brave isn't that bad i know
i gotta save our homie oh should i
extend the i have two more chests should
i put it
um just a minute
culture is he moving is he on the move
i mean
he can't be far he's not getting far
right
yeah yeah he's dead no he's not he's not
dead
[Music]
wait what's happening okay he opened the
door did he just watch it we made it
we made it down what's
[Laughter]
hello i come in peace fancy i wonder i
wonder if there's another village that's
closer
whoa i guess that one we found is the
closest one
yeah oh you called that no
i found him oh i hit him in the village
i'm riding on him but i'm i'm on fire
i'm on fire
[Music]
yeah i caught on fire i found him but
then i caught on fire
uh i don't know where i am
um uh you're probably oh it's fun
ah
are you okay good uh you're fine we're
fine we're fine
did you die you play calm we're calm
we're calm we're cool collected we're
calm we're cool
i'm scared okay oh we're fine did you
die because of you
no no no no we didn't panic we're good
we're good i'm scared i don't want to go
down there
i don't know
[Laughter]
sounds good this area is familiar i
don't know where i am but there's a
village i'm going to go look in it
wait are you holding it i don't know
where i am actually
go to a high place and look for the h
and that's the entrance to the tunnel
and you can just take a mine cart in
there from uh
the emergency exit i need to get ready
okay
do you see the h okay uh i'm in a
village hold on a sec
right now hang on are you i'm good i'm
good i'm with strider and i got cali
stuff
thank you you gotta you're gonna have to
move my friend are you gonna be here
where are you yeah how are you like can
he jump
i see a house i i this is a rando's
house
i don't know how i'm gonna do this can
we swim
up lava probably not right
so it is all my fault i'm sorry no no no
no no i'll just
park him down there i think he'll stay
there probably
wait i should have my pickaxe here yes
yes
yes yes yes hi friends
[Music]
i require assistance no where are you
where what's going on that's nice
don't panic don't panic don't panic oh i
guess i can't
get out of here okay um assistance is
required
in the netherlands oh i'm okay are you
okay
i'm okay give us your coordinates
i'm right outside i can see all your
names um i um
there's a gas do you see oh huh
oh they're on fire oh wow you guys take
out the gas
that's why i saw one but it like went
away i see it
um it
getting closer to the pig village
because there was the path that went
sort of in this direction
over there she's down there well
over there i don't think our friend will
leave i think we can leave him here so
i'm just gonna
yeah just park him there it's his
parking spot
yes that's a really far far a parking
spot
hello can you guys clear my uh headspace
here
oh you're good oh wait it's good okay
yeah yeah
okay nice then we got a house
we got a panic room and we got a portal
i'll be
back soon i'm on the way oh wait i could
have ridden on the strider but he's so
fast i don't trust myself
well if you guys want to play gotcha
before we go i got i brought a bunch of
gold
i brought some gold too that sounds fun
but raid up is alive well we'll
we'll wait for cali to get back and then
let's go
does anybody have a chest i can put
cali's stuff in oh there's a bunch of
guests
thank you gooda for doing that by the
way i will make it up to you
oh no worries yeah it's okay i'll put it
in uh what did you
have um i just want my nether
stuff like uh to build my house with
cool things like uh there were some
i feel so stupid why didn't i put that
stuff in chest before i
second time you're inspired i'm silly
i'll come help in just a second
building a nice path to the gacha
welcome back
i'm here thank you everyone
we're sticking out another
let me know if i missed anything i think
you got everything thank you
can i mine write
yeah so strider is down there where we
left him he won't really go anywhere i
don't think oh okay
uh i wonder um yeah i guess there's not
much we can do about that huh darn it
i want it to be i can come back when i
don't have anything
um yeah yeah yeah you can build like
staircases
for him oh yeah
outside of lava right so we can just
build him a really really long
long staircase yeah yeah
we have enough rocks
but that's
[Music]
okay i just wanna put some stuff away
i'll come back i'm right
before the ah yeah i wanna go put some
stuff away too actually
you should put your armpits on yeah oh
okay oh that came off huh
um i'll continue to mine the path to the
village
sorry i lost the gold snapback hello
hello
oh yeah do you need some gold or
mercedes
yes is it this way
[Music]
yeah i'm just going to put my things in
my chest no
oh yeah it's gone huh oh well
i know i used it i panicked and i used
it oh it's okay
oh that was yours oh my god i'm so sorry
it's okay you're good thanks for doing
more
you don't have to it's okay we have a
craft table at the home
oh okay you don't have to it's not that
far okay
what does it do anyway i don't know
it's purple yeah it is very beautiful
but do i really want to waste all my
gold at the gacha again do i
do i have gold for you okay i have like
a ton more at home
oh my god oh my god
yeah the gold woman
damn i want to play guns yeah me too
let's go let's go
oh why don't this railroad oh it is
thought it was the stairs
uh make this
wait
[Music]
i have and i don't have any rock
no i haven't just mined them from here
look is it called rock or
wreck yes wreck
like quack
yeah yeah another wreck
are you guys should i take the pig
village path uh yes
yes yeah okay i'll follow the torches
nice shiny sword you got there buddy
oops
[Music]
so i guess nether spawn points can be
used instead of beds i didn't know about
that
we used the crying obsidian to make
those oh
the bright the bright one
the crying one the degree tested the
greenhouse
oh my god oh we can mine it back with
our
diamond pickaxe that brought mine wait
where is it yeah
yeah almost died almost
died oh my god gold armor
uh you know are you this is where the
ender dragon is
i'm just making it so we don't know good
idea this is not where he is
where's the ender dragon i want to see
him
maybe it's for another time how do you
summon him what do you got to say
and we have to find that gate thing and
then like complete it
and then like we gotta go find him
i'm ready to go knock on his door boom
boy think we have to be like
all diamond everything to do that right
and nope uh not at all i mean like for
our own safety
basically uh uh i watched like
20 hours of uh and and
uh rta of um
enderdragon rta so i know how to do it
but we are not ready for it we're not
ready for it
oh why you kind of make a different kind
of portal
but you need lots of ender pearls and
there's a few ways to get the end of
pearls but it takes a long time
oh but it's not really yeah eventually
nevermind i like yours oh are you able
to move sir
sir you look like you're having a hard
time down there ready
are you okay do you need help getting
back up sir see ya
thank you i hear it oh i hear it
no above you know
i'm okay oh there he is oh i see you
gonna break our bridge i think he's gone
oh he's right there there he is yeah
hello i'm at me hi hiya
oh we taking down the the big jellyfish
in the sky
come here that would be the safe choice
go do it girl i don't think i don't
think i can make that shot
i can't make this shot he's still making
a little closer
no that's so far away i don't think i
can make that
there's our other portal too nice let me
shoot him out in the open
oh here we are again
no he's too far up where are all the
villagers there were so many here before
they died what what
[Laughter]
there's some homies over here maybe
they're sleeping maybe it's night time
for them
yeah where's their house do you have a
crafting oh they're tr they're training
the little one
uh no but i can make one i think
well then
run away all right i have one
oh right here put it right here by the
bridge
[Music]
gold gotcha all right
do it i have a gold to give you guys
thanks amelia for the free gold
yeah big ups green you get three thanks
oh you picked me sorry oh oh he doesn't
he really doesn't like me girl why is he
i agree
oh god i'm gonna die it's fine i'll help
ah all right thank you i wonder why he's
aggro
oh yeah i have one heart we'll see what
happens
wait do you need food yeah who's that
girl
thank you
it's okay who wants to gotcha with me
i do where's the gotcha dude okay some
gadget boys
i have i'm actually don't have any
golden things there's a man on fire
boy you in the gold pants you're in the
cold helmet here
come back sorry amelia i think that when
you gave me the gold you accidentally
picked it up again
i don't know yes give me something good
sorry
mm-hmm ah you okay
i'm okay thank you thank you thank you
big ups thank you
i don't see yeah boy
okay over here
[Music]
where are the villagers yeah it's really
just dead dudes huh
i see one he has a gold helmet come here
oh he's running away
why are you scared of me oi here
no he's hurt he's back i died oh my god
kelly
i'll grab your gold chase
oh my god take this oh i'll take the
steak
yeah take the steak
yeah oh my god hell
i was just gonna give him gold and then
he turned on me
i think i think if you're holding gold
they'll attack you because they're the
they're not the villagers it was the
villager though it was a regular dude he
wasn't like a zombie like guy or
anything
not a single good thing came out of this
i did something weird with my son looks
rich
yeah let's see if he gives me anything
what
give me something good not a single good
thing
i did something weird with my keyboard
oh
a string i think it's the end for your
boy
on this one here yeah we should probably
call it soon because
cali's got a string key yep time to wrap
it up wait did did anyone find any
of the trader gotcha trader
no i thought i did he started blasting
nice
i didn't drop anything actually that's
good because then i can
take the guts at home and don't waste it
all right we can go back okay let's go
back
[Music]
i'm in that same village too i got lost
again
[Laughter]
somehow i doubt that you tried this one
are you still in the village i'm trying
i'm looking for watson's uh tennis
racket
oh okay okay okay no
it's a magnifying glass rocket
oh my god oh my god
wait where did you die because in
[Music]
[Laughter]
clearly this is the wrong direction got
it okay
are we gonna do operation find kelly
sorry i will find it don't worry i'm
getting up high
what did i what did i gain for this from
this
okay so listen i wasn't i wasn't wearing
any gold armor
and apparently that's a thing oh yeah
yeah remember that's why i said
should we give you a gold armor ah
it all makes sense now yes
i'll make some i promise i'll start
mining my own stuff i don't want you
guys to have to do everything for me
no no no help we help yes we help each
other we help
yes team we are one
we are one thanks guys i want to be good
at video games
yeah maybe someday
gosh where is watson's tennis racket
where's
where's waldo where's watson where in
the world is
watson where in the world is watson
hold on
[Music]
oh i do okay
wow minecraft is so pretty another i'll
come back
[Music]
i see an incredibly tall buildings this
must be the right way
like ridiculously yeah building
kiara
oh no
[Music]
wait how did you drown i drowned my
house
i just kind of watched it you watched it
what was i supposed to do
all right gotta call the vanguard
okay hopefully our house will survive
i'm in the basement okay
all right i shall wait for you all here
[Music]
remember stream's gonna be a sleepy
stream
it's okay it'll be fun
all right we're all here yay
can do the the ending right here by the
tennis racket
i know it's a mining i'm not a mining
magnifying magnifying glass
yeah it's a beautiful patch on it you
guys will see
yeah it's a beautiful magnifying glass
and it looks like a mustache record
um i just got a good idea
here up on the stairs have a good idea
for a future collaboration do you want
to do a minecraft stream with me where
we build a huge
chess field oh my god
uh we can do that
[Laughter]
[Music]
i think this is your stuff okay oh yeah
thank you thanks
oh i'm sorry i don't mean to make it all
right good here i have a present for you
too
a present for me look over here turn
look at this oh crossbow
you should enchant that oh
okay she got it oh uh cara i have a
present for you too
here we go
because you can draw it and then you can
just have it drawn and then you can
shoot it
oh baby nice
the one and only gold now anyway present
two so here you go
yeah doors purple doors
i just changed my door to the purple
thank you it matches it
it's santa claus yeah
the color i'm in santa claus
ew thank you i love you santa can i sit
on your lap
okay sure lunch what do you want for
christmas little girl
um you nice baby
i have crying obscenities
[Music]
maybe she wants me to wholesome way she
wants me as a friend
yes and flowers she just got friends
don't care
oh that's okay i i just want i just want
a friendship that's all i want
a deep friendship friendship forever and
ever
yeah okay gather up
okay yo
it's magnifying glass i'm sorry i know
it now i understand now
yeah yeah wait ah there we go
yay oh we didn't yeah we didn't take a
screenshot previously i want to take one
now
oh i'll take off my i'll take off like
oh i don't have spots in my inventory
who was that a skeleton over here
there's a skeleton over here oh
yeah i was trying to shoot him down
photo off time
[Music]
give me a second
how do i make the chat go away
does someone know how to take the to
make the chat go away
you wait i need to see f1 there you go
[Music]
successful another trip yay
this is the bird perspective thank you
everyone who watched
a good perspective
everyone who watched magic
yeah thank you for watching
[Music]
me and gouda are planning on playing uh
minecraft together next week so tune up
i'll be there yeah it's gonna be fun so
yeah come on
i'm having another okay hold up japan
collaboration next week
[Music]
like who secret
okay cool
uh schedule for me will be out uh
tomorrow or the day after tomorrow yeah
new week almost
all right okay thank you everybody for
[Music]
watching
i guess i i should turn off the i'll
i'll stop the stream then
goodbye hey i'm gonna mute this goodbye
sorry but okay guys just want to say i'm
not streaming tomorrow
and yeah no stream on monday uh gets
your behavior nice
thank you for watching i'll see you soon
bye bye
sorry for being quiet i just didn't want
to speak over the other girls
it's always difficult with five girls at
once
[Music]
bye
so
shut up
i need breakfast yet
yeah yeah the arrows are in the chest
[Music]