[Music]
he
[Applause]
[Music]
part party party
party
[Music]
he
[Applause]
[Music]
one
zero
[Music]
for
ie
[Music]
fore
youing youing youing
[Music]
[Applause]
you
[Music]
good
the
night night we Night Watch
she
what I'll sh
it I'll
[Music]
it
[Applause]
mean a s hey everybody it's me Mory kipy
from hola live English myth everybody's
favorite hardworking Shinigami back in
Action today with a brand new show for
all of you guys that have been working
super super hard for I hope you guys are
as excited as I am this is my official
officially officially my second birthday
live official 3D 3D live show I hope you
guys are super super hyped for it
because oh man there's so much good
stuff I can't wait to show you but
there's a special rule for today's for
today's live and that rule is no down
time which means which means I mean
there's no downtime there's there's no
slow anything no slow songs no slow MC's
no slow Mor um
100% Going real crazy that's why you got
to use the hashtag hash no down time and
post a bunch of screenshots can you do
that a bunch of screenshots and your
thoughts screenshots and your thoughts
about this show and I'd be really really
happy if you did that cuz we got a lot
of great guests we we got a lot of Great
Performances and not to mention we have
a great stage would you like to take a
look at the stage with me take a look at
the underdome under under underworld
don't I haven't come up with a name for
it yet but isn't it great it's a special
secret place that I found in the
Underworld where the moon sometimes
comes down on the 4th of April which
happens to be my birthday so I figured
that it would be the perfect setting for
all of us to have a great show together
I invited a bunch of my friends and it's
going to be amazing there's a lot of
great surprises ahead
additionally um I can see a bunch of you
in the crowd I know you're cheering for
me hey what's up skeletons except you
look a little more human- shaped
congratulations on that but I'm looking
forward to doing my best for you guys
and as a matter of fact the next song
the next song is one that I know you
guys have really wanted me uh to perform
for a long time um and I did perform it
before at Fest but this time I want to
try and perform it in a way that is even
more explosive and my like and my own
home stage I hope that you will enjoy it
so everybody please listen to the next
song which is my brand new song that you
guys should definitely stream and listen
to a lot if you haven't had time and
check out the MV4 because the art is
amazing that song is called Overkill
check it
[Applause]
out
a man say
[Music]
this theam my nature chip stop stuck
ring lovely animals until they crack
yeah you know you
know am me see black break when
[Applause]
you but wor I a
hardness the computer sh gambl by Nature
shifts down to St racing lovely animals
until they crack beautiful
Tre close your eyes and'll see us
[Music]
black dad so is
no uh
know know
how
tox black break
down not
[Music]
impr
[Applause]
[Laughter]
let's
go
[Music]
dead
n will come out of the
way yeah
yeah trick cheat front fly sulfur in the
air
[Music]
so let it be or let it be
the six times knocking on the door no
response but hey y ready it back to back
death coming on made my
TR back to
backous is scaming to the
end back to back cannot let anyone do it
again back
back I can't
no J I'll break it
down just want to get my
again down what a heavy
[Music]
day now you hear the realm from the
ground
yeah trick cheat FR like clown is
dancing
around yeah
yeah so let it be let it face seem I'm
the
great six times knocking on the door one
chance you've got to stand back to back
death comes running on in my
train back to back conscience scaming to
the
a back to back cannot let anyone do it
again back to back I can no
longer me break it
down just want to get my light again
bling down what a heavy day
[Music]
he hey hey hey all
right everybody all together
now let's go hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
[Applause]
woo
[Music]
we made a contract with a clown and had
a high time nobody doubted his true
purpose oh yeah not knowing we had given
up everything we had left all of the
options being I trapped here in a stand
back to back death comes riding on the
midnight train
back to back C CH to S into
the back to back BL is already on your
jug ve back to back it's now we never
last
St can break it
down just want to get my day again
blazing down what a heavy day
[Applause]
Nina my enan thank you so much for
coming and singing heavy day together
with me it was so
fun happy
birthday thank you for inviting me today
the St looks great those pillars of fire
were hot
though yeah that's right you know
they're hot just like our intense GG
Vibes and our Synergy this is this is
maybe I don't know I think that we've
you've been at almost every single one
of my birthday lives and so I just want
to say sincerely thank you from the
bottom of my heart n
my keep it up and good luck with the
rest of the show bye-bye wishing you all
the best bye-bye Ena thank you so much
for coming
yeah well we have a bunch more guests
that are coming but I can't allow myself
to rest for even a moment because you
guys the theme is # no down time so I'm
just going to be here jogging in place
chug in place if I allow myself to rest
then it's false advertising right dead
beats that's what that is false
advertising so let's go keep it moving
keep it moving no breaks no breaks no
breaks no breaks on the
mar on to the next what could it be what
could it
[Applause]
be
[Music]
for
C
[Music]
begin on the
moon ha
[Music]
speee
[Applause]
[Music]
fore
let
[Music]
fore
[Applause]
so I stay yeah yeah with My
Soul
[Music]
it's
like I'm in AIC hurry oh there
[Music]
is one two three steps on the St stage
where's your flag Mar F coming
[Music]
where's my soul where's my
heart go
[Music]
this
[Applause]
[Music]
where is the star now I found the star
now but so beautiful
[Music]
so one two steps to the
[Applause]
[Music]
Royal
break it all take it
all
[Applause]
[Music]
just
[Applause]
me
[Music]
[Applause]
ande
[Music]
CH the
my soul with my heart
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
get it up get it up get it up get it up
get it up get it up get get it
up get get it up get get it up up get
get it up get get it up get get it up
get get it
[Music]
up can
be no one gets close to me black memory
[Music]
[Applause]
donut
Miss can't get it up
get it up get get it up get it up get
get it up get it
up get it up get it up get it up get it
up get it
[Music]
[Applause]
up oh
[Music]
me said the
[Applause]
[Music]
yesy hey hey hey everybody's get it now
come
on get get it up get get it up get get
it up get get it up get get it up get
get it
[Music]
up
for he want
he
they get it up get it up get it up get
it up get it up get it
up 1 two get it up get it up get it up
get it up get get it up get get it
[Music]
up happy birthday M
[Applause]
bye
yeah
back in the let me Shake It Up do
what I want sh got to reck got a thirst
for the
looking sh got shake it up looking all
you do is talk get your head out your
ass you
got
[Music]
down
do what I want you know what I got
may be the pinle first give the my and
may I just you act full just got to find
you C A you already know steady get the
show they want to get real close can't
learn to let go dance with r look to the
be back haveing till the next night
where we
go
I don't care
sing time you don't to
[Music]
run it give it
[Applause]
yeah me the S you got the rest Mor and
coobo in the building so you know you're
already dead you're
dead
[Music]
ch
yeah go up and
[Music]
down B Bo
Kobo Kobo thank you so much for singing
with
me thank you as well come wish you a
happy birthday best birthday yeah you
know you you spit some Flames you're
you're a great rapper actually Kobo you
should do more rap I think yeah it was
so difficult but uh Kobo is a pro rapper
and yeah you know we are one blood right
yeah Daddy yeah singing together with
you was awesome no no no you nailed it
that was great
wow you're amazing wow maybe following
in Mor's footsteps a little bit I don't
know release the Cobo mixtape start the
Cobo SoundCloud and D since I'm here
let's take a picture okay okay let's
make a cool po first okay okay picture
time let's go yeah right in front of you
okay you kids these days with your
you're always taking photos in your
hashtags speaking of hashtag Hey take a
screenshot of us and then make sure that
you use the hashtag it's the one time
where I won't feel embarrassed if you
spam my hashtag on Twitter SLX so please
do it stga pose
jeez yeah get fancy with it blue and
pink is the best combination what do you
think I think we look pretty good
together okay looks good right ah one
more daddy cute post okay say say oooo
okay Daddy
yeah yeah yeah yeah o o like that okay
let's go cute
balls
[Music]
O Okay looks good right thanks again
Daddy for inviting me uh Kobo wants to
go to the mall with Mommy okay
bye-bye see you later Gobo bye-bye
thanks
again oh wait no down no down time no
down time no down time hold on okay no
downtime we keep it moving we keep it
moving on to the next I'm going to
[Music]
[Applause]
die a beautiful star I a beautiful star
a
Beau
[Music]
[Applause]
Beau
happy
day beautiful
star beautiful
star
a beautiful
star a beautiful
[Music]
[Applause]
star
[Music]
[Applause]
for
spee spee
[Applause]
spee
rest
[Music]
in
Beau
[Music]
baby to night happy
lucky you a baby so sweet me beautiful
star beautiful
star
[Music]
yeah
the
long
[Music]
foree
for
[Music]
spe
foree
canot
[Music]
say
D
make
[Applause]
[Music]
h
yay thank you so much everybody that was
zanki time left speaking of time left
there is none there's no time left but
uh this has been a really really amazing
no downtime live show with you guys and
all the amazing guests that came here so
thank you so much for coming to support
me and have a great live show my fourth
one wow my fourth my fourth birthday
here in Holo and I'm so so happy to have
gotten this chance to celebrate it with
you here in the Underworld it was
fantastic
but you know it is my birthday and when
it comes to birthdays there's there's
something important to
announce what does everybody announced
during their birthday um hold on I'm
thinking I don't know I forgot I forgot
wait it's I remember I remember I
remember to beat some a little scattered
brain I'm sorry it's cuz I'm excited
birthday Goods
Tada
kop 2020 24 birthday Goods check it out
everybody this this is definitely a set
that I'm super excited to introduced to
you guys by the way check it out me
playing the bass hey it's not a lie
because for my birthday I bought myself
a Bas yay I'm going to start learning
again I'm not a fake bass player stop
don't call me that I'm not a fake bass
player Bo I'll beat you up okay it's
cool the illustration is cool and um and
it's on a couple of these Goods I guess
I'll introduce them to
you next so um first of all first and
foremost Eternal rest Square cushion
would you like to sleep forever dead de
well good news for you I have a cushion
that is extremely comfy and super
special and has a picture of me playing
the Bas on
it you're going to fall asleep
immediately if you use this cushion but
but I can't guarantee that because I
think there's like some legal stuff um
check it out the art is beautiful um
it's high quality and amazing um I think
it's high quality I hope that you enjoy
it um and you can take lots of naps with
it I wish I could take naps I can't
really take a lot of naps next next
slide is hey dead beads do you guys like
fashion I like fashion do you like
fashion there are a lot of designer
brands in the human world that I can't
name right now because also legal things
um however in the Underworld we kind of
have our own designer Brands as well and
I have collaborated with one of my
favorites to create this underworld and
designer
Muffler yeah I kind of consider this
like the Riz pack birthday birthday
Goods check it out um Ki Mori symbol um
you can find other dead beats out in the
wild without just having Mory on your
shirt you know it's very convenient and
the tag is also super cute so make sure
that you get nice and warm and snug uh
for fall and winter I hope you guys
enjoy wearing this and adding it to your
wardrobe next slide please additionally
we
have dead beat honorary ring I know you
guys will be excited about this one but
do not get it twisted this is not a
marriage
ring dead beats I'm not going to marry
you I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm too busy I'm
too busy but but if you'd like you could
go ahead and purchase this dead beat
honorary ring so that you can also find
other dead beats out in the wild it
makes it a little bit easier right and
plus um if it doesn't fit on your finger
your finger is may be too big or too
small you can go ahead and put it on a
necklace and it's still very very
fashionable I really love the design it
reminds me of you guys so I hope that
you guys will enjoy wearing this very
special ring and next last we have the
your last shot glass set of shot glasses
go find a dead beat and cheers them and
drink some alcohol that reminds you of
Mory or maybe even myy alcohol I don't
know um but they're they're very cute
it's a cute set with um some Mor designs
on them and I want to see them at every
deadbeat birthday party um every
deadbeat party in general I hope that
you guys use these a lot um to to go
wild and party no down time woo um I
guess that's about it next slide please
um we also have a situation voice it's
called backstage with
kipy I don't know what this one sounds
like because it hasn't happened yet but
maybe if I see you after the show oh I
might remember it I don't know maybe
because it's yet to happen also if you
get the full set you get a super secret
special special one that's included in
there which is pretty neat so please
look forward to that and next slide for
the entire full set um if you buy the
whole thing you will get a signed card
by me myy kipy and I'm signing all of
them I'm signing every single card
because you guys are great and I want
everybody to get a chance um to get Mor
signature I've been making it really
easy for you guys recently to be honest
between all the things I've been signing
but but this one I definitely um I
definitely will be signing just for you
as many of you guys that buy the full
set you will get a handsigned postcard
from me um so yeah please look forward
to it and next slide please uh here's
the full set here's everything that you
get with it and the cart will open as
soon as the live stream is over or on
the hour uh so make sure that that you
check it out uh make sure that you're I
guess you don't really need to be fast
because I'm signing every single one but
make sure that you grab yours today low
down time woo so that is the that's the
merch situation um those are the goods
my birthday Goods I'm very happy with
them I can't wait to receive mine and I
hope that you guys look forward to
getting yours now we do have something
else that I want to show you a very
special PV that I think maybe some of
you guys have already seen I don't know
but it's about something it's about
something really really awesome and I'm
very excited about it so let's watch it
PV
[Music]
Doo
spee
spee spe
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
rning
everybody woo so I have been chosen to
sing the ending theme for the TV anime
Suicide Squad eai to air from
July I'm so excited about this I waited
so long to tell you guys about it and
and I know I already did tell you about
it but even saying it now it feels like
a like a dream I mean even even when I
joined h i I said in my my debut one of
my goals was was to make a song for
anime but really it's been my lifelong
goal to do something like that and H
I've I've already cried a lot over this
so I'm I'm not going to here but I'm
very emotional about it so please look
forward to it um the the animation
production is by the amazing wit studio
so you know it's going to be a banger um
it's incredible and uh I really want
everybody to watch it when it comes out
so please make sure that you stay tuned
when it does air and there's still
something else I'd like to show you a
bit of a teaser of sorts I don't know
but let's see what else Mory has cooking
PV Doo
[Music]
[Applause]
wow what was that what was that H new
song but what kind of song I don't know
is there is there are there any guesses
in the chat what could this be well we
don't really have a lot of details about
it yet but it's a secret for another
time so please keep your eyes peeled for
the big reveal coming sometime soon I'm
sure look forward to it now that's it
for the announcements however however
there is uh there's still one song left
that's right because this train doesn't
stop moving no downtime baby I'm
starting to feel it I'm starting to feel
it but perfect timing um I'm going to
change clothes so don't watch meame look
over there please don't watch a lady
change whoa that was fast oh Callie's
very fast check it it's my rapper Reaper
t-shirts I have a bunch of different
designs you can choose your color and
stuff like that they're on the my store
make sure that you grab yours if you
haven't already it's very neat check it
out I'm very very proud of this one this
one in particular I drew myself so it's
very special to me um now let's do this
last song you guys a song that I've
wanted to perform since my early days in
Holan I think you guys will understand
why it's so special when you see it
everybody thank you for coming let's
[Applause]
rock this thing
on let's go Callie yeah
yeah roie it R it
out right right and Ro and hey rid post
all
[Music]
night1 Crank It Up hand the back the
boys
theow
down down to play like a shine hide
[Music]
forever guys G Fortune Talent you can't
dance around it they'll just tie you
down boys
like this old man hey you with the bang
attitude the
one down
to down
two down
two don't you get it twied y the one to
take a roing rocking out roing rock and
roll strong that to the river that just
won't stop don't stop let me see you let
out rest in peace and ready down keep
rocking rocking out rocking rocking
all right to hold up like what's the
plan right a first Banger like I know we
can in the worst case hang around seeing
underground got a rep not a crown
so what got something say you better say
it loud you got to whack I sound a
little more profound on and on it goes
on and on and on and all switch for
opinions not bad shot when you got to
take the heat burn St up with the makeup
style you can B to a ganger a little
[Music]
while real take a
selfie selfie
[Music]
s you ain't going to die on me we got to
stay alive rocking rocking out raing
rock and roll even songs of Love Ring
emotion that just won't stop don't stop
she's the girl in my Bel love she her
world and Light It Up by rock and rock
it out and rock and
roll give it up for H English MB talking
usara on
keyboards
[Music]
ulele
guar so we one half ass playing to
the m Mar we P hey with medicine give me
give me that pressure and apprehension
keep stressing the present leaving I'm
guessing under the weather dis believe
suspension big sorry guys I to apologize
how can you tell that my voice is up and
done
huh
huh I mean we can still perform if you
guys want to I don't know better know
get a grip cut that
baby
baby you ain't going to die on me we got
to stay
alive rocking rocking out rocking
rolling that guitar to the rhm that just
won't stop don't stop let me see and let
it our to ready keep rocking rocking out
rock and rock and roll rocking rock
out
[Music]
rocking I won't die here you ain't ding
either music ring fire it's how we stay
alive yeah yeah all right thank you
everyone Miss rock rap and Ro
and
roll
[Applause]
woo