[Music]
do
[Applause]
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
um
this is my
[Music]
fried chicken taco
fried chicken
in english
um
[Music]
uh
um
foreign
[Music]
now
um
foreign
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
um
hi everyone actually actually i have to
speak
english but yeah my main language
obviously is german because i'm from
whole life
german but i might mix in some
english every now and then we will see
well i don't know do i even have english
speaking viewers
i don't know probably not so who cares
japanese
[Music]
so fast
is
um
[Music]
rpgs
ah
[Music]
um
kelly
kenny
where's kelly
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm
it
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
m
um
[Music]
foreign
um
i guess so guys is it okay if i'm gonna
sing a song
[Music]
i don't know this might be the first
time i'm singing this song
[Music]
foreign
oh yeah
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
myself
is
[Music]
tell
is
[Music]
foreign
this is wrong
i'm not
i'm not from a whole life german
that doesn't exist
eh wait
bad music video for me
it's made by kali
huh
[Music]
[Applause]
i
[Music]
yeah that's how it's supposed to be
this is how it's supposed to be
[Music]
me
is
i've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
a stay
[Music]
could you tell me please
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
i i
[Music]
i
i remember everything now
so clearly
almost almost half a year ago
i joined whole life english
aka alive myth
how could i ever forget
i don't want to forget that i've made so
many
memories and so many friends
but i can't help it whenever i
revive i just
i can't help it i forget about the
things that are
important to me and the things that are
making me happy i'm sorry
i'm sorry for forgetting i don't want to
forget you guys
sorry
sorry guys i'll try my best for this
i didn't wanna i didn't want this to
happen
i didn't i don't know i don't understand
why i
i don't know why youtube just keeps on
killing me
i don't get it
but will you guys continue to
support me from now on too
as takanasi kyara
[Music]
oh i'm so happy recently
uh since 10 years 10 years 10 days ago
and my streams didn't show up to all of
my subscribers
let me join that echo my streams didn't
show up to all of my subscribers
and most of you didn't see my recent
streams and you couldn't even see them
now because my
uh streams from the past two months have
been deleted as you have seen in the
disclaimer
um we're working on it uh my management
side
is very very um
fixated on getting this [\h__\h] cleared up
as soon as possible
so don't worry if we're just waiting
it's just a matter like today they
unbanned me
um all of this was
as far as i know i mean we'll probably
never really get a clear
answer but um some kind of you know
my channel has been hijacked therefore
we wanted to protect you so we hid you
all of your content from all of your
viewers for 10 days
yeah that's why many of you probably
didn't watch my streams for the last 10
days
uh yeah and
after you know getting in contact with
youtube for genma
and they have fixed the shadow band
today which is by the way a bad word in
my chat now because uh
you know anything can happen um
and then but then you know shadow ban
gets
fixed five next problem for some reason
now
the videos of the past two months are
gone but i'm sure it will come back it's
just probably gonna take
another 24 hours or something
meanwhile you have me here now and today
was supposed to be minecraft sorry guys
for that um let me turn
bgm back on today was supposed to be
minecraft but
i felt like you know i wanted to do this
uh germany debut
once i since i moved back from japan to
australia
and i was like i want to do a german rew
at some point but it
it does um require some kind of
planning some a certain amount of
planning
uh so i spent all day today because um i
i didn't really want to do it today but
then this happened
and i was like what the [\h__\h]
well what choice i have this is my my
third
my first w this is my third
w yeah yeah yeah yeah already three
times
um well my third revival
ever since joining hollow life
i don't want to die again please don't
do that again
this time is uh this time has been a bit
different
from the last time down because last
time if you guys remember i don't know
so maybe some people wearing were not
there but my channel got like
completely deleted from it got wiped off
of youtube like it got
like suspended not exactly i think yeah
i don't know we got deleted any case
yeah and that was resolved somewhat
quickly and was
i was having quite some fun with it but
this time it's a bit different
it didn't get deleted like the channel
didn't get deleted but
it got shadow banned for one whole week
and then yeah now the shadow band is
gone but
uh the videos are gone
but that's why i did that uh in the
shadow
video because i was in the shadows for a
whole over a week
10 days thank goodness your feelings
yeah otherwise i wouldn't be able to
revive
thank god
um i have a i have a fearing
uh why this all happened
but i don't i'm i think we
don't really need to talk about it too
much and
however yeah youtube claims that it was
a security
thingy and um now that i
the more i think about it um it makes a
bit more sense to me
now and um it really sucks
that it happened because i was really
trying hard to
get you guys to notice that i'm
streaming but you know
for times like these you guys should
follow me on twitter so that you don't
miss my streams
um yeah because
so many people miss my streams and it
made me really sad
because i put a lot of you know effort
into
what i do and then
to have it destroyed by a freaking
shadow band is pretty sad
um but yeah hopefully hopefully it will
not happen again anytime soon
and yeah hopefully youtube
and i can be friends uh yeah i
i totally want to be friends with you
youtube
no no no it was not not because i moved
because
see one thing that i don't like is when
people try to make up their own fearings
that just don't make sense because they
don't have all the information but it's
the shadow band started since before i
moved
to australia before i changed my ip so
um please don't make up
any fairies it doesn't matter what
exactly happened
please just that's let's not try to
you know make up something or
you know assistance just accept the fact
that it's back now
and that youtube bamboozled me once
again
i blame casper casper is not a false
casper is the cutest little baby i love
casper
yeah yeah conspiracy theories will bring
us nowhere
so let's let's stop it no one is
actually yeah really no one is at fault
if i have to say someone in this fall
then maybe youtube but besides that no
one is at fault
so yeah [\h__\h] happens exactly shy
surpassing it
did you guys someone understand what i
was saying
in my german debut you guys have no idea
translating hino tony to german was also
wow
difficult i spent all day today
preparing this
and i have some really um
nope nope no yes i did
nice i think everyone who understood
speaks german
i understood five words well guys if you
would have watched my
um german introduction
lesson on on my youtube channel that's
one of the few videos that haven't been
heated away from the youtube
channel so you could have studied german
before you would have entered this
stream you could have studied it but you
have chosen to not do so
and you have chosen to be confused
hello cat hello thank you for um
behaving while i was doing my very
important debut thank you very much
thank you thank you thank you oh you're
really walking slowly
um in front of my monitor and you
enjoying it
is there wow so slowly are you gonna
thank
thank you
oh you want to drink my cocoa and that
yeah you really shouldn't so probably
not you just want to eat
i know you just want to sniff
yeah anyway um what did you guys think
of the german version of hinototi
what did you think of the german version
of hinotori
was it cool i have yet to sing an
english version of hinotoni
well there you go i made the german
version
oh amazing it was fire it awesome
stop i mean um i i i didn't have much
time to practice it
i think i can make it even better like
the the intonation of the words
like aligning it with the melody it
can use a bit more um
it can use a bit more practice fire it
was amazing thank you bring it to
spotify
maybe i should release my own cover
version
of uh hinotoni but this time in german
hey actually that
sounds like something i could do wait
can i buy
or it's not gonna be sold unfortunately
but you're welcome to listen to hinotoni
on spotify
itunes and amazon music apple music
etc it's everywhere as well as heart
challenger if you haven't listened to
heart challenger yet
my second single that i released on
valentine's day
is absolutely adorable and it is a song
that i dedicated to cali
and it's the music video is currently
wiped off of the youtube surface you
cannot watch the
music video right now but you can listen
to it on itunes spotify
apple music amazon music etc as well
just put in takanashikiya and you'll
find it
the lyrics are like already so so like
too nebula like really um fantasy
like and uh i don't know the choice of
words was very
very specific in japanese
[Music]
foreign then in
in german i mean i think i tried before
to translate he not only to
english i feel like i tried but i failed
because like my vocabulary in english is
not as good as obviously
my german vocabulary so for translating
it to german was actually
yeah not not as hard as i thought it
would be it was still hard because
i still wanted it to sound like you know
not like a direct translation
but actually like something that you
would sing
and so the choice of words really
matters
[Music]
really important
ah so we're gonna have um
some super special streams tomorrow and
the day after tomorrow as well because
wait a second okay yeah no okay oh my
god i'm getting so confused there's so
much to do
um but tomorrow and the day after
tomorrow i have
a special karaoke stream where i sing
whole live original songs
only and uh that is on that is tomorrow
and then on sunday i have a stream where
i teach gooda some german
yeah and for both streams i have to
prepare a lot
because i still have to practice all the
songs and i still have to prepare the
german lesson
even though guna actually speaks some
basic really really basic german
as far as i know so we're not gonna do
like
i don't know i still don't know actually
how i'm gonna do that
but if today you found an interest in my
in like the german language in general
or you just want to hear
could i speak german or hear me again
speaking german then you should
come on sunday to the guraka but you
should also come tomorrow and i sing all
the whole live original songs because
i i love those songs they're great oh my
god what's going on
and besides that that's pretty much it
for this stream
sorry it's kind of short but i'll be
reading super chat if you guys are okay
with
that and is that okay
you can have some more chit chat time um
yeah
but also don't forget to uh if you're
not subscribed subscribe
and follow me on twitter so in case that
something like this happens again you
won't miss out on anything
if you follow my twitter because i
always i always tell
uh people on twitter or when i make my
stream reservation
and then follow up when the stream
actually starts so
you should follow me on twitter
twitter notification saved me the past
few days yeah i think that
all of my viewers in the past few
streams which have
been heated from the youtube surface and
will come back soon
which is why you cannot watch them right
now and all of those
uh streams i think we're 90 percent
uh viewers from twitter
which i'm really helpful really grateful
for
uh without my twitter followers i
probably wouldn't have had an
audience at all in the past few streams
so thank you everyone for supporting me
in those 10 days it was pretty
frustrating i
i yesterday i was i took a day off and i
was
pretty i i got to a point where
i was really frustrated and today this
morning when i woke up
first thing i see is shadow one lifted
but video is gone
i came from reddit well thank you guys
thank you reddit gang as well
so when i woke up and saw that today i
was like honestly
i was definitely not in the mood of
doing a german re-debut stream
last time i took it really well but this
time honestly 10 days
and then that that was just i was so mad
but i did it anyway because i felt like
now i never got to do this i got to take
this
timing is important so i did it today um
and in the end it was fun
so yeah yeah but still
pretty annoying what the hell but yeah i
want to thank
i want to thank janma for my manager for
supporting me and for um you know
helping me out with this
uh stressful situation thank you thank
you janma
jmt jmd
youtube
[Music]
let me repeat uh disclaimer there is no
whole live german at least not yet i
don't know i cannot say that it will
ever exist i don't know
i have absolutely no idea this was just
a joke from my side
and i think it was pretty obviously a
joke but just gonna make it clear you
know we're making it clear
it's a joke guys i mean i personally i
joked about
uh the fact before that the whole life
german would probably not be a thing but
who knows who knows maybe i
maybe i inspired uh the management
to one day make something like this
who knows who knows maybe maybe one day
we have we have all
of espanol and whole live
brazil and whole live finland will help
sweden who knows
whatever which country one one day we
will have them all gotta catch them out
hold our friends oh yeah sexy what i
really want
is all of um
weird english accents so scots
brits or the fake australians give me
all of them give me the canadians give
me all of that i want those sexy
accents i wanna hear those sexy accents
give them to me
amelia was
totally real brit yes yes yes totally
real rich
[Laughter]
uh did that sound like anything did that
did that sound like anything at all
i don't know it does sound like
something
sound southern dammit god damn it
i used to what actually i don't know i
don't even i don't even know what i'm
doing
um i used to speak
like low-key british accent
because my english teacher in school
used to say like hey kiara you got quite
the british accent going on and i was
like
thank you mate okay no i didn't say meat
sure no really i don't know i just
i just lost it because i a lot a lot
i've lost it
i lost it and i don't know where it went
uh i think i think that was probably
because i listened to a lot of lily
allen
back in the day you know that i sang a
lilly ellen song in my cuddle
on the archive karaoke stream the other
day and uh
i i i i tried to
recreate her accent a little bit i don't
know if you i don't know if you noticed
back then
but people were like oh huh people
didn't react to it so
yeah anyway
[Music]
so yeah and we will read super chat if
that's okay i think we only have to read
from this stream i've
frankly finished the super chats the
other day
wait i don't know i don't know what it's
gonna look like if we go to the chatting
screen
i think the stamps are off
let's see what happens when we move to
the chatting screen
and i can now do it with like a with a
button
i got um i got the stream back the
elgato stream deck
with way too many buttons than i would
ever need but hey
let's push it push the button stand and
yeah that's uh oops wait let me go
um one second
one second
i'll fix that i'll fix that here uh
how about we just read super chat's here
today
how how well we just read them here
you know having the having the
the whole nostalgic vibe going on
i'll just i'll just read them here
and one second let me get them
push the button
[Music]
one thing i want to do is pop out the
chat so i can read the chat while i'm
doing my super chat pause
oops why did i push that
time to learn how come you don't know
german yet
it has always been time to learn german
and now you're just starting now
too late it's too late
still scrolling uh still scrolling
um okay oh wait there is oh there's
super chats on the in the shadows as
well okay
did you like that one it was it was a
bit hard for me
to like you know i usually don't do
videos and stuff
but that's the most i could do
that's the most i could do for making a
video
i wanted to show like me being
in youtube prison and
yeah that's how it turned out it was
high quality vague oh my god
well thank you
it was it had needed to show you know
the frustration and the
loneliness that i have experienced in
the past
10 days cinematic masterpiece
i wouldn't go that far i wish i had more
skills with
uh uh premiere like i'm using premiere
pro at the moment and i wish i had more
skills more you know i wish i could do
more stuff
hmm anyway
beside
from now on i will mix it in german into
mushrooms just kidding just kidding it's
just today
just kidding i will not do that
unfortunately i mean there might be
another
um german-only special german only
stream
at some point you know special occasion
but generally
generally not gonna happen okay
also hey i'm sitting on my new gamer
girl chair
and but
it's actually not as comfortable as i
thought it would be because
i have this issue that that that the
desk that i'm
uh currently using
uh is like so small
that i have to put like it's not it's
not like super tiny it's actually normal
size
normal size desk but um
my pc is so huge and i have to fit it
like
under the under desk like the middle of
it
where normally your feet would go your
legs
so i can't really fit my legs
here uh so
i can't really go in far with my
with my with my chair either yeah it's
kind of interesting
set up right now gaming chairs are very
bad
gamer chairs all bad why
why it's a free language i thought i
thought the same thing first but no
that doesn't work either because um
on um on top of my pc
is my switch so i can't rest my legs on
there
anyway let's start reading the super
chats
uh first off is uh the
whole live hello the debut
the debut ones are first and then
there's some some shadow
super chats mixed in and then this goes
back to
uh the debut ones okay
titles
are prettier they're prettier
and cuter okay
i mean it would be more way more
comfortable if i could actually
have more space here yeah
but oh well uh i'll figure a better
setup
i'll figure it out at some point
at some point
world cover you just released can't wait
to see you finish fire emblem and
hopefully takamori honeymoon
yeah fire emblem we haven't finished it
yet huh
seems like uh the last episode is
yet to happen right i've seen that yeah
i'll i'll get to it soon yeah we have to
finish it it's weird i felt i feel like
i've already finished it
weird very weird
plural foundation skye duncan
thank you a reply message potential
scats and kfp
tree i know ll translation live love
love it is only a small bump to us
what what i don't understand what you're
saying to my cats thank you that thank
you
and this is
your vassal and humble servant greetings
albedos escape from kfp's army forced us
to hasten our leaving nikaya
we proceeded on our journey for three
days
on the fourth day the bamboozlers
having collected themselves from all
sides sat up
sat upon the smaller portion of our
employees
and drove that portion back to their
camps when these employees were just
terrified by fear the standards of the
larger group of kfp
lft the great and the duke of fa
were riding at the head the count of the
love and the vulnerable bishop of jesus
followed
for they had heard of the battle and
hastened
to our aid the bamboozlers was estimated
at 260 000.
all of our army attacked them bonked
many and ru
routed the rest after that day our
employees remained together
therefore in traversing the countries of
romania and armenia we found no
obstacle until iconium
we who formed the advanced guard
saw a few bamboozlers after routing
these we laid siege to their forces
at antioch is that it
are you done okay that's that's it that
he's done for now
thank you
thank you for all the super chats i
think that might actually be a red one
uh 20 40 60 80 000. yeah
i can do maths
i can do math
formatics thank you
decibel thank you for the inspiring uh
story very interesting very very
interesting i see you have a
benefit a lot uh
i i have no idea what's going on
but thank you very much
i hope you will be fine i hope you don't
we i hope we don't lose too many of our
army
um i see you got some
very important uh members in the army as
well
so please keep them safe will ya
protect them at all cost i can die for
them
no matter how many times i will die for
my army
because i am a phoenix and i will revive
again and again
but my army are mere chickens and i have
to protect them
if i let them die then i will have no
one left
duncan
if terrible things happen to you or your
channel we will always be there to
support you the best way we can
broke super chatters vod live chatters
and lurkers we're all here for you kiara
thank you
and thank you thank you thank you
swan flyer danke soon again pig pig peg
dunk
[Music]
excuse me your radiance you say your
eyes are galaxies i've been thinking
they remind me of the ocean
deep vast full of life and vibrantly
colorful with a current pulling me
deeper in
envelop and enveloping enveloping
till there is nothing in me but you
wow
beautiful
wow this comes from our kfp philosopher
he wrote that himself after all he's the
philosopher
amazing amazing that's how i like people
to flirt with me
yeah more place
more more that's pretty good though
that's pretty good thank you for the
support the philosopher is a symbol of
course he is
but there's nothing bad about that don't
judge it
you're a simple too it's a good thing
not a bad thing
[Music]
thank you for the pinky oh it's german
um
can't wait for your w wait that you gave
up quick on the german
about time we got a real phoenix there's
this girl on the em branch claiming she
is one but we all know she's only
a chicken
[Music]
you want to fight her where is
you better be careful everest
better be careful
what you say to me huh
you better be careful
atgm
mm
fluffy panda thank you thank you
[Music]
i like how many of you guys are writing
in german i love it
debri thank you soon
thank you for the red super chat oh wait
deborah also sent the pinky weight
thank you for the pinky debris stuff
will dry that's the skin
lesson skin let
us go yeah thank you thank you for
coming i hope you enjoyed this little uh
season three
hmm thank you for the
rest of the chat thank you very much
there's so many translators in the chat
right now oh my god
because i think nana is cute and want to
tease her with super chat i asked her to
demonstrate how to
hiccup and i tried to make hiccup
several times i found it very funny
afterwards i felt that it was very bad
and guilty
please forgive me why are you asking for
my forgiveness i think it's totally fine
that's totally fine don't worry about it
don't worry about it
thank you thank you for the subscribe
thank you for the red super dad
[Music]
thank you very much for um turning that
into
a red one translation brought to you by
deep l wow i've never used deep l before
but apparently the translation is pretty
good
thank you for the support efforts
thank it was a hard fight
my fellow chickens but we have triumphed
over youtube's shadow bamboozle
and now we witness our phoenix rise
again from the ashes
hidden in the shadow no more she has
been brought back into the light where
our empress belongs
yes i am a bird of fire and light
i must be in the light when i am too
long in the shadow i will die
as i did in those 10 days
the shadow was hurting me
and with that loneliness and that
coldness i have perished
and died and here i am once again
yes yes yes uh i feel like we're
probably going to have
more re-debuts in the future please bear
with me whenever i
lose my memory a little bit please uh
please be patient with me i need some
time
next time if i lose my memory again
please spam
spam things in the chat that i will that
will you know
help me regain my memory please help me
okay
who is cali this time we also had who is
ame
how could i forget amma i just tell club
of her two days ago
unbelievable
thank you thank you comments tonight
once again
fluffy panda duncan f.o.d.e thank you
you changed your name too i see a lot of
changed names
i think so after the thousand for them
debut
totally and most definitely didn't use
these alphabets everyone's using dpl
everyone's using default very
interesting thank you for the red silver
so
man for a moment you made me think that
maybe maybe you knew some german made me
a little bit
you know excited but it was a lie it was
a big lie
it's okay i forgive you you just wanted
to do your best to communicate with me
makes me happy
thank you
[Music]
i know exactly who you are
again thank you good news is that i can
find your videos by searching again the
stream reservation appeared on
on my homepage without me having to
search for it notifications still aren't
working but it is a start
notifications i thought they worked for
this stream
and hopefully a good sign that the
youtube sp is ending
yeah i hope that too i mean
you know uh the the sp
shadow bamboozle it worked uh it happens
every now and then for like single
streams which is
i guess okay they worked
like for single streams it's bearable
like i'm like oh and whatever
i guess this stream will be
forgotten and unseen
it like gets shadow shadow bamboozled in
the middle of a stream
but this time it was like my whole
channel you couldn't even look it up
like it wouldn't show up
and it was for 10 days and my streams
didn't show up to anyone so
that was a bit too much
yeah if it's just one stream
okay whatever but other than that
this was uh too much
i know i know i know i know that now
this i am aware
that now this shadow bamboozle is fixed
and i show up in your subscription box
again
finally however it is not yet over
because my
videos from the past two months
are deleted currently but i'm sure that
will come back
probably tomorrow or something i hope um
[Music]
is
pinky you let my mama go
oh wait this is a in the shadows uh
super chats now
ever since totang those are the in the
shadows super chat
let my mama go i have no idea what
you're talking about whereas for rick
thank you for the pinky though
angela wrangler thank you
forest thank you soon
shadow super chats that's it um
i did that video and all the preparation
for the
debut stream all today in like
five hours you guys proud of me
i could have i could have spent all that
time to
cuddle with my shadows but i
i did everything in like five hours
and practiced and translated the whole
song
[Music]
i made that video and
remade the slides in german
yeah thank you guys thank you
thank you thank you thank you i'm glad
i'm glad you guys enjoyed it i'm glad
you guys liked it
campus night thank you we're back to the
debut stream
uh super chats i'm thank you for another
pinky that makes actually probably like
two
two red ones now probably
tantra i swear to god if your amnesia
strikes again and you don't look at your
bracelet and remember
i will stand to blank akka and protest
it will hurt me more than it hurts you
hashtag free kiana
well now maybe that's why i should
always be wearing the bracelet
to always you know look at it i have it
i have it actually in my
um in my desk drawer
because it's still kind of too big to
wear i need to fix that somehow
but it would help next time
if i you lose my memory again kelly said
to not use it but you know that she
obviously means
to use it when she says don't use it she
means use it i mean why else would she
have made
a friendship bracelet
eh
why else would she make that it's
logic exactly that's exactly what
i'm surprised you guys didn't get that
surprised you guys didn't
pick that up
hey cake cake thank you for a double red
super chat in euros this time
normally you uh donate in japanese yen
and now it's in euros
um
not bad doesn't doesn't even sound like
a
dbl translated that sounds pretty
natural
thank you for the rest of the job cake
thank you so much
thank you i hope uh you could understand
something of my stream
uh burger at kfb
in germany or cafe australia are pretty
much the same as the ones
i made in uh like mostly all over the
world the menu is the same
mostly you know just um
kfb italy just does whatever the [\h__\h]
they want i don't know
why they do that i told them to
have the same menu but they just do
whatever they want
i don't know but other than that
everyone
does the same menu so that's that
hey we are working on it really really
really no spaghetti they're putting
spaghetti in the
in
damn 300. donation in in
german in in um the text that i'm i'll
be reading now
is uh
australian dialect german so probably
many of you will
[Music]
[Laughter]
there's more australians in the chat
than i thought there would be
now i'm worried australia is a bit of
small country you know
in the immortal words of gods of the
iron hand
what youtube can make um
licking
dude i i i i am so
mad like honestly i tried my best to
make
this into a funny thing now once again
but this time i'm like honestly so mad
so
i agree with you thank you very much for
your
uh kind super chat speaking out of my
sailor out of my necessity
i agree but i also don't understand
i love how inside that turned into a
little meme
did youtube put you in jail again yeah
i'm already out of it but i was in
youtube jail for 10 days and most people
didn't even notice because it didn't
show my videos and my streams to anyone
for 10 days
so yeah you probably you guys probably
missed a lot uh but you can't even catch
up on it now
because now that i'm out of the youtube
prison
uh two months worth of videos are
gone but they will be back soon please
check my channel like tomorrow
i appreciate everyone who noticed yeah
it was very important for me everyone
everyone who was there
whoo thank you so much thank you really
really
water attacker did i give you a kiss
christian
thank you soon
um
yeah it is
some of the words got in wrong are in
order for w i see
expect no less from immortal phoenix
seems about right thank you
digital then the german
one in the german pronunciation in me is
coming up
ah um think that's a i think that's a
reference to
shitty japanese memes okay
and he wrote it in me
to me
i'm getting really confused here if i
should speak german or not because some
people
send super chats in german today because
they speak german
and they understand german but some
people send super chats in german
just by translating them in dpl and now
i don't know if they want me to answer
them in german or not but
yeah that's what you got yourself into
you might get a german answer and don't
understand what i'm saying to you
oh my god colonel koti
[Music]
i already regained my memory i'm not
your i'm not your kohai
you know exactly what you are to me
you you shouldn't be you should be
helping me regain my memory not play
into it you should be telling me
that i am your senpai
it's already over i already regained my
memory
just laid always late ollie always late
thank you for coming ollie thank you
do you understand some german
if you don't understand any german on
sunday i'm teaching gouda german
in a stream so maybe you want to comment
and and
learn some german with the viewers
together
yes yes
there is no escape
you cannot escape
everyone has to learn german now
anyway and yeah it's rich to traverti
back to traffic
[Music]
uh that foreign google translated that
that doesn't even sound
too bad that was pretty accurate good
job good job
thank you thank you love you too thank
you
more german songs
there's really not many german songs
that i like i've said this before
uh that i like and then i want to sing
on stream
well one thing i've realized like so for
example there is like a bunch
of german anime songs like for sarah
moon
and uh pokemon doors are maybe
good candidates to sing in um
in an unarchived karaoke stream or maybe
even aircraft i don't know
sometime in the future
although all of those animes i've never
watched them
in german except i mean the pokemon the
pokemon the german pokemon opening
is way more familiar to me than the
english one
so but but for example sailor moon i've
never actually watched sailor moon so i
don't know it by
[Music]
yeah that's that's kind of how it goes
in german
we i could sing that in german sometime
soon
[Music]
i really don't know because i never
really watched that or paid any
attention to digimon
i lived in town oh that's from digimon
okay i've heard the song many times
before and conventions and stuff
liptine and
[Music]
what that's how we say it in german what
the [\h__\h]
and how do you say it in english digimon
you say digging one
god damn it now we say diggy one and i
will not let you
change my mind you say digimon well
that's stupid
i guess i actually in japanese to say
that too
i've been folding up and quite possibly
bamboozled by the german language
thank you it's adorable shut up you're
adorable
we say uh digital we say in german we
say digital
that's probably why we say digimon
why you put me in this kind of
embarrassing situation
uh no you're adorable
no you're adorable shut up you're
adorable
trevor t once again thank you
i'll sing some more german for you soon
noisy neighborhood ghost rider thank you
oh thank you for the ransom for chad
i haven't seen you in a while in a long
while and even in germany
what the [\h__\h] it has noisy neighborhood
ghost rider
always been german speaking because that
german sounds like so perfect
like a normal german person is writing
that
has was ghost rider always german
does that sound so perfect
oh my god what ghost rider is
german the ghost strider that always
shows up in cali streams
i'm very curious now there's so many you
know
hidden germans between us
they're hiding and
they only show up when you ask them
but you never know the person right next
to you
might be a german speaking person
bamboozle always be ready that's why you
guys gotta learn german
secret germans everywhere they're
everywhere season
season i was just like me i was also one
of them
oh how would howard please in danger
monkey thank you monkey
thank you for two pinkies which makes
one red
what is this the common dodgers for our
hoon
okay they're dutchess phonics
[Music]
jokes glad to see the bamboozling has
ended although sad to see that it came
at a cost
i sincerely hope that this small
independent
media company running this fine video
platform
she will be able to get their issues
sorted out soon for you
thank you um
first of all yes i am not a fire chicken
i am a phoenix
god's sake and second of all
i have been unbamboozled but at what
cost
don't worry they will be soon back i i
i'm pretty sure i mean last time
um when this happened
i mean when something similar happened
my community posts all got deleted
and i thought they were gone forever but
they got
re-reinstated very soon automatically
and in this case my videos aren't like
deleted they're like
uh thank you guys for the memberships
they're like uh they got like um
they're like i mean i guess they're kind
of deleted but they're like
uh
yeah the terms of service yeah yeah i
mean it is
obviously ridiculous and all just uh
a bug because
do you really think that
i'm from was against the terms of
service of
of youtube or
um i don't think that that is against
the terms of service and also
while i was shadow band i made a new
video which probably many of you didn't
see
i made an additional video which was
m sheep i made that one which many of
you guys didn't saw
which i'm very very sad about and it's
now
gone but it will be back soon so once
it's back i want everyone who missed it
i want you guys to watch it because i
have become a sheep
and i have a playlist that is called and
zoo
and there is free videos now and there
and also
i want heart challenger to be back and
once it's back i want everyone to watch
heart challenger
got it okay awesome
no no no
japanese viewers about the shadow band
they don't use the shadow band word i
don't think they really have a
kind of word for that so it's hard to
explain
okay and 99.99
[Music]
thank you very much for supporting my
third debut
it's it's it's kind of fun to redo my w
again and again and again and again and
again
it's quite a lot of fun thank you for
supporting me and look forward to future
debuts thank you very much
jacked crabby thank you and thank you
for the pinky
afterwards
uh wow uh two and a half
two and a half red super chats
but no words with it
why why thank you very much for your
support
thank you i appreciate it
thank you unbelievable
thank you very much thank you
at least it translated well
the nothingness of that yeah yeah it's
it's
yeah translated perfectly
thank you thank you soon
thank you for the pinky
[Music]
um
thank you thank you thank you
thank you very
and that wasn't uh
oh queen is going at
uh i'm getting really confused
and thank you
hey felix style thank you for
wow a 500 red super chat oh my god
welcome to rectangle thank you i am back
i'm back
i'm back thank you for the support
wow what a generous and huge warm
welcome
back thank you i'm glad to be back
finally things are getting back to
normal slowly slowly but surely
thank you for the support i don't know
what to say that's amazing wow
wow huge support
i will use it wisely and invest in ksp
songs thank you thank you very much
cowboy
what
thank you for the red super chat though
mwah
i'm very very confused take a cake i
never know in what gym
what language to answer you because you
always donate in a different currency
it's very confusing
i don't know i don't know
huh
if
[Music]
okay i think you're writing in german
um about being in the usual room
who put i guess i guess i put you in
there
makes sense i was gonna question how how
you got in there but
i guess i put you in there stay in there
yeah
stay in there live
only thank you soon alex thank you
typhon thank you
for supporting my shirley soon to be
favorite video
yeah first definitely a first ivan
ramirez thank you dominique
helen lovelock thank you kinda thank you
star
wait do you even understand it when i
answer you in english in german because
you
donated in dollars let me answer you in
german i
am fine i'm just a bit tired and um
worried about to the streams for the
next two days because they also take a
lot of preparation
yeah yeah bye yeah i'm fine
so yeah we gotta end this stream soon
but can you guys believe one thing it's
been a couple of days now like a week
since i've come back uh to australia
australia yeah and uh
even though like for example the the
collab stream
with amelia started for me at midnight
and i went to bed
like um soon after that and i maybe fell
asleep at like 3am or so
but still i managed to wake up like
around 10 a.m or so and today i woke up
again at 9am so
it's not like like i thought that the
collab with ahmed
would [\h__\h] up my sleep schedule but no
i'm i'm like maintaining a a really good
sleep schedule
yeah it's
i don't know what's going on i think
it's uh
i think really one big factor might
actually be
that i don't have like um light uh
blocking curtains right now and that the
light actually comes in in the morning
because in japan why am i winking for
japan japan is japan
in japan i had light blocking curtains
everywhere
on all my windows so it would stay dark
like forever
and i think that might actually really
be a thing yeah
because on the last uh few days
when i took off my curtains for
like you know packing uh i was also
able to wake up earlier i think it
really is a thing yeah
sunlight is like a natural alarm clock
yeah so that's probably one of the
reasons why i've been
sleeping so early and falling asleep so
early
uh that's the same thing
what uh sleeping early and waking up
early
although i mean sleeping early has
nothing to do with that because it's
already dark
i i don't know why i'm able to fall
asleep so early
that's uh probably
just because i feel super cozy with my
kitty cats
two brain cells just collided again shut
up
see i'm already getting tired it's like
9 p.m and i'm tired
amazing amazing
so yeah that's how i am joestar
christina manzanita
goddammit legendary 231
friendly neighborhood lesbian
i'm not done thank you for the
[Music]
i am jelly doughnut and now i want a
donut
why why are you a jelly donut
that's so random where did that one come
from
but hey now i want a donut too that's
like a domino effect god damn it
oh because you're jealous i really want
donuts now god damn it
now everyone wants donuts what did you
do to us james
unbelievable i need to get some donuts
soon
and donut
did i give you a kiss james there you go
double dunkitian skill paints duncan
thank you for welcoming me so kindly
in her life german which is by the way a
joke once again let me just repeat
this is a joke this is a joke this is a
joke
uh thank you very much thank you for the
support
thank you thank you for being here and
watching my re-debut once again
on to many more
thank you
did you see my twitter profile i thought
that looks so good
i love it i love my i love
it looks so stupid and that is so funny
and so cute
my twitter profile pic
i want to keep it for a while
[Laughter]
i want to keep it can i keep it for a
while
i'll change back my name and my
description but i want to keep the
headband for a little while
[Laughter]
okay i'll keep it
um
[Music]
now that's where you get that super
chatomani
give them the first taste of they are
they had catnip before but
um i gave them catnip uh again yesterday
because
i received some
i received some uh
i bought some new things for my cats and
some of the
those things came with some catnip so i
gave it to them again yesterday
it wasn't the first time
they they like cuddle with the the floor
when they get
catnip so cute
but i don't really give that that might
have been the third time maybe
that i've ever given that to them
they're like over three years old now
and that's only the third time or second
time
that i've given catnip to them i don't
really do it often
[Music]
thank you for i think that's a red super
chat thank you for the red super chat
now go
why oh
wait a second uh
wait i think you misunderstood something
yeah i i get it though
uh because
you're a nagel which is a nail
in german but cleveland means um
cleveland means to summon clip
means that to to put something together
with uh um glue yeah glue something
together
you got something wrong because he says
please use me if you need to glue
something together but you're a nago
you're a nail
um that was probably google translation
thank you though i will make use of you
although i'm kind of
i usually let other people i let friends
do that kind of stuff
when i need to nail put some nails in
the walls or like
build furniture i honestly
i probably never nev
maybe once maybe one time in my whole
life maybe in school
in like uh a class i probably
used a nail in the hammer before but
besides that never
probably never hmm but it was clobbering
hammering
how does that
translate to to summon claim what the
hell that's
weird thank you shinto thank you
[Music]
thank you for the support i'm also
looking forward to a great time together
wait why are you acting as if this is my
first time
y'all should be helping me to regain my
memory yet you playing with me here
she did not nail the translation
unfortunately oh daisy
captain jelly thank you thank you for a
red super chat
the eyes and cancer lip that's for
stickies
i don't really understand that but thank
you thank you thank you for the support
thank you for the generous donation
stocks
invested very smartly thank you thank
you
lolli keller thank you and starkey
gymnastics
[Music]
i know only enough german to tell this
one joke i offer no apologies for it
when is this
boot
i've never heard that before it doesn't
it doesn't really make sense to me
and
sorry eh that's a reference
i don't get it i don't get it at all
but it seems like there's been like two
people
[Music]
the killer joke what
what
i don't get the reference
monty python what's the what's that
again
[Laughter]
am i lame now for not understanding it
monty python's flying circus what is
that a movie
[Laughter]
i shall educate myself a british comedy
show
oh sorry i didn't know that one
but good that it taught you some german
it must be a good show then
thank you
and we what
thank you for renting
[Music]
um
good
[Music]
empty though nothing no text of it
goddammit you guys
you guys time is night how many times do
i tell you
how many times please add something
there
i'll eat i need you to talk to me say
something i'm giving up on you please
please thank you thank you doll for the
support i appreciate it
mr mr
you mean uh you want me to say squirrel
in germany
it wasn't protest because you forgot oh
that one oh you mean
ah i see i see that that was the
protester but that makes sense thank you
sorry i can't help it i can't help it
it just happens and you want me to say
okay
ah yeah yeah yeah yes there you go
honestly we don't say that though we
don't really
like it's supposed to be some kind of
australian dialect word but we don't
really
use it i say
i say i when i speak german i say i
can't and i don't say oh
whatever weird maybe some people in
from other regions of australia because
in australia there's like really strong
dialects
um
keanu forced diago to make her d e so
she could be number one idol in her t
and that's a that's a lie but i think uh
i'm i mean i'm now the only whole life
member that lives in europe i suppose
and uh
statistically statistically speaking am
i now the
the biggest german speaking retriever
i mean i don't mainly do my streams in
german so that's like us different
i guess i can't call myself a
german-speaking victor but when i don't
actually stream in
uh german but in theory
yes
maybe i should stream more in german so
i can take that title
you're the biggest chicken witcher what
the [\h__\h] shut up
i'm not evil chicken noise i'm not a
chicken if anything that's evil phoenix
noises
stupid stupid
stop it
the biggest in europe i wonder
am i now that i'm i live in the
australia am i the biggest feature in
europe
that would be cool that would be a cool
title to have
biggest biggest european youtuber
residing in europe
yeah getting all my titles
[Music]
i want i want that i want um i want a
thingy
i want a a thing i want i want
i know i need to fair i want a trophy
give me the trophy
is like one year anniversary maybe i can
actually really
release a german cover
of it
thank you for the pinky i wanted to say
your first rew was how i got drawn into
this channel really
then i'm glad i did it i was very
impressed how much you fun
you managed to make out of a bad
situation it's still fun in a language i
don't understand well
thanks to the overworked translators
yeah when i
spoke in german i spoke i think pretty
fast
and i don't really i don't even realize
it yeah that's just what happens when i
speak in my own language i guess
the translators that probably had a very
difficult time
sorry not sorry sorry not sorry
gave up on translating immediately
maybe there will be like a full
translated clip or something i think i
mean probably there's gonna
be some clips made out of this probably
so if you wanna
uh listen to what i said in more detail
then look out for the clips i suppose
thank you clock and show i'm glad that
you
were here for another debut
thank you very much i'm glad you enjoyed
it makes you very happy thank you
f j v thank you so much
[Music]
wait should i answer in german sly do
you actually understand german
sounds like you do honestly eh
let me pour some water
i can't give it a trophy yay
anyway i'll reply in german because you
wrote me in german um
[Music]
there is no chicken next to your name
what are you talking about darren wait
oh you mean oh i mean now if i would
look at your name in the chat then i
guess there would be a chicken next to
your name
that's what you actually don't see uh
you guys membership emotes when i read
the super chats
it doesn't show them to me oh
i mean in the chat
oh dear lord anyway
thank you thank you thank you it's so
sweet how you guys uh
are so supportive of my stupid ideas of
my stupid activities thank you very much
i'm glad you guys had some fun hopefully
even though most of you didn't
understand what i was saying
thank you but i hope i made i hope i
made your
your day a little bit brighter today
i tried to make myself my own day
brighter too because it kind of sucked
these uh 10 days of being shadow
bamboozled kind of sucked
not gonna lie i was pretty freaking
frustrated
almost wanted to cry really it was
pretty close
but yeah finally it's somewhat over um
stupid [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i'm so sick of this
[\h__\h]
i'm so frustrated
[Music]
language kia look
meg valiant arc black thank you david
mini
batista no one thank you soon
you're awake actually now i keep on
forgetting that you guys are
from the fake australia and are awake
very late right now thank you for coming
even though it's like in the middle of
the night for you
thank you very much thank you for the
pinky
hope you can get back to sleep now
okay thank you
[Music]
happy birthday i guess imagine my luck
getting caught in my birthday first
superchat ever thank you for the super
chat and happy birthday
swan flyer
and thank you milk thank you scarlet
maggie bone thank you and fire trap dunk
in the red
[Music]
thank you for those sweet words yeah
thank you very much welcome back i guess
to you guys too
it's not only welcome back to me but
also welcome back to a lot of the
viewers
hopefully we will not lose each other
again some so
soon or ever again i would prefer
thank
[Music]
so about that never doing a german
stream remember saying that so how's
that working at
shut up this is special occasion okay
special occasion
pink one thank you for telling me thank
you for the pinky
you should also add the the color of
your super chat as a
as like a like a memo for me
in your super chance but don't try to
deceive me because some people here
have been trying to just deceive me like
pudding i see you i see you deceiving me
don't use my trust i know this is a joke
though because that was too obvious
[Music]
you to be like yo dawg i heard you like
debut so we will ban kiana again so she
will debut again comfort
elastic blue snake on the green glass
with good polyphonics powerful house
long liverpool
thank you very much yeah i'm glad uh i'm
glad i'm still here
going back here again thank you
thank you uh um
that looks like a christie that i would
honestly not see as a red super chat
when i read them in my list so i'm going
to say it now thank you for the red
super chat morrison
four times chum but you're saying this
about my debbie right not like you sent
free red super chats and i didn't
see them i didn't notice them and and
and oh my god i hope that i hope you
mean the
debut third time it's trump i hope that
i hope that's what you mean
thank you for the reaction thank you
thank you for the support honestly like
some currencies like i i will say it
again
because some people don't know um in my
list where i read them
and they show me the name and then the
currency
and then the amount and the text and
then where in which stream it was sent
it doesn't show the color and it shows
like mixed currencies
it doesn't i wish it would put it just
together and like
convert it all into one currency that i
choose but
yeah it doesn't do that so for some
currencies i just don't
know if it is a red one or a pink one
does it mention a rank no it doesn't
anything nothing
nothing nothing so it gets some a bit
confusing in some currency sorry
if i missed out on anyone you're welcome
to remind me that this
specific superchat was a red one
welcome to tell me if i missed it out uh
yep
yep electro john duncan
red hood seven seven seven talking
justin reinhardt duncan that two
[Music]
a big shout out to all the people live
dreams live translating the german prize
of the stream
as someone who doesn't speak german i
would like to give uh
a a hug plus one to you doing more
germans
a huge what am i reading i'm getting
confused oh my god a huge plus one to
you doing more german streams also we
know that you will overcome problems
thank you
more german streams uh very unlikely
very unlikely um
but
maybe special occasion as i said
thank you thank you though i appreciate
it
i will i will do my best it's i'm i'm
happy to see that there's a
somewhat big german following makes me
happy makes me
feel like i want to do a bit more german
content so yeah
at some point thank you also morrison
since i will miss that again no no no no
no no
no no thank you for the red super chat i
will try to remember that
thousand uh uh i think uh
uh seeds that care like a
check check and it
check is it is it check uh currency
i think thank you for the red zipper
i'll try to remember that that's a red
one
[Music]
thank you always creation not shank
no it should be czech isn't it
and i meant the first times the time
with the debbie of course okay thank god
shall i send another red one to make it
freedom no please you don't have to
for real thank you thank you only
only whenever you feel like um oh kiara
deserves a little tip now then that's
when you do it okay
hello
[Music]
[Applause]
hey if i miss my cats gotta end the
super chat reading soon
baby baby
oh she meowed at me but you guys didn't
hear it right
oh she doesn't ask me
i'm cat
thank
[Music]
thank you thank you for the support
oh so that was another australian oh
fake australian buddy
awake at a very late time thank you
ashman house
stupid
jmg jmg jmt
i agree thank you
for supporting jmd
oh he did it again he made it the third
one
oh fruit superchat is the charm
it's czech crowns although you can tell
you can't tell me what to do
have another one you immortal chicken
cheers i'm not a chicken
i'm not a chicken but okay you sent a
red super chat so i must
accept your kindness
thank you very much for the support i'm
reacting now because i don't wanna
uh miss out on the fact that it's a red
super chat later
so yeah you're getting you're getting uh
express
service right now thank you very
much for the kind support and the the
generous donation
i appreciate it thank you very much
check crowns quite close to australia
i've been i've been there before
actually i've been i've been there
before
um i've been to a casino
yeah i think yeah that's
pretty much all i remember did i do
anything else
did i do anything else there i don't
quite remember it's been a long time
gambling
[Music]
i didn't really do much honestly because
i didn't have much money to
begin with to use it on in the casino
uh i had like maybe like 10 10 euro like
and those disappeared very quickly
it didn't really do much yeah don't
worry i don't have a gambling addiction
don't worry
uh if anything i i would
maybe say i use a little bit of money on
gacha but
not too much i don't have an addiction
no for real though you guys are going to
say x
x x x but really you guys press x on
everything
you guys are over using x
hello
let me let me let me get you up here
wait one second
i'm getting tangled
hello baby hello
my baby you want to say something
huh
you i love you
i love you
she's like why have you been speaking to
the
i don't scratch on my chair behind me
she's like why have you been speaking to
the computer for like hours now
what hello
next cat hello now you're on my now you
are on my
um on my on my lap
baby baby
baby baby baby
[Music]
i love this baby so much
okay back actually that was the perfect
timing because i have to refresh your
super chat anyway because i've
reached the point where i have to
refresh
and hydrate
okay going down again
[Music]
uh scroll scroll [\h__\h] squirrel
scroll
scrolling scrolling
scrolling
to
here i found it
wow rick xboy thank you for a red super
chat double red super chat
saying i'm rick x4 i know you are
thank you why are you guys tapping jj
because of my cat she didn't why are you
guys
why are you guys writing that what
happened why
what why
yeah i know i tweeted that but not now
why
did i say jjj how did you guys come up
with that now
oh you're just saying it because my cats
because i mentioned my cats
[Music]
i have to admit that my cat ran over the
keyboard and
it opened like i was on twitter and it
opened the the the tweet
window and she tapped in jj
but i pressed enter
anyway rick explained thank you for the
uh
red super chat thank you for the genuine
donation thank you for the support
i appreciate it very much thank you and
i acknowledge your name
i do i do thank you
stormtrooper
shadow music thank
20 years ago oh god i'm old no you're
not oh don't worry about it
and the german was okay it was okay
maybe on the same level as gouda
yeah thank you
thank you for the support maybe you need
another german class though
um a couple of ones
[Music]
[Applause]
that are talking about
why that's [\h__\h]
captain jelly i don't know that's just
[\h__\h]
i that has nothing my my pc is too thick
my pc is too thick for my setup and my
my air my my my table is too small
but but it's fine for now
i can deal with it thank you for the
support
foreign
too thank you for the red super chat
hello just want to say you're wonderful
and your hard work is one of the
inspirations that's caused me to become
a fellow youtuber oh
hopefully we'll see each other in the
circles in the future and i can fanboy
over you like you fangirl or piccola
thank you that's cool congratulations on
becoming one
and have fun with it and good luck with
it hopefully you know have
a lot of success thank you for
supporting me too
thank you soon
hello
thank you for a red super chat
i've got no no mia today and woke up at
the very end of the stream how did it go
wait what's
what's that again no i know me i heard
of it before
what was that again
[Music]
what's that again
ah oh wow i like this on out here
oh what nancy keep are you okay
are you okay i hope you get well soon
but if you're sick then you can watch
lots of my streams
thank you for your support and i hope
you get better so please take care of
yourself
i wish you the best
hope you'll be up and running again soon
you gotta work for kfb after all
sick leave is not paid
as you can see because you're sending
the super chat you're paying for your
sick leave
and el dankeshen el canada
from amiibo 89
411 15
whilst in the careful play area
oh my god someone help the child
there's a child lost in the kfc play
area
darwin johnson thank you for the pinky
as of now
tradition i'll send a variant of my
first ever super chat for your reader
views
i don't usually like watching streamers
but i can't get enough of your streams
thanks for doing all you do and all you
go through you have my respectant
oh i'm happy to hear that thank you
honestly like um i get that like i used
to also not really like watching streams
so when you say i'm like the only
streamer you like watching
that makes me really happy it's a big
honor thank you for your support
i'll do my best in the future too
ace crown donkey
thank you
german anime songs you say so could it
be possible we could hear blumenthals
from killer kill in the future
i would be in your dev forever is that
originally
german or is that just a german version
of it
i don't know that song i didn't watch
kayla kill actually
sorry maybe i'll take um
my suggestions for uh
german anime songs that i can sing wow i
skipped your pinky
sorry emily all right where is it let me
go back to it
which one
ah that one sorry sorry foreign by the
way i'm broke now
no i don't want you guys to
um send so many super chats that you
guys go broke please don't do that
please don't do that but thank you for
the support really
thank you soon
[Music]
thank you and
where was i up there
here there you go okay axis one two four
seven dancing thank you for a red super
dad
the village hidden in the german what
what's that supposed to mean is that
like a song title and you want me to
sing that in german
what me not understandable
naruto reference oh okay
is that a naruto song
i didn't watch naruto oh
village hidden in the leaves
ah okay i don't really understand that
sorry axis
sorry i don't understand your joke ah
thank you though for the red super chat
also elvis thank you for the rest of the
tattoo
i'm going to say that now because that's
another one that i will not recognize
later on probably
wow thank you elvis and brooke thank you
for it don't do that
don't do that when you broke please
please don't do it
first put yourself
opportunity number opportunities
english
priority number one that's what i wanted
to say
um
[Music]
i really don't know what language to
talk to you you seem to speak every
language so i'm just going to say it in
english
thank you thank you thank you for
supporting
always always very nice to see your name
thank you very much
yeah all right
what's the other one i think it's this
little korea okay
thank you thank you for a triple red
super chat oh my god
welcome back can't really watch live
while stonks are trading so split the
super cat
evenly between you and the ah and the
two cut out that's why i said the triple
one
give them their free taste of the
devil's blend catnip
yeah yeah as i said uh before actually i
reacted to the super chat when they came
in
and as i said before they already had it
before their reactionism
like it depends on on the cat some cats
have different reactions some cats don't
react at all actually
but my cats they got like really cuddly
and they like
like like wrap themselves against
whatever surface the catnip is on
like really aggressively like
really aggressively
it's pretty cute pretty damn cute
i just can't stop laughing when i see
that
wait maybe i should put catnip all over
my body
i have legit gonna try that
as genius oh caillou enters the room
oh my god i gotta try that
[Laughter]
oh my god never had such a good idea
ever in my life before
ah smart
smart i just want them you know to come
with me
it's gonna be fun crazy cat lady mode
what's what's crazy about that
that's genius cordon i just like that
let me try it at least like let me put
it on my
feet or so and then they rub their
their faces against my feet
i think they will not cover you no i
think they will cuddle me why would they
not cuddle me
if i put it on the ground they cover the
ground if i put it on the sofa they
cover the sofa
if i put it on me they will cuddle me
yes i will do it i will report back to
you guys how it worked out
thank you soon thank you this love korea
for this great idea
thank you tango 33
34 thank you soon thank you for the
pinky
hello
slider
so
thank you for
oh
[Music]
um
you for a red super chat
scenario
called canadian not sure i understand
what you're saying with these
this badly translated german
not very short
honestly i really have no idea
well thank you for the support you try
you get it you gotta a for
trying for effort and
good job
thank you
again with a red super chat this time
i understand it anyways here's the last
of my lunch money
thank you thank you i didn't know lunch
could be so expensive that this is your
lunch money wow
thank you for giving it to me
um i hope you i hope you're not hungry
if you're hungry let me know i can i can
cook some eggs
or fry some chicken if you want
and give it to you
of course no employees will be harmed
why why would i harm any employees
no no no no no don't worry
don't worry i
don't ask where i'm getting them from
don't just don't ask okay don't question
it otherwise you're going to the usual
room
[Music]
not a lot but please accept my love and
support blue super chat
interesting razzie dazzies you sent me a
red super chat and tell me it's a blue
one
that's an interesting strategy
not sure what you're trying to achieve
with that well thank you
thank you thank you very much
thank you thank you soon
sponsored hot chicken kisses for eduardo
oh oh you're giving a red super chats
for other people
eduardo takashi okumura ellen john kfb
cassidy for mark smith and courtesy of
the soviet union
uh and kfp barrett of directors oh
we got some sponsorships
no no residences i see the color though
i remember this
hi i'm watching from the other
australian i'm glad i could finally
catch you live again the other ones
are the fake one i wanted to suggest
name las is for your cats since you
can't use their real names
i was thinking they could be called kiki
and ricky
that's actually pretty cute that's
actually kind of cute
because they are similar
names you know like fitting for sisters
uh okay um
which one is ricky though i mean ricky
kind of sounds more like a name for a
boy cat
and mine are both girls
i like the kiki but the ricky
[Music]
good try if one of them was a boy
if i was a boy
[Music]
i'm too tired attention good night oh
don't worry you i hope you're already
sleeping because you gotta you gotta put
your own health first
thank you for watching though as long as
you could thank you very much
i appreciate all the support so much
thank you really i'm glad to finally
have
my viewers back it feels good to finally
everyone here again feels really good
and we're streaming during uh
european prime time so yeah
i know fermented
black friction it's not german but i
love it if you
could sing clumsies are told from the
end of evangelion movie
actually i also want to sing i think i
never sang it before
um fly me to the moon on i want to sing
it on stream
fly me to the moon
and let me sing forever more
[Music]
you are all i long
in any case in any way
[Music]
peace
in other words please be
true in other words
darling kiss me
i love that song it's so pretty please
be
true
in other words i love
you yeah
one day hey
claymore 727
don't know what to write so here you go
thank you very much
thank you very much i like i like the
support i support it thank you i support
the support thank you
i'm getting confused sorry guys
[Music]
thank you please step on me thank you
federico
thank you for the pinky holiday
oh my god my cat is kneading on my
blanket
she really needs my clothes oh my god i
really gotta go there but i'm pretty
much done
okay let's get this done and your
schedule says
i have a schedule for tomorrow i have
german
we've got a schedule for tomorrow but it
but then when do i have the karaoke
schedule do i have that for sunday
did i mix it up was it saturday and
sunday it was it was it saturday good
out and sunday singing
wait i have both tomorrow am i [\h__\h]
crazy no way
oh my god i'm crazy
now today i used all day to prepare for
this stream
yeah i don't think i can do both
i don't think i can do both
because i barely know the songs yet
i want to like take like a like a half a
day to learn the songs
uh yeah
sorry sorry
sorry oh dear no no no no neera is not
gonna be canceled no no no no
i'm playing near on sunday um the
karaoke stream will be my god she's
kneading
blanket oh mommy mommy
that's so cute she doesn't do that
she doesn't do it that often so every
time i see it it's like
so special to me it makes me so happy to
see her happy
oh my god that's like the best thing
ever
okay anyway okay then tomorrow and the
stream of gooda
and then sunday near and members only
[Music]
the cuba
no i want to do it um i want to practice
properly
for those songs postpone the member
stream
no no
no no i don't wanna i wanna do a memory
stream
i want to do that but hey guys next week
we actually have some
exciting things a lot of exciting
streams going on next week is actually
also packed because um
uh half year
anniversary although i might end up not
doing anything
for like um half year
kiana anniversary but
homo talk is coming back and i'm also
having another collab with
uh
senpai next week i'm doing a collab with
the senpai which will be like my my
kind of japanese only stream next week
because i haven't done the japanese only
stream in a long long time
and i kind of wanted it to i wanted to
combine it with a collab i mean we also
have holo talk next week but that's like
i mean i'm translating so that's that
but i wanted a stream where i can just
focus on you know having fun
i haven't done one like that in a while
haven't done a proper
uh normal japanese collab in a while now
so yeah that will happen next week and
and yeah whole talk guest will be
announced on sunday
and yeah and then we have the half year
anniversary
um stream and
i will play new year again next week and
raiza
possibly maybe i'm not gonna promise it
even though i said already we might do
it next week but
i'm not gonna promise it i gotta check
my schedule but
we might pick up yakuza again next week
uh because i now got permission to play
yakuza uh again on
pc so we can actually pick off where we
left off
i barely remember but i guess i'll just
watch my own stream
to remind myself of what we did and you
guys should do the same although
wait was that in the last two months
is it even possible to re-watch that
stream right now
does that stream exist right now when
did that happen didn't it happen in
december
then i guess it should be there i think
it's there
i think the yakuza stream is
watchable right now so if you guys
didn't watch my first
stream of yakuza you should uh watch it
soon
because i'm going to pick it up again
back then it was a sponsored stream but
i just want to continue and it's not
going to be sponsored
i just want to continue um playing it
on my own because it was pretty much fun
it was quite a lot of fun
yeah uh
uh
will probably not be next week but the
week after yeah
sorry that's a big delay but i already
pretty much planned out the whole next
week i already planned
most of it ah but actually you know what
i guess i could do that as my kind of
half year anniversary stream
that would work actually that could work
okay
okay okay no contest though because
that's like
to me right now that's too much to
organize i don't
i just don't have a brain for that right
now sorry
i wanted to do something exciting but
we'll do that for my
birthday and for my one year anniversary
i'll do something big again
i'll do a contest again but at the
moment i don't have the brain space
to organize um
another contest even though actually it
would just be making a reddit post
saying hello i'm doing this contest but
later than reviewing everything
it's going to be stressful because also
you know what's coming next week as well
which kind of stresses me out now white
day and we said that one mom one month
after february the 14th one month after
valentine's day
i would look at the chocolates again
exactly so that's
on sunday and i am aware of it and i am
at the moment planning to really do a
stream for that
um so i will do my best to fit that into
my schedule
new um chocolates are not going to be
reviewed everything that has been
sent in after the uh until the actual
deadline
will be reviewed everything that came
after will not be reviewed i didn't
check actually i didn't see if there was
anything after that but yes
yes yes yes it's very busy for some
reason i don't know how
i deleted my chocolate post why would
you do that what the hell were you too
embarrassed or something
what why would you delete it
what about april fool april fools april
fools is still so long to go
i don't know maybe maybe we'll do
something for that
will you pick up new again yeah on
sunday this sunday the day after
tomorrow i'm playing here
and i have new year planned for next
week as well so
we're gonna get near done soon
i'm gonna do it every week now from now
on
also i got a new controller i got one of
those uh razer pink
ps controllers it was really pretty one
so i'm gonna play near with that one
well super bunny one return eventually i
think so yeah eventually when i want to
collab with america we could play that
again
that was fun i had so much fun with ame
on that night it was nice to
bond a bit more i want to bond with
everyone more with
the whole live english girls we need
honestly like
if we could meet each other all together
that would be just the greatest thing
ever
oh at the moment it's just difficult
because everyone is busy
everyone has their own schedules
everyone is like
in a different time zone legit now
so it's so different to actually like
do stuff together besides those collabs
that we do every once in a while
so i'm putting i'm i'm trying to make
more
collabs with one-on-one at least yeah
anyway i'm almost done with the super
chat so let me finish them
down um
yeah thanks for coming like at the end
of my stream hey
hey hey hey hey hey you missed my german
w it was pretty funny
maybe you can watch a bit of the archive
if you're bored or something
i have finally been on shadow band in uh
i've been shadowgun for like
10 days and now my videos are gone
so unfair but hey i'm back
a phoenix always comes back phoenix
always revives
phoenix never dies invincible
thank you for everything you've done for
camping for staying strong though
through very tough times you never
forgot that you had comrades along the
way helping you
please thank gemma for kfb from kfb as
well and never
forget we got you back we would never
desert you green
that's not a green one that's the red
one
thank you soon thank you thank you
thank you very much
thank you um yeah i'll thank
genma again from you guys i think she's
listening anyway oh my my actually she
might be asleep now
i hope she's asleep honestly
i'm worried about genma because she's uh
definitely the oh god she's a wig isn't
she yeah she's awake
oh no so hard for her
oh no she's destroying her
sleep cycle for me if there ever really
was one no i want some wonder to be
healthy
please please don't watch my streams
don't watch them
oh no honestly
that's that's so crazy like
she's she looks like on the other side
of the globe and
watches my streams even in the middle of
the night
and i think that's just
wow she doesn't even need to do it but
she does it because she's a great
manager and the best manager i could
ever ask for
[Music]
i'm making myself sad oh
man
starship sn10 thank you for the pinky
i flew i barely flopped i did a flip i
landed then i become
became a fireball permission to rise
again like a phoenix and revive as my
next is
it iteration is that how you say it
wait wait starship sn10
i flew i fell apart i didn't flip island
is that about like um
i think i saw that is that something
that landed
like the the rocket that flew and then
it landed but it did like a fr
whoop and then it landed again is that
is that what we're talking about
is that the thing ah
i i give you permission to rise again if
you can didn't you like it looked like
it exploded i don't think you can rise
again but keep trying good luck with
that
unfortunately you're not a phoenix but
you can try
maybe they'll be so nice to repair you
if that's possible
i hope they can repair you
good luck
almost close enough thank you soon it's
truman
uh for saying thank you
soon
okay i need to color with my cats and
eat and hydrate and sleep and do all
those kind of things
um hope you guys had fun
on behalf of kfb thank you for
everything that you do
oh you're talking to jenna well she
deserves it okay
you work so hard and bring joy to so
many i don't know what we would do
without you but through these tough
times we'll stay with you please take
care of yourself we love and respect you
gemma oh hi kiara
but i mean she does deserve that but why
do
why you gotta do me like that why are
you gonna do me like that yeah
now i will not give you a kiss because
gemma would be the one to have to give
you a kiss
thank you for a red super chat you also
don't get the kiss because that one
would have to be you know
obviously you're directing that super
chat at genma not like me
so you're not getting a kiss
i hope you receive your case from janma
soon
hope that was worth it thank you
thank you so thank you thank you for the
pinky i can't really read that
echo and stone there yeah
does have it mean basketball i'm dead
perished in head towards the
slovene i think i understand part of
that
thank you dominique okay guys
thanks for thanks for joining me in this
fun fun adventure once again i'll see
you guys tomorrow
collab with gooda i'll prepare
everything
and the collab with kuda will be the
only stream tomorrow i'm moving the
karaoke sorry sorry sorry
uh so yeah see you tomorrow and everyone
in german you must know by now what we
say in german
and in german we say auf wiedersehen
thank you all of you
i'm back now let me push my elgato
stream deck button for the ending
thank you
[Music]
you