[Music]
i like that it's bagging time i'm
stealing that
it's batting time
[Music]
it's
backpacking banking
[Music]
yeah yeah
i'm bagging
i'm banging
she's
back your pardon
[Music]
uh
everybody
welcome to
hollow bags
what's in your bag
quest bark
hello
for this occasion i have put on some
very versatile glasses they however
won't really stick to my face
so i have to hold them
they wobble so much
they move so much
please give me more
options please
i need more options
hello everybody what's up i
am i have this stream prepared uh in
exchange for something else i was
supposed to do duolingo today
and study korean but
duolingo is on vacation
like i'm not even kidding
apparently some companies are on summer
vacation so i could not get permission
in time sumima sorry
can't paint it to my nose because i
apparently i have no nose yeah
and anyway that's okay because i had
this idea actually
a long time ago
and
i don't remember how long ago it was i i
talked about it on stream though
um
and i may have even typed the request
for people to participate
uh on the stream but that was a long
time ago yeah
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah long long time ago and and i
i i first you know what i did back then
is
i wrote
like we have like a channel
where
yeah we asked like hey who wants to
collab or i want to do this and then i
have this idea and this and that so i
wrote
like hey i want to do this back review
would you guys like send me
your
[Music]
contents of your bag but the problem was
probably number one i made it like like
an open
call thing like oh whoever wants to join
please feel free to join and send me a
photo sometime soon the second problem
was that i didn't give a deadline i
guess
so
um
nobody
nobody answered to my request that i did
months ago
nobody
so after a while i was like okay this
was i guess not the right way to
approach it i'm not sure if they're all
um too nervous about showing the
contents about of their bag maybe maybe
they feel like it's not secure not safe
enough or they just couldn't be bothered
because there's no deadline
[Laughter]
but i got no reply
so
yeah this week i remembered that idea
and i was like you know what i really
kind of want to do this it's a good idea
for a short stream relatively short i
might do it longer because i got more
bags than i expected because this time i
messaged
everybody
uh
privately in a dm instead of doing it as
an open call
which gave me
much more results than
previously because previously i got no
results
[Laughter]
yeah and i also gave them uh i think
about 24 hours
so
uh or maybe even more partially but yes
i i gave people only a short amount of
time i told them hey i'm doing this
tomorrow want to send me a picture
before you go to sleep please thank you
and then yeah
[Music]
if you give people like a deadline of
one week later or so
they will probably forget about it they
will be like oh i can do it then in two
days or so i could i don't have to do it
now so there's no sense of urgency right
so
actually i think the smartest choice
when you want something from whole life
members
is not give them a long deadline but
give them the shortest deadline possible
of one day
if not even less
some girls i gave them a 15 hour
deadline not even a full day
so then when they read it if they
actually would like to participate
then
they have to do it the moment they see
the message
and i also said
you have to give this suggestion how
about you do it before you go to sleep
isn't that a good idea huh so it worked
really well this time
i have um
oh wait i just see something in this
here is uh
messed up you sure i am
i think i messaged yeah message
everybody in en not everybody got back
to me but that's okay that's
understandable i didn't expect everybody
to get back to me i messaged some of id
and some of japan members that i thought
might be up for it uh in a short amount
of time if we think this was a good idea
then we might do it again because i am
very
very convinced by this stream idea of
mine
yes
you're welcome
yeah yeah some japanese members
show me your back you have 16 hours to
comply
smart right
now i also gave all of them
kind of a sample picture
of how i would like it to look like
yeah uh but most of them went by that
sample picture some of them
looking specifically at a certain
someone you will understand later
um some of them did it differently
but that's that's okay there is an
explanation for that
and um
what was i gonna say uh
brain empty
oh yeah you want to know who got back to
me instantly the fastest like literally
after like two minutes
you wanna know
[Music]
oh wait i can't tell yet
i can't say it because
actually
okay you know what so there's the the
person who got back to me we want to
make this a riddle but the person that
got back to me
the fastest
is also the person i'm gonna show the
first because
let's use her as an example of how we're
gonna do this because the image that she
sent me
already no matter how much i put a
mosaic filter on it it's still
very obvious who did it so
let's get this party started whatever me
taking myself
come in please screen come down
um
[Music]
screen please
beautiful
hello screen
[Music]
okay now we need a photo shampoo
polisher
[Music]
there we go
this time i got it to work and i now i
know now why last time i tried to
capture photoshop it didn't work but i
figured it out because i have glasses
now so i'm automatically smart
let's go
this is how we're gonna do it i show you
a mosaic picture
and then you guys gotta tell me what you
want to look at first
i might comply to that and then i'm
gonna reveal one by one i'm gonna get
rid of the mosaic and then you know
eventually we're gonna find out who that
belongs to
and you have to guess in the chat but
the first one is so obvious that's why
i'm using it as a sample
the problem is maybe you see it here
but
there's something suspicious in the top
right
it's okay ollie i don't think i actually
told you that i wanted to be a like a
mystery so it's not your fault at all
that's i guess something that kind of
you know came to my mind later on
so this is what do you guys want to look
at
what do you want to look at first i'm
going to get rid of the mosaic some
things are maybe so big that you can
already guess what it is but
who is it
who
[Music]
but this is the only one that will be
that easy i think yes that's let's
change to change to jazz you like jazz
okay so what i wanted to say is ollie
got back to me the fastest immediately
she's so motivated and when she replied
to me i was like okay maybe
maybe this
idea of a stream has hope after all
maybe some will get back to me after all
if ollie gets back to me
then i have some hope
oh
okay what do you want to look at what do
you want to look at next
um i up actually i didn't ask so many
from id next time i gotta ask more of
them but anyway pgm oh sorry
uh
how do you know it's chess
she apparently carries many chests with
her wait wait she actually also some
people sent me a little bit of an
explanation to the items she did send me
uh some explanation that i thought was
really interesting and made me
think olly must be quite a
nice person to be around with
yeah so she has a mini chest and
you know i'm actually gonna uncover the
one right next to but what do you think
is the one right next to it on the left
side what do you think that is
[Music]
because
i want to talk about those two items
she does have a miniature hey
phone phone calculator
sliding puzzle phone phone phone phone
that would be a fancy phone
no it's turret cards
which i found really interesting because
just recently i talked about wanting to
pick up how to read tarot cards again
because i kind of forgot
yeah different cuts and they look shiny
and fancy
so
i think ollie is like pretty much the
only person who i know
not quite true but always one of the few
people who brought like games
with them in their bags and she says to
why i have turret and chest in my bag i
only go out when i'm meeting up with
friends and family and sometimes there
would always be that awkward silence
where we run out of topics i don't like
it when we start pulling out our phones
and stop talking so i prepared terroret
in chess hoping that we can still talk
without looking at our phones
i love that
i love that that that's what made me
think you know actually that's kind of
similar to me like i don't bring games
but
yeah it's i i don't like awkward
silences and she tries to overcome it by
bringing games i think that's really
nice
to get people off of their phones
and
i i would i would love to have you know
when i'm around the volley and we
if we ever run out of things to talk
about
i would love her to read me some tarot
cards
and i would love to play some chess with
her
i love that
nan
[Music]
oh we can do that surely ollie's you
still here i'm up for it let's do it
okay what do you want to look at next
that almost looks like something that
nenechi would
own in my opinion
[Laughter]
yes
you want to look at that one juice box
oh i guess it looks like juice box but
it looks like a necklace to me
[Music]
yeah
but what is it
sticky notes and a pen
ah cute it is a carrot it's like a
carrot with tiny eyes on it
oh oh i see some korean on it is it from
korea what did she write no i think it's
from korea that looks like it's um
printed on
oh
my momma
sticky notes actually but i i like cute
sticky notes but i bought like a million
sticky notes in my life so far and they
never actually stick
like especially the cute ones maybe the
the most well-known like professional
like
basic looking ones
from that most popular brand i don't
know what they're called again
but that was a baby stick but all the
other cute ones they they don't stick
yeah post it like the official post-its
those stick well more or less i would
say
these cute ones never stick it's so sad
yeah what the hell that's the only
purpose that's the only job you have in
life to stick
why can't he even do that
oh my god
okay what are we gonna look at
next i'm not gonna i guess i shouldn't
ask for everything because
then it's gonna take ages
i'm gonna ask you one more time
um
the red one yeah it looks like a
japanese um shrine charm if you look at
it like this what is it i don't know ah
oh no
it is keys with
some it's not quite um
it's just like a bag to put your key in
i guess that's what it's supposed to be
for
a wallet for your key i guess
woohoo it does look like a charm kind of
yeah
okay let's let's reveal the other things
i guess that's a phone yeah
oh with like a lavender
silicone
uh
[Music]
is that an iphone i don't know what
phone that is it only has one camera
nowadays all phones have like five
cameras
which phone only has one one camera
these days i'm roasting your phone ollie
what phone is that do you guys recommend
it uh
um recognize it
an old phone
iphone
xrs e
it's a rarity yeah
but even though it has just one iphone
cameras even the older ones as far as i
know are pretty damn good
even if they only have one
that's my backup phone my very phone
yeah yeah yeah see that's what i also
when i was about to take a picture and i
had my my main phone laid out oh yeah i
actually took a picture too of my stuff
um i was like oh
hmm i guess good that i have another
phone to take a picture with
okay
not on the nets not her not her main
phone
makes sense yeah you may not see phones
on everybody's pictures because that's
probably what they used to take a photo
but we'll see we'll see let's open up
the top thingy what is that a wallet oh
a wallet
that's all
not what i expected um
from you know as a wallet because it's
so thin and small but i guess it's just
full of cards maybe only only uses cards
oh it's a coin purse
oh okay now what is this charger cable
uh-huh
this
thing
these wireless earbuds i swear to god is
there almost an every freaking
picture that i got sent everybody has
wireless earbuds but i don't
i actually don't so i was like yo these
kids they all have something in common
they have wireless earbuds
should i be jealous should i feel
should i feel intimidated inferior yuki
oh is this yukio no
did someone think that's yugioh cards
it's a backup mask from bt21 it's cute
cute
very colorful sasuka only
airpods yeah but i i would just you know
think i would lose them i prefer you
know
the good old cable ones
then what is this what is this black
thing on the side it's not nothing's
written on it now maybe it belongs to
the bag no i don't know
but anyway the purse the bag itself cute
i have a similar one like that
i like it
oh cute
a light pink purse and there you go
that's ollie's back yeah
the first is cute yeah
pink
very girly 10 out of 10. but yeah what
stood out to me very much was the the
cards at and the mini chests
now now i'm actually looking forward
that sounds as if i would have not
looked forward to it before but now i'm
looking forward even more to meeting
ollie
it's a great conversation starter too i
would say um
[Music]
nice nice nice nice flies
okay yes
[Music]
then uh did i tell you how many bags i
have i have i think 13 bags it's quite a
lot i actually got like two or three
more this morning
[Music]
or four even yeah last night it wasn't
that much yet but we still got a few
more it's actually more than i thought i
would uh deal with that by the by the
time i made the slot yesterday the
reservation i only had like six and i
was like even for six i can do an hour
i mean it's already been 23 minutes and
i showed one bag so
um
[Music]
okay
um
the next bag
has quite a lot of items
[Music]
and looks
on the first side looks kind of girly
because of all the
pretty colorful colors
on the first side what do you think
who's who is this
just by the colors maybe and the amount
of items
[Music]
yeah because of the purple
amma kelly muna muna shion
yago
rena
but one thing that already you guys are
seeing clearly
is the switch and i was impressed by
that switch because what is that cover
it looks so cool
i want that too
yo it's so fancy i like it it's like so
space themed or like
i don't know it's really cool
[Laughter]
i i think yeah i mean i guess i could
see mona using that
but i i want the cool case like that too
i guess it's not a case is that stickers
because it's just is that just stickers
i wonder
recognize
the green stuff up there
so
wait we have a switch and we have oh
pokemon
games
this person brings pokemon games whipped
up
and
a nintendo ds
on their travels on their
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
i mean you know sano space and she likes
pokemon
switch yes yeah i feel like
she probably doesn't bring all of this
all the time
maybe it's just like
she sometimes bring that brings that
with her
or she brings one of those with her
maybe i i can't imagine having so much
stuff with you all the time
what do you want to look at next
[Music]
is that a ps or ps vita on the right oh
you mean this lengthy thing wouldn't
that be too small i forgot what it is
let's take a look
oh that looks like a glasses case
of
is that a poke is that also pokemon case
oh isn't that pokemon that's pokemon too
a glasses case who needs glasses
could i guess you could probably also
put sunglasses in there but usually do
people not just use it for normal
glasses
even more pokemon oh must be quite the
pokemon enthusiast
i love this because we can get actually
quite a a nice insight into the person's
personality or like hobbies and
interests yeah that we didn't know
apparently
maybe
okay so that's glasses let's take a look
at
this bright green thing here oh okay
double mint bubble gum
uh-huh so bubble gum type of person a
gum gum type of person
not a hodor
let's take a look at all of those
i think this is
quite a giveaway
because
i mean maybe maybe not for you guys
maybe you can't see i think those are um
band-aids but
[Music]
it's
band-aids but there's japanese writing
on it
do you see it
[Music]
now that changes everything
[Laughter]
okay okay let's take a look
what is this oh
more japanese items a protein bar
do we know someone who has some
member claimed they like pokemon and
protein bars
[Music]
is mozzarella time for a protein verse
really
is that song
this is fun
okay what is this
ah that's just uh
oh
ah it's um okay this is quite the girly
thing that maybe uh the the dudes among
you don't know what it is
it's like a oil um paper for your face
when you when your face gets oily these
are like really thin
sheets
that you tap on your face
uh
to make it less oily
who brings that
who has an oily face
it's getting
it's getting girly is it getting girly
let's take a look at this
a gucci something like either a perfume
or a mist or your hands cream something
a body oil a shimmer body okay okay it's
getting really girly
[Music]
a gamer girl this is totally a gamer
girl what we have here at hand
we have a
ah this is like a lip um lipstick lip
lip lip gloss
hydra bomb lip gloss not a doll
is this
oh eyeliner eyeliner eyeliner don't know
the brand though a lot of makeup yeah
chanel oh it looks like a mascara
more makeup this net
how about how about this
more makeup
now
i
think i have seen this person use this
before
[Laughter]
eyeshadow and
oh
[\h__\h]
isn't this some this art this is from
kate but this artwork this art style
looks familiar to me
oh yeah
huh
ah
quite the popular makeup brand in japan
at least i've never seen it outside of
japan though
um
isn't this like zoom in okay okay
here if you want to take a closer look
this is what we have so far
wow
okay okay
[Music]
what if it's yours mine
nah i wouldn't have japanese ban ban
so-called band-aids anymore
oh there's really a lot of stuff in this
bag what is this
poor poor what poor professional
poor what
poor poor what is that what is that
for your pores
porefessional the porefessional pore
what puller port
pour
yeah maybe a concealer like a cream yeah
and this oh a little brush okay small
brush because not much space in this bag
anymore
let's take a look
it's a little wallet
ah for for the keys maybe
oh
well well well wow
does that give away everything but it's
an avid gosling
[Music]
i'm a ghost link
who has i'm a keychain specifically
and all these tiny uh polo myth ones
i mean i mean maybe makes you think miko
senpai but would miku senpai really have
all of the
myth
small baby keychains i don't know man a
more makeup i guess a lipstick
here earpods as i said everybody has
them
some hair ties
and last but not least let's take a look
at the bag i like this one
i like it
there we have it
so what's your final guess guys
why is it gouda's bag
it is
kali's bag
[Music]
[Applause]
i think you know that the america
keychains confused and surprised me too
um
why am i specifically we will never know
but i think all of the pokemon uh and
the makeup gives it away if you know her
maybe not if you like if you just watch
her streams you maybe don't know about
you know makeup but she always carries
quite quite
um she always carries makeup with her
that's for sure
and i think the protein bar
is also a cali kind of thing uh
i think she you know tries to get that
protein because she wants to work out
and also she doesn't have much time to
eat so maybe you know a quick snack
yeah
yeah and uh
she does like you know pink she's she's
pretty girly actually here and there so
yeah you know the pink colors and i love
the bag it's cute it's kind of you know
the the creepy kind of cute art style
cute cute cute very cute
yeah
um
the pokemon everything else makes sense
yeah well kelly
um did not ever make it a secret that
she likes pokemon i think she was when
we were allowed to play pokemon she was
quite enthusiastic about it i think
um
yeah yeah yeah
pokemon trainer cali
scythe
oh you know she doesn't always bring her
stuff i guess
she's on hiatus anyway
i never thought when i looked at kelly
that her face is oily but i did notice
like i i don't think i ever saw
anyone use these oil papers outside of
japan but when i lived in japan like
every japanese friend i had every girl
friend that i had they all had these
these old oil papers they all used them
i think especially like also in in
summer in the humid weather your face
gets even more oily and then you just
pat pat pat your face and it gets better
but i don't use them
no no it's not alcoholic wipes it's just
like a really thin dry paper
that takes the oil
off of your skin
it's not wet it's dry
ah
maybe maybe kelly will talk a little bit
about this in her stream sometime maybe
i don't know
but that's that was kelly's bag yeah
[Applause]
let's take a look
at the next bags
i hope i'm allowed to show this
so here it's not too many items
not too many items
it's not so much
to be honest like these days i also
don't carry that much around with me
anymore i carry as little as possible i
used to carry much more
in my bag than i do nowadays but
yeah so we see a big freaking spider-man
plushie
is it or is it is it even a plushie
maybe it's the bag itself
maybe it's one of those plushie bags i
don't know
this one is a little bit nuzzle
oh sure
so spiderman fan do we know
of any spiderman fans
[Music]
crab you want to see the crab yes it's
the crab this one confused me too
i asked what it is and this is a pen
holder
[Music]
doesn't bring a lot of people
things doesn't bring a lot of things
with them but
brings a pen holder crab
[Music]
[Laughter]
what do you want to look at next
[Music]
the pen holder
yeah
who could be bringing that pen holder
the picture actually the person who has
this crab in their bag
uh sent me a picture of how to use it
and
it was being used not by a normal pen
but by an
a digital tablet pen actually
so maybe somewhat of an artist hmm
hint hint maybe
[Laughter]
oh
it's definitely
eaten now they think it's yours oh yeah
what is this
now this is uh this looks like final
fantasy to me
[Laughter]
okay okay
okay okay okay okay that was too easy
now we have a um
a peanuts
makeup bag i think i think i was told
that both of these are makeup bags let
me check again
[Music]
ah i know this is a makeup bag that she
brings with makeup inside from peanuts
snoopy
oh it's not be cute
and then this one
this one i was told
she carries like um you know like stamps
signing stamps with her which is quite a
japanese thing to do um instead of you
know writing signatures with their hands
they normally use a hankle a stamp
han kotoka haiti
so okay well i mean it's no use hiding
it anymore
what's that what's that though
what is that
the turquoise thing is that something i
should know
is that marvel too or so oh that's lucky
i mean we definitely can recognize the
interest here
the bag is from
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah i feel like you know
the the spiderman kind of already gives
it away a little bit i already saw
correct answers in the chat when i
showed the spiderman yeah and matt but
the keychain
is very obvious i think she's playing
final fantasy right now as we speak
um
fubuki is a marvel nut yeah as far as i
know yeah she likes marvel a lot as far
as i know
but i just wonder why does she bring
the crab
[Music]
[Laughter]
when do you need
i guess you could not only use it as a
pen holder but you could also use it as
a
as a
um chopsticks holder
pen
no no
no
why not bring the crab i want the crab
but i wouldn't bring it with me
i love crap crap for moral support
defense mechanism oh yeah pinch pinch
your enemies yeah
pinch them good
pinch butt cheeks of marine senpai when
she has recordings with her
oh mine and senpai would be like oh
please continue
i can actually see that happening
i can totally imagine that
yes okay
next back next bug
next bag
okay
ah
what is these
um i will not reveal the top thingy
because that actually reveals whose it
is
[Music]
now these are drawn um i was asked if
drawing is okay drawing is okay um i
think she took a picture and then drew
on top of it or so
um
yes yes yes that's totally fine well
first of all we see i think the bag
itself
is a heart-shaped bag
it's very cute i i actually i used to
own a black heart-shaped
shaped bag exactly like this
yeah
exactly like this one
i think so i don't own it anymore did it
go i miss it now
[Music]
don't
where did it go i missed it
i feel like
this one will be an easy guess
eventually depending on what i show you
guys first um but the thing is i don't
quite remember what all these things are
when i look at them in mosaic
so what is this oh
well maybe the
maybe the handwriting will give it away
at least we know now it must be an
english-speaking member
ah random trash i haven't recycled yet
not a hotel well i'll be honest i have
random trash and like receipts that i
don't need in my bag all the time too
ah
[\h__\h] the handwriting gave it away did it
oh no what is this
cat pouch wallet oh
cat shaped wallet this person must like
cats surprise
random hair ties
yeah i do have that around sometimes
although recently my my hair tie supply
has been
getting smaller and smaller because they
just don't disappear god damn it what's
this
lip gloss ah lip gloss type of person
what is this
goddamn those earbuds and why does
everybody have those fans here but
i'm still using cabled wired ones
[Music]
it's
her cell phone
with
apparently avatar
[Music]
i don't know the hand lotion
that i think i know that brand um
that looks like from what's it called
look look
leave something with
something like what was it look look
what was it how do you pronounce it
that's green with that round thing
i think yeah look look
looking look yeah i don't know how to
pronounce that but
that must be a yeah
what's this by the way
[Laughter]
okay okay okay it's fun now yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah lip balm
a cat plus keychain
i knew i shouldn't show this fake
i knew it was something that will give
it away
yeah and
i know these are random coins
yeah as we know
from the story i told you guys when i
asked fauna fana can you can you tell me
what these american coins are she could
not help me so this is very much
compliant to the story i told you
previously she puts down these coins and
she doesn't know what these are
i don't think that's what's how she
meant it but um i mean
what's in fana's bag this is infauna's
bag
fanatic
[Music]
cute
obviously cat related stuff
some makeup like not much though just a
lip gloss and lip balm some hand lotion
[Music]
ear buds random hair ties yeah it's not
too much stuff in there but also the
back doesn't fit that much stuff anyway
[Music]
those two vata and fauna
it fits one alone yeah i think it's very
fun like i mean i i had the pleasure to
meet her for one day and i must say
this represents her well yeah yeah
okay
next bag
where do we go which one should we do
all right let's go
let's go with this one oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
is not the only artist in whole life
okay could be eof
could be
marine
i don't know could be a couple people
let's find out
now i liked how clean this picture was
how
well
um how well made
so let's take a look what do you want to
look at first
daniel mira
[Music]
smells like taco
uh
the black and white all over this one
meow meow meow meow meow meow something
with cats oh this one's cute
kitty cats it's a it seems to be
a notebook
it's a little notebook it's very cute
let me show you the pattern
[Music]
okay let's just act as if we don't know
okay guys
let's just act as if we don't know
who could this be
what's this thing
oh
a pen holder
and now the person who's bringing just
like football senpai who's bringing a
pen holder but i mean for for inani
actually kind of makes more sense i
think because she's bringing
art supplies with her as we can see
yeah
a bear pen holder
cute yeah you know it's here
inna is here but this is not not totally
not inna's bag i don't know what you're
talking about
what did i just say
did i just say
oh
anyway
um
airpods
i feel like the cool kids all have
airpods man what
what
[Music]
he's so cute he reminds me of there's
this anime
uh shirokuma cafe or something like that
ice spare cafe i don't know um something
like that
it was cute and there was like a bear
like that but
in white because it's an ice bear a pole
out there sorry paula bear
yeah cute cute and then the air pawns oh
wait this is what you wanted me to see
there's like oh you see those guys it's
like a
[Laughter]
very typical inna
a cow emoji on top of the airpods but is
that really on there or did you draw it
on it is that really on there i guess so
airpods special edition oh it is on
there well how do you know you know this
is totally not your bag how do you know
must be someone that ina has met before
what is this
big [\h__\h] relaxo cat
it looks like a mix of a rela oh relax
so what's um
relax so in english again
uh
german name for the pokemon snorlax
still like that speaking of snorlax oh
it's a hat warmer
it's hot water inside a hand warmer
but it's a cat it's not it's not a
snorlax but it looks a little bit like a
snorlax cat
yeah in german it's relaxing because it
relaxes yeah
well
okay
i wanna look at this
it's an umbrella
the smarties umbrella i love it where'd
you get that from
i love it i already just recently i had
to buy a new one
but i didn't buy a cute one like this
and i like this one it's cute i like the
color
and the chocolate color mmm smarties
m m's oh wait i'm saying smart did i
just say smarties um
you guys have smarties too like smarties
is like the big version of m m's here i
guess like a little bit bigger than a
little bit bigger than m m's
i said smarties yeah it's not the same
thing i guess in my head it's like the
same thing but it's not the same thing i
don't think it's the same company
you're doing canada smarties are
different in the u.s oh
interesting i have to look it up
[Music]
yes we have smarties smarties are better
smarters are different
different canadian smileys versus
smarties
hard candy
oh here they are filled with chocolate
they're just like a bigger version of m
m's
as far as i remember i haven't eaten
them in a long time but i'm pretty sure
pretty sure was this
candy
yes this
uh this
this is the one from
harry potter perry hotter
hotter new nickname i just recently gave
him the name harry potty and now we have
perry hotter
yo those are those yeah the perry potty
snacks
there you go i thought i misread i
thought i didn't read it properly that's
really what it says
yeah the beans
[Music]
are there like the
the bad tasting ones too i wonder
i wonder
you could do like you know those
challenges where you eat them and you
don't know which flavor is which but
then there's like a lot of really ew
tasting ones
[Music]
yeah ear wax and vomit
ew
why is this cute
ah you know i really love this stuff
that ina it's totally not inna but i
love the stuff that ina has so unrelated
but you know i just love the stuff that
ina has because
it's so cute
it's so cute it's so simple
like simple designs but very cute
very solid cute designs
and i mean we almost don't have to
uncover it but
here we have a sketchbook
and here we have a tablet and i asked
inna about the tablet because i was like
didn't you bring like your ipad when we
were together
yeah apparently she she uh when she
travels she brings either the tablet or
the ipad mm-hmm
that'll
well not everyone has to show the actual
back we're just asking what's inside
yeah so this was ina yeah
see she takes you know she takes
the art of art very serious she always
has to be able to
draw everywhere everywhere she goes um
yeah when she was uh
going around places with us she also had
it's ready at all times that she could
draw at all times it's a backpack
usually so it didn't fit in the picture
oh yeah yeah i remember yeah you were
you were carrying a
a pretty normal looking backpack
a pretty normal looking backpack i think
it was
yeah gotta fit as many things as
possible and you know a tablet and a
sketchbook that can they can be pretty
big yeah yeah thank you
thank you i love how this is so clean
you know not not every picture was this
clean
thank you so much yeah pro artist ina
sasuka
very recognizable just by looking at the
mosaic very obvious
sugar
yeah
okay
so the next bag did not quite follow the
um example
in like how to lay it down but that's
okay
um there is one that's even worse so
uh this is so
yeah this is so
close enough
let's take a look
well well well i already see
a water bottle
[Music]
okay
thankfully no label on it that gives
anything away
the haunting points
what do you want to look at
black bag yeah
it looks like a black bag
bottom right
next to the bottom like so okay
aha
it's that looks like hand sanitizer
what is that is that hand sanitizer yeah
it looks like aloe vera hand sanitizer
water water it must be good enough
[Laughter]
totally ah
little i don't know that brand
this has to be based why does it have to
be based
only given clues only
what did you say
there's a indonesian brand somebody said
that yeah
interesting
[Music]
let's take a look at this phone looking
thing oh what phone is this oh google
google phone
google phone there's nai
don't see that very often
do we know of anybody that uses google
phone huh
huh
[Music]
crony cobalt
here we have
them again
those freaking earpods right but those
are from uh samsung
everybody has them
maybe i should get them too
oh what is this
song oh makeup
that looks like some lip gloss and
lipstick some fancy
oh from that's from dior oh
oh
a little bit of a girly side now like so
far it didn't look so girly but that
looks a little bit girly
what is this
[Music]
looks like toilet paper i'm uncovering
it but it's all blurred um like from the
get-go
what is what is all this
trash who brings trash so much trash
with that that's a lot of trash
[Music]
so those are yeah those looks it looks
like receipts
it looks like receipts actually a lot of
very long receipts
[Music]
from shopping that she keeps in there
randomly i think
she did tell me oh yeah yeah yeah
uh
a lot of receipts because i never clean
out my bags what's the comment
to this
mess
[Laughter]
big spender
attacks and kai mono stereography
[Music]
what is this
oh
some candy
oh dear oh dear okay we have some candy
it says coffee candy in the explanation
but that looks like there's some
oh oh oh cool
ah
isn't this a
korean snack korean
oh
god
[Music]
what's this
it's a mask ah with a little daisy cute
a mask yeah yeah and we have the bag
what is this does this give away
anything the bag the this person on the
back
does that give away anything
so okay oh that's awesome water awesome
candy huh isn't that korean writing on
it though
wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
i was actually surprised by this because
uh the one time i met bills for a very
short amount of time she was
uh
at that time she was very fancily
dressed
so now i have this fancy elegant image
of her but this looks a bit
little bit more i don't know more casual
sporty
i don't know
cute but clean the back
the amounts of receipts
takes up the whole bag basically
the bay bag vague
it's the bag
but they and only above you samsung
[Music]
i find it funny that ollie recognized
that it's bae's bag by looking at the
candy have you guys talked about this
candy before
is it a well-known thing that bae likes
those candies
or are they well known for
[Music]
we all did everybody did
she's addicted
aha they told us she's addicted to that
ah she likes coffee oh yeah okay i don't
even know these candies though i've
never seen them before ever
we don't have them here
you don't have them
hmm
[Applause]
[Music]
vails is here what's up i watched um
i watched the panel from you guys
yesterday i was even in the chat my name
was kiara for reals but nobody reacted
to maybe they thought i was fake but
yeah i was in the chat i was watching
the whole thing interesting family tree
you got going there
good job on the panel yesterday today i
have a panel with ina you can watch it
live even if you can't go for
crunchyroll expo
yeah it was kiana for reals
i was commenting quite a lot
i thought it was fake
it was real though it was hormonal
i'm glad someone noticed me because i
was wondering if um if maybe my account
got banned or so and i don't realize it
father was fake
no that was me
panel in about eight hours oh yeah
probably something like that yeah maybe
maybe eight hours really i feel like
it's a little bit less i'm not sure
um
[Laughter]
yeah yeah what's up what's a fun battle
crunchyroll expo has been going pretty
well
all right next bag
[Music]
girly
lots of pink
even though the
floor is pink
wait wait where is it i just saw bails
there again
that's the phone that comes in the
shower oh yeah right she said water
damaged phone the one i used in the
shower she told me
it's already water damaged so you can i
guess take it without worrying about
it i thought if it's water damage then
you can't use it at all anymore but it's
good that you can still use it
[Music]
you guys can um i'll give you a little
little help advice you can stop um
guessing guda because gura didn't send
anything
okay
it's not there's no no good or bad
contents i'm sorry to disappoint you
so you can stop
yeah maybe that will make it easier
because you guys have been guessing cuda
for everything
sorry
all right what do we have let's uncover
hmm
again
right those are earpods i didn't realize
they have like a
oh you charge them when they're in
in the box
immediate earpods i didn't even
know that they were there
always your airpods wow fancy
charging pot cool
ah
what is this oh this
wait i think i asked what it is let me
check
[Music]
this is a spray i
i
will not say what spray it is yet
not yet
uh
what's this
okay we have some makeup
peeking out of a make makeup bag from
rirakuma
[Music]
oh everything's so pink
damn a lot of pink
also um cream
perfume maybe i don't know some some
gels very pink very high hydrating kind
of stuff
according to santa
[Music]
not sure what that is
ah it's a little face towel
face a towel a small towel for your face
if you're sweating in your face a small
towel
a pen
and
oh
related stuff oh that's like a like a
folder um clear folder kind of thing
it looks pretty small
judging by the size of the pen
oh
we have some these these i've only ever
seen before in japan so i guess we can
lock in that is
someone in japan
these are like mints
[Music]
and last but not least we have
uh those are wet sheets wet wipes
wet wipes
possibly
sanitizing yeah so now we'll tell you
what the spray is the spray is actually
a throat spray
[Laughter]
[Music]
i was told it's a manuka
honey
spray
and i was like oh does that actually
help and she said
she it you you be you get the feeling
that it helps
just like mentally
and she likes to use it when she has
recordings
so a lot of you guys are saying iris
well well well it's
senpai
so girly
what so much pink i mean i guess i
wouldn't say marina is not girly but i
don't didn't expect this girly so pink
so
what
[Music]
someone in the chat some japanese person
knew it immediately the moment i showed
the picture without without showing
anything ah because she likes to come on
well don't we all love ridakum i love
ridakuma i just don't have access to any
ridakuma goods anymore hmm
she's 17 after all
where is the voice level
where are the voices of the daughters
she wouldn't bring that with her outside
would say
tokyo
[Music]
[Laughter]
because actually she also replied to me
very fast
and yeah she was very open to doing this
thank you so much
[Music]
again
maybe she wanted to show off her
girliness
and her young freshness
by the choice of the items that she's
using maybe maybe it gives you a feeling
that she's 17 after all
girly girl yes
forever 17.
um
i did meet maddie in senpai before and i
guess she did have
a girly aura i guess so
yeah
the pens hit different now why
the pen looks pretty normal to me is
that also
[Music]
it's kind of you know blurred so it's
hard to see but
pretty pen multi-colored pen yeah old
school pen
it has a multicult so what so what
are there chew marks no
no
okay okay next bag
[Music]
nice back where do you want to start
who's whose back will this be sunglasses
and see sunglasses
orange orange
fashionable fashionable
maybe yeah it looks already looks very
properly laid out
where do we start
i don't know where to start
let's start here
oh
it's awesome
i related oh cute cute
cute
mask
i want that mask
what's this
it's okay i just wanted to uncover the
the lower fingers two things it's a
little
louis vuitton
scent
and uh
a little i think that's a i think that's
a hand mirror
small
round hand mirror i think
i could be wrong
could be wrong
but i think it looks like it i think
all right let's uncover the
thing here
oh
who is this
oh it's peanut snoopy again oh peanuts
pity it study ah
that looks like a little memo kind of
thing
remember yeah snoopy snoopy cute
what
the phone
i might not be the only person who has
that kind of phone yo
for little notes yeah but
study i guess it's for
yeah for language study or something
like that
because like you put
i guess you put it on on one side like
like the vocabulary study
um
let's look at the back oh
oh oh oh it's a guest bag
a guest
guess bag
in orange a beautiful color isn't it
i love orange
thank you to this person for using the
color orange
[Music]
more people need to use orange
appreciate orange
now let's take a look at the phone
because we already know this is a phone
oh five cameras
that is indeed the same phone as i have
but that doesn't mean anything
that doesn't mean anything
not necessarily
and it seems like matching to the back
we have a little
purse
wait no that's the purse that's the
wallet
it's a wallet
matching also orange
we shall
this is definitely yago a hundred
percent confirmed chiago
okay oh what else can we take a look
what about here
oh two pens two different kind of pens
it's a
a permanent marker maki
and a
a normal pen normal looking pen
monkey now that's from that's a japanese
permanent marker um
now what is a key
a key with um
[Music]
yeah for autographs this person maybe is
always ready to ride autographs
no earbuds what the [\h__\h] maybe they're
still there maybe they're somewhere
where where could they be well here we
have some sunglasses
beautiful sunglasses
and we have some some hand sanitizer
and we have some lip tints oh from etude
house oh my god i have the same one
i have the same one
[Music]
it's from a korean brand it's jute house
ah i have the same of the same
what's this oh a bobby pin and a hair
tie
a tic-tacs
and
a random ass
a lollipop what the [\h__\h]
the [\h__\h]
and
complete
copy them
thingies what do they call love for
blisters
who do you think this is from twinsies
yeah let's go
i mean i mean i mean there's some items
you can only get in japan
[Music]
so why would it be me
[Laughter]
feed lipstick it's not feet lipstick no
yes it's me
wow wow
well let me explain i wanna i wanna
explain a little bit because it's my bag
so let me explain a little bit
shut up
shut up you didn't know it was not
obvious at all
but actually so the mask is something
that um genma uh gave me
uh because i asked her to bring me masks
so no wait no wait she break she she
brought me other masks i got these ones
on my own
i think in daiso when i was in america
so never mind never mind that
i did get those in a japanese store in
america
yeah and then the
peanuts thingy i got that a long time
ago i found it randomly in my bag i'm
not actually actively using it
but maybe i should now that i found it
again i will you know what i will it's
actually for language study meant to be
because it's like it's like separated
that way for vocabulary
oh it is used there is like a few pages
that are used you just don't see it
um
and no airpods
[\h__\h] airpods i don't need them i don't
need them to be cool i'm already cool
yeah might as well use it i think it's
cute i got it in um in japan
um
for a while yeah so flash card it's kind
of like a flash card for a while they
had um
peanuts snoopy related um stuff
merchandise
in a store called plaza in japan which i
loved it was my favorite store when i
went when i lived in japan
and then i've been using the etude house
lip tints for a million years those lip
tints there i love them they're really
popular
yeah and uh i have the siding pen
because
it was randomly in my bag because
because um i think i guess i got that
one from gemma when she gave me some
stuff to sign
yeah
um
i'm not [\h__\h] blisters man i get
blisters on my feet a lot when i go
outside like literally every time [\h__\h]
it these compete ones are actually
pretty helpful
and then the
look honestly
that um candy
it was somebody gave it to me
and i put it in my bag and it was at the
bottom of the bag for like months i
think
it's not like that's what i eat
like randomly but yeah it was just in
there and yeah orange
actually
the bag is pretty new when i got it uh
you know i was like oh orange well i
guess you know my image color is orange
i should probably get something orange
so i bought it
thinking about my image color orange
kind of like
yeah
[Music]
thinking that you know i am kiwawa so i
have to get something orange
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
okay that's the key wow i'm back oh
actually oh one more thing i'm pretty
sure that the keychain
is um
was a gift from
uh
i think i received it
at dokomi
last year i think
and i was like that's cute i mean i'm
not a huge fan of card captain sakura
but i did put it on because it's cute
maybe somebody in the chat will now
remember oh yeah that's what i gave to
her
so honestly i've had it on my key for a
while so i don't remember
i'm sorry but
but i'm using it
yeah such a pretty bag you're so stylish
thank you i have so many bags mom wasn't
sure which one to put on so i put on one
that i actually don't really use
yeah that's twist i actually don't
really use the bag
anyway
continuing
next
back small
there's not
many contents here i'm very high
technologist now
shouted
the truth is
my bag i had quite a few contents but i
don't always bring that much these days
yeah this is a minimalist kind of person
maybe
hmm
are those smokes
no
it wouldn't be any small oopsie there
wouldn't be any smokes here
[Music]
i don't know what is this
i'll open something else
why is this
a wallet
cute yeah this is some um a painted
version it's totally fine
[Music]
a little wallet cute brown maybe leather
so much here to uncover let's see it
this is for glasses a glasses case
[Music]
okay everything's just too revealing
animal treats could be amen you know for
bubba
notes to self
yes we all have some
notes to self and trash aka trash in our
bags don't we
okay okay okay okay bobby pins
just like me oh my god we're matching i
got random bobby pins too secret book
secrets about humans oh
so
i don't know i i'll take this as moment
oh wait
if this is moomin rumba always takes a
book with her but this is just a book
that she currently carries around i
wonder i wonder what kind of books she's
read so far
uh
oh yeah i lost all but one hair type
which i'm using now
oh wait it's similar to me too i also am
losing all my hair ties
and then we have
a phone
with me may stream and my stream i think
she took a a screenshot of the most
recent
um hold on yen streams
work phone uses dark mode why do you
have to
show off that you use dark mode
is it so bad to use light mode because i
use light mode and i'm proud of it okay
i like light mode
judge me
go on
don't care
live mode is just fine
but i love how there's like an
advertisement for the stream that we're
doing right now yeah
happy birthday again
i i did make a video that she played
on her stream because it was like 4 30
or no 4 a.m or so i don't know no
earlier 3 or 4 am so in my my time zone
i was sleeping when i was going on
unfortunately
[Music]
um happy birthday mummy
secrets about humans i want to look
inside that book
what secrets does she have about us and
why does she not share
sharing is caring mommy come on come on
please let us know we need to know how
can we improve ourselves if we don't
know what the secrets are
yeah so this was mommy
said
[Music]
interesting okay
thank you mommy for the submission she
put in the effort to draw over it to
make it look so clean thank you
okay
next bag
here again very pink is looking
kind of girly
but i remember there were some
interesting items here
[Music]
i'm seeing
coated headphones oh
yes and that's what made me feel
so connected to this person
i didn't have mine
on my photo because i forgot but i
usually have
wired headphones uh
carrying around in my bag as well so
this made me feel very connected
[Music]
just because i say connected doesn't
mean you know anything
but it would be funny because connecto
but yeah we have some uh
wired
earphones i got the same ones
[Music]
yeah so tangled they're always tangled
but that's the fun thing you know it's
like a game before you start listening
to something you pull out your uh
earphones and then you have to first
untangle them alexa play untangle
it's fun it's a fun activity okay
oh
oh what fun is this i first thought it's
maybe the same as i have but i guess
it's oh it's an apple
oh no no no maybe it's just the work
phone
maybe maybe
because you need one phone to take a
picture obviously right so
[Music]
need wired for ribbon games oh is that
so does that help more
why so that they don't pop out or so
[Music]
the audio quality is better less lag
yeah
[Music]
even with the super expensive [\h__\h]
expensive airpods really
[Music]
really
that's pretty bad yo charging that much
money
holy [\h__\h]
ah
well then i am superior after all
with my wired headphones let's go
now this this thing i found very
interesting
this person carries batteries around for
what
for what
battery or motor
several of them one two three four six
[Music]
six
batteries
like i don't even have i mean i don't
have them in my bag but i don't even
have batteries in my home and i always
like when i need them i'm like [\h__\h] i
don't have any batteries but nowadays
thankfully not like barely anything
needs batteries these days
thank god
it looks like bullets yeah but it's not
it's batteries yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
nintendo ds nintends doesn't need those
kind of batteries does it it's been too
long i don't remember
what is this
oh a little uh
hairpin thingy hairpin
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes doesn't yes it's tragic yeah that's
what i thought but i mean i guess like a
like a game boy
used batteries right i think i think
game boy color used batteries
like that
those type
now here we have
a lot of coins
which i also felt so connected to
because i didn't show it in my photo but
i also have a [\h__\h] ton of coins every
every in every single one of my bags but
these are japanese coins saunas
yeah we have some random coins scattered
in her bag
and here we have
some batteries here and now i'll show
the writing because now you know it's a
japanese member yahoo
iphone
yeah
okay
[Music]
okay it's a it's a um keys but you know
hidden because
for safety yeah
here we have
oh quite a simple designed uh
purse a purse
wallet wallet
a little wallet but it's kind of like a
pinkish color
still still girly cute
simple is best yeah simple styles yeah
gives gives this person a little bit of
a mature girliness because of the design
mm-hmm
oh makeup we have some makeup going on
here
lipsticks two different lipsticks i
wonder what brand burrando
[Music]
the coins don't go into the wall no no
this the coins are probably just
scattered in her bag and just flying
around in her bag you know
that's why they're not in the
wallet made hopefully she put them into
the wallet after cleaning out her bag
for this photo instead of just throwing
them back into the bag again
mood want a mood
i'm still confused about the brothers
right because there's nothing in the bag
that you would use them for
i was thinking okay those make sense if
you have something to use them for in
your bag
some device but nothing
maybe it's local senpai yeah
so she can charge herself
and then we have
some noodle america some fruit candies
so seems to be someone who also takes
their approach
status very seriously
a girly person
but i feel like japanese members here
like almost all of them are super girly
so who could it be
teen
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
so
how did you know what in the beginning
just because i said connected that
wasn't even on purpose that really was
not on purpose when i said that you
don't say
[Music]
why does she have those batteries
but yeah orenzo orenz no kizuna the
orange
bond
you know we have we both have the wired
headphones
i love it
makes me happy
[Music]
[Laughter]
m is there the batteries
there's nothing to use them for it's i
need to knock on my couple
maybe we'll get an answer now
now she had her revival stream today by
the way she's back
she's back
where batteries
[Music]
why what
everyone is confused
[Music]
for her headlight but why is it in your
bag
[Music]
headlight
forest
[Laughter]
i'm even more confused now
exploring yes just exploring to find
find stuff in the in the forest
that's son and that's it huh
oh i guess it's for the
um a torch not torch torch the the light
but oh wait she did say headlight wait
so she actually walks around with a
headlight on her forehead
i can imagine like a really dorky unity
with a headlight walking through the
forest looking at beetles
in english
she looks for kabuto
in the forest for real i thought i
thought it must have had some different
meaning oh my god
wait you would get a long walk with amme
kensaku
[Music]
she should go looking for beetles and
moss
with ami together
and ammo would bring some really
high-tech
equipment to help her out
[Laughter]
she did say she met some nice beetle
boys what
she met some nice vehicles
damn
enemy hi king
[Music]
[Laughter]
i said go with ahmed but i want to go
too
[Music]
that's interesting that was an
interesting bag because of the batteries
okay we don't have many bags left we
have one two three
bags left
this
now
the next bag is
a mess
and there's not much so this is the one
i was talking about but there's a reason
why this is not the the format that
everybody else was using because this is
the only person who even though she
didn't send it to me she at least
apparently took took a picture after my
request but never sent it to me just had
it somewhere in her phone so this was
taken a long time ago
and
uh
i also did not give like a photo example
of what it should look like
so
and that's why it looks like this
is so let's take a look there's not much
in here this is literally a direct photo
into the back
do you have a little
plushy a little cute fleshy
even be a a little wallet i don't know
not dryer oh yeah oh yeah it has zipper
it might be like used as a wallet
and we have a pen
a
bird
bird is that is a pen i think
[Music]
are those pretty glasses
yeah it looks like
there's some fancy pretty glasses
and then
there's some
random
nuts
scattered in the back
these are the only items you can
recognize now tell me who do you think
this belongs to
i was like you're welcome to take
another picture now you know where it's
actually all properly laid out like in
the
examples you're welcome to do it but she
didn't she just you know went for this
one
so
[Music]
not
and the 3d glasses maybe she just came
from a movie or so
and stole the glasses
[Music]
i feel like mikuti
would
lay it out properly and make it very
girly and clean to be honest
so
let's say no it is emily yes
[Music]
it's almost back amelia
yeah
yeah yeah cause she took the picture a
long time ago and she told me
um
she told me
this was her bag after traveling
and she says she had a [\h__\h] ton of
roasted peanuts
that she saved in her bag to feed
squirrels so don't worry she did not
just throw them into the bag like that
and then eat it herself
nor was it an accident it was on purpose
she had them because she wanted to feed
squirrels
aka lisu
to feed this and your body was lisa's
back but no this is just a bag to make
lisa senpai happy
yeah but you know i thought this was
even though it looks messy and not not
perfect like the other pictures but i
thought it kind of has personality you
know
this just
this is so real you know it's real it
gives you that
relatable real feeling
[Laughter]
abby just wants to feed those animals
so she throws in some random ass nuts
yeah there's no explanation about the
glasses though
maybe it's normal to have them
thank you almond for this don't know why
you never sent it to me but she always
had it she had it in the back of her
hand in the back of her phone for a long
time
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's normal for ammo to have them of
course of course of course
yes
okay we have two more bags
[Music]
which one should i show first hmm
i'll show this one first
[Laughter]
hmm
it's a fanny pack yeah
it's nicely laid out yeah thank god
[Music]
okay let's start um
[\h__\h] airpods
those goddamn airpods right those are
airpods right airpods with like a
keychain kind of thing
hmm you found you want to look at the
fanny pack
it's really simple
wait is this okay does this give away
everything let me try let me check let
me try just i don't want this to
be spoiled too early on
let me see let me look at look at the
original
aha okay
yeah okay i'm not a hold up i will oh
keep something to myself
let's uh take a look at some other stuff
first
we have some
what is that
i don't even know what ah it's hair ties
hair ties little
crocheted
uh
flowers and stuff on on hair ties
cute
looks like it even could be handmade i'm
not sure
crochet yes
and now we have
oh oh
a little
uh
nail kit
yeah it's a nail kit
a nail kit it has a little nail scissor
uh and the one way and you know i don't
know what those are called but it's a
nail kit i think
crochet aha crochet
thank you
nail file yeah it's a nail file and the
clippy thingy
you're thinking lena interesting
interesting
we have uh i think
that's
either
uh sanitizer or eye drops is it eye
drops
has um has somebody seen that brand
before
eyes eye drops ah there we go i thought
so because of the shape but i don't know
the brand
drums
and then we have a little brush and
like a makeup pouch i suppose probably
some makeup stuff or or i don't know
could be something else but i think it's
a makeup pouch
we have
a little
oh that's probably a coin purse like i
don't use those things but
is that maybe a tiny coin purse maybe
cute it's shaped like a macaron
adorable
we have some sunglasses ooh for the
perfect disguise
okay
we're getting there guys
a little hairpin
don't know who that girl is but
a cute hairpin
now
interesting i found this to be very
interesting
it's a
pen light
an orange
or orange
oh a light stake
is that ultra orange
metal
[Music]
you have been officially bamboozled this
is not a hollow bag
it's pogba's bag
bamboos
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah i asked her if she wants to
share her bag with me
and there it is
i feel like you know the the metal gear
solid and the pen light makes it so
obvious that's why i kept it for the
very ending
[Music]
yeah thank you bubba for sending me your
bag wow your contents now belong to me
my mind but fanny pack pomo really fanny
pack really
really
i mean i think the currently only
acceptable way to wear a fanny pack in
my opinion is if you wear it over your
chest i guess
she said yeah i didn't see what pom pom
pom pom pom pom
oh you're right she's not a mod so i can
barely see a duckle
um
pomeranian my sweet pomeranian
i can't see what did she say
what did pomeranians say
[Music]
come on
i like to call her pomeranian
did she say i'm poor moo
that's how you wear it oh thank god she
just dm'd me told me that's how she
wears it over her chest okay that is the
only acceptable way but i still think
it's
kind of the side promo i expected
something more girly from you
i'll be honest if you thought you were
gonna be more girly than that
i'm bamboozled
why where is that where's the girlie bag
huh
although that bag is uh judging by that
face on it isn't that what's it called
again
what was it again
there's just this
character this japanese yeah mifi mifi
daion
this japanese character i think
called miffy yeah
but then the makeup bag is cute the
makeup bag is girly and the the hair
ties give me like a
like a morty girl vibe
if you know what that is like a fashion
style
the nail kit could have almost been a
sewing kit i thought for a moment it's a
sewing kit and it kind of gives away a
little bit too
oh yeah
yeah
[Music]
it's like um forest forest uh
aesthetic forest girl cute hakatoku
forest girl vibes that's like kind of a
fashion style
anyway thank you so much palmer for
sending me your bag
thank you for complying and setting it
so last minute thank you
i have one more bag
one more bag don't worry it is a hollow
bag last
it's a whole life member back or maybe
it's from europe is that so
i didn't know
i didn't know maybe it is i don't know
it could be
this is yogurt
totally
well what do we want to uncover first
for the last bag
[Music]
what do we want to look at first
hi
and there's a
big eye staring at us this is kind of
creepy
this is kind of creepy and edgy so not a
very girly person i guess that we're
dealing with here
[Music]
tacos lipstick yeah this is yago's
lipstick everybody i presented you
yoga's lipstick
wonder what color
[Music]
we should do is makeup sometime
and i guess there's also makeup what is
it no it's like like a little um
satin
pouch maybe for them maybe for the
lipstick oh
not sure do we have airpods
of course we have [\h__\h] earbuds
[Laughter]
i am getting mad at their puns i have a
problem with them i have a personal
vendetta against them
everybody has airpods but me
and energy
[Laughter]
boomer no
no no i purposefully choose to not have
airpods i choose against them i don't
want them no thank you
caveman why not get that okay we want we
don't want latency delay we don't want
that no no no
totally the reason why i don't own them
here we have some t-shirts i think those
are tissues
small very small baby tissues
for this baby
hope you excuse me
is this
ah i think that's a oh
a leather leather uh wallet i think
looks like a wallet
and we have what is that maybe some
mints
have you guys seen that before
because even if i zoom in i don't really
i can't read anything
non-double iris
i race
funny
[Music]
ah
what
i think it's probably
could be mints but i don't know
and then we have some sunglasses
so
uh a pretty empty bag not much in there
but i feel like the bag itself has a lot
of personality
i could see kelly wearing that to be
honest but we already had kelly
iris
do you think that iris bag that i bag is
just such a big hint
it's an eye turn
it's so easy
[Music]
oh
the last bag
belongs to
drumroll
baby waited thank you from whole life id
yeah
[Music]
of course reyna sent me a submission of
course she did
couldn't go without laying a bag but i'm
personally very surprised like we we
spent a whole week together but i have
not seen this bag like she didn't bring
this bag and i think i've seen her use
the sunglasses
but
yeah the rest of the items i mean
there's not that many items to begin
with so
i don't know i i
think
i would have expected it to be a bit
more a tiny bit more girly but this is
fine it's cool it gives her a different
kind of uh aesthetic different kind of
vibe um
the eye bag ball is such a eyeball bag
this is an eyebag ball
i'm ball bag
yes it's very edgy
engineered golfing oh my god did we get
some golf playing the fan art now
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's go
oh now you know yeah your daughter's
fashion sense a little bit
i think it's um
overall you know really really really
interesting to look at these bags some
are a bit more surprising than others
some are very much a giveaway on first
sight
some bring some weird items like i'm
bringing the nuts and ninety bringing
the batteries and stuff
and then the football key with the big
spiderman plushie
and the crab pen holder
items
yeah yeah i hope you enjoyed this i'm so
glad that i got so many um submissions
from the live members thank you
everybody for sending them to me
[Music]
now i wanna try again i want to give
actually the id members and the japan
members i just um contacted them myself
i didn't do like an open call but next
time i'll do an open call so that as
many of them as possible can
do it if they want to if they want to
participate
[Music]
i should do it again i will maybe i will
do it again but it will take a while
because you know we want some space in
between
i hope you enjoyed it yeah
what's your favorite what's your
favorite could there be your favorite is
why is it why is it kiana bag
oh by the way look at the ground
underneath the beautiful marble that's
my new table that's my new dining table
it's really nice but i have yet to
get it to stand properly it's so shaky
because it has like those spider legs
and i just
we could not figure out
how to make it stand properly
it's so weird
yeah
it's it's quite the instagram photo
isn't it
the aesthetics are on point
on point yeah
[Laughter]
ah my favorite bag is i'm a bag it's
just unexpected
i'm in this bag maybe
maybe next time she can participate
again and do like a proper picture like
this but then it would not have the
other personality you know
[Music]
like i'm just back
yeah yeah almost back stood out a little
bit mommy back
[Music]
today
i'm sure she must have some proper cute
bags somewhere right
and fauna fonda's bag was also quite
quite obviously fauna bona was very
girly um
all these back was just too easy
oh i thought callie's back was you know
from all of us very surprising actually
not not all of us i mean the makeup for
me makes it so obviously cali
[Laughter]
um but yeah
most of you guys thought it was other
people everyone except kelly
until it was kelly
kelly's back yeah i wanted to explain
this back i wonder if she really carries
around
all of this stuff all the time
cause i
think yeah i don't know i never saw her
actually carrying like all these game
devices with her makeup yes she's
definitely carrying those around she
also always has hair ties
and the airpods definitely
[Music]
but i love the bag itself yeah
cool stuff cool stuff
yeah mary girl it makes sense it does
make sense yeah if you think about it
if you think about it kelly destroying
this girly
i guess so yeah unexpectedly girly
mmm
kind
that's uh all 13 bags that i was able to
collect
for today's stream have you guys enjoyed
it i'm gonna take a break now because i
have a panel later for uh crunchyroll
expo and i wonder if you guys have seen
i've been tweeting uh all about it all
the time uh maybe if you're on twitter
you saw it but if you're not on twitter
then
check it out anyway because like we have
a cafe concession
over there like a food food court and
cafe is taking over
yeah
yeah and it looks so so nice everybody's
enjoying the food it looks really tasty
and from what i've heard it is really
tasty
so everybody's who is going to
crunchyroll expo today too please
continue eating jimmy's legs
for example and phoenix slider for
example yeah yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
have fun at the panel yeah me and ina
will be having a panel and you can watch
it even if you're not going to the
convention so keep an eye out for the
link on twitter i might even do a
community post maybe
if i remember but you can also just go
to the quantum realm expo website they
have a link there to their live stream
for the panels
and yeah we're on in a couple of hours
so see you there everybody thank you so
much for watching
[Music]
yeah
thank you for watching
[Music]
[Applause]
some fine bags
beautiful marvelous marvelous bye-bye
[Music]
do
you