Christmas is the time of giving
forgiving love and family one person on
this world who certainly doesn't
understand this is the CEO of everyone's
favorite fast food restaurant chain
KF takanashi Kiara for years and years
she has been overworking her employees
and they are
suffering okay Goa that was a nice walk
wasn't it let's bring you back
inside good cat shark hey not so
fast hey Kiara I brought back gooa yeah
yeah sure whatever thanks um I just
wanted to ask if I was going to get my
pay anytime soon you haven't paid me in
like 2 months huh excuse me do you know
who you're talking to I'm a mult M
billionaire genius entrepreneur and
owner of the mighty fast food Empire K
ofp you will get paid when I deem you
worthy of it it's just I've been trying
to feed the animals in my shelter and
need to get medicine for them too but
with no pay from the side job and me
still having to pay all kinds of other
expenses I just can't give the animals
the support they need anymore enough
don't you see I'm busy here I need to
monitor the usual room and plan out the
new punishment mechanics now leave or do
you want to go to the usual room too uh
I I apologize I
just I'll be back tomorrow
then a poor FAA I hope her animals are
okay anyway Kiara goes to sleep for a
while after getting her work done but
maybe it's finally time for a
change
what the heck who are you it is me Hol
lives number one uh never mind wrong
script I uh I'm the ghost of the
past weird I felt a sense of deu there
for a moment oh you're the ghost of what
I am the ghost of the past and I am here
to show you something very important
come with me hop hop uh how about
go away or I'll call the police oh
foolish rich woman you don't seem to
understand the gravy gravy yes gravy of
this situation you will
[Music]
come every day I work and I work and I
work I wish I had more time to take care
of my sickly mother I'm so worried she's
just doing worse every day I see
her mother I'm home
[Music]
my dear where have you been so long
again it's Christmas Eve or by now guess
it is Christmas light night I'm so sorry
Ki just wouldn't let me go last year I
worked on Christmas too and she promised
me this year I'd get Christmas off but
now she's acting as if that never
happened oh my oh my it's okay my little
I I understand you're just trying your
best to pay for a rent it's my fault
too I should be the one taking care of
us not
you no mother don't say that it's not
your fault that you got sick and I don't
mind at all I just want you to get
better thank you sweet part
[Music]
night
mother I will make you some tea right
away no
wait all right mother here's your
tea
mother are you asleep
[Music]
already
wait
mother
mother what's wrong please say
something no
[Applause]
[Music]
no you see this Kiara this is your
employee M but this happened 5 years ago
ever since that time her mother's been
in a coma and mum's been working hard to
pay for the medical expenses well life
sucks it's not my fault you may think so
but as an all- knowing ghost I can tell
you if she would have had more time to
take care of her mother she wouldn't
have fallen into a coma well but at
least mum hasn't been complaining and
begging for off days anymore ever
since wow okay this one's going to be a
hard nut to crack for sure speaking of
nuts I really want to eat some more of
these nuts that have at home what are
you mumbling there don't worry about it
let me bring you back home no about time
this was a weird
dream
huh I guess I got to say it a bit
louder h no wait I'm not Santa uh hi
there I'm the ghost from the present
presents Santa you're real no no no no
the ghost of the present you know the
here and now a oh another one of you
guys huh what is it this time yeah just
wait you'll understand in a moment Come
Along come
along okay okay I get it but how is it
my fault I have to do my job you have
been doing this job for one year now and
I have been trying to be patient but you
just never have time for me anymore for
so many years we have always been super
tight and nothing could tear us apart
yet this new job just seems to be more
important to you than me hey that's not
true true you are important to me and
you should know that I've been trying to
get time off of work but I don't want to
risk getting fired either I I get that
but it's not normal anymore today is the
first time we are seeing each other in 4
months and before that it was 5 months I
missed you old times and I told you
again and again but you would even reply
to my text messages you're acting like
we didn't have some rough patches before
like when you were obsessed with reading
some weird fanf on the internet 10 hours
per day instead of hanging with me
that's totally different I was studying
them for science don't try to change a
topic and point fingers at me I'm just
trying to make you understand come on
shiori you know how important our
friendship is to us and yet all you talk
about these days is about your CEO's
butt and I am sick of hearing about it
well and I'm sick of hearing you
complain all the time well Risa maybe if
you gave a crap about me I mean I like
my job yeah I I know they overwork me a
little bit but at the least at the least
I have I have my boss I have the CEO and
you know she does have a nice button I'm
not sorry for talking about it I will
continue to talk about it as long as
it's the one thing I get to go to work
and enjoy okay can I just have do you
see Kiara how your ridiculous demands of
your employees make them struggle to
keep up even the strongest friendships
that one could think would last forever
it seems like they will reach their
limit soon is my butt big is it bad damn
can't believe she was checking on my b
were you even listening what oh man I
think we need to bring out the big guns
I've got just the right person let me
take you
back howy I had a feeling this wasn't
over yet one can't truly reflect on
their wrongdoings without my wisdom I
will show you how miserable the future
would be if you don't do anything
yeah yeah let's see what you
[Music]
got I know somewhere out there there's
someone looking for me I've had this
feeling for years and years ever since I
found out I had a twin sister after all
these years of me trying to find my lost
twin sister I had to give up no
financial resources and no time why did
it end up like this I just don't don't
have any leads even though I had so many
leads but now it seems like I have
nothing I feel like there's something
missing that's left me feeling
incomplete all my life I wonder how life
could have been with her I wonder what
she's like if we're similar or complete
opposite will I ever be able to move on
will I ever be able to let
[Music]
go
oh so
alone I missed the good old days the AR
fting about stupid stuff
like if only B didn't choose work over
me back then things could have been so
different the TS what we would find
loving me to death in the block game
seems just like yesterday if only she'd
love me as much as when she'd get
jealous over me flirting with z
even with her
sagginess she was beautiful like no
other she accepted me for who I was
always even when I roasted her endlessly
I remember when she stood by my side
when I needed her the most for coming my
new voice when I didn't have she was
just trying to get money for my dream
wedding I couldn't give her
enough she deserved so much more I miss
her I miss her see how you ruined and
split up a happily engaged couple their
wedding could have been so beautiful but
you don't even pay minimum wage and
overworked her so hard that not even
their love could save them well and you
held mocho back from finding her lost
twin sister fuaa how will they ever feel
fulfilled without each other I
[Music]
mean also I saw in the future that kfp
investors are all leaving and your
branches will dwindle one after another
eventually you will lose your whole
business if you don't change your ways
oh God no no please no okay okay okay
please take me back I will fix it I
won't let it happen I will let them have
a Merry Christmas and a happily ever
after for all of
them I may be a SE through ghost but she
couldn't see through that lie
huh oh hia I'm happy to see that you
finally understood what I've been trying
to tell you all along yeah I'm sorry I I
won't make it right from now on but what
about M and crony isn't it too late for
them oh don't worry you can leave that
to me and my clock I'll bring you back
in time to fix it before it's too late
wow
[Music]
sasuka and with this Kiara's attitude
toward her workers has finally improved
and so was their quality of life she
even donated 1 million Super Chat had
to's animal shelter and started walking
gooa by herself wow kfp started thriving
more than ever and stonks are through
the roof
hooray merry merry
Christmas happy
holidays
[Music]
[Applause]