foreign
[Music]
i see it as my personal obligation
i saw someone tweeted at me someone
tweeted at me
uh asking me if i know where it is
because her stream was supposed to start
half an hour ago is that true is that
true have are you taking that
correctly do i understand what the
situation
she has she's not showed up i actually
don't see her online on discord eva
around this time she should be uh i mean
when she's online then she is online
normally i'll turn them
sorry sorry sorry sorry i turned down
the wrong thing yes yes
the keep is it true is it true is it
true that ina
is currently sleeping
what what is that is that a possibility
we will find out
i am now here i feel the obligation to
wait we don't know this might just be a
10 minute stream
who knows it could be longer like little
medium is not looping
is absolutely scuffed i actually have a
lasagna in the oven
i am waiting for the lasagna which will
be faster
the lasagna or inna garfield
uh sorry no takanasi kiara is waiting
for the lasagna
but i think since i've thrown it in the
oven 25 or 30 minutes ago
the lasagna might be faster than inna
can ina
however for some reason beat my lasagna
can she do it i am
here for you guys to report uh on you
got for you guys on this current
situation
i will now uh do the honor of uh
writing in a discord message and asking
her
where the hell she is uh let me see let
me see
um the thing is i have a huge cintiq
tablet in front of me
is very difficult for me to type let me
bend over here real quick you won't see
me moving
[Music]
where are you okay okay
i have done my part i have done my part
i have written there a message
this is all i can do i can only wait i
do not have her personal phone number
but one can only hope that those uh
11 000 people waiting in her minecraft
lobby have enough patience and the
strength
to wait for her and to to welcome her
the moment she comes
this has never happened before this has
never happened to
my inaudible who would have thought that
she is the type of person
to oversleep wait is that is that really
english
uh i want to remind you guys my first uh
language is not
english uh it is german and i don't know
what to say
i did not think that i would be doing
this right now but
some gods or or or angels have told me
it is my mission
it is my mission is it is fate i am here
to wait because waiting is the only
thing that we can do
let me drink some water i've been
talking nonstop for five minutes i
didn't even breathe yet i don't know how
to breathe
i can only breathe once eno arrives let
me drink some water
once ina will be awake
if she's sleeping who knows maybe she is
not sleeping maybe the ancient ones
have gotten to her maybe they have i
don't know maybe they had a fight
and she is now vanished in the void i do
not know
but i can only hope for the best i hope
nothing happened to her
currently there it has been 40 minutes
since her stream was supposed to start
has ina ever been late
i am here to ask the taco duchess has
ina ever been late before
i don't i don't know i think actually i
am the only one
yeah i said that something like this has
never happened before you know my
inaudible
how late was i before how many shields
was that
um i think i was an hour late perhaps
an hour i i personally don't see anyone
in this as a type of person who would
come late
on purpose so something must have
happened maybe we need to call
emilia watson to help us investigate
because maybe something else happened
maybe
maybe the ancient ones are evil don't
trust them
don't trust them but in any case
i'm sure we can save her we can save her
and protect her
together with kfp as you can see on my
new table we also have a new logo by the
way yes
and i'm obviously best boss together
with the kfp
combined with the power of takodati i'm
sure that we can bring
her back hashtag bring ina back
yes make it trend or whatever i don't
care
maybe maybe that will help maybe it will
spread the word word
maybe maybe her uh the people who live
around her i don't know does she have
neighbors or has she eaten them all
does she have an appetite for
that she surely doesn't seem like that
kind of person we all think
we are fake we all think so don't we
but i have also come to the knowledge
that ina
ina is not as sweet as people think
i've heard that she bonks her taco
duchies
and actually they also are asking for it
i said is it true is it true are you
guys hurt
is she abusive towards you i hope not
i hope that
but but if if something ever happens to
you
please know that you're always welcome
at the kfp
i will always welcome you you might
get even more hurt here but but
that's better it doesn't matter you guys
like it anyway so whatever hashtag bring
it up back passing bring in back where
is she where is she why is she sleeping
didn't she wait did she sleep after she
posted her schedule
we can look back when was that when did
she post her schedule
uh let me see how many hours
was that a goal let
[Music]
my tablet is way too [\h__\h] cute
there we go okay
ah that was seven hours ago by no
you would think that she got enough
sleep
i've heard that normally she uh goes to
bed after posting her schedule is that
true taco daddy's
is that true is it really so is that the
last thing she does before going to
sleep
but then normally how many hours does
she sleep
do we have that kind of knowledge ah
she doesn't quite come to me as
a very long sleeper i think she normally
doesn't get much sleep does she
poor inna maybe maybe we should not
bring her back
maybe we need to let her rest i also
heard that sometimes
she even sleeps on the floor yes the
lasagna
i should actually get the lasagna out of
the oven but i am so focused
and i cannot take my eyes off of the
stream
of nino my inani's channel hololive yen
i'm waiting for it it has been 43
minutes
and my lasagna is starting to burn will
nino my enemies show up so that i can
eat my lasagna
my dinner my heart earned dinner that i
work for so hard every goddamn day
or will it burn and women have to make
pizza instead and
eat and uh lasagna will be wasted i hope
i can eat the lasagna i was really going
for lasagna today as you can see
orange cat hahaha and i hate mondays
in any case i hate mondays but that's
okay because today is a tuesday
and unfortunately maybe tuesdays are
just not inna's days
does she ever say does she have a
problem with tuesdays is that
is that the thing or or did alexa
who she asked to play on gravel did
alexa
quietly kill ina i hope i hope that is
not the case i cannot take
i cannot take that i don't i don't know
how to live without nina my inanes
especially this week it's two she's
turning one year old this year by our
by about this week by our logic it is uh
uh her first
birthday since uh the the creation of
whole life english
we want to witness her birthday we don't
want it
to be a funeral please nina my inaudible
come back to us we're waiting for you
please
and more importantly my lasagna
i need my lasagna please save me save my
stomach
my cat's also going crazy because i
cannot stop talking
are you turned into a cat because of
them it's all just crazy
what is happening where
are you where are you should i try to
call
should i you know what i will i will try
to call
maybe maybe she has her this worked
before with uh
kaliope mori uh if you know that girl
she's uh the reaper the reaper in our
group and uh previously when she was uh
late um uh actually that happened two
times
i called her and uh you know everyone
was messaging her but she
didn't react to the messages and i was
so smart after a long time
i was like maybe i'll give her a call
and now that would never work on me who
knows if that will work on inna
but kelly actually woke up thanks to
that
hashtag bring ina back i will try to
give her a call maybe that is that is
what we need to do let's try
uh yes my discord is german
and i am listening i'm trying to call
her
i'm currently trying to call her it is
beeping it is ringing
people people people moshi moshi please
pick up the phone you know my inaudible
a life sign is that is that how you
would translate it i just
directly translated it i don't know
wake up the conspiracy theories are
starting
help help i'm going crazy i don't
no it has not worked this court has cut
off my call
this may be discord is behind all of
this discord recently changed its logo
they are trying to hide something i am
sure of it
maybe this court is behind the
disappearance
of nino my inanes i
don't know what do you guys think could
it be discord
could it be the ancient ones place your
bets now
who has taken control of her life
who made her fall into a deep deep
slumber
maybe she needs a prince to kiss her
maybe she needs a taco daddy to kiss her
to make her wake i would love to kiss
her i would love to kiss her she has
such
a cute face we talked about it today
i was just drawing cucumbers maybe
maybe it has something to do with the
cucumbers
maybe it was the cucumbers in any case i
would like to kiss nino mai inanisino
just give it a little bit of a chew
a little bit of a [\h__\h] in german we
like to say
not avidazin but [\h__\h] um
yes what would her lips taste like we
can talk about that for hours
until she arrives here to say
hello i am awake i am awake there is
currently
12 436 people
waiting in her lobby waiting for her to
greet
us and show her her lovely presents and
to play minecraft for us
for us and the taco dutches most of all
the tago dashes are the ones who are
suffering now
i would love to talk a little bit to the
taco duchess maybe they can
tell me their feelings uh i would love
to do a
live interview now ah do we have some
taco that is in the audience is there
anyone in the audience who calls
themselves
a taco that you proudly and can tell me
what they are currently feeling
maybe there is also someone with uh with
some evidence perhaps
i would love to have some evidence that
would really be very very
helpful i currently have no idea also
the whole life english discord server is
quiet as [\h__\h] no one said saying a word
no one maybe they're all behind it maybe
hello live english
as a whole has consumed my inanes
so where are the taco dutches right here
right here right here
i am suffering oh my god i am a taco
daddy and i'm scared
oh my god they are scared what is
happening oh my god
hello i am a taco that's it this neglect
is making me feel things i am not proud
of
i feel insufferable pain oh my i'm
feeling worried what what the chat is
going too fast
uh what you feel worried i am both an
employee and a taco daddy
both kfb and takodaci well at least you
have me that's
you got at least got something the the i
only support takodachi
and i only support the the holy
priestess
type of taco batties might be
having some scary thoughts right now
does anyone have
any evidence please i need to know i am
shaking i am
legit shaking right now my lips are
shaking and i'm waiting for my freaking
lasagna
in any case if you're scared i have a
safe room uh taco that's just if you
need a safe place to wait for nino my
inaudible
uh it's called the usual room trust me
on this one
i think all the kfp people can uh swear
on the usual room
it is a very safe room because you will
only
get out if i let you out and i will only
let you out when it's safe and when ina
is back
hashtag bring ina back make it trending
on twitter maybe it will rate her as i
said
we don't know maybe the neighbors maybe
she
maybe she did something with the
neighbors maybe the neighbors did
something with her
but maybe maybe that didn't happen we
know you know
that ina is such a sweet angel no one
could ever
ever even think about touching her or
doing something to her
i am very worried i am very worried i
would love to check on my lasagna can
someone do that earlier please
i should i don't i can't even even if i
will get the lasagna i'm so nervous to
eat right now
please nino my
i guess both is inaudible same it
doesn't even matter and in the end it
doesn't even matter
really the title for today's minecraft
stream is so fitting alexa
play on gravel i feel i'm feeling that
song right now i'm feeling it in my
veins
ah it is painful when will she come
when can i stop talking i cannot stop
talking
help me please help me i am one of the
taco badges according to my psychic
ability i think
cucumber is the most suspicious i
i have no i have not i just i just would
like to say i have nothing to do with it
i was drawing cucumbers today i wasn't
drawing inna today
the only thing i was drawing was
cucumbers and that has nothing
absolutely nothing to do with inna and i
i
i i was i was also eating cucumbers but
that doesn't mean that i was eating
enough i'm not really into
seafood i do not like seafood of any
not well i like some normal fish you
know the normal fish the normal fish
they're grilled not raw but i would
never
think about eating her squishy squishy
tentacles um i would like to touch them
or have them touch me
but eating them is not an option even if
they're grilled
definitely not if they're uh raw no no
no what about you guys would you like to
nibble on her we talked about that too
by the way her
little tooth it seems like she might be
a vamp
well vampire what if she actually is not
a human but a vampire and
she has just had such a huge lack of
blood
and and now she fell over after posting
her schedule
just because of the lack of blood she's
she
someone bring her some blood maybe kelly
can help with that she's a
she's an x-ray afterwards she must have
some
bodies hidden somewhere right right
or she can rip some down and take some
of that blood i mean we don't even have
to
hurt someone for that we can just take
it from someone and then
say okay or oh yeah we can call mega
senpai she's also a vampire as we know
maybe she can help out
with the case of ninomar inanis
i i i think her little tuffy is quite
suspicious in combination
with her ears and we know that she does
stay up all night and sleeps all day
right right
is that true i don't think she really
lives a healthy
lifestyle when it comes to uh at what
time
she's awake or whatever
so who knows maybe she fainted because
of the
lack of blood but it could also just be
i don't know
maybe maybe alexa really never answered
her
and she's so sad and she's having a
discussion with alexa and alexa got so
freaking mad at her that she punched her
in her face and now inna is trying to
fix her face maybe she's currently in
surgery
ah i hope she's okay but she wouldn't
she called me wouldn't she call me if
that was the case i think maybe she's
really just sleeping on the floor
uh when is my lasagna done it is
probably already done can i get my
lasagna no i cannot stop talking i have
made it my personal challenge to not
stop talking i will eat
pizza instead today by the way the other
choice of food
uh the pizza it is a tuna pizza i know i
just said i don't like seafood but if it
is a tuna pizza
i will gladly eat it i have also
eaten takoyaki before i have tried it
you know
in german we like to say vasa bao and
it's kid does
it means translated what the farmer
doesn't eat
what the farmer doesn't know that he
does not eat
so i do have a severe case of that
most of the time i don't want to eat
things that look weird
and tentacles definitely look weird uh
but i did try i did i did i have to say
i'm proud of myself for trying
a takoyaki um but it i did not like it
i even tried it without the taco because
the people say that
if you do not like takoyaki maybe give
it a try without the taco
but is it really takoyaki then and i
have to say even that
did not did not satisfy me no it did not
let me drink a little bit of water that
at least that is something i give to
myself
okay guys can anyone tell me what is
going on
it has been hour
freaking out now what do we call this do
we call this a shion do we call this
something else or do we call it an ina
do we make it a whole live english thing
actually the first one
the first time live english member to um
be linked to their stream and then sleep
too long with me so should we maybe call
it uh kiara should we call it one
phoenix
how late was i how late was that back
then can someone actually
look back on the information does
someone have the information how late
was i because the time
the the the time of how late i was
equals one
kiana i guess one hour was it one hour
was it one hour
then i think then i think we might have
reached one kiara on and you know
this as well however one kiana doesn't
have the right ring till it does it
maybe one chicken oh one phoenix one
bird one
kfp
has a good sound to it you know what we
will call it one tension
one hour in home life english one hour
of delay in her life english equals
one tension you owe me a freaking
lasagna because it is burning
in the oven right now you know what i
will take it out of the oven and then
eat it later when it's cold
then you at least owe me a hot lasagna
not a cool i will eat the cold lasagna
or i will even warm it up in my super
new
super huge microwave it's okay you guys
keep an eye open for nino my inaudible i
will leave you for
exactly 30 seconds be orbeez
hello
i have indeed returned i have indeed
returned either any updates my lasagna
by the way is not burnt i think
i could even go as far as putting it
back into the oven
as soon as ina is back but how long will
it take
how much time will it take how many of
my brain cells
am i going to burn uh until she arrives
this is currently uh a reporting by
takanasi kiyada from australia wink
don't forget the wink uh let me just say
that australia is in europe
and don't get it wrong i know a lot of
people have been maybe perhaps
uh misunderstanding it recently
as of recently i think some people might
misunderstand and think i am from
the fake australia but no i am from the
real australia
which is located in europe and is the
creator of the famous red bull
so currently here we have together with
me watching
uh and awaiting the arrival of the
priestess
seven what how many wait wait youtube
tell me the actual number
18 338 if i can read numbers correctly
sometimes they confuse me a little bit
and on the other side currently waiting
for ninoma
inani's still patiently waiting after
one whole hour
waiting waiting and probably also having
two windows open for watching my stream
as well and then getting the latest news
here
eight hundred so that is a lot of people
nino my inaudible
can you hear me are you listening i will
try to give her another call while i
pour some water it is ringing it is
ringing ina where are you
ina no where are you
where are you can you hear me do i have
to call
the ancient ones maybe the ancient ones
can help me
abby's here please help me move my
investigation
i'm going insane i am here currently
reporting
on the news that nino my inanes has no
news
she is not here it's been one hour and i
am talking without
a stop in between i cannot take it do
you have
any any clues as to what could have
happened we
have had uh oh i'm as honest
are you serious would you like would i
like to call me because i have
opened up a lot of uh conspiracy
theories um
probably mostly all by myself they're
all my crazy
crazy ideas but someone like amelia
watson
uh the totally british detective could
know more about it if you want you know
what i will go
in the uh in our voice channel you don't
feel
forced or anything but if you feel like
checking
it out and it's saying hello and giving
me some
help uh helpful advice or clues or
whatever
i'm here waiting or you know what i'm
writing also for nino marina it is
she is welcome of course i am always
welcoming him
please relive me release me from this
uh is there any any taco touches
reporting from the scene
is there anyone who close to her who can
say something about this i think
emilia watson has just turned on there
she is
emilia watson is here let me turn on the
desktop audio so you guys can hear her
hello moshimoshi emelia watson here is
takana
do i have the detective on the other
line
and hello hello nice to hear you
i'm on my phone in bed okay you are in
bed does that mean that you are in bed
with nino my inaudibles and that's why
she's not streaming
she was here but she's gone what
happened to her
you you you were in bed
no no i sorry i misheard the question
okay
i was asking if because you say you are
in bed and it is mighty suspicious that
nino my inanis went to bed after posting
her schedule approximately seven
hours ago what how she always does it is
as she goes to sleep after posting her
schedule
and here we are waiting for her to
stream it has been over an hour
and the taco judges are going crazy so
perhaps she's sleeping right now but
where
is she sleeping she's probably sleeping
in a bed but not my bed
yeah not my bed you know my inaudible
can you believe it is she awake or is it
like her inner consciousness or some
hands that she cannot control we know
she has tentacles that she doesn't have
much control over
she probably opened this court to stop
you from calling
well then i would say that my tactics
has worked i hope that she can maybe say
hello to us
to release me so i can eat my lasagna at
the moment my lasagna
is still hot piping hot i could not eat
it anyway because i am a kitty kit and i
react back to hot stuff and so you
hopefully uh had some nice dreams mrs
emilia what's in
i dreamt of legs just like your
beautiful legs
yeah did you see my legs like your legs
not too i mean i always had like they're
so good
they even animated yeah
of course they're animated because i am
uh anime girl with cat ears
yeah sorry mine are usually frozen in
time i don't know it's like a weird
i love your legs though i also uh i also
love the
love the grenades because they were like
so far apart like she was like she was
really like giving no [\h__\h] she just
spread her legs like that i like how
comfy she was
i have to say my legs are starting to
get a cramp
but yeah one of them looks a little
squished
yeah yeah it's okay though
i i i need to stretch my legs after
after you know appears
well do you have any any uh recent
like happenings with you know that could
explain the current situation why she
has
overslept
i think probably uh she was eating too
many snacks because it's her birthday
soon yes and she's been getting she's
been getting a lot of snacks you know
sometimes when you eat too many snacks
you get a little sleepy
yeah okay you think it's the sugar that
that is trying to sabotage her
can we do something about the sugar we
need to get revenge on sugar
the taco dashes are made i can provide
inna with some salt
salt yes that is a perfect counter
measure and you have more than enough of
it please
pour some salt over here i'm sure that
will wake her up
finally because she is back she's
offline again
as she tweeted maybe it was just
automatically something going online
let me check twitter she hasn't tweeted
has she
no no i see no sign of her she also has
not written back to me
then what happened did she did she just
look at her phone and she was oh
whatever is that time anyway go back to
sleep oh my god this is a yabai
situation we have lost her completely
emilia watson what do we do what do we
do do you know anyone close to her
who can help us out
maybe we need up goodness also sleeping
isn't she
y'all are sleeping always
wake up then next then maybe maybe
after waking up guru maybe we get a
chain reaction because you woke up then
then guna wakes up and nanino wakes up
perhaps
i thought maybe you had kidnapped ina
because
i saw your stream and you're in a
suspicious
office you look very intimidating with
your legs
it looks like you kidnapped her you're
waiting for a rant
um i would not mind a hefty some uh
from the taco taxis to um
you know just to release a cucumber i'm
i'm only talking about cucumbers i'm not
talking about any any
any processes i i only have cucumbers in
my fridge i don't know anything about
ancient code word is this a conspiracy
isn't everything a conspiracy amelia
watson
that's true isn't it also a conspiracy
that when you joined whole life english
we thought you were british and what did
you get
sorry i can't i can't really hear you
the connections really
[Laughter]
okay what did we get from amelia watson
the detective unfortunately i did not
really get anything new but but but what
what i am sure that something like this
will never happen in the future ever
again because
she has uh provide offered us a huge
uh providiation uh
yes english words i'm making them up as
i go of
salt because she thinks it might have
been the sugar
she thinks maybe because ina has been
eating too many snacks
are there any taco dutches who can tell
me if that is true has she been snacking
a lot on her streams
did why did the ancient ones not stop
her from that and the ancient one's
there
to protect ninomer inanimate she is a
priestess after all of what she is the
priestess of i'm not sure has
has she ever explained that does do we
know what she's the priest itself
in any case she needs to be protected
and the ancient ones what are they doing
why are they not waiting help i thought
they always have access to her i thought
they can
always knock knock and then say hello
why the hell are you not waking up you
know mine maybe we need to call her mom
that's it i however do not know
god damn it i let amelia watson go she
knows all the moms
she knows all the moms she wouldn't have
access to nino marina and his mom
wouldn't she
i'm pretty sure that that her mom and
ame have made acquaintances before
maybe she has her phone number do you
think amen collects
the numbers the phone numbers of the
moms that she meets
i would hope so because that would be
really helpful now
but she probably has so many phone
numbers in her book
that she cannot even count them anymore
and i see
there's so many names and then she just
doesn't know who is who maybe she
doesn't even know the name of nina maina
and his mom
but then she probably would have saved
it as ina's mom you know
that should be pretty obvious as to who
who is xena's mom
however she has not offered us any any
help like that maybe we should try to
get back to her but i think as she is
offline once again on discord
i think she just went back to sleep and
however it was really nice to hearing
someone else's voice as i'm going
absolutely insane i was trending do i
hear it correctly
the numbers which numbers what do they
mean the numbers well i see that we have
24 000 people watching and on twitter
wait where are we trending oh in which
country are we trending hopefully in the
right country to make uh inna notice it
where is it we're definitely not con
trending in japan why do i even have it
set to japan let me see
which country is it let me see uh the
the glorious uh
america how do i how do i make it show
me the glorious america
anyway show just the numbers myself what
are you talking about is that some kind
of meme you know i don't understand
memes at all
surely just show me a freaking
screenshot as a proof we need proof we
need to show it to ina afterwards that
she went trending
because she always slept isn't that an
accomplishment that is the kind of
accomplishment
that i wanted to have in life however i
was not trending
back when i ever slept that is okay
guys okay it doesn't matter that because
that means that people can forget about
it i'm sure that you guys as much as i
did uh forgot about it a moment ago
until i mentioned it
i actually uh really forgot about it
i thought you know was the first one in
all of english to oversleep for his team
oh well she's the second one
congratulations
congratulations it has been over an hour
an hour and ten minutes approximately
the numbers crack the numbers may send
who is that what are you talking about
what does it mean what does it mean wait
i am am i just playing into your memes
right now is that what i'm doing by
saying
i don't know what it means what does it
mean am i playing into your little games
right now is that what's happening
i don't want to play games with you guys
i am not here
to play games number 11 in usa we're
[\h__\h] dated please spread the word
bring how's it bringing about it that
was it right i almost forgot it i just i
i need to remember the only hashtags
that i create there's another one
by the way here let me throw it out yeah
hashtag will cast a yolk those are two
famous famous hashtags in kfb
they stand for wait hashtag book stands
for watch only
kiara every day and then the other one
has like yolk means and not egg yolk it
means
you only love kiara was that it
it's been a long time since i made up
those uh hashtags
anyway this is serious business exactly
i need to understand what happened to
not nino my inanes
currently there is literally no one
online in our
discord server um it's only me i'm all
alone
here in my room in in front of my super
new
huge uh tablet that keeps me away from
my keyboard i wish i could spam on
twitter and discord and everywhere
but you know what maybe maybe we can try
calling her again
let me try i'm now calling her uh you
only love kiara was that it what did i
say
what did i say did i say you only love
kiara
hashtag i don't know but anyway the one
that you'll need to make training right
now is uh having bring eno back bringing
of it i need her
i need her in my life i wanna i want to
make sure i happy birthday what if she
where she just doesn't come back
there's just been too many
disappearances recently that i'm worried
about
this is just okay i say too many but
this is actually the second one anyway
yes i am losing my mind i need to drink
some water i've been talking too much
can i ever take a break from talking
also by the way she did not pick up the
phone nope she didn't
so
what number 10 without the guys you
kidding me someone just said number 10
and then
two seconds later someone sends a
comment that says number nine oh my god
we are making records here
whole live english is becoming famous
for being
late to work because essentially this
these things
are not only streams they are more than
just dreams they'll work
but they're also more than just work for
taco duchess
it is their uh daily bread and water
that they need
to survive we need to think in these
tough times
we need to think about taco duchess
those are the ones who are really in
need right now
they are asking for their priestess to
come back and bless
them with her existence but who knows
maybe nino ma inanimas
is currently in a very difficult
situation where she feels
embarrassed who knows is she a human who
can
feel that emotion there is no need for
her to feel embarrassed about anything
ever at all except oh
you know what
i think i know what it is
i think i know
you see her crying in the thumbnail
is obviously sad she wants alexa to
play on gravel you know why she's sad
it's because you guys bullied her for
her forehead
and plate tic-tac-toe on her forehead
in the end that was the taco dashies
themselves
you did it yourself you did it yourself
there is nothing no way there is no way
that we can deny the truth
and it's our old fault i have not played
on her for it however it was not me
because i myself am a victim of forehead
bullying
i myself am a victim of that i would
never do such a thing to enough
but you guys have been playing with her
she's crying
we say she's not here but she is here
she is representing her she is showing
herself in the fault name
she is maybe on a strike right now maybe
this means
that she is not crying but she is indeed
on a strike
because of the pain that she has been
through and she doesn't want to go for
it again
she is even wearing that exact hat and
showing her forehead
as a sign of pain
taco she's showing in the pumpkin
sadly playing her melodies on her
recorder
doing the dudes the dudes don't you know
she only does it
when she feels emotional and sad and
like she has some pain inside of her
that she can normally not
release in any other way does she have
ever the opportunity to talk to the taco
that she's about her feelings like that
well not
if they are playing take the toe on
their freaking forehead that's not how
you trade your freaking princess okay
paint taco paint taco it might be so
painful for her
i totally understand you know i wanted
to stop them when i saw it i wanted to
stop them
but i didn't i guess i am
i am partially also at fault i
i i will say
it's also my fault for not noticing
early enough
i was talking about it in my stream
today that it must be
very painful for her because it was just
as painful for me
how did i not notice early enough and
now she's gone
she's just gone
what's she ever something to us again
will we ever be worthy
will we ever be worthy of her sweet
sweet
words and face will i ever
be able to speak to her again i was
looking forward to
her birthday party i was looking for it
i really wanted to see it but who knows
if it was going to happen
it's just tough you know paint taco this
is stuff
out there and you know she was such a
big inspiration to me
i have a discord message
oh
this is it just clyde the bot telling me
i was in the call too long
over five minutes and the the network
police has
asked him to um cut off the phone
okay cried why discord why
i'm trying to reach my friend i'm trying
to apologize
i'm calling her again i'm calling her
again i'm trying to say
sorry okay not only in my place but also
in for for all those taco dads is out
there because i know you guys regret it
i know you do
don't you are you feeling sorry i feel
i i'm filled with regret
oh all this flowing out of my eyes right
now these tears of pain taco
i don't know i thought i thought you
know i was blaming it on others
she didn't pick up again i was blaming
it on others but
you always have to look at yourself
first you know
you think it's someone else but it might
just be you
the reason why she's not here right now
oh
what did i do who have english is
five not four
you know come back to us i promise
i will personally personally
bring every tagutachi who's playing
tic-tac-toe on your forehead i will
bring them personally
to the usual room and they will get a
lifelong sentence i will not
let them out unless you show you mercy
on them as we know the priestess usually
does
you are such a sweet priestess and we
are not worthy of you
but i will help you i will help you for
the revenge that you cannot take
yourself
because you are just too kind-hearted
for this world
i will i will i will do the the job you
know i will be the bad person i will do
it
i'm used to it i'm used to sending my
people to the usual room
but but they they also used to it and
they
they they usually learn from it but then
they go back in again there's some
some out there some chickens there that
do not learn from it but most
most of them learn from it so i'm sure
that it will work on the taco batches as
well
we are currently at the one hour and 18
minutes mark
that is we're getting quite close to
half an hour that is dangerously close
thank you guys for the memberships by
the way thank you very much
don't worry i will never never
disappoint
you hopefully not as much as i just
supported myself because i couldn't help
her early enough
i am in a lot of pain right now it
is just terrifying i'm going crazy guys
where is she is late for her stream
it has been it's been over an hour so
many people are waiting for her to bless
us
what can we do is there anything we can
do
to make her come to her senses and
forgive
us for everything we have done but maybe
you know maybe all of this is just me
crazy talking
and everything's cool and she's just
sleeping on the floor i mean that is
totally possible
what do we do i'm also waiting waiting
to eat my lasagna after all when will i
be able to eat my lasagna
[Music]
guys so what did you are you guys while
we were talking about it ina has a
birthday
coming up very soon uh are you guys
preparing anything for her hopefully
he'll make your prisons very happy
she has a very special birthday stream
this week and maybe you didn't know
about it maybe you're not a taco dodgy
maybe you're just a kfb
chicken but we are all here to give her
lots of love on her very special day
if she if she comes back until then i
hope
i hope that i hope that there
there will be a birthday party where i
can also participate
hopefully she'll also do collins where i
can personally call her
and give her my gift and then you know
ask you for the lasagna an explanation
and explanation how this could happen
and how i can prevent it i also ama
needs to give her the salt amis said she
prepared uh something herself it seems
but is it more than just assault i think
at this point we would be very grateful
already for just the salt
i i have already enough salt myself but
i need it for myself
because i am a very salty gamer it seems
i know i have in the beginning claimed
that i am a calm gamer you remember
back in the days when we start just
started out eight months ago and i said
i am a calm gamer but i
i i was wrong myself and
i i didn't want to deceive you guys it's
not like i wanted to do it but it just
happened okay
guys give me a break the thing is you
guys
maybe maybe you would maybe maybe do
your presents rounds me up i don't know
but
in the end it's all just fun and games
no salt at all no
i'm not salty this is this is all just
fun and games i i
i am a calling gamer
oh this doesn't matter because ena is
not here
and i can't i
can't live
are you losing your mind as much as i am
please tell me if you are still
caught uh if you still are here or did
you faint already
from sadness and crying too much losing
too much uh
fluency kite liquid liquid from crying
too much where are you my dear taco that
is tell me tell me where you are raise
your hands
are you feeling okay are you okay
i'm here i'm here for you guys i will i
can give you hugs i can eat okay i can't
give you the house i can give you kisses
though
we are losing our son right now oh no
sanji tikka
how did i get that back to you how can i
help you well what can i do
is there anything i can do for you we're
failing the sanity check i must be
strong
yes you have to be strong maybe the taco
dachis have to hold
hands and stand in a circle but you guys
don't have hands don't you
that is the problem how are you gonna uh
hold hands and stay strong together and
give each other power
when you don't have hands have you ever
thought about that
you also don't even have those long
tentacles that ina has that she can use
for a lot of things
you can't even raise your hand you guys
are now posting the hand
raising emoji but that was a trap bamboo
yeah you can't even do that that is fake
because you don't have hands gotcha did
you know that when you aware that you
don't
have hands well now you know i'm sorry
about that maybe you can grow some hands
maybe you can ask your priestess for
some hands
if she ever comes back and the emphasis
is on if she ever comes back we are sick
stop trending
thank six on track six trending on
twitter thank you very much for that
information that is the current
most recent information we are sixth
training on
and i think the u.s and maybe somewhere
else as well thank you very much
everyone for
for taking this cause as seriously as i
am taking it i think
all we want we all just want the same
thing we have flaps oh yeah well what do
you do with those wraps
what can you do with those flaps show me
what you can do
can you do a flip okay you might be able
to do a flip i'm pretty
i'm pretty sure that you guys can do a
flip but can you with those hands
bring your braces back it seems like
you can't
as we can see you can't
anyway it has been the 1 hour and 25
minutes we've been waiting for a nino my
english a first generation member just
kidding we don't say generations in home
life english that is not a thing
and just call us the the first people
of the english uh whole life very no
and don't don't give us generation names
we don't do that
yep yep i know it's very confusing but
in in any case
oh inanis meaning my ignorance she will
always be
in my heart no matter where she is i
feel her i feel her pain right now
she is suffering and i'm suffering
because i have some weird pain
on my tongue right now i it's weird
maybe i bit my tongue
maybe i'll burn my tongue i do not
remember what i did with it
can you guys check you know what forget
it i want enough to check
because i i don't quite trust you guys
with it with my tongue
i i you know what that is going into a
dangerous
uh endangered zone i should probably
stop talking yes whole
live live english myth that is indeed
our official title
which if you think about it if there's
gonna be more generations to come
still that might be kind of confusing
but okay
let's get used to it thank you everyone
for your continuous support
in in supporting the the this cause and
for for the memberships i was actually
not going to stream anymore today what
ina
did someone call inna is she here no
you're just you're just you're just
really messing with me
don't play with my feelings like this i
i
i am my tippy toes i am on my okay no as
you can see i'm sitting down but in my
heart i'm on my tippy toes waiting
for her and waiting and waiting and
waiting
where are you please release me from my
suffering pain taco
it is just too much too much for me to
take
where are you where are you you know
what i'm going to try to
uh at least throw away my wha wha
chrome tablet that uh i have once
this is so sad because this walk from
[\h__\h] tablet reminds me of inna as well
because we talked about this when i was
about to get it
and she recommended me to i remember
shouldn't we talk about
should we talk about stories of nina my
because we miss her so much yes okay so
so that um i wanted to get a big big
big big tablet yes yes yes and then i
don't know how much
we don't use inches with centimeters but
for some reason when it comes to
clumps of these tablets they always use
inches and i just don't understand i
cannot imagine how big that is i mean
i can totally look it up on the internet
how much that is on centimeters but
who actually does that so anyway i was
thinking about finally getting a new
welcome tablet because my old one is
broken even though i tried fixing it
so i wrote to inna and i sent her the
biggest welcome cintiq
in existence which is like over 30
inches i think
and and i was like should i get this and
she said no
maybe not that is freaking huge even she
doesn't have it i think she has what the
24 inch or
something like that uh so yeah she
brought me back to my senses thank you
so much
i am so grateful for that because now
that i have the 22 inches in front of me
it is also taking up so much space on my
desk
that i do not know what to do with it i
don't know where to put it i
need to put it down so i can type on my
keyboard but it's also so heavy how do i
uh can i at least make it flat you know
there's this foot on it let me take a
let me take a look uh
how does this work
don't know i i there's there's his foot
and like
it like makes tiny movements but
i want to put it away
help i don't me it's so heavy
too oh my god okay uh you know what i
have i'm gonna do a live hack i'm gonna
i'm gonna do the following thing
it's it's probably gonna blow your mind
but i'm gonna put
the keyboard which is behind the tablet
i'm gonna put it in front of the tablet
oh so i stopped moving for some reason
because i am
covered up by a tablet right now it
seems it's just too big
let me try to move the keyboard
so that i can spam inna with some more
messages
oh [\h__\h] ah my my
my table is a freaking mess okay no no i
got the t i got the key i have it on my
lap
now well the things that you thought
were impossible
oh my god okay i'm moving again
okay okay okay for now well i'm leaving
the keyboard on my lap i would like to
inform
you anyone everyone that the keyboard is
on my left now
let me write to ena okay
here listen to this wake up
here hey some are you like that don't
tell wait why my face i don't have space
on this desk
look at my face where
are you i am suffering currently
25k people waiting for you
wait i love you though uh this is fun
uh having
the time of my life i
wanna eat my lasagna
i was going to eat it but i
am taking up on my fate
my duty that has been
bestowed up upon me
which which which is
uh reporting
on these urgent news
when no one else does
as well caring for the
taco duchies who are
currently suffering and
in urgent news this really hurts my
wrist
when i'm typing on my lap like this it's
not this is not working
and an urgent need of support
love and kindness
however they
will not be satisfied
just by my support
love and kindness it must be
the one of the holy
holy priestess so what
happened tell me girl
i am here to listen
did the ancient
ones hurt you or something
uh did
the did the sugar knock
you out what else did we say that it
could have happened what else did we say
what else did we say i'm writing i'm
writing an essay currently
i'm writing an essay what is maybe ah
was it the togodachis
that hurt you because
they were playing a
tick-tock toe on your
beautiful forehead
i need to tell you that i
am sorry for not
noticing earlier oh my god my wrist
really hurts can we [\h__\h] move all of
this this is ridiculous okay bye-bye
i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna i can't
talk like that i need to write to my
braces
wait let me
this [\h__\h] tablet is so heavy and so
huge
okay i can't really do anything about it
this is unfortunate
very unfortunate situation anyway so i
need to tell you that i am sorry okay i
am not moving anymore hello this is not
working out i need this tablet to go
somewhere else ina how do you even do it
she probably has one of those arms
doesn't she
where is she it's been
over one and a half hours i am i i
i am losing noodle arms shut up these
are my wrists if anything call them
noodle wrists okay
it's not my arms right now it's my wrist
let me drink some water oh my god
oh my god i thought i was going to take
a hot bath and relax you know
first eat my lasagna and then go into
the bath or do
the same thing and the both at the same
time you know eat the lasagna
in the whole bob that would have been
fine for me too that would have been
maximum
relaxation but originally i was going to
eat the lasagna while watching game of
thrones i'm currently re-watching game
of thrones it is absolutely
not fun because it is pain taco but not
as painful
as waiting for nino my inane is and
losing my mind over it i would
definitely prefer to be in bed with my
lasagna right now or
in the bathroom with my lasagna because
i don't have a choice because i don't
really have a dining table or anything
like that i could also be sitting here
eating my lasagna but yeah we have to
stop talking
and we know that this is not gonna work
out because you guys need me right now
you are in urgent need of this little
kitty cat this little
garfield uh reporting to you on the
latest news of nina marinas i am the one
closest to her uh out of all the taco
dashes out here yes
i would like to call myself taco dacis
and takodaci as well
um i am i am a fan of every one of the
whole life english girls
and you might not believe it but i am i
love them all so much so i am also
one of you guys i have one of you i am
takata as well
what was where was i going with this
anyway anyway let's continue writing our
letter to nino ma inanes
[Music]
in truth i know what it feels like
to be bullied for a big
forehead but i
have spoken with that the taco that
you need puns it must be so pimp you
know what ranted on the list after i'm
done writing this letter i will tell you
guys sometimes i will look them up on
google because i cannot come up with
them myself i really try hard every day
but i cannot i am not one of those
talented people in fact we haven't
we have a kfp owl you know how all the
kfp people like to you know give
themselves a job there's one out here
that is really really good with puns
i don't know if the owl is here right
now and could provide me and the poor
tackle that is with some puns
if anyone it would be him but
is he here is he gonna be able to
provide 25
000 people with puns no
that is one owl is not enough one ounce
puns are not enough
for 25 300 people currently waiting for
the prom queen
the palm queen does that sound weird the
pong
queen oh is that does that sound weird
should i be saying that it sounds kind
of wrong
and the queen of puns is maybe better
anyway so i have spoken with the taco
duchies and
they surely regret
their actions and
i i will personally
uh kata pulled them
in to my usual
room uh if they act
up again because i know as
a high priestess uh
with such a good good reputation
you can not uh risk
to hurt that reputation
so i will do the dirty work for you
that's that's for sure for sure
for sure
cat cat a fool thank you i didn't even
notice that without you
thank you very much no more tick
tock toe it is
banned i promise also
i ate i ate i
i will eat all
the cucumbers in this world so that
you don't have to see them
anymore i will gladly
do it because they are yummy
especially with some salt
speaking of salt amelia watson
the detective has spoken
to me a while ago and
uh while it was
very suspicious for her
of her her
to answer my question
so you are in bed
is ina with you right now
with she was here
she isn't anymore uh
well that was very suspicious um
she claims that
it was a misunderstanding so
i will let that one slide
she however
says that the cause of your
disappearance
might have just been caused
by a simple over dose of sugar
which she says could be
easily counter
countered countered countered by
the huge amounts of salt
that she constantly carries
with her she has too
much of it anyway so she would be
grateful if you could
take some off of her we
know you normally are chill
as heck and don't deal with salt
that much but it could help
you since you seem to have uh how do i
write this deficit
b-e-f-i-c-i-t
of it anyway are you
ever planning on streaming
today just asking for a friend
um
you maybe decided
to take it easy but we will
[Music]
appreciate some
uh uh uh uh uh um
clyde clyde quite quiet uh
clyde what's the word in english
hey why is oh my god the the the
comments are like so late here
for some reason
i will gladly uh put up this uh
a whole letter for you guys later to uh
read it later on
way that was was that not the actual
word a clarity
is that really the word i'm looking for
oh well that's what we're going for
clarity there you go my uh letter to her
is completed
should i read it out for you again
wake up inna where are you i'm suffering
currently 25k people waiting for you i
love
tho oh i forgot i wanted to write
you i forgot that you okay here we can
fix it
i love you though this is fun having the
time of my life i want to eat my lasagna
i was going to eat it but i'm taking up
on my faint my duty that has been
bestowed upon me which is reporting on
these urgent news when no one else does
as well care as well as here i
feel this is good that we're looking
over here correcting my homework
as well as caring for the taco dodgers
who are currently suffering an
urgent need of support love and kindness
however they will not be satisfied just
by
my support love and kindness it must be
the one of the holy priestess so what
happened tell me girl i'm here to listen
did the asian ones hurt you or something
did the sugar knock you out was it the
taco dodges that hurt you
because they were playing tic-tac-toe on
your beautiful forehead i need to tell
you that i
am sorry for not noticing earlier in
truth i know what it feels like to be
bullied for a big forehead but i have
spoken with the taco dutchess and they
surely regret their actions
i will personally catapult them into my
usual room if they act up again because
i know as a high priestess of such a
good reputation
you cannot risk to hurt that reputation
so i will do the dirty work for you
that's for sure no more tic-tac-toe it
is banned i promise also
i will eat all the cucumbers in this
world so that you don't have to see them
anymore i will gladly do it because
they are yummy especially with some salt
speaking of salt
amelia watson the detective has spoken
to me a while ago and
but it was very suspicious of her to
answer my question so you are in bed
is inaudible right now with she was here
she isn't anymore
she claims that it was a
misunderstanding so i will let that one
slide
she however says that the cause of your
disappearance
might have just been caused by a simple
overdose of suga
which she says could be easily countered
by the huge amounts of salt
that she constantly carries with her she
has too much of it anyway so she
would be grateful if you could take some
off of her i know you normally are chill
as heck
and don't deal with salt that much but
it could help you since you seem to have
a deficit of it is that really the word
i'm looking for
anyway i am planning on streaming today
just asking for a friend
maybe you just decided to take it easy
but we will all appreciate some clarity
a plus on your homework thank you cool
story bro
huh you're making this everything in
this letter is exactly how it's supposed
to be it's very clear i think we all
understand what i'm trying to say
help me wait let me go back into my
channel maybe someone wants to join me
although there is absolutely no one
online i'm actually surprised that
amelia was up and said hello to me
what did i walk into well let me tell
you there are currently
over 25 000 people waiting
for that return of ninomar inanis who
has been
gone for almost two hours
that is what did we say uh one hour
equals one tango in whole life english
we have our own measurements because we
do things differently in our very own
way
and she was supposed to start his stream
at 11 pm cest yes that is c-e-s-t
that is gmt plus two that is my time
zone you better get used to it
uh but now it is past midnight
almost 1am my time don't worry about me
i usually stay awake until 5am if not
even
6am so this is nothing for me for me
currently
it is early evening time but
the one thing that i am indeed lacking
is some
decent dinner i would love to eat some
dinner right now that would be
nice uh so how much longer are we gonna
wait here
i need to drink some water that is for
sure let's drink some water
almost one shield wait how much how much
was
she owns again how what is the
measurement shield is what three hours
oh two hours
ah where are you now i am in australia
where are you and the most important
question
where is ninomar inaudible where is she
two hours is one she
on well we speak in different terms here
one
ten show is one hour will we ever
see something like this ever again i
think every whole life english member
will learn their lesson after watching
this
stream from me because i will be
reporting on you if you
don't get your ass out of your bed yes i
will do it and i will i will investigate
because no one else
seems to be taking up on that in the end
it is me yes i will do it it is my duty
i am ready for
all of this i am always ready i'm ready
to do it if no one else does it i will
do it
the taco touches at me we are both going
insane and the kfp people as well
because they are putting through
is suffering as well the kfb people
might not even care that much but they
care about me
i mean okay we all love each other don't
we so i think i i guess we can openly
and
with lots of confidence say that the kfb
cares much about the tacodachis
as much as they care about okay maybe
not me
okay i'll take that back no you guys
love me more right you guys love me more
than you love to tackle dances but we
still are friendly with one another we
are
actually in a collaboration kfb and
taco bell are in uh quite the friendly
positive kind of relationship business
relationship of course
um because a while ago a while ago we
assigned some contracts here and there
and taco bell is now
in collaboration uh how do you call this
i don't even speak in business terms how
am i intentional
of a worldwide fast leading leading as i
may say
leading fast food
chain restaurant chain whatever if i
don't even
uh speak proper english how um
some people might even ask why am i in
whole life english if i cannot speak
english
i don't know i am the chosen one i am
the chosen one
okay i can't do anything about it it's
not it's not really my choice
i mean it personally was but in the end
in the end it's also the ancient one's
choice um but i don't know if i can
trust them ever again because they
apparently did something to ena and
partnership thank you that is the word
that you asked that i was looking for
for some reason because i started to
stream with absolutely no description
and something whatsoever i just thought
uh you know she might get up in five
minutes and i gotta be really quick to
do this stream
uh i was disappointed uh because it's
been way more than five minutes
um but yeah i didn't do anything with
the settings it seems i forgot to set
the
chat settings to uh the setting where
the chat comes a bit quicker here
kind of bad but can't do anything about
it now we're in this together now the
taco dodgers the kfps and me and maybe
there's even people from outside maybe
some outsiders
um as i was saying yes taco bell is in a
in a partnership with
uh kfp and so the thing is that with if
ever
if if the case of me not being
able to fulfill my attention duties
whatever happened
is that um ina has promised to
you know help out and and take up on
those duties and then
lead the kfp it seconds
to definite success
so that's basically what what the
contract said and she signed it
yet here i am and it is the other way
around i am waiting for nino my inane is
not the other way around
we are here for one another you know in
whole live english the most important
thing
is being here for one another we are
five girls
in this together we are the first ones
of our kind
it it might have been tough sometimes
but we are in this together
and now i would like to uh go through
some puns
so let me look up
puns on google and see what we get
101 funny puns
wonderful okay let's go guys uh this is
what you need in order to stay sane
especially the taco dutchess who are
in in at the moment in dire need of
that word of puns by the way
keep on trending that tweet twitter
thingy the trending twitter
thingy bring in back tweet it out loud
say it
tell the world let them know maybe
someone has seen ninomer
in any case we will continue uh with our
little reporting session
by now starting to read some 101 best
bad funny puns let's go
number one why did adele cross the road
to say hello from the other side well
that was horrible what kind of concert
only costs 45 cents
a 50 cent concert featuring nickelback
okay that one was good that was funny
number three what did the grapes say
when it got crushed
nothing it just let out a little wine
now i get it that's funny because you
know whining
and you make uh wine out of grace
you know having to explain it makes it
very funny
ah number four i want to be cremated
as it is my last hope for a smoking hot
body
couldn't be me i have a smoking hot body
and i get like you know i turn into
ashes
all the time i'm actually this is funny
because i'm always smoking hot
um after all i am a phoenix
but couldn't be me yeah and i don't have
those kind of worries
yep number five time flies like an arrow
fruit flies like a banana
shut up shut up stupid website
number six so the guy who invented zero
thanks for nothing
those are not puns though those are just
jokes how is this really puns
when i think of puns i think of you know
word puns
with words and then and letters and say
oh well whatever we're gonna continue
because this is all we got this is
i'm hanging on to this this is my last
piece of hope
number seven i had a crazy dream last
night i was swimming in an ocean of
orange soda
turns out it was just a fantasy
yeah maybe if you guys keep on telling
me enough maybe that's the way to summon
that actually could work let's try to
summon her by saying enough
enough all the time well i'm telling you
stupid thumbs
these will never however never make up
for
[Music]
inaudib
i'll continue number eight a crazy wife
says to her husband that moves are
falling from the sky
the husband says it's reindeer
number nine ladies if he can't
appreciate your fruit
jokes you need to let that man go oh
oh yeah i like that one i like that has
a good
good good pun in it i like it i like it
okay
okay continuing number 10
geology rocks but geography is where
it's at
i mean i guess i get it but
that's just stupid number 11 what was
forrest gump's email
email password one forest one
oh because i've run the forest front
it's written here with the number one
and then forest and then the number one
again
because it sounds like run or run
it's so hard for me to pronounce the r
right now by the way my my the inside of
my mouth is getting sore
and more sore and i i i feel like i
can't speak if this goes on much longer
it's almost been so [\h__\h] hours
continuing number 12. did you hear about
the restaurant on the moon
i heard the food was good but it had no
atmosphere
you know come back to me
number fourteen can february march no
but a prayer may oh come on shut up
number 14 need an ark to save two of
every animal
i know i got oh that's that sounds like
something eno would say
number 15 i don't trust stairs because
they're always up to something
uh no actually no i'm not laughing about
that
[\h__\h] that joke number 16
smaller babies may be delivered by stork
but the heavier ones need a crane
oh that's just rude that's insulting
that's insulting hello
love is 17 my grandpa has the heart of
the lion
and a lifetime banned from the zoo
number 18 why was dumbo sad
he felt irrelevant
oh i mean
my head hurts from speaking and talking
so much and waiting for inna
i just saw something because i have the
other chat open as well from inna sign
hello everyone hi hi
you're standing stronger aren't you i
have that one open as well and just i
just saw someone writing
um it's been almost two hours it's been
two hours and no sign of
be released inaudib this uh when she
went online on discord but
i don't know what happened there maybe
we should try to call her again maybe
that will help let's try
uh i'll continue reading the puns though
and number 19
a man sued an airline company after it
lost his luggage
sadly he lost his case
number 20. i lost my mood ring and i
don't know how to feel about it
mood rings wait that that's f that
reminds me i used to
tell when i was younger when i was
months younger
i was uh i loved those mood rings and i
was kind of you know i was never really
the type of person
who would who's like into those what do
you call that uh
um what do you call those things like
ghosts and stuff
uh your quest your answers are probably
gonna be much much later
than uh then i would like it to be
uh what's it called again um um
um
[Music]
thank you answer is now superstitions
thank you
i was never really the superstition type
of
person i still am not but one thing that
i really
liked back in the day that was kind of
superstitious
is those mood rings you guys know what
i'm talking about you know they change
color
that supposedly turns color depending on
how you feel but i guess it really just
is about
how uh hot or how cold your your body
temperature is i guess that's what it's
um measuring but they were really pretty
and kind of cute and i like them they
were
they always came with like a piece of
paper which would say
um like like um
crack yes uh
which color means what thing and i don't
know i just thought that was really cute
you know
i'm very happy that this reminded me of
such a small detail of my childhood
thank you enough for that
continuing uh yes yesterday i
accidentally swallowed some food
coloring the doctor says i'm okay
but i feel like i've died a little
inside
oh dear oh dear
and number 22 so what if i don't know
what
apocalypse means it's not the end of the
oh shut up i'm not even gonna read the
end of this
no number 23 my friend drove his
expensive car into a tree and found out
how his mercedes benz
serves them right oh that's a good one
i like that one okay okay we're getting
very close to the
hour mark by the way we'll have a little
intermission then i guess cause this is
what we're doing now i guess
oh my god i gotta stay awake until she
wakes up
i mean she slept what nine hours by now
so at some point you would naturally
wake up right
unless maybe something really happened
but i really hope not
um number 24 becoming a vegetarian is
one big mistake
that's just no that's not a pun what the
hell
why is this not a pun
what is this number 25 i was wondering
why the ball was getting bigger
then it hit me
that's funny because it's like coming at
ya
and the water comes after it gets bigger
and bigger
and then it hits you
i like that one i like that one i like
that one thank you thank you that was
wonderful
thank you number 26 some aqua aquatic
mammals at the zoo escaped it was
other chaos
they make up everything
oh science huh
you're talking to me with science
language i understand that i totally
understand it i know exactly what
you're talking about and guys we have
officially now reached two
two one shield i guess which equals two
tanjos
you know my internet has been missing
for two tantrums we have been waiting
for two hours
for her to start her stream and there
are currently still
25 25 500
uh people waiting for nina my inanes to
appear here together
with me while i'm losing my insanity my
mouth hurts my head hurts i am hungry
i don't know when i will be able to go
to sleep i don't know when i'll i
probably will not get my bath today or
or tomorrow or any day i will i will
probably have to wait forever and
everybody
know my inaudible
bringing back is trending number six in
canada with kia
wonderful thank you guys keep it
trending keep it trending we can do it
we can make it reach her
if we continue to hash tag bring ina
back on twitter together come on guys
come on let's do this let's do this
also it would be nice to at some point
maybe really move my tablet i think we
have waited long enough
for me to you know get my table a little
bit organized what do i do
okay you know keyboard you go here for
now maybe if i just
you know what i'll just disconnect it
for now
uh let me just disconnect it hi oh my
god it's black
okay
and now i should be able i'm just gonna
lift it and put it on the ground
yes dangerous for my beautiful new
uh welcome but it's gonna be fine i'm
gonna put it
on the carpet and then
hopefully not step on it okay oh it's so
heavy
i have done it i am free i am
afraid of the curse of the welcome yes
i must we have attacked the scripture
are you kidding me what oh my god there
it is wait let me
virtual youtube attack host a live
stream titled waiting for inna after
fellow content creator nina who my idol
is late for her scheduled minecraft
twitter are you watching oh my god
so does this mean someone from twitter
is watching this some
some i don't know who writes these
things
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you it is an honor it is an honor
to
um be trending together you know this is
such a beautiful text it makes so much
sense anyone who's
reading that who doesn't know about
youtubers will be like
and why why i think and the question
that everyone will be asking themselves
is
why anyway i really hope she's okay
though this is very
worrisome no one told me that this will
actually make me worry a lot about you
know
come back to me no no she's she must be
fine she's
she's fine she's fine
drink some water guys don't forget to
hydrate it's very important in these
times
to take care of yourself you know even
if enough is not here
you guys gonna take care of yourselves
that is very important we cannot let
this
get to us too much we cannot let this
take control of our lives i mean i am
obviously letting it take control of my
life right
now at the very moment but
i don't want the same fate to happen to
you guys i want you guys to get into
your bathtub if you want to
i want you guys to eat your lasagna if
you want to
i want you guys to go sleep if you want
to i want you guys to play minecraft on
your own if you if you really want to
watch someone play minecraft i guess you
could play minecraft on your world as
well
but you know it's something special on
email places i know
it's it's just so thing is what we need
after a stressful day at work tell me
about it
um i am currently one of the blessed
ones who works from home
thank god but i know there's many many
many people many taco dodgers especially
who have really stressful days and then
seek for
wisdom and and love
and kindness and peace
when they watch enos streams i get it i
i understand
it must be very painful for you now
don't worry i am here for you
by the way i every now and then i see
some japanese comments popping up being
like
what is going on let me just say one
word for you
[Music]
um
i've just tuned in what's going on oh my
god you
where to where to even get started can i
tell you about it there's like so many
conspiracy theories of what happened to
inaudible we are waiting for her to
start her minecraft stream that she has
scheduled for
approximately two hours ago in my
before this is current time
11 pm my time 11 pm gmt
plus two whatever time it is on your
side i don't know
uh but yeah well she's not here
and i don't know i don't think this has
ever happened on her channel before i
don't think she is someone who
comes to her streams late starts in late
i don't i i still
i still don't think i've received an
answer from the taco that dodgers at
least i haven't
seen them whose leg legs are those those
are my legs
aren't they looking nice they're even
animated thank you so much eden exile by
the way
shout out to eden exile for making his
beautiful feet
my voice is slowly starting to get
pretty slow
uh i don't know if you can hear it but
i'm kidding
i'm losing my energy here right now i'm
doing my best but i'm losing my energy
let me just um uh
right in our chat has anyone seen inna
maybe someone can help me there's barely
anyone online actually emma is back
online but
as we know she doesn't really know where
she i mean
she claims to not know where she is but
i still think it is extremely suspicious
the way she answered the question
maybe i thought about it i thought about
it guys
what you know i asked her
do you know where inna is and she said
no wait i asked her because she said
she's in bed emma said she's in bed and
i asked
is she in bed with you because inna
should be sleeping now or like not
anymore but yeah we know she's sleeping
and she said
not anymore she was here but not anymore
so you know what could have happened she
didn't say that she was in the exact
same bed but
this she was at least in the same room
or in the same
apartment or house or whatever which
could also mean that ame is currently
staying over at ina's place
visiting her mom and
that that's just that's just i'm just
i'm just trying to figure it out myself
you know
but so yeah she has seen her because
she's in the same house
visiting someone else so she doesn't
really know the exact details
of where she is now i will shut up now
um you know she could have done some
of her ground pounds you know
i hope she's safe it'll be fine don't
worry guys it will all be fine
the priestess will come back to us and
bless us
bless us with her presence i'm sure sure
of it because i need her to taco dash's
nature they are crying
they're crying so loud they're making a
literal ocean in front of her door
at some point it must reach her
it must be like getting wet around here
and that should wait that should be the
last thing that wakes her up
because it's like creating an ocean of
tears from the taco badges
that makes her wake up because i'mma
visited your mom kiara
not yet ah but my mom is aware
of oh my i think she knows um
about all the members um my mom is very
supportive
and uh actually she also watched
her my stream today and she also watched
um parts of the
yakuza stream that we did the other day
and if you don't know we're streaming
yeah cause i like a dragon recently on
my channel
and there was some happening uh
with chickens in that game and that's
what led me to tell the story of my mom
recently killing a bunch of chickens
and that's why she called me today to
tell me that she saw that i told the
story to you guys but
she was very happy uh because of you
guys reactions to that so let me just
tell you that
she was very happy that you guys were so
supportive of her killing those chickens
uh
don't misunderstand this she was she had
some chickens
for a bunch of years two years two and a
half years and she
was taking their eggs every day you know
okay don't don't judge her okay this is
just how people do things you know
and um apparently my mom told me
that after here's some chicken knowledge
after two
years comes the time when a chicken
isn't very productive of laying eggs
anymore
so you usually around two years or two
and a half years
think about making an end to it also
because they get very sick apparently
their lifespan is not very
really that long so my mom just did the
thing that she had to do
she had no choice she did it because
for the sake of the chickens yeah
and actually i told you guys it was free
chickens but uh turns out it was five
chickens wow
wow five chickens we lost five of our
brothers
[Laughter]
five of them are we going to be eaten
i don't know what you're talking about
i don't know that is that is definitely
definitely not the fate
of the kfp members on this channel
uh no no no no i don't know i don't know
what you're talking about
in any case it has been
2 hours and 11 minutes since the
the waiting has started and people have
been getting suspicious
and worried about nina my in on his
whole life english
where is she where is she i lead her
i lead her i miss her what do i do about
her
what do i do what should i do where do i
stop
even what what if this takes five hours
well this takes six hours
i do not know can someone look into the
future i cannot look into the future i'm
gonna
check out what happens in the future
perhaps
perhaps now we can time travel a little
bit she's a detective after all
oh i'm just here waiting and waiting
because that is all we can do you know
what i could have been drawing all this
time i could have spent this time
continuing to draw for a certain
somewhat a certain cucumber's birthday
told me not you know you know it could
also be possible that ina
is fully aware of all of this and
watching
this stream right now let me see no
no no she doesn't show up when i at her
and i think normally it does do that
when you call them
uh when you when you act down so anyway
let's try to call her again
[Music]
where are you sleep on stream until
you meet i should be sleeping i'm
waiting for someone to wake up
and the best way to do that is sleeping
i guess yeah i guess yeah but um
i think on youtube that's not really
allowed is it
chickens are like batteries you're
either working or you're dead oh that's
so sad don't say it like that
don't say it like that makes me sad okay
ina has once again not
picked up the phone i'm very sorry for
this sad
message taco that's it i wish i had a
happier message for you we can continue
with the puns though you know what maybe
that cheers us up
it's the only thing we can you know hold
on to right now
is the funny puns that remind us uh
remind us of inna
so uh let's go as long as i can still
speak
my mouth hurts though oh number 28
waking up this morning was an
eye-opening experience
i i hate this joke and i wish enough
would wake up
number 29 long fairy tales have a
tendency to dragon
that one's funny though that that one i
like
call
[Music]
[Applause]
before you start your stream i think i
think you need to come
here let me go back into this
please come here before you start your
stream
feel like thank god my mouth was really
hurting
i don't know what's going on but my
mouth the inside of my mouth
my tongue really hurts i can't move it
anymore
[Applause]
[Music]
it's like even like room temperature now
what do you think it actually
it's been one and a half hours since i
took that uh
lasagna out of the oven right no wait oh
maybe maybe not maybe one
hour maybe about one hour maybe
she saw my message i wrote i would
please come here before you start your
stream she she saw my message so we're
just now
waiting for the last last stage that we
have to overcome and then you guys can
go
and what's your priestess um i i am so
happy for you guys i'm so glad
i was getting really worried
i was really getting worried here but
thank god everything is okay
that is the most important thing um i
hope you guys will however
you know we still don't know the reason
who knows maybe she didn't maybe she was
crying maybe she wasn't sleeping maybe
she wasn't
crying because of all the bullying so i
want you guys like she might not even
admit to it
maybe she's reading my long letter right
now that's why she's taking so much time
[Laughter]
that letter was quite long but just make
sure to not bully her again
okay because she might
she might you know just disappear like
this again she was probably really
like contemplating about her forehead
whether or not maybe to get some hair
implants you know some people do that
but i want to say you know
you are beautiful the way you are okay
you don't need to change anything about
yourself
so what is the what is the count two and
a two
and one and four of shields how much is
that in uh
ten joes it is two two point
[Music]
one five potentials
am i doing my math correctly
am i doing it am i am i calculating it
correctly because it looks like two
hours and like 15 minutes or something
like that
it makes sense to me yeah wait wait no
one hour
doesn't have 100 minutes it has uh 60
minutes
it's something around that it's in any
case it's definitely two ten twos two
tens and a tiny bit and we can't
remember that
if you can't count you know chickens
have some problems with numbers
maybe maybe the taco batches can do
better when we talk about his
strength is uh 2.2.25
wow that's actually chicken saying that
as well you guys are quite smart
chickens thank you for doing the math
for me
two point two five ten toes
is uh how long it took ita
to wake up from her beauty slumber and
i'm still wondering she's probably
i don't know maybe uh washing her face
uh putting on some clothes you can call
me naked you know it's okay
it's okay unless you sleep they get to
chill did you ever talk about
it talk about it
[Music]
maybe she has been very busy you know
she must have been very busy and
had a lack of sleep or her alarm just
didn't go up
but then i wondered doesn't she have a
mama who takes care of
her like that like quite a lot and and
is aware of what she's doing and stuff
wouldn't she maybe like be aware of her
schedule maybe
maybe not maybe not that closely huh and
also that schedule just came out
and then she went to sleep so her mama
maybe
just didn't even see the schedule yet
but
yeah uh we need to make uh
better use of of uh you know mama if
that happens more often then i need the
phone number
um or or you know amma probably has the
phone number she can provide it
for me as well official discord tweeted
about
why discord though well okay let me see
what are this what is discord saying
about this
about all of this huh
but i don't see it did they tweet ah did
they tweet at her
they did thank the ancients you had this
word for a second no
you had us worried for two hours
not just a second discord let me answer
them
that was two hours
of pain taco
not just one second
i answered this one yeah this squirt is
quite the symbol i know
of the wisdom what is your stone
or um
i did at least a record uh i mean a
whole lot of english records yes yes yes
hold up english record and we were
trending
thank you thank you and discord also
just answered
official discord answer to you uh so we
have uh because i was the first one in
hell
of english to um you know uh oversleep
uh we took potentials as a measurement
one hour is one potential and you
officially
have reached 2.25 10 congratulations
oh thank you so what happened
uh your
time machine broke and uh
and i gotta say i only managed to get
out of it
because i heard i heard your voice from
the other side
are you still dreaming what time machine
what wait did you actually maybe she was
really in bed with um
we've been uh we have we had some
conspiracy theories and i was the only
one
i not the only one with a time machine
right since when do you have the time
text do you have to watch my full two
hour stream to get the context
oh my goodness there's a lot also did
you read my letter are you probably
still too tired to read my letter you
know what
read the whole letter i literally i
literally
just got out of my blanket did you sleep
on the floor again
no i slept in my bedroom which is
probably why i slept in
yeah it's too confident now i understand
why you sometimes sleep on the floor in
order to not oversleep
this is so blessed have you ever um
blessed your taco badges with such a
sleepy voice before
oh all right that's actually wonderful
what about what a what a legendary
moment
everyone's waiting for you but um uh the
lender that i sent to you on discord all
those messages you're welcome to read
that after you wake up and after you
stream uh
when you start your minecraft you're
planning to stream today right
oh my goodness i didn't even see your
letters pop
it's not in my notifications so it must
have been
it must have been pastina who read it
and they'll see
yeah yeah that's the thing that i want
to ask you about is uh
uh you some some
you know in those two approximately two
hours
quite in the beginning around maybe 40
minutes or 50 minutes
i saw you popping up as online on
discord for
a moment and i thought i was released
from my suffering
but daniel left again
oh that was definitely pasadena waking
up
and checking messages
because all of those messages i sent you
basically were telling you you're really
you okay i gotta tell you i'm gonna tell
you a story about
okay pastina okay so
once upon a time there was pastina
[Music]
she she sat her alarm so many times
oh but
she's gotten too smart she knows how to
turn off alarms oh there's the
door fell i could have woken them right
now um
she got so good at turning off her alarm
she doesn't even wake up
and it's pretty bad yes maybe you need
your mommy to wake you up
like back in the day when you were a
little little baby
sorry for the right no excuses
[Laughter]
for a moment we had the detective ahmed
uh here to help me out with the
investigation
uh investigation haha and she said uh
what she thought i mean after you know
um
acting very suspicious but she i ended
up saying that
um you probably ate too many snacks and
then with the overdose of sugar
you fell asleep and you know couldn't
wake up anymore so she offered
to give you some of her salt that she
has too much of uh to help you know
balance the sugar
what do you say i see detective
detective
however however what i must raise an
objection
i did have a lot of snack however
they were not sweet snacks oh they were
indeed
salty chips okay then then that was not
it i guess okay did you not like did you
stay up too late after posting your
schedule
um yes oh man i thought you weren't
right
i i heard from the taco dodgers because
you know the taco dances have been
with me through this a very tough time
we've been through a lot of suffering
pain tackle um hashtag bring eno back we
made that trending
um but uh where was i where was i going
with this
uh i forgot uh what was i going with
this
freaking hell i forgot what was i saying
in the beginning what did you say before
i was starting to talk you know i lost
my mind with this and i lost my lasagna
as well
you know she's losing her sania phones
guys
so i actually had that in the oven the
moment i started to stream
and yeah the lasagna is now cold
oh well well it isn't the consequences
of my actions
exactly
it's okay though i said i'm glad you're
fine um
and oh yeah yeah and now i remember what
i was saying is because the taco dusters
have been with me so they've been
telling me that
you normally go to sleep right after you
uh post your schedule
and yeah you had probably more than
enough sleep normally
if you would have really gone to sleep
but what have you done did you watch
some
netflix or what um
no it was um
[Music]
i was i was
i was and i was like
and then yeah yeah and then i also
worked on you know you know this is not
helping your case
because um i still have this theory
that is uh kind of r18 and you
beeping out words makes me now you you
said something about a time machine
and ami said something about uh you were
in her bed
um and now you're beeping these words
when you're trying to explain what you
were doing
it does not help your cause
um you know what
i i do i do i am aware that you are a
high priestess and i should
i should try to help you um uh
here uh because i am in the end also
nothing
but your servant so um i will now let
you wake up
properly and then go start your stream
eventually
also read my letter please when you
start your stream i like after
like in the stream uh it will be funny
um
and yeah i wish you the best of luck and
a good night i will eat my lasagna now i
love you ina i'm glad and you're here
uh i'm just i'm scared nothing happened
thanks for thanks to the uh
waiting for my stream to start it's my
duty it's my duty and my fate and it's
my job
and i will do anything and at any time i
will do it all over again
no matter how painful it is and how many
painful puns i have to reach to make up
for the lack of puns when you're not
there
yep oh my gosh this more often
no no no no
oh yeah i'll check out your stream later
okay bye bye bye
wonderful um okay guys thank you
and uh tomorrow is my day off or like
today is my day off is uh
half past 1am uh thank you guys for
watching that was fun
and painful um and very unexpected
but yep you guys are
uh free now free to go i'm proud of all
of you
for um you know staying strong holding
the lines in such tough times you guys
are amazing
i wish you a lot of fun in the stream
that you know is doing after this
and in german we say
alvina then
bye bye finally
my shift has ended
there's lucky a reference to game of
thrones
[Laughter]
[Music]
bye-bye
do
[Music]
so
take care everyone love you kids people
love you it was an
honor to serve for you
[Music]
cookies proud really you think so
you know so lookie was the reason why i
why i got into her
life
look at that
[Music]
so
hey i'm tired
[Music]