[Music]
don't need no drinks tonight
moving my feet to something so new
[Music]
give me that bit get me dancing
with you
[Music]
no no no
so small
hello
i look smooth today no you may not look
small don't ya
small child
hello
you miss small kiwawa
i thought maybe today
is fitting
to be small
because my brain will also be small
one must adjust to the games they play
also
wow
this is a screencaption
amazing
uh
hope the settings are okay
can you do a flip yeah i actually can
um or can i yeah i think i can
ah
where is the flam
what
they took
he took it away
it doesn't work anymore
they nerfed me
they nerfed me i can only lift my hands
they updated my camera and now they
nerfed me
i can't oh my god this is unbelievable
wow
taking every little last thing away from
me until i'm so hopeless
that i fall into the preso espresso
state of mind
wow
well anyway uh the background noises
are office noises and i think they are
coming from the game
and i will play this game today
uh for the first time in my life i'm
really excited because i always wanted
to play it
i was waiting for the moment until i
came playing on stream here we are today
i can i can do it now yes i can i think
i can do my eyes yes yes yes
oh my god but yes eyes are still okay
uh but yeah so we're gonna play this
today uh not too long because i got some
[\h__\h] to do i i i i actually i should
probably shouldn't even be streaming
um but it's okay we'll figure it out on
the way
and if it's about backseating please
backseat me
i feel laggy but i don't know
am i lacking i feel a little bit laggy
but maybe maybe it's my kino say but
should i
should turn off uh be sync
you know what maybe i should turn off
freesync
yeah i feel like i actually actually
feel better
yes okay
um i heard that this game is as short as
i want it to be which is good i don't
know if we're gonna be able to get a
second part out of it uh gude is playing
it for a second time so i suppose in
free or yes
the game will backseat you okay that's
wonderful
game cable packs really
all right then let's go don't have much
time ever at the end is never click to
skip this is the story of a man named
stanley i won't skip
stanley worked for a company in a big
building where he was employee number
four employee employee number four
seven's job was simple twenty sat at his
desk in room 427 and he pushed buttons
on a keyboard i love the music came to
him through a monitor
telling him what stats to push how long
to push them and in what order
this is what employee
i tap down and turn back in now can i
see this again
oh there we go
i wanted to adjust the sound
i wanna
no i want the intro
cannot get in trouble
return to me okay
this is the story of a man named stanley
stanley
stanley worked for a company in a big
building where he was employee number
four to seven nice orange carpet he
number four seven's job was simple he
sat at his desk in room 427 and he
pushed buttons on
very depressing job but why is he
pushing them like that telling him what
buttons to push how long to push them
and in what order
this 58 milliseconds did every day of
every month of every year
there's only that room there's nothing
around it what the [\h__\h] what's
stanley was happy really
really and then one day something very
peculiar happened
something that would forever change
stanley
something he would never quite forget
he had been at his desk for nearly an
hour when he realized that not one
single order i didn't do a starting
tweet on the monitor
this is the right way to do it
i didn't do it starting to heat
it's too late too delayed at all you see
where my mouse is funny
uh
starting
we have started
getting here you are late
hajimata yo
the other side what do you mean the
other side hmm
okay
for him to follow no one had showed up
to give him instructions call a meeting
or even say hi that's sad everybody quit
their job the company
this complete isolation
something was very clearly wrong
shocked frozen solid stanley found
himself unable to move for the longest
time
but as he came to his wits and regained
his senses he got up from his desk and
stepped out of his office
so he's telling me to step out of the
office what if i never step out of the
office i can't jump you're kidding me i
can't jump
can i go down i can again go down oh
i hate mondays why as long as there's
lasagna mondays are okay
i'll go down while being small because
today i'm small
hello
i'm small
small kiana on the moon all of his
co-workers were gone oh what could it
mean
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
i like that phone
stanley look he couldn't find a trace of
his coworkers
where the hell are they
are they in the computer what does this
computer say
i can't say it's installing something i
think
number one dad
can i open other doors
no can i go back no
okay
well three seven stanley went around
touching every little thing yes i did
yes that didn't make a single difference
nor did it advance the story in it i
like what i like work i just hate my
boss um
and who is your boss
is it my boss too or am i the boss
because i have my own office like
looking at that
me having my own office while these
people all have to work together feels
like i'm kind of important
um
well
i feel like i'm important
anyway
is that austria
looks like austria
so [\h__\h] bright outside
hello
can i get some more narration
dude
funny
number funny number
open open well everybody does this right
i read the papers but
fifth annual subcommittee meeting of
internal revenue analysis of four
committers of the royal revenue
discussions club
not a hotel and some stuff i can't read
i don't know what that means
eight months on more people who hate
mondays is it like a conspiracy of
people who hate mondays and they want to
get rid of mondays and today is a monday
so they just decided to not go to work
on monday and that's the only reason why
nobody's here just because they decided
to
boycott mondays
that looks like austria too
maybe it's all really not just not such
a big deal it's just trying to get one
more day off
when stanley came to a set of two open
doors he entered the door on his left
funny
i'll go right this was not the correct
way to the meeting room and stanley knew
it perfectly well perhaps he wanted us
to no nothing toy lounge first just to
admire it
boy lunch
cool i don't want to go there oh you
know just to check if someone's there
but
ah no one's there it's truly a room
worth admiring it looks nice really been
worth the detour after all just to spend
a few moments here in this immaculate
beautifully constructed room
drinking it all in
drink how do i drink
how do i drink
drinking it all in he says
give me the soda other rooms gave me
other games gave me soda a room so
utterly captivating that even though all
your co-workers have mysteriously
vanished here you said looking at these
chairs and some paintings
really worth it
it's the same picture they only have a
few couple pictures huh
all right i'll leave eager to get back
to business stanley took the first open
door on his left
on my left okay whatever what if there's
other open oh there's an
open door right in front of me
which one looks more interesting
it looks this looks like
portal
and subliminal
mixed together i played both but i
didn't play this
um i go
and this one is dark but there is a
bright removal there uncle i'm here
you didn't say anything yet do not lie
if you're lying right now stop
no i was so bad at following directions
it's incredible he wasn't fired years
ago
i'm scared
maybe i should just beat good girl and
follow the instructions that looks like
portal
sorry everything looks like portal to me
now but honestly
it does look like portal a little bit
oh
[Music]
penalty for misuse of cargo lift wow
jumping of the 5 000. do not jump from
the cargo lives while it is in motion
will cause death
it's not in motion though
where else will i go
the doors are
closed
is this
oh it's moving
we've got not on the wrong foot here i'm
not your enemy really oh there's so many
boxes a paradise book's
difficult but the fact is that the story
has been about nothing but you all this
time you know i've been uploading stuff
you've been neglecting stanley
someone you've forgotten about gladys
please stop trying to make every
decision by yourself now i'm not asking
for me
to prove that he is in control of the
story and no one gets to tell him what
to do stanley left from the platform and
plunged to his death
good job stanley everyone thinks you are
very powerful i wanted to go
first ending let's go
i didn't want to go there i wanted to go
to that platform there but but all of
his co-workers were gone what could it
mean
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
is that the ending that you can get like
when somebody told me that i can finish
the game in two minutes is this it
wasn't even two minutes if i could go
there faster
now
[Music]
open doors he entered the door on his
left
see the thing is that i'm i'm very
traumatized um by narrators
trying to tell me what to do
so i can't trust you but maybe you know
maybe you telling me you know that i
will use the right door so
this is reverse psychology
and i will now
take the writer
this was not the correct way to the
meeting room and stanley knew it
perfectly well perhaps he wanted to stop
by the employee lounge first just to
admire it yes
wow
yes
this room wow what a beautiful room much
blue
very sofa
thank goodness
he had taken this detour on his way to
the meeting but eager to get back to his
head
he took the first open door on his left
nah
see this time stanley was so bad i will
at least it's incredible he wasn't five
years ago not jump okay i will at least
not or will i look stanley i think
perhaps we've gotten off on the wrong
foot here hi i'm not your enemy really
i'm not
i realize that investing your trust in
someone else can be difficult
the fact is that the story has been
about nothing but you all this time
there's someone you've been neglecting
well if i jump down here someone you've
forgotten one please two stop
good job everyone thinks you are very
powerful i want to go there
platforming
all of his co-workers were gone what do
you mean
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
very unfortunate from side when it goes
over
from the side ah stanley came to a set
of two opens
not the correct way to the meeting room
i am i am apparently very very very um
by the employee lounge first insistent
on going that route sublime a work of
art but
stanley took the first open door on his
left
now
oh that's a pretty picture that's
probably austria
stanley was so bad at following
directions it's incredible he wasn't
fired years ago
well you only have one worker left
apparently so you better not fire anyone
uh chad what should i do
really i'm not
i realize that investing your trust in
someone else can be difficult but the
fact is that the story has been about
nothing but you all this time i'm gonna
fail
a third
[Music]
i was in the middle of something do you
have zero consideration
are you that convinced that i want
something bad to happen to you yes i
don't know how to convince you of this
but i really do want to help you to show
you something beautiful oh let me prove
it let me prove that i'm on your side
give me a chance
okay
i'll give you a chance
one chance only one chance
but which side do you want me to go that
side or are that toys closed
is it close
is that all you're gonna say stanley all
right i guess there's just one way
i'm going that way
out of my own will
danger
on you
oh no i think i chose the wrong way
ah
oh
very dark disney
uh
no buckets
um
the door is closing is it only me or
they look uh that is that oh
they sound like cats to me
now listen carefully this is important
yes stanley walked through the red door
hmm
[Music]
i said i'll give him one chance but
maybe this is the
opposite run
perhaps you misunderstood stanley walked
through the red door
i still don't think we're communicating
stanley walked through the red
door
did i just come out of that door
all right fine guys tell me you want to
know so badly what's out there you want
to find out what lies at the end of this
road you've chosen world don't let me
stop you
it's a brown door
that's so pretty
um
oh [\h__\h] is this portal free
you see
there's nothing here oh that looks like
super liminal
because you were never supposed to be
here in the first place broken rooms
exposed developer textures is this what
you would wanted was it worth ruining
the entire story i'd written out
specifically i would like to go down
there
do you not think i put a lot of time
into that because i did and in the end
it was all for nothing because this is
what you wanted to see help me here
stanley help elucidate these strange and
unknowable desires of yours what would
have made this game better jumping did
you want to see it jumping vehicles
jumping
jumping back with me you give me
absolutely nothing so
tell you what let me take a stab in the
dark at a new design and you can give me
some feedback
a third option this already feels leaps
ahead of where we were before it looks
shitty stanley take it for a spin no
three options is too many i only want
two options
let go here
okay i'm going to stop you there now
tell me about your experience with this
new version would you say that the game
benefited from allowing you more choices
feel free to be honest i'm looking for
some real critical feedback here
wait well what is good is one good or is
five good
what system are we talking about huh
well i suppose that five is the best
or is it um
how do we know
you know what i cannot
i cannot work with this
do i really have to give him a rating
oh [\h__\h] i think i do
i will give you a free oh of course a
three
really maybe next time because of three
choices
any level of critical thinking or
engagement with your surroundings does
that sound good think we can do that yes
oh [\h__\h] you should have told me what's
the good one what's the bad one based on
the data from your previous playthrough
i've compiled a new word previous
playthrough
i think i've knocked it out of the park
with this one i mean where it died
oh what's that it's a moving screen wow
worldwide leaderboard me
are these real people
two
yeah two milliseconds
did you know that twenty one point three
percent of players skip the interest
sequence how could you only the worst
three percent of players chose the blue
door
wait where's to it
complete again
to get
to the correct
yeah are they playing with me
i am
[Applause]
i'm nine thousand three hundred twenty
eight thousand nine thousand what do you
mean
also i haven't played for seven hours
what do you mean
stamp
a dead rat
dead red casper
casper took three hours 29 minutes i
haven't taken seven hours
all right uncle for it but does he want
me to go for this one now
now would you say that competitive
leaderboard helped you feel motivated to
keep walking through doors again honest
answers please
where's the yes and where's the no
one hey i nearly forgot i've got a
prototype of a new game i've been
working on and now would be a lovely
opportunity to give it some play testing
no comment on my reading look at it
would you perfect let me boot it up oh
[\h__\h] i'm scared i'm scared i'm scared in
this scene the baby crawls left towards
danger you click the button to move him
back to the right and if he reaches the
fire you fail it's a very meaningful
game all about the desperation and
tedium of endlessly confronting the
demands of family life i think the art
world will really take notice but of
course the message of the game only
becomes clear once you've been playing
it for about four hours so why don't you
give it four hours of play to make sure
it's effective oh you're saying that
it's an endless game experience
[Music]
well then we better make it fast
i don't have time
you heartless bastard
did you do it because you hate babies or
purely despite me because if it's the
latter well i don't know what to do i'm
completely out of ideas
think of a single thing that might
improve the experience for me
i'm not even going to jumping i'm out
i'm out i'm done
it's over oh thank you
your input was extremely valuable
since my game was so awful why don't we
play someone else's game just to ease
the pain
let's see
what do we have here
you gave up on me i'm just that good yes
this seems that's frustrating let's give
it a shot hmm
what game are we playing now alden ring
oh
ah
fascinating what do you think this game
is about i don't know do we have permits
for this game
can i really play this
hmm
but it seems obvious to me that you are
meant to play as a creepy moment spying
on this it's a real game millions below
you from the real game in your creep
tower perhaps for some sort of twisted
erotic purpose
hmm
yes that must be it what a fascinating
venture into the experience of total
mental depravity so far i love
everything about that stanley and it
seems there's even more come let's
venture outward and see what else is out
there
i came here to play the stanley parable
parable
[\h__\h] okay i got myself into this
it's my fault
what what do you mean it used to be
minecraft source version was minecraft
import what what are you talking about
oh
my am i going to die
used to be portal in minecraft organic
origin
ah original version had minecraft here
that's what you mean
so this is an actual real game
no no no it can't be
um well then like honestly i said it as
a joke but do i have perms for this
what can't be
firewatch what is it about actually i'm
interested
but there's so many pounds
it's an open world game
go everywhere suck it off
[Music]
just wandering around no right or wrong
directions no path to follow you can
just go in any
[Music]
oh
thank heavens we avoided it
we're out of the woods now stanley
why are you so scared it's beautiful
another game no preferably something
with walls something with nice big
insurmountable walls i mean i wouldn't
mind going back to stanley parable
okay
i think this will be just graphics okay
[Music]
now this is game design stanley managed
to figure out management i'm so sorry
i'm impressed
um
am i gonna get in trouble
okay so what exactly do we do here play
soccer there are lots of cars here in
the back but obviously there's no race
track okay i'm seeing that there's a
ball of some kind back here is this game
sports ball stanley i think it's sports
no it's rocket league we shall run the
bases and do a touchdown together
surely we must okay stanley here's the
ball have
fun let's go
go which side am i on though let's no
this is orange
are you winning oh this is fun is it
better than my miserable little story
that i worked faster than before
[Music]
here comes
you're not gonna say anything about that
i gold
ah does it have to go in
look at that
what are you doing
i am
the ball
oh stanley don't do that i can't follow
you there i can't help you
how will you write a story without me
you can't do it you know that me come
i'm alone now
i'm alone i think i'm playing this game
the right way
it's so dark
yo it all looks so broken down
when do i go
one two three
well
four two four
was in my room four to seven
it's open
i can go back to work now
but what is different in here
everyone is so dang
what are they monitoring
where's the big red button where is it
yeah i don't see it here
you wait to
move on here
oh
no
all right
i wonder what he found
if what he wanted was to be the leading
man in his own story well perhaps he's
gotten it down in wherever he is right
now that's it i wonder if he's happy
with his choice
and if he's learned the heavy cost that
comes with it
he'll understand soon what i was trying
to tell him
he needs me
someone who will wrap everything up at
the end to make sense out of the chaos
and is this an ending
that's who i am that was the original
mod
oh yes yes i'll be back there's no other
way once this ends after it all comes to
a close then i'll be back
i'll be back and we'll be here soon i'll
be back that sounds like what a certain
austrian dude said before
wow
um
i think
we've seen more of other games than we
have seen of this game
all right
all right coworkers
perhaps he had simply missed a memo
maybe
i'll
for now unless you piss me off if you
piss me off a set of two open doors he
entered the door on his left
as long as we're friendly as long as
you're nice to me i'll do what you say
isn't that very very
professional of me
waiting room
tips for not getting fired
can't be listening
disbelief stanley decided to go up to
his boss's office
let it ball up inside you talking take
it out of a passive aggressive uncle
resent clovers for not supporting you
more hmm
use this let's assure employees that
everything is okay make sure your slide
has a slick blue graphic in the header
and throw some bevelle on all the text
all right everyone is unique you most of
all me yes i'm very unique because i'm
small
thank you
that's it
ah number five
what do we learn here
what do people want things
happy
peelings
follow james you're fired oh no james
money more money things but with money
to buy more things
graphs crafts about things and money we
have our new product wow
the bus
all your boss appreciation minute
worksheets circle the top 20 things you
love most about i think we should do
this guys
let's look at a kfp so
if you ever find yourself in a company
where my name is two people to satisfy
right now you're both of them
wow that's so inspiring
wow
iris
oops we're not okay we're back there
okay appreciate me
buy quality pulse reveal reveal
i don't care anymore i lost my my
interest
targets push for funding of r d of new
coffee mission get chris out of the
broom closet
hire someone to set synergies guys
papers papers are too synergized fire
paper guy hire somebody to fire the
paper sooner this energizing guy who
moved my desk please keep the targets on
the topic of humor
unfinished again i like the
the handwriting nice handwriting oh wait
is he so scheduled
without consulting whiteboard there's a
whiteboard manager also it says r.i.p
france is that the whiteboard manager
then it will never be altered ever again
well that's a problem
anyway oh the prep closet
i didn't think it would happen
oh wait if i walk in i'm gonna get stuck
in here aren't i
i'm not walking in
i'm not going in
coming to a staircase stanley walked
upstairs to his boss's office okay as
long as he's still nice to me as i said
i will follow what he says
oh
fancy i like it here
hmm
nice
i like the old dark wood beautiful
wow a chimney
this looks like out of the handmaid's
tail the office from the commander
anyone with me right now
stepping into his manager's office
stanley was once again stunned to
discover not an indication of any human
life
shocked unraveled stanley wandered in
disbelief who orchestrated election
planning secret was being held from him
what he could not have known was that
the keypad behind the boss's desk
guarded the terrible truth that his boss
had been keeping from him and so the
boss had assigned it an extra secret pin
number
two eight four five
but of course stanley couldn't possibly
have known this
are there any other numbers that work
no
stanley just sat around twiddling his
thumbs trying to import anything on the
device was useless
the combination was two eight four five
hey
eight
two eight
like a
like a number to win the the lottery
wow thank you
oh but that didn't really do much
besides giving me achievement but it
turns out that the panel's emergency
override kicked in and the door just
i wasn't about to do it the hell along
with the story
sorry
um what
you said it opened
what do you mean it opened oh different
door
oh
this is scary why are you bringing me
oh no
i'm not good with elevators
is there another option i think he wants
to kill me oh oh
no
[\h__\h]
can't
follow the light follow the light
right maybe i should have pushed up oh
descending deeper into the building
stanley realized he felt a bit peculiar
am i morbid was a stirring of emotion in
his chest as though he felt more free to
think for himself to question the nature
of his job oh why did he feel this now
when for years it had never occurred to
him
this question would not go unanswered
for long
[Music]
but but he hasn't
he hasn't fearing not been mean to me
yet
hey
oh oh
oh stanley walked straight ahead through
the large door that read mind control
facility
all right
i'm out
of this place
that's it i knew you were just like
gladys end of this hall stanley would
meet his violent death
no i don't believe that that's exactly
the same strategy gladys used on me
it's the same [\h__\h] the door behind him
was not shut
stanley still had every opportunity to
turn around and get back on track you're
probably just using a voice changer at
this point stanley was making a
conscious concerted effort to walk
forward and willingly confront his death
why the [\h__\h] you lying why the [\h__\h]
hey really
i'm alive
i think
as the machine word into motion and
stanley was inched closer and closer to
his demise it reflected that his life
had been of no consequence whatsoever
stanley can't see the bigger picture he
doesn't know the real story trapped
forever in his narrow vision of what
this world can't jump perhaps his death
was of no great loss when clucking the
eyeballs from a blind man
and so he resigned i thought was reverse
psychology this violent end to his brief
and [\h__\h]
wait no no no no no no no please control
my mind please
no no no no no please okay please please
please please
[Music]
farewell stanley cried the narrator as
stanley was led helplessly into the
enormous metal jaws in a single visceral
instant stanley was obliterated as the
machine crushed every bone in his body
killing him instantly
[Music]
wait i scraped
and yet it would be just a few minutes
before stanley would restart the game
back in his office as alive as ever
what exactly did the narrator think he
was going to accomplish
i won once again i just can't stop
winning
oh my god incredible
incredible
i found
isn't this like more or less a good
ending i didn't die i wasn't crashed it
stopped and then the lady narrator
pushed over
the male narrator she was like [\h__\h] off
for a second let me do this thing right
this looks like inna's art gallery when
every pass okay not quite has been
created for you long in advance death
becomes meaningless
do you see now
do you see that stanley was already dead
from the moment he hit start
yes
i see
the pacing of this opening section was
important to get right this corridor has
been moved and altered to make sure the
player reaches
wow it's actually like actual notes from
the people who made the game
this blueprint shows the office from the
beginning of the game the path from
stanley's office to the two doors was
the first part of the game that was
built sections have been added and
altered throughout the development for
uh though the core layout remains almost
identical to the first
iteration
nature paintings well they're from
austria obviously right
except for maybe not
that ocean
unless it's one of our big ass lakes
the two doors the side of the two doors
the open doors was the very first
concrete piece of the stanley parable's
design once this room was created the
rest of the game emerged as an extension
of it an exploration of the
contradiction just room post
yeah violin cabinets this is cool it's
like a museum stanley parable
oh the games
old game i still don't know how to play
poker and stuff like that
and maybe it's
yeah
austrian ocean exactly no i mean we do
have some really really really really
big uh
lakes
yeah
i shall
that's solid yeah
oh that's
well it's a form of poker
no
oh my god jesus was involved wow
hashtag blessed
the buttons
this a selection of sounds used
throughout the game when buttons are
pressed each sound is a mix of keyboard
stroke and a synthesized tone
synthwave
can we play fifa night with this
stream favorite night
this is like the real ending because
like you actually go through a museum
where you can look at parts of the game
isn't this the realest ending have i
accidentally stumbled into the realist
ending that exists
that was really easy
huh i was such a gamer
beautiful look at that
ultra deluxe announcements oh what is
this a war zone
i was not here
eh is this a place i can go
all right hold on
this is the place i can go on maybe i
want to go there
oh is that money
all these super
chats is that the super chat room
i do like
the architecture in here beautiful
please i would like to you to keep this
proposal as a top secret and delete it
if you
no go back on the right now write the
emails ah after the second channel we
sent out we asked people to email the
narrator for questions
while we had
lights in the control room
wait deserve emails from
people who played the game the who
watched the no
watch the trailer
business broker please partner with me
and my rewarding business wins the
details will be sent to you this is like
that that one um those spam emails are
like i have a really really really
amazing deal for you you just need to
send me five thousand dollars sir
huh
what while we had initially planned to
use these
uh use these further promotional
materials we never found the perfect use
for them here are the selection of those
emails
am i stanley are you spying on me i
don't know
why oh
this is real
yes
the
nigerian princess scam
nigerian
well the game feature capyba can't be
magnet that was probably sent by a
japanese person
michael the rock martial okay okay we
need to go we need to go we need to go
very interesting but we need to go
lounge oh
you mean the employee lounge looked like
this before well they really improved it
the office best show ever
oh what's happening
the previous version of the choice
leading to the apartment ending a tower
would give you 15 seconds to pick up the
phone not picking up the phone would
lead to a different ending oh
cargo live don't
gargle it why do
wait is there like an exit or should i
just leave by
like here
i don't know most of these things i
haven't even
been through most of these
oh
there is an exit
oh really old trailer from 2012.
is this
where's the exit
is that where did i come from
and that that that room
that that elevator looks familiar i
think oh wait
oh look at these two
how they wish to destroy one another how
they wish to control one me and the
narrative oh they both wish to be free
oh
is this the accent
i turn it on you see
can you see how much they need one
another
no perhaps not
sometimes these things cannot be seen
you can't jump exactly i just got an
achievement that says you can't you can
stop the program before they both fail
let push escape files quit how is that
the way and the good ending as long as
you move forward you'll be walking
someone else's path oh stop now and
it'll be your only true choice
[Music]
i believed i
had a good ending
[Music]
oh man what why
is there a good ending
oh well okay so all of his co-workers
were gone what could it mean yeah
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
i want a good ending
i don't want to die i want stanley to
stay alive
maybe we should really try to follow all
his instructions
all of them
when stanley came in
two open doors he entered the door on
his left okay
i keep on walking yet there was not a
single person here either so sad a wave
of disbelief stanley decided to go up to
his boss's office hoping he might find
an answer
there i need to test this out though
stanley i need to know the truth closet
but there was nothing here so i turned
around there are some things here
there's a broom
and there's some tools
i will not leave there was nothing here
no choice to make no path to follow just
an empty broom closet no reason to still
be here it's safe in here
could use a coat of paint on the wall
still baffling that stanley was still
just sitting in the broom closet he
wasn't even doing anything at least if
there was something to interact with
he'd be justified in some way i could
interact with this team they're doing
sweet fa what's up youtube
[Laughter]
are you are you really still in the
broom closet i'm talking to the tube
nothing
why
please offer me some explanation here
i'm i'm genuinely confused
i'm not talking to you anymore
i'm talking to the tube because i'm a
youtuber
you do realize there's no choice or
anything in here right if i'd said
stanley walked past the broom closet at
least she would have had a reason for
exploring it to find out but it didn't
even occur to me because literally this
closet is of absolutely no significance
to the story
you didn't tell me to not go in here i
thought to mention it yeah that's your
problem that was your mistake
we all make mistakes it's okay dude
i forgive you maybe to you this is
somehow its own branching path yes maybe
when you go talk about this with your
friends or say oh
did you get the broom closet ending the
broom closet ending was my favorite oh
my god some people said that
the people in the chat did say that
how did you know saturn ugly and really
really stupid hey he probably only got
the job because of a family connection
that's how stupid he is that or with
drug money also stanley is addicted to
drugs and hookers that's all lies
hey
take it back
take it back that's me and i'll say
something bad about you about what's
going on right now
you're dead
no i got to this broom closet exploded a
bit and we're just about to leave
because there's nothing here when a
physical melody of some sort shut down
your central nervous system and you
collapsed on the keyboard
well in a situation like this the
responsible thing is to alert someone
nearby there's no keyboard sure that
your body is taken care of before it
begins to decompose
hello anyone who happens to be nearby
the person at this computer is dead they
have fallen prey to any number of your
countless human physiological
vulnerabilities it's indicative of the
long-term sustainability of your species
please remove this what do you mean
player i am there's no player stop
killing the immersion this dude is
breaking the immersion basic
first-person video game mechanics and
filling them in that game is right
[Music]
so
is not lost on this it's just you and i
we're not made for each other dude i
just step out into the hallway
we see things differently
that's a problem
i see things for this perspective you
see it from all there above i don't know
from wherever from everywhere
you should see everything
sometimes you just need to stop looking
at things from every perspective you
just need to look at it from your own
perspective
stop trying to
to control other people
i want to live my own life
i want to live stanley's life
i'm stanley
what
how long am i staying in here
i'm standing
why are all these sounds noises of me
clacking on the keyboard when
loud and come back okay
ah second player it's good to have you
on oh
t you can't do any worse than the per
you too
unbelievable i'm at the mercy of an
entire species of invalids perhaps
there's a monkey nearby you can hand the
controls to the fish fungus
you can hammer out the details i'm not
particularly there's no hammer here when
you're ready to pick up the story again
this is the story isn't this riveting to
you
a monkey i was a monkey before so how
dare you assume there's your second play
i'm playing this on my own i don't need
my brother to play games with me anymore
i'm independent now i'm a gamer girl i
don't need my brother to babysit me
anymore not only chat even to backseat
me i can do this alone
that's it
that's all the dialogue
i can go now but i don't want to go i
thought this was an ending you guys lied
to me
did you guys say this was your favorite
ending you only said it because the game
said it that you were gonna stand
wow
that's so sad
ah
let me close the door at least
all right
i give up
you win coming to a staircase stanley
walked upstairs to his bottom
[Music]
you guys said it was over
ah
did you say go up all right
you said it's over
next time
we'll get him sometime
someday
stepping into his manager's office
stanley was once again stunned to
discover not an indication of any human
life what could it mean stanley wondered
aloud is that wrong
he began wildly tearing through papers
on the boss's desk pulling books off the
shelf looking behind paintings desperate
stanley was in such a rush to get the
story as quickly as possible he didn't
even have a single minute to just let
the narrator talk
that kind of anxiety isn't healthy so he
relaxed for a few moments with some
calming new age music
[Music]
feeling soothed and rejuvenated stanley
calmly walked forward into the opened
passageway
passageway you mean
all right we've been here before
let's follow his instructions
he interrupted me yeah i wanted to
introduce you guys to my new song
he interrupted me you can blame him for
that
i guess for now you will have to
continue to stream favor night
you thought i would follow your
instructions never mind stanley actually
got back into the elevator and went back
home that's right that's what i did
why did stanley do that when he knew
that it would just lead back to his
boss's office i don't know i want to go
back to work i just can't wait to find
out
i want to work quack quack quack quack
quack quack
quack
stanley wants to twerk twerk twist with
yes
maybe can i go down now
[Music]
here we are stanley it's your boss's
office exactly the way it was before you
got onto the elevator it's still just
exactly what it is it's scary what a
decision you've made to come up here and
look at the office again this has
fleshed out the plot of the story in new
and fascinating ways i could have never
anticipated it's that keen eye for
storytelling that you have an incisive
rapid fire of critical plot points one
after the other weaving a rich tapestry
of uncompromising narrative wow
he's impressed my seat
why would you not be impressed by my
actions and
just purely by my existence it's
understandable
i can't leave and what now
what no
i know what sarcasm is i'm clay i'm also
sarcastic you're telling me that he was
started doing talking and sarcasm it's
just you don't understand that i was
being sarcastic too
anyway
now he's getting back into the elevator
and going down again ladies and
gentlemen how does he keep coming up
with all of this
coming up
did you did you just say coming up with
all this all right he wants me to come
up he said that right
did you think we were going to go
forward down the spooky corridor no
it's time once again to go back up in
the elevator i can't even begin to
grapple with what might be up there is
it the boss's office again or what if
it's the boss's office it could be
something else this is killing me
let's go let's go let's go excited
let's go see what's up there
what's up dog
what's up there
where let's go
wow books
oh music
oh my god
it's the boss's office
absolutely changes everything for me
give me your time out here for a minute
while i process this i need a moment to
[Music]
once again i'm winning
that's a bird okay i'm ready and
prepared to embrace this stunning
revelation and to move forward with no
no wait
no i need more time to process i agree
[Music]
i don't drink coffee though this bird
really likes coffee
can't relate
[Music]
which bird really likes coffee
and me
all right
i have fully come to terms with it
really not so world view for this
astonishing new reality
as before i turn to your expert eye for
gripping narrative master stanley
what's your name by the way
how do i address you sir
that's so rude you're not telling me
your name
i'm gonna talk to you
let's get personal you know
of course
going back down in the
i not anticipate it i mean sure now it's
obvious but you have to understand that
30 seconds ago this kind of thing had
never been attempted before i had no
frame of reference to even anticipate it
that's just how revelatory stanley's
decision-making is a breath of fresh air
in a landscape of storytelling that has
grown stale and repetitive
repetitive
repeat
repeat please is that what he said i
think that's what he said let's hurry up
we don't want to waste his time not
repeating things
huh
sir he's not talking to me hmm
you know what what i know everything
hold on let's stop for a moment
don't you realize
it's the anticipation stanley you and i
we have no way of knowing what will be
at the top of this elevator
dispense the agony of waiting and
anticipating and having to guess that's
the real threat exactly now you're
getting it you don't want to let that
feeling go it's so precious so fleeting
yes we can stay here forever elevator
ride nice
and slow that's fine with me
well that's all almost too fast here we
go
isn't this so much more exciting we
should go slower it seems like nowadays
the only thing that audiences want is to
be shocked as loudly and frequently as
possible anyone big explosive moments
right in their faces
the moment the things get started so
true where's the tension where's the
trust in the audience to build a slow
and nuanced appreciation for the story
the characters what's wrong why aren't
we given time to imagine the surprises
to have to think and to anticipate and
then to marvel at the eventual reveal
this is storytelling standing what you
and i are doing right now this is the
most exciting narrative oh it's never
been 17 years and it's really all
because of you you're the one who took
this bold step of revisiting the exact
same locations over and over
this is unique and different it's not
like anything else out there you see i
want stories that surprise me stanley i
want to have to think i want to be
engaged and not pandered to we're being
fed such unimaginative drivel all the
time and we all know it which is why
we're so staffed for content that makes
us feel sharp and vital and alive that's
why people like you so much stanley
because you're not afraid to spit in the
face of tradition you're a role model
you know people look up to you
though i didn't know when to spring this
on you but well i've gathered a little
press conference wow so that you can
talk about your work and your
storytelling and your life what's going
on because i know you're not much for
the public eye but i don't do it for
free you know a lot to the people who
have been following you from the
beginning they really look up to you
stanley yeah if you really don't have so
much time you have on them you can't do
it for free sort of gesture that might
leave a tremendous impact on them for
the better you think so oh good we're
here
wait wait
that's super liminal
okay the rumor we're holding the press
conference should be just around the
corner here somewhere
oh nice i'm standing but that looks like
super lemonade
am i going crazy i mean come on this
time it really looks like super liminal
[Laughter]
what
well it's healthiest human being
me i know right i'm still healthy
recently you know i always wake up
before 10
how i did at the pyramids the guy who
went to my say all of that was me
oh that was me
ah carpet's so soft you know why because
the carpet is me
world peace baby yes
yes that was me that baby was me
ah yes here it is just through this door
this is meet-and-greet area
selling parallel blue stanley tonight
with
it's me
wow
well it's first sentient machine is this
supposed to scare me
what
just doesn't
it doesn't look like
maybe it's just backstage backstage i
guess sometimes looks like this
i guess so welcome stanley are you ready
i've told them you're going to speak a
little bit about the nature of surprises
and storytelling and what it means to
craft a truly unpredictable narrative oh
don't worry you'll do great just be
yourself and speak from the heart i'm
really proud of you stanley thank you
god they're ready for you no wait i need
to do my makeup wait
when i'm not ready i'm not ready it
doesn't have enough time you don't need
some time what is this golf
mini golf
that's right that's really many many
many many many many many many many many
golf
remember where you came from
australia
it was trailing up
all right i'm ready i did my makeup
okay time to have my ted talk the dude
who came up with pizza that was me
that was also me everything was me
your mom that was me
your dad that was also me
[Applause]
finally
what i deserved
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god
amazing eurovision song contest 2010
you're free
huh
is this a dream
cause the other thing was real his
co-workers were gone what could it mean
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
hmm
meeting meeting bro
waiting room
huh
the one door i open is the right door
welcome to the y forward ending
[Music]
oh
i have
dog with me now all my clicks are dogs
no but
it's not an ending though
rare ending
all right
i guess
stanley went around touching every
little thing in the office but it didn't
make a single difference now they didn't
advance the story and stanley came to a
set of two open doors he entered the
door on his left
where'd i go
dog
of disbelief stanley decided to go out
to his boss's office
[Music]
i'm not going to encourage you i'm not
going to say anything at all
i'm playing with my dog i'm having a
good time okay me and my dog we're best
friends forever right
he's so happy
you're so excited
my beloved dog
matt
his name is um
bruno
he actually uh came from the marsh i
rescued him from the mars
yeah he likes to sing for me
he's cute very cute he's very talented
we don't talk about bruno i actually saw
that movie on uh my last airplane ride
i finally watched it yeah it was okay it
was okay should i go out again i'll come
back in
yeah he will catch a grenade point
that's actually what we always do when
we play ball we don't play ball we play
uh
catch the grenade
let's go in
and he doesn't like me anymore
talk to me in the reader song
it's hardcore enough but it's okay cause
he always catches it gently
it's okay don't worry about him
oh
ah
what am i doing wrong
he's not enough he did say he wouldn't
like
he wouldn't well he wouldn't pay
attention anymore to me when i do this
he wouldn't engage with me anymore but
it's okay i'll have my dog
is that enough what about the ending
where's the where is the broom closet
ending
that's all right bruno coming to a
staircase stanley walked upstairs to his
boss's office
bruno where should we go
really
up really
okay i'm gonna go up with you
oh
[Music]
okay i think we all know the drill by
now blah blah blah dark secrets the
keypad stands pushes some buttons oh hey
look it's a new passageway kill surprise
um i think we all know what i'm gonna do
right
but this time
this time
with dog
will he let me
whoops nope
stanley actually got back into the
elevator and went back up
why did stanley do that when he knew
that it would just lead back to his
boss's office well that's a great
question i just can't wait to find out
wait it just repeats
it never really got closure from before
it didn't say the end or was that an
actual ending
my dog is still here all right
it just repeats
okay exactly the way it was before you
got onto the element
it's still just exactly what it is turn
that [\h__\h] on again you've made to come
up here and look at the office again
this is fleshed out the plot of the
story in new and fascinating ways i
could have never anticipated it's that
keen eye for storytelling that you have
an exciting rapid fire of critical plot
points one after the other weaving a
rich tapestry
telling you it's my passion
i'm bolted to the edge of my seat
okay we can go now
now he's getting back into the elevator
and going down again ladies and
gentlemen how does he keep coming up
with all of this let's get down
let's get it down
surely this time stanley will walk
forward into the spooky corridor won't
he yes i will only
mind control facility
we've been here before so i guess
me and my doggo we will go to the mind
control facility
the lights rose on an enormous room
packed with television screens
what horrible secret could this place
hold stanley thought to himself did he
have the strength to find out
sorry guys i have a really excited dog
with me he's really happy to be on
youtube he always wanted to be on
youtube i was too embarrassed to show
him because you guys know i'm a cat
person
uh but it was about time to tell you
that in reality
i'm a cat dog person i know it's
shocking
now the monitors
their
each bore the number of an employee in
the building stanley's co-workers the
lives of so many individuals reduced to
images on the screen and stanley one of
them eternally monitored in this place
meant nothing
yeah no raccoon is
yes
of course i'm also a raccoon person you
got me there forgot that i'm sorry about
it raccoon currently is being timed out
so
i forgot raccoon did something really
bad again
raccoon ate by chimkin
this mind control facility it was too
horrible to believe it couldn't be true
had stanley really been under someone's
control all this time was this the only
reason
that his emotions have been manipulated
to accept it blindly
i'm good at this kind of stuff just look
at kfp
he refused to believe it he couldn't
accept it his own life in someone else's
control never why was that one number
broken
wasn't it was it even possible it was
just one number broken like 200
something entire life utterly blind to
the world
narraton there's a cat hair in my in my
drink what do i do
i drank it anyway because when you drink
it it goes all the way back to the other
side of the glass
it's safe to drink for now
here was the proof the heart of the
operation controls labeled with emotions
happy or sad or content
walking eating working all of it
monitored and commanded from this very
place and as the cold reality of his
past began to sink in stanley decided
that this machinery would never again
exert its terrible power over another
human life what the [\h__\h] for he would
dismantle the controls once and for what
if i walk in
it's just like if i walk in i die it
looks like death
but where are the controls up
so disabled
mind control status offline
don't try it do it what if i lose my dog
oh
what did i what did i just press
okay that's risky but
on the fly oh button
ah
nothing happens when i press that oh
wait i can also go up here
facility power five
what did the five do there's several
these bright ass buttons
mind controls idol awaiting input
all right and when at last he found the
source of the room's power he knew it
was his duty his obligation to put an
end to this horrible place and to
everything it stood for
what does that mean offer on
oh can i call an i.t technician
maybe he can tell me if i should turn it
off or on
i don't even know if it's currently on
or off i think it's off yeah it's like
offline
we should turn it on
but then i'm going to be mind controlled
turn it off
[Music]
and a rising chill of uncertainty um
was it over
is it
yes
he had one i always do had defeated the
machine oh wow unshackled himself from
someone else's command freedom was mere
moments away
it's opening yet
even as the immense door slowly opened
stanley reflected on how many puzzles
still lay unsolved i mean are there
endings co-workers that is
what other mysteries did this strange
building hold but as sunlight streams
how fast my dog really needs to pee
for it was not knowledge or even power
that he had been seeking
but happiness
that's his goal had not been to
understand
but to let go
no longer would anyone tell him where to
go what to do
or how to feel whatever life he lives it
will be open world let's go that was all
he needed to know
it was perhaps the only thing worth
knowing
stanley stepped through the open
the immense possibility of the new path
before him this was exactly the way
right now
that things were meant to happen
and stanley
was happy happy sally let's go
happy ending oh do i manage to get a i
beat the game
i got a happy ending
is it the only happy ending more than
more
oh my god with stanley happy and dogo
was finally able to relieve his bladder
we touched grass
but that was so fast i guess i'm gonna
play some more endings hmm
the point is that you only got to this
ending by listening to what the narrator
told you to do so not really free
oh
no i didn't follow everything he said i
got a dog
he didn't anticipate that
although he never mentioned anything
he's like ignored my dog completely did
it mean
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
yeah let's find the memo
what's on the memo where is the memo
when stanley came to a set of two open
doors he entered the door on his left
this was not the correct way to the
meeting room and stanley knew it
perfectly well perhaps he wanted to stop
by the employee lounge first just to
admire it
standing now in this incredible room
stanley for the first time understood
true happiness
then the feeling went away and he felt
sad again no i'm not sad you can't tell
me how i feel or two
now it's only half there just a kind of
um tingle tinga
no i'm actually not so sad anymore
things things have improved okay yes
really really worth it being here in the
room
a room so utterly captivating that even
though all your co-workers have
mysteriously vanished here you said
looking at these chairs and some
paintings
really worth it
oh but yeah um
anyway
at this point stan is obsession with
this room bordered on creepy not green
people on his overall purpose you're
creepy it's possible that this is why
everyone left ha because of me no way
i love because of you because there's a
creepy narrating voice all the time in
this office it's like it's a haunted
mansion around waiting for more dialogue
yes but when a long time had passed and
there was no more he decided that the
game was trying to send him a message
maybe you should try calling me instead
[Music]
not reachable for a message nowadays you
need to call me directly
i want to have a talk
is this a message
is this the last message
is it really the last one
narrate a song
let's banter a little bit more won't we
that's isn't that the memo
let me pick it up the memo it's it's
here i'm sure it's written on the back
side of that piece of paper
it tells me where everyone went they
probably just went to watch a movie or
eat lasagna
all right i guess
that was it enough of the amazing room
and got the message the most open door
is left to get back to business hey
yes let's say we
maintenance section walked straight
ahead to the opposite door and got back
on track
elevator
we have only one button
down
let's go
but stanley didn't want to go back to
the office he wanted to wander about and
get even further off track so now in
order to get back he needed to go um uh
uh where do you have a map
from here it's um
left okay i'll scroll left i will always
do
uh what he says
no it's to the right oh you're [\h__\h]
with me now
i was gonna follow what you're gonna say
no no no not the right
why would i have ever said it was to the
right what was i thinking it's clearly
oh dear would you hold on for a minute
please
oh you're not doing this on purpose huh
now let's see we went down right left
down left right
yep
i've got it now this story is absolutely
definitely this way
is it a car
it's an ambulance
wait what
what the hell what
is it stuck in the
in the gate
what the hell
i miss my dog
so lonely
oh
yeah that's the broken screen ah but
there's there's one fired here oh no
but there's one bergen screen no no no
no no no no no this is here again you're
not supposed to be here yet this is all
a spoiler i already saw it it's not a
spoiler anymore okay um
just we just had to get back to um oh
who am i kidding
it's all rubbish now the whole story
completely unusable
however rather than waste my time trying
to salvage this nonsense we'll just
restart the game from the beginning no
and this time suppose we don't wander so
far off track
okay from the top
i don't go that far
you just left me the wrong way because
we're gone what could it mean
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
i'm getting sick and tired of you
commanding me around bossing me around
when stop wait wait what
no
no i restarted i swear i definitely
restarted the game over that's an
interesting twist everything should be
oh did something change yeah we have
more doors did you change anything when
we were back in that room with all right
[\h__\h] did you move the story somewhere or
uh hold on
i'm trying to blame me now you wrote the
story uh-huh it was right here just a
minute ago i know for sure that it's
here somewhere okay then maybe try going
up
come stanley let's find the story
every door is open but i want to go
through this one that i can't go through
maybe
one next to it
yes
everyone knows what you did they just
holding back to let you torture yourself
what does that mean
welcome to the backgrounds i'll say it
this is the worst adventure i've ever
been on i can promise you there
definitely was a story here before what
happened do we need to restart the game
again no no no no no i find it unlikely
that we'll ever progress by starting
over and over again but it's got to be
better than this
okay let's give it a shot why not no
i was in the middle of something dude
huh
we know what you're doing
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
is this feeling like a deja vu to you
yet dude
it sure feels like one to me
no doors dude you forgot something
i might be remembering this one you
shouldn't have restarted the story is
back where we just came from why don't
we go back the other direction and see
if we missed anything
missed something what did we miss
well maybe wait
door not
open
uh-huh wait this one doesn't even make
an opening sound well this one does why
i miss something
ah
there's a door there
this doesn't open
this one this one no okay i want to go
there
aha i knew we'd miss something the story
comes here comes the story
was it always this dark wait this
i'm just
no wait never mind not the story okay
let's head back the other way and
re-trace our steps
you [\h__\h]
i'm getting my
my miles up today though
lot of steps
on my non-existent step meter
holy [\h__\h]
wow moody lightning
quite the atmosphere now this
well i'll be honest i don't recognize
this place at all it's actually quite a
tricky story i don't think so
i can't quite recall but i believe my
story took place in an office building
it is that correct
hmm this could be
in the middle of renaissance i've
completely what we were supposed to be
doing how about this
you win
congratulations what i know you put in a
lot of hard work and it really paid off
so
okay
i won
no i don't feel right about this at all
you stop playing now no you didn't put
in any actual work for that win that's
not true people win fair and square and
this was not one of those situations
okay
i'm getting weirded out by whatever this
place is i don't care what might happen
this time i have to restart
all right i've got a solution this time
to make sure we don't get lost i've
employed the help of the stanley parable
adventure line
just follow the line how simple is that
that is
very very
linear where are the side quests
we're at cyclists
we need to help old grandmas
find their kitty cats
well that's new
but what if i go straight now
what if i go straight
wait let me put some water
water in some more
now the cat hair is higher up so now i
can actually
touch it
and then take it out of the water
genius
i think i think i got it
oh
should i go straight
no let's follow the line let's follow
the line for now for now
see where it goes
he thinks he got it right now the line
knows where the story is it's over in
this direction onward stanley to destiny
i like how the line knows that here's
like some trash on the ground be our
destination even if there's no story
there or to put in another way is the
story of no destination still a story
simply by the act of moving forward are
we implying a journey such that a
destination is inevitably conjured into
being via the very manifestation of the
nature of life itself okay stanley i
need to follow this trick dang really
excited huh try and follow training
disagree that the nature of existence is
in fact a byproduct of one subjective
experience of that existence right
okay
i lost your train man your existence
rests inside i lost you man where are
you of this office
is in fact the skeleton of my own
relative experiential mental subjective
construct
hang on that got a bit weird back there
it surely did where i was good i like
trains you know what i think what we
need right now
you're drunk
[Music]
[Applause]
the music really fits
wow nice office can i have this office
somebody using this
[Music]
oh this is so fun monthly ledges
corporate imbalances fun work game
paperwork
[Music]
go back and look at that fern right
stanley this fern will be very important
later in the story my god make sure you
study it closely and remember it
carefully you won't want to miss
anything
how did i know how did i no it's because
i
am the real storyteller
he just doesn't know
bring her music back
we're back at the office ah no
no no lion you do know we're looking for
the stanley parable right the story
is any of this ringing a bell
what
[Music]
and after we trusted you after
everything we've been through you well i
can't take this to me go to hell with it
are you playing it
what
you know what stanley i say forget the
adventure line what you've ever done for
us i've already played nice music
why can't we make up our own story
something exciting daring mysterious
that's the thing i am the story
perfectly doable why don't we simply
start wandering in well i don't know how
about this direction
which direction oh there okay
i was always wondering about this
direction and i always i kept on writing
these feedback letters to corporate
saying we should go into room 437 but
they never would let me see i've been
telling them for years and finally you
agree with me thank you i knew you were
the only person who had my back thank
you soon
oh let's go
yes this is exciting just me and stanley
forging a new path a new story well it
could be anything what do you want our
story to be
wild it's a love story
i'm ready for it
you're ready
i'm ready to
i think yes i think it's time for us to
take
the next step further into our future
future together oh no not you again oh
[\h__\h] you stanley i'd also like to veto
the line from having any role in our
awesome new story we agree this is a
relationship for two people just don't
acknowledge it and we should be fine
it's tm you don't even say its name
anymore wow you're really
only interested in me now aren't you
it's love it's true love
but i don't want to follow it where am i
supposed to go i don't want it no i
don't want it to be part of our story
let's not have it interrupt our love
story
but where else could we go
it seems like
it's destiny
i'm trying to find a way never the sun
my finger's just leading me back
and there it is again
it's inevitable
yeah
i'm sorry
maybe we need to i don't know adopt it
i know i know that wasn't what we were
planning
sometimes things don't go as they are
planned
here we are
all right let's give it a try
i believe we can do it together
if we act as a team
this land is going crazy look at it it
needs to be controlled by a couple of
too strong people
oh it escaped
the moment it heard that it didn't want
to be controlled all right let's see
round round
we get to make a decision from here the
story is in our control
how important we mustn't squander the
opportunity in fact i believe i need a
minute to think here just walk in
circles for a minute oh i was doing that
already hey so i know that each door has
to lead somewhere which means that
somewhere at the place where we're
trying to go there must be a reverse
door that leads here
and that in turn means that our
destination i think i'm falling in love
with narrative converted reverse doors
origin so starting from the right let us
ask will taking the right door lead us
to where we're going and since the
answer is clearly yes then by all
accounts the door on the right is the
correct one
come stanley our destiny awaits
19 minutes confusion ended
oh hold up what's this hmm
that's what this is
it's all one giant ending huh and we're
supposed to restart the game up eight
eight times
oh that's really how all this goes it's
all
determined
so now according to the schedule i
restart again then what am i just
supposed to forget
well what if i don't want to forget
my mind goes blank simply because
[Music]
do it i won't do it i won't do it yes
let's stay together forever here
stopped
we win does that mean
did we do it did we break the cycle can
we break the system whatever it is that
made this schedule are we not part of it
anymore no
will someone come for us will something
happen
it's okay nothing needs to happen okay
i guess now we just wait you know
i suppose in some way that this is a
kind of story wouldn't you agree our
story quite sure if we remember
or the journey though they're always
saying that life is about the journey
and not the destination so i hope it's
so true right now life goals why not
weren't we eventually
well in the meantime
no way the sun do you remember me
it's me stanley
wait what the [\h__\h]
overruled
i thought for a second it was um
what's it called like the keyboard lock
thingy when you push a button for too
often or too long cause i pushed ctrl
for so long i thought
i thought it happened because of me
i thought i killed him
hello how long was i sitting there
stanley wandered to himself minutes days
centuries did something crucial happen i
think it's here
he made a note to be more careful with
time from now on
wow
i think he forgot about
the nice time we had together oh
new content what does that mean new
content
what
is actual like ultra deluxe new content
like actual
new content don't yet go there huh
it's actually i'm going there i've come
so far
[Music]
what is it
is it okay to go
okay let's go
go go go go
spoilers endings ain't really
spooky hello and thank you for playing
the stanley parable ultra deluxe you're
welcome as you may know the stanley
parable was a video game released in
2013 on home computers so cute
after receiving critical and commercial
success it was expanded upon in 2022
with the stanley parable
of the game for conscience this is like
a
ride
a theme park stanley parable ultra
deluxe features exciting new content
that brought amelia into the world of
the stanley parable what are you doing
this is the world over
oh my my
please step inside and see what
thrilling new adventures await in the
stanley parable ultra deluxe exciting
let's go sounds delightful indeed i'm
very excited to see the thrilling new
ultra deluxe content ultra mega super
flap fragrance disney so far it's an
elevator nothing special yet i love
elevators but there's nobody
mesmerizing adventure our adventure
remember
okay
um
is it broken ah what's going on here
should we
should we be moving somewhere or oh it's
not moving all right finally at long
last it's on to the new content i've
never been more ready let's do it
how far are we going hmm oh [\h__\h] my eye
my ears are popping not my eyes stanley
parable i'm pulling out my eyes
mythius it's as if them
oh okay let's see the content give me
the content
excited and happy
i didn't paint the walls yet did you
need some blue and some orange
jump circle
all right
all right let's see it's
good
[Music]
i don't have endless gems i only have 15
jumps i need to
be really really really really careful
and treasure each jump
yay
ah
i need to really feel every single one
of them i need to save them for
that's a good idea i shouldn't use them
all up at once yeah
i was too greedy i already used up so
many
but you're right guys i should i should
keep them
i should keep them
so i can like maybe
in 13 years long
once per year i can jump
yeah
sounds good this
is that it yes surely that's not all the
new content that's amazing nothing else
right it should be outside of the circle
too though
that would be better
what else can we do
what else what else what else
walsa what about the furrings
another elevator stanley i have to say
initial impressions of this game are not
positive it's just elevators and jumping
is this what passes for exciting new
content i was super excited i think it
passes the test there's 20 hours of new
content right there hell i could counter
30 trillion you could put that on the
box the stanley parable ultra deluxe now
with over a thousand hours of new
content and if oh wait
there's more
very good but when there's more i knew
there had to be something let's see it
i'm ready for whatever it is what about
portals
maybe you should
just an idea i don't know where i got
that from but
it's probably totally original i think
because the only things i think of are
original i think you should try
a thing where you know you make a portal
here
and you make a portal over there and
then you walk through this one and then
you get out there
i think that's genius what do you think
mind breaking too
also what's really important with that
is momentum but that's another story for
another day i'll tell you more about
that
that's it
now you've got to be kidding me you see
stanley this is what happens when greedy
video game developers with no respect
for their fan base rush a cheap
expansion to market for no reason other
than to make are you a genius why are
you guys so surprised put it on the
level of craftsmanship that's gone into
it in fact i'm looking right now at the
game's achievements and it's hard to
believe one of them actually says test
achievement please ignore what quality
assurance department signed off on this
i'm infuriated and i'm offended and i i
intend to find these people on twitter
and hold them personally accountable
the evil bird i built up too much
anticipation around the new content i'm
afraid it could never have lived up to
such expectations if you're still with
me why don't we just reset the game and
we'll try to get back to what the
stanley parable is really about
yes no frills
no gimmicks i like frail stuff you and
me having a great time together like
always that's exactly what i want okay
i will give up on jumping if it means i
can spend more time
with my beloved narrator son
okay
i think he did forget about our
adventure but i'm just
so lovely that he fell in love with me
again all over
immediately
friends no it's not friendship no what
are you talking about
have beautiful pictures of our
adventures
mary the son where are you
[Music]
where are you
stanley yes come over here yes in the
vent i wanted to show you something yes
my beloved
i will come to you
mumma why
i'm venting
don't tell anyone
there it is on
how deep must i fall to come to you
it's a bit scary but i will it will be
fine
problem probably
they read the song okay you remember how
cheap and unsatisfying the new ultra
deluxe content turned out to be well it
got me thinking about the past and how
much better the stanley parable used to
be
so i made something special and tucked
it away here where the game's developers
won't find it
just something little secret smart
the developers don't know what they're
doing after all okay what is this whoa
this is a church where are we having our
wedding ceremony
ah
i knew you would come through my
beloved oh
not quite
i call it the memory zone
it's where i've been storing all my
favorite memories so i can relive the
peak experiences of my life whenever i
want marvelous experiences like the
launch of the stanley parable on pc wow
let's take a look at that i mean i
didn't know you back then but i wouldn't
mind getting to know the old you
yes let's do it
wow
2013. you see stanley doesn't the memory
zone remind you of how wonderful stanley
parable was before it was solid with a
cheap re-release
remember back in october of 2013 when
the game originally launched i don't
remember forgive me your games had
integrity back then is that your face
you're beautiful even if you're missing
an eye
i just want you to know that
you're beautiful just the way you are
i will love you no matter what
that's not the time
our first kiss my first car the release
of stalin
who's
what
i thought it was only me that you loved
what is this what is that all about now
write a song you need to explain that to
me who do i need to destroy
humpst
who did you kiss
what
i don't understand
whatever are all of these memories just
memories of you of something else
someone else
i don't want to be in this memory lane
is that the first super chat you sent to
the other youtuber that you follow
wow
i thought i was the only one
huh
achievable it is impossible to get this
i want it
give it to me
now you show me all these things that i
can't get
all this love that you had with
humps that i can't get
oh i heard a chicken i heard a rooster
alright [\h__\h] you i'll go to the rooster
that's my destiny chickens are my
destiny
where are you
[Music]
let me
and go here is where i keep reviews of
the stanley parable like this stunning
triumph of games journalism 10 out of 10
from
destructoid.com james stephanie sterling
writes and i quote
we're so many games that aspire to be
more than games end up less than any
form of art stanley parable strives and
then succeeds to be every game ever
created did you hear that stanley every
game ever created that's how grand and
all-encompassing the original stanley
parable was it was literally every game
ever created it was skyrim it was
persona 3 it was all of them and now
it's nothing
it's no games at all
it isn't even the stanley parable
anymore it's just a husk now
a lifeless husk with an hour of new
elevator content
what he was reading wasn't written on
here
how do you review a game like stanley
parable to describe any one part of it
is to risk its ruination
the detail what it has to say about game
design illusion of choice and psychology
of the game is to tell you too much
comparisons too are going to be woefully
inadequate perhaps his closet cousin
would be there esther but where dearest
waste is
race the form of interactive
entertainment stanley parable uses and
subverts it where so many games that
aspire to be more than games end up less
than any form of art stanley parable
strives and then succeeds to be every
gamer every game ever created
even still holding the game to the
standards of any other title is simply
not going to be correct so how do you
review what has become known as the
stanley parable hd the full-scale
reimagining of one of the most
intriguing mods available online how do
you discuss the analyze and recommend it
is this review
your true love loretta
just looking at how you built a shrine
for it
you really seem to love it a lot
maybe you should
start to accept other reviews too
because this is [\h__\h] creepy
up or down
we
stimulating commentary on the nature of
choice in games and one that offers some
of the most enjoyable surprising and
rewarding choices i've ever been
confused i don't care you're just you're
just crazing yourself now
the game was perfect no i didn't need
anything else it didn't need new content
it just needed to be left alone
to spend the rest of time collecting
dust in the hallowed hall of beloved
video game memories
okay
these were simpler times stanley
but i wouldn't give to go back to have
it all over i'd be the protagonist again
why is that where's the stanley parable
the game the protagonist now i want to
be the protagonist that's why the name
is gamed after
ah wait
hang on yeah yeah hang on
out of the memory zone before
what's this what's down here
didn't say nothing i didn't sing i
didn't see nothing
what
oh no oh god no stanley it's a
collection of reviews from steam the
online video game distributor i haven't
looked at these in years let's not look
at them imagine what's being collecting
done yeah i can imagine they're [\h__\h]
only these reviews were you bombed
oh i can imagine though
oh
that's so sad what they say
honestly i could not be bothered to play
this game to full completion the
narrator is obnoxious and unknown
with his humor and dialogue proving to
be more irritating than entertainment oh
gleby are you a little [\h__\h] funny i'm
not trying to be funny i'm trying to
make a serious work of art i suppose i
could write up a handful of gags to
insert into the stanley parable but the
game is already such a densely layered
web they're real that's so salty this is
just the developers living out their
anger
and trying to roast people
holy [\h__\h] though the person who wrote
that
if that is real
i wonder how they must be feeling oh
[\h__\h]
oh and they even put i can't believe
they put up the name
is that really their user name
they must be feeling really really
really [\h__\h] stupid now
what is this
no little job
this preachiness gets annoying fast
preachy stanley i'm not preachy am i
you can tell me if i'm preachy honestly
you can you you become cocky i can tell
you that you're shocking for me right
to be honest i had always thought of the
game's dialogue as being rather tears to
begin with
you can't know how much fluff i cut from
the game to get it to feel as light and
airy as it well i always thought it did
but maybe it wasn't
what an awful memory to have to hold on
to
these black marks are my otherwise
unimpeachable track record who's this i
feel that's actually a good one
a noodle chat by the way means noodle
sheep the stanley parable isn't quite as
sterling as i always remembered um
yeah maybe
maybe it was
not that i mean i i like him but
you must have done something to upset
upset those people right
looks like
pokemon
a little bit better though
reviews reviews everywhere so many
reviews man
wow maybe you shouldn't look at the
steam reviews dude they're they're uh
not doing anything good for you
what is this one the last one what's
this one got to say it's like a titanic
moment should we like take it to stop
doing anything so the narrator can catch
up with his long-winded explanations of
what
i wish there was a skip button that was
me who wrote that review
well well yes yes i think we can do that
if i'm truly too preachy then then maybe
letting you skip ahead for just a moment
i'm sure it couldn't hurt i'm gonna go
swimming if it means we can strike these
negative reviews from the record only
positive reviews of the stanley parable
that's my motto today and it's always
been my motto i'd do anything for the
customer standing yes is he okay
we shall have
and i feel like we kind of angered him a
little bit too much
uh is that i i i i personally didn't
need a skip button
i'm i was fine without one
what on a new one um i'm i didn't ask
for skip button
but i guess if you give it to me i guess
i'll use it just go ahead and give it a
shot
i didn't even hesitate
oh you're back you see you were only
frozen in time for a few minutes but it
was plenty of time for me to deliver a
long rambling monologue full of
unnecessary verbal flowers what have i
listened to ruminations on the nature of
choice in video games i wonder how long
you would have had to believe it was
perhaps one of my more profound such
ruminations not that of oh wait should i
do it again no but but if i had to
describe it i'd say it was perhaps less
oh it loops oh anyway
you really didn't catch me rambling on a
bit didn't you
[Music]
okay welcome back stanley now i should
say that the amount of time the button
has been skipping through is becoming
longer and longer that last one was well
i want to say maybe 30 45 minutes what
if not uninjured you may have an illness
i tangent but i wouldn't call it an
illness but for you i do suggest that we
not press you have a serious tangenting
problem dude
stanley please don't push the button
again
but it's not my fault you've just been
frozen there i don't know why the skips
are getting longer but they're really
truly getting longer and my god there's
no way out of the room i think it's
because you keep on talking and talking
and talking and talking looked at it
from every angle
is this the way i talk about him right
now is this what the chat thinks about
me stanley there's no door there's just
you and the button and if you keep
pressing it i have no idea what will
happen i have no idea how long i'll be
made to sit here and more than anything
else i don't know how to stop
anything in this room stanley i can't
touch it and i have to believe you guys
want to skip button on me
no matter how no way right why would you
want that press the button again why
would you i've been thinking and
thinking and i i don't know what i can
do to convince you otherwise oh my god
oh stanley look back are you dying back
goodness
someone hasn't been 84 years
stanley i i think it's been a week oh
about two weeks you sound like you're
dying here all that time just sitting
here not a single person ah
and you'd think that that's just how
it's always been right
me talking and you saying nothing
would you think that it's exactly the
same as always doesn't that feel like
what we've already been doing me just
talking but it isn't standing it isn't
the same at all don't escape my
monologue because i know you can't hear
me once you push that button that's what
i'm realizing now stanley i'm realizing
that i needed to know that someone was
listening i needed there to be a vessel
through which my words were moving
if you need a vessel you should audition
to whole life none of that matters
anymore i'll give it all up i'll give up
every narrator for all of english learn
my story
and god i can see now that i needed more
than anything
to know that someone else you're just
talking about these words that i'm
saying i need to know you can hear me
because maybe maybe if you can hear me
then maybe
it means i'm real maybe a real boy yeah
maybe just a fiction okay was i scared
of that all along perhaps yes
perhaps i've been scared this whole time
oh stop speaking i'll slip backwards
into the silence and be consumed by it
maybe every word he's saying is exactly
how i feel deep inside my heart between
you and me when you press that button
you're still right there but i know
you're so tremendous it's like when you
guys press the x button on your browser
don't press it guys
don't leave me i need you and it's
unusual you being here makes me feel
real feel the edges
i am alive i am truly and completely
here i am
[Music]
you can see what this means to me i'm so
clear about it now stanley i feel a
certain amount of lonely i've ever felt
about anything at all i feel renewed i
feel restored and already i'm good for
you looming silence as you will press
the button for the next time what a
terrible dread it strokes in my heart to
think of it to think of returning to
such coldness
let us sit in silence together here for
just a moment okay check shut up
silence
let us not run from it
yes
you
what the [\h__\h] sneezed
oh hello it's you you're here again
welcome
i have had time to think about you and
about us and about everything we've been
through i've had so much time i stopped
keeping track after a year have you ever
done in one place not move for one
entire year let me describe it for you
there is only regret there is only the
turning wheel of missed opportunities i
felt nothing at all but regret for the
longest time stanley days months i lost
it all in a blur of the deepest longing
to undo the past
you sound like a [\h__\h] drama queen to
me it's what i can only describe as the
collapse of every moment i have ever
experienced my entire life all of them
collapsed down into a single instant in
that instant i could see myself clearly
calmly with a collected heart it was an
impossibly rich wellspring of both
delight and disgust simultaneously a
year of doing nothing at all sounds
honestly like 2021 and 2022 like an
eternity for what i now know was far
less you see it was a revelation for me
it was unlike anything i had ever known
it was a space without consequence
without action or outcome although it's
ending
just like your now
oh you're dead now am i killing the
narrator
he's dead and i'm laughing he's dead and
i'm laughing what hello
hello
hello is he sleeping
sorry
wake up
[Music]
[\h__\h] that alarm
[\h__\h] shut up
shut up i don't like it
i don't like the sound
is that coming from the back
no
is it his alarm
but they didn't understand the game was
never meant to be funny was meant to
have a point it was meant to speak to
the human condition but where are the
jokes where are the jokes they bemoan
this boundary
entertain us
say hello to me greet me acknowledge me
thumbs down review and make all of their
pitiful demands
he's talking too much they said first he
didn't entertain us now he went shut up
it's the inconsistency it's the lack of
accountability it's the unwillingness to
examine with an uncompromising heart the
words that they are speaking into the
world so basically basically what you
did with the dlc is just not really put
any content in there but just put in
dialogue and talking talking talking
talking talking that's just [\h__\h] you
sort of just added more jumping freddy
jumps was not enough i'm i still have 13
gems left but there's honestly not
enough what the [\h__\h] this is nothing you
said that just jumping wasn't good
enough and now all you do oh you add to
this dlc now is your dialogue you stupid
ass dialogue that's all you can do and
first before that it was just praising
yourself because you're a cocky little
dip [\h__\h] so he kept on praising herself
until the very moment when you saw that
there were a few reviews that were not
the same opinion as you own a few
reviews that didn't stroke your super
[\h__\h] deluxe altered it looks huge as
ego was that oh it was a little bit
hurtful to you was it a little bit
painful hey chad why are you trying to
skip me you want to skip me you want to
skip me all right i'm trying to [\h__\h]
skip me try it
you're happy now
happy
you happy
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's never the is it's never the end
it's never the end it is never the end
is never the end it's never the end it's
never the end it's never the end it's
never the end it's never the end never
the end is never the end is never the
end
[Music]
is
it's never the end
oh [\h__\h] apocalypse let's go
is it an exit now
oh we need a few more years maybe then
the apocalypse will have created an
accident for us
wow we're getting there there's daylight
there's a hole up there just need a hole
like on the side because i can't [\h__\h]
jump
well it seems like the narrative is dead
beautiful where's the fern the fan
dude you said you said the fern was a
joke but here it is here it is all over
this is the answer
the birds are chirping
ah beautiful
yes apocalypse is the
ideal way of living
hmm
no wait what the actual [\h__\h]
what happened
what is it now
what happened with the fauna
and the flora
doom is upon us
what the [\h__\h] it's not even changing
anymore
i broke the game
accent
wow let's go
but wait this is amazing because that
means we survived the apocalypse as
seemingly the only
human being or phoenix being on earth
[Music]
freedom because
i'm the only one left
skull
sand
[\h__\h] sand
i hate scent
this course and raffle gets [\h__\h]
everywhere
anyway we just gotta go
i don't know where
you're telling me that
that did not count as an ending you know
how much effort i put into that
wait stanley thought to himself am i
sure that the orders stopped coming in
how is that possible they never stopped
surely i was mistaken
mommy i'm scared
my mom's watching this by the way
she likes the game and i don't think she
played the new one yet
wow
a new new content
i mean if there's neon lights
if there's neon lights and it must be
exciting
huh
oh good you noticed my sight it was very
noticeable i have something very
exciting to show you really
your tangent so what more reviews i hope
it's not more reviews
more jumps are welcome though
all right
let's see what we got
you don't want to talk about what just
happened to me i've been reflecting on
the stairs
and about how roundly disappointing this
ultra deluxe version has turned out to
be you remember it being disappointing
but you don't remember talking to me
before any new content for it should
live up to that legacy so forget this
ultra deluxe nonsense i say we take it
one step even further emotionally
i'm very proud to announce for the first
time ever
the stanley parable
two
i mean why not
yes you see isn't this far superior to a
measly re-release with a few minor
additions think of all the territory
we'll cover with a fully fledged sequel
an entirely new experience built from
the ground up yeah there's so many
possibilities it could go in so many
different directions yes this is what
fans have truly been asking for
yes
yes yes yes i think a lot of people want
it stanley parable too is just so much
catchier than ultra deluxe don't you
think i agree with that what does it
even mean yeah that just sounds like a
revamped version
like improving the graphics right there
it's future oriented it screams progress
and obvious and long term wow automatic
doors let's go
over what's this the color red yes color
red very important
yeah yeah yeah yeah you're getting it
now
they're back two doors oh my god stanley
powerball two also comes with two doors
let's go wow
oh oh let's look at those logos oh
oh funny they put the two and the b and
the l
oh [\h__\h] the comic sense
that one looks like a pretty ugly little
liar kind of uh
logo
um all right let's go then
i think the logo that you chose there is
the best one
[Music]
now
i haven't quite nailed down what exactly
the stanley parable 2 is going to be but
let's take a look at some of the
features i've been developing for it
i figure that if i can loosely organize
a handful of interesting things why i
hate comics the game will sort of you
have to hate common sense around them
you have will work itself out game
development is much more of a fuzzy
magic than anything scientific or
logical really
oh
oh it's so stylistic beautiful
this way to the show
oh it's like a netflix premiere
let's go oh
fancy
you got new graphic designers huh oh a
bus
that's driving you directly directly to
the seats mmm i call that service
wow
red carpet and all that oh
holy [\h__\h] toe
here we are go on try out some of the
new features bucket
reassurance bucket
button that says the name of the player
that is playing the game
that's new
hear a name in the game whoa
wait wait wait which way they'll go
there's so many ways
and they're speaking my language
who's selling it hello where are the
people
where are the people oh which door
all right i'm going here
the bucket the common complaint of the
stanley parable was that it was
confusing and paradoxical that it
engendered a chaotic sense of reckless
despair in those who played it well
i'm happy to say that after much
consideration i've engineered a clever
solution to this fundamental problem
where's the bucket it's the stanley
parable reassurance bucket stole the
bucket stanley anytime you're holding
the bucket a sense of calm and ease will
fill your mind and your heart yeah i
know a thing or two about them my people
know the thing something or many things
about that stanley parable will feel
perfectly normal
even comfortable you know what's even
more comforting not holding the bucket
but being inside the bucket of
dissonance while the bucket is in your
arms become the bucket it's a much more
convenient solution be one with the
bucket actually redesigning the game to
be less uncomfortable can you imagine
what a pain in the ass that would be yes
the bucket is the perfect solution
come on give it a try oh can i
i'm usually the one putting others into
a bucket but this is great thank you so
much
[Laughter]
can you feel it um the glow of comfort
even in the face of crushing despair
must already be sweeping through your
body and in fact can i say that i do
believe the bucket lends you an air of
charisma as well
i think that just holding it has made
you the slightest bit more attractive as
a person
the benefits of the bucket seem to go on
and on don't they all this and more
await you in the stanley parable too
you
are such a weirdo why did he laugh like
that
at least i have my bucket i don't have
my dog anymore but i have my bucket
my bucket and now i need to fill it with
another awards for most enjoyable bucket
in a video game
that really should be an award if it
isn't already
okay i'll be honest i haven't yet
decided on this one i think that in the
new version the office could use a bit
of decoration
balloons but i'm undecided on get well
someday and happy 10th birthday wait is
the game 12 years old
yeah it can't be 12 years old
what do you mean what what am i
i can't open door what do you want me to
do
oh here oh
what oh
[Music]
i think this one is better
i mean this one i don't really
understand what you mean yeah it should
be nine years old
what
twelve ah stephanie's
so weird this is more generic and i
think
everybody wants to get well someday
so let's go with that you know sometimes
when you solicit another person's
opinion it makes you realize that you
knew which one you actually really
wanted all along
happy 12th birthday step nice it is
no i am very sure that that's not the
one i wanted
ah
or actually
maybe i should have gone with no no i've
made my decision we're moving on you
made a wrong decision but i guess that's
okay sometimes you make wrong decisions
all right
this is free new easy achievement i
can't believe it's give me give me give
me give me kill me
give me
pull the lever receive your new
achievement no more steps it just works
get yours get yours now i want a warrant
here's something special you remember
that broken test achievement that got
left in the game on accident well i'm
developing a technology to simply give
you the achievement yes you see you'll
come to this lever and when you pull it
the achievement will be given to you
it's as simple as that
a cute robot let's go let's play
okay perhaps i should have clarified
this is technology that will exist right
now the achievement is still fully
broken i'm not a wizard stanley but i
guarantee it will be fixed in the sequel
[Music]
ravenous fans all over them you promised
gamers
we hear you yes that's
i don't know what to think of this guy
anymore what other exhibits haven't we
seen
[Music]
they didn't you know what's wrong with
brushes actually i think the jump circle
was a pretty good idea it would hang on
to that for the sequel
i still only have 13 no i think uh many
years have passed because we've been for
an apocalypse so
we can use up at least one
oh
gravity feels so strong in this game
i feel like i'm really really heavy
maybe the bucket made me heavier than
before
oh
infinite hole
infinite it's like a convention
it's like a convention like a
stanley powerball convention
oh
infinite hole
well
infinity
wa
not not a more hole oh wow such hole
it just keeps going damn wow i want to
test can i go
here's an idea that i'm truly fond of
it's never been done before in a video
game are you sure this is in fact a hole
that you can fall down forever that's
right
infinite
you can fall until the end of time is it
longer and deeper than the hole that i
fell for in minecraft
all right all right i i like i like me a
long long deep hole let's go
are you guys ready
free
you see isn't it wonderful yeah one of
my more ingenious concoctions if i do
see it it better not be ending anytime
soon since you've gotten to see the
infinite phone you can press the
teleport button to pop back up to the
top and we can continue onward no
no
no i don't mean to be a bummer but i do
recommend you use the teleport button to
go back to the top no maybe do it on the
sooner rather than later spectrum of
theme no
no
i like falling
free falling stanley i don't know how to
say this tactfully but it's possible
that i slightly exaggerated the infinite
nature of the hole
is it a very very deep hole to be
certain it is
it's an extremely deep pearl i don't
want anyone to say that it isn't an
astonishingly deep hole it is is it
infinite
well that sort of depends on your
definition of it is you lie to me again
from one perspective the infinite is
merely philosophical in nature it's more
of a
okay
good for you you found the bottom of the
hole you found me outstanding yes i will
expose you on the interwebs i will tell
everybody that the infinite hole was
eliminated fascinated by falling
what normal person actually wants to
fall infinitely i mean
that's what [\h__\h] don't you put this
on me maybe you're the problem huh
look things got a little heated
[Music]
no if that works for you no then go
ahead and press the teleport button to
warp up to the top of the hole and we
can move on i'll just be up here when
you're ready doesn't work for me no no
still it's exaggerating
i've had longer holes than that
no no no
no
every pause button
is a roman numeral too
wow
[Music]
amazing
meeting at 2 p.m
uh do i really have to
[Music]
hello
mind
right right i actually i can't play this
for much longer uh so let's go great
i'm very excited to show you even more
of my ideas for the sequel all right
i can't [\h__\h] around that much longer
please show me more
maybe there's a hole to go back up why
do i have to walk up you just started to
hole up there then i wouldn't have to go
down the stairs you know
[Music]
ain't nobody got time for that
is that whole ending
really you guys told me before this is
ending starting but it doesn't end
at least not properly oh for heaven
you see
i was right
the problem is you
the problem is that you like holes too
normal a normal person would have said
yep that's an infinite hole right there
goes on forever till the end of time
don't need to see it all but not you oh
no no no no you have a weird sword you
underestimate me
buddy did the hole seem even shorter to
you this time actually it would feel
like you spent a little less time in
there than you did before i mean
admittedly i didn't make an infinite
hole but i didn't think it was that not
infinite well i suppose you're making it
worse if you decide you've had enough of
the hole you can hit the teleport button
and come join me up above
well
this is what
whole life feels like
i'm positively thrilled
i really do have so much more to show
you and to talk about gosh how could i
have guessed you're back in the hole
this stuff to be coming up let's go
wow so disappointing man yes so shiny
i'm starting to become extremely certain
that the whole is not only you cannot
call it infinite at this point no no
definite
i suspect that i'm starting to hit the
point where it's no longer feasible to
call the whole infinitely deep exact
mother lacks overall standards for
accountability and marketing i think
that would be more satisfying to me too
yeah apparently i have no explanation
for the uncertain nature of the hole's
length here let's try something let's
pop back up to the top and we'll see if
it gets any shorter
well there it is
come to haunt me not only is the hole
not infinite but it's barely even the
thing is i can't jump so even if i jump
in there
i can't jump back up
that's so sad
i will be stuck forever if you don't
help me narendra son
how is this still appealing to you no i
know you're obsessed with holes but at
this depth i just can't see this sketch
not really a hole anymore who am i to
judge very disappointing
0 out of 10.
i think i need to write a bad steam
review see
you even have to help me by giving me
the g button once again
[Music]
just for this
this
ridiculous
shitty piece of hole
well that's so sad that's so sad
zero out of ten
is it gonna be filled up now
is the um
teleport button not working uh-huh
you sure would you mind creating the
jump circle right here perhaps
explanation it was working just a moment
ago try it again
still nothing ah well i suppose i
i suppose there is one thing i can do to
fix this
i'm out goodbye stanley you couldn't
bear to be away from the hole and now
you'll get more time with it than you
could ever have asked for it's a win for
everyone you get to be with the whole i
get to do literally anything else okay
take care stanley
i also have a bucket which is
kind of a hole like this one if you
compare it
uh
where's the sound
what is the sound
hello
mario
wow
my
[Music]
i'm gonna cry
i'm so moved
it was worth believing and waiting
change my perspective
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
what
change my perception
[Music]
wow it's a rhythm game
maybe
bravo game
baby
weapon game
[Music]
it's a rhythm game
baby baby yeah baby baby oh [\h__\h] we have
reached a level that i never thought
we'd reach before what is this are we in
hell or in an ocean
i don't know what's going on but i can
change myself
i am a robot that's okay hey oh [\h__\h]
that was loud i'm so sorry i didn't
expect that to happen even though it
happened so many times before i'm a
robot baby now i'm not where am i i'm
stuck i'm head over heels
for you
narrative son maybe i can change my
perception again
[Music]
i was grooving what did i do
stanley stanley
stanley oh good you're awake no it seems
you had sort of dozed off there what
you're doing lifting away into dreamland
what'd you do this was a perfect ending
because this hole is just so darn
fascinating that i want you to be wide
awake for every second of it you don't
want to miss a single moment so how
about if i just pop in from time to time
and wake you up to keep you really truly
focused on the home i mean as long as i
can stay you and i have many many years
here in this hole and i'm looking
forward to all of them okay shut up i
want to go back into my hole i'll be
back
rabbit hole let's go
a little
let's go
live
here we are go on try out some of the
new features
[Music]
that wasn't ending
it's so unsatisfying
because it doesn't tell me
the end
is it because the end is never the end
i can't stop if it doesn't tell me the
end
where are the endings that told me it's
the end
okay
well we got to know
who i am what i look like
i want to play more but i'm kind of um
time pressured i need to do things
i actually still need to uh record
something in vr
well that was fun
thank you everybody we might do a part
two i don't know do i have to save this
game
i also have to show something to you
guys um
let's go
to my office
it's all safe okay hello it's my office
let's go
i just wanted to show you
isn't this so perfect and cute
oh my god it's a small office
i just wanna say it's made by uh twitter
user velvet day uh with um um the four
is the a is a four
let me link it in the chat just in case
a small face
it's so cute and and even has small
small froggy quinoa
it's so good it's like the perfect
imitation of the style
yeah oh my god
oh my god i love it thank you for making
it it's so cute the craft paper project
yeah yeah yeah yeah
looks so cute
my uniform in the back the notes the
trees the the the all the all the
paperwork in front of me
ah the shelves
the logo
wow
amazing
yeah it's so cute
[Music]
straight island comic yeah it's so cute
um
hope you guys like it um i can't read
super cheats super chats today because i
need to
go
and hopefully record something uh
successfully i hope it goes well uh but
the game was fun
the next coming weeks will be
a very very very very um busy i just
want to say
the things that i said yesterday in the
members only stream partially
um haven't really resolved itself but
let's just say we're making our own
solution
and um
because of that
yeah in the next couple weeks it will be
very very very busy i need to
yeah i really learned all those koreas
uh but it's gonna be
a good result hopefully
wrong solution yeah we're doing it our
own way you will see what i mean when it
happens
[Music]
our own way
yes
[Music]
thank you guys for watching i need to go
i can't drag it out today i really can't
uh
tomorrow on my channel a german
class a quick quick dreaming class with
virus i'm gonna teach her some words
in german because she's gonna be with me
not really with me but kind of with me
at the dokomi a german convention if
you're going there i'll be there on
saturday i'll be performing there you
should know it by now iris is going to
be there on sunday yeah so
she doesn't know german
so i will try to teach her maybe some
useful words um
it will be on my channel so i'll see you
guys there and in german we say
au
eventually yeah
yes
bye-bye
have a nice evening good night
maybe part two sometime if you guys want
to see more
yes
bye-bye goodbye narrata-san
i won't miss you i've had enough of you
for today goodbye
i'll go and write a bad review on steam
now
[Music]
do
you