for
[Music]
welcome to
the today we'll be doing Collins and
what kind of Collins you ask we'll be
doing a Hol life quiz Callin so
basically I got to be fast because the
guests are coming in five more minutes
so let me explain what'll happen is that
the guest will call uh and then I'll
give them a question and if they get it
right then they get these exclusive Yago
pins for free yeah and then they can
just put it on their models whatnot Yi
[Music]
yeah oh thank God I got that that out
real
quick because it turns out there's
actually quite a lot of big enthusiasm
for
the and if you guys want to know just
how hard the questions are they're not
hard they're just like the things that
you can find in the hollow life website
or in their Twitter bio very simple
questions but you know we there's a lot
of Hol life talents in Hol life
sometimes even I can't keep up so these
are more of a refreshing your memory
kind of qu
[Music]
I'm totally going to fail this it's fine
we can feel together yeah I tried to
make this as how do I say it as beginner
friendly as possible because obviously
if I started saying stuffs like oh they
have a famous clip of them saying this
what time stamp it is like I think
that'll be way too difficult for
everyone so I just decided oh I'll just
make like an easy one you
[Music]
know yeah it's like general
knowledge yeah oh I'm glad I got that
out also a reminder since the guest and
the callers will be the one answering
ing the questions I would really
appreciate if you guys don't give them
answers or cheats that they could look
into the chat just like the ones that I
I already have a pinned comment as you
guys can
[Music]
see yeah and each person I'll be giving
them 10 seconds to answer after I read
out the questions I even have like a
timer already there's this
timer you can't hear
it can can you hear
it yeah it's a 10 seconds timer and I'll
probably turn off the bgm during the
timer yeah yeah yeah and if they get it
right I'll give them this if they get it
wrong they'll get this yeah did ital
sace
everything's going well great all righty
I can't wait he'll be the first caller I
told him that I'll be opening the call
at 335
[Music]
I can't turn them uh I can't turn them
up because the systems already like this
anyways yeah I don't actually know how
to do it
that how many questions are there I
prepared about
22 questions but I don't know how many
people will be coming today
it's going to be the
first yeah I'm curious too
[Music]
who's first I don't know because again
uh this was not planned unlike my
previous toes where I would make a
server this time I just told everyone
hey I'm doing a to so if you guys want
to get up and call me then do that yeah
on umy
[Music]
if we get no one we could make it a chat
quiz true we could just make it a chat
quiz if no one shows up that'll be so
sad
oh okay who Am I who are you from
ghost's comic this yay
how many lifetimes
ago so what should I do here cuz I don't
know anything about this
[Music]
uh JP JP okay okay
H hi
[Music]
hello uh
JP uh uh
[Music]
okay okay
yeah
hocan r o r r o b o o s i n y
of course
because yeah yeah yeah yeah
one more one more one
more
okay sorry Twitter
handle uh
[Music]
yeah
okay good job
yeah thank
[Music]
youy Comics the first one was J ghosty
Comics yeah
oh I think we have a second color
[Music]
already yeah yeah all right let's see
are they
[Music]
coming hello hello hello
hello hi oh I'm watching this is so cute
I love this uh I I I I had to do my
homework I had so I hope that I I don't
bring shame yeah no don't
worry so um introduce yourself to the
audience
please sure hi everybody my name is Miss
Lala I'm a 1950s Diner Waites
vtuber uh and I'm very excited to be uh
calling in and testing my Hol life
knowledge we're going to see how it
goes yeah Yi so to put you in briefly uh
I'll give you you can answer a Max of
two questions and if you get it right
you can get pins you can get two pins
Max like the one you're seeing right now
oh my god of of best girl oh my God what
an honor
yeah so um how difficult do you want
your uh quiz to
be ooh I'm going to say I I I'm I'm
going to say uh be be beginner entry
level that would be so nice oh okay then
I think I have the question for you
you'll have 10 seconds to answer okay
okay
okay then the question is what is her
first ever song kir senpai's first ever
song
go uh it's it's definitely uh Let It Go
from Frozen for
sure
really I took listen I'm taking a swing
in a minut at least I said a song name I
think I think I was pretty
close yeah well unfortunately that was
not the right answer but good guess it's
called I was so close look it it's it's
just a few letters off it's like the
same title
practically so close you're fine you're
fine okay um maybe something a little
bit more easier is there anyone in
hollow life that you watch other than
me uh I do love uh I love Gamers so uh
cor and and and those girls ah I think I
have the perfect question for you then
um next question uh your last chance
also by the way
oh yeah shami huki what is her OSI Mark
go I'm
sorry her oi Mark uh her ooshi Mark is
wait a minute wait a minute
I remember an animal I remember an
animal and I need an answer okay uh it
is uh it is
a a fox mm
and there's a
V and I want
to Corn wait no maybe maybe wait is it
cor is
it so sorry yes oh my God I didn't
expect
it congratulations you got one yeah hell
yeah hell yeah oh I got that I got best
girl I got a best girl hell yeah oh my
God best girl bad yeah yeah let's go
congratulations I'm so happy for you do
know your
Gamers I love Gamers was my introdu
that's how I got into vtu and was was
gamer the hollow live gamers branch and
so that was my Gateway into vtu and and
so I I I I mean they introduced me to
Hol live and then ultimately all of
vtube and so I love those girls so big
UPS wow I didn't know that big UPS Big
Ups
yippe Yi congrats I hope you enjoy your
bat thank you I will thank you for
having me Olly I hope I didn't bring
much shame I I'm glad I got one right
not at all have a great rest of your day
day thank you bye girl bye
bye okay two guests so far looking
good just a
[Music]
moment oh uhh we have our next Contender
ready hello hello hi hi so who's this uh
Hall live number one fan PE yuo slime
alien V we're here to absorb the
[Music]
zombie I'm sorry that was a little bit
late I was looking for your uh profile
picture it's okay it's it wasn't it was
an a awkward horn at least it wasn't
a so it's
fine yeah so Pia are how confident are
you in getting these uh answers right
gosh I want to say I want to say that
I'm decently confident but then I I
don't know I you know yeah you know what
I think I think I could answer any
question for sure yeah I'm a master yeah
mhm hit me so okay then I think I have
the perfect question for you do you want
to go for two rounds or one round or uh
you know uh let's see let's see how the
first round goes okay then I'll get the
first question ready are you ready I'm
ready are you uh watching the uh stream
by the way no oh okay and then should I
be watching the stream no I'll just read
out the questions for you all right
first question what is Elizabeth's
Twitter handle go oh Elizabeth Twitter
handle M I mean I know everybody's
calling their herb so like their Twitter
handle mhm I'm guessing it would be herb
like it would have herb herb herb with
their last name herb blood blood flame
flame can you spell that out for me okay
e RB for the Elizabeth part or sorry e r
for the Elizabeth part b l l o d and
then flame f l a m
e you got it
right let's go I BW my own hor W you
have your own horns
cool so there agle pin for you nice J
heck
yeah yeah you want to go for another one
yes this one's going to be a little hard
but I think you can do it yeah okay okay
so next question um what is takan Lou's
character color go oh okay so I know
that her hair is like pinkish
mauvish but there's so many pink Chara
is it like is it like kind of like an
off color pink an off color how do you
describe an off color pink like your
hair like a plum color would it be like
Plum ah well
unfortunately oh no it's actually
burgundy isn't that what off colored
Plum is wait that's an off colored Plum
I don't know like isn't a plum like kind
of like a like a weird like a dark pink
like a really dark pink oh oh if if
that's what you meant then yeah
yay I feel like I cheated a little bit
on that one no no it's okay well it's a
very hard question we had to be specific
but I just didn't get it so well cuz the
only reason I would have I would have
just said pink but I remember that
coyotes in that generation so there's no
way she was straight pink she had to be
like a darker pink wow you're you know
your
stuff well I
try that's so cool well thank you for
coming do you have anything you want to
say before you take your leave um I
played your dating Sim and and it gave
me it gave me all the feels and I would
eat your dirt Bento any
day thank you you're making me
BL ay thank you for having me on olly
and thank you for coming by have a great
rest of your day pey byebye you
[Music]
byebye oh next car so quick hello hello
hello hello good morning good morning M
yourself hi my name is JX Ora um Ollie
is really cool H let's go let me look
for your Prof Victor real quick y
what time is it for you right now even
that it's not even that late it's like
well it's not early it's just not it's
not late it's like almost 10:00 a.m.
it's just I'm epe today a very EP out
guys oh somebody said that they were
just watching clips of you before this
oh thank you I hope they were good
Clips yeah so um Aura how confident are
you with the Holo quiz
um semicon like the thing is I I know
like uh I don't know really no Twitter
handles cuz I looking at the other
questions I don't really know Twitter
handles but like I I I know maybe colors
and stuff more I feel colors but also
some trip some trip people up right some
are not even you look at them you're
like wait is that color like for M
sometimes I wonder is it brown or is it
green you know cuz it depends on the pen
light as well you know
sometimes the color changes for the pen
lights and stuff so yeah that's true
that's true uh not every penl have like
the same Oshi color yeah exactly so I
don't know we'll just see how it goes um
I really would like a pin though so you
have to be you have to be easy on my
sleepy brain okay it though brain I'll
give you something that I think this
question is perfect for you since you're
still
sleepy okay okay so
Ready or Not the first question is
babang I want you to spell her name m
abis
Gard Moko abis Gard yeah spell her name
for me okay sure um it's not F waa cuz
and she's not a
Chihuahua um uh it's m
o for the mot M and for her last name uh
a mhm b m y
m
s
mhm s
mhm oh and then g a r
d well more looks like you got that
correct yep thank you I'm so excited to
receive my car thank you ollie yeah you
get a pen would you like another
question or would that be
a I um I'll go for another one sure okay
then um let's see what's a good one
since you're not oh this one might be a
little bit difficult but would you be
okay sure I mean I already got a pen so
oh okay then next question hollow life
ID by the way oh Ana is an ancient
weapon but what type of weapon is she in
Indonesian it isn't she a wait would you
is she a sword yeah but there's the name
for it the name for the sword uh I don't
know an Indonesian like an actual oh AR
arm um I don't know Indonesian I'm
sorry do you have any
guesses is the word in in
Indonesian yeah it's a name of a word in
Indonesian um
um I I don't know I'm sorry that's okay
that's fine well the answer is goodies
she's got oh yeah yes I remember now I
was think for some reason I thought it I
was thinking it started with a K but I
didn't know what
ah I see I see but well you were close
it did start with the
K yeah just like Ki yeah but I think you
did will you got one
yoin I'm going to wear it with
pride I hope uh you uh you have a lovely
morning uh than you yeah thank you for
coming by the way thank you for having
me and I just want to say you're very
lovely and cute and I love you I love
you
too not on the the
stream save it for private okay I go now
good luck with the rest of the TSU thank
you
miies
byebye wow people actually came we have
four four
people four people already I'm so
happy I hope that wasn't too hard but I
think the Ana question was a little bit
hard maybe I was going a little bit too
hard on
or let me make them just a little bit
smaller just in case we have uh more
[Music]
colors hello
hello hello hello so who hello my love
hi darling um this is Umi kyoku I'm I'm
a silly yandere whale shark um here to
to keep you company hello my
[Music]
love hi baby hi oh Ora is still in the
chat hi thank you for coming by the way
Aura so
Ora M were you watching the whole
time I I did watch I was watching yes I
was um and then I closed it because I
didn't want to I didn't want to be a
cheater so it's always like okay I don't
want to I'm not I'm not going to like
look at chat or anything so I've been
watching I have been soaking it in
actually I even I even because my
current profile picture on Twitter is so
cursed I I even like made a profile
picture to give to you in case you
needed to find one I was like oh I'm
ready I'm ready so yeah you see um I
don't think I can do your profile
picture due to copyrights and whatnot so
um I had to use like a different for you
yeah yeah no it's okay if that's just
like my my um my tired form after after
after a birthday uh so you know after a
long stream so you know it's okay it is
okay that you didn't show that form I'd
rather you show me on my
bed and I heard you've been studying for
the
quiz yes I have I've been I uh what's it
called I was scouring the little Hol
life website I watched a video so you
know let's let's hope that um that I can
I can kick some of that knowledge into
gear I like to think that I I already
know a decent amount of um things about
Hol live but like there are some
obviously there's a lot to take in so
it's like you know what we'll find out
we'll find out how much I actually know
In This Moment yeah so
mhm how hard do you want it to be by the
way
[Music]
um I don't know uh I don't know what it
I don't know what a difficult question
looks like really so um we can maybe we
can try easy okay first easy first let's
see oh okay I think I have an easy
question for you okay baby hit me with
it okay so first question for
I wait which one was it this
one uh B bam in Hall life inesia uh in
Hall of Indonesia every generation have
a unit name what was the unit name for
hollow life Indonesia first
generation timer Starts Now wait wait
can you re can you say the question for
so what is you are you saying like what
is the name of like the F the first gen
yeah the the unit for the first gen
um oh shoot uh I'll start the timer
again okay so I would so the first gen
for
Indonesia is oh shoot I don't know
this it's fine maybe maybe that was a
little bit too hard um the answer is
area 15
oh okay NAU okay oh wait no I did know
that funnily enough because I was like
wait a second I kept wanting to say Holo
and I was like wait no that's you
um it's okay it's fine it's fine you're
good it's okay it's okay but do do you
want something a lot more easier I could
find something easier no no no I keep
trying okay trying let's see oh okay I
found a quite easy one I feel
okay um next question last chance to get
the Yago
pin uh
uh what does
[Music]
m call her
fans m is in
it
uh so so her fans are NEOS and then her
um her membership
is like uh isn't it like she also has a
different name for her membership it's
like n n prod like n production or
something
oh and but like it like her her fans are
called necos yeah my yeah I think yeah I
locked that in NEOS yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah oh wait I don't is that is
that true because oh she got it okay you
got
[Music]
it yeah you see the the the I took this
from the website and they just showed
like husband or
wife oh okay okay I yeah but you know uh
somebody said oh she got it turn I'm
like oh oh maybe that's what they're
called I don't
know I love that we we were both like
wait wait is which what yes to all of it
sure all of
them yeahi said she's also a husband oh
oh
you know what it all counts so it counts
you
[Applause]
get that's that's so funny I'm going to
wear this the next time I I I the next
time I stream I'm going to put this on
me and I'll be like guess what I got to
do this is so cute yeah what yeah
actually I didn't even know I I only
knew cuz Chad said oh yeah she got it
right
oh
okay that that's how you know you know
what even the quiz Master can always
learn something new every day um you
know so chat we you know what I think of
it as today we are all winners we're all
winners we're all winners we all of
H
exactly we all love Hol live and we all
we all just want want to to be happy
with wonderful music and wonderful
people
yeah thank you for
coming of course of course I took a
little nap so that way I could be Smiley
and and make sure I can
go just for you thank you de of course
of course I love you very much thank you
for for asking me to come on for a
little bit it's lovely to hear your
voice my pleasure is there anything else
you'd like to say before you take your
leave
M no just that I love you and I'm very
grateful for you and I think you're
awesome I love you too thank you for
coming of course I'm going to head back
to sleep now so have a wonderful rest of
your stream bye chat bye babes bye bye
bye and that has been Ki IU people I
can't believe she got the n one right
because you know I literally did not
[Music]
know see even I don't know what the what
everything
is that was impressive that was
impressive wait let me give
a let me make be a moderator and we have
our next
caller hello hello hello hi hello hi hi
hi hi want to introduce yourself real
[Music]
quick
Mo
hello I'm always confused like what name
should I call you is it alpha or is it
vaa I know it's so confusing please
everyone call me Alpha oh see the alpha
guys
yes yeah hello hello welcome have you
been watching the stream I have oh okay
so I was like I'm a hollow life fan I
can get these questions right and then I
saw your questions I was like oh
oh yeah they're they're actually very
trivial but you know sometimes we'd
forget we do we do it's in the back of
our minds we just do you know we forget
that's all is there a certain branch
that they're very confident in very very
I'm losing confidence um maybe maybe Ian
maybe Ian but uh maybe we can start with
like an easy question oh okay then since
uh Ian okay I got it I got you a
question just a moment let me I hope
it's easy it's easy I promise uhhuh all
right are you
ready yes as ready as I can be all right
so your question is what is iris's
Twitter
handle timer Twitter
handle Twitter handle
mhm
Iris you got to give me an
answer um Iris uncore Hol
livean you were close you were close no
underscore Iris Hol live again it was
actually Iris
Ian yeah you were very close oh no yeah
I was like is Hol live in there no she
has a different uh handle since you know
iris is taken everywhere that's right
that's right ooh trick question those
Twitter handles are hard
yeah this is actually the last question
for the Twitter handles by the way
so is there let's see how good are you
with
debut
order or birthdays or do you want
something that's a fan name or maybe
greetings
maybe debut order has the highest chance
of me answering it maybe correctly maybe
correctly right then this will be um
okay maybe that's too hard um
uhoh what about I I think you can get
this one right this is pretty easy
uh-huh okay it's it's a birthday
question birthday but it's very easy I
promise you
the question
being when is yuzuki too sensei's
birthday timer Starts Now was it
Valentine's day was it February
14th or am I
wrong well no
Alpha I have to say your answer is
correct yes so you get a Yago pin yay I
got a pen you got me
thank you for the best girl
[Music]
P got it right me too oh my heart is
beating so
fast yeah is there anything you'd like
to say before you take your leave oh not
anything in particular but I'm so happy
I got to talk to you again and thank you
so much for inviting me it was fun I'm
definitely going to be watching
everybody else's questions as well ooh
fun
thank you but have fun I'll be looking
forward to your announcement yeah it's
soon soon
soon we love you ollie I love you too
ala have a great rest of your day thank
you thank
you Al is Alpha
people such a sweeth art isn't she what
announcement there will be an announce
announcement at the
end okay and we have our next caller
ready as well I'm so happy so many
people are coming to
theti
hello good my mic is working I think
your mic's working perfectly let's
go let me just adjust your volumes real
quick
sorry okay sorry I'm always
quiet so yeah would you like to
introduce yourself to everyone M hello
I'm a V fan I I very much Thrive at
hours I should not be awake so this is
peak time a day for me let's go let's
go I I I I don't have your profile
pictor give me one second I'm so
sorry no that's okay I should have sent
something I'm just like my brain it's a
time of day where I feel very awake but
everything I do says otherwise if that
makes sense no no no no you're you're
great oh what a lovely profile picture
it's new I just got the drawing a few
days ago oh yeah it's really nice well
then um before we get into the quiz
here's the question how confident are
you with the quiz I'm extremely super
very very confident that I'm going to
get it completely
wrong would you like an easy one
sure I I'll probably still get it wrong
I'm going to be real I have so much like
random weird knowledge but then anytime
I need to use it in my entire brain
short circuits and I don't know anything
I I feel that so I feel that so hard all
right well here here's an I'll give you
an easy question then to start
off okay so oh oop oops oop nope that's
not the question
uh uh here you go right so your question
is what does ym d stand
for ah my I actually don't know my
entire brain is saying yes my death but
I don't know if that's right oh you
you're so close Oh no just a little
bit am no it's not yes but my brain gave
up it's it's yeah wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait love Plus her name is
like L plus Darkness so is it too late
to change my answer you you can change
your answer because you haven't locked
in yes my dark yes yes my darkness not
death I went a little too
dark and that is correct let's go let's
go you got
it I did not think I would I'm so I'm so
proud this I'm I'm sure my mom will be
so proud of me tomorrow yeah you got
yourself a Yago pin yeah best girl girl
yeah would you like to have another
attempt in more
yoins sure I'm feeling slightly slightly
less confident that I'll get it wrong
now slightly more confident that maybe
I'll get it
right all right then H let's see what's
would you how hard do you want it to be
because the ones that we have left are
pretty
hard H hit me I'll try it let's go how
about oh okay how about this
one what is to
Yuma's greeting catch phas her
I I'm your starts now I've seen oh no
I've seen stuff of TOA I've seen some
like clips and stuff but I've never
caught the beginning of a stream oh God
uh I'm just going to make an absolutely
random guess hi it's just
hi it's technically probably not wrong
just maybe there's more to it hey what
well Tech well it's it's 10% right I
guess
hi it's okay in my heart it it carries
the meaning of hi it's just a different
way of saying yeah well you're right
technically but the the the corrector
answer is
going ah okay that makes sense I figured
it was probably some sort of like
variation that was that was like
specific to her so I was just like the
most generic
answer
yeah but hey you got yourself a Yago
pencil yeah I am satisfied yeah
congratulations on your Yago them thank
you and big big hype for the
announcement thank you I'm I'm preparing
a lot for
it so exciting so before you leave is
there anything you'd like to
say I'm just really excited for the
announcement honestly like I'm sitting
here the whole time being like
woo so I'm just really excited for it I
I'm probably going to have to check the
Vlog but as soon as I wake up I will
come and check it I just got to see what
it is right it's super early for you
isn't
it or it's depending on your definition
it's it's early late it's it's it's a
time but I'm usually awake this time
anyway so it's fine okay
well yeah thank you for coming again I
hope you have a lovely rest of your day
you as well good luck with the game show
thank you bye
P let's see 1 2 3 4 5 6 seven seven
people most of them are a girlies I
wonder if we'll be getting any uh mail
callar soon it'll be uh that's something
that I'm looking forward to
[Music]
thank you bomb yeah oh oh speak of the
devil mus M hey yo what
[Laughter]
up hello oh long time Noy o long time no
introduce yourself to everyone hello
guys my name is GM aroma
I'm a a a blue blue hair guy yeah he's
that VR CH guy guys let's go let's
go and the CEO of the blue jump B trer
company let's go let's go he's a CEO
guys like a real CEO wait you you
actually give me the the Yago bad if I
correct well well it's a it's a it's PNG
okay okay okay okay okay definitely okay
yeah it's hard
shipping
see okay okay okay got it got it got it
you said you've been watching the stream
um what do you think of the question so
far I mean it's kind of easy I think
it's easy oh you think it's I I know I
know 99% know about the Holo live
okay okay you 99% no yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay then I'll give you a really
easy one then just for you wait what
what you want the you want the difficult
one I
mean okay it's it's no matter of about
like easy or difficult yeah you know I'm
yeah yeah here's your first question I
hope you get it right because you only
have 10 seconds to think okay got it
okay let's go your question is how tall
is Kaku timer
go
hey uh be um beu to
40 401 40
cm for only
40 yeah
yeah def okay 43 43 cm definely
correct I know it I I knew
it oh this she look so short you know
listen you got the 40 right it's just
that it's not
enough what it's
140 what you almost got it
yeah but but it's so close it's just one
number one just you know yeah you you
threw the 100 cm away a [\h__\h] I'm so
close oh my God that was actually really
close good
job ah got it got it got it okay do I
have a more chance yeah you have one
more chance I'll give you one more chany
okay okay got it got it all right all
right uh well then I'll give you an
easier one okay this one's very easy I'm
sure you would
know your question
is okay I'm ready P senpai's fan base
name timer
start
oh
uhi
is uh you're
close pretty warm
huh what's her fan
name
um
hun wait
[Music]
what it's wrong it's
wrong you you were actually closed the
first
time oh my God no
Sagi
oh yeah a [\h__\h] I'm so close oh my God oh
my God so close yeah but listen um I
kind of feel bad because every single
guest that have come here they at least
get one Yago
pin what you you really you're the first
one to actually get two questions around
how
what is every
every oh my god there no no no more Yago
batch no more Yago pictures listen since
you're a very special friend of mine
Moon I'll give you one more chance
okay I'll give you one more chance than
I'll give you a question that I've
already
shown and let's see if you remember the
answer
okay is that that easy okay very easy
make it really easy for you so this is
your last last
chance okay I'm
ready what
[Music]
isk you've collabed with
her dog no kit in is and
corn so what's what's your
answer kid then
corn you got it
right let's
go I'm so
[Music]
glad I'm I'm Sweat Right now I'm so glad
that you got that right well let's go
thank you so much you're welcome and I
want this one do you want this one the
the pink
one oh I want a pink one oh you want the
pink one you don't want the yellow one
got it let me just delete that real
quick yeah and thank you so much oh my
God you're welcome is there anything say
on your way
out
um
uh
BBA and he just left he just left like
[Music]
that there he goes into the
Oblivion
yeah so
um MOA
people yeah and I think we have our next
caller but I'm not sure if they're
online right
now so such base Moon I know we love
that guy we all love moon in this
household at least he was confident he
was very
[Music]
confident let's
see there's a few people who uh DM me
and they're like oh can I go but oh okay
here we
[Music]
go we have our next caller hello
hello happy non birthday yay it's not my
birthday
CH hello Kyla
DC Kyla I'm so happy you came
[Music]
y let's
go okay
[Music]
let's go
okay let's
go Luna when is memory Luna's birthday
timer Starts
Now random
random
foree
[Laughter]
spee okay okay
let's
[Music]
Go's go
okay
y
[Applause]
[Music]
let's
go thank you
than
uh you're doing amazing you're doing
great I'm so proud of being your co-
high thank you for having me here thank
you thank
you thank you by byebye
[Music]
oh next
color hello hello
hello mind introducing yourself all
righty all righty con Nana my name is
nanaia I am a song of the Galaxy
reincarnated to V and V singer and I am
also miss ol's beloved she is my wife I
love her so
much welcome to
this you okay doing know right yeah I'm
having so much fun giving everybody pins
and whatnot I'm glad I'm
glad yeah so you know being the crazy uh
Hol fan that you are um how confident
are you with the quiz listen I am so
confident when it comes to some specific
people but then for like some other
people um Maybe not maybe
not well uh then uh is it what branch
are you most confident
[Music]
in what branch am I most confident in
I'm most confident in like specific
people that I like of course you being
one of
them
stop
stop well then H do you want it to be
hard or do you like
[Music]
Kai yes I do okay cool then I have the
perfect question for you
then I was thinking when I could
actually get this one out because it's
actually pretty
turkey oh
oh wait I suddenly feel so much
pressure I think you got it though I
think you got it the
bag okay okay yeah just hit me hit me
baby hit me all right here's your first
question Nana bang what is
toas and Aman's unit
name Jesus Christ oh
do I have a timer is there a timer wait
wait wait I know this I know this I know
this it's a it's a angel and a demon so
so so it is was it t huh
t wait the teni being an Angel and the
Gori
being oh or maybe it's
AK wait
wait that's kind of rude
wait my it's it it you got it wrong
though see with it it yeah so um the
correct answer is actually
Oro yeah because they're uh they're
polar opposite of each
other K will remember this no no she's
not watching you're cool you're
fine don't wor one yeah it's it's it's
fine I knew that yeah yeah oio yeah I
knew that sorry I was testing you I was
I was actually also testing you
yeah okay well
then uh have you oh you're you're fun
you're cool you're
Gucci then um have you been watching the
stream actually like from the start no I
haven't I was about to go take a bath
and then I was
like oh that's great that's that's
that's super great because that means I
can reuse some
questions okay okay okay so this is
going to be your uh last chance to get a
Yago pin mhm are you you ready yes so
your last question is what is na moner
putter handle
[Music]
go like just
Nat it should be it should be right no
underscores no dots no nothing no I
don't remember I don't remember seeing
any dots or like underscores no are you
sure it's not matu
Nat yeah that was my other thought but
for now a Lo with
Nat well nana I have to say that you got
the question absolutely
right so that means you get a Yago pin
si si you I totally knew that I totally
knew that yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
[Music]
you you didn't fall into my gas lighting
good
job I mean you can gas me any
[Music]
day like you can tell me that it's I was
like you're
so oh no you're you're a you're a piece
for sure
like one
y yay yay yay yay yay yay good job so
before you leave is there anything you'd
like to announce
everyone
hey uh I'm planning a lot of fun
exciting summer events so please stay on
the lookout and also I want you guys to
tell Miss Ollie that she is very cute
and that she's very hardworking and that
she deserves all the head pets in the
world okay I need all of you guys to say
all the cute all cute all cute okay all
of you guys do that spam that and turn
right now okay okay doesn't M she say
all cute all cute
cute so so so thank you
Nana of course I'm so happy thank you so
much for inviting me dude I was sweating
I was like I'm so ready I'm so ready man
you're you're you're welcome and thank
you for coming no of course I was I I'm
always so happy to talk to you yipp y
very cute very Demir very elegant yes oh
my God yes the way you invited me to
this toachi very demure very elegant
very cuty see how she puts everyone's
profile pictures in line very demure
very mindful very mindful see how she
made these badges very demure very
elegant very cuty see how there's a
yellow one see how there's a pink one
very considerate very
demure thank going it's fine I'll see
you around Nana I'll see you around all
time byebye love you
she's such a joy to have I love Nana so
[Music]
much all right just a
moment
[Music]
okay
okay all right with the wet kiss I'm
sorry I I can't hold myself back in
front of my wives I just love them so
much than you if only Maran comes as a
guest how do I explain the questions I'm
so glad there hasn't been a single Dy
actually cuz uh you know I I don't know
how to actually tell them oh you got it
wrong like that that would be a punch in
the gut no yeah so I'm glad but we have
our next call ready
hello
hello hello
hello hi who am I speaking
with how are you good morning good
afternoon good day human my name is
Human M from face Conn gen to face Alias
hello thank you for inviting
me yay have you have you been watching
the Stream yeah I've had you stream on
the side law I've been working on like
my um own work and stuff so honestly
hearing some of these questions I was
like oh crap wait Chad am I
cooked you'll you'll be fine you'll be
how confident are you anyways I mean
I've been watching vtubers like all
since
2020 so I think I got a pretty good shot
honestly I'll try I'll try my best I'll
try of us oh 2020 then I got a 2020
question for you okay okay it's though
um do you watch Hol life Indonesia
often uh not too often because I don't
speak Indonesian but um I keep up with
your activities like music releases and
on social media and stuff oh stream
Jolly Jolly by the way thank
you well without further Ado here's your
question unfor fortunately I'm giving
you tricky
one okay okay okay who debuted six in
Hollow live Indonesia timer go uh okay
so first was the first Area 51 and then
it was uh your gen right
so uh it's you onion R I'm going to say
I'm going to say Raina I'm going to say
rain are you sure it's rain are you sure
oh no don't try to Gaslight me I'm so
easy to
Gaslight so are you locking
in I am I am locked the freak in I am
locking
in well R you are
correct it is raining she's m of allive
Indonesia yeah cuz I remember your gen
was uh like hold on remember you guys de
view at the end of 2020 I think so yeah
I watched your deuts it was really nice
thank
you so you got one Yago pin but do you
want to keep going wait hold on is this
is this a conflict of interest am I
going to get fired if I put on the if I
put on the Yago
pin you know you know that's that that's
for you and manag that's between me and
my Manan
okay yeah would you like a n
question sure um I I'll do my best I'll
do my best has anyone gotten two
questions right yet yeah we have pei and
Kyla I believe oh okay well Kyla is kind
of a given but Yi good job yeah p is so
intellectual about H life oh that slime
holds so much information mhm so are you
ready for your next question or are you
good with your Yago pin oh oh I want I
want another I'm going all in baby
gotcha well your next question
is uh what
isi greeting catch phase timer start now
oh god this is my Senpai oi
uh I'm not you know what I'm going to
I'm going to go the same um similar
answer with the previous person who just
said
hi
hi I know I know she says
like but that's not that's not her
introduction is it no that's not her
greeting unfortunately okay you know
actually I'm going to go something
different from the previous person you
know just to switch things up cuz like
you never know they might they that
that's how that's how they get you right
they they ask you a question you think
you know the answer it's just it's just
going to be hi but I'm going to switch
it up on them I'm going to say
bye I think her intro catch is
bye well
um you tried your best yeah I I try like
thank you for doing it for the sake of
entertainment yeah you know what you
know it's for the bit it's for the bit
yeah it's
com ah
have you heard of it I think I have I
never really watched uh L of it I mostly
watched um my okay so my my oi is from
um hell so I mostly watch and I keep up
with music mostly um
yeah oh is there anything else you want
to say no no no no no I'm going I'm good
no no no I I was actually waiting for
like a continuation I'm so sorry uh oh
it's it's okay it's okay you're
good do you have any announcements maybe
that you'd like to share before you
go um everybody go play all's game is
super cute um also uh stream stream
Jolly Jolly stream all music and um look
forward to the announcement later I
don't know what it is but look forward
to it look forward to the announcement
y thank you
R thank you for coming
yeah thank you for having me I got I got
I got to run now I got I got have dinner
okay have a lovely dinner bye me yeah
thank
you what a cute little lady I
love uh let me just um let's see we
still have some colors don't worry and
the announcement is in 15 minutes so
we'll we'll we'll we're on track we're
fine
this
who Yago Yago yeah everybody gets a pen
I'm making sure that nobody leaves
empty-handed I'll give them like
questions that have oh next
caller hello
[Music]
hi welcome to the
stream thank you for having me and thank
you for
coming yeah I mean of course I'm kind of
drowning with assignments all of a
sudden but I had to make time for you
you're you're such a lovely person I I I
love you so much because you know I got
to be honest with you you're the second
Hall life member to come
the first one was Kyla so I'm really
glad you
came oh I mean like you know it's like
everyone's busy and everything but you
know I wanted to make time for you cuz
yeah thank
[Music]
you well um so I'm having a Hol life
quiz uh you you'll have 10 seconds to
think and then you'll have to answer how
confident are you
not at
all damn honest
though he's being honest C thank you I
uh you know if there's one good quality
of mine it's
honesty you're you're great you're Gucci
anyways I have a question ready for you
I think it's an easy one so okay I'm not
ready let's go
well um Ready or Not here's your
question who debuted first and the unit
NE timer
starts it's the fifth 10 of
JP
oh
lamb
simp mom
[Music]
are you sure you're not going to answer
NIS and by her name is in the it's first
in the
unit oh oh may maybe actually you know
actually maybe then they
P so who are you locking in
with well I mean like uh I don't know I
I mean like honestly like at this time
of the hour I can't really trust my
brain but usually when I
say like you know I think I'm wrong and
then I go with a second choice and then
my second choice is wrong and it turns
out that my first one is right most of
the time so I don't really know so like
should I go with the first one but I
feel like the first one's wrong now that
you say that and maybe you're giving me
a hint so that you know I don't mess up
especially since it's about my Senpai so
I mean our Senpai so you know like I
don't really know
um uh I'll give you an extra 10 seconds
here okay
okay uh uh uh ly Senpai L Me Senpai yeah
you're going with that yeah cuz it would
it landed on the left side well I'm very
sorry crony but you are absolutely
correct
oh oh my god oh I'm so
scared you got yourself a Yago
pin
yay oh my God you nearly let me gasl you
I mean I'm pretty good with getting gas
late so you are very
convincing well oh my God looks like a
bobble hand yeah you can have another go
and get another pin if you want what do
you say if I ask for another pen and
then I lose that one do I lose all my
pins no you still can keep your uh
previous
pin should I leave while people still
think that I'm
smart or should I just ruin it all I
don't know what do you think I'm kind of
in decisive right now I'm I don't know I
I feel like you should well wait what
what was your first decision again I I
don't really know what my okay my first
decision I didn't make a decision I gave
options
uh okay I guess I'll have to go for
another one yay
yippe yippe
do okay since it's going to be your
second question I'll let you choose do
you want a jpen or ID
question why are you
laughing see if I say JP and then I get
the Senpai wrong then I'm going to be in
deep trouble and then if I'm confident
and be like oh maybe if I choose someone
from you know arbre
and then I get that wrong then how am I
going to ever going to live it down then
I won't be able to go to sleep I mean I
can't go to sleep anyway but I would
have a harder time going to sleep and
then if I choose ID you know where
you're there and then if I mess up
especially if it's something that's
related to you then how am I ever going
to live it down oh she she's going
through it
guys oh what am I what am I supposed to
do can you choose can you help me please
okay I'll I feel like I'm lose either
way I'll give you an easy one then this
one I've already given to one of the
guest so you know if they can do it you
can
too no pressure by the way that's so
much pressure thank you I'll try all
right so spelling me time I want you to
spell a Moo's full name
go Moco mhm okay m o c o c o a b y s s g
a r
d are you sure that the only thing
that's double is the
S what are you sure that she only has
double
s abiskar
[Laughter]
you are
correct okay oh don't do
that I'm so sorry you're just so cute
right now I can't I can't help but bully
you I'm going through it right
now you did it you got two pins thank
you thank you so much for being so kind
you're welcome and thank you for being
so kind to stoping by yeah yeah no of
course everyone you know what everyone
has been saying go check out all these
songs Jolly Jolly and stay tuned for
what she has to announce by the end of
the stream yeah stay tuned don't leave a
thank
you all right all right so I'm going to
go back to my homework then yeah I um
wish the best of luck with your
homework yeah me
too yeah good luck
yeah and godp speed for what I don't
really know I'm really going thr it
right
now
bye
[Music]
me oh I love bullying her oh
she's hanging in there guys let's wish
her the best of luck because like she
said she's really going through
it yeah you bul listen I got to I got to
trick the hollow life members a little
bit because you know they're hollow life
members CR really needs to get some help
I know you also need to get some help
you're doing homework too Kyla but
thanks for coming by the
way yeah we're so close to uh 5:00 p.m.
the uh announcement should be coming
[Music]
soon a thank you for coming crony love
you good
luck yeah let's go announcement we have
one more person before the announcement
so they'll be the closing quiz person I
think let me call
him hello hi hi welcome to the Hol life
quiz I
am I think
ready well can you introduce yourself to
everyone here yeah hi my name is
porcelain made I'm a man who died and
got my soul trapped inside the body of a
doll yoee Soul trapped in a doll oh
boy so you might be the last person
before the announcement Joel oh excited
announcement time yeah so um have you
been watching the stream I have been in
and out with my dad watching the stream
he thought I was watching
Naruto ah yes Nar with his hollow life
quiz
Jitsu mhm that's what we're all waiting
for my knowledge is so bad on this well
uh you know um listen I got to be honest
with you the last questions that I have
they're pretty hard so do you want me to
like read out
some easier questions or well well I
don't think it it I don't think the
concept of easy matters to me because
what do I know well I know who I know
who do I know I don't
know
well it's like 0% knowledge 100%
confidence and it's slowly dwindling
like a blind man in the
desert you'll be fine Joel you'll be
fine well I'll give you the freedom of
choice do you want jpan or
[Music]
ID I you know what uh I'll take an Ian
question for an Ian question okay let's
see
oh you'll be fine okay it's okay I speak
English I should get this right right
yeah yeah definitely so that's what that
means yeah and you have two two guesses
anyway so like um two guesses two
questions that you'll be answering
anyway so you'll be fine okay yeah so
first
question how tall is Kiki beu timer
Starts Now
oh bbby uh uh they're short do I have to
answer this in American or in other you
can answer in CET or in feet you're good
they're like
410 are are you sure they 410 you're
really close do that mean are you
allowed to say that I got to tell you
it's very
close just say
in uh 49
are you locking in are you gaslighting
me listen Joel with with a desperation
that you have in your voice I'm trying
to help you right
now okay wait wait hold on
four
48 are you locking in
47 is that your final answer oh God it
was I going lower instead of higher
I 47 lock locking in 47 well Joel you
are correct oh let's go it's 4T 7.1 in
but you know we don't count the one it's
basically you got it right basically
yeah what were you worried about I got
that easily there was no issues at all I
told you 100% confidence it's going back
up I'm like the factual knowledge is
going up too I'm so glad well you have
like another go for like another
question for another another Yago pin do
you want to go for it or is this like
double or nothing do I lose something
from this no you don't lose anything you
can keep your pin that you just got well
I lose my pride from that but yeah let's
let's go another one uh do you want a JP
or ID because I feel like another Ian
would be too easy okay uh give me id I
know I know Oli that should be fine yeah
all right well oh this is actually a
recent question that I gave to someone
else um um wait where is it let me look
for it real quick there's way too many
here um while you look for it can you
like like maybe text me the answer like
a little bit no so next question okay
that's cool that's fine yeah that's okay
who debuted six in Hall life Indonesia
so we have nine members in Hall life
Indonesia who's the sixth person to
debute I'm so mad I literally was there
I was watching when you and gave this
question I don't remember who it
was
um
uh is
it I I'm going to guess one of the only
other H life is it the the the sword the
sword one the weapon one is it them is
it them the one with the weapon the
sword like Excalibur they're cool you
you you have them in like your brain
sometimes is that them or is that a
different
person so so you think it's the the
sword is that is that it well maybe un
fortunately no it is
[Music]
not it was she's the fifth one actually
so you were close the sixth one was the
Pea foul lady was I actually close you
were close U the the sword was the fifth
one so you know my Pride's not totally
shattered yeah that was a close one that
was a close one
congratulations you still can keep your
Yago pin it's all good you're not going
to like take it away from me right no no
you're fine you're
gucy okay thank God that wasn't that bad
man I you know what 100% confidence yeah
you got it yippee yippe so before we go
is there anything you'd like to
announce well I think it's it you know I
think the only thing I should announce
is that Ali's about to announce
something and that's more important n
about you you're going to announce
something I have no idea what you're
announcing please let it be really cool
and hype and happy I will well thank you
so much Jo for coming by thank you for
inviting me I'm going to go pass out
okay have a lovely pass good night bye
congratulations thank
you all right and that people is our
last caller for today we're actually on
time
so
everybody this is a very exciting
announcement that I'm going to make it's
something that I've been looking forward
to so I hope you look forward to it
too in a few days on the 23rd of August
I crazy Oli will be unveiling my new
costume
let's
go new [\h__\h] new
[\h__\h] let's
go I'm so
happy it's been a while it's been a hot
minute I'm very
[Music]
happy yeah hype hpe Hye
I can't
[Music]
wait
yes and
no but hey new
[\h__\h] I'm swiming
because you know um most of the the last
costume that I got it was the kimono by
the way that's more of a how do I say it
that's something that everybody has and
the theme is already given to
us this one I came up with the theme
myself so I'm very excited because the
last time I came up with the theme was
on the mafia outfit costume
[Music]
um please look forward to
it
hello yeah you want to take the
quiz
sure yeah we still I have some questions
why
not yeah let
me hello
hello yippi ah I'm not too late I mean I
am delate obviously but welcome thank
you for making time for me yeah I didn't
think you would still be doing this now
let's go well I mean if people want to
come then I got to give them some space
no oh yes yeah and we actually have some
questions that have not been given out
because it's way too
hard no I think you'd be able to answer
I don't know I honestly don't have that
much confidence um I feel like I used to
be more knowledgeable in the past but
we'll see we'll see you got I I believe
you have this in the bag I am is there
like Jokers H is there
Jokers Jokers yeah like when I don't
know something can I use a joker I could
give you a hint
okay yeah because I myself I'm not sure
if this is oh oh wait I got here I
myself I don't actually know if the qu
the the answer is right so chat will
have to tell
me okay because like different places
say like different answers so we'll see
oh okay I'm curious okay done I'll take
the difficult
questions are you ready no but let's do
it now where was ah here's the question
MK4 who debuted
Before Time
start well I mean of course like Sora
Senpai for example no no like directly
before her like the person oh directly
before I I'll give you more time to
think I'll give you more time to think
um well maybe I've heard of that before
directly
directly not that it has to be someone
from but what about mik Sena I don't
know could be I don't no probably not
but so hey oh no wait wait wait wait a
second wait wait wait it might be
someone from the first gen right is it
from the first gen well you're kind of
the
cold
cold no no it's not the first
in
[Music]
about is that your final answer yeah
because she
also I mean it's G to be
yeah this is a trick question because I
I did a lot of
research and um some people say it's
like another person but from the
research that I've done oh it
was yeah so she came out
Gamers like on the same day well not on
the same
day like same
week it was the same month oh okay yeah
this is the hardest question so far so
if you got it wrong it's fine because I
wasn't so sure either
yeah interesting okay I got to do more
research huh yeah but don't worry that's
that's literally like the god tier level
difficulty so you still have one another
one yeah next question you have any
preferences JP n ID um I want all of the
remaining questions oh that was actually
the last one because
yeah so the others they're more uh
repetitive questions that I've
asked okay give me an ID question an ID
question okay yeah I oh this one's way
too easy uh let's see I oh
okay uh this is someone you despise so
much I'm sure you would
know oh God
ah yeah so Ana is an ancient weapon and
the ancient weapon has a name what is
the name of the ancient weapon uh kuris
kuris yeah Chris yeah yeah yeah locking
in
yeah well you
are absolutely correct
[Music]
X call
Bo wow see now that one easy that was
that easy really because I think that
one's pretty hard even for like some of
the others nah I mean I watched your
guys' debut I watched the debut I
remember true oh my God what a hater she
knows her
enemies I got to know my enemies I have
to know what they're up to and what
they're capable of yeah a so you got one
Yago pin and it's also the color of your
beloved
enemy can I get another question oh you
can uh do you want Ian or DP this time
Ian okay this one's going to be pretty
easy actually okay I mean I've been in
Ian since the beginning so yeah
obviously you're like the dim by ien
yeah I'm the
Creator so here is your
question what what if it's about me oh
there was one about you but I can't give
you that what her Twitter handle yeah
what is Elizabeth's Twitter handle timer
go is it something
weird yeah it's not the usual name and
you just write it down oh you said it
was going to be
easy well since you're a senpai I would
assume you'd find it
easy I know that like for example a ia's
um name is like H Twitter name name is
something like the not the usual
combination because her name is like too
common yeah and ebast is just too long
so I'll give you a hint it's just not
Elizabeth Rose blood flame all together
it's a little different yeah okay um I
do call her herb
mhm but
um I don't remember like her Twitter
name but
okay
H uh how about e e RB and then under
what do you call it under bar underscore
under bar the
lower like bar thing and then whole
live yeah
are you locking that in you're you're
I'll say this for you you're pretty
close I am oh that means I'm not there
okay then let's let's kick the Ian away
let's say whole Liv e RB under bar score
uh whole alive only locking in
yeah
[Music]
wellfor you were almost there it was er
blood flame oh wait yeah herb alone
would be pretty weird huh yeah but hey
you got one
pin
[Music]
y yeah what do you think of the quiz I
like it did the others get questions
right did crony crony was here huh did
she get something right she
did what question did she get uh wait
her question was what was her question
um I believe it
was uh spelling moco's name and one more
was oh who debuted first in
Neu
ah yeah she said she wanted an easier
one because it's very early for her and
she's
easy those
excuses he okay give just last but not
least give me a Japanese question come
on okay okay one last one okay yeah okay
then um ah this one should be perfect n
[Music]
NY perfect it's p
related then let's not make it P
related what is a
to greeting
catchphrase you got
it
yay I asked you about p senpai's a fan
name ah no s yeah that's too easy to
yeah that's way too easy but hey you got
the other pin great
job y
y all right thank you you're welcome
sorry I interrupted you you talking
about your new outfit so everybody pay
attention to all's new outfit
woohoo thank you when are you when are
you releasing it I'll be releasing it on
the 23rd of
August oh that's so soon yeah which is
why I'm announcing it today today okay
in three days let's
go it looks cute
already thank you do you have any
guesses what it is
ah uh although wait H there's like a
jacket in a bag and a big twin tail so I
don't I would I would have
said
like wait it could be a lot of different
things it could be casual it could
be could be an like an otaku outfit with
a like you know the Japanese howy
happy cuz the the sleeves kind of look
like that it does look like a happy
doesn't it yeah but I don't want to I
hope I'm not correct because that's kind
of
[Laughter]
weird I don't know but whatever it is it
will be cute thank you please look
forward to it I'm excited for it than
letting me take the quiz you're welcome
and thank you for
coming byebye
love so good was so good
job Ollie thank
[Music]
you oh she's gone oh who was I
kissing
yeah thank you car boy for taking the
quiz I'm so
[Music]
happy yeah and you know if people still
want to call that's also okay I believe
we still have two two more callers
[Music]
yeah I'd feel um bad if they didn't take
the quiz because I've already invited
them so they're going to take the quiz I
mean we're only counting down for like
the announcement anyways so you know all
good two more sweet two more
[Music]
YY just sent me a video of her wearing
the pin makes me so happy oh
[Music]
hello
hello h i uh huh are you there
I I can't hear
you hello there we go oh my God oh my
God oh I hope my audio quality isn't too
bad it's not too bad don't worry about
it oh my God I just landed I just landed
at the airport and I literally like ran
to the corner near the
bathroom you know you didn't have to do
that but thank you for
coming of course thank you for inviting
me to yeah so would you like to
introduce yourself real quick oh um hi K
I'm K and I'm a nin tailed fox and I
like to
sing
yeah also um um um um I also want to
congratulate you on your new outfit
let's go thank
you I've been holding it back for quite
a while yeah oh I'm sure it's going to
would be great yeah so have you been
watching the stream
actually just a tiny bit just just a
while ago oh what did you think about
some of the questions that you've
seen honestly I feel like I could have
answered some of them the last one
seemed kind of easy
but but I I don't know maybe you have
only the hard questions left don't worry
we we you've actually been through all
of the questions so I can give you an
easy one a hard
one okay okay is there any branch that
you want to look
[Music]
through
maybe it got it well for then we
have
okay here's
one okay what is that laugh no it's
because you know was here and I couldn't
possibly ask her this oh okay yeah so
your question is what is kir Senpai
first ever song
release first ever song release shoot
um oh shoot something
something fire
wait no I forgot the title heart wait I
think it had heart in it or something it
had a what heart heart ah heart
calendar yeah are you yeah yeah are you
locking in okay I'm locking in are you
are you sure it's hard
Challenger I I that's the one that I
kind of remember so yes
I you almost got it I believe that was
your second or third but her first of
song was
hinotori oh wait hory oh my God yeah it
is firef fire
something
oh what the heck it was closer to my
first answer then yeah you were you were
almost there oh my gosh okay close
enough I guess close
enough yeah so H that was an Ian
question do you want to try me be a JP
or an ID
question okay we can
try which one would you
like gosh surprise me you
choose I'll give you an easy one okay
ready ready in hollow life Indonesia
every single generation has a unit
name okay for Gen one gen two and gen
three what is the name of the unit name
for the first
gen first gen
shoot I feel like it's at the tip of my
tongue wait I should know this it's
related to your
birthdays birthdays oh God my
my characters
oh God yeah my brain is not braining
right now uh oh he just landed so that
makes
sense does it
no no okay what is
it it's oh uh you don't have any
answer yeah oh it was Area 15
oh she's mad no I'm not mad
but yep yep yep this is something that I
probably would have been able to answer
under normal circumstances
I I'm I'm so sorry how about no it's
okay how about one more question this
time a JP maybe you can solve this one
maybe maybe we can try one last one okay
so here's your last question question
okay I want you to spell robo's
name oh r o b o c
o with just a Singler
C yes you're locking that in
yes you are correct yes
y Yi yeah good job a lot of people
sometimes like to put double C's in it
oh okay okay okay okay okay we got at
least one that's good enough we got at
least one
congratulations let's
[Music]
go yay thank you for coming even though
you're so busy in the airport no no no
no I'm not I'm not busy at all it's
okay it's okay thank you for um this
opportunity I bet the um people are
looking at me crazy right now but I I
don't care I I don't I don't want people
to think that you're insane so I think
I'll let you go now do you have anything
to say before you
leave um thank you very much again for
inviting me and congratulations again on
your new outfit we're all looking
forward to seeing it of
course yay thank
you you're welcome have a lovely time me
too there we
go uh
oh and that everyone has been K let me
just uh straighten her profile picture a
little
[Music]
bit oh
let me
[Music]
yeah yeah Kong not Pichon it's
Kong and we have actually one more last
guest m
so uh let me just get this
off and it is now Dawning on me that I
yippi and jumped up and down and
P never change kcha never change I bet
you I bet you were so cute would have
loved to see that all right so our last
caller of the
day
hello hello
hi
morning right it's so early for you are
you okay no yeah I am I I was just I
played a little bit of among us last
night
and you were playing Among
Us
yeah well would you like to introduce
yourself to everyone here yes of course
so hello I'm Mari I'm an artist vtuber
from
[Music]
Portugal Portugal yeah
yeah and I'm o you say it so well every
single
time um and I'm very stoked to be here I
I heard the questions you asked uh kitan
and um I'm very scared you you'll be
fine you'll be fine you're you're easy
I'm a very very casual H life enjoyer
it's fine um I have some easy ones for
you don't
worry than thank you so is there a
specific branch that you want me to ask
you
um I guess the most familiar one I would
be like the one I'd be most familiar
with would be probably Ian I'm guessing
but I don't even know cuz I just I I I
don't know I'm very nervous you're good
you're fine well I have an Ian question
for you right
here okay yeah it's a person from Ian
and I'm sure you've heard of
her oh wait not this one I've already
asked this one
uh sorry just a moment um here you go
what is iris's Twitter
handle time starts
now Iris Twitter
handle I think I'm if I'm going to guess
I would say it's probably like oh uh uh
Iris Holan or okay uh Iris uncore holoen
Yen sorry that's so is Holo
Yen are you sure oh it's not
[Applause]
no
um Ira um I can't think of what else it
could be
Iris uh yeah IR
isore
answer yeah well you're you nearly got
it
right no okay what is it it was
Iris so
close that's true yeah oh these are hard
yeah it's pretty hard as a casual
enjoyer I would say because even some of
them I don't know
know yeah do you want to try again sure
sure what do you have for me I also
don't want to keep you too long cuz it's
been a long time by the way
congratulations on the outfit thank you
just from the silhouette it looks really
really cute thank you so much I I put a
lot of thought into it and I think it's
going to be my favorite outfit I'm
excited I see some rings on the hand I
I'm excited to see what it's all about
yeah let's see as a casual enjoyer I
think I'll oh you're familiar with Ian
right uh yeah like casually so here's
another
one I want you to spell moco's full
name oh um M oh is it Moko or Moko Oh No
Name by the way oh
um so it's not just a
m okay okay so I'm just thinking is it
Moko or M for no cuz I think the rest
should be
okay um so I know she's abis Gard which
I assume it's it's like regular oh no um
so I would I think abiskar would be a b
y mhm SS
m
g uhhuh a uhhuh or D I don't think it
hasard what about the
Moco I don't think it's
Moco so I think it's m o c o c o I think
it's just like I don't think it has uh
two C's I think
it's so if you were to spell everything
out how would you spell it oh
uh uh m o c c o c o mhm a b y s s g a r
d oh
Mari oh did I get it wrong again you got
it
right
yeah y oh my God I was like oh my God is
it m
no you got it right yay oh my God I got
one yeah so here is a yo pin for you oh
thank you you're welcome you know I'm
I'm somewhat of a h life expert oh it's
so cute you can stick it on your
forehead and show the whole world I will
I'll send you a picture
yeah anyways thank you so much for
coming I know it's super early for you
oh it's not really anymore but I was
dumb cuz I was like I thought when you
said when you said like hey just like
let me know I thought it was right away
so I was like okay Ollie's going to call
me anytime and so I was like putting my
my alarm
clock like every 10 minutes and I was
like okay Ollie hasn't contacted me yet
I'm sure it'll be soon and then I opened
the stream and everyone was here and I
was like oh I'm so dumb it's fine it's
fine there never was a what's it called
we don't have a schedule for anyone
anyway so anyone can just come in
whenever they can yeah I'm so sorry for
being so late though but thank you for
having me yeah and thank you for making
your way to
come of course of course
anytime I hope you have a lovely rest of
your day by the way yeah you too have a
a great I guess rest of your night right
good evening
yeah heck yeah and uh thank you for
having me good luck with your debut it's
on the 23rd right yeah oh that's so
exciting I can't wait to see it thank
you
Mari yeah um okay I'm going to let you
go and um I hope everyone has a great
rest of their day bye-bye byebye thank
you thank
you and then everyone is our last color
money money money money
money money money
[Applause]
her name is so cute yeah and with that
everybody is the announcement and also
the Holo quiz wait since it's a toachi
doesn't that mean I complet
wait just one
moment to a minute that
means I cleared one of the Bingos
right right
yeah the B wait let me just edit this
out real quick I
edit where's Bingle Bingle
Bingle let's go now we just need one
more
Bingo I'm so happy I announced I talked
to all of my well not all of them but so
many friends
and I got a bingo
[Music]
I'm so
happy two bird one stone right how come
he just realized it well I was you know
I was getting ready for the to and you
know um this is my first ever well not
really first ever but first in a while
for the first time in forever I hosted a
tumati that's actually you know legit
cuz you know sometimes I would open Tsum
matis all of the sudden like the Sally
stream the Sally stream had a t but I
didn't really organize it but this time
I organized the whole thing and it went
well and I'm really
happy the announcement was too exciting
yeah I hope you guys look forward to it
um if you guys want to know when I'll be
showcasing it it'll be on the
23rd on 700 p.m. wi I let me write that
down for you guys
pleas oh nope no uh
sorry
um
August
wib or
jst there we go
[Music]
oh it'll be so
fun it's time to go to gong kidle to buy
fried
grasshopper I kind of don't want to
finish the Bingo but yeah I hope you
guys are as excited as I am because
again it's been a while since the last
self
themed new out
[Music]
fit
yeah there will be an event also to
celebrate the new costume reveal so uh
keep your eyes peed on Twitter
[Music]
yeah you have EV yeah it's going to be
such a fun week month
[Music]
maybe and a little um
little spoiler for you guys L
Lama was the one who designed my new
outfit as well that is going to be dope
I don't know if people say dope
[Music]
anymore yeah it's going to be a
masterpiece it's going to say this is
going to be fire
yeah I think that's all for me for
donations I'll be reading on
another I think I will be ending the
stream
here thank you so much for coming by the
way oh that was fun
[Music]
yeah yeah everybody please look forward
to it Lama I'm going
phoh y I'm happy I don't know what else
to say I'm just really really
happy well
then with that said oh who should we
raage fubuki Senai
fuma
yeah excited for you thank you
money M
friend
who wait uh who do you guys want to
watch
thisai
okay fuma
[Music]
Stars there's so
many okay
all right so everybody that's all from
me thank you so much for coming
to please look forward to my new costume
reveal this has been and I am signing
out what crazy bye-bye
ending screen
[Music]
[Applause]