[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
chicken
um let's do introductions and every time
someone introduces themselves they like
put their hands
yeah so first of all
[Music]
overseas Birds Channel streams
[Laughter]
[Applause]
and we brought uh Jenga it's everywhere
back oh no not Jenga just block game
in the moment who who do I pass on to
[Music]
um
okay attention please
Indonesia generation two I'm purple
Arena let's go
we put you know our names here to make
it very obvious I mean I think I was
pretty obvious but you guys all match
yeah
yeah and then
she's using my gloves so if there's like
any characters on them those are from my
cats
Chihuahua glove game yeah I kind of
brought gloves for everybody but I
brought three pairs but one of them is
like stained with paint so instead Elena
is wearing the the genma gloves
yeah oh my hands debut over the door
[Music]
give me your head
ah it's spicy
why are you two not hand holding oh okay
I'm sorry
[Music]
yeah so oh
um I think you know I was kind of like
really I don't know about you girls but
I was really like I had to say like
surprised by the way horotori suddenly
was announced so I wanted to make it
like more a little bit more like you
know a little fish one more song
[Music]
look at our beautiful beautiful
swimsuits
it looks so good I keep like gushing
over like how how perfect we look like
all lined up right I know we're so
colorful and so cute I'm so mad my hair
is blocking your lovely leg though
OMG
has been kind of a thing for a while
um we've been doing like you know
streams here and there and we're getting
more and more members but uh now that we
have finally reached our Perfect final
form question
[Laughter]
it seems that we have been deemed um
good enough to be turned into official
units
and we will be at The Summer Event of
first or second day first
[Music]
um
check both just in case yeah yeah and
and so because of that or maybe just
because I like these two girls I decided
to do a little collab with the overseas
bubs
sorry I look forward to horotoni
activities from now on into the
hopefully far future forever forever
[Music]
oh Birds feather birds birds birds
feather ever forever yes Birds
domination we're gonna take over our
whole life
we're gonna pick it everybody
[Music]
yeah and so what are we doing today well
I know I know maybe a little bit
repetitive but I really thought it was
so fun when I was playing uh some fun
games of uh Lapras uh like three weeks
ago so I brought back the block game and
I brought back the
stick game these two girls don't know
why don't you know the stickers and we
will learn the stick game and this time
we're actually also gonna play this
block game the block game with the dots
yeah
What's this called
five no wait Domino
what's it called
Domino exactly you got five parts for
that no that's how you play dominoes you
answer the question what's this game no
no but uh yeah we're gonna play this and
uh actually the official more or less
official way I'm gonna tell them we
watched a tutorial before this well now
just dance
we watched two different stories I'm
just like we watched the first one it
was like oh my God no you're right I
don't understand this well please I've
ever played it like five times like this
is part of me like such timing though
because yesterday I just played like I
was playing a game and it had like a
domino puzzle and I did and I mean Chad
found out that I I don't know how to
play someone else oh well today is the
day I have a quip now you equip yes
equip are you equipped
yeah
knowledge
you know how to play dominoes right I
know how to stack them in a spiral I
don't know I thought I thought I thought
for dominoes you just like did it yeah I
mean that's you know maybe at the very
end we can try to make something fun
with these dominoes but it's not even
that many you know oh yeah you can do a
nice line yeah just one straight line
yeah
so we have those three games and we also
have snackles snacks yay the the quest
was since we're very International birds
for everybody to bring snacks from their
International places this looks
International
oh well yeah okay now uh failed it but
she has all the rights to fail it
because she's been in Japan for a while
and you what is it it's this these are
churros this is totally from Indonesia
yeah no it's from a convenience store
but me and Lily brought some some snacks
from our countries oh yeah or I mean I
think mine might partially be from
Germany or whatever same thing uh and in
between I I will annoy you girls
even more but after taking a block
everybody has to choose truth or dare
and I have a list of Troops in theirs
and I should possibly dare us to do I
mean it's not I didn't come up with the
but for example if if you have a
specific dare or that you want somebody
to do you could use that or you get one
from the list that's Jenna has okay
[Music]
spicy spicy spicy birds all right okay
I'm ready
then let's go let's start with the Jenga
um oh should we do rock paper scissors
rock paper scissors for starting I'll go
over there who starts you know okay okay
with your name hands
[Music]
um
um can I say it in German oh yes yes
because otherwise my brain does that
function okay
I forgot to do it anyway for some reason
I thought I thought it was twice
you're out okay
first wait I don't want to go for okay
we should go first I've never played
this before
this is my first time you've never
played before I've never played it whoa
first time looking do I have to I just
can't take it from the top right yeah
and then you take any and then you put
it on the top okay but don't make it
fall right what happens if it okay what
is the strategy here I don't know um
when I played with laplos she was
purposefully taking it from really
difficult spots
I should do it this way okay she's going
the second row from the time I have
really shaky hands oh gosh
you're making the tower
looks wonderful we can see it's coming
out wow wow that's the first block of
the game sugoi
sugoi oh my gosh my hands are so shaky
I just use both
if you don't think you can yeah maybe
you should not necessary
okay okay
truth or dare
truth truth
a number between 1 and 50 and what one
in fifty fifty oh and 42 42 is
um
what is what is the law because 42 was
kind of edgy uh one is the longest
you've ever
been without shower
probably when I've gone camping cool so
maybe like five days
spicy spicy okay you have um
I've won okay
[Laughter]
I have a shower tent for that very
reason oh yeah I guess you couldn't get
like showering things even for camping
you think I'm that good of a camper
it's fun
okay when do we go clockwise or what
um I don't know because I'm clockwise
depending on where you're sitting
but I was second with this rock paper
scissors so I'm just gonna go next okay
yeah oh the whole thing moves are you
allowed to use two rounds okay
[Laughter]
well it's too late here I am hello okay
um ask me true for there
oh Truth or Dare
oh my gosh is there a list is there
something you want me to do you want to
DARE me or else uh we're good I'm not
ready I got nothing okay
devil list yeah
um okay pick a number from 1 to 52
500.69 wow oh my gosh
you have to read it out to me is it is
it is it something I could do though
right now
some of these are not really something
we could do I'm curious what the what 42
was
ah okay we'll show you okay oh 66 yeah
it says uh narrate the game in a
newscaster voice for three turns for
free turns
okay I love that I've been practicing
that recently
okay uh and next we have a volume
brainer it's her turn let's see what she
can do is she gonna successfully take
out this this is so scary she's
apparently very scared but does she have
experience with this game no oh my God
this is so hard it is she's very nervous
looking even it's even more gloves
You'll Play This for it doesn't seem
like she has it until she you break it
doesn't sound like she has any issues
with the extraction of the block she
places it carefully on top of it and she
gets the successful block
do
[Applause]
[Music]
oh I'm very curious I think the audience
is also very curious about this question
what is the weirdest thing you have ever
done in public the weirdest thing I've
done in public is
I think uh I uh taking pictures of
myself uh for example like uh
lying on the you know there's like a
slide or whatever and then you just like
lying down face down
yeah like yeah something weird like that
and then you take a picture like that
I think it was pretty
selfie or someone else taking it you
like a liquor with a tripod oh my God
I'm sorry I'm just lonely oh
yourself yeah
yeah
that was extremely interesting but now
we have to look back on the other bird
yes let's see what she has to offer in
this round give it a go
uh do it uh she's hesitating what does
that mean is she hesitating just to make
her opponents think she is insecure
about her block games
[Applause]
oh is she really insecure about her
blocking skills I really still care
about this apparent Trevor that I have
uh no this is not um
the audience is really really
anticipating this turn I've been waiting
for this for a long time
they're placing your bets right now on
on mummy or against mummy well it's
gonna fall is it okay if it falls of
course it is
fall or should I still make an attempt
you should ideally try to not make it
fall
are you sorry I'm like learning
something new today
oh yeah that's totally a good idea here
lowest we're going for the lowest for
the basement of the tower we're going
for the middle one oh that's a very
bottom that is almost as if somebody
told her to do this turn she knows
exactly what to do I just have this
voice in my head she's got the whisper
you know oh
wow
and while you're doing that you may as
well tell us truth or did it I'll do it
there this time
5200 please tell me your number
[Music]
oh you can actually do that
okay oh no you um put your chair at the
very corner of the room and sit on it
and then spin it for huh yeah let's
throw it to
let me read out the prompt maybe so you
understand it I've been in a swivel
chair for 30 seconds and then try to
walk a stream
coincidentally on swivel chairs
this is
interesting you won't be able to see it
guys when we can commentate it
see how straight this bird can walk oh
30 seconds the music is really long
30 seconds is really long wait does it
oh wait that's I guess this is oh this
is
we do have swivel chairs though
oh oh and I would be really bad at this
I think I am oh I will be oh do we need
a timer
we'll come together countdown very
exciting
okay uh but maybe put the chair away so
she can uh walk straight thank you thank
you
all right all right
one two three four five
six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen
Seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty
twenty one twenty two first number
[Music]
28 29 30 walk straight go vertical
she's hesitating to get off of the chair
but now she's walking
she's tumbling she's stumbling almost
but she's she's keeping very straight
legs almost like a flamingo did I do it
yeah yeah
her way of walking was very funny
[Applause]
[Music]
although we were counting 30 seconds
pretty fast I think normally 30 seconds
or longer
congratulations congratulations thank
you thank you very good very good work
good job oh my goodness all right next
is am I done with my uh announcer voice
I think I'm done it's not been three
turns I've been very very even very good
three turns worth of a good announcing
I'll go with proof
this time
um wait did you oh my god
12 please
if if it's not NG uh 12.
okay what is the worst Food you've ever
tasted
oh
what a heavy questions oh no like up off
the top of my head I don't think this is
the worst although maybe it is but I'm
scared to say it
why scary because I think it's here
as many Indonesian viewers maybe
durian
[Music]
cooking
I mean that's the one I can think of
right now it made me puke almost oh my
God why is it the Dorian the dried one
the tree with the one that was worse for
me was the pancakes for some reason even
though and so on they said the pancakes
would be like easier to eat but I don't
think so can I say something I've never
eaten durian pancakes oh yeah you should
[Music]
if it's from someone who has like
neutral opinion about durian it's like
kind of I don't know if you're trying
they're in before I've smelled it but I
haven't tried it for durian beginners
they say just like eat the durian ice
cream because they can taste it's all
very mild and like it's so much more
milky it's easier to eat anyways yeah
it's totally valid not everybody likes I
liked other Indonesian food okay this is
like you know I mean durian isn't really
specifically Indonesia it's not really
yeah but but you know it's kind of you
know a thing I ate there
okay okay it is my turn and I'm kind of
curious which row are you going for
she's going for
bottom middle
all of them are difficult
[Music]
I feel like the side ones are earlier
because the middle ones are almost
easier but she's going for like a
somewhere around the middle row I was
poking I was poking like the middle ones
but all of them are so hard wish we had
a side Cam and unfortunately only for
this game it's a bit you know difficult
to see but you'll see when it falls
apart guys
[Music]
do your best impression of a fish out of
water oh wait like with your body on the
ground maybe like you know
you guys can see that unfortunately I
can't
see that nobody I'm getting up to look
at that out of the water
is that enough
[Music]
she was
so good
with her whole body
nice I can't believe we might learn to
do this
nice good job good job
next which one will it be oh middle side
one she's in the very middle right now
oh oh
she can do it yes yes
it's fine it's fine everyone is gonna do
something stupid yeah it is fine
it's all right oh
[Music]
oh my gosh the pressure it's truthful
dare truth one to fifty
the 21 21
oh wait it's not over yet though
oh yeah
oh oh
what is the last text message you sent
or like Discord message you sent to a
council member to council
I think I told bae
that I was coming here oh and she I told
her to have fun playing only up okay
that's really not interesting
the last like weird one I sent
do you want me to look yeah it was
probably their Tiffany
yes give me more interesting stuff
secret secret messages what while you're
looking for that I'm gonna try my luck
oh
oh this one's easy this one's like
barely in there oh so fast
um I will go for there because they're
fun
dying fish too yeah
um there what number 79 79
spicy spicy spicy there is you gonna get
a spicy one
oh okay do you best interpretive dance
or gymnastics floor routine floor on the
floor on floor routine oh I gotta see
this gymnastics dance on the floor I
gotta see this you guys ever dungeon
gymnastics no I don't think it's not
even like as a kid what what is that
language it's like you like walk on a
high beam you do cartwheels or something
[Music]
um
go outside and do the best little pile
at the Moon is the next one but I'll
just do it here okay Moon
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
play it too yeah oh yeah of course
there's like they play really short
sounds
and you have to guess if it was
so crazy if you fail it's a sign you
have to go to the doctor
no some of them are really actually
rough difficult I have to I have to
agree okay
oh
okay
that looked really easy that did look
easy oh triple there a truth
[Music]
uh 14. did I chose there last time or
did I do Street last time you did there
last time
the fish uh so okay I want the truth and
then 49 49.
besides your phone what's the one item
you couldn't live without
um that's a very interesting question
um I couldn't live with words
[Music]
I wasn't I wasn't I'm not even worse
um I was gonna say like my house key but
that was like that's awesome
my my PC of course oh which part of the
PC everything okay
yeah I mean you know we're all addicts
so we can't stream with no PC too
gamer gamer yeah all right mummies I
swear there's like every time I look at
my hands there's more and more hair that
wasn't it I don't know anything about it
let's not totally not my cat's here
all right my turn oh I'm gonna
this the bottom part is like pretty much
falling apart at this point gotta go to
the top
they're they're all like pretty
oh no they're pretty like they're pretty
they're beautiful
[Applause]
[Music]
nothing will work I see one that's very
loose
yeah but I want to keep that one for
myself
[Music]
oh you found one is that the chosen one
but it's the no I'll be balancing on
just one ear that's fine that's fine
brisk it for the biscuit for the for the
snacks we need to eat the international
snacks
oh that way okay
[Music]
true for the Army lady did I do last
time true that's right yes oh was it oh
yeah yeah we'll text message I'm gonna
do another truth oh Truth uh one to
Fifteen
if you suddenly had a million dollars
how would you spit it stuck
thank you a million dollars
I don't know I'm not gonna spending
money uh you can't say save it okay
can I invest it or is that saving it
keep going
oh it's even worth a million dollars I
feel like I should think of the house a
boat a car or several cars
um
I'll get
what kind of boats can you get a yacht
oh what are you okay I can get a yacht
with a million dollars no I want I want
um like a thousand canoes
yeah Mommy that is so what are
you gonna do with the house
then I'll make more money yeah okay it's
just starting a canoe business
that can happen if you want
thank you
thank you let's have a canoe party
only at the not miss Mirage
he's gonna spend one million bucks on
the canoes but she's not gonna have any
money left to actually get like like a
store
and I'll save up for that okay yeah I'll
work for that oh separately separate
through the one million dollars yes how
much can it cost
Shack that would surely be the smallest
problem yeah if you have so many
carnoons
maybe sell some canoes after you got
them that's a good idea yeah I'll buy it
and sell them for half price and then
you'll totally make profit I will
that's the point I'll make profit okay I
already put mine on top there so I'm
gonna go for
um
[Music]
[Applause]
what number
six no
um
88. oh
no that's also people gonna think I'm
annoying
okay act out a commercial for a product
chosen by other players okay choose
anything in the room and I'll sell it to
you these churros like uh jackbox sister
us oh wait I have an idea everything
um
oh this oh the skewer goldfish a
singular goldfish
well well well
uh sure okay
um are you guys are you guys lonely
do you happen to have a container that
can hold a certain amount of water well
then buy this singular goldfish for 51
bucks and 99 Cents yes that is the
perfect value for it you can throw it in
the container throw it in some liquid
and it will swim surely it will turn
into a real goldfish because it's called
goldfish of course yeah yeah and then
this fish actually has a special ability
it can talk if it doesn't end up talking
then you do not complain there are no
returns we don't need that any returns
but this will get rid of all your
problems this one little goldfish can
you eat it of course you can also eat it
but why would you do that if you're
lonely and you're getting this for
companionship then why would you eat it
so get it for your companion I want it I
want the fish
no I'm selling it to you because I'm
that was my prompt
[Music]
tastes not fishy and I've heard that
when when fish don't taste fishy it's
fresh then they're fresh right so it was
a fresh fish oh nice high quality go
ahead
that was almonds goldfish oh no look at
her look at her head it's still there
plenty of fish in the sea yeah yeah
that's so true
that was one of mume's necks I hear yes
I bring it
what made you choose goldfish I was
thinking of the best snacks you can get
oh my God I'm so scared
that's the Goldfish luxurious I'm so
scared
now believe in the blocks
that's okay though
oh you have chosen one okay okay
looks like it should be fine
so another row complete
Truth or Dare huh
six
six t one 61.
I don't know okay it says go outside and
sing you are my son I don't even know
that song
Maybe another number maybe
um
can I see uh
well okay uh oh oh that's interesting
hold of plank position until it's your
turn again
what's planking position it's like lines
completely flat like but with the arms
like this no no well I guess it depends
but like the trend before was like just
flat like by your side
yeah
it's like you don't oh I don't know
shouldn't have been difficult oh if
you're doing like that like the exercise
oh I like the exercise all right okay
I'm gonna do no planks do you know how
to do planks yeah like oh that's right
yeah okay let's go okay let's go let's
go okay no you've got to keep it though
okay okay okay tell me what I wanted
okay okay
tell us when you're feeling unwell
waited
I can't see how's it doing how's it
going winner
ah not good not good it just started
my mama is very slow I'm sorry yeah I'm
the worst person to go after you
this one is good but I can't oh yeah I
can't it's coming out but I can't reach
it
oh I go around
come on come on
how are you doing I'm not good damn it
it will get better it'll get better over
time my socks are like slipping
it's so slippery what are you doing it
my socks are so sweet she got all out of
her plank to fix her socks unbelievable
we'll forgive it once
you guys can't see it oh I see him oh
they're so small
feet okay uh meanwhile truth or dare
dare oh dear what if the Dare takes uh
maybe we'll get a fast there okay okay
um can I have you choose okay if it's
fast wait and why are you up get down
[Music]
he's just doing whatever she wants
um
give me your phone and let me tweet on
your Twitter account
[Applause]
I'm gonna do Randy a favor and quickly
pull out uh
I'm going for the second row
oh
very unstable this one there oh God why
my body so unstable
okay why should I tweet oh dear oh dear
this is
you gonna try to make it sound like me
or is it gonna be obvious
[Music]
you're writing the truth only the truth
okay okay
do I have to wait till after the stream
to see or should I see after you've
conceived right away
I mean I didn't think that blocks could
last so long
maybe it's time to destroy it
thank you
what
mimsies
women entertain them while I'm writing
um okay can I do any cool tricks
probably not
yeah do it do like a trick look like you
know like
is that cool
I can't really do anything in the gloves
did you already know how to do it no I
still have to do my weight I know this
is is this mine is this where it is
okay um
no not really I will do truth and we'll
make your you phone oh my God
you say I ran past Kiara today because I
didn't recognize her even though she
looked the same as usual I'm so proud
I walked like I was walking up to her
because I was picking her up and and I
was like that's that's the moment I
haven't met her in a while but that's
weird I think that I'm pretty sure this
moment and then I was like staring at
her and we walked we were like so close
when we were walking you know past each
other but she just walks away I guess
it's not ume but I think it's allowed to
sit down okay you can stop it no I but
what's my name what's my truth though oh
yeah explain yourself I saw I saw a
person person was looking at me I go oh
God this person's looking at me don't
even process
don't worry I didn't notice you're
making I talk eye contact with me don't
worry I won't make this awkward for us
stranger don't worry I pretend I didn't
know if you knew I was picking you up
you should have like been there
I didn't think you'd be there I thought
I thought you'd be stand like waiting
yeah I guess so
my mind I'm like I gotta get to Kiara I
got to get to Kiara I'm like oh God This
Woman's staring at me
here
and I'm I'm I'm choosing truth I will
these are all kind of boring though um
[Music]
high five this one okay
what what is the dirtiest room area of
your house
[Music]
um it's
um the dirtiest
I mean I know oh you know yeah what is
it litter box yeah I mean I think so too
logically it's probably
um the guest room where I also have the
the cat toilet in but actually no it's
not that bad because like I I vacuumed
the leftover literally quite often and
it's not that dirty I mean my mom stays
in that room and she says there's no
problem did you get a really nice litter
box I got a robot toilet yeah that turns
like this yeah and like the the poop
goes into a hole down there and then it
closes so it doesn't even smell it's
amazing I love talking about my robot
toilet I think I remember the pictures
I remember I wish all the animals used
you should get a robot toilet uh I think
so too no I don't know maybe it's a
really good investment it is I wonder I
never I really looked up how much it
costs there's like cheaper monsters
they're like they're really good
um I'll have to train my cat to use it
though mine didn't need to be trained oh
really yeah you just use the same litter
and then they recognize the scent maybe
in the beginning they're a little bit
like what is this but they'll figure it
out scare me what are you pointing out
I'm just poking at the eyeball
okay wait who's turning oh wait a
welcome back for planking today's
workout successfully completed
[Music]
I think it will break soon because I
made it very unstable for real it's a
good thing though yeah
she's barely touched it and it's like
oh that's not gonna move
oh
yeah
the pressure they have a different
pressure because they don't know yeah
um
[Applause]
she took one from like the second row
right uh yeah the second bottom second
bottom second
Ary
[Music]
[Laughter]
when is the last time you apologized and
what did you do
the last time I apologize
um I uh I was fine no you apologize to
me because you fell asleep
oh yeah last night yeah I did that
wasn't the last one oh I did do that oh
you do apologize yeah I was supposed to
like make the thumbnail but I fell
asleep that's what Cali made yeah
I woke up at midnight but that was too I
think yeah and the last time I
apologized I was playing Valerie and I
died in a really stupid way so I said
sorry to my chat to my team yeah you
know because I brought my laptop but my
Photoshop right now I can't get into my
Adobe account so I was asking Brandon
can you make a thumbnail and she's like
yeah yeah until one time
I said um maybe around this time and
then later on she was oh I couldn't
contact her so I was getting worried and
I asked Kelly
thank you Kelly
a mommy got one thank you
that's making me very nervous the fact
that mommy got one
okay
uh truth or dare
250 200.
try to drink
a glass or I guess a bottle of water
without using your hands what like I
guess like you know like like can I
please have a different one I'm 100
gonna spill it of course you will but
okay we shouldn't do it here the
closest ones do oh do an impression of
another player until your next turn oh
my God
[Laughter]
to your right
give a shoulder rub to the player to
your left
he told me it wasn't right okay
so you're to your to me right no left
I'm on the left I'm on her left no not
on her left no no that's just your right
you're her Ryan right no like anything
if it reaches the edge of the screen
just like shoot it goes back to the left
it says right right please
[Applause]
well since you know
yeah that was my turn yeah
[Music]
oh that's pretty good though I mean it
could be stronger
it's nothing there's nothing really get
the jackhammer
[Applause]
[Music]
oh you use this are you tough or mine
use your elbow oh
yeah like
does it really work stronger what shut
off
oh yeah yeah oh yeah I'm so curious I
don't like I can't tell if I'm weak or
she's strong you're weak and I'm strong
oh is she and she's strong my shoulders
are just I don't know how to do this oh
yeah oh yeah deeper stronger oh yeah oh
yeah all right now we're talking woman
okay okay thank you thank you
so we're done with blocking
and now um before or maybe while we do
the next game
it's a snacky time
for real OMG one of the snacks I have
brought is
this oh my God how do you pronounce It
Again Sport what what sport what what
come on
yeah
yeah they have a lot of like different
kinds of chocolates but I brought
strawberry today it's really good please
take one
um
my favorite one is uh what's your
favorite flavor and it's the one with
the cookie and so on
this one's good too there's one with
corn flakes as well right yeah yeah
before yeah yeah yeah and they have it
in Indonesia as well
yeah it's really good chocolate I think
they even have it in Japan
it's from Germany I love what does what
does Moonlight have
um
I have something equally as good I have
goldfish goldfish goldfish crackers
I already have one you try one yeah
it will be inside me
taste of America
is that like something you snack on like
generally I mean I feel like it's a
pretty common like lunchbox snack
I don't know
good I could snack on them
it is goldfish
I don't know what to bring I couldn't
think of stuff
good is there anything I could think
about Japan has better ones better
goldfish no no any type of food I was
like oh I could bring chocolate
I do not agree with that but maybe
compared to American children oh yeah
that's what I mean
even when I was um before I left I was
like oh I could bring gifts from people
I was like no I should buy gifts in
Japan because everything
like food wise food wise
I think I mean there should be some good
snacks in America I mean only Pop-Tarts
but you've had Pop-Tarts no please
please I never want to eat Pop-Tarts
ever again what flavors did you eat
again
it's only one good one which one I like
the Sunday one Sunday what's up with
Pop-Tarts why are there they suck those
strawberries
I tried once and then I was like I don't
know if I made it incorrectly or it's
just like because it just you tried one
there's no I think there's no incorrect
way because you can eat it raw as warmed
up I tried microwaving it or something
this would work out they're toaster
toaster toaster best awesome but like I
said like strawberry blueberry those
will give me headaches
yeah the shamore one is okay but it's
not that good we had like I think four
or five different ones Gas makes three
languages and she chooses to speak the
truth
yeah
you oh whatever have you had toaster
strudel before like that it's not good
you know they're just gonna try there's
a famous dessert from Oscar it's called
oh that is the real yeah I'm not
gonna eat them I feel like it'd be funny
for you to try it no it's like the
commercials it looks so good and then
when you do it yourself it was awful I
think I've seen it before yeah I have to
try it at least once do we have another
snack oh yeah I brought more Delicacies
um these are so bright I also have some
more oh okay we're going for a similar
category I have shower patch kids Wow
Let's Go
which one tastes the best I like the my
favorites are red blue and orange but
that's just because I like those types
that's like more than half of them yes
[Music]
raspberry oh Orange
orange okay
um
first or shower then they're sweet
are you guys should see the commercials
for these I love the texture too
I mean I feel like we can get similar
very similar snacks in Austria like to
this okay now it's sweet yeah but it's
probably banned in Austria
because of the dye that they use
maybe we just use a different dye
because I'm sure it has a lot of guys
and um American food or a band like when
you put inside wait there's um no you
know like cereal like fruit loops like
the Europe version and the America
version is different it's like the
American version is like so bright and
then the EU version is you know the guys
are important yeah
I think it's like something from Beatles
or something Beatles but I I forgot
exactly what it is but I've actually
brought something here that is
apparently banned from being sold in
Japan
[Music]
but there's technical is not being sold
it's not being sold I'm just giving the
kids green is sour apple I like that too
this is so funny I'm so glad you guys
are complimenting Sour Patch Kids now of
course they're green I love these I mean
I feel like only as a child I was eating
like jelly candy you did stuff nowadays
I don't eat it anymore but when someone
gives it to me I like it
I have I don't know if this is I think
it's from Germany
um malam I think are from Germany I
looked it up pretty short from Germany
and this I I've been snacking on
um
we have
um raspberry we have lemon we have
orange and we have
which one should I get
okay
[Music]
and then the one that I'm really proud
of uh Germans and austrians will agree
maybe even Swiss Swiss Swiss people or
other people this is the greatest one of
the greatest chocolates ever
[Music]
with orange of course the classic orange
filling yeah oh yeah oh orange sauce I
love orange chocolate Jam it's more like
gem yeah It's Like Biscuits
I love this stuff so good so addictive
it's lit
I'm still eating the mouth please try
one once you once you have your an empty
mouth
oh yeah
see it's like like this
these are chewy and yeah inside this Jam
so good I'm still eating come on I'm
eating dinner me too it tastes forever
it's true oh yeah it does um Oh I
thought you meant the cookie
managers
[Music]
there are managers in the room to
support this stream yummy
if they would like goldfish or Sour
Patch yes yeah oh my tooth hurts
oh this is so good this is so good
oh what's up all right
it's so good
all right thank you thank you Reina did
you have it look where is it no I didn't
I didn't take one
later later no no okay now let me
[Music]
I was gonna say let me feed you but it's
a bit difficult of the camera
I'll feed you later you can feed me if
you like get up and go here
oh well
okay yay
this is the texture is surprising so
good I thought it was gonna be like hard
biscuits no no soft biscuit
[Music]
oh that looks so interesting
I brought special how are we gonna eat
that special band it's not really banned
but it's not sold here okay okay so wait
there's there's catford and that's from
the globe cat hair let's go I might be
making your words
Rice Krispie treats with actual
marshmallow
rice krispies apparently are not sold
I'm gonna have these cut but I think
just this one into three Pieces perhaps
I love Rice Krispies so much
actual marshmallow I don't I never
really see that you know this kind of
stuff I can find similar stuff in
Austria but the the Rice Krispies I
don't think I can find some because
they're not allowed
wait wait wait just the cereal it's the
cereal the cereal it's like the cereal
you don't have Rice Krispies Cereal I
mean cereal yeah but not like in this
block form oh do you have the cereal
because I read it was banned Rice
Krispies Cereal like um not like my band
I mean like it's coming you just can't
sell it there oh because of something
that's in it maybe or maybe they have
like special ones that they make for
other countries I don't know I mean I've
never seen something like this before so
Moonlight needs to be locked up behind
bars I know I brought I brought sweets
I'm sorry who made this book what did
you do I brought sweets what'd they say
why does America put so much like
illegal stuff into their food
that's my question
like we have those uh oh I should have
brought the image I had the surprise
eggs
people started eating like a choking
hazard oh my God it is Kinder Joy yeah
but the chocolate that they use for the
egg is like one of the best chocolate
ever oh my God yummy oh
they have arrived wow
why is it so I thought why is it so
sticky
if you don't want it I'll eat it it's
very sticky
oh my gosh
wow I love you can you can like mix This
and like make it by yourself in a
microwave
now people make them at home you just
need to take the cereal and marshmallow
mix it and then you put it
yeah like you melt the marshmallows and
you just I mean it's good it's good very
very very very very very sweet
[Music]
um put a really thin layer of chocolate
on top
I think maybe even chocolate lunch I
made this like once but I did have like
the white marshmallow so I put you know
like the duct shape yellow marshmallows
and then there's like red food dye there
and then it was good for the color it
just turned really weird
oh these are good I'm not generally not
a big fan of marshmallows because it's
good
[Music]
the other ones are kind of like I don't
know they look very processed I mean
these are processed too there's like the
old the bar thing too right the manager
sound is trying to pick the the chewy
marshmallow off of the knife that
was used
okay okay okay while we're snacking we
can continue snacking of course but
we're gonna play dominoes now because I
want to play dominoes
just the most simple rules basically in
case you don't know yes Domino can be
played as a game wow so good so I don't
have so many pieces but basically
everybody gets five first of all let's
turn them all around and then mix them
and you can choose five and then
[Applause]
choose your yeah everybody wants this
looks edible it could be maybe it's
another one of my snacks yeah they do
look edible sorry everybody chooses one
and around how many just first one
okay I'll choose one
woman is building a tower with the
blocks
let me choose one
um
room is making a house or something I
just want making stunning
oh
okay
[Music]
um me for you that was your last one
yeah the main last balloon Licorice and
I chose okay this is our our dead pile
okay yeah so everybody look like put
them up in like a like a you know like
if they can stand okay yeah
put them in a row like this we don't
want that wish to see it okay
okay
and now
um I think it was the one with the
highest double starts I
okay who is the highest does it need to
be a double oh I have a double I have a
double okay what doubles do you have F3
four four you start place it in the
middle all right okay
and and yeah okay so now you can attach
like a four piece for example you can
connect
go next you're gonna go perfect wow wow
we know how to play the game wow and I
think you can only you know place it
like this if you have double stubborn
if you have doubles as well or say if
you have four
whoever gets rid of older's uh uh first
wins I guess that's like the simple
rules
so I'll hit you next me next
no no it's gonna get really heated
really I promise really yeah I'm sure
that
can you okay now in this stage I have
one question could you yeah attach it
randomly to the middle there yeah
wouldn't there ever be would there ever
be a problem then because it's so easy
to find oh you're right you're right it
probably is not something you do no okay
yeah I'm wondering okay yeah no okay
it's a no okay okay
you can only attach to the ends I guess
and if you're doubles and you can okay
okay
but you can like Bend to an L shape that
there you go yeah yeah oh you can bend
it um okay
go away now we can continue to snack too
by the way I'll take a shower
so there's like what's a blank one
what's a blank one do
uh I think that's like a joker is it
blank one like a joker
um
the flank one is like a joker I think
you can place it anywhere anyway all
right zero
so that means
um
oh so if so if this is like six can I
put a six in the middle no no it's only
at the ends you can play something okay
okay then okay
and then if I don't have it I will you
have the bigger now one I pick another
one until the pile is gone as far as I'm
until the pile is gone that's all until
you finally fine
then you're kind of you need a four or
two yeah
that this is like disadvantage for you
because you're getting more and more
blocks
okay you got one
okay okay so then here can I do this
yes okay
yes yes yes yes yes
yeah okay I don't have one
thank God
oh District Health Buena
yeah because you had like some some
empty ones right yeah
[Music]
only has two left but are they the
fitting ones are they the fitting ones
can I put it here
really you can because it's like kind of
an end I think is it I think that can I
do that what is it
um
considered an end oh it's hard to say it
here is is this considered an end still
even though we attached here no no no
too bad mommy okay you can only have uh
on like a zero or a one oh
oh
really take it from the dead pile
Oh you go on okay I do have a a zero but
with another zero there I put it there
[Music]
let me see if I can
I think I will do the zero then I feel
like we're like old ladies in the
retirement Channel I love it
oh
I still got one oh I only got one left
no okay Muno
[Music]
no I mean does it matter it doesn't
matter because I win
oh no she's moving
[Music]
oh okay okay congratulations
can we try one more game yeah one more
one more help me turn these around
mixing
okay choose quick quick everybody picks
one okay let's just pick foot until we
have this first one okay
she moved all over us
on your Graves you get a Sour Whatever
oh
yes
oh blue I don't like blue
[Music]
I haven't tried the orange orange is
good okay
I have the highest double I'm pretty
sure unless somebody else has a double
six I do not level five okay starting
well
clockwise yeah whatever clockwise is
no are you gonna have a difficult number
what do I have why do I have to be the
person that catches
oh my God this is suffering oh no you
know this is like I really like this way
of collabing games because like these
are kind of the kind of games we
normally can't play together right we
can only do this in off the lamps
different really a zero
six or I know this does this one still I
guess the other way you could still go
I think you can yes I can I totally can
okay
me and all these
yeah this is fun with friends I barely
play like board games and stuff with my
IRL friends do girls play board games
with your IRL friends ever
what are real friends
[Applause]
oh my God okay
um
no did you just do one yeah
please
what is this what is this
it's so fun
I know you can rearrange it if you want
oh we got passion for maybe
like this right okay
did you just Place one yeah I did the
double thing
ah
[Applause]
oh sorry sorry anyways yeah
I feel like this looks like like a
dungeon map yeah especially from that
field
you put a five
zero
I could have won one
must where can I know huh it's either
here or here
take it from the dead
I can't go this way right now
it's time for she got one she got it she
got one already yeah yes yes
[Music]
I wish we had like more card pools
yeah yeah okay we can we can we can we
try to like do The Dominoes okay okay
but but uh quickly because we still have
to play one more game all right I think
we can do it last okay okay first this
is welcome back to the stick game
everybody said welcome back
yeah remember these sticks they're
called Mikado it's a European
traditional very old sticky game what do
you do it then well let me tell you
first of all you stack them like this
and then you let them fall like in as
messy as possible
okay that's pretty good that's pretty
good and then um
that's pretty good let me look you know
purposefully like make this more
difficult
okay
uh okay we're kind of on the way though
unfortunate can I move the whole thing
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
there you go perfect okay what a mess so
um this it won't really matter to you
girls now because you won't have the The
UU to choose by colors anyway you will
have to try to pick up these sticks
without making any of the other
surrounding sticks move
and one of the ones that are touching it
so this one for example would be easy to
start off but once you have all the like
outer ones then you know you do
something like this and then okay maybe
that was okay but you gotta be careful
so you don't move on the sticks like
this one yeah that's so difficult but
then later there's like strategies let's
say you have one stick you can do like
stuff like this
[Music]
that moved of course so you gotta like
look which one is like the easiest and
you gotta work your top your way from
like the top layers to the bottom when
you can finally reach them eventually it
will be easy because then look at all
these These are placed so easy to take
you can just like yeah
okay I made I made it too easy
oh
I just want to mess it up more make it
more difficult
oh stop okay now these are to eat I will
mix them again one day when we get to
the layer okay so understand yeah yeah
just don't make a move a little bit I
will forgive but don't make a book oh
and uh once you touched one you have to
go for that oh If It Moves then next
turn okay okay
all right let's go let's start who wants
to start me okay
ah wait ah you can continue picking
until something until there's something
else yeah
oh
that will move oh
it's okay it's okay suddenly stable
hands
[Music]
okay I take
oh no
oh that one is not touching I think
oh smooth she moved like my cat's moving
yeah
I could try this one you're allowed to
use like both okay
whoa
scale
[Music]
maybe this one
oh
opportunity to be first I'll let you go
okay
um
it's more difficult with gloves for sure
it's definitely all uh yeah yeah that
okay yeah that moved a bit too much
first I would have said okay but yeah
it's just really hard to pick things up
it goes slowly sometimes it's easier to
just go
oh
I can't see it's fun it's so hard with
the gloves
I'll forgive
last try
I don't know questionable you can have
it if you don't continue
game master
take it okay
well I want to turn these gloves they're
too big yeah
I'm gonna probably mess up I would like
to you know when you play this privately
the good thing is you can like go around
the table and go from different angles
so it's easier but what kind of like
staying where we are so yeah
huh oh
[Music]
you can go
I'll give you the turn
yeah take the easy one
that one goes
I don't think I don't think I can ever
like you have to get a thing and now you
can use you can use a stick to like help
you pull it up for example you would
like go here underneath but you know
yeah and maybe support the other end
with the finger or so let's go with me
I probably re-frow it in a moment
because these are all the same direction
it's still fun it's still fine
okay I have to start getting strict now
that you're you know losing your
training wheels but I'll do us all a
favor
and I'll let it fall again because it
didn't look very interesting
oh
okay
[Music]
but it's my turn so I feel bad about
this so I'm gonna place it here okay
okay
I'll leave some easy ones for Wayne you
go
[Music]
yeah there's some freestanding ones
fingerly
I didn't see it okay
it's just you can go another one wait
wait wait she can go another one no it's
all right try try try
like you know you can do something like
this or you can lift it on one side oh
yes yes
okay that's okay that's okay it is hard
with the gloves it is really hard
yeah yeah
you can still take one oh sorry I'm so
eager yeah
[Music]
see if I can be greedy
uh maybe this is too much well it could
work
you just have confidence you should have
confidence yes I can't grab confidence
but you did you did touch it so you have
to go for this one
yeah yeah yeah oh yeah you moved a lot
yeah if I move a lot that means I can't
take it yeah yeah sure okay next up oh
mumsies is going with bad fingers okay
I'll try the same one
oh
[Music]
um
it's like dominoes right you want the
least of them yeah no no yeah
um oh wait I think this could be the end
of me
we're not fighting we're just uh I don't
know
I don't even know what I can do
that
I gotta improvise oh thank you
can you eat it without being fed yeah
okay wait you got that one without
moving then you can do another one yeah
uh-huh
[Music]
she has learned this the trick of being
fast
trick shot
six like
win it do a flip but with the sticks
um do I return it yeah
yeah I
can't use it
should I like move it closer to you
maybe
[Music]
I'll still find a way to move so now
it's in the middle
perfect
yeah yeah
oh my gosh okay one more are you going
in these are really oh that's actually
yeah it's hard
maybe we need a flicker like Wayne and
[Music]
come on come on these are literally oh
believe in yourself believe in yourself
if anything move it for the sake of the
other boobs should they want Strawberry
oh only the one that you want is moving
yeah it keeps you keep on pushing it
back I know
I can't really push it from the Middle
look at the shaking yes
it moved okay
hmm
for the sake of the birds for the future
I will attempt to sing because like what
else can we do
but my eyes
[Music]
it wasn't that much
I need to get rid of this one yeah or
let's see what we like progress at all
you know what for me
I love my sticks a little paint is good
but that was like
was it there huh was this there yeah
yeah okay
what happened I was looking at the
screen I feel like she should have
gotten it better
it's fine
yeah
of course it is every game is your game
you just kind of making your game that
was smooth
hmm
but the others are rough
ah okay you go
oh
yeah yeah why
okay okay okay
it's day the other day
you can go one more I guess
very very muzuka sorry
I don't think I should be yeah
I have to get one so I can say hi
Oh
I need to
[Music]
um
which one which one don't you want one
to help you
one of those sticks but wait you only
have three sticks I have three you only
have three things
[Music]
should I put it closer to you again it's
okay
I can't see
my hand is in my way I should put it
closer to you it's okay I'm just gonna
this is fine
[Music]
oh yeah
oh my gosh I can't group it is
[Applause]
one more go go go go go go go
[Music]
try flip okay this is good it's gonna
fail it's gonna be fine kind of funny
can I just try I'm not gonna take it
yeah okay
okay
well it looks more interesting now
no this is good because now I can oh my
God
hi wow
no no we can't we can do a collab
yeah yeah yeah oh dude
all right
thank you it's upside down oh really yes
sorry I'm not thinking oh wait oh there
we go oh like this this is very good the
setup makes this a bit confusing there
we go hi
hi hi
you go me
um
which one is oh this is yours I think I
think that that's yours the eye is yours
really okay
oh yeah you gotta remember which one is
yours because they have different points
oh the eye was yours right the eye is
yours
it's fine
we're doing okay
flip incoming
ah no no you can still go you can move
that much
[Music]
is carefully gently show your your
PayPal precision
when it landed back on the tables
[Music]
yeah for cleaning out the tent once the
top one is gonna like rearrange it I
mean
I don't know
okay okay now we have to erase that
maybe like
that okay
um
get all of them
wait closer to you here so you can touch
it with two hands
[Music]
oh dear careful
yay
[Music]
I'll accept
oh that was like a really special one
that one I think that one gives a lot of
points
or it gives no place
yeah
when you're eating something what are
you eating sour patch Sour Patch
[Music]
determination movement if you want to be
successful in hotel you need
determination
let's go
away sticks
oh
yeah yeah
okay too much just a little bit more
would you like to place it a little bit
closer to me oh I don't want to do it
because then I'm like thank you
Jesus
there's something like that baby this is
very difficult really sorry no it's okay
oh
no I don't know
why
and now it's basically freebies free for
you
and now we'll give them two staff asan
to count them and meanwhile while one
stops on this country we'll just you
know snack and chit chat so this is one
stack and no stack and no stack one more
stack don't mix them okay
[Music]
as fast as you can
roll it do something else mix it all up
wait I know two people version that's a
little bit more complicated yeah it's
like that one yeah yeah and also like
there's a back one in there
[Music]
so it's like if I do this like one plus
one two and then the goal is to like get
five right but if you get if somebody
gives you like free if someone gives you
four then you're over five so yeah yeah
something like that okay so
but Ed don't you like lose your hand at
some point you want it back though
is that one over this is like the goal
is to get rid of all the hand I think
okay the Ever Changing rule game okay
okay we can do house rules house rules
okay
[Music]
can three people do it at once yeah yeah
yeah look at this yeah all right okay
um then it's it's like this pointing
fingers and then you can also choose to
like yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay and then I'll just keep like this
okay I got two
are we do we choose who we give it to
them yeah I thought it was clockwise
okay
and then I have
I give it away so I'm on zero no no no
no don't give it away
you get to five so like you you never
have them taken away you just get them
yeah you just like get five what why do
I get five nah for example like see you
do this but like if if I'm in the state
and somebody else gives me two if
somebody has no choice but to give me
two then I get five if you get five you
do yeah okay but I just had two right
and I gave you two what happens to this
hand it just it stays true yeah I think
I played it differently before maybe I
don't know like four eggs and then oh
sorry this is one right yeah so I'll do
um this
[Music]
you're gonna give me one of those Tunes
On which hand oh yeah it makes it like
this and we give you another two or even
a one one day
I remember that if you have like like
this no wait you had four right what did
you have I had two two this and I gave
yourself like one okay yeah wait what
happened what did I have oh you gave me
one yeah
[Music]
ah wait you don't you want five right
yeah yeah yeah something like that
something like that okay
so
okay
oh thank you
give me two
I'm gonna like if you're free
and then
I think the score may have been
completed but let's see let's see we
finished this
you can't do this can I
can no yeah
I'll give you
I could give you five again but I will
not of course not is that wait is that
free yeah sorry and that's one that's
one
this will go on forever and ever
[Laughter]
and then this will go yeah
um this one
[Music]
if you have like four then you you can
only give two is what I remember oh is
that what you were taught yeah and if
you have like let's say free if you have
freed and it splits like uneven but if
you have an even number then it splits
at half is what I know is the score done
yeah oh
going
wow
announcer kiwawa will announce the score
which is surprising I thought it would
be less clear
all third place with compared to the
other points not such a big difference
we have drama
46 points I'm in the top three remember
Dad
I'm Number Two
we're 49 points
which could possibly mean
that with one more point 15.
[Laughter]
so like how does the accounting work
like there's different yeah yeah
depending on on the like and
sticks so I need to know how many like
what does it mean like
um
yeah there's like spider line them up in
the right uh give me the paper too
okay so yeah I was I knew you got a real
special one but one reason yeah that you
got so far is because of this one which
brings 20 points
almost half of your score I'm skilled
the next best one is one that gives 10
points it's a red blue red somebody got
red blue red
dress
blue red blue red red blue red blue red
brings Five Points oh yeah wait no I
said blue red blue that's what I mean I
have blue red blue so it's 2010 and then
the next one the red blue red blue red
yeah that's five oh thank you
blue
no I don't need one okay red and blue
only red blue red and blue it's two
points
and that's it okay so uh it's this order
guys
let me add this one the one that's only
you know there's only one of these
let's celebrate by eating sour patch and
yeah everything else too
Malaysia many fun games now we already
like uh pretty pretty long in terms of
streaming time you can like build a
little Tower while I announce something
or a little line if you want
so everybody I didn't announce that
there would be an announcement yeah I
didn't announce it there would be an
announcement but there is an
announcement
oh maybe I will tell you oh let me think
what is there to announce something very
special as we have been waiting for a
long time what my
new outfit oh my gosh for real yay this
is my
2022 outfit but it's 2023 but it's my
2020 outfit
um actually reveal hashtag kianaalter
Kiara alter yeah
time zone July 21st 2023
[Music]
um
let me tell you the exact times
um my usual time zone CEST GMT plus one
I think it is 11 p.m and it is also it
should be if this is not incorrect
[Music]
I don't know if this is correct I hope
it is uh but yeah PDT 2 pm EDT 5 p.m I
don't know is that really correct is
that 11 p.m CST
hope so
it's very special and actually this one
is uh drawn by a different artist from
usual I will not say who yet but it's it
was a chance to make something very
different and very exciting and very
special so please come to my outfit
reveal I prepared something really
special for it besides the outfit
obviously so I would be excited if you
guys could all come and check it out
it's been a long time in the creation
yeah you two come too yes
it looks really the like this like the
Solitaire not just the silhouette also
like the like the Sparkles and stuff it
looks so pants I mean the Sparkles are
you know they're not coming with the
outfit
I just think it looks like you know well
usually like those pretty
[Music]
finally I'm just getting really old
doesn't really look like it could be
that I don't know about that for him
yeah
it's it's this Sunday uh or Monday
depending on your time if you're like
sea and it's Monday if you are not SCA
or so it's probably Sunday well
what do you mean I thought you were
making something that's got like this
yes
and you failed but it's just really hard
[Music]
I love hands
yeah it is difficult
I think I see a dragon or something like
that oh yeah we had a dragon okay okay
I'm not crazy
[Music]
yeah anyway that's kind of the end we're
gonna continue snacking and burbing
around and maybe you will see some of
our verb activities again in the future
right babe yes yes
[Music]
next stream
I don't know I have a streaming setup so
I have to set it up like
she will stream when she streams yeah I
have a computer and stuff
but I'm busy I think
it's two days at least okay we might be
busy together
we're doing bird stuff okay
okay
okay bye Bye Bye Bye Mom bye-bye
thank you guys for watching
I'm board games or whatever this is
collaboration and in Germany
your greetings please ladies
[Music]
oh yeah you never had a good fight I
can't I have the mean one a simu major
simulator
oh
[Music]
ending number
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]