foreign
[Music]
thank you
hello
cute
welcome hi everyone to our Minecraft
burp craft collaboration
[Music]
is my super new kohai uh junior I
suppose yes from Whole Life Council and
I was so excited uh when she told when I
knew that she would be joining and when
I found out that she is a bird because
well she's a bird and uh now I'm not the
only verb anymore and you know hello
burp hello hello
yes hello ABM yes burp what third are
you if I may ask oh
I believe
I happen to love owls and I have a lot
of owl friends and they're all called
hoodle
yeah
very cute you are you are one of them
thank you and you are you are I am a
phoenix
oh yeah yes of course a phoenix yeah
that's what you like what was that what
was that what was that what was that
reaction I just went a little slow
sometimes that's it so you doubt my
phoenix-ness
I have no doubts I also have
no
uh
knowledge
oh that's the one
that's the problem is it all right all
right Council love come we are the
Council of knowledge no I am I I
collected all the people the collect
collectiveness of knowledge yes where's
the different kind Collective knowledge
I'm supposed to only know the things
that that other people know yeah only
what people know
oh do you know what animals know oh I'm
on reverbs that's awkward oh not on my
side
it is it is it is it is for no reason
okay what did you ask I'm sorry uh I
forgot I forgot you forgot
ah do you know do you know do you get
what animals know then what animals know
um
unless a human knows something about
animal that animal knows then no
generally I don't
oh
oh okay yeah even though you yourself
are an animal I I
know you know how
you know how people don't always know
that much about their bodies and
themselves
unless they study should I teach you
about your body my anatomy
uh I can I I don't know
um yes continue
well you know not everybody can be a
doctor or a surgeon because they don't
know all the parts inside unless you
read about it so I don't know that's how
I am as ow I don't know unless I read
about it
what was the point of the circumstation
um
I forgot okay join me in uh sleeping in
a bed over there because I have no beds
currently in my apartment oh man oh it's
night time we're so fast where did you
go
oh oh I will teach you how to be the
fastest fast and Sonic fastest
you don't know how to be Speedy in
Minecraft I know how to run but you are
just so fast that I could never I'm here
I thought you went but you were so fast
oh my god oh there's so many beds now
yeah enough bids oh and you choose the
one right next to me of course it's
outside and it's cold sweet Kawaii I'll
teach you everything so the fastest way
to run is uh press uh uh wait uh okay so
it comes natural so we press W and space
and a Ctrl at the same time no wait no I
only knew that URL is just for dashing
but if you jump you're actually even
faster how are you flying
I can actually fly both my elytra but
yeah
try it again run to
rental
I hurt myself
about Ctrl in my chat how do you say
that control
oh
okay who else was that recently that I
was talking about uh she says it's Ctrl
why does why do the people who was that
who was that
someone in whole life English says Ctrl
Iris and God scolded for it yes yes why
the hell she's not the only one she's
not the only one I mean it is C Ctrl
yeah it is
all right all right all right all right
where did you go oh there you are
I am speed you are speed I collected uh
a lot of materials already that we need
oh yeah I was supposed to give you my uh
uh tools okay so look little bird yes I
will give to you stream heart Challenger
oh oh it's a it's a pickaxe of mending
The Mending you know what that does no
uh it's a it's a special enchantment
that you can put on weapons and tools
and also armor in order to
um every time you get exp from like
killing a mob or farming a special
material sometimes you get XP from that
as well uh it will fill it's a thingy
backup that so it won't break
it doesn't break so currently you see
the the green bar below it I think it
was like around half or so yeah
yeah so if that goes to the very left
side that's bad but with mending then it
will fill it the durability it will fill
itself up again so it doesn't break
exactly it's wait with mending
it it's
does it actually break if I don't fill
it up again I forgot it doesn't
automatically break
there's a buffer of some sort it can
break uh if you don't repair it oh so be
careful uh tell me if you I don't think
we'll be using it that much today uh so
it should be fine just just don't make
it don't have a break please okay I will
keep an eye on it and I'll also
give you uh this one but please return
afterwards all the fancy diamond tools
please return afterwards and uh tell me
if they're about to break because that's
a bit worrying okay
um
I will also give you this shovel there's
oh it's also very very good shovel wow
and I think that's all we need I think
everything except the ax has mending on
your side
okay and uh you don't really need armor
so we should be fine and yeah so let's
go okay to the building area follow me
little boob yes I will try to keep up oh
my goodness yeah
I'm too fast keep on pressing Ctrl if
you
if you um don't eat enough and fall to a
certain down to a certain level of uh
you know no food yes and then you won't
be able to run anymore that's right
always keep your food bar at the maximum
okay if it's even like a half uh a meat
thingy
um uh Gone
wait are you following what I'm saying
yes yes but even if it's a tiny bit left
then when you get hit by an enemy and
have uh no hearts it won't
oh [\h__\h] oh it won't fill back up again
so
always keep your uh at the maximum I've
died hard to regenerate I have died
because I did not do what you are
telling me to do
all right uh you know how to write this
thing I do put the the thing you just
picked up put it on there I have it
yeah I think you picked it up yeah I did
oh I don't see you anymore and
oh
let's go in this direction
first time I'm going this way oh really
nowadays I only fly you know like a verb
usually does oh
oh is it a secret how you can find
um I have this thing called elitra or
elytra people pronounce it differently
it's some kind of wings
foreign
on it though that's because of the cape
that I wear that's another story uh so
that's called an elytra and you get that
um in a place called the end yeah this
you can get there if you want to fight
the End Dragon ever heard of him I
remember you you all fought yes yes yes
he's that big evil dragon that is
basically the end boss of Minecraft but
that's where Minecraft really begins
I've seen good at where his head
yeah yeah the head you don't get from
him though you actually so once you beat
the dragon the next thing you want to do
in the end is travel from one Island to
another and even in between there's like
only the universe there's emptiness
there's nothingness but you travel
carefully from one Island to another
Island to another Island and eventually
you'll find some kind of end cities in
the end and it's like big big buildings
that look like castles and only uh
enemies are there no no nice people only
enemies live there and you fight them
and then you take over the city and then
in there there's Treasures there's a for
example the elytra and a lot of a lot of
uh and the chests and shulker boxes and
all that so this for example is a choker
box this used to be an enemy
it was an enemy now this is the shadow
of an of an enemy inside was like a
monster that would attack you and throw
balls with you that made you fly it was
crazy
it's so cool
yeah it's this box you know what's
special about this box you as a beginner
will probably not get to use one of
these for a while but
um is normally so with a normal wooden
chest yeah if you put something inside
and then you let's say you destroy the
Box
and everything that was inside will
scatter around it it will not keep it in
the Box you you have everything
scattered but if you put something in
the shulker box and then you destroy it
then it stays in the Shocker box and you
can carry it around like a backpack you
know what I mean ah
I think I think that saves a lot of uh
space in your inventory because you can
basically you don't you can't do that
with a wooden chest you put everything
in the shulker chest then you put the
shoulder chest in your inventory and it
will all it will only take up one item
space even though inside you have so
many items like a backpack like you said
oh yes
yes okay good okay I'll teach you a lot
of Basics today as many as I can follow
me I have decided and cleared out uh oh
here I am I'm I just was wondering why
there's so many fish in buckets that's
because Bay was billing here and she's
um I think if I heard correctly she's
making uh out of this Pond she's making
a axel little farm
there's one here already
and they're really popular right now
because they're the new craze that came
with a new update and they're cute and
all and now uh Bae wants to make a oh
nothing out of that that's not my box
okay so follow me okay uh there's
already so much here built already so I
decided I'm gonna build over there I
already started clearing out uh the area
and made some nice stairs over here off
screen off screen screen and just some
of my stuff okay
so
[Music]
we are going to be building
a little Japanese classic little
Japanese Shrine a Shinto Shrine because
I thought the Japanese girls
uh they they grew up around Shinto
shrines and it will look very familiar
to them and they can go there and pray
and make their wishes and also can get
uh omikuji a fortune Japanese Shinto
Shrine style a fortune and it will be
rather small and simple for that I
collected a lot of dark oak logs in this
box
and we need oh some gravel it has more
gravel you have some gravel yes
okay put it right next to this here the
gravels here do you see them yes yes yes
nice wonderful beautiful yeah put that
together and organize
yeah we're trying to stay a little bit
organized today
and also I'm gonna put
here and since it's night time we should
sleep did you bring a bed with you
uh I did not I know there's one okay
down over there there's one over there
the right one you can you can uh you can
sleep in the yellow one I'll sleep in
the red one for now okay
and fast yes and sleep
I watched it all happen
all right little movie good morning
sunshine good morning
okay
we're gonna
um have you start working right away
okay
and please with your ax get rid of that
tree and in order to get rid of trees
properly you have to hold your
application
don't worry Fire doesn't hurt me I'm a
phoenix oh don't worry okay please get
rid of this tree and you have to get rid
of every single piece of wood otherwise
the tree doesn't despawn you don't have
to get rid of the leaves just of the
woods it goes so fast yes do the same
thing with uh uh this this tree
here another tree
and this you saw this one and and and uh
this one uh that's half in the air yes
yes
get out of here
a little area that we're gonna start
building in yourself
[Music]
that's all we need we need we need a
space of uh wait a second
organize your inventory always
sure
oh berries where did those come from did
you just give me berries
I don't remember you should keep them
though
thank you
do you have food on yourself I have
bread and I have potato
okay good if you haven't eat food tell
me little bird I don't want you to
starve okay thank you
um your chef with
oh
um with your shovel
shovel yes and with your pickaxe
depending on the material that you're
bumping uh into yes please
uh maker
ah ah just just dig behind me
okay
yeah get rid of one block behind me
so okay
perfect perfect
I think can you count uh how many blocks
that was in that length
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven
okay and how much is
two
plus two plus three plus seven four
eleven
nice okay
ah cool
where's that from mathematical
no no I don't know please connect this
square and then get rid of
everything in between
that's everything
I'm gonna move the yes yes keep on
Switching yeah then you can get rid of
them faster
[Music]
but you're doing well you're doing very
well
I think it's it's good that you have
someone to teach you Minecraft you will
get much much better in a very quick
space yeah why are we why are we doing
this
because we're clearing out the main area
where we're building this thing
so you
you I will fill it up now with a
material oh
I am keeping an eye on the health bar
I don't think you have to care so much
about that right now because we're just
building we're not fighting if you're
adventuring somewhere then you might
want to be more careful about that maybe
I should have picked a different
material
but if I want it to be the same that's
that all right I want to be the same
oh I contribute down
okay let's go down here and what's what
material do I have enough of should I
put the diagram please cobblestone
you can put yeah you can put the direct
back okay
back up back up back up back up back up
pick up and while I'm doing this
and in each corner where I already put
Cobblestone Each corner
actually this is difficult to explain uh
in the box where there was a lot of wood
yes get get uh two stacks of the
um
of the dark oak that is uh uh what was
the words dark oh there's log or doctor
strip dark oak glove the strip one yes
yeah the striped one
have it two stacks or so I have two
stacks
good and then put uh for now
put towers of seven blocks high in each
corner
okay when you build them keep on jumping
on them like look like so oh
oh my game is kind of can't hold you
right now for some reason
yeah yeah
you only can jump on it if it's one
block High okay and yeah be on it and
then jump
and then while you jump you you put a
block there yeah okay
yeah seven now you have two okay three
four
yes five
yes six
good job and now you jump down it might
hurt a little bit oh
so now this is where you have to be
careful of yourself
oh I see it but put that in every corner
please every corner one two three
I think
always always leaves
special
I forgot I forgot and remember
I I I think it was at four or five and I
forgot okay
one two you can do it you can do it five
six
six seven
peace
you're not a phoenix like me okay
two
three
you're sure five six seven
okay
[Music]
one two three four five six maybe like
that
oh
okay nice and now
next part I will do and here is a
I every block that I place now you can
continue making uh all of them seven
tall oh okay seven blocks tall please
one two three four five two words being
helpful with me I'm glad I wish to
contribute
yes lunch no three
four five we're gonna be really Speedy
building this thing
oh yes
two three four five six seven
have you eaten my child
I will eat more okay okay the hearts
just fill up slowly or I was not paying
attention
I do they do fill up a little bit slowly
oh I see
[Music]
oh have you wondered about the the fact
that this is stripped Uh Wood you know
how you do that how
if you go to a tree
uh like oh while you're up there I
wonder if you can reach that tree up
there and get rid of that one can you
reach that that other one up there
oh yeah
okay don't worry about it I'll take care
I'll take care of it it's okay I didn't
even finish I can do it
um no it's okay Finish Two Towers okay
don't hurt yourself no more
okay now
and so basically
when you go to a tree with your ax and
then instead of mining it with with left
click if you oh come uh maybe come come
to me for one second yes
look at what's gonna happen look at the
tree closely I'm looking very closely
and then did you see that
how special effects yeah yes right click
this gives you a special look on on the
special nice
wouldn't look so if you want to build
something that looks like that and you
can strip it and it looks like that and
you can mine it and it will still look
like that
but yes
yes it's matching I never I never knew
about this
now you know it's nice
[Music]
it's a semen what why is my game so
buggy today why is it am I spiky too
at the bottom please connect
and every Tower like so but keep one
block uh free at the bottom does that
make sense
like I'm doing here but just the other
way around I mean like there
uh uh uh yeah yeah that looks correct
yes it looks like a fence in a way
okay this one though is oh so
this is three apart and then three oh I
see I see
just keep one block space uh underneath
and then just connect them all like I'm
doing at the top and I think that should
be correct I haven't checked my
reference in a while but I watched the
video two times and I feel like I
remember at least the beginning part
this is from here on and we'll get a bit
uh complicated maybe and you should
uh once you're done with that you should
aim for a bit bed time Little Owl you
might be a night owl are you actually a
night owl or not really
oh wait I forgot a tower here oopsie
out so careful
I forgot this one
sometimes night owl sometimes sometimes
oh be careful that the whole life
doesn't destroy your sleep schedule
because it does that for usually
everyone oh it has been it has it has it
has it did all right
follow me to sleep you sleep in yellow
bed I sleep in Redmond okay okay I
should bring the red bed over here
[Music]
yeah I will I will torch put some
torches around in a minute oh I think
you're aware of the fact that if you
don't make make the area uh light up
then enemies will spawn right I just
forget yeah
have some torches actually oh okay
um yeah just scatter them all around I
guess you can take the left side I'll
take the right side
Oh you mean up there oh that's that's
that makes sense um I
I pretend I didn't do what I just did oh
yeah we need some light here
I see
[Music]
skip a few every few blocks put a torch
okay it doesn't have to be too close
together
but just in the surroundings well I mean
anytime when it's night time we're gonna
try to go to sleep anyway just to make
sure
to be safe
yeah oh
we don't want you to be attacked by
zombies do you like horror games
[Music]
it's a creeper
don't worry I'll protect you horror
games please please one I'm running
wait I shouldn't run over here though um
this one's fast
don't worry he's almost dead there we go
he died well the creepers
where the creepers you gotta be careful
because uh they if you if you you can't
fight them without having them explode
but it takes a little bit of skill
and but if they explode well then yeah
that's that's not good for the
surroundings so bad Evo ran fast or
fight them from the distance with a bow
and an overall
or let him explode somewhere where it
doesn't matter I see okay
bow and arrow that's where these came
from uh yes they have I should oh yeah I
don't I don't know I do have a number
where did I get ah From the Mob just now
all right the next time I'm just going
to shoot him down
let me look uh at my reference for one
moment
okay and you tell me if you like horror
games or not oh
I will play them do I enjoy it is it
enjoyment I feel
or is a terror
are you asking yourself questions I
I truly don't know
do I enjoy the thrill
do I like the rush
yes
I hate them
I can clearly tell you I hate them
uh was that connected to is this it's
the seven blocks is this as tall as the
other ones
uh-oh one two three four five now it is
yeah okay
uh
seven seven
uh sorry looking at my reference what's
your favorite horror game my favorite
horror game oh well I don't play many
oh
it is not a genre I have partaken in uh
often oh are you planning to I suppose I
should or could could or should Coulda
Shoulda
I've only really played
um I played pacify
pacify yeah
it's I suppose it can it yes pacify The
Pacifier
but it kind of made me laugh actually a
lot
oh yeah that one uh
how tall is this
uh it's one oh wait actually I think
it's the same
no it's not
okay this is where I'll start using
scaffolding
scaffolding is my biggest enemy in this
chest you can find uh 32 scaffoldings
please take them
first row I think
okay recently I've made friends of
scaffolding but I didn't like it for a
long time so basically let me teach you
how scaffolding works it's like a ladder
for building stuff if you place one on
the ground and you keep on aiming at the
ground
um and click one more right click to try
that on this one uh yeah but that's
that's what happens if you don't aim at
the ground it builds to the bad maze but
if you aim at the ground yes and it will
build upwards oh hello
is she streaming Minecraft today she's
online like every day
anyway so if you build upwards then uh
yeah you have to aim at the ground but
if you if you're for example up here on
the tower and you wanna like build
around the building you're really up
high and you want to build around then
you can do this or you can go this way
and see it's floating but it will stop
floating at some point and then yeah uh
have them like oh what's going on
maybe she maybe her game was booked yeah
yeah then it will it will let let the
scaffolding fall down
and then you will be able to continue
Building from here see how that works
yes anyway
you can easily get rid of it with one
left click oh sorry I think I hit you oh
you didn't but I appreciate you saying
sorry
stop yourself yes you got that okay so
now this way
I will grow up you go up by the way with
a space try that try going up uh yeah
with space and then in order to go down
you press shift
oh elevator exactly and when you put
down at the bottom you're saying you
don't need it anymore
and it all scatters easy
that's right nice so useful yeah
okay useful but for me in the beginning
it was very frustrating
um we are now going to do something with
the sand
oh I have lots of sand oh yeah can you
give me one stack
please oh would you like
ta-da
[Music]
um I think what was it Chad our stone
color is the best choice to make
something out of sand right wasn't there
one was there one here
no
I don't want to cut a Wi-Fi case there
was one uh I don't know if it's still
there oh I don't think it's there
anymore
I remember there was one over here
I don't think it's there now
no something's happening with Guna she
keeps on logging in and logging out oh
daija blue
oh
okay I think uh oh I'm gonna I think I
have the materials for a stone color
um I'll make one I think oh I didn't did
I not have one in my chocolate box
let me check
no is that is the stone cutter how they
get nice looking uh Stone like this
nice looking one stone
uh yes and it also like there's many
things that you could uh do in with the
normal crafting table
um but people choose to do it with the
stone cutter but because it saves
materials like you get more for what you
give the thing you're working with you
know what I mean I see
stone cutter needs ah one iron
[Music]
time thank you
ah cute
how do you say things
we use that a lot in kfps state Duncan
after every
um after every Super Chat so it's like
burned into the brains of my chickens
they learn German whether or not they
like it it doesn't matter
there we go okay nice
stone color I'll put that it here
and now
no pain
I have miscalculated
I have miscalculated oh yeah all right
what do I have to go with sense
funny looking oh
I should have brought my Sandstone I
thought I could just start working with
sun all right all right uh please take
uh but not not all of it uh no don't
don't don't worry about it
whoa I made one and it gives you options
uh uh uh San sandstone
we need we need a bunch of sandstone but
we need normal sand as well later so
don't don't just use it all on this now
I want to make nice move do you want me
to go grab the Sandstone I found yes get
as many as you can okay let me drop some
things off first I'll leave the sand
here
how do I get the smooth one and then
I'll leave the slabs here too
okay and I'll be back
oh it's movies
[Music]
I'm on a mission
cook ah cook Santa oh it's a cookie
Hooks and stone not the sand right what
happens here
[Music]
um
don't get lost don't look at the
chickens okay
[Music]
wait it should have been normal
we'll we'll get there we'll get there uh
if you find a bed then please sleep in
it let me know of course
I will find the closest Bed
to glue that gave up on Minecraft
oh no she didn't come back anymore
what is she streaming today
is she even streaming today
doing Minecraft every day the hype is
real but it's bad I see it
that
here I go
yes sleeping it's my favorite thing to
do oh
a member is only streaming a few hours
aha all right no Minecraft and I guess
she's just playing she wants to play
privately
are you in bed I'm in bed but good on
right now oh good I want my dad
instead of leaving a good noise I think
now is it is it the time for her to stay
oh wait I'm supposed to get my sand
that's why I'm here uh
I went to bed and was about to head back
to you before today
yeah that's why you went so far away
just to go to bed for the bed oh There
She Goes Again
[Music]
before you join the whole life with me
that you are watching some of the whole
live streams right yeah
oh
yeah who who who did you watch
gura I watched a bit of everybody oh
I mentioned before but I usually would
have
uh I have bad Focus
so it's hard for me to just focus on a
stream so streams that were uh
I feel I can do more that uh than one
thing at once
and also uh
also because she would be streaming when
I was doing other things
that I oh that can multitask what am I
doing
yes
you you and Maury stream at a bit
awkward times for myself
oh it's in here normally at this time
right now normally I don't stream I
don't start my streams at this time very
often yeah it's a bit later than what I
when I would usually stream and I guess
for you it's pretty early uh to be
streaming right
um earlier then I would usually stream
but yeah I would have been too early if
it was I think your normal time so thank
you
no thank you thank you I'm glad that we
can collab at this time yeah it's a good
time slot for me yay
I was about to run all the way back I
forgot about the pants to express
yes yes take the pencil Express and look
at all the gorgeous panties speaking of
what is the color of your your opinions
oh I forgot
did you forget what color it is and did
you forget to put on panties it could be
either
Somebody's gotta check at some point
wouldn't it be you probably that would
that would I think be most appropriate
[Applause]
the question was just a joke it's a
question I I asked all the whole talk uh
guests
important questions
but I don't care I don't care about it
you just thought you asked the important
questions and that's all that matters I
ask what the viewers want to know you
know
um yeah but why would they want to know
that though
yeah because
that information culture cultured
knowledge
okay I guess I could understand that I I
question it a lot myself but you're not
supposed to question it
um okay I will not question it I'm
supposed to question things Bible not
come on you're supposed to know things
not to question them
forgetting sometimes
[Music]
wings with you
actually I have an extra pair of wings
but but but my young powder one you are
not quite ready I'm not ready I must do
what I must to deserve such wings
could you even fly if you were given
Wings could you try
just likely not
oh
hello welcome back well thank you I
probably got the sandstone and this is
cut or uncut but it is it just says
Sandstone nice
haha okay
um how much is it you can throw it at me
oh I will throw it at you
ciao ciao oh wait that's not how you do
it um that's that's the story hold on
there
there huh
oh
Manny Manny sandstone
don't even need that much but
[Music]
I see I feel I feel a sense you are a
good candidate for teaching you some
German perhaps
cute girls trying to pronounce uh German
words it's very very small
it could go the other way
Pinky
what oh
some people get mad
oh
no how dare you how dare you corrupt my
mother tongue
oh don't worry about it don't worry
about it I think it's actually good
because people have a very
people have this image of German that
it's a aggressive language
and you are for example also gouda
uh speaking
German kind of disproves that
I think that's that that should be
enough probably for now so
I will I will actually keep that in
there follow me burp follow me okay
we go back to our little build it's
moving along nicely it's taking shape
already yeah we have just started the
most important thing will be the roof
I'm not looking forward to that oh
um
um I think if we build around like that
uh please your next mission is filling
out
and
those holes
these with these holes with the
um lift it with a smooth Sandstone uh I
have it right now I wanna give it to you
can you pick up those blocks I have them
smooth yeah and now uh please fill out
the host I will make this
so that you can go around it
such as like this
oh wait let me see yes yes
and fill out actually I made a mistake
this one is not supposed to be there
okay there it is
by the way I liked your journey stream I
was watching that a little bit
in my journey
it's your journey
it was it was so cute how you were so
worried about uh leaving the friend
whether or not it would like you you are
very considerate you should play uh
cookie yummy have you considered playing
cookie yomi oh is that the consideration
game yes I have not I would like to play
it
it's a really fun and short and simple
uh series of little games
bro oh yeah yeah bro I'm
we're streaming
in case
in case you want to say something else
but
what's
going on with your Minecraft
have you ever seen someone play cookie
yomi I've seen a compilation of oh a
single part
oh
it's very funny actually there is a
English version of the game so even if
you don't know Japanese you should be
fine
oh I probably don't know enough it could
be good practice but I also could be
completely lost
I am lost right now uh we're not lost
but I'm trying to do this okay he left
again
she's very determined
yes she wants to make it work what's
happening how broken can you game be
okay what
all right
it wants to stop you from your addiction
I'm a little I'm a little lost not lot
well not I'm figuratively lost trying to
do the scaffolding I haven't filled
enough it's just
uh no uh yes this is why I don't like it
well uh give me the ones that you have
I'll make a nice scaffolding for you
thank you you're welcome love you I
don't get it
you have to just look down at it
um well it depends how you want to place
them if you want to place them like I
just did then
yeah you just right click on on the
scaffolding several times no I think I
see
the problem is just when you're up here
already it's very difficult to keep on
building up
I have never succeeded in doing so
well now it goes all the way around so I
think it should work
cookie bye
gargoyle don't call her gargoyle
gargoyle
chat said gargoyle
[Music]
playing Minecraft all day every day I
think she's working very hard on
Atlantis right oh not Atlantis but that
that's that is that supposed to be the
the temple thingy that she's making
mm-hmm
oh I think no this one can be empty
sorry oh that one can be easy I see
I think you need a pickaxe to get rid of
that yeah got it
um yes that's it oops for now those are
filled up let me look at the next step
uh yes
yes
[Music]
yes yes yes
indeed indeed I understand all right all
right all right all right okay
okay
all right let's sleep in goo okay I'm
just gonna bring this this red bed over
here I keep on forgetting okay I'll wait
for you
okay
I am looking forward to meeting Japanese
girls randomly on our server I'm so
scared
why I haven't talked to anybody outside
of Ian
has anyone tried to like DM you and be
like Hello nice to meet you I don't
think so
not yet oh I probably die as well I am
not sure if you even speak uh Japanese
do you know like baseball conversations
[Music]
I don't trust myself
I can't form sentences fast enough for
conversation
can you introduce yourself
in Japanese
I don't know how to say hello life
English cancel inside of that
inside
is I think you would you would probably
say oh well
arrival English
Council
no no no
Namaste will made this oh
I love English Council no no
nice thank you definitely
got the point across yeah
it got to the point
why have somebody got them flowers in
here get out of here get out of here
I'll keep some coming in
[Music]
we are now going to make
no [\h__\h] what did I make sorry I brought
a bad language onto your channel have
you ever sweared sworn before on your
channel I accidentally almost said a bad
word almost okay then I took that uh
away from you your first time swearing
on your channel I swore on your channel
I'm sorry I mean
that's okay it also depends what kind of
swear
uh-huh
what you determine to be a swear well
that was what I just accidentally
said definitely does it have any other
meanings
you know like um yes yes it does it has
all the meanings oh no I mean
in a in a uh uh example I will give an
example
ass is a donkey
but it can also be used badly and [\h__\h]
is a female dog
wait ass is how is ass a donkey I can
teach you uh ask me ass is originally a
name given to a donkey
what uh a way to call a donkey
yeah so in that context it's not a bad
word
or a [\h__\h] is a female dog
but in a different context it's
something I know I know the I know the
[\h__\h] thing yeah
donkey yeah
[Music]
so so I was wondering well where did I
stand it also has a different meaning
but it's still a swear isn't it I was
wondering if it had another that wasn't
a swear maybe maybe it does maybe oh
okay
probably not
maybe not
um
well I'm looking forward to the day
where you use the word finally on your
channel for the first time I was very
close when my brain gets very scattered
it kind of comes to the Forefront
but at the moment you still are you
still have a very oops damn it no
still have a very Cecil image I respect
that do I
when I first let me tell you when I
first met you
my image of you was
say so
really
yeah and it still is you know you seem
like a very social person to me
I appear that way
yeah I do yes yes am I wrong I don't
know would you say you're not special
I don't think I'm not but I don't know
if I am
I think you say so if you say so say so
if you say so
[Music]
whoa whoa
mm-hmm yes
is there an in between
in between of say so and not say so or
is it just it is or it isn't
I think there is an
nope I don't I don't there's no in
between
but here take these fences
okay
and then you know what you're gonna do
no how did I how did I not notice that
um
I don't know how that happened but uh I
remember the more I look at this the
more I regret
um like I chose that color offense but
oh well can you they're probably not
gonna be very reasonable can you put on
the top
bro fences in the same way that I did in
the bottom row
you know what I mean are we I think
we'll have to build up with the
scaffolding
oh you're fixing that oh no thank you
okay we're just scaffolding I think it's
okay if you're not if you're right top
on the top ones you don't you can just
walk around the woods
oh
I see
yes yes
let me see if you make it correctly yes
exactly exactly that's what I want you
to do wow
there we go and I shall look at the next
step balance
[Music]
what was your first expression
impression of me then of you
when we met
yes a lot of the times when
we first were being introduced to
everyone and I was around it was super
late for you so usually you were typing
I remember like uh you girls were
um in the voice chat a lot like when it
was already like 2 A.M and 3 A.M for me
but I didn't want to miss out on any
action and I wanted to hear you guys
voices as well so I was just chilling in
bed listening in and then everyone was
talking I was just uh typing I was just
like don't ignore me I just want to
listen
but I remember uh I was really nervous
meeting everybody
and it was wasn't for a long time until
we actually heard or at least I heard
you speak
so I got over my fear with most people
with everyone else first since I heard
them but you were still the not mystery
because I know what you sound like but
I was like I haven't heard her yet
oh
so I was
like the word
for a while I was scared I was very cute
Keen is that the word
waiting
when I come up here with me
yes hello what I would like to do how
many fences do you have left I have one
one I gotta make more but uh can you uh
wait I have one I have some fences that
are the wrong color but I'll just show
you what I would like you to do
on the on the second row not the top row
uh please around the whole building
oh I want you to do this
just one okay well I first have to make
some new fences wait
for sure oh this is the wrong color
it fell down you okay
oh fences
sticks
in order to make a fence you will first
have to make a
you have to use a spruce log and make
that into Oak planks and then with the
oak planks you make the sticks
and then with the sticks and the planks
you make a fence it's very very
complicated
let's see one second my chat is
Disturbed that there is a human voice in
this song
that is royalty free but they still come
without talking about it there's a fake
audio stuck audio stuck audience
oh audience talk would have been better
I would like hearing them I I need to
figure out how to use audio saw
oh I can teach you you because we have
to use that uh Japanese version of the
site right if you don't know how to
handle it I can teach you
[Music]
I can give you a few keywords that you
can look for on the website to find what
you're looking for
[Music]
me a while to figure out
okay so I got uh
I got the fences
you have to come down yeah like that and
then you remember what I you remember
what I told you to do I remember nice
the second block
yes all around the building
[Music]
no not there
effective building
usually I build most of my things alone
so I'm glad to have someone here I mean
okay recently I've been building with my
mommy
oh yeah but before that did you say that
my mommy was playing Minecraft with me
yeah we'll see I did
she's really good at Minecraft she could
teach you as well she's not gonna become
she's not gonna come to the server
anymore oh I noticed that uh I I saw
things that were around kfp I think and
I said well you got yourself good at
building which you are but then I was
told that it was actually your mother
who did it oh it depends it depends not
everything no no the most things the
things that kfp I built the kfb I built
the chicken coop
the paper Farm we built that together my
mom told me how to build it
[Music]
if you have time
but you can't I did if you're already up
there then
finished
noise
I will inspect that in a moment
let's see if you did it correctly did I
do a good job
we'll see about that we'll have to see
good morning sunshine good morning
you didn't do the corners how do you do
the corner try to connect the corners
um by just placing it uh yeah exactly
oh I see it's very easy oh oh oh did I
do it wrong oh where did it go oh
there's oh I must fix it
I go all the way up
stay the stretch big [\h__\h]
oh shoot me out at me she's like beach
oh sorry I swore now that was not me
swear there's a female dog nearby was
there
I'm the female dog apparently wait
help
she she's like
why don't you pick me
did you turn the XLR not yet okay but
you're getting one aren't you I will it
has like all these super easy effects
and you can beep yourself
oh
[Music]
cool
yeah I'm so excited I'm a DJ
I can
I can do this I don't know what I'm
doing
and I can do
you summon the demon
oh no no no
don't swear
don't swear I can fix it
um hi hi cat
um well
yeah I feel if you if you know how to
fix it um
you're welcome to do so I'm fixing it
oops uh
oh wait that's strange
why did it do it like that
um because yeah it really matters like
how you place them
um wait uh uh I can I can place it uh
yeah you should probably do this uh
depending on the angle like the way you
placed it you were aiming at for example
the sand block but you have to aim at
the for example the bottom of the block
right below it's
[Music]
I'm learning my brain is growing
um
go get some dirt and fix this this one's
for thanks
all right good though we have so much
dirt that's
that's creeper about to try and figure
this out uh
that one time when I am not being
careful that one single time
where I'm not looking at the game
but distracted that's when he got me
there's a leaves up here
up here leaves yeah did you put those
there should I remove them
oh yeah you can get rid of them just
with your hand my hands normally the
easiest way to get rid of those are
shears but we don't have shears right
now
it's a helmet we move
a bee
I still need to yeah connect that corner
correct noise
oh a baby
hi
there are the beast in this game was so
adorable I love them they are they're
very big
oh
okay I'll check the next step Next Step
get flour to the bee
[Music]
oh it will be very thankful
beep
my friend
be it that might be like me
oh wait that's uh
okay
and next thing we're doing oh no we need
uh
the other type of wood here oh parkour
oh parkour
are you skilled in parkour perhaps I am
but also this bee is
oh
I wonder why that but you learned that
you've been watching me
are you asking to be I I don't think the
B can answer you why it's falling oh
it's so cute it's following you you
really got a friend I do it won't leave
me alone why won't you give it the
flower it obviously wants the flower I
gave it too
oh good at his back she didn't give up
it just doesn't give up
Reckless please server uh please be kind
yeah
I'm hungry
well goodbye
it just wanted me for my flower
wow wow rude that is okay next step take
these stairs
and then I give you a sample chicken
chicken over there he's watching
I have just uh one of my viewers don't
mind him okay
he's a VIP
oh oh God damn it ah we need to get rid
of this
oh
I am making friends with my audience I'm
looking at him
looking respectfully hopefully I don't
want you to harass my employees oh no no
no no no I've never you would never do
such a thing I know I'd never do
anything of this work
although they would probably have don't
mind if you harassed them
probably uh a reward for them
okay so are you are you looking for me I
am coming back to look
I'm looking now
oh
okay
one moment
um okay so I want you to come up here
and then the stairs that I just gave you
I want you oops upstairs
oh I do yeah uh how did she place that
I first have to figure out myself what
is the best way to do this okay bottom
no
oh wait was it that way
what
I wanted to be the other way around oil
okay
okay they all have to be around the
whole fencing I want them to be placed
like this now that I placed one of them
it's gonna be
relatively easy to continue them
yes good job good job you have to aim at
the very bottom of the block to continue
it uh not not quite or you could aim at
the bottom of the fence that should work
oh my God why is it lagging
just like that
oh
I'm I'm sure you'll figure out a way
I will I will figure this out don't
worry oh there you go
I'll fix the scaffolding
I'm going to die at this rate what
I have not been a good example of eating
food in Minecraft oh no you need some no
I'm fine I got my bread
mm-hmm
I have eaten
ouch did you figure it out oh no you
fell down I I'm doing it but I'm not I
haven't figured out how trial whatever a
trial and ever you will learn
I'm sure of it
I don't know around here
oh yes yes yes yes yes yes
mmm
I'll I'll do it on this side or at least
I'll try
the bottom yes yes oh this is the right
way okay I figured out a speedy wave
away
uh aim at the fence
um at the middle
middle part of the fence at the bottom
like standing right in front of it
straight in front of it uh sorry I have
to build the
[Music]
stand right in front of it oh
uh stand right stand right in front of
them look at the middle part of the
fence yeah and at the bottom of it click
right click
yes this is the best angle
it's nice to be able to teach someone
Minecraft I like this
you can do it believe in yourself
believe
oh
no
no no no no stupid scaffolding
well maybe what kind of music do you
listen to music
um
I like folk music
folk music and I like punky
pop punk metal sometimes yeah poppy Punk
metal puppy
punk what is that sounds cute oh it's so
cute isn't it uh it's cute they yell
it's people yelling in your ear they're
really mad
why do you like that that's so
surprising very uh unexpected makes me
feel alive
cool wow you like people yelling at you
interesting that makes you well now when
it's time and sleep please young lady
what
come down to sleep please all right
yeah I like when uh where's the zombie
pumpkin
I like when uh they're not yelling
really at me it's not really directed
towards me it's just I'm listening to
them as they yell
it's in my ear but I know I know they're
not actually mad at me
oh of course not what's your what's your
recommendation then for a band
of the end
um one of my favorites called The Story
So Far and I'm looking at that right now
he's he has good mad voice
a mad voice yeah that's a good yelling
mad voice
would you recommend the song A Nurse
yeah
okay I will mute my audio my desktop my
my
okay I'll mute my audio film and listen
in
person too I'm gonna mute myself
okay that includes meeting you though
um
I don't want to do that
for two seconds I'm gonna mute you just
two seconds
[Music]
oh
yeah yeah I liked it
I think I see when you said I'll mute
you know when you said like he's he
yells I thought more like of screamer
like oh yeah he's just yelling scree uh
if he wants screaming there's others
yeah
I call that a yell
you're gonna still have scaffolding by
the way raised voice ah I have five
oh damn it we need more nice okay I'll
uh we will just uh get rid of this
and then because we're done on that side
that actually sounds like something I
would listen to when I was in my not
face edgy emotori place oh yeah a lot of
Facebook it is good for the edgy face
which I'm totally not in
you're not in the edgy phase
I'm not sure what I'm not sure what
Arrow this is
hmm
it reminds me of some songs that I
listened to back in the day that were
that were a bit similar to that do you
if you ever wish to share I wonder if we
listened to similar things
what do you mean
like do you know what who
what who would you listen to back in
your edgy earrings oh uh
you could tell me privately of you so
much no it's okay one one that would
maybe fit into the genre maybe that I
can remember right now was fly leaf
I don't I think she also yelled a little
bit did she did she know
does anyone know
my child knows I don't know if I know oh
wait I'm on the right side
often though I'll uh oh no songs from
artists do not know what the artist was
I'll know a song and not know what the
song was I had a I had a double check
which song nerve was so I needed two
seconds to remember which one because I
don't remember the names because you
forgot I forgot you're in just as smart
as I am doing it uh-huh
oh wait this actually works I don't need
scaffolding what the hell whoa
[Music]
efficient I think I said half of one
side
you did a good job on me thank you did I
help
of course you're always joking
chicken let me look at my reference
while you you look at the chicken
aha
chicken
[Music]
wait don't buff up
check out buff on me now
so I'm so sick I remember that line from
Flyleaf oh man I need to listen to that
again
you know I'm getting stuck again in that
face
this chicken
I can't look at it anymore YouTube
the Rasmus
do you know have you ever heard of the
Rasmus oh
say it again
THD r-a-s-m-u-s
it's not processing
it's it's uh I guess you're probably
more of a Zoomer than I am I think I'm a
boomer I think that's the problem oh
[Music]
oh man
what are you doing Googling these things
[Music]
okay my YouTube is working
again
Okay so
we are now going to add on to that roof
wait is she looking it up right now oh I
was
oh God that's embarrassing
I I will listen after
and I don't even know like I was so
young when I said I liked that I wrote
that in like a friendship book and we
discovered it recently you know how
friendship books are right
I I had friends with books when I was
like really really really really really
young like seven eight nine or so oh my
goodness and um I found them recently
and on stream I was like reading uh
stuff that I wrote in there
which was really cute like
and and my favorite band I wrote Into
the Erasmus but I I think that I wrote
that just to like look cool to the other
people
I I like maybe one or two songs from
them but it's not like I was I was
probably more into like pop music than
the Rasmus though all right I'm
downstairs
yeah I used to do that too with
different things
wanted to impress the other cool kids
yeah cool music place just wanted to
feel accepted
yeah although I'm not sure how much more
they would expect accept me by liking
the restlessness
[Laughter]
back then which is not
you know what I guess she was yelling a
lot back then Paramore oh yeah yeah I
like she did yell a lot I think she did
have an angst uh it was it was not it
was a uh not indoor voice
I give you the following thing oh I give
you Spruce slabs wait not only one I'll
give you all of them and what are you
going to do and you are going to go up
there and add it onto the stairs all
around the building all around to the
stairs yeah just elongate elongate the
roof I suppose let's see if you'll get
what I'm trying to say
like aim at the bottom of the stair
exactly yes good luck with that and I'll
look at the next step
I'll just go down
oh my god
there that goes all the way around yeah
[Music]
beautiful beautiful
okay I'll do that step now
how many do I have oh not enough
myself
you okay
yes I remember learning how to balance I
was I was just reminded by my chat if I
press shift then I won't fall
oh yes yes that's very useful yeah I
didn't remember that I built a lot with
shift usually
especially when you build in a very
um dangerous uh on a cliff or something
like that or in the end
where there's literally only Cliffs and
Islands
that's where that really comes in handy
[Music]
nice I'm going to remove the scaffolding
usually when I build roofs I get really
frustrated but I don't know if it's
because you were here but I feel
nice I feel calm I feel like
because I was going I'm really
frustrated by because you're here I'm
like I know I make the process slower no
the opposite oh I'm glad I'm enjoying
this is like therapy
I was very worried that uh I was gonna
slow you down a lot
no because you had to show me you don't
let me down you're helping me
at least I don't have to do everything
alone slow down in a not bad way
yeah okay I did all the collabs like
slow poke hello
okay I'm going to
hurt don't Stone breaks I need Stone
break stairs next build all the way
around
[Music]
and then with a stone break half block I
elongate it again okay that's those are
the next two steps let's sleep first oh
yes
it's about time
here I can't keep track when she's here
or not oh that doesn't mean much
has she not been kicked oh yeah right oh
no she has been kicked a million times
but but it has she been too bad
this game is game okay
um
I can't remember how long she's been
here without leaving
what am I doing oh yeah uh
do I need stones or cobblestones for
that let's see I am here
okay
I will play they cannot stop me
oh man
I wonder if she's like looking up on the
error message on Google or so trying to
help herself
I would love to help but
did I actually have something like that
getting kicked out of Minecraft I wonder
okay
Next Step ume yes I give you
and these stairs downstairs
oh
we go all the way up to the roof
oh yes
here we're locked off now I'll gather
some scaffolding for you
thank you you can take it I'm not very
good at using it behind you actually no
don't worry I'll bring it to you and and
do it to your face
ready yeah I already have enough I
already have enough oh yes okay
I'll take
over here
[Music]
while the roof is really getting bigger
and bigger let's just
build here
get up here
oh
[Music]
okay so the stairs
um please build them where I stand right
now along this fence and the blocks okay
facing this looking at the same they
were exactly at the same direction that
though
the wooden blocks
and I will
add on to that with oh
no
no it's for making such a beautiful roof
wow
wow did I
oh no I didn't okay
women do you have any like any goals
what to build in Minecraft in the future
is there anything you want to do I want
to make a tree house where I can live oh
I'm kind of homeless right now
well you want to live in a tree like an
Alex
Woods
good idea I think Daryl there's like
plenty of tutorials on how to build a
treehouse you could look on YouTube for
some Inspirations and then either copy
it or just take some inspiration and
then build your whoops sorry build your
own thing
I did see some tutorials and I wasn't
sure
if I I wasn't sure what that was my
etiquette is if you can just build it
based off of
tutorials because I would that's totally
what I'm doing right now
I'll do that too
um what would be nice and what I will be
doing afterwards is adding the video
that you used as inspiration uh to your
uh description that's generally a very
very appreciated oh
[Music]
I saw some really cool looking ones and
I thought I wanna I wanna do that
I'm sure you can do it treaty house
seems I mean it depends how how Grand
you want it to look
but just I'm sure you can do it I want a
home
oh
sorry I'm looking at the video okay I
think I understand
um
uh how do I get up there now
God damn it uh
also oh oh
ah here I come
hello hello let's get on the roof and
now this this part is a little bit
difficult to explain so just watch what
I'm doing like this and let's just relax
I guess I guess you could do the same
thing on the other side
um another stairs all right I give you
some some slabs oh they are slabs
thank you we'll place them on the other
side the same way I'm placing them
oh
ah you have to aim at the top and once
you build one you can just aim at the
slab
[Music]
yeah nice
and oops now I'm missing somebody ah do
you still have some stairs I do I have
29.
oh nice
can you right click on it that gives me
half yeah if you right click on the
little stack thank you
I have received now if I understand
correctly
like this we continue
facing outwards exactly oil fast
you'll be fast
I remember
think you have potential to become a
Minecraft Master just like me oh
so you be nice to be good at something
I don't know what I'm doing you're good
at drawing I saw that and I'm like it's
so cute are you sure I saw how you drew
Reina
she should draw a phoenix as well yeah I
was actually wanting to draw all the
hollow birds at some point yes
you I wasn't sure uh uh Phoenix please
okay
[Music]
sometimes I just get a little confused
okay for you that's a excuse I will buy
you
still have some slabs I have five
oh maybe try to do the same thing that I
just did uh oh wait no I have seven
slabs
oops continue on here
but now I made a block oops
swing it I messed up a single one and
I'm doing it oh
no I gotta go get them will I die from a
never mind um
I'm finishing it up but do you still
have stairs or do I need to make new
ones I have five stairs
yeah I think we need a little bit a
little tiny bit more for now maybe later
even more
this is how you make roofs
okay there's
and then
um
[Music]
oh that's me I see my shadow
you get entertained by Shadows it's cute
son he
son the son is responsible
ah
I need I need
okay I'm coming back up there are you up
there I'm up again
little trees
are there any any sapphires from Whole
Life Japan that you want to collab with
of any and everybody
that's gonna take a while not even I
have accomplished that yet
I uh
I'm very nervous too because of the
language barrier
yeah some have already made it work even
with the language to everyone if if you
collab with hachama you don't have that
issue because she speaks really good
English yeah
speaks good English yes if a God if they
speak to me like I am uh six months old
then maybe beautiful work
well then you'll have to speak to them
as if they're six months old as well I
think they'll actually understand
because they also they're very eager to
understand and communicate with us so
yeah they like to use a deep l
oh yeah that's a good one I think
I never used it but yeah
you don't have to
[Music]
yeah
oh interesting interesting yeah I think
right I think it's supposed to be more
uh less it will translate things less
formally
uh-huh so we have one slab for me one oh
I still have I have two
hit me please there you go oh
where did it go oh it's over there over
on the other side oh
nice throw it over
oh
you could do
you could try like you could do a
drawing collab maybe with maybe even
with mine in Tampa for example like like
when she collapsed with uhuda and Ina
she kept on using deep L and it kind of
worked kind of worked so
oh you shouldn't you shouldn't already
give up on it you should give it a try
it'd be cool if we could uh draw
pictures too to explain what we're
trying to say
yeah oh yeah or something like that oh
yeah that's right if you do a drawing
collab you can communicate by drawing as
well yeah if it shares the canvas thingy
hmm
I wonder could that work there's also
games where generally in the
communication doesn't really matter that
much anyway so right
hmm
I would love to
you I want to okay and there's there's
some
uh
on the roof I have to make some kind of
decoration
and to go to a idle meeting question
mark is that what you call it yes good
luck with that oh thank you I will be
back in approximately two minutes
all right I'll be waiting I'll be
building yeah go ahead don't you don't
delete for me go ahead okay I'll be
right back
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
like a bird she eats scenes I need to
step up my burp game I see yeah I need
to eat more bird food stuck in my teeth
oh my chat didn't actually hear I ate
sunflower seeds that's what happened
could you please
um move a little bit oh
um
where am I oh hi
hi thank you what have you done oh I'm
making the the edges of the roof look
fancy
yeah I I will do the same with the with
the wooden part as well actually
I think
sure and then get rid of the bottom one
there we go okay the top part is done
now into this
ear
but I don't have Spruce UPS okay I'm
going down
yeah slabs are there's a half half
blocks
you're still
I need just just a couple ones
[Music]
there you go that's probably enough
I think
for sure have you ever seen a Shinto
Shrine before
hmm
I've never been into one I've only all
seen them from outside
I'm pretty common though usually as a
normal tourist you wouldn't really go
inside of those
oh yeah
[Music]
get rid of that get rid of that
and then
build onto here
it was nice I think yeah oh you might
have to get rid of on the bottom one
after I go down
one two
get rid of this get rid of that
[Music]
um
there we go
does that mean you have
visited the Glorious nipple lamp before
I have visited
oh when was oh maybe I shouldn't ask you
don't have to
I visited a few times I only remember
the most recent ones but I visited back
and you know
like 300 years ago too 300 years ago
that's a long time ago yeah I just don't
remember that was very different back
then
I think it changed a lot since 300 years
ago oh what I might want to go check it
out again yeah
go take a look see
what was your
favorite part of Japan then
um any any area that you really liked a
lot any City or is part of the city in
most recent years I've only been to
Tokyo
but I really want to go to different
parts did you go to Harajuku island
did you eat crabs
did I I know I remember seeing them for
sure it's like the
the typical food if you go to Harajuku
especially
oh everyone takes uh purchases a crab
I don't think I got I know I got one
when I was in Japan but I don't think I
got one when I was in how to do
collection
it's so crowded there's so many people
when I went through so many people
there's so many crab places but they all
have like endless lines at least on the
weekend you should really go to Harajuku
and takeshadori when it's not the
weekend or even better if you catch a
weekday uh when it's raining then you
will have you know oh yeah
that makes sense I think you know what
if my memory serves me correctly
I didn't actually get uh one
yeah I'm not Street
I got one in a I think it was a
department store nearby oh but honestly
craps I've eaten that in a lot of places
in Japan and they all are magical no
matter where oh yeah I like the egg
strawberries a lot so I really like
getting them or the pancakes
special thing about crabs in Japan in
case somebody in the chat doesn't know
they are not like typical French crabs
no they like top it with a millions of
things yeah
um but like a lot of whipped cream and a
lot of fruit and sauces and sometimes
they even put cake in the crap they put
like cheesecake cheesecake inside of the
crab it's crazy I haven't had that yeah
that's crazy
yeah apparently you have to care we have
to get rid of that part
and and I have no I don't have okay see
there's a lot of like small adjustments
right now that's uh why it's a bit
difficult to tell you and instead I'm
just gonna try to get through those
parts right now that's okay I'm enjoying
watching it develop but you know what
you could do in theory oh in theory
so the I think you could for example try
to build the path oh
it has the somewhat specific pattern
though oops oh dear
um so from
where are you I'm here okay from here
where I just built a Hole uh made a hole
um to here so at the very edge
and then all the way down the stairs
maybe maybe oops maybe until oh this
point
um
foreign okay our stuff will be in the
way but when you reach that point we'll
just move it okay and that point
wait
cool yeah my thing is really strong it
is strong it is like three at once
wow I can't do more than that
so I'll [\h__\h] is it bless oh how do you
say it oh how do you say it uh
you're welcome I was blinking I was
trying to say you're welcome
foreign
[Music]
oh wait
yes
oh what the hell
out here
here okay so you see you see the outline
of yeah I do
um get rid for now get rid of every like
the the most top row
of all of this up until that point you
know because we're gonna replace each
block with an actual path block Okay so
everything within
the top block here like this
uh and then everything inside of that
too like so
okay so everything in here do you want
me to move these things over
yeah you can you can do that yeah but
the problem is actually no no because
the boxes if you if you open and they
will scatter everything but you can get
rid of the blocks underneath without
moving it
like like so
yeah so just well you need help let me
know but we should sleep first all right
sleepy
we're making a stone path yeah and with
different kinds of stones uh we actually
I would appreciate if we could get some
more gravel wait could I still in the
game actually she managed to stay online
yeah
but gravel is a little bit of a pain in
the butt to get sometimes oh it is it
hurts yeah
so okay you know you have a mission you
have a mission let me know if you need
help
I'm slightly confused about the uh
here it's like here I get rid of this
but
like what do I do with over here ah just
the top block so all the top okay I see
this one and then this one and then this
one I understand
okay I gotta melt some Stones okay
some cobblestones
oh wait could I not
milk
traditional
I'll need way more than that
okay
gravel would be nice is there a specific
area where gravel appears the most
checked help me out here
this is gravel
I'll take that
give me
mountains there's a gravel Mountain wait
where do cold
it says gravel right here what is this
oh if you found gravity can put it in
the chest I'll use it later oh no
problem I get them confused
I don't really want to look for that
right now on the map ooh but I can't I
can fly around a little bit see if I
find something quickly
gravel Mountain that sounds uh like
something special
what about here is there gravels most
no no gravel
gravel are you gonna oh what I found
presents that's awesome oh and you found
a bunch of gravel nice
wow easy
has no one ever seen that one before
I found gold mermaid gold gold
I still haven't even found gold gold
blocks of course you haven't you haven't
have barely played this game that's true
I must learn how to mine I kind of know
but I'm very scared I keep running into
trouble I found gold without mining
though that's the thing what
sometimes you just find it in the middle
of nowhere but you must you must be a
traveler an adventurer yeah I see
and then this to the goddess of
traveling and adventuring will bless you
with treasures
and valuables what if they if she finds
you worthy that is
I
I'm happy I don't know if I'm worthy you
will be soon young Padawan I will be
I will be
I'll train you
Now train me let me get that gold
no
[Laughter]
okay I'm okay I'm driving to Lava
because I thought it was gold see this
is when when you get too greedy that
that's what happens shiny
shiny shiny things
must follow the shiny thing woman you
understand me oh I I absolutely relate
yes
shiny sometimes people just don't
understand yeah that's how I ended up
taking your stuff before
Oh wait that was actually you yeah I was
in a village and I I wasn't sure if it
just spawned if I was just lucky and I
said oh I'll take it and then you were
missing stuff and I realized
why is that so huge
though oh that's huge
so tall this chat did not no I I
accidentally stole her prized
possessions
yeah like uh never right
it's okay as an as a real beginner of
course you don't know that kind of stuff
I saw shiny now you know pretty shiny
shiny like I can tell you everything in
that Village you were in is self-made
and not naturally created yeah I took a
few other things I didn't I didn't cross
I was like well this is a really nice
Village
yeah I actually the story behind that
Village is uh
I
I was starting to play Minecraft with
Callie and we explored the area around
the spawn point trying to find like the
area that we could live in
and We Came Upon This nice Village we
looked inside looked for some Treasures
and the thing is and this will be a good
lesson for you for the future if you go
to a village
um and like take everything down and all
that or just by simply entering that
Village
um you might uh be creating their death
scene at this very moment
because oh yeah and there's like there's
like pillagers not Villages there's
pillagers that will go to that Village
after you have been there and they'll
they'll attack them and then they'll
kill them all and they yeah they will
not recover from that
oh so you're taking their resources and
then they die that's like that's just
down that but that's just kind of like
the natural thing that you do uh when
you play Minecraft you find villagers
and you take what they have
uh and it is a total totally natural and
normal process this happens
it happens it happens it is the nature
of humans
it is it is the nature of Minecraft
players
a Minecraft
craft yeah
um actually I didn't get a bunch of
gravel I would wouldn't mind having a
little bit more for a new civilization
to form another Must Fall
right that is that sounds so wise
thank you
no don't no I don't want
I'm gonna look around that stuff when
you are back let me know and I will run
oh yeah wait but actually I forgot to
finish my storage oh yeah
uh so uh uh
uh basically
so basically
uh what I was trying to say is uh
basically
yes wait does this automatically turn
into clay no I still get the gravel
right okay
so we destroyed it
because I'm also very last yes
so we kind of like uh ended up killing
everyone in that Village accidentally
without knowing it you know
um and at some point I I came back to
that Village and I think I'm not sure
what my exact motivation behind it was
but I think I just felt sorry and
um wait does Jack know what was my first
motivation of for Reviving The Village I
just decided that I wanted to revive the
village I don't know why
um but I made it my mission so I brought
Villages from somewhere else into that
destroyed
Village uh-huh
yeah
I built it back up from scratch
and I I raised a lot of villagers and
then I gave them jobs and I made it into
a really really valuable thing on This
Server wait what's
extended I
Phoenix 10 was a different village so
when I came upon the actual Phoenix 10 I
thought it was a randomly spawned
Village
oh so that's where I don't know if they
found an egg
oh
no no
[Music]
um
naturally spawned villagers look way
simpler than that yeah because that one
was insane yeah at the time when you
joined and looked at Phoenix then it was
already pretty pretty evolved I started
that's when I started the renovations
actually
oh that's that's definitely not natural
but in the future you will you will have
an eye for that in the future I'm sure
of it I will no longer take shiny things
from chess let's say unless you didn't
you didn't break it or anything yeah I
didn't I didn't used it at all right
I can explain to you why that never ride
pickaxe is so special
um so there's a
um there is a wooden tools right
and then there's stone tools then
there's iron tools in that order that's
how they get better iron tools and then
diamond tools right and then you can all
build them with uh wood and the the
material like diamond board iron and so
on but never right pick axes or or or
accents or shovels there you can't just
mine never rides the same way as
diamonds or iron or all that I mean you
could you can but it's like so it's a
really really rare material and once you
have the net never right you build onto
the pickaxe the diamond pickaxe that you
already have by adding the netherride to
it but the never ride is really so
freaking rare and even if you find it
you like that one piece of netherride it
will not uh
be enough for one pickaxe you need so
much of it oh really there's a lot what
is this place really hard to make
cool lives here
but I found Anna's house wait I was just
I was just there
are you close by I just left I'm lost
it's really near oh yeah I'll guide you
you know the way back yeah it's super
close by and sleeping fun is better you
want to join me is there enough room
oh because that's good at sleeping oh oh
you're coming oh here I am
seems like good I was playing normally
right now whoa yeah she's not getting
good for her good for her
yay
so yeah devil red is just really really
hard to come by uh I will follow you now
oh okay
it's really hard to come by and it's
very precious so never at pickaxe it's
really something you would get in the
very very
late part of playing Minecraft I see
[Music]
is that if you throw your oh and we're
so close yeah if you throw your never
ride pickaxe or whatever into lava it
will not melt will not disappear oh so
if you accidentally die from lava you
can go save it
yes that's very normally you will lose
it all but in this case you will not wow
wow it's a great job movement oh I did
it right
oh man
oh I just need to do the same thing here
on the top level but the stairs already
look amazing so I do it on the top just
leave these two
and uh no you can get rid of the what's
underneath as well wow okay
nice nice my helper is being very very
useful
let's see sure
oh here
he's doing it correctly
[Music]
what's that
no
um
uh I will then
show you how the path should look like
let me pick up my stone by now it should
be nicely melted
Stone how you doing
yeah looking good oh I got way too many
materials what do I do
okay
me yeah oh don't don't mind me I'm
coming back in a moment okay
do I have more
no okay
okay okay
I'm running back
hello hello
how are you doing mermaid is everything
all right I'm doing swell how are you
as well as well
you're doing swell
so well swell
I've never heard of that
is this how they oh I don't know when
people speak uh that's how some strange
people may speak
okay uh let me look at the ground
pattern
um
oh
okay uh
[Music]
ah
okay okay uh
come with me to the Top Welcome to the
Mountaintop
welcome to the Mountaintop hell yeah
you should give wrapping a try I I I
wonder how that would go
see and this part
um only those free
and the row of three all the way to the
bottom I want you to feel with gravel on
the inside on both sides exactly I'll
give you that
and in the meantime I'll see what else
I I'm supposed to
do this
um
Challenger
by the way is uh
is a um
it's in yellow but I'm a little worried
I'll keep an eye out on it though
I will be fine it'll be fine okay I
actually I used that was that used to be
my favorite pickaxe but nowadays I have
a better one but never I think
well we don't want it to break so tell
me before when it gets into the red area
that's when you should tell me okay I'm
sorry where how far did you say to do
the gravel ah all the way ah two yes all
the way down here okay
I might run out
oh I have still some more I'll put it in
the I'll put it in the chest okay
there's oh yeah there's a bunch of
gravel in here
some more
[Music]
one two
trying to make this as accurate as
possible
[Music]
yes
okay hopefully that's enough I need to
stay here
bless you
thank you soon
[Music]
would you like to sign up for some super
special 101 private German lessons that
are not so private because they're gonna
be watched by an audience who are you
offering
I am offering free lessons yeah you're
taking new students
yes yes I would be interested
[Music]
I wish to learn
what is dude would you would you be
would you be seriously committed to it
yes
I'm gonna take it seriously yeah I'll do
homework oh
I believe that and you say that I
believe it you have to practice every
day otherwise you'll lose it yeah lose
your polish okay I don't I don't expect
from you to practice every day I'm
actually get uh flew into the language
unless you want to become better soon
foreign
[Music]
what else did I learn today
yeah
one thing that I always say at the end
of my streams is uh I'll Vida scene it's
goodbye I'll feed us
yeah they say that in that song
oh the uh oh what is it sounded music
yeah I'll say something I like it The
Sound of Music Of course oh
of course you have
I'm not even surprised
[Music]
you see it properly
you know what you know what Elvis is
right I think people know even though
they don't speak German
I thought it was a place
oh no it's the flower
oh our national flower in in Austria
it's a flower it's a yeah now our
national flower
I want okay I'm gonna google it
um
on on like on the mountains on top of
the mountains
did you know
flower sorry I can't say it like crony
flower
oh
hello hello
[Music]
[Laughter]
sounds amazing oh thank you
[Music]
what is that voice I've been working on
it I call it the Hang kill voice
but what voice Hank Hill
he's like hell he's a character from an
adult cartoon called King of the Hill
King of the hell and he has an adult
cartoon yeah hey what kind of stuff are
you looking at not that it's a place on
TV it's on the television that was so
shocking that I fell down
it's all the time it's on the Telly the
television on the deli they say they say
you're cultured though my chat says your
culture I'm a culture hey it's so pretty
it's something it's not a good show
Mommy
this is not exactly how I should build
it what are you doing I wasn't even
paying attention
um building the entrance roof thingy I
mean it seems all right
uh-huh
okay well that's why they're called
Teletubbies
Teletubbies I was watching that does
that make me culture I think that makes
you very portrayed I don't think
that
which one was your favorite Teletubby
I'm gonna be honest I can't recall their
names right now I also don't remember
them okay no no no no no no listen
ing
[Music]
that's how you that's how you remember
their names
am I not missing one
[Music]
and I mean at least in German that's
their names I think it's the same
definitely think you definitely mean he
definitely Lala definitely pull
yes that's dumb shall we sleep
there are four oh Tinky Winky that's
just a long name
I'll sleep
I'm surprised they have the same names
in English
thank you because in English it oh in
English it doesn't uh doesn't really
it doesn't mean the same thing but I was
also always as a child I was very
confused about uh one of their names the
the red one called pool I felt
embarrassed about that or was I was like
always giggling every time I heard the
name because Paul is but in German and I
was always laughing at that and his name
is butt
that is they didn't even change it
did they know what they were doing
um I think they knew especially because
of the kids show they're obviously gonna
laugh about those stupid things
it's called the butt
buttons
it's it's a childish way of saying oh
but
ah in German like booty or a more a more
facial way
[Music]
but how most people do say it is Ash
it's also a very common way to
um insult people we do say that a lot
Ash and ashlo
I feel uncomfortable swearing oh am I
swearing oh
they just they just mean things
way worse things in German than that way
worse
oh go get that call but don't don't get
don't get hit by the zombies
shallow in here I hope there are none
um I'm hopeful they're around
sorry this is the part that I'm doing
right now is again very detailed but
I'll tell you how to continue the path
oh
I am good at entertaining myself if uh
well this game is just as hard to not do
of something
but don't Don't Stray off too much don't
go too far away okay I'm coming back yes
good amount of coal
okay hello the the first roll next to
the gravel row on the inside yes
it shall be filled
not with that
what stone is that seven wait I have to
test it out okay normal
Stone
no it's not
oh wait do I just oh wait would that
have been much smarter oh would I not
have to melt it it's like oh oh I've
just had a revelation oh all right but I
want a specific Stone how do I get that
type of stone
revelation
no
that's not the stone that I want I want
the the one that has a little border
around it if you place it with one next
to another what are you guys polished
and decide oh hell no I don't want to
use that side ah no this one
is
do I get this one by I think this might
be it
or is it smooth on the side
do I have and the site somewhere I'm
gonna quickly
fly over to my home
[Music]
do you think I'm cool that was the
coolest thing I've ever seen
I'm not even sure what I just saw
how you saw a bird flying it's only
natural
fly
oh wait what's this nature
I could use slabs
I guess or could yeah I could use slabs
what is this
smooth stone slab yeah that would
probably
be fine
what did you guys say
the rep wait do you want do you know
which video I'm looking at Chad
I guess some of you know
I think I'll just I'll just take this
polished oh
I mean it looks
similar
it smells I'll just cook it again yeah
I do have some medicine but no I will
not be using that okay
I'll just cook it again and wait do I
have some more coal here brownie chance
but wait wait for me I'll come back in
an instant oh I'm well I'm watching okay
flying fly you fools
have you do you like Lord of the Rings I
haven't
thought of the Rings
oh why it's really long
what it's it's the best movie ever oh I
landed far away from you probably didn't
see it oh well I see you now
I've seen the Hobbit
oh the Lord of the Rings is actually
better than The Hobbit but
interesting you've seen the Hobbit
before watching uh Lord of the Rings
interesting this is interesting
I should watch there's quite a few
movies that people often say You must
watch that I haven't watched oh you have
to watch it you have to I'm very open to
this it's so good but um do you like
like fantasy movies
then you will love it it's so good it's
such a classic
yeah yeah
oh what are you doing I'm I'm mining but
with my silk touch pickaxe see I will
tell you the difference
but you're going that way you've seen me
here up here oh you're you're showing me
sorry I got distracted yeah let me see
I'll show you something nice okay see
currently I carry a pickaxe that has
sick touch enchantment on it if I mind
this block or try to mine it with your
own pickaxe
once you get out of that looks different
from what you just mined doesn't it it's
called it's called Cobblestone yes now I
give you this pickaxe try to try to mine
it with this pickaxe
okay
oh
it's simply
Stone it's a different Stone right it's
exactly what you see in front of you
that's what you get oh this is with silk
touch you can mine certain things and
get something else from it yes yes
that's useful if you don't want them the
other thing
and actually you will need a silk touch
pickaxe to mine for example an Ender
Chest you cannot mine an interest and
Ender Chest without a pickaxe I mean you
can end but it will break so for some
things you will need a silk touch
pickaxe oh there's so much to keep track
I feel so smart
there's a lot of knowledge in that
Noggin
let me teach you Council of knowledge
Council of collection of the knowledge
or whatever
it's a very long name
I I'm not even I don't even remember
what it was that sounds about right
oh that's not what I'm supposed to do
look at that I'll I'll give you a new
job in a moment I'm just trying to
collect the stones for that
and then I have to melt them which will
take a little while oh how long have it
been for free two and a half hours okay
we're doing good we're doing good
I think I will give a heads up that I do
run on a battery
that all cannot be recharged yet oh
don't worry don't worry but it's good
for now good for now it in worst case
I'll finish this uh off off screen
tomorrow or do a gorilla
um uh Minecraft stream to Miller worst
case you're sure
Chris on the 30th is the deadline for
all of these buildings I wonder I mean
that's probably not like a scandal if
someone doesn't get finished with their
build but
probably preferred if everything is
finished then then they're gonna
swarm in here right we want it to look
nice smooth Stone hell yeah
all right let's add those in here let's
grow
you're doing a good job at being a boob
thank you
I'm proud of you one of the few things
that come effortlessly for me I'm so
happy to have you I'm happy to be here
foreign
yes
this is something crony's building
yeah
oh yes she is doing the museum it's
confusing because I think I saw you
right on Discord you want to build a was
that you yeah but I don't know how I had
no idea where to start it would not have
gotten done in time so her building one
is works out very well but did she tell
you she was feeling well or did you just
assume oh uh my bird wants to have a
museum I'll get going I really don't
know was it supposed to be a surprise I
heard you and the crony are like like a
cute couple or something like like you
do a lot of things together and you're
taste together and so it would just be
really cute if crony without saying
anything hears that you want a museum
and then the next thing she does is
build a museum
uh oh
that's just cute uh oh is this supposed
to happen What Happens cry
that I stumbled in here I can't be a
surprise you would have to do a better
job at hiding that huge thing yeah I
wouldn't I would have wandered up to it
eventually as I did
yeah I wonder what she
I don't know or maybe she really did
just have also the idea to make cookies
well maybe she reads your idea and then
she forgot that she that you wrote that
and she just on the next day she was
like I want to build a museum being like
influenced without knowing it oh yeah
that could happen and she thought it was
her own idea yeah that could have So
Many Factors I'm Laura I'm glad she made
it though because I would not have done
it in time and it would not have looked
this nice this looks really nice
at museum is a quite a commitment I mean
feeling it uh out inside with paintings
is not difficult yeah as I told you yeah
[Music]
I can show you how that works by the way
I think that one didn't have paintings
inside already or no there's a single
very big painting in there rule from
which painter da Vinci da Vinci actually
I can't I can't remember Angelo I don't
remember what it looked like let me
check
wait what's DaVinci on hardest
okay DaVinci was many things
yeah right he invented he had ideas yeah
he was smart he was very very big brain
oh I'm not sure actually what I might
ever live up to that
all right I think soon I think I have
enough stones
I don't know what this is
not a pink one it's a painting of a
skeleton I need to protect my
Burger is attacking my
business don't worry it's just it's just
it's flat
so now I can teach you how that works by
the way
oh so you have this item a painting it's
an empty painting it's empty now if you
place that for example here look
oh it's different oh we're all right
okay it doesn't look like what um well
let's look look uh if I do this and this
I close it off I put the painting there
and it looks like this it gets uh more
narrow what it's a bit so I don't know
who it is it's a man now it's a guy it's
a person a person
yeah but if I if I do where's my yeah
where's my there it is if I get rid of
the block and I place that block one
next to it like here
oh I'm sorry I had to place it above
again uh here now it's so on fire
yeah it's some dude
and even and now same shape but
different painting so it's different
it's a randomized
now what's this again
yeah so there's all kinds of shapes and
all kinds of paintings
now we try to get the Skeleton Man again
the placement is off isn't it was that
the scout
oh
here was it there there oh
birthday cake or something like that no
that's not a birthday cake
it looks like it it is it looks like one
but it's not inside it's yeah it's a pop
it's it's a Donkey Kong game
oh oh now I made a list shape
because I placed it at the very top
Donkey Kong is it it's a Donkey Kong it
is
Chad says it is
[Music]
well it wasn't placed like this I you
know what
um black crony
uh remember that's up to her to remember
because if it's this size it will never
be perfectly in between I think that's
right okay okay let's get out of here oh
don't tell her that okay don't let her
do this
she built the whole museum for you I
don't think she will mine
oh
[Music]
the art and one day when I am good at
building maybe I can do a natural
history I saw one when I was looking up
uh I was looking up
Minecraft museums and people created
entire
dinosaur skeletons on display for a
museum
it's like a lot of work yeah
I don't think I could do that but maybe
something kind of like that
oh
[Music]
what will she do oh what will she do
all right so
um yes
um
[Music]
I guess we can use the full stone okay
I'll give you
this
stack of uh Stones you take I have it
you follow me I follow
and then oh this place did you run out
of gravel I think this needs still to be
filled up with gravel I simply forgot
and then afterwards
and please do these
all the way to the bottom okay but only
on only one row on each side see
yeah and all I really have to figure out
what the hell I was doing I forgot again
what was I doing
uh
oh dear I did it
oh that was fast
I'm getting used to it
uh okay next step
inside of that
uh I think is brick stairs and Bricks
now the video stop loading again
I'm pretty sure it is that's what I just
said perfect
whoa
[Music]
I need more of
oh
yes no
um
no
I need to mine some more of those fancy
stones
huh
needs more light
a BRB I'll get some more Stones okay
really need to make a a Trader that
trades
Diamond silk touch pickaxe or just an
enchantment for a silk touch
that would be nice
to one day
talking about Phoenix then by the way oh
um I need to keep on improving Phoenix
then
to get the economy running
economy
yeah good ahead has been using Phoenix
then but unfortunately
she has a hard time finding things
because it's under renovation
oh by the way I've noticed when I was uh
in Phoenix 10 yesterday evening that
Shawn Mendes has lost his name tag and I
honestly don't know how the hell that
would happen
any idea a chance
that's why gouda couldn't find him
because she was looking specifically for
someone with a nametag but he lost his
name tag explained that to me Minecraft
why do you keep on taking things away
from me
yeah isn't that weird yeah
yeah yep yep it's really weird
Minecraft is trolling me a lot
gosh hi
he died
no he didn't I didn't have a second guy
was mending
there's no way
oh
I'm really sure
but he wouldn't lose his name though he
might lose his profession but not his
name
there are too many guys really well then
maybe Shawn Mendes really died
okay
[Music]
next suitable oh this is probably not
not quite enough but for now here take
these I take and take these take them
and with the blocks
you can fill up this area for now uh
okay that one yeah yep yeah
and when you reach the stairs you use
the stairs oh let's see if you can
figure that out oh not there so that's
where a stair will go
[Music]
here uh no no not one above I understand
so
they're here
oh
you're doing it you're so fast
I can't even find what I'm supposed to
do
all right
[Music]
how long is your battery by the way that
you talked about
um
I actually I am not sure uh
it's it's so battery bad if battery's
zero then I die if battery goes to 20
then I fall asleep sometimes oh so
battery's at 32 percent
32 wow that's that's already pretty low
where you were 100 when you started or
already below I was at 100 when I
started
[Music]
what battery man it's a bit short and I
I thought I ordered you don't have
stamina I didn't know I thought I
ordered something to increase my stamina
but it never arrived so I have to order
it again
oh what is that and then it's your drink
or coffee an extension cord
extension
or no you're speaking riddles to me not
an extension cord yeah
I don't know what I don't know uh
that video so many things happening I'll
just do something else right now there's
not enough Stone
yes I I was I I thought that that would
happen so let me get some more
Okay so
a charger
but charger that
can go places other charger cannot go
what is your charger
it's not long enough
is your charger your your bed
charger is my
um
nutrients
my food food yes
so that I can continue on
BP is visiting
riddle riddle
oh this is literally just a b there is a
bee in the temple it has left
you speak in riddles I give you 32 more
blocks I hope it's enough oh yes of
course yes it's enough
oh let me just fill that up
yeah okay
um wow
wow it is difficult to do like to to
tell you what to do about showing you
what to do but look at it what I would
do and do that by the time that I looked
at the video what I would do you're
gentle I have to look at the video again
to see what you would do
that's okay
although I could give you the do you
think do you think by watching the video
you could figure out what to do
[Music]
I might be able to
try I guess I could try but it could be
things where again you need explanation
that's why I've been trying to teach you
everything uh with my words
uh let me I'll take a look-see and I
don't have much time in my current state
of being uh left anyway so yeah I can
just look and you can do what you gotta
do and I'll see if there's anything I
understand that I can do we don't we
don't have to finish it though today
also okay
no stress but uh yeah in that video
maybe go towards the end
um the path is pretty much
done no oh you know
[Music]
the 20 gate would be really easy but we
don't have to um it only have a little
bit of the red concrete maybe in the
video you can find the the the point
where they build the 20 gates it's at
the very end
yes that I will go to it let me see oh
where'd it go oh there it is
I'll try to make some more red concrete
I think I figured out what I need
I need gravel and sand and the dial I
have that my first time making concrete
I'm learning too
[Music]
yes so let's hear this never rack no I'm
not gonna use never rack for that that's
ugly
already
gravel sand
I'm watching
why is it not automatically doing it
so fast
am I doing this outside
of me
black there it is
what do you need the two black two black
oh something black
wait a second with the red concrete
powder
how do I make it into actual concrete
I put water on it I place it and I put
water on it
oh that's so annoying this is why I
don't like making concrete okay yeah
we are
in in the shock box the white box here
there's four buckets
I see them go fill that go fill it up
with water there's some water here okay
no I guess wait a second no don't do
that I don't know can I just place it in
here
[Music]
I'm placing concrete powder in the water
and it turns into concrete oh
I vomit
oh there's some stuff away
wow
I have a full inventory
mummy can you pick up that concrete
that's on the ground
[Music]
where is it
ah here sorry
[Music]
okay is there any black
ah I'm wondering if they're using uh
what exactly are they using there
it's some type of very dark
the video doesn't know from uh we could
also just uh I could put a placeholder
Maybe
uh yeah for now just put some wood there
and I'll I'll put the black concrete
there later on
okay
um
whoa
we'll only make one totally gate though
ah wait I didn't tell you where to build
it though because we're only making one
but I guess this is where I wanted it
exactly you can read my mind I watch the
video
verbs of a federal flock together
that's what it is that's all it is
that's all it is nothing else
do you have any foreign
[Music]
can you pick up the rest of the red
Concrete in the world yes I cannot tell
them and my inventory is so full I got
it
I want there is some more in the chest
in case you need it
good luck building that good luck I
think it's I'll I'll try to focus on
something else then
um
one two three four
special
[Music]
not tall enough
let me
I just shovel dirt shovel
get ready to go okay
I have no that's yes
see
I'm so slow my brain is also not working
I don't like building for a long amount
of time in Minecraft oh
and more the adventurer type of
Minecraft player no yeah
pickaxe I think I need the pickaxe to
remove
oh yes for the concrete yes okay
oh yeah
Maybe
one more
I know that was by far not enough
actually now that I think about it
that was a lot
[Music]
hungry
you could if you wanted to you can
always you know scaffolding oh I have a
bunch of them here
oh 40 is scaffolding
okay
oh my
yeah that will help you
so that you don't get hurt so often
[Music]
I'm still making oh I am off center I I
oh golly
at least you're
trying to get the video for reference
and figure out what you're supposed to
do on your own I'm proud of you
the 20 gate isn't wide enough is that so
I just I just am making it now
okay
Daisy I'm sure you'll figure it out
I hear my name is oh my God
see I wouldn't be good at horror games
okay um
fight me
fight me I didn't heard it coming and I
still got started let's sleep
okay
hahaha
though that doesn't seem to have a bit
it would appears so
I can't so next I do
oh
I'm looking and learning
scaffolding
oh wait
yeah oh there it is
I really need more red concrete
oh there's a bit more in the chest did
you take that I don't think I did one
second okay
okay
who's challenging me voice
Perfect come here
you're in the coordinate you should
never let your enemy corner you
learn that from a part-time Warrior
alright so I did that at least
what in your devil You released or
showed a teaser of your song when is the
full version coming out oh goodness
uh tell me
I will give you an idea
hey video production has not started
yeah
do you know who will be working on it no
no oh well then that probably will take
a long time it will uh there's some due
dates coming up first
there's what coming up some due dates
to make decisions yes
ouch I understand I don't know I know
the
how that Angeline goes
yeah I've never done anything like this
I'll try to fix the roof oh I think I
think my my focus because this is
actually I've been streaming four hours
before this stream today yeah
actually not really 100 there Eva but so
I don't think I'll finish this I just
want to add like some obvious things
that I can still look at easily and the
details I'll finish them off stream
tomorrow
yeah okay sounds like a good idea
um can I have some of that scaffolding
that you have oh yeah yeah
there's at least half you can have more
thank you
oh wait I was already oops sorry I never
actually didn't even need that
what's next about it you know what you
know what happened today at kfp
what happened
so today was actually the one year
anniversary of my membership oh yeah
and uh or like of the day when I started
memberships hmm
and my membership it starts out with
eggs and then they hatch and then they
grow up
and then eventually today was the day
when they got fried and turned into
buckets it was oh it was a very special
occasion
I see
so I was having a second yeah I was
having a special anniversary
uh celebration with my dear chickens but
you know they always act like they're so
so panicked and shocked about it but
they actually were asking me to fry them
and we watched we watched the chicken
run the movie together you know oh my
gosh that would be traumatized me
oh I didn't that and Wallace and grommet
did you watch that one
yeah
okay for me it was actually kind of the
other way around I I was thinking was
the one that really traumatized really
which one
there's a few first ah the first one
definitely the first one actually I
don't know why I asked that because I
don't remember what order they are
because they always watch them in
different orders oh
do you mean the one where where he wears
those pants the automatic pants
so familiar yeah oh hello oh it's
there's a merchant a merchandise no oh I
want to see what he sells
the beginning of chicken run absolutely
traumatized me though
oh because he caught up there
yeah yeah
that was incredible I didn't remember
that at all but then like today watching
it again I was I wonder how they could
like sell that as a children's movie I
know she was so it was horrible how they
made it happen too it was she was so
scared because she knew and it shows it
in a shadow
that I don't but I'm sorry I'm not
letting you realize if I actually
um realized what was happening as a
child though it's too long ago I don't
remember well if I really realized but
you seem to have realized it oh I
realized whenever I watched it
I knew I think I actually didn't finish
the movie when I when the very first
time I saw it I think I had to like
after that I was so upset I didn't watch
anymore and I was until a few years
later I watched it fully
I think
um that's probably why this one didn't
really traumatize me but Wallace and
gromited because I did probably as a
child didn't realize
that she was getting killed I thought I
probably thought just like that other
chicken said and commented I remember it
very clearly now because we just watched
but she commented oh
did she go to a vacation
yeah oh so you thought you just
lucky I probably did think that yeah
um
again she said it like that so it must
be you must be I guess it is a
vacation Market retirement
[Music]
yeah so sad
oh my
goodness
I'm surprised you didn't watch Lord of
the Rings but you watched these like
Stop and Play movies uh
yeah I've seen things is there a pattern
to it no
haha
you've seen horrible things yeah I have
no [\h__\h] out I used to watch Wallace and
ground it all the time though I don't
like them that was so creepy I'm curious
which one I want to Google it right now
first one the one with the toast and the
pants
on the cheese yeah yeah let's see it and
the newspapers yeah it's one of those
things that just get ingrained in your
head satisfying to watch
and then yes
yeah wait first what's the first one A
Grand Day Out
I don't know what I'm doing am I doing
oh my gosh
made of cheese
oh
oh there was something like that yeah
what was the uh what scared you
there's the little yeah the whole vibe
of the movie I forget a robo at the
pants that they took control over him
and he couldn't do anything about it I
don't know I didn't I remember that now
the robot pants
oh I mean Wallace looks very very
strange
it's covered in fingerprints too
is that fingerprints no that might just
might just be texture although I place
this I don't understand cheese holidays
oh but it looks so it just looks really
I don't get it
[Music]
the tea or the cheese from the Moon
Mommy we should do a movie watch along
not maybe not of Wallace and Grandma's
Lord of the Rings I I don't mind
watching it again would you really
there's a few aren't there I want to
watch it with you yeah
[Music]
I am interested
I believe isn't one of the main no never
mind that's not their name what is
Frodo that's what it is Frodo hold up
and and Sam Vice County
who
Sam his his best friend he was in the
hobbits as well I don't remember
oh you need to remember some he's my
best boy
uh actually
for my birthday this year kfp got me uh
um a birthday video message from the
actor of Salam Vice Gumtree from Lord of
the Rings that's who that was
oh you saw that message were you
watching my birthday stream
I swear I saw
oh wait I I know for sure I saw
something some I don't know who it was
but one for Buddha
oh and I feel on Twitter I must have
seen
hmm yeah got some videos like that as
well but I thought I saw one for you
what sorry I thought I saw one for you
too no possibly yeah yeah oh I'm I
probably retweeted it yeah
myself
I don't know
don't remember the faces he has a very
Charming sweet face
he has he looks like someone you would
definitely want to be friends with
[Music]
hey you'll remember soon enough I'll
force you if I have to there's llama's
here
huh
that's what the Llama says
why why is the merchant invisible
oh at night they automatically drink an
invisibility potion so that they don't
get attacked by monsters that's why it's
not to hurt me
no no no no
they would only hurt you if you heard
them okay but then the llamas will
attack you then he actually doesn't do
anything oh the llamas will hurt me
they'll spit on me
so cute
I am back let's sleep I don't like the
night time
talking
oh I'm traumatized by people being
invisible well I've only had really one
experience of people being invisible
which what what what's what experience
was that oh as well tell me about those
many
oh there's a zombie it was many uh
okay maybe like maybe a moon ago
maybe it was a boy was it longer
it feels so fresh though feels like it
only happened yesterday
oh I actually oh yeah I I kind of took
part of that in that I'm sorry it
provided
yeah
indirectly
allowed this to happen
I would now that I know you better I
would never do that again
that's okay
oh you're kind of done with that thing
up there holy moly uh this is the ground
that's just for now or Granite gravel
gravel for now I will replace that with
whatever actually is supposed to be
there okay uh
and now I'm trying to figure out the
banners are supposed to go there but I
think there's also
fence
yeah there's a fence up there
um
[Music]
do you want the llamas actually Sonic
got me a llama
is that her house when llama is not
enough I just have nowhere to put some
right now I don't have a home good did
you get them with a leash uh Sonic got
it for me its name is soil
soil so yeah hers is named snowy
oh because it's the color of snow and
mine is the color of soil and so I named
him soil
I don't understand that
it's okay
have some bread
no it's a potato
what
I want to understand it please again
explain again so soil
yeah
it's brown
sometimes it's like well it's like dark
you know it's it's brown it's brown
brown soil
soil is brown yes so
is the color of the llama
oh
and she has the white one and you have
the brown one yeah yeah yeah
that's such a weird name to give to your
llama thank you
oh that was not a compliment I
I didn't hear what you said but you
don't have to repeat yourself don't
worry
laughs
yourself uh
uh what am I doing my
I don't know what I'm doing
[Music]
are you okay
no no
wait I am okay
okay this one's easy this one's easy
this one's easy this one's easy this
one's easy
there's so many small details here
I'll put that here and then
get rid of
wolf
because it automatically takes both and
then this okay I feel like yeah there's
a lot of things
a lot of small details that I will fix
later
don't worry it will be done by the time
the Japanese girls
come on the server so much progress
yeah it already has a beautiful shape I
would say you can I think especially now
with the red Tory gate I can already
guess what it is I would say I think so
um unfortunately
um it seems like a battery yes it seems
I'm entering falling asleep
spontaneously mode
oh
and now I understand you you understand
my struggle I thought you meant like
your own health food oh I didn't think
you meant actual real bad
yes it's figurative and not at the same
time such a funny issue to have it is it
is quite the awkward one yeah
wait but don't you have a
no did you try connecting it to your PC
because I did that a while for a while
it doesn't keep up in time right okay I
have that issue too yeah but you don't
have a plug close by not I need a longer
charger
or you could just get an extension cable
not a longer charger because those don't
really exist I actually have an
extension cable but it's not what I have
is not long enough
and I thought I thought I ordered one
and then it never arrived so I guess I
gotta order another one
did you know that you're not used to
streaming so long and you can get tired
[Music]
I am adjusting but it's just funny the
moment you're gonna say say that your
batteries are running out right now I
thought that you were literally just
like you decided this is the precise
moment where you feel like you don't
have any more energy right now
foreign
it's a bit more external
whoa all right that's that's
understandable
one day
I'm streamed without moving as cardboard
look three times but we could also end
it here that's fine too because I can't
focus either anymore I'm like out of
focus as well if you want to I mean what
I was thinking too if you did want to
keep working on it I could keep helping
you I would just end my stream and I
would just exist in voice only on your
stream if you want it but it's up to you
what uh if you want to keep going or
huh
um
it's my no I don't think I can do it
anymore my brain is empty that I
understand you feel that you've been
going for a while yeah it's 1am here
yeah I my brain my brain you know you
know what I'm talking about oh I fully
understand don't worry mental wall yeah
there's a wall or at it right in front
of me invisible but it blocks me from
doing things I I it's it happened see
for me for me it is actually a mental
battery unlike yours which is a real
battery that's causing the issues right
now I have two batteries but yeah
currently ours are a bit different
one thing that we can still do though
that will be fairly easy for even for me
to do we will um I wanted to do a I
wanted to do um
uh uh omikuji Fortune stick oh
we can place it uh
I would say
well here is not really enough space so
I guess it should be at the bottom
um
I want a place
uh so just I don't have a reference for
this so I'm just gonna do it what the
way I think it's gonna work I want to
have
one
one one one
[Music]
I could uh I'd see I don't know how to
make a dispenser yeah Callie's Carnival
has one
um so I want to build something similar
to that with sticks that have numbers on
it like one two five
and the with including uh three and four
and
um
um with those sticks each one has a each
one has a number like I will name the
six and each one will have a number on
it and then you take the I think we can
even just make it as simple as
having the box there with the sticks and
you're free to take whichever it doesn't
have to be a dispenser
um and with that you take a stick let's
say you take number two and then you go
to the next box
and or as or are you or a place to sign
here
a big sign that says number one is bad
fortune number two is little Fortune
number three is very very good fortune
number four is very bad fortune number
five is normal Fortune even either I
make it into a random dispenser and have
them have a big Shield here big sign
that says all those things or
just name the six no no no I wanna
because like in a in a Japanese Shinto
Shrine when you go get your omikuji you
go to the to the um to the lady
and you say I want one omikuji and she
gives you a box with a lot of sticks
inside that you shake it you shake shake
shake it like a Polaroid picture and
then you take one of the sticks out it's
like really thin sticks and it has a
number on it and with that number you
either it depends on the shrine but you
either give that stick to the lady or
you uh there's some self-service uh
umikujis where you uh you just go look
for the right strip of paper that's why
I want the sticks to only have a number
on it and then the the pieces of paper
with the actual Fortune you understand
chat I think Chad understands don't know
about mummy but it's okay mummy doesn't
have to understand
[Music]
did you understand it no
okay that's fine
[Music]
oh how do you make a dispenser dispense
oh is it easy to do let's figure it out
a bubble oh and Redstone okay that's
easy movement we're gonna learn
something really cool uh oh
[Music]
oh oh
hi
I
am uh it's okay I out of motion
I have died not me the batteries you see
Oh Oh I thought you said you broke my
pickaxe oh no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no
safe I'm gonna actually leave it here is
a dropper too
which one is easier though
how does it work isn't that dispenser
easier I might
I will
I'm gonna end my stream but I'll still
help you
so if you're on my stream it's gonna end
but I'm gonna help Kiara in her stream
so just go over here okay it won't be
much longer on this side Eva okie dokie
are you done papa is easier because it
doesn't need a bow a drop okie dokie go
go to Kiara oh oh wow okay
foreign
[Music]