[Music]
Ben
te
[Music]
Good, good
Got it
[Music]
Got
it
[Music]
th
Atta,
got it, got
it, got
it,
yeah
hey, oh, I did it again Pooh
Photo i Regular 0 items
Kyuri tb Gem-kake 4
ok Ahahahahaha
Japanese viewers
I wonder if they even exist. I
feel like they're just the usual English-speaking mayors.
No,
no. Erojapani Village Itsenro day 3 eee
all are I feel a little relieved
. Really, there are some Japanese
viewers.  I feel like there are people who are copying it,
people who say "Hello" in bad Japanese, and
people who use Google Translate to sell their comments, huh?  That
's absolutely true. It
was like that before too.
Ah,
no,
that guy doesn't have to be Japanese, but you don't have to be Japanese to see this cat's IC.
But he doesn't speak
Japanese. Someone who can speak Japanese.  That's what I wanted you to live
today. I
'm not here, Yahiki Etan Park. I'm
just going to do something obse.
Yeah,
how many times have I woken up in my chair at 1:30 a.m. and turned around?
Tsukune is still good.
Hmm, the sound is good. It feels weird if you don't speak English.  I
had a really strong desire to translate my Japanese into English, but now this engagement skill has become a natural part of my body.
Ah, I don't have to get engaged today, but I do
n't have to do it today. I don't need to do it today. It's coming. It's
half past half the time. There's a
7-hour jet difference.
By the time before.  I used to live in Japan, but now I'm back as an art king. Um, I
lived in Solaria in Europe.
Did you understand? Oh, that
's right, Japanese people
are here, so I'm
always a Japanese viewer.  I
wonder if I should explain a little bit about the house to the woman who uses it.I guess I'll just say it's okay if you come, but I'm sure there are people who don't wear it much now.I
don't really understand houses, so I don't come here often.  I'm sure there are some people who don't have it.Why
don't you look at this?I
'm talking about the Australian scene, but have you ever noticed that I'm always using Winx?
Oh, that's a good thing for privacy.
At first, I was
trying to hide it, but I don't know where and where my obsession is.
When I started performing, I lived in Japan.
When I started performing, I was in Japan.
But for the sake of safety, I thought
it would be better not to say it, so I
was trying to hide
it. Yeah, I wonder how many weeks and months have passed. Before long, I said it.  I
wonder if I was able to hit it. I wonder if it appeared on Mayo Mamomo. I'm confused. I said, ``I'm not sure.'' Honestly,
even if it happened, the ruling party honestly said that they could speak Germany. Where
is that sushi?
Well, that's amazing, I guess, and the
possibility
is slim. Well,
most people would think that this person is German if I told them that German is a Japanese language.  I'm
sure the character was already saying that even back then, she didn't have an older photographer,
so she's a different woman now. Well, it's become commonplace that she's
not German, but she's from a German-style high school and speaks her native language.  There's only one country next to Germany.
Well, even in Switzerland, there
's an area where you can talk about Germany, shovels, and buses.
Well, that's okay, because
everyone has already become a member.  I
was shocked when I said that, but
now there's a
Gooki shop that I'm pretty familiar with, so the
atmosphere was like,
Well, Chiara, I'm one of the Bingre people who can't dig, so Kitakubo is the one.
No, you're probably thinking there's only people there,
right? That's why, Moon.
And
for those who said there was a story, Australia is
full of people who fix things.
Well, I guess after that, I
started saying it
as a
joke, saying, ``I'm going to attack you.''  The color that was known
to me has always been a noator in my mind.Haha, I
bought sputum.It
was in the Kansai dialect.It
was in the Kansai dialect.
Oh, it's easy to understand, it's good, I'm glad I'm glad I did that from now on. Well, everyone, I already
have two dogs. As a matter of course, I said that I'm from Australia because I don't have my own country right now,
but that doesn't make any
sense.  No, everyone knows it, so I'm just saying it because it's interesting.But
vacuum cleaners are new
to English-speaking countries, and surveys show that newcomers have a hard time understanding it, and there are
some who don't fully grasp it.  I
feel like I'm really Australian.
I'm a newbie and I'm working a lot. I don't
know what to do with the spoon, but I'm still working. When I
wink and press it, it's a lariat. It's a pen called my mother.  Makiya's older brother and
Makiya's English is pretty
good, but he's
really fluent, but when he hears
one color of English from a certain country, he
goes home.He's
like, ``Hmm, Kiritani Bagger Exiled.''
My home name
isn't English, so I can tell by my physical appearance.I'm
not very good at speaking, but my pronunciation is pretty perfect, but I don't know if I can understand it.There
's also the idea that Dotsujin has grown up with both sides of the sky being so-so.  Eh, I
wonder what the armor is. I was thinking of Zaku for the locals.c Um, I
don't want people to talk about it too much, but it
seems like they're from another country.  I do
n't like it when people
think of me like that.I
want to make it clear that I don't like it when it comes to rules like that.While trying
to keep myself safe, I
say, ``
Hmm, I
wonder what it is.''  I'm so happy to
see all the comments in Japanese.Ah, don't you get a headache after google 200 times?You copy me so much that you
don't even notice me in the first place.Let me
introduce you to the stitches in Japanese.
Kanpekunpeko Competition Car He is a 3rd generation member of the live
Japanese rabbit weather paper
Why did he do that? Why did he do that?
4 eco-senpai! That's
right, he's not Japanese. Donmo
Dou
From the land of rabbits of love  I'm
nervous, but did I mention the name of the country?
Abe Abe Koyano appears in the background. Sorry.
Kume: I know that, I should know. I'm
from Pekoland. I'm not Japanese. Well, it's a perfect knitting. You
can tell by looking at it, but what kind of thing are you chasing
? Ah, Ecoland g, Ecoland now, I wonder what kind of place it is today.
Today is good,
Aichi! It's been a long time
since I've thought about doing a live stream in Japanese, but I can't really think of anything other than 3000.  It's
quite common for me to repeat what I'm saying in Japanese in my broadcasts, but it
's completely normal to start with only Japanese in Ingredients or Hahn, but it doesn't happen that often.
Good 4th day too,
uhm, if you don't talk to government officials, then a
This is
good. It's the second time I've spoken Japanese since my debut.
Hey, I
can't speak Japanese at all. I think the last time was last year. Last time was last year.  Nanka's pace is slow
ah  Oh, that
kid was playing that marshmallow.
Hmm, they saw that. Khan: Do you all remember? Turn nyan!
ana: When you
do collaborations with Japanese members, like grandchildren, talks, columns, etc., well, it ends up being all in Japanese,
but I
asked a question.  Thank you,
thank you.
That's the story of No-nee in the cheek episode. Oh, even I was a good girl.
That's Hanahiko's decoration.
That girl is from the political world of Japan. Ah,
that's Chiara A. I wonder
if Chiara is okay. The trip to Hokkaido was in English. I'm glad that so many Japanese people
seemed to be so happy about it.  I
think it's the day I went there, and then I
add it and pop it. [Music] It's all jumbled up with cutouts. I
wish it was real, but I feel like it was the Japanese army.
Oh well, that's a lie.
So Abe Zunya isn't here, so today I thought I'd play something about the Japanese defeat.
Actually, I was thinking of playing the best game, but
somehow it was meant to be in Japanese.  I was
wondering what it was like to sell games, and when I was looking for them, I
found all of them, but they were made by the person who created the atmosphere reading, G-Mode, a company called
Development Saa.
Yeah, yeah, I made it a theme. I don't understand, Moon. I
wanted to do another two pitchers, but Mojipitta hasn't gotten stronger.
Ah, I
tried that Rikusu, but if
there's a Mazong game and it's a bad Kobe, then oh well.  I thought I'd give it a try since I've already been given permission to do it,
but I bought Liu Yuuho, and I wasn't
sure if I'd get a mutual offer.Everyone
knows
[Music]  I
think it was released quite a while ago.I
know that the military is a bit of a joke in Japan, and
even more so, it's a
rural area.  I knew it and thought it would be fun if Amarth Sora was included every time, but
when I saw the video of the game, I could
n't really understand what kind of game this was.Gunma
Gunma.
You've been there before, but you've never been in the delivery department. If you
go to the boom, you'll probably go to Funsport. It's a
little too late, so you'll have to go to the fun sport. The
investigation got sad, so you stopped and
shot it. Hmm, this is simply what happens in Japan.  It's a meme.
Kunma's number 1 when I read it as a fairway. It
makes me sad. I wonder if
Kanashima is a good example. 0
Una, that airport
feels really old.
Yeah, I'm going to the military.
Or rather, I wonder if it's a sliding door.Miyu Gunma
asked me if there was an Internet connection, and tried to play around with it.Oh,
it's because the house isn't stable at all.  I
thought it would be easier to mess around if I made an egg,
but it's already flowing perfectly.It
feels nice.What
Gunmarbahn: The
World of Daypleats Please.  I'm
fine with the relationship with the listener who stopped talking.
That's
what I thought, and I said how I wanted to do it.It
started with Katamama Ring.Oh,
let's talk about lager.
For example, if the chat connects the words of the issue, Gyan would say gorilla, and I'd do my
best to remember the story of Son Ridan.No
matter what I try to do, it's the viewers who decide the next word.What's going on
behind the scenes?  Even if I connect it with Lotte or something like that, I don't know
what I was thinking.
Hehehegori, Kanata Hana doesn't make me laugh, that's wrong.
Okay, I'll do that. I'll
do it. Please join me. Will you do it?
By the way, this pre-show is only for about an hour, so you can
go back and watch your Japanese members after that, but I
think it's an easy time to watch if you're in Japan right now, but there's a lot going on.
I know you're wearing it, I'm sorry,
but that's why I wanted to make it a comfortable time to drink Ah, I'm sorry for
forcing you to share it with me,
but I don't know who you're wearing it with.
Kitani's a delicious lie.  I'm
really sorry, that's sad.For some reason, I guess I don't speak Japanese very well.When
my child speaks words that are worthless to me, I get so angry that it's okay to say I'm sorry.I
just repeat what I'm saying on my own stream.  Please forgive me for the Japanese style,
new, my
mother has forgiven me for the first time,
meow, please forgive
me, meow.
Please forgive me, please forgive me. I'm
cute. I'm happy for c.
I'm meowing. I'm a bit clumsy.
If I didn't collect this, I'd be pulling all of this. Ah, I'm glad I paid
half of the Aebo.
English is fine, cutter. To be
honest, Japanese is good.  I'm glad you gave it to me.
Please forgive me, Zach, I
forgive you.  Eh,
even if you don't know him, he's using his imagination to tell you about the bends and rivers. He
doesn't know because his house is famous, but
he's
active in Rotor.  I used to
go to many concerts because I loved Air's Enzu Konbu, and I often went to
Nunnally's concerts and got tickets for good seats.
Hello, it would have been nice to hear that.
Hello, there are other people out there.
Are you saying that I love Boi? My
first love plate, I love it, I love it, but everyone already knows that. It's hello.  I don't think
so. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yajima Mai Mizuki Sakura which was good even if it was more dangerous I
graduated from Serious book is also skin I
don't know those
who played Inazuma Eleven Those people also want to see the coin I didn't know anything about
Inazuma Eleven That
Right, there are a lot of meteors,
right? 7 Hey, Ryusaver.
Daa daa daa. Pattern 7 Rona's Ryusaver.
My child sings that a lot. I love it, I
love it.
view I
love the moon I wonder if I'll sing it at karaoke next time Kazetamahashi
Hey, it's already been 30 minutes
Yeah, no one's going up in price Oh, that other thing
Before I had that surgery, I had high expectations with Phil,
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  The characters are
being teased by the viewers like this, but the reason why it takes so long to read things like that spa building is the reason why it takes so long to read something like that.  I do
n't know how to say this in Japanese in front of the store, which I always do when I'm drinking water,
but instead of talking about Jalopeki, I'm constantly connecting it to other places, expanding the conversation, and
talking about all kinds of things.It
's 10 gents.  Hmm, I've gone off
the rails. You're
saying it too. This guy seems like he's going off the rails all the time.
There's a way to say that in Japanese, too.
May day, it's called a character who's afraid of going off the
rails. That's what I'm talking about, but it's in the background.  Uchiwa is
already gone, Sugakiya lacquer, it's
almost like the story has gone off the rails.
That's why Takanashi Kiera remembers it, so Spa Sayomi takes hours and hours and hours.
This is it.
If you want to go, don't do something like this.If you want to go, wait a minute.
Yes, that's wrong,
this is hot, this is what I'm looking for, and I'm going to jump at you.
During this time, a little later, yes,
there's a way to use your IC Jajan belly. Eh, there's a
collaboration on Mr. Tamaki's channel.  Yes, it
seems like he's asking me a lot of questions.Ah, let's talk about
that day.Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy?!s that sweet?  I was really
happy about the collaboration that Unkami said.I was so happy when he called me after the wilderness.Hmm, I've been
following him since before he stopped, and I knew he existed, and I've seen various broadcasts and
clippings, but
this character has started sailing.  Masuko's Sorrow
[Music] We'll
be outdoors in an hour Well, I don't know when it'll end, but I'm here, that's 1 e 9 That sea, my
own ship  I
want everyone to see it when the issue comes out.It's something everyone is doing, Maki-san.New
Honor: You've
collaborated quite a bit on that hood.This
time, for the first time, there
's a sentence without saying who the collaboration partner is.ee-ah, that's a good idea,
eh, that's it.
Yeah, I'm a little nervous about the brothers' Hakkei channel, but it's my
first time outside,
hmmm, but Kubo
is the first step.
Something that other people are afraid of is
Takanashi Chiara Wow, that's dangerous. That's what everyone calls it. There's nothing dangerous about it. I'm a
Tamaki effect. I'm
a bit like a streamer. I don't think there's anything like a tree or something like that.
Thank you for your hard work. Well then.
The house is okay, hey, hey, hey, probably not.
Fufuyufufufufufufufufuyuyamabikobuta's pet is a little good for Chiba
What e o
[Music]
Look at it,
say it and look at it.
Previous: You're
good at a lot of things, so I'm really looking forward to it.
Dirty sexual harassment  Loss of shrinkage I
guess I might make some dirty jokes, but the 6 prefectures of characters are also like that.Sometimes it's
not just Maabanuma, but I
'll say it like that.Well,
first of all, I'm a headchair idol, and Kunkuppa.  I don't care
if you don't know.I
think it sometimes comes up in those areas where everyone has a back, Ra, and other defeats.Do the
bots also know the meaning of f etc.I think it
would be better to explain it once and for all.  It's
already distorting meaning and meaning.I
know that's what happened.No, it's tragic, but I don't know why, but I have to go after it.Yeah,
Grap.Oh yeah, that's right, where did I explain that earlier?
Well, it's easy, Holon is good,
Konabono, Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa first collaboration in the early days I was
making a graph of Ra on the norm channel I was making something like that if it was just neat and clean.  It
's big, but it's thanks to Hokke Papa,
but it was a hill, so I got off on the left and gave it up.Otherwise, I was
stuck in a setting that said, ``You're an idiot.''Blow it, Papa.''
Philly Star pupa, you know, back then when I cut it up, I asked where it was.
[Music] It's the one
on the bottom left.
Or so my dad said. If
it's my dad's rash, then it
's impossible to refuse evil.  Reno's soooo pasapa
was taken away
Well, this is the viewer's fault, but
ugh, that's right, that's right.
Well, that's it, that bottom, bottom
left, ah,
after that,
that
h 0 idiot.  It's
been a while since I was pushed by the setting, and everyone has come to terms with the meaning of that word.Well, it hasn't been a while, but even
now, even the character Harris is saying it all the time.Why?
The word has come to be used often by the other members of Kaano Horiya
Now, and even now, it is often used even today, and even the Japanese members probably occasionally
use it in English-speaking countries, such as trading companies.  Probably.  I
feel like I've seen it already. It's
just
one of those stupid words. It's
been passed around so many places that it's
become a catalogue. It's
amazing, but isn't that what it is
? It's still used today. It's amazing that you created minmi and moon.  In a sense, it's amazing. I
knew Shiritori, Shiritori, it was
too much of a vision. I was
thinking that if I didn't do it, it would be a standing turn, and it would be the next time, so I thought I'd try Shiritori.
But it's derailed
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah has been
derailed for more than 30 minutes, so its been derailed for over 30 minutes.
Did you know that it's really cheap in Japan, but it's really expensive in Japan?I wonder why it's so expensive in Japan.Hmm, it
started all of a sudden.a
So, do you want to connect 71 to the owner? Ladies and gentlemen, the
second you press the garter
play, the cheapest fruit that was in the country of that house is
green 5 door 4. It's too
cheap to be popular, but it's you, sweet Hiro.
Something like 10 ribbons and
1.  If I'm going to buy two pulls, I'll
change the country at least five times.
[Music]
Maybe I'll change more, maybe it'll be like one big bag.
But in Japan, I feel like apples are treated like princesses, and each and every one of them is
packaged in such a gentle way
that I wonder if that's why they're so popular.  That's it, that
parting,
that one thing, one by one, Ann, um,
politely, yeah, very politely,
uh, that
big, oh,
that kind of person, that plate mirror, that kind of day Lord, that kind of thing is really necessary.  I do
n't think there are any apples,
but there are a lot of apples in one box, and I
grab them in that plastic bag.  I'll
take it with me sometimes,
ana, so I don't think there are those two bullets in the package anyway.Well, I
don't care about that story.
Please connect me to that girl. I want to know what it means.
Corn is a gorilla, isn't it? I can only talk about the gorilla meow.
He also earns a lot of salary. I do
n't like 5 minutes. Nokko Orira.
We're like
this.  Course
Lolly: Anyway, I might want to talk about my grandson Leela. I
don't have much to say about my second wife.
Well, I can't say that she's cute either. I'll
come after Grandma dances.  I'm
waiting for you,
change to gorilla.
5th place dealer.
Yeah, yeah, it
was you. I'm sorry, but that's what happened
to my senpai. Hmmm, Wakana, it's about my senpai.
That's how I see it. I
met him at the studio on the first floor.  Yeah, I
heard it was a plan, so I went after recommended seniors, and I
went after those seniors, too.There were
a lot of other door
members, but yeah, I was
overwhelmed.Undecided.I started getting money very quickly.They said it would come from my family's funds.  I had
already gone to my other room, but
Canada-senpai was the only one who
seemed to be protecting me.He
chased me, and the estuary area where there are many people chased me, and the
senior in the distance was urinating in my house.  In the bazaar,
Day ran over and said something to me.Chara was
alone, but I was
standing there, and Kanata-senpai caught sight of Noah's ship.ahkah, I
feel like that cat's plan is in there.
Asai is an angel
Thank you very much Sun Wu
Ri, there's an electric shock
Beta
Ah, I wonder if it's healed
?
[Music]
Haha
me a
Frequently asked questions all the way to the bottom
Um
7 Neaso n Senpai is petit
Haa
Senpai may have recovered.
Nao-tan got on the train. He
calmed down and calmed down. He
talked to his seniors. If I recall correctly, we talked about
Hello!  I got excited,
and then I got sick and had to leave again, but I was so happy when Konata-senpai
talked to me and I thought, ``I'm going to do something after that.'' Well, it turned out to be
Polo Nakahara.  I was going to
introduce this for people who don't know much about black, so I
thought we'd do a collaboration like that,
so let's use PowerPoint and talk about Hello!Pro because I'm an angel.
That's
what I thought, but when I
asked Yasu about it, I thought, well, just like in the game, you might have to pass through a giant carbon.
Um, I made a complete decision to make a par point first, but then
it was confirmed, but once it was confirmed, there was a possibility that it would be thrown away,
so I was able to celebrate by making it.  I'm
thinking, ``Hmm,'' and then I'm going to try my best, and then I'm going to try and create this tone, but oh
,
well, I've got to do exactly what I'm supposed to do.
That's right, buy it.The reason for that is
coming.8 I understand that you don't want to do that, but you left it up to us
wh.I
think that you probably only talk about the past.As for the
characters that day, these days, well...  Hayakoro, I have
n't really gotten into it, and I guess that's the case
with my seniors too.Next
time, what's next?
What about Milan?Everyone, let's
talk about gorillas a little more.That
corner, huh?Three days ago, there was that leftover.  Huh?
Well, that senpai's voice is really low. Everyone, Ura-shoku-senpai. The
senpai who's been talking since he first joined Discone is saying, ``It's so
expensive that all of them are here.''  I
didn't really do anything.When
people came into the channel in the corner, they all shouted Tachiko and
said, ``Twig!''Ah, ah, that
was interesting.My teacher's cutter was an amazing scutter.  I
want you to say this once more, ``
It's a rubber.'' Well, it
can't be helped even if it's over in terms of time, but I think it's
time for the director to go.
Hello, our company is here!
Raki is now a sister, and Riser Nakata is no good. Knives are also evil. Is
Dami-senpai's life
completely non-existent?
With Aoi-senpai...  I
wonder if it hasn't changed at all. I'm going to miss that broadcast. It was quite a while ago, and I got involved with it, and the broadcast on the course machine channel was a bit colored, but I can't say much about it. I like it, but I think it's cute.  Well, wait.
Well, I'm sorry. Um, I was
praying a little about the big rider.
Dizer.
Everyone thinks this is fine in Edo, but I
won't lend you the Kisai bar. I'll leave and wait. It's written in katakana.  It's
not katakana, right? So I went back to the atelier and the theater, thank
you, Utaskipapa,
guess ok Anno Kihara 1 I
think it's safe to say that I'm the only one in the north that can't say anything,
but je Japan's Alpi jip g I've
been doing it all the time.
Before I was doing it, I always did at least one thing, two a week,
and I kept that same schedule, but the
other day, I did it pretty consistently from start to finish, and then I did Raisa 2.  It was
released in the English-speaking world at a pretty good time, so they were
also printing things like that, so yeah, that's right, Fire Emblem in Japanese.  But now Yakuza's Ryu is playing Yo-kun, and
he's already a
super stable patient.
Ah, Donkey was crying at that time. I can't wake up without Gekko. I'm
crying quite a bit, but it's like that Sopu style, it's so fast.
Fuka's life season moon is like that.
Well, anyway, it's a naughty sabo
after Ryza. It's quite popular in Japan though.  It's not very popular overseas, but Rai-san
did a little bit of a shallow meaning overseas as well. Um,
Mounaiza was a little popular in the paintings, but there's something about Chiara.
Hmm, JRPG I'm playing this game because I love Japanese One Day Home games, but
the problem with playing the game is that there isn't much of a difference between games.And it
lasts a long time, so even if there are some people at first, I'll keep playing it.  Over time,
over the course of several weeks, the 1 difference decreases rapidly, and
some people say they can't watch this game forever because they want to play it.  I'm
worried about it, but it's
hard, but room
But I love teaching Ibi,
so I don't really like the popular games that other people are playing, FPS, shooting games,
horror games, etc.
Ugh, I also
want to play games that I feel like.  That's what I'm thinking when I
play the game, but I'm going to say it to the Japanese audience here: I wonder if I should
throw it away.When I play the gel visio, I always end up thinking, well, of course the game itself.  It
's that support, but that brave
man and his sister or something like that. Oh, that's
destruction. What's going on with
Nanjo alone?
Ah, voices, voices, voices. I
thought it was an unjust, soft circuit. voices are  I
always say it in Japanese, and it's good
for two reasons.
Well, Kanae generally sounds better in Japanese, and that voice
actor is better.  The
other thing is that I want Japanese viewers to understand and relate to what is going on with Kin and Kabodo Wood,
so I will be broadcasting a Japanese version of myself.  I
want you to come. Right now New is doing thing 5, but I've lived quite a few times. Hey,
Solo,
come on, Ollie. But it's a long series, isn't it? Hmm, it's
still the 3rd seat Shisa.
Alright, Yarigisugi-chan, come on, there's something.
As a hobby, Riser's butt is the best, her thighs are the best, she's super cute,
jazz is cute, and she avoided disscare and played all kinds of rear games in the latter half.Overtime
rate is 4.There
is no gender in the contract.  It's full of clutter and clutter, wait, that's
where we should be chatting.
Eme Blue, that bar is nice.
Let's live. I didn't have to make a fuss, so I tried the
Sachertorte.  I do
n't think it's too much to talk about yesterday, uhm
, you know, I'm throwing away the Sachertorte, right? You've
heard of it, right? Ah, I can't think of anything else.
Motomachida Tachitaumi 3-4 Yeah, I ordered it.
Seriously,
Ieki from Germany.
Tsk.
Well, that's different.
That's different. ana
Eh,
that's
different. I won't explain it here, but
that day, I played the only famous thing in that country, which was German.  You
know the character is from Solaria, right?
Nya is a very small country. There are
n't many famous people, but there aren't any famous people, and
well, everyone and number 3 are already dead.
Well, there are
n't many people who are famous these days.They're famous overseas, too.If it's too
late, they won't come around.Ah,
but when it comes to food, there's also food, Anne-Marie.Food with
six colors.  Don't think about it, I'll just become your wife  Well, I do
n't really know why, but it's in the Miu Loppa video. I
don't really like it. Cree is surrounded by many countries with different cultures. For example,
Italy is next to it, and Switzerland is next to Germany.  Hungarian is next to
Eichi Check Czech Japanese and it
's next to ``Cheetah'' Before you know it, there are
many countries next to each other, such as Spain,
France's subordinates are also nearby, and there's a
Czech face pocket.
So that's it,
hundreds of years of water 2 Burn
a in my house. Various dishes have been mixed up on the road, Solier and Procellar Cap. When it
comes to cooking, it's a lot of
things mixed together, Hungarian food is very good. It's
been purchased by Arts and is the same  The food also
uses premium tea. I didn't say that, I said that you can get a lot of it.
Ah
m. They also sell music.
But, for a really good putt, the cap percentage is Solari Optra.
If you don't forget Feb Ink, it's tooth bottleraria.
That food is a.
For example, I've heard that it's
something like pork cutlet, but it's on the right side of the pork cutlet, and there's just a
little bit of bread crumbs.  The only difference is that
Suzu Momotsuki, a member of the committee who loves pork guts, loves tonkatsu often at home.Instead
of tonkatsu sauce, it's jam jam.
At Onsolaria, there was a time when there was more of that kind of potato after eating it with jam.I
googled it and found that it was good for once a week, so I
decided on the regular jam, not the apricot jam or something like that.
Carly, it's
really good.
Jam Jesus iss. If
you live in Tokyo,
can I tell you about a restaurant that is highly recommended by Chara?
Can I tell you about this? A pitcher's place where you can eat authentic sushi nip.  I
want to know what you said in that reply.I'll
check what the name was.Tokyo
Up I wonder
if it's too much?The standing porter enlightened me.It's
already in Ginza.In Ginza's
Hidden Absburg Fairy Fairy Ruthin  If you
search for ikn Aha Ginter maps blog, I
think you'll find a cherry blossom story that's so good that it makes you wonder if this is what Japan is aiming for, or if this is the only thing that's good.  I
once went to a restaurant in Japan and missed the cuisine of my own country and really wanted to
try it.I looked for it, found this, thought it was an amazing arm, and took it with me.
But really, that red seal was 100% authentic.
Yeah, that's so cool. Well, you didn't bring it to me at first, but please put a jamu charm on it.
Yes, it's a
good thing, it's expensive, but oh well, it's that
good.It's really delicious.It's really delicious.I went there once and
tried other dishes as well.
Well,
the camp is close to ok, but it's not completely fine, but the final string was a divine tool.Anyway, I'm
not talking about sweaty huddles if I get off track after sorting things out.
Even if the big waves stop, the sound stone rear is that cake from Strania Audi Festival. I hope to
see you there. 5 I tried it. Seriously, I went to that store. Hmm, I got a little lost about that character that might be hard to find. I'm a
little lost.  Well, that
entrance is a bit difficult to understand.
Well, that's the chocolate cake in the village. I've seen it a few times in Japan, like
Zaba Tora,
so I'm sure there are some Japanese people who have eaten it.  But  The
jerseys for the judges are a little different
Ainu
Ah, well, it's a normal country and the jerseys
are a little bit ah Oh yeah, what did you get now? What summer did you
get
?  Rute a Aso is also available in Japan.Oh
yeah, I also saw Ribbon 1 after the first round, and it was at Sebring, which was really boring
.
Yes, I ate it, and everyone may have eaten it too, but it wasn't that person's. Is
n't there something like this? I want my relatives to understand that. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's ok, but the
texture and taste of the inside is different from that of food chocolate, and I do
n't know what Jeanne is like.Oh, it's
different, the real thing is different.
Leather Hatori ended with the return of the phantom oysters, but I'm
sure that Japanese Yamaata bar
wasn't very authentic either.
Hatori: Well, I
thought it was a little different.
Yeah, yeah,
Sturm's case. tai
n cure 22 now.
4 I love it, I love it, I love it a lot.
A. Also, I can get it in Japan.  I'd like to
introduce you to the real Sachertorte.
8 I
often find pepper in department stores, but it's Demel and it's
called Rebel. I do
n't know if it's a story about that German car,
but it's Demel. It's pretty
close.  They have it all over the place.It's really delicious.Well, it's
a little expensive, but it's a little expensive to buy, but it's definitely delicious.They
sell Sachertorte, and I ate it and confirmed it.It's real.It's real.
It
's a demon thing, Demel Show.
That's right, it's a seamo thing in the basement of a department store in Shinjuku. I think it's available all over the country, and I
think it's also available for mail order. Hmm, you're
advertising it really well, Master.
Even if it's not a small fry, it's something else.  I didn't get any other messages, but it looks delicious. Hey, there was
also a cake that looked delicious in that book. I met Mr. Vader Kitani and found out he had a really strange name.
But Schwarz Club Welderch Rushu Toru Kei
said in Japanese
Well, there's also 2, so be sure to finish it and try it The
project is coming Ah, I'll
be waiting
[laughter]
Wait, Marth's master is Shuba Shiba Shibare 2
Binding 2 Welder Healing Kill  I don't know if that's the one you see on Shutoru, but I
don't know if it's German-looking, but it's a delicious cake from that area. Is
that Sachertorte seriously chocolate? It's amazing.
Please disguise yourself and eat with someone.I
tried my best on the piano and ate that one hole cake by myself, but I
couldn't do it in one day.Normally I love the area, but that was a
big
one.  That's
going to happen
Okay, wait, what time
is it? It's still okay. Audio break is big. Hey,
hey, sit-dad. It's
fun. I
got really excited when I spoke Japanese. Today is 8.
Wait, I took it with Zanami, so
Maeda 2,
let's connect it with another one.
Okay, I'm
here. It's delicious, Dad. I
can't wait to see the TV iron door, Mom. I
already have a wear monitor for the TV, but
hey, I
don't like the en-plated template.  It
depends on what's inside
Jan
Ah, I want to talk about that. That's right. Mr.
Bandai Namco, the original material. I want the third child here to listen to it. It's
crazy. The
first reason I got addicted to Japan is
Stop 2 Minute Ob.  It's Sinfonia. Hundreds of years ago, increase and progress happened.
My mother gave me a Christmas gift for Christmas, and I played it with my older brother. It was a
chain
RPG.  So I really liked it and got really curious about it, and I wondered what kind of game this was, and I thought, ``What kind of game
is this? What's so
cute about it? What's so interesting about her body?'' I was like, ``I
hate it!''  Since then, I've
become a big fan of the series, and I've played all kinds of games,
such as the Tales series, and the
game that was released almost a turn ago.
It's as painful as May's body,
but I'm really looking forward to it, so I asked for permission, and of course I encouraged Momo, and of
course I had to do some other duties as well.  I got that permission a little bit,
but I do
n't have time for that little gal right now, but luckily I already played it in the first place, and the
game that I got permission from was also played by Araf.  The
game is ok and there are some issues at the top etc.
akane The
key to the race is the house
ana
tn Daisuke That's because I want them to win and I love Bandai Namco
Burn I love Auntie's games but getting 10,000 is too depressing Seriously - I'm doing a survey based on the Saab Leica lens.  Polyleather
, it's here. I
hesitated to say I'd do anything. I bought my ambition.
If I couldn't help you, it would be my life. If it weren't for Tentsu, I wouldn't be here right now.
Ahem, haha. I
like everyone who reacts like that.
But I really want you to listen to the nature of that mountain.
If it hadn't been for Tales, I might not have gotten into Japan.
Or maybe that was the trigger.  I loved it because it was James,
and what I want people to pay attention to is
the hood, this is the internal king dish, and who is the one who does all the jr pitches
? That's right, the fish seats.
That's why Izusuka, you do
n't have to worry about anything. Don't worry about it anymore. Don't worry about it. No, who are you going to give this case to? Kitani, right?
Uchihara, right? You like him, right? b That's cool!
Me
Farmers
Now, at the beginning, uh, uh,  From the three to the end, it's easy, so I'll hit it with that one.If you want me to
do it, I'll do it with Rio too.Ah, I'll
serve rice after bread, but I
want that Aken.
Nyanya Eyei Shimizu
Rach
[Music]
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhidages -There
has been a moon Larth festival.
I love speed games 0 I
love the characters too, but to be honest the character I'm not really interested in
is Lineyo.I
think it's amazing, and I think the performances are really good too.  I do
n't think I'll look into the voice actors until I find out they're pinch
hitters.When I went to the Dakakaateru festival, I was so
surprised.  I
thought that almost all the audience members were there for Senju-san, and
everyone knew the voice actors' names, so when Seibu-san appeared on stage.  I'm
learning about things like that, and everyone next to me already knows a lot about everything, so it's annoying, but when I was there, I
kept asking them to say here and there.  It
was a really interesting experience, but it really made me laugh.
Don't say that if you don't have money, but it was really amazing. I
didn't really understand what was going on,
but it was my first time.  It was
interesting to see such an event. I can really say that. Hmm, it
was interesting to see a voice actor with a lot of different brains abandoning his casual acting. Hmm, it was interesting, and I was
really impressed by that reaction.
Everyone was so hot.  I don't think he has a passionate heart.I
think Ponkya's voice actor is amazing, but he doesn't know that much about it, or at all,
and I don't think he'll look into it that much.  Even
though it's a character, the world of the game is the most important in Bar's game.Hmm,
that's true of any game, but
c Yu-san isn't Hirabe.What about everyone?What about
everyone?Game carWhich one is the voice actor?Which one do you
care about?
Well, I guess it's a game, but
basically the voice actors, the voice actors, the voice actors, the giant girls, love, love, love, love, love, love.
There are so many people who are admired by people. That famous voice actor has already become an idol,
but it's just like Ido.
Hmm,
that's
amazing. That kind of sensor is amazing. I
think it's great to give a little support.  The
people are also doing a really good job, and I'll point out that the people who sing that song are really
amazing, too.  I
guess they cast voice actors with the intention of selling it. Well, I
think it depends on the time, but I see it quite a lot. Hmm, it's
interesting, it's interesting. I was really
into Nana Mizuki's 4 big things, and I was in love with the color.
Akashiba Charya Car.
Nowadays, it seems like they hardly ever do that. I think that's fine.
But the voice actors are always very young and cute, and the older sister's face is what she used to be.  It
didn't matter, but now faces are important too.Hmm,
but I guess it's become a bit more of a target for people who are aiming to become voice actors.The
story has become a bit more realistic, hmm.
Well, I
can't wait now, Fukuda.That's
right, I'm 27 now, so I'm going to the forest.Here's my
dad.That's
right.The taste is Ah,
this outerwear.After
that, Ah
[Music]
Bouburn
Quinoa Bach
Even at times like that, I want that mini version of English. I hope you don't understand English. Even
when Chinese and English are being abolished. Even when all the kids are talking, I'm always drunk.
But, as I always tell everyone,
with that person and that Japanese...
Oh, Kitani's character stands out in the comment section, so you might not want to stand out, but if you stand out,
the character will be picked up as a Japanese word, so
for those who want to be in Hiroma
[Music]
Please write a comment in Japanese.
If you're a woman, that's okay.
When you're studying abroad and doing things like that, it's
amazing when you hear a comment from a Japanese person for hours on end.  I'm more than happy cc
Um, I won't use aid, but the Japanese will run out of aid in April
4 a
Yeah yeah
none  I stopped
brushing my teeth because I was talking all the time and there was a cat too. I'm
helping you use your happiness. I guess you're using the character man smell,
so I can't comment in Japanese.
a Ah, that's a thing.  It doesn't matter if you translate it to the best of your ability.Yes,
Ogata, try to find happiness.
Heiseikan talked about it.I
wonder if it's Entetsu.Ah, ah, I don't think it fits well with the armor time and the abolition of characters.
By the way, by the way, I
guess that's because no one was interested in me.If I had been able to
live in Japan, I hadn't originally planned to do 51 Hours, 1 Year and 4 Volumes.  I
heard that it was 11 years, so I changed it to 11 years, but it was
1 year in the village.
Hey, hey, I know, Kira mentioned that very sad story, and on this day, the
old woman got a visa, but it's a visa that can only be obtained once in a T-e's life, and it
entered her body.  Mr. Tezure's house is standing there.If you
can get past your plan to go to Japan for a year, you'll
have an apartment or something.You'll have to prepare all sorts of fries.When everything is in
trouble, Mr. Corner
can't do that pointless camp, so anything is fine.
Part
1 e I thought it would calm down,
but the timing is not right. 2
This corner is better. Kokoara Sangan. It
's a horse tree and it's a miscellaneous article.
In pre-war Japan, it was on the verge of running out.
When I entrusted the pigs, no one was wearing them yet, and no one was
wearing them all the time, but almost no one was wearing them, and no one was wearing them at all yet.It
was before it became popular.
But he's already doing it in other countries, and I was like, well, he's doing it in Japan as well, but I was
like, ``If only I had a little bit more, I might be able to do it a little bit.'' But I thought, ``I'm sure it'll
be over soon as Kuro.''  I wonder if it's okay to say "boo-boo". It
was before the boom.
So, well, that's why we
lost in that one year, and what
happened was that we couldn't do anything and owed something to Japan for a while.  I can't do anything I want to do at all  You
only get one once in your life, and I couldn't use that incredibly rough and free burlap,
so I ended up in a depression, and it
came in that spring, so between spring and the end of summer, I had to
buy it separately.  Day, I
got a job offer, then I
turned to my right hand, and then I waited and did nothing,
staring at the wall,
thinking, Wow, wow, what's the point in coming here?
Asaan
Even if it happens once, you can't stop it. You
can't repeat it, and you can't stop it and go back to another time.
So now
that you have the color, it's just money.
So, to connect with another good story, that summer, I
saw English Sakura Dictionary on Phone Live.Oh yeah, and I was always watching Pekoya-senpai
's stories, and I was
always watching the latest broadcasts.
Well, it's great that Ibushi
has that position.Well, I
don't have anything else to do, and it's
only because I'm wasting my time, and I don't have any money, so I can't work.I
don't have any money, and I'm busy soon,
like that psychic phoenix.  It looks like it's going to come back to life, so I
thought, ``Should I take the Hut Eve?'' But I didn't think to change it.There was no
way I could pass, so I took it, but it was supposed to be 6.  It
was a time when I was really into it, so I tried auditioning for it while promoting my love for Follow Live,
and ended up buying it.Ah,
ok, Chon.EU Ofuji Sculpture 1 time, that's back.Ah,
thank you for not giving up.  No,
I've given up, I've
given up, but I'm totally honest about everything, and I've
been living in Japan for about half a year doing live shows, but that pizza visa thing.  I
made good use of the remaining time and spent some time in Japan, but now I'm back, but this job was one that I could have done even if I wasn't in Japan.That
's why I still ended up working as a vacuum cleaner.Well, I
still feel a sense of regret.
Wow, there's quite a lot. There's a lot of things left to do.
There was a little bit like that in Japan before that time, so I had a lot of things left to do at that time, so I'll
come back sometime to celebrate and paint them.
I thought that I should just do something.
Ubahori's visa is free right away, so it's hard to get any
other visa for East Japan or Japan,
right? Even if you've endured Bizan, you
can only do certain things, so it's
pretty strict.  Well, it
's difficult, it's quite difficult, and there's nothing easy about it. It's difficult unless some kind of company comes along with us.
And
again, there are various conditions.  After
that, when I lived in Japan for the first time, I was like, wow, I haven't made any mistakes.
But Harrier can really do anything,
so on the contrary, I thought that was good, and what's more, I
used it a long time ago and just now.
Oh, you didn't use the old word, you used the present one, Sakura. It's difficult to
say that. What the heck?
When people take celebratory holidays in Japan.
In other countries, for example, he had to take the law on the same day, and in Japan, it was
decided that he would take the law in one year,
but for some reason in our country, it was only six months, so it was very
difficult.  So I thought I'd make this for Daikun,
but it happened around last year,
just before the real big characters went crazy in Japan, and it
was a year ago.  I
thought I had no choice but to go, and I thought it would be great to have a good vocal range, so they extended my studies from six months to one year.I
went to Japan thinking I could do a lot of things with 12, but in the end I couldn't do anything I wanted to do.
Well, it was a great release, but you see, the story is that he was saved by his little sister.If it
wasn't for the Horo Live, I wonder
what he would be doing now.I'm probably crying.Ah, there
are 9 of them.Thank
you for the Horse Barking Live.
Yes, to all the viewers here,
thank you for welcoming and accepting Kihara to this live show.
Yes,
thank you.
Kiara has truly been born. I've
worked so hard up until now, but no matter how hard I try, no matter how
passionately I put my feelings into it.
But no matter how hard I tried, no matter how hard I tried, I just couldn't succeed.No matter what I tried, no matter what I started, no matter what I did, I just
couldn't succeed.  I can do something on my own island.  I feel
like it was a real success, and I
'm so grateful that it was really good.I
can't believe how it's unfolded.I never
thought it would turn out like this.It was originally going to come later.
When I received it, I was like, well, well, well, it's not like I'm going to postpone the whole thing, but I'm looking
forward to it again, but it's
more than I expected.
Canary: Yeah, I feel like it's
been a success and I'm very happy.  I
was saved a lot.
So, thank you for your support, Japanese people. I've
talked about this several times in English, so I
think it's a story that fans of the 5 Okiyas have to wait for.
[Music]
Hmm, meow, meow, what is
this?
I tried so
hard, uh, I gave up, even when I gave up,
miracles do happen. I
want you to know that. Hmm, but by the time the miracle happens,
what should I do with my handwriting? It's an illegal miracle.  of
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, are you high? Do
n't let it happen, don't let it happen,
you Japanese, who are you? I've already
given up, I don't know
what it is, I've completely given up on all the possibilities that are approaching me.
There are people who play blocks, it
seems like I'm no good anymore, no matter what happens,
the ball is no good.This sounds like a good story, but for me,
well, it's not me.  I
think there are people who take that kind of stance, ye.
Eh,
and Chiara was like that too. Hmm,
what are you doing? It's a negative bullet. No matter
what I do, it's no good, and I end up thinking like I'm no good.  I know, but when I
look at that kiss character, I realize that miracles are possible. Wow.
That's why after this,
Aksu-chan will see through the differences with Mr. Ki and play the taste game.
This is the end of this transformation.  About 1 and a half hours
Thank you for watching. It was fun. It
was fun. I
still speak Japanese like the eldest daughter, thank you, thank you, thank you.
There's something I always say at the end with that German face, but by the way, today's Kitasuba
chat will be read in the next bag.I have some preparations for a collaboration after this.
I'm sorry, I can't read it today, but I'll read it next time. 8 Yeah, the ending is the usual not ba's
sky full 7. I
copied and pasted it from that other person,
German's Sayonara's Sayonara Beri's.  It's Aizuki, but I'm
going to tell the doctor.
OK, the 3rd generation engine is made.
Feel me,
good, good.
If it's a 3rd form,
then the tsunami attack will turn on the token girl. It wo
n't be long. It's not a kofun.
I'm going off the rails again, but I'm
sure the guest, the
guest, has already hinted a little bit on Twitter, but the
situation is such that the
oldest and best senior is far away from the usual, and the
promising one.  I've been reading a little more about the Institutional Regulation Authority Regulations and Rikio,
but next time, I
'm choosing a senior here, so I've
been in the business for a while, so I guess...
Please look forward to this talk. You can
listen to detailed stories, so
please come.
Yes, that's
why
[Music]
1 ban
Fake aon It's going to be hot our hour after a
nao ob Maiko is the soul of democracy  It's a good seat for the councilor Sucha Oto owner is a phone
aapofu Donto Mura e Maa
by Barber
Event 2
[Music]
me
N
[Music]
N N
N
[Music]
N url  Should I
put it on? Wait, wait, wait
[Music]
Yes, this is Kochi.
The mark is here
[
Music] 125 minutes.