oh
[Music]
bu oh
e
[Music]
chunky wonky has raided the
desk
[Music]
I
am
good it
again I'm quiet
[Laughter]
oh meow meow
meow
[Music]
look at my new
ride let's
go I got a new
[Music]
ride I'm still wearing my helmet though
cuz who knows maybe the glass will will
be shattered by ultra light
speed do this SC that a is it a muscle
car
no should I raid it I would I would not
go on a date of this it's a one
seater always wear your
helmet eat at all you want want to don't
you you want one of those cars what are
those what is
that I had so many good laughs today
watching some YouTube videos
man so many good laughs
man just wanted to
know
M I mean some good laughs and then
some
somewhere just the best cringes of my
[Music]
life I'm just even remembering it I feel
good
[Music]
I can't watch cringe too
painful well generally what depends
don't you
think B body cam footage hey don't you
roast my body cam
footage you liked my body cam footage
didn't
you my Vlogs were body C
footage I can't watch cring videos too
hard empathy hits too hard depends on my
mood well it was um I think you guys
have probably seen like clips of it
before but I watched like like a
reaction video of the full
thing um
K uh what was it called it's the the
like a show where it's Love at First
Kiss I know I know already the title
cringe U but it's like like one person
is in a room awaiting someone the person
comes in and they they kiss and then the
person leaves that's it and
then and then and then they decide if
they want to meet again just deciding by
a kiss but there's like a couple of
famous scenes from that
show cuz of the
cringe H and it's just oh man like
wow wow sounds out awful no it's
great if you just want to have some
entertainment sounds like a good way to
spread disease I was thinking they
brought in a kiss coach and I was
thinking she must
have
purpose
right she teaches people to kiss and she
kissed the guy too and she said she
kissed uh what was it an Italian Prince
or or something like
that and she went to The Bachelor and
stuff like that
like
well with such little time and so much
entertainment Out Pass such little time
are you dying are you okay
are you okay I hope I hope your lifespan
is still long little
chicken is it
Brave okay okay
okay nothing will surpass I marry Harry
well I don't know that or at least I
don't remember
[Music]
it yeah I guess yeah you have no time
cuz you're watch watching me all the
time see that would be
understandable I'm Marry Harry is crazy
oh oh have you watched Tru for drink you
mean from cut a couple ones but that's
that's not my favorite content from that
channel I watch a couple you are our
cringe cont you little [\h__\h] where's my
compilation I'm waiting instead all let
you posting
is the Hat
edits cow
Caren that video today that was funny
where you put a chicken in my spot where
I was talking about waya you made it
like the chicken is talking about me I
was kind of cute that was pretty
cute it got me like I was like wait did
was I did I say these things or is this
a chicken actually talking and they
changed the voice of the kfp member or
is this actually I like if I didn't
remember for the first couple seconds if
I really said these things about myself
but then I realized ah I said these
things about
[Music]
Winer U by the way guys okay for AOE on
Friday I'm currently trying to get it to
work um but uh with first first uh some
some you know um things have to be done
behind the scenes but trying to get it
to work but I'm I'm I'm I'm I might be
getting the coach for
Friday yeah we already talked on
DMS and uh yeah I might be getting my
AOE coach on Friday let's go it would be
awesome cuz like this is the perfect
point where I need my coach
I just need um yeah management to you
know give me the
okay
mhm but we'll do it in English
because uh like I listen to her German
and it's it's fine but uh it's it's like
uh
maybe doesn't sound as
like like she tries to speak proper
German instead of s with German and she
can't do it like I understand her but
it's not like
perfect uh and now I have a stream lined
up on my English Channel anyway rip rare
German
content maybe another time maybe another
time maybe another coaching
stream yeah okay okay okay like I want
to welcome her to my big Channel first I
don't want to disappoint her with my
small Channel first you know what I
mean okay guys it's been a long time
since I played
ff99 ff0 99 fzero not FF
what can you take the heat of the
toughest F zero track no probably not
participate in a king leag Grand Prix to
find out king League new tracks are now
available in f399 prot tracks and Team
Battle races along with all pre
events okay oh my God another ticket
yeah but I need to
practice cuz like I don't remember how
to
[Music]
play let's practice I thought it was
like moving on its
own CU it's like glitching around I'll
practice in I don't know M
mity it's like riding a bike we'll see
we'll see I'm riding what is this even
race
car
uh oh B okay
B uh we charge up here uh how do I oh
that's the
Turning oh oh uh how do I use my Boost
ah there
hey there we go there we go
okay
oh what's
this oh ow [\h__\h] hurts ow [\h__\h]
hurts race car backwards his race car
what amazing you got this of course I
got this I'm racing against
myself
you
uh uh is that all wasn't there like a
like a
sideways a
sideways thingy like
going ah straight okay so that is that
LR y it doesn't really work
not that I was ever using that
anyway
SP LR it's not doing ah wait okay well
it no now it's not doing
anything I never used it
anyway I love your racing GE thank you
it's so cute
right why am I turning I I really like
to turn it seems
my car does not come with a chandelier
there's no space for a chandelier in
here that's so
[Music]
sad yeah spiners for crashing I know I
know do I not get extra points for
spinning on when I jump like that that
would be like Mario
Kart I'm a Roomba car yeah
Roomba Goomba Roomba
[Music]
go my little
Sharky I miss you so
much just as I miss your
touch Gooby woy Goomba on a Roomba she
do be on a Roomba every now and then her
touch
huh okay I guess that's fine then I'm
good enough
I used to be better but I want to find
the new tracks let's go
guys sorry I didn't warn
you are you guys
here [\h__\h] feel like oh I see I see like
five people maybe that that belong to
me next time I'll countdown
okay you you got to be no give me new
track what the [\h__\h] where the new
tracks you got to be ready sorry but
hope you get to win well I I'll
definitely oh what what is this
coincidence all my rivals can't be I'm
quieter than usual Okay Go Okay I I
I what was I
saying what was I
saying I don't remember hey this guy's
orange I like
it oh look at my balls but it didn't
help it cuz everybody just
immediately
yeah everybody's
twirling like a
ballerina actually now that I look at it
the number one sign that they
have go
away it looks just like the one in Mario
Kart
wow doesn't it I mean I guess it's just
a
typical
oh
nice W I'm still not KO
woohoo ow ow ow really wanted to Bunk
into that wait how how do I do that
again how do I do the super wopa [\h__\h]
help me help help how do I do it how do
I do okay I got it was I think it was x
[\h__\h]
no don't leave me
no me wait for
me oh cow car I saw you KF meow kfp Rock
M there's so many of
you move move
chickens wait wait I forgot that I I
shouldn't use too much of that
[\h__\h] okay careful
H
but at least I'm I'm not missing the
curves oh there it is there's the
charge okay that's all I'll be
getting oh
soon
Yahoo or KF be being destroyed one after
another don't give up kfp we need to
have a strong presence in the
world we need to dominate made the
world here for all the kfp that died I
will fight for you what the hell is my
rank oh that's not bad I didn't
[Music]
die bam you're an awe right I look
amazing thank you hi kiar hi
K hi K what does that remind me of hi K
hi k
hi
K hi K from what TV show is that like
when there was like uh one like
character
person who just says hi and the
name who is number one
[Music]
Yoshi Deadpool no I never watch Deadpool
so I don't know it from
that no
idea
no no no no no that's not what I
mean hi brother no I don't think that's
what I mean either anyway kfp is is Evan
from
us who who is the highest
kfp may like the obvious one is number
18 and kfp mik
Mike it's not Evans uh
L
D what are you
wearing uh totally this is my basic
driving
attire okay freaking flyer let's go I've
been working on that title for a while
now oh nice
backdrop okay so I guess I'll just do
another normal
one uh in I'll I'll go
in how are we doing this
uh I yeah when the clock here
[Music]
says
15 which is probably in the moment when
uh you know you know a moment when he
saw bro
uh but yeah look like next time look at
your own hey there's plenty of you guys
in here look at your
own uh I don't know and you own switch
and see what the timer says what second
it's
on hey I don't know these
[Music]
people I don't know them they're
strangers stranger
danger
stranger
danger now it was really slow I didn't
get
the the the a
[\h__\h] I'm so far behind oh so
sad but I can pick up everybody's golden
poop so you know
a chicken's golden poop is worth a
lot 91 you okay I get it thank
you okay this is
a I will use
my
ah oh okay okay
okay not the best moment to use it okay
here we go
charge charge important to charge always
get it up as much as you can and bunk
the golden
egg
OT we
are driving in the
sky I've Got The High Ground
now and here we go
speeding
hi kfp how you doing so the the um
wallpaper for next month for the members
is finished and it's so beautiful I had
to change
my um my own wallpaper for the first
time I I figured
out [\h__\h] I figured out how to do several
different wallpapers per screen I always
had like the the same one for each
screen now I have a different one it
looks so
nice looks so nice hey wait for
me
yay do I still have a chance to get
ranked a little bit higher come
on ooh red is dead no Taco Smo
no just saw Red's
ashes hey
Mar if you oh well okay whatever I mean
if motion just is above me by one it's
okay cuz I got the
69 I bet you're jealous about that oh
he's behind me even didn't even get
across
me
loser look at all these
kfps
W the higher we go the less kfp that's
kind of sad where are where are the
pros
no I'm actually no there's still quite a
bunch of
them look number two number three holy
[\h__\h] we're
strong but I got to 69 which is the real
number one
[Music]
right okay when this says
55 enter ring the normal
[Music]
one I mean we're definitely oh I missed
it in the
[Laughter]
[Music]
majority I forgot I forgot I literally
have shortterm memory or long-term
memory I don't know
no why I don't know why it happens that
fast why how can time pass that fast
what the hell that has not what what
what how's that
possible I'm eating white chocolate by
the
way cuz you guys were like last time I
said white chocolate is amazing and it's
it is chocolate no matter what you say
you guys were ganging up on me
that was kind of
rude and I'm eating like a children's
white
chocolate I don't know why but it says
Junior on top of it and like the whole
packaging is kind of aimed at
children people in German speaking
country will understand probably which
one it is has some like crunchy
crunchiness in
inside like I don't know if it's Corn
Flakes or something like
that how can people be so
fast let me be a bit more aggressive
then okay I [\h__\h] come on come on let me
up let me up but I can't oh no okay you
can charge here too good good good good
good okay what my rank is good my rank
is good my rank is
good [\h__\h] off [\h__\h]
off go
away how far is it
charging oh it's there go away go go
away go
away okay okay
okay
I've always
been like always like in this mid-range
like I can never get past
that
careful
okay why did I why did I Dr W that was
by accident my my fum just kind of
slipped okay
[Music]
enjoy my time up in my safe haven as
much as I
can what's a
Haven is it a
heaven just fancier 79 so close to
Greatness damn you guys really got
better while I wasn't playing this game
[Music]
man
man everyone practice just for this why
you're too good for me
now Roger base who who
I haven't died well yeah at least I
haven't died that's one thing I can do
quite well even though dying would be
okay as a
phoenix okay entering the normal one
when this when this says
35 6 seconds 5 35 sanj scopio okay okay
I know that was barely any
time I should give you guys a bit more
[Music]
time oh why do I not get the choice for
a new one these don't look new was Red
Canyon
new oh is
[Music]
it what still they make it in look at
all these kfps they're all kfp so I'm
taking no complaints they're already
already ready to read my
mind yeah why do you keep on getting
rival cuz you're just as bad as me
that's
why hey oh slow slow start SL oh the
music I'm going to go
straight and then right cuz I feel like
it oh and now we can now we can try uh
use our boost yeah
boo oh sharp oh sharp oh bunk
oh what is this disco
floor oh oh [\h__\h] oh somebody died how
can you die so
early loser oh God these
craves okay okay
okay
Bonk the golden car but already had the
golden
bar so what was that for
oh what 50
[Music]
60 oh
God a I have it under
control
no AR don't go on the Disco floor I
think it's
bad or is
it okay golden car give me something
tasty give me give me give
me hi
K go oh almost bed into the wall let's
go it's hard to hit the x
button when you want to stay on the
gas oh kfp Wonder race let's
go I win I
win
woo 62 oh oh my best today perhaps oh H
Get Wrecked lunchbox H Gun Get Wrecked
you you've been too cocky once
again probably bunked against the the
besides too
often cocky little
[Music]
[\h__\h]
damn there's so many people in here from
us wa top four is like all us
damn my a she can't be this
toxic I've bested my rival CU up try me
again try me try me little
[\h__\h] oh just
lucky
wow oh that was new For Me
[Music]
Maybe how is it you have to enter before
the the this timer is over or is there
another timer
[Music]
afterwards before
okay shall we
enter shall we enter okay let's enter
when it says three
minutes I gave you enough
time let's see if I will follow up on
it here we go
yay You' think I I would have a good
feeling with time thinking back on when
I had the ID
collab and we had to
count in that cooking game and I did
amazingly during that my inner clock I I
do want to press oh hello I do want to
praise my inner clock uh quite a bit oh
here's a new one that I haven't
seen which means I might
lose but my inner clock like wakes me up
a lot when I'm supposed to wake up for
example like 1 minute before my actual
alarm goes
off or even when my alarm for some
reason
like didn't
work then also often my body just wakes
me up somewhat around that time at least
early enough so that I I can salvage
it
okay pretty good I I don't know this
track what are these bumpers I'm oh I
there's oh out there's mines oh
[\h__\h] nice
curve M let's go
oh landmines what the
hell oh I didn't get the the
Speedy oh they're like why are they also
shiny is it because their thing is ready
their their
Highway uh sorry I forgot to drive like
a good driver mananita was dead there
no
okay okay 85 next I'm 85 all is good all
is
good
okay oh I didn't get the I didn't get
the
car let's go don't R me out you little
[\h__\h] can't you can't take me I won't let
the aliens take me
go go
oh go up in the sky he why am I not
going
up maybe at that certain point you
couldn't no please Tello
please this highway is useless
man didn't get me any much further at
all
disqualified look at us disqualified
suckers how do I get this good skill
issue for real for real let me out let
me
out just like she has shut
up K
Lau sand ocean no let me out let me out
let me out let me out let me out let me
out let me
out have I had this one before sand
ocean is it
new let me
out
okay how do I how do I get out there we
go uh no
how that's me I don't know what that no
there's a there's a K-Pop song from YY
where they just say k k k
k did I miss the timing to get out of
here oh there it
is that
was sad also cuz I was one of the last
people to be eliminated oh like the last
two people
people but I got mute City let's go okay
here now
in now okay now when this says 10
[Music]
okay if you stop driving in the dirt
things will
improve okay I shall attempt
I'll give it a try get in here guys why
is this filling up so slowly cuz they're
ah cuz they're still in the
ah damn I've never seen it fill up so
slowly they're still chilling hanging in
the whatever in the
cup My Stream ah why why did I not
notice why did you guys not spam it in
the comments
oh
no no get mute City I want something new
okay okay you did well it wasn't loud
enough okay hello
guys here we go again you didn't notice
oh
really oh oh you guys are you what are
you looking at man what are you looking
at
okay more mute City
[Music]
fun why are they so
fast hey he pushed me away from the
speed thing [\h__\h]
you
stay away they said stay away from the
dirt they
say how can
[Music]
I come on La you can do better than
that
at least when you furever behind you get
all the special golden
stuff let's
[Music]
go okay
okay go go go up in the sky why won't
you go H it's the wrong
button wait H what butt listen oh it's
normal boost well there I was pressing
the wrong
button how how did I ever make it up
there how did I ever make it up there we
will never
know I just smashed several buttons
together okay that explains a lot no no
okay Go Lacy why are you always where I
am hi space
waterfall wow
Christmas
oh oh not bad not bad let's go
[Music]
oh look 64 eliminated some people I mean
could be worse yeah
nice okay back in there wait there's Pro
Tracks now wait first we go here H when
it says zero 14
Z made it 32 she you beat me
[Music]
yay la la la
la oh
[\h__\h] wait what
huh
what what just
what well oh M too please please please
please please please please please
please please please bullet I thank you
gold
it's still like within
the
tolerable frame time frame
right yeah yeah
yes
yes oh my God I'm 99 that's so bad like
so terrible [\h__\h] rigged
game oh yeah push me push me from behind
try
me go
away go away go
away W look how far in the front I
am never again going to
happen also this track might be again a
first timer for me left or right let's
go with number one cuz they surely know
what's the right thing to
do they jump over that how how how oh I
guess it's cuz of this thing okay I'm
back to where I'm supposed to
be between 60 and
[Music]
mhm I've Got The High Ground oh yeah oh
this is the perfect place to go on The
High
Ground then you can skip that huge
circle
[Music]
awesome I couldn't I wanted to Bunk
it everyone's dying everyone's
exploding I got to be
careful okay a
[\h__\h] I didn't do the jump ah
[\h__\h] come here what I koed someone did
I did I do that wa nice cornering well
when did I
Corner what does that even
mean oh
ah what kind of name is that underbar
underbar underbar under bar ooh number
one is in and I'm in oh 62
again W turning okay okay okay okay e
can you got 11 what the
[\h__\h] wait so I koed someone did
I cuz one time I had this like did it
say kfp or did it say KO and now I'm not
even sure anymore why would say kfp but
what in big letters on screen there it
is
Kos who did I
KO a gray
bumper what it was just a moving
obstacle
what what that you even a real person
huh okay here when it says
10 5 4 3 2
1 I'll
go a they controlled I yeah right
they're controlled by defeated play I
forgot about
that yeah yeah yeah which never happens
to me so that's why I forgot about it
I'm I never get I never get to that
point I never get to play the gray
ones yeah so you know I'm just kind of
buil
different where are you
guys me
hello
hello you went to a different
Lobby what we're empty we're going to be
[\h__\h]
CPUs are all of those
CPUs no not all of them
right you went prot tracks no way you
little
shits
[Music]
I might have a chance to win you're
saying that you guys are uh better than
normal players that Mak it into the
lobbies then I have a higher chance if
there's less
kfp I don't know about
that oh [\h__\h] is that
slow wee
[Music]
okay let's
bust 95 iuz nobody's
safe oh I got the Boost I got the Boost
now I didn't get this one
oh why hey what was that what was it the
aliens I'm at 50
something what the wind is so
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] the wind so
strong oh I'm getting all the Boost
okay fre oo
why am I being alienized
again okay just going lots of
straight oh
oh get that Bo get it yeah come on
charging oh wait that's the charge alien
iing is the charger right right
I I felt like it was attacking me get
out of here I have a chance on a good
ranking for
[Laughter]
once
oh let's go got to be careful now I
don't want to get hurt oh there's a
charger still safe I'm still save B
let's go come on Finish Line what
free6 Carey was holding me back right I
think it's time to
separate this you guys were holding me
back back around rank 70 to
80 is what that
means I think I need to from now on
drive on my
own
that's what it was I finally come to the
realization that we have a very toxic
relationship nah of course not oh next
rank
level okay I'm going to go to the prot
tracks when it
says
[Music]
we can
change if you see someone flashing right
there close to
death
ah I don't know if I want to play that
aggressively let us redeem ourselves
okay okay I'll give you a
chance let's go avoid mines at all cost
okie
dokie
how are they twirling so much in the in
this loading
screen I want to twirl too I
can't oh you got Health back oh oh they
change ships
[Music]
ah am I
twirling I think I twirled cute
um I don't really
care I think I did quite well on death
wi though but whatever
whatever twirl to power
up let's go
kfp
wow the most polished clean streets in
FZ
I do really want to play the new tracks
in Mario Kart 2 by the
way don't let me forget about it also
you know what you let me forget about
again even though I talked with you guys
about my
schedule we forgot to schedule GTA again
you guys reminded me about Hotline
Miami but not
about GTA even though we just need
probably like one more stream and then
we're
done oh the Disc Go the
Disco yeah we could finish it in one
more stream a [\h__\h] hell this is
certainly a prot
track [\h__\h]
wall oh why did I
charge
[Music]
um all right guys I'm out uh have fun
uh I'm a
bum I I decide when to explode
right do I have to speed I'm just really
slow here no oh oh ah I didn't get
anyone I didn't know that would be like
a
[Music]
countdown
rip
goodas number one is not in yet oh it's
the final ranking spin
Champion
oh at least
something when you're bumper the most
hated person I wouldn't say so I don't
hate
bumpers but it is a reason to hate you
indeed okay when it says 120 let's go
here
I how to how to drive calm
if you hold down after a jump you don't
lose speed
NY
[Music]
NY I'm drinking
smoothie cuz she's been too annoying
yeah just kidding she's fine she's
fine every once in a while oh I missed
every once in a
[Music]
while know why she lets me sleep through
oh but she still wakes me up early
sometimes why me to
why this is what the society that we
live in has done to
us with all the social
media destroying our brains my attention
span is so
low I thought I wasn't so bad I don't
even use Tik Tok how can my attention
span be so
low oh the pink car is cute looks like a
fish me I thought I had more time and
then I immediately forgot about looking
at the
time ah but you guys made it in anyway
right right right
[Music]
right
sing with
me
[Music]
[\h__\h]
W here here we go wow got to go fast did
you see that Ena got sponsored for some
Sonic thing where she wrote uh God damn
it have to do the curve she made a comic
she drew a [\h__\h] hell she drew a
comic a little comic I I I have no idea
who those characters were
so I wouldn't have been the right person
to be sponsored by
Sonic
yeah but she's on the main Sonic Twitter
which is pretty
[Music]
cool hate this
curve I hate
it
okay track kind of empty looking here in
the
back oh it's a
bumper okay careful careful I always go
the right
side even though I'm
left-handed okay [\h__\h] it we're we're
speeding over that section I still have
enough
energy no go go no such a bad ranking
but still why do I always get
63 didn't even know it was a comic and
it's just like a a Yona four
four
square comic Probably I guess they do
that regularly and maybe they every once
in a while get a different artist to do
it I don't
know I got all the rivals let's
go oh I get yeah extra points for that
right
right okay guys I I
promise night League test your manine
ultimate five race series let's go let's
go at 6:30 okay I promise I promise 6:30
look
the night League I've never been in the
night League I
think look at the
numbers 40 seconds at 30 we're entering
at 30 we're
entering yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah let's
go
oh
hi did you bring a rifle no I got a nap
I had such a comfy nap with my
cutos I didn't even sleep that little
but I just felt like taking a nap cuz
why the hell not you know I'm I'm an
adult if I want to take a nap I will
take a
nap and you know smoothie let me let me
rub her belly through the whole nap I
don't think I actually like I feel like
I was half awake for most of the nap but
yeah the baby the baby I'm an
adult I can nap when I want
to sleepy time is when I want
it you can tell me what to do I want to
I want to write a Lonely Island verse
for naps for that
song Let's replace one and make it about
naps sounds good sounds good
damn chy pretty good over
there get out of
here beautiful
singing
okay Al I've been drinking an energizing
smoothie so surely that has been
energizing me
sufficiently let's go
my I don't believe in it but you
know thanks for stopping me there and my
rank is so bad cuz you guys are so
good no I'm going to be ranked
out
no no no no
no
no okay okay okay I got the golden
car please let me let me at least one
more one more one more one more just one
more
okay okay 69 my lucky
number
okay come
[Music]
on oh that's the Finish Line
yeah
[Music]
Wooh ha shy Get
Wrecked captain me out too A A what
happened did you you outranked or do you
exploded I guess the fire Mark says that
you
exploded your interet died sure
[Music]
did
wow
oh oh oh oh next is Big
Blue big
blue big blue
ocean toxic I'm not toxic I'm your rival
then let be nice to me please
please
[Music]
ta [\h__\h] [\h__\h] someone pushed me mommy
they push
me
stupid bullies
everywhere oh pretty smooth pretty
smoth
okay was raiting for the right moment
whoa right out of the Boost still kind
of slippery slope
oh already back at the charging Point
okay okay I can I can use it a bit more
maybe
[Music]
okay
yby y
don't rank me out no
play
[Applause]
give not
cool but look at all the others that
ranked out before me yeah
look at them this is the Hall of
Shame be
ashamed for your
failures yeah yeah yeah
yeah how's it feel ranking out before
me
Shame Shame ding
shame
h
all right oh I could enter one more time
but no no no I'll go to I'll wait for
you guys a little bit to rank out like
is your
destiny come on come
on oh I dripped some spoofy on my
[Music]
shirt
SMY
pets what flavor it has um
strawberry Cherry Apple
guarana L
salmon and
vitamina what is line salmon in
English I don't
know
okay here in 10 seconds when it says
20 no no pineapple I didn't say
pineapple just Apple a flax
seed flax seeds doesn't sound like
something you want in your smoothie but
okay sounds better in
German well well well well
well yeah that's uh that's why it's
energizing but I'm losing my energy
right now anyway what was I going to
[Music]
say what was I going to
say I
[Music]
remember so oh yeah yeah now I remember
do you see the sua game now instead of a
watermelon you get a as a Halloween
edition you get a Kaba
[Music]
pumpkin
interesting yeah they had a little
update for the season it's purple now
the whole window instead of
yellow I just saw it
today ow [\h__\h]
you it's game now
not s a
game but I'm not going to play it
anymore don't worry like I don't I don't
feel like
it I don't think it's worth
my time at the
[Music]
moment I've got other [\h__\h] to
do
so much other [\h__\h] to
do oh I actually have a bad message like
I was told that the merchandise that I
wanted to
do let's not say what kind of
merchandise but the one that I was
probably going to
show like at the end of that 3d
concert that is currently planned to be
held within this
year um
I told it it probably won't be able to
start
sales
[Music]
until if I if I want the plushy then
March just so
late so
late don't rank me out please no please
I I was a good wa on here
if it's without the plushy then uh even
then only
February and I say I want the plushy
so why do I always get this ranking 72
[\h__\h] it's a long delay but yeah I want
to I want to pair the sale
start with some big event right so maybe
maybe I can do like some kind of outfit
reveal around the time but don't get
your hops up I have I have absolutely no
idea when my next outfit is going to be
done like there should be a you know how
I revealed my 2022 outfit recently my
2023 outfit we still don't have an
artist even though I've suggested
millions of them by now and we have a
pretty clear concept of what it's going
to
be but still don't have an artist
so yeah I don't know how long it's going
to take but maybe I'll try to pair those
two
things sell that merch when I when the
new outfit is ready to be revealed yeah
you just played with me nice hope we can
play
[Music]
again yeah but what about
what about the you know what
week no not not quite only about being
[Music]
busy pineapple
outfit the quack
week well so no merchandise anymore at
least not individually from me which in
some way makes you probably relieved
anyway so you can spend your money on um
more general merchandise or or on your
own or yourself or on the pool
[Laughter]
Awards so uh let's
enter let's end a team
battle in
you ranked
out oh
no normal merch for the conert
yeah yeah the planning started too
late but I didn't think it would be that
delayed
it's kind of crazy oh am I pink or am I
[Music]
green pink pink team let's
go no no it's okay it do be like that
that's okay that's okay I mean it's just
like it doesn't really matter when it's
being sold generally but for me I think
like especially with the exper erience
that I had with my birthday merchandise
I just feel kind of like I need a big
event if I want to start sales for
merchandise
successfully you
know
uh so
[Music]
yeah we will win this let's go Team
Pink
hurt who is with me Team Pink you little
ship why W so low rest I'm low rest oh
the whole stream or just
me these people are so shiny are they
waiting for the what do you mean team Ko
No no no
no they they were waiting for that
shitty curve I
understand
no no
wait get
going
[\h__\h] go go go
go unlucky yeah you're unlucky because
you're not on my team so
sad
I feel for
[Music]
you no no La not rank out no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
no
no I find it kind of funny I find it
kind of
[Music]
s
no no
it is what it
is oh
man
why why is life like this [\h__\h] I'm not
even going to tell you when I'm going in
I'm too
[Music]
sad
I've experienced a big loss in my life
so I'll be taking the following days
off to think about how to move on
forward just
kidding don't call me kcho I am Teno how
many people going to call me consol it
makes no sense get it
right get it
[Music]
right
I
[Music]
okay
oh all right all right
okay all right okay okay look at my
[Music]
ranking let's
go
I didn't even get a single boost up
there cuz there are only like two one in
the beginning beginning and one in the
end
n
ah dangerous but I have to get more
towards the
front
Okay charge it all up suck it up that
was not much just I
know
okay yeah I was I was around 40 for a
while why am I so bad
[Music]
again final
La It's the final countdown oh it's a
gray one the gray one is the one that
detonates was
it oh 60 okay
okay okay okay okay
egg no why did I why did I do that why
did I do that I'm dying bad idea um come
on make
it is that person in the
chat is that person in the chat that V
smell are you from
us cuz if yes and I will destroy you and
your
future I will find you I will find where
your house
[Music]
lives
yeah no one it doesn't seem to be one of
us so they don't understand who they're
messing
with okay when this says
610 we go
left
C see those kind of um variations
oh I was going to go on a tangent again
those kind of variations are
fine cuz
K one of them their name says
goiv no sto is not
okay call me stenu again and I will ban
you for life and you can go to your
second
[Music]
OSI
how you feel about that huh how you feel
about
that Stant is cute it's not cute what
the [\h__\h] is wrong with
you my second oi is Sarah Gutenberg oh
what a good taste you
have
[Music]
nice not nice what I even went off the
gas
you know guys what I did yesterday at
3:00
a.m.
guess what did wa do at 3:00 a.m. last
night there's not a single one of you
who will get it right why would I ask
you what I did when it was that I
slept why would I ask you then that
wouldn't be
interesting I used my rowing
machine and ironically even though I'm
not on the
ocean it made me feel a little bit sick
after a little while of
rowing also I noticed it takes like so
much strength from my arms even though I
wanted to help my shoulders so I tried
to focus to put more pressure or like
like power on the
shoulders I hope I'm doing it
right I hope
so what the [\h__\h] is a rowing machine
it's it's like you sit on the thing like
uh like you're in the bathtub I don't
know that's the best example I could
think of right
[Music]
now
and then you hold on to like go like as
if you're in a boat
actually actually it's just like you're
in sitting in a boat and
Rowing there's like you can set how much
resistance you
want it's supposed to be good for
shoulder and arm strength I
[Music]
guess now just I was watching um Home
Improvement while rowing on my rowing
[Music]
machine kayak simulator
basically but I couldn't do it for very
long why at why at 3:00 a.m. cuz um I I
I got a lot of stuff done yesterday for
my tax lady
meeting and then and then I did some
other stuff and then I took a smaller
smaller nap I think and then um I did
this and I did that and then I ate
something and then and then I was like
well I want to do one more thing to feel
even better about my productiveness
today so I decided to use my rowing
[Music]
machine efficient use of time yeah it
was just a short amount of time also I
played with my cats
so everybody's happy um did you sail far
yeah um basically across the lake
because Austria only has
lakes when are you finishing the show
the problem is I keep on like um when I
when I'm really falling asleep I try to
switch to a different show like Seinfeld
because I already know it too well
and so but I I tend to get actually
actually pretty uh fast tired tired fast
um so I watch like one episode and then
I switch to Seinfeld and fall asleep so
I don't I don't really binge watch it
it's actually pretty slow
progress slow slow okay guys uh
f99 in when this says
20 even if it is 15 minutes I don't
think it was even 15 minutes but I I
started with quite strong
resistance I did it as long as I
could stay strong and and you
know I did feel you know quite exhausted
pretty fast cuz I I haven't used it I
haven't done like shoulder work out for
a while and I I haven't been going
swimming that often either these days
because I I've been like
swimming outside I could go swimming
inside too somewhere but I won't want to
I'm too lazy now so I think now now I'll
just go use my rowing
machine no not below I think it was if
anything between 5 and 8 minutes I don't
know I have no feeling of time as you
know as you have
seen maybe I'll go rowing on my rowing
machine ah again after this the stream
and after cooking cuz I will be
cooking I must
cook I've I'm I'm I'm I feel so bad I've
been wasting a lot of ingredients I
think cuz I don't feel like cooking for
like 3 weeks now now but at least for
this week for this week I deactivated my
hello
fresh
please [\h__\h] why I never get I never wait
for me no I never get the [\h__\h]
wind all
right hold holy
[\h__\h]
okay W the wind is so
difficult all right here we
go let's get some distance covered
quickly before we get ranked
out
[Music]
oh I missed the golden
car I missed it again oops I missed it
again oh my God everybody's exploding be
careful
guys oh I koed someone I did really I
didn't do anything I was just driving
buing my own
business oh I have like oh it really hit
me all the way back
up what's my rank I didn't look I killed
you really
50 let's go I didn't I was like I wasn't
even thinking I was brain empty
[Music]
who did I
kill rival
[Music]
defeated oh blue I don't need blue okay
one more uh 30
6:30 murder
[Music]
okay hi
kfp
hello
murder let's
go k murder that doesn't sound like
makes a lot of
sense murder
chore Port Town
hard did we have this one
today you were my
rival did I defeat you if yes then no
more no more rival nness that's one good
thing I guess about
your early
disposal get out of here guys get out of
here no
space
putties stinky
chickens searching for an insult that
wouldn't insult you too much but just
hurt you a little bit oh no those shitty
bars ouch ouch
[Music]
oh yeah the music is Absolut B
op [\h__\h]
hell okay I don't like this map somehow
it makes me Bonk Bonk against the wall
so
much basically just here to enjoy the
[Music]
music did I kill leano or did he kill me
but I crashed on my own though you have
nothing to do with
that
I'm so
sorry it's
okay I that was bound to happen like no
matter what you
did are polars redeemed here no no no no
what we're not doing that
today they killed you no it's okay I I
killed
myself mini PR let's enter mini PR at
free
20 which is soon TM my tummy
H oh my tummy
H guys I tried for breakfast I tried the
Manuka Honey on a bread with butter a
butter bread with butter so soft
bread was pretty good like cuz normally
I wouldn't eat honey like that it's not
my
thing considering the fact that
eating honey just like that is not my
thing I would say pretty good pretty
good Manuka Honey pretty
[Music]
tasty leano here again to hopefully
assist me
positively her is healthy yeah well how
healthy can honey really be I don't know
like they say Manuka honey good and this
and that but I mean it's so like sugary
right can it really be that good for for
my
body best on toast I didn't toast
it cuz I tried uh toasting this butter
bread before and it didn't really didn't
really it wasn't so
good healthier than corn syrup uh corn
syrup I don't think we do corn syrup
here wasn't it even
banned
then in America so many things are corn
syrup and
uh makes you wonder if
there's like anything real honey
anywhere yeah it's just kind of an
American thing cuz it's pretty bad right
I don't know I don't know what's bad
about it I just heard it's
bad
[Music]
high fructose corn syrup comes to
mind which is the kfp member I love when
kfp members names pop up in my brain
just because I'm like thinking of a
normal
word is high fructose corn syrup like an
especially especially unhealthy version
of corn
[Music]
syrup they were flashing I wanted to hit
them but I I don't know
how yeah it's pretty bad oh
man danger
[Music]
danger
a healthy food intake is the best way to
a long long life as a chicken at
kfp 51
baby let's
go did I kill someone at the end end
there I bonked one really
hard oh wait we're a mini pre right so I
can at least go to the next
[Music]
one yay hello new uh
Rivals be nice to
me
clap clap next
race here we go here we
[Music]
go is that why there are more obsessed
people in the you obsessed with what
with with shitty
food let's
go so want to do R reveal I mean kind of
but there's so many things that I want
to
do don't even listen to me when when I
say I want to do this I want to do
that but it's okay cuz like you you know
I stream so often you that I need to
keep some good ideas for times when I
need a good
idea yes yes
yes oh
God [\h__\h]
h
yeah skip all those shitty
curves get that away from
me T so there's someone who's called
tonat best Japanese
food
ever speaking of Japanese food remember
I think I I showed you all the Japanese
like whole life snacks that I found in
convenience stores on my last trip
right and I didn't open one of them for
a while
right I opened it
now guess who I
got if you know who are even the
options if you
remember oh my God somebody
exploded I got vam
Miss it's so cute it's like a little
card little not even that
small she looks so cute I love the art
style from John
sensei
okay look at how many times I bumped
that golden car must have been a kfp
chicken
inside controlling
that the country Mama snack is what that
was by the
way save rank
[Music]
oh oh oh I'm not going to make
it the some someone want to stay behind
someone who's really far behind with
me they Abed
me
[Music]
again abducted life on stream
man she that's
rough yeah you couldn't stop that's
okay you let go what as soon as I said
you let go of the gas up but you drifted
over the Finish
Line God damn it i' be going on ahead
why are you even taing this
message I guess you had a little break
there andwritten let's go orange car
wait your car looks so much like a kfp
car you have orange and
teal how the [\h__\h] also look how far in
the front you are
[Music]
what come back everybody let's go
and let me go to the
[Music]
front is there kfp in the front kfp T
are you hearing
me space
waterful wait no we're at the end
now I went too far to but these top
people they don't have kfp in their name
so I don't know if they're really kfp
[Music]
damn what what are these people doing
that I am not
doing everything
probably how do you do
it playing good playing a lot ah shut up
I'm playing fine
too
straing we should just play Mario Kart
again although Mario Kart man there's
like so much waiting time in the lobby
and then people who don't leave the
lobby even though they
should and then the games Crash and then
not even that many people can
participate and then they take so much
more time actually than
fzero
[Music]
okay some of you guys are still in the
mini Prix right yeah I'll wait a little
[Music]
bit M you me you're improving of each
race am
I from tiny baby
steps are you done okay
okay doing better than you
wow that is not hard to
accomplish cuz I'm not even trying my
rank is Raising I guess
so small wien with my smallow vampire
model I love for you to check it out
it's called Halloween collection there's
a mini game for each home myth member
oh how do I find it maybe on Twitter
what do I typee in
Holloween I know even for for uh wait
I'm not
looking even for fan
games we have to get
permission
[Music]
Halloween I don't know where it is okay
right now I can't find it maybe
[Music]
later
yeah drop it drop it somewhere where I
can see it I guess I should look for
your
name son go pop wait you I think I saw
you in one of the top Racers I thought
you weren a kfb because I didn't see kfb
in your name and nothing else that
really speaks for kfb like a like a name
that seems familiar but now you're in C
woohoo
wow they're fun for a short while all
right I'm got to check it out haven't
played fan games
much oh my so many
mines going to change my name now ooh
well now I know now I'm already aware of
you how do you get so
good tell me Teach Me Maybe I need a
coach for this game as well I need a
coach for every
game no for real I'm looking forward to
getting coached in ede of Empires though
because I think once I get over the
hurdle and having like actual live input
from someone who who can micromanage
pretty well I think that will be great
help great progress to be
made like I was looking for her twitch
and most of her things are like her uh
casting other
matches but I found one where she was
actually
playing and
sasuga she is like when I met messag her
she was like oh I'm not I'm not sure if
I'm like you know good enough whatever
I'm
like you are good enough to teach me
something cuz I'm I'm
[\h__\h] I checked her stream and yeah she
can
micromanage she know what she knows what
she's
doing so no worries oh we're already at
the end 60 oh 60 60 not 73 so that's
good
[Music]
it's going to be fun yeah I I really
hope it works out for Friday but there's
some like you know checks going on
behind the scenes when when we collab
with someone outside of H live they want
to check is this a good person to collab
with top 10 super spark collector woohoo
Sparks stream Sparks No don't stream
Sparks stream love rush and uh
tgw 25 really only
25 and no I don't I don't think I'll put
her on the screen like just her voice
and maybe a
picture don't stream
Sparks stream teach W and love
brush let's go
f99 when the clock says a 8
[Music]
15 stream all of my songs in general yes
yes yes yes
yes I have to start learning
coros
too think my motion capture suit should
be arriving soon
[Music]
what
and um I made it I made it I'm here I'm
here I'm here what do you
mean yeah sleep talking Coro kind of
difficult that's the most important
right now and then I need to learn for
um the
concert freedy waa
concert yeah I told you a time I I was
saying it I said
8:15 according to the melody why you
getting a mo cap suit yeah well I
already have one I have like already two
motion capture at Home Solutions but
they're both
shitty uh and scuffed and not made for
dancing just for messing around a little
bit um and this one I'm getting
is hopefully worth the [\h__\h] money
13,000
bucks 13 ,000 is hopefully I want to see
the quality okay otherwise I'm going to
[\h__\h] lose it but like I'm really
scared but like I have to remind myself
that like kanu uses the same one and it
looks
good it look
good oh that was a freaking good curve
let's
go
who big business
investment is the suit all you need well
this I have the I'm getting the
subscription I'm getting like like
everything else you need too that's all
included in the
13,000 while I told you the most
expensive thing is the
gloves how much was it
6,000 you know there's even crazier
motion capture gloves than that there's
like some gloves I think they're called
called Manis ma Manis
gloves those are even more
expensive I'm doing pretty bad right now
cuz I wasn't focusing at all on the
ride okay okay okay
[Music]
hi hi
hi
huh you better dance with your fingers
too of course yeah I think finger
tracking is really important um
especially for like when we create my
coros I do tell uh Kiana that
like
that there shouldn't be too much detail
in the fingers
because you know it might not look so
good
actually when um when we motion capture
it I beat you again let's
go but there's still you know
like some hand motions in in my Coro so
have to handle at least a small amount
of
yeah finger movement otherwise it would
be too boring just having flat or or
fist hands all the time that's that just
really
limits surprisingly even though it's
just the fingers it limits a lot uh of
the choreography if you can't do fancy
stuff with your
fingers okay one more at four minut when
it says 4
minutes
[Music]
yeah once I get the suit I'll be
recording for the last MV cuz uh
retrospective is finished another simple
music video Just to promote the
song and and then and last one would be
sleep talking and I am just waiting for
the suit
still
sleep talking sleep
talking sleep
talking twerk with me boy that's toally
the lyrics I always hear twerk with
me
[Music]
uh
well whatever song I made for your
vision yes it it will will be released
after after after it's finished but it
also needs a proper music
video whether or not I make it doesn't
matter it will be released and it will
need a proper music
video hopefully also fre cuz then I have
my suit honestly after that once I have
the suit I'll be making
every and I say that but it's so
expensive I want to make every music
video in the future in
3D I want
to I think I think I
can right now it's just difficult
because I'm releasing so many little
videos one after another because of the
promotion
period of
POV but after I'm done with promoting my
album then it's just a single every once
in a while so I guess
probably budget wise it shouldn't be
such a big issue
anymore
hopefully and just going to say just
going to throw this out here when a
previous single does well then I get a
bigger budget for the following
single just going to say that now
clearly for creating the next one
yeah so always worth supporting what I'm
doing even if it's just listening on
your music
service Spotify or apple music or Amazon
music or whatever YouTube
music doesn't
matter everything matters no yeah I said
doesn't matter but it matters it matters
but it doesn't matter how you support
hey that wasn't too bad was it 62 okay
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay yeah I saw laas I wrote to her I
saw her practicing to
you is she
okay she was really
really passionately and intensely
practicing do you on Twitch on her
twitch
stream going back in in here or should I
go here okay let's go special let's go
prot tracks and in at
15 yeah she's she's like H going crazy
over it she's like oh my god what the
[\h__\h] oh my God oh my God
k oh my God what
[Laughter]
the she also really likes pineapple
which I was surprised about if she liked
do you I thought she would uh latch on
more onto uh where are you guys did I go
in too
late I thought you would latch on more
into sleep
talking I was a second to l
what where are you guys
no are these all
CPUs well maybe I'll do better without
you guys again
come pineapple qu catchy well at least
pineapple has a music video so maybe
that's really what got her to listen to
[Music]
it could be just catcher because it's it
was easier to listen to cuz it was the
one with the music video but I'm sure
once I bring out a sleeptalking music
video she will latch onto that as
well I made a Korean version for du I
should have made a Japanese version for
just for lapasa so that she can sing it
[Music]
properly can I go there oh I can but at
some cost of
damage
damn what a
nice nice
uh backside of your car they look like
phoenixes I could even ride the Japanese
version myself ah what
what I fought oh that was the first time
I ever saw that I just went for it for
thinking it was
realistic oh did you also just di Z
kfb you need a boost for that one huh
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah we both tried it I saw you I
saw you after
me okay now we know now we know guys all
right
then I'll go to the normal one at
15 Laura
kurash do it do you do it with lauras in
Japanese do it maybe maybe maybe you
know we did a hand
cam uh off collab before maybe we can do
a k off collab cuz she seems to like
doing K
like I don't uh I feel like
like when I see her streaming it's often
a Koka stream seems to be like her go-to
thing then I'll make her sing do
you and I'll try my best not to laugh oh
wait
that did
I how do you guys still make it in are
you anticipating me being
late he distracted me
too
ah why are you like this I know right
[\h__\h]
I I forget
immediately you're in
nice at this point you should anticipate
it yeah yeah see see all these
professional KF people who anticipated
it ki's chicken
people I wait that's
kcp oh got wrong Kias friendly
people kata's friendly people are going
on a little stroll he I missed it
because of you
[\h__\h] I
drifted I tried it out
[Music]
again ow all right I don't I don't think
I like this one do
I ah [\h__\h] forgot to turn oh my God oh my
God
okay I'm up here looking downward you
guys you look so tiny tiny smaller
small oh I should have skipped this
section oh okay wait you can go straight
if you don't like wobble wobble in into
it gobble gobble wobble
wobble then you can just go straight
through
it oh see and now I wobble gobbled into
it
let's go let's go everybody follow me
let's go everybody follow
me oh they're winning and I'm winning
too look at me I will be
winning I'll be winning
yeah 50
yay woooo
[Music]
yeah look at these kfps chilling in the
top never even getting close to me like
do do you even feel like you're racing
with me when you're always just at the
top
meanwhile these kfb always see me these
ones always see me cuz they're like
close to me in rank maybe you top uh
drivers should come
down to my ranks to hang with me and let
me hire uh at the same time you know you
know that way you can actually make use
of your time racing with me and actually
seeing me not being 5 kilomet away from
me at any
time
you know you know yeah just form a
circle or a line just form a line behind
me can we try
that I just want to see if we can as a
whole manage to be somewhat coordinated
can you try to like go can we all just
like chill and be in a line like in one
straight line I will be in the
front as much as possible and and I'll
also
try to like not drive away from you guys
wouldn't it be
funny but not in the mini
pre yeah chicken line hold hands while
we're at it no n come on let's give it a
try okay there's so many times where we
can race
seriously just this
one R
my at least let's do it at least for two
uh rounds and then afterwards we can
scatter how about that two out of four
rounds we race in a line and then you
can
scatter chicken Conga
[Music]
yeah okay I'll be front sorry I entered
already you
it [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it's not going to work like
that with so little how many kfb are in
here not that many oh wait maybe who
knows one line
okay sorry I just like it was a it was a
it was a
reflex they're going to they're not
going to stay behind me are they
try
please let's do chicken conga line for
two rounds only
okay find me I am I'm in the middle I'm
in the very
middle
okay let's go find me find
me are
they Captain meow you need to go behind
[Music]
me hey I don't know if it's
working I don't think they're doing
it this is not really one
line sorry I pushed someone away maybe I
should do that oh it's not working damn
go behind
me I will fire you all
otherwise are they trying to save I'm
too fast I'm the last one in no I'm
supposed to be the front you're going to
be behind
me oh
[Music]
man oh
man well okay while I'm up here
obviously you can't be behind me maybe
this whole system is flawed
[Laughter]
can I look at the
back wait it kind of looks like they're
in the
line or does it like they're trying to
at
least are they can I I want to turn
around kind
[Music]
of I want to see I want to turn
around well uh we're way past the the on
line rule anyway
huh okay after we're done you guys got
to tell me if you actually tried to do
what I
said I want a a formal report about your
actions and your
decisions hey under 50
[Laughter]
I did try it killed me oh yeah right at
some point the
lion if you're in the back of it yeah I
guess I'll kill
you look at all these GI bees behind me
hopefully properly in one
line look at these who who sacrificed
their lives in order to be behind me in
one
line surely this chicken cona has
succeeded
oh and now we're kind of in a line
driving automatically this not really
how I imagined it though I wanted us to
really be like in a straight beautiful
line touching each other's
butts that wasn't quite the way I
imagined
it maybe it's more possible in Mario
Kart I think I think we can try it in
Mario Kart sometime m
M yeah private games private lobby it
doesn't exist yet
no I doubt let's enter uh when this says
45 with more Head
Start I don't know I can't even check if
you're really doing it I kind of wanted
to see it what if I'm in the back though
oh
I'm here I'm here I'm
here I'm here I'm here I'm here I'm here
I'm here I'm here I'm here I'm
here I'm here I'm
here what do you mean I'm
[Music]
here okay no need no need for the line
okay
for
eh uh Phoenix arrives Never Too Late
Phoenix arrives when when when she wants
to uh I should be able to quote that
better how
disappointing a phoenix there's a
phoenix Phoenix I shall eliminate this
Phoenix because I am the only Phoenix
allowed in this
world Oro that is accurate precisely
when I need to yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah a phoenix Wawa arrives precisely
when she needs
to you know I was asked
a a question today that made me feel
like oh oh European bluntness yeah
yes maybe this is how people feel
sometimes about the things that I
say
h oh man it was it was a funny
question
um I can't even I don't think I can even
recreate it
properly but it was something along the
lines of are you oh by the way are you
in some kind of like psychotherapy
and I was
like
because
uh I thought they were really going to
ask about like my mental health or so no
no no no no
no
because with what you're doing it seems
kind of like you need to be kind of
schizophrenic
for doing what you you
doing
like I had my mouth so wide open from
the shock of what how that was phrased
at me but like in such an
innocent way like you know just European
bluntness
like are you calling me
schizophrenic and asking if I'm in
Psychotherapy because of the
this oh so funny that was so funny to
me H I think I just said no it's like
pretty normal to me like you know like I
I I've been doing this like I'm I'm
familiar with v tubing and and uh
and like the Japanese culture from my
whole life I got him I got the
Phoenix and you know so it's like all
very normal to me I don't know I don't
know how to answer this
question Phoenix
down it's okay I I I uh I know it wasn't
in a mean way it was just like in a
curious
[Music]
way I I was not insulted I was
amused fua isn't
real is kiaha
real I am
real
okay
entering another one at 120
I was amused yeah it's fine honestly
anybody who can't take a question like
this without being really [\h__\h]
insulted weak weak
mentality weak
mentality
honestly
yeah don't be insulted by
everything
[Music]
M St okay
okay some people are too
weak yeah like mentally weak like not
like I guess maybe it's like a
confidence issue I don't know know maybe
the maybe lack of confidence results in
being easily insulted I don't know what
could it be just cultural difference of
course but like I don't know I I
I I I even talked with narissa about
this trying to understand why European
bluntness is seen as being so blunt like
I think it's
normal and me personally like especially
if you think about
like like the the typical American Ken
for
example how if that's like such a common
thing then how how is like for me for me
from my point of view I
thought Americans should be or are quite
blunt
too and speak their mind too like I
don't think uh generally I don't think
America is really like a country that uh
a culture that can can't take emotional
damage that
easily more like entitled than blunt h
n
[Music]
entitled I don't know I feel like I feel
like generally like Americans deal with
so many different kind of people and and
personalities already within America
like I don't see
how
how why would
they you little [\h__\h] oh did I do
that generally from my own
experience outside the internet maybe I
don't I don't think that Americans would
be
sensitive or
whatever much more than the Europeans
are you know what I mean I don't think
we're that
different actually we're not that
different I feel like it's just
like
people I don't know what it is I don't
know what it
is we're not that
different I would
hope
[\h__\h] this track oh thanks for waiting
for me I love
you it really depends on where
mhhm I guess so hey I killed all half of
my
rivals let's go let's go look at that
ranking not I'm I'm able to finish under
70 these days
face yeah yeah I think like there's a
lot of variety
in people in America obviously like you
know so surely some people are too
sensitive and some people surely can
take European bluntness and those people
are here at
kfp yeah okay let's go
uh when this says
25 I'm always
offended yeah chill chill chill out a
little
bit what about us Europeans well you're
hopefully here too think um I don't even
I don't even think European blondness is
really a thing I don't really believe in
that anyway let's do big
blue
triggered but that's probably just
because I am European I don't know is
really that much of a real thing is it
really I experienced it yeah but like I
have no issue with it
[Music]
so
H it's not a thing don't let it bother
you then if you don't let it bother you
then then it's not a thing I don't know
what I'm saying I don't think I'm really
making any points right
now I think none of what I'm saying
makes any sense anyway right now what am
I
saying I don't know if it really makes
sense I'm
stupid just babbling and yapping I I
heard about this new word
yapping stop
yapping I'm yapping I I've been yapping
all day is that is that how how it's
used was I actually yapping I think I
was SI him
kiar no s k was obliterated by the the
dude who always gets l number one
here
yep oh did I I was not even looking I
was looking at the chat and I koed
someone
[Music]
wo i
w w w w w w wow w w
oh unlucky kfp dead on the
floor that is indeed
unlucky I got to be careful with my
energy there we
go yum
yum
yay I got the golden
stuff will it be enough to get up one
more time yeah
yeah maybe not why did I do that why did
I I killed another
one
oh he even with that
damn I got all my my health back but so
late so I couldn't really make much do
much with
that did I kill Jaws who did I
kill wasn't 30 just a bit ago
[\h__\h] I did two
koos
wow it's about sending a
message okay I 11 let's go at
25 one was a great bumper the other one
was a real person let's go I sicked
them I sicked them 20 20
oh I was about to pour some
water thank God I caught it I caught
it I apologize for my
um scandalous take just
[Music]
now
probably insulted a lot of people by
talking
about people needing to be less easily
insulted
ironically oh man
man I'm so insulted because she said I
shouldn't be so
[Music]
insulted oh man it's hard it's hard out
there not the same Lobby so
span welcome to Wawa [\h__\h]
takes today's
take European bluntness does not
exist it's a pigment of your
figmentation what a figment of your
pigment what I don't know what how do
you say a pigment of your
illumination uh pigment of your
hallucination that that pretty much
covers it
how do you say
it Austrian more rude what what say that
say that again straight to my face when
I don't have to look at the [\h__\h]
world say that again into my face cuz I
can literally not read the comments
right now when they're so long a figment
of your
imagination
ah
[Music]
sit to my face you little [\h__\h] you're
just hiding behind the chat box cuz I
have to look at the street at the
road I read it I read it
Hanan
[Music]
vamos
catch me outside how about that catch me
outside how about that huh how about
that catch me out
side stop
[Music]
yapping stop it with the
yapping oh my God can't take your
yapping
[Music]
so now say it to my
face m
m I said that you really aren't saying
it I said that I thought a were more
root than Germans when I went to Europe
asking for directions for different
experiences I'm Japanese e well I think
that depends in which city you
were
and I don't I think austrians are very
friendly I guess it depends on the
region and really it's just like maybe
you got unlucky Vienna yeah I think
Vienna is known for having more
unfriendly
people um but I felt like I hear that
more about the the the like Vienna is
famous for the coffee houses where the
waiters and waitresses will
not be taking your [\h__\h] at
all they are
certainly rude but in a Charming way
it's just a
Von coffee house
thing that's how it should yeah like you
go to a viese coffee house like
expecting the same thing that you expect
when you go to Japan to a Sund fed Cafe
where they'll be like I hate you
Onan that's kind of how
um V coffee House's
atmosphere should
be yeah it's the thing Japan is all kind
of uh
themed the stuff like that yeah yeah
yeah t for
sure people told me berene is also rude
in a Charming word but they weren't
Charming at all just
smelly I didn't talk to many people when
I was in Berlin but it's not my favorite
place it's kind of
intimidating aling coffee house is the
equivalent of Japanese sunnd made Cafe
checks out yeah that's what I say that's
it's truth
but it's also not true for every coffee
house anyway it's like more for the
classic looking
ones cats the Cat Cafe are
also yeah I mean Berlin will always be
scary for me because I got robbed in
Berlin once which sorry it's just I I
also know it's quite common in Berlin so
is forever engraved in my
memories yeah my phone was stolen and I
was like so lost because I just arrived
and I was supposed to uh go somewhere
and meet up with someone and I would I I
first was on a train ride and then I
switched to a bus and then when riding
when entering the
bus uh someone just slipped it out of my
out of my
pocket and I didn't I I no this actually
pretty quickly it was in the moment
where like all these people were
entering the bus it was kind of crowded
people were pretty close to each other
and then once I entered I already wanted
to grab for my phone and I then I didn't
find it I was like what the [\h__\h] and the
bus was already you know off on its way
but without looking at the phone I
wouldn't have really remembered where to
get off and how to coordinate finding
the person once I get off so I was like
really really worried but through some
miracle even though I don't think we
really said that the this is how we do
it when I did get off the person was
there but I was like terrified yeah I
thought oh my God how I don't even know
the final address where I'm going
to all I can rely on is hoping that I
will be uh like found at the bus station
cuz now I don't have a phone I don't I
don't know like who remembers phone
numbers nowadays I feel like back in the
day when I was younger I would still
remember remember like maybe the phone
number of my uh best friend maybe and
and my
mom but generally now I don't remember a
single phone number besides my own right
why why why did it
change like I I imagine we already had
phone uh books to register in our phones
like we we could already register
people's numbers in our phones but I
guess we used like other people's phones
more often back in the day so we had to
remember some numbers Maybe like when at
a friend's house wanting to call back
home or whatever maybe maybe that's
why yeah if I would lose my phone now
and I would have to call someone I'd be
really [\h__\h] cuz all I know is my own
number I'd be so
[\h__\h] but yeah that happened and I
never got the phone
back uh
obviously sad
and
Berlin just uh surely there's nice sides
to Berlin too but just overly overly
felt pretty intimidating and
spooky
scary and oh well some nice places to
though some nice areas that I saw that I
found because I was in Berlin quite a
few times for some business
trips have you ever gotten no on the
wrong bus of course I have
like false Transportation method
often yeah it's a capital city so you
know yeah yeah there's scary areas
everywhere of course but I just over all
overall always was
like
[Music]
scared never picked the Berlin Berlin
Berlin Berlin English pronunciation
please Road in Mario Kart no it's fine
it's
fine yeah clubs kind of Sil n for me the
nice the the cities that I like in
Germany are Munich
or anywhere in
Bayern and uh I I used to go more often
to lipic so I also really like lipic for
some reason it's not even I don't I
don't even know why but I likeed it
seemed clean and
friendly and I went there quite
often and I haven't been to like uh the
very very north of
Germany I know North is beautiful like
Hamburg I should go to Hamburg someday
but I never really had a reason to go
we're not done racing I'm just taking a
little tangent
break I really like I like Munich for
having big wide streets looking clean
and you know
friendly know
Mo hurg
V
OHA one more City that scared me in
Germany was
Frankfurt I think cuz I went for the
Frank fora I thought it would be fun
just like the
lia book fair but I went
alone and it was
scary it was scary
yeah Frankford is scary I don't know
it's like yeah oh you guys even agree
with me yeah help fun hope yeah main
train station so scary there I don't
know why did it turn out like
this but I was more easily intimidated
back in the day I
think no one is Saye near
Frank
yeah it the frun food does have a
reputation for being scary especially
around the main train
station yeah so it's not just me making
this [\h__\h] up
okay is there wobbly water
probably okay let's go racing when let's
go mini PRI at uh
[Music]
let's see how far I get this time in the
mini
Prix was quite an experiences in
American never being in a hub like that
took some getting used to
really
really well if it's your first time as
an American in like Germany or Austria I
I would say everything would take some
time getting used
to
Lio oh we start with big blue
[Music]
big H you plan on visiting let's
go Central Europe yes big
recommend Europe honestly every every
European country is recommend for
me I say Berlin scary but there's still
so many other nice places in Germany and
you know you can go to so many other
countries from
there
go to Italy go to Greece go to
[Music]
Spain go to
Austria go to uh whatever
[Music]
Switzerland go to Buddha
pish
let's go
budha
oh
[Music]
Ean okay come on W Focus
Focus yum why am I like
this well as long as I don't get
abducted everything's going to be all
[Music]
right
Francy golden car be nice come on
wo that wasn't much you didn't give me
much what the
hell I'm so far in the back for messing
up so
[Applause]
much come
on let's go
hello kfp
OU leak in
German it's kind of
M wa I got a few uh ranks up at the end
there
next how does one get first place that's
the question I always ask myself yes yes
yes go
NE
clutch oh oh that kind of fancy
everything going
[Music]
on I don't want you to be my rival you
look like you know what you're
doing
ready yeah 3 2
one should I not get the Boost in the
beginning does that end up making me
kind of slower I don't know cuz I don't
see the others boosting that
much
[Music]
W I tried the no not this little [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] off I hate this
one
always pulls you over there it's the
worst I didn't get the last boost leave
me alone leave me alone leave me alone
how do you guys not get sucked into
that
[Music]
how
we sick
wa no no leave me alone leave me no no
no dangerous
dangerous my rank is fine though no I
said that I take it back lunch boox go
behind me lunch
boox oh all
right
dangerous what I'm 47
okay
yay
W
45 hey hey
hey hey hey hey I got the kind down
oh oh made to the finals this will be
today's last race I would say yeah 45
years
[Laughter]
old let's
go
now this one I'll obviously not make
very
far it kind of is back what
why
I'm your rival let's go be nice to me
let me let me go past you why am I at
the very
left oh the windy
one it's the windy
one I got it I got it I got
it
oh I
okay I got I I just got to focus on
getting uh staying strong against the
wind getting the the
[Laughter]
boosts great great [\h__\h] that what
the
what oh my
God W the shitty
track I can't no please K them K them
please sacrifice yourself to me I will
remember it
[Applause]
forever no no no no
no super boost how long did I have the
super boost ready
oh
okay
oh get those golden points to laps left
I can't make it so long no I'm already
like ranking out again no please can't
be nois you're in front of me would you
like to stay
behind what
[\h__\h] got make it much longer okay okay
okay
okay no no no no please don't no don't
rank me out don't rank me out no no no
no no no no
no made it pretty
far
oh
oh what not bad I made it pretty
fast yeah let's blow him up let's blow
him up oh this one can't oh can
they
God
damn yeah I've got all more Rivals
so all
[Music]
right
at wow good job guys good
job didn't even I made it past the
middle pretty good pretty good pretty
good I got you early on I
did yeah okay that was
that better luck thank you Ethan to
Tomato Man and I do know congratulations
on the
win
uh I would have liked to win today but
it was never a realistic goal but I
would say I'm a winner in everybody's
Hearts here
today oh I got so new practice course
death WIS true did I ever get that
one see defeat an s20 as B minus is
super rare s20 was that the kind of
one what's an s20 just what what is that
level 20 dude
or that's the one I just did oh the
death
road yeah the kind of oh yeah yeah I
defeated them twice
actually
right high
rank oh it's the highest rank who what
are they doing back here are they a fan
of me and just felt like you know doing
me a favor what's going
[Music]
on didn't make it EV crashed out oh
man but we all tried our
best good job everybody pat yourself on
the
[Music]
shoulder that's the spirit I a lot of
fun playing with you yeah me too thank
you guys for playing with me again it's
been a little while but this game gives
the opportunity for a lot of people to
participate so that's nice I'm going to
read the Super Chat those I guess and
also so let me show you the schedule for
the whole week to just so that
everybody's aware I didn't upload it on
the community board yet I should be
doing that
um is it this
one
yeah here it is today
fzero tomorrow members only drawing
first day I'm taking the day
off uh oh but I will be
uh no um doing stuff no as per
usual Age of Empires on Friday maybe
with a coach and Final Fantasy weekend
and on Sunday on the night of the
Saturday to Sunday is when winter time
is happening and the clock goes back
from me by 1 hour so that will oh I have
to change GMT plus 2 to GMT plus one
then I forgot
thatuh uh but uh family field family
field is like Monday morning for
me early morning so it will be on the
next
schedule yeah time change means that uh
for certain countries we're going to be
a part even more like Japanese time is
now going to be like 8 hours instead of
7 hours in
between yeah but I'll be closer to
others who don't do the time chain who
do the yeah yeah on the left side of the
globe the ones who don't do the time
change I'll be closer to them but on the
right side of the globe who do don't do
the time change I'll be further away
from them right yeah yeah oh yeah yeah
that is
true so now EST time difference will
only be 5
hours left side it's left side from my
POV I'm I'm in Europe I'm in the middle
Europe is in the
middle I don't understand how any how
anybody can make the map look different
Europe is supposed to be in the
middle you guys are on my left side Asia
is on my right
side no
no Europe is in the middle
okay accept the
truth pun
American Ms with them in the middle of
hilarious yeah is that how you guys
actually like in America if you guys
have a worldwide map do you actually
have yourself in the
middle oh you have Europe in the middle
he there you go okay okay okay okay okay
yeah okay so so it's super then why are
you even asking me what do you mean left
side then you know what I mean then you
understand you should
understand all right it's Cannon yeah
hey hey you're up in the middle let's go
let's go and then I'm even in the center
of Europe so I'm really in the center of
your map hey yo hey
yo hey yo you always know where I am if
you have a globe you can like point at
me I don't know what that will do to
you okay W in the
middle I'm in the center of your world
so true so
true and you surround my my
world you surround my
heart K centrism
what yeah yeah you you are the planets
of my Planet system I am the sun you
circle around me isn't that
beautiful but you can't get too close to
me cuz I'm too hot can't touch this no
no no no no no no no can't touch
this this is
true
I'm going to change the music though
I've been listening to this for too long
now so
[Music]
music I
realized something just
now I have
to
use wait a
second
oh
[Music]
wait wait let me
finish I need to use the Halloween
office but I didn't finish it but I have
to use
[Music]
it oh come on
Pomo was playing with
us Pomo was in one of the
[Music]
races we didn't
realize she was a pom was real yeah she
was on 68 and I was on
64 she wrote me almost touching
wink oh you thought she was fake she was
real she was real yeah
let's
go no I beat
her oh my
God
wait no wait not the office uh that was
the old the old uh Halloween office I
wanted the I guess I wanted to prepare
the girls talk Halloween
version
cuz wait here girls talk
H follow me we are in darkness let me
put everything
together
wait let me copy
myself okay we are here I am
here actually let me remove my
car it's not fit
[Music]
okay and then I'll give myself
the
[Music]
okay okay I'm here it's so dark dark
yeah that's the spooky thing about this
is just this is the this is the
Halloween version of my girls talk room
just a black screen because that is
scary on its
own
no
um wait
Eden or
the the other asset do I just use the
night version I guess so
so I guess so well then I can actually
go
here if the other assets are just a
night version okay okay
okay what was what
ah
okay okay okay
okay golden thank
you
well let's see look at look at the
Frog and
then look at the
now wait wait wait wait
what
huh huh there it
is oh Frog's still there why is she
still
there let's look at this
room
oh wait wait wait let's look I want to
see I want to see I want to see I want
to see I want to see I want to see I
want to see I want to see I want to
see
T Halloween version
we have pumpkin do we have any surprises
oh no it's just rain raining a little
bit oh yeah it's raining a little bit I
can see on the
windows on the back
window but no no pranks right cute
pumpkins
cute what's that
happening froggy waa escaped and the
windows are like barricaded and then the
lights turned
off where did she go there
she it's so good that I just react to
this now she was up
[Laughter]
with no way you did a she's on the bed a
cute oh my
God wait I hope the table isn't covering
up any action oh oh oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh no oh no we're free
again oh that's so funny why did I enjoy
that so much that was so
funny
oh [\h__\h] she's coming to get me guys I'm
terrified I'm not safe here
[Music]
anymore let me see can I make myself a
bit
darker there we
go
okay frog
W everybody who comes here for the first
time will be like oh what what's going
on oh my God
froggy be
careful tiny hat and froggy waa are
terrorizing
me Cali CH oh yeah oh my God I didn't
notice the picture of C changes
into me is there anything else I didn't
notice
this the shadow is so good the lightning
oh my
God my hat is haunting me don't go on no
don't go on my head go away stay away
from my head don't come too close I
don't want you to be on my
head
where is she where she
she
away my haunted Girls Talk room it's
amazing I love
it yay thank you Eden exile for making
it even more
awesome wow
now to get other girls in here look at
the right
window this you mean this one right from
like my side my
POV l miror
oh oh does that happen every
time
does it happen
[Music]
again you missed it look at the
mirror wait oh I no now it didn't happen
only happened before the Windows shut
close I
guess second time after it LO you mean
yeah you mean the one time that I saw it
right
yeah I know the Cal painting I saw that
I saw
that and my pants have always been
there so nice I love
it okay let me find some
bgm
help
help I'm fine I'm fine I'm
fine audio stock I'm keeping an eye on
the window
still oh no this one was Nor okay so I
think I saw
everything I think I saw it all cuz now
it's going to be the the the vampi waha
thing
right next one there it
is remember this bgm
kfb my Halloween bgms are back
again nice painting if you want to see
me paint again I'll be painting tomorrow
actually I didn't decide like what to
paint
but you jump
scared I don't know what I'll paint
maybe I'll paint myself who
knows Cobble drawing I guess I could
finish it especially cuz her 3D oh 3D W
is this uh week
yeah I guess
so dodge dodge dodge the
Hat go
away Nissa in kfp
uniform well the cobal thing makes sense
cuz it's like
her the uh yeah Fredy showcase thing go
away frogy waa not taking you seriously
[Music]
anymore I'll think about it maybe I'll
maybe I'll decide spontaneously although
that one was really close to finishing
anyway I was doing the outlines right
it's a long
[Music]
time
has been a rough week for her what
really what what what happened I thought
she was having a good time because of
her Min collab and stuff she lost her
wallet
no maybe she can get it back cuz in
Japan when you lose your wallet you
often get it back I got it back before
like the the chances of it being like
stolen for real for real are kind of
low when did that
happen I heard her dad oh did she talk
about that yeah that's the reason why
she couldn't be at the collab that we
did no U that's why it had to be without
her and she went back because of that
happened
today hey po not don't give up because
you might still get it back if you go to
the I'm sure that the managers will
bring her to the uh police station they
might have
it that's how I got it but let me Rite
to her but I'm sure they're taking care
of it B you lost your
[Music]
wallet m in Japan
usually these things get picked up and
brought to the police
station quite often so maybe go with
your manager and
check I wonder like depending on how
many important things she had in her
wallet might be
problematic
oh she said K's manager is with her
along with a couple other why is my
manager why is jenma with
[Music]
her
yeah well it will go uphill I'm sure
from here cuz uh the debut will be I'm
sure it will be fine and
fun and
I I I I I will be watching
in you guys should be watching
[Music]
too she's taking care of my
daughter SAS GT I thought she was on
like a smaller smaller vacation right
now not really but like not supposed to
be working but of course even then she
works you you
know I'll be there for sure yeah
everybody should watch k Frey it's
before my AOE 2
stream cble
vacation maybe I can catch the end of it
that would be nice try
try oh froggy waa scary
scary
all the ID free ID free showcases have
been great yeah Kyla was
funny I knew that she was going to do
something like that because I asked her
beforehand like oh what are you what are
you planning for your showcase and then
she told me she was going to do some
exercising thing I'm like
what
nice
nice Sasa Kaa doing weird weird things I
love it okay guys super chats only from
this stream
right and then tomorrow remind me to
read the members only super chats from
the previous member
[Music]
stream oh my God y shutting down my
windows Age of Empires for
H well right now I want to focus on Age
of Empires 2 but maybe in the future I
can try other ones
yeah oh my God Kobo had so much cash in
her wallet
no for the future you know that you
shouldn't carry it too much
cash but don't give up you might still
get it
back wait that's a lot of money oh my
God
coo
H H yeah
who carries cash these days well when
I'm when I'm overseas I carry cash too
when I'm in Austria I only really use my
card
put
maybe onto
[Music]
myo sua and use it like a c credit card
for
Supermarket or
transportation and then I just
rill what happened I missed it for a
second kble apparently lost her um
wallet in Japan and that's stressing her
out but I'm telling her she might still
get it back and in the future don't use
don't bring so much cash all the
time
oh yeah wow
wow
okay she I'm I gave her some advice how
I handle money when I'm in in
Japan she's like you're right new
knowledge unlocked
okay apparently my advice is pretty
good let me know if you find
it so like with this advice maybe she
will remember who her real mommy is and
not give up on me so
easily
oh no money for
gcha yeah she maybe maybe I think she
goes shopping a lot maybe it's good that
we take away her wallet for a little
while okay let's bring out the thumbnail
wait it's just from today right so we
don't really need the thumbnail
[Music]
wait I didn't have the chat on the
screen there you
[Music]
are I'll make you a bit longer
still there you
go ah you you cover froggy want here
let's go
here all
right Psy D soon Jacob 47 D soon M
arcade look so awesome and cute always
so creative lots of love it's not my
creativity it's Blue's
creativity but thank you CH danar D Ty
D well that's not what I meant though H
so d
d and your boy Steven Adams D I'm not
sure if you remember attending the anime
convention Fort Warf Texas cuz that's
where I will have my first meeting first
time meeting a v
yipp
h what do you mean are you meeting me am
I going to
[Music]
Texas right in December there's still uh
some yeah right I'm going to I'm yeah
you mean me Steven Adams you mean
you mean cie actually right you you're
or she's Cali
[Music]
right I guess you're meeting me too
we're not doing meet and greets though
right as far as I know we're just doing
a
panel I think we should
sing I think me and cie have a panel
together right I think so so we I we'll
probably be singing like make it into a
little concert I don't I don't feel like
playing games I don't know what you guys
prefer
I feel like we should sing cuz like
we're very
musical members of H live
English concert concert concert concert
yeah I agree I agree son gold power D my
car has your colors nice I want those
colors
too you rap she sing she sing what
no the other way around Frey rap oh we
do rap battle but no I'll be so you guys
always like
um Praise My freestyle skills but
they're non-existent like I don't know
what you guys are talking
about I don't know El D thank
you funny h d thank
you now
thear fet D thank you Sean R
than it's like we're on a driving
T yay
cute would not take these cars out for a
driving date but
sure have you heard the bars you Dro
well if I can prepare it beforehand then
it's
better did you see call in tgw when in
that one super long Koka I saw her doing
some of my songs yeah Nathan coton thank
you for the red CH hi attention just
finished making my first B of L cookies
ever oh my God I was worried after they
finished baking that they might be too
hard or too crisp but after adding The
Filling uh I had one turns out they're
quite delicious and my fears were
totally unfounded did you make them
because I was talking about them you're
so
cute if that's the
case did
you did you do that because of me
you're adorable yeah I guess you are a
baker home
Baker wait can you try um what are they
called again next next Christmas cookie
that I want you to try and then I kind
of want to learn myself how to
make um what are it called
uh um
ah ah
l
yeah wait I'll show
you I want I guess they're not really
like Christmas cookies but they're
definitely very popular cookie to buy at
Christmas this is what they look like
they also have apricot jam in the
middle and they're kind of soft and on
the sides you have some chocolate
glazing but I if I make these myself I
might just cover the the whole thing in
chocolate cuz I love the chocolate part
the most and I always wish they had more
percentage of chocolate on
[Laughter]
top I love
this chras
cookie got do it my way but I wonder
like the the shape of it has like this
like wavy shape so I guess you need to
um place the dough with one of those
like bag things to get that shape I
guess and then probably you bake them
like separately like the top layer and
the bottom layer and then you put it
together with a gam and then you glaze
it with the chocolate easy seems
manageable no I never made them before
I'm generally not much of a
baker y
flash are those really Christmas cookies
no not like only Christmas cookies but I
eat them all the time during Christmas
time I normally don't buy them outside
of Christmas time or like winter time
and they're also they come in different
shapes they come in like a quas shape
like round like like in in a in a quo
shape you know and they also come in a
star shape kind
of they come in all kinds of
shapes but generally they always have
this like chocolate part at the
tips and the jam
inside yummy yummy yummy yummmy
I'm looking at pictures of the
[Music]
cookies let me show
you here this is the
shape usually kind of smaller than the
the the straight
shape
oh yeah the jam filling makes it really
really fruity and refreshing I love it
it's so
good looks like chos but it's it's
really soft it's not
crunchy supposed to be kind of
soft all right I'll look up how to make
these I want to I want to learn how to
make them I want to make all of them and
I want to cover them completely in
chocolate not just
partially I'll do it my way I am under
control wa under
control but I'm happy to hear that you
baked one of my cultures cookies that
makes me happy that makes me feel closer
connected thank
you handcam Christmas cooking yeah
sometime before Christmas though I would
say like a couple days
before skellum Dan oh another Baker bean
and Dish and any German austan F you'd
recommend I try baking egg why are there
two baking super Chets in a row you
could try those cookies too try try
German Austrian Christmas cookies the
season T the
seasoning and also if you want to make
something bigger if you want to make a
cake try s should generally not be too
difficult it's basically just like
chocolate sponge with some Jam in
between the layers just one layer of jam
and then a a thick coat of nice rich
chocolate but I think the the coat is
very
important the texture and the flavor of
the chocolate you choose I think must be
very important I never tried making
myself
but like it can't just be any chocolate
I would
think you made that but you didn't get
the icing right I can imagine yeah
I don't know it's probably dark
chocolate or or mix of dark and and milk
but you would have to look up a recipe I
don't know I only eat finished
s makes you
hungry want to try making gam noodle but
couldn't find Plum gam gam noodle sounds
kind of difficult but I don't know I
don't make those myself
either try kaash man skum skum try kaash
man
I feel like it's such a simple thing but
kaash man Ka i s e r s c h m a r r n
that's like my favorite Austrian
dessert yum yum yum yum
yum yeah the emperor
Miss tmy than thank you I did I did
remember I love how people keep on
asking if I remembered the stream idea
that I was losing my mind over I did
remember mon amiral now now let's look
that up let's look it up we have enough
time Mon
amiral oh they're on
Steam wait this person makes other games
too what the [\h__\h] this looks like
professional kind of like a professional
indie game
oh here's the H myth one oh Ena has like
a potion making game or something like
that that's
cute oh my
God nurse Mar's
medical what
something oh it's spooky oh my God no
it's like an escape
thingy oh oh [\h__\h] vampire queen kata's
midnight snack what do I
do what's happening what's
this oh do I have to hide no I have to
attack them before they get me or
something like that oh Amia Watson's
pumpkin
party oh that's cute it's a I just shoot
the
FPS cute I love this I love the the
visuals too
I know you can hear it that's fine
Godzilla so good as game is just uh
destroy as much as possible in
guardzilla
form oh and she's like being attacked
too
though oh oh my God I love it that's so
[Music]
cute hey I got to get perms for this
immediately you don't have um we need
your email address here I'll DM
you email address please because we have
to like get perms from you through that
can't get it through Twitter you can't
just say go ahead and play our games no
it's not
enough I don't know if you're still here
in the chat but I love that thank you
for making that oh this person's a
French from
fr oh hi
smoothie yeah did you come from the
toilet again or
what yeah even for fan games yes yes I
know it's that's kind of weird but
yeah
hi mommy is still reading super
chats but mommy will be done soon don't
worry she's so cute
[Music]
okay I touched her
tail how the cats doing the always doing
great thank
you
a thank youi happy birthday for
tomorrow early little bit early happy
birthday
congratulations I hope you celebrate
yourself
well what are you
planning actually me wishing somebody an
an early birthday holy macaroni what a
rare
[Music]
occasion love you wa thank you wa loves
you
too very much my
child unheard of what's going
on going out with my sis a that's sweet
enjoy maybe at the end of the day you
can check out my stream oh wait you're
from Australia
so huh I don't know where that would
fall into your day I am a team beep than
space wonderful than every C
than
and thanks for the pinky he was in the
middle because Ki is in the center of my
world you saying the right
things good
chicken
EBY every was was every not
uh a usual room
[Music]
regular I can't keep track of them but
right now you you you seem like a good
chicken to
me
no that was you guys all say Hulan but
hokan is not the only one being regular
in the usual room
okay there be good chicken okay okay
then your how do you say your slate is
clean and stays clean protect me from
froggy delar Mo py golden I have to run
to work but it was an honor driving in
your Shadow kiaha if we ever play again
I will train to get on your level so I
don't keep crashing or getting ranked
out getting on my level that's really
not a big problem I
think
and I saw you chilling in the chat even
at this weird
hour thank you
Kam and then we have unknown dun for the
pinky thank you for stream BS I love you
no thank
you thank you so much are you you trying
to make the stream longer by adding more
Super
chats cuz we're
ending I I didn't think we would end so
like with so much yyu so much extra
room I can actually cook before midnight
wow
no
no yeah every once in a while this was
supposed to be a shorter stream anyway
cuz the other streams in the week are
going to be like Final Fantasy is going
to be long long long
long when are we getting your pic what
do you mean the polar rids I think next
time we'll be like around
Halloween I want to get Halloween
frames and some Halloween
[Music]
options
there we
go I got the cat
hair H thank you unknown anyway hope you
enjoyed the stream today
Lau would you like planes games what you
mean plane games where I ride on an
airplane or
what simply
D yes I don't know would I like that I
don't know if I would like it if if it's
a airplane
simulator maybe not that much sounds
kind of a little bit boring flight
simulator
maybe
maybe it's zly D thank you and the lost
Hazard one happy birthday oh my God
congratulations
Star Fox oh I wouldn't mind playing Star
Fox everybody wish a happy birthday to
the Lost Hazard one congratulations
induction for the Super
Chat the one with Crystal that that one
especially although it seems like that
one kind of like is an unusual
one I definitely want to maybe in 24
I'll play Star Fox
Adventures I'll get myself a GameCube
again unless they for some miracle
release uh uh uh remaster or
something was she a first furry Crush
she's my only furry
Crush ma eight thank you D Adventures
GameCube the we please I I know but I
currently only have a Wii U I used to
have a GameCube and a Wii but not
anymore hi foga thanks for giving me the
knife to start cooking now she's just
giving she's just helping me to start
cooking you
[Music]
know it's kind of a unnecessarily big
knife just need a normal knife but thank
you if G you are hard to come by we have
the GameCube stuff build okay okay yeah
but I like the visuals of
GameCube but I guess getting a Wii would
make more sense cuz then I can play Wii
games and GameCube
games I
gu price is the issue
[Music]
maybe one of my friends has one that I
can borrow I don't know who one of my
friends I know has one but they live
really far
[Music]
away we games with the exent
suit yeah once I got that suit no I'll
be using it for all these kind of things
for
sure the games can get crazy
expensive if only we still kept it I
don't know did we throw that
away at some point I don't know what
[Music]
happened uh can't play every game c g
really
really you should be able to find them
in Japan easily probably reach oh
oh true cuz I considered buying like
some older console in Japan before cuz
they seem easier to find and cheaper but
if they're re un locked yeah that's an
[Music]
issue
n Only a handful can't be played on the
way okay
okay you want to land me your
we remember we played M Prime this
year if only Nintendo would release for
the switch Star Fox
Adventures
remaster if only that would be so
great
yeah it must have been this year it's
not it can't be that long ago it must
have been this
[Music]
year H where's my 1080 snowboarding
where's my 1080 snowbo where is
it you guys notify me if it if they
finally release it
please I know where is it they [\h__\h]
lied to me like if they don't release it
before the year ends I'm going to
[Music]
M I really want to play 108s you got the
cartridge oh
man no remas unlikely oh I
understand o o froggy wa it's okay I'm
going to start cooking now okay she
wants she's hungry okay okay froggy why
is
hungry
wait did I miss the people stand Super
Chat orange Super Chat for K orange car
I was the one who was right next to you
on your first match and also one of the
people who crashed out early because I
swerved off the map thank you
than hopefully we can play together
again okay and in German we say I'll
this in guys bye-bye thank you for the
fun time I'll see you in the member
stream tomorrow I
[Music]
byebye sleep go to sleep all of
you or
[Music]
else it's 1 p.m. it's 3 p.m. take a nap
do it just do it
thanks for the membership thank
[Music]
you you're at work well if you can watch
me at work then you can also sleep at
[Music]
work
okay then I guess have a nice day at
work good job
[Music]
today