[Music]
This program is
sponsored by the following sponsors
[Music]
Worker 19v
Young and
talented  Goods
Hawai'i Lukai Shiai
[Music] Good
evening everyone How are you
? Welcome everyone, let's climb again. I
always explain that program at the beginning of the talk, so
please wait.
Default talk is about English-speaking models.  The
purpose of this interview talk show
is mainly to let overseas people learn more about Japanese talent through live interpretation, but Japanese people are
also welcome, and it's okay to express your opinions in Japanese.Eh,
host.
This is the 19th time, no, it's me.
[Music]
Everyone say ``Hey!''
[Music] It's
Wolf Miyo! The
crackling crackling.  I'm
Wolf Mio, please.
[Music]
No, it's a rare house. It's
so unusual that people call it that, and when they realize it, they
realize that it's scary. Yeah, yeah, I
guess. The characters were talking about what happened earlier.
Maybe Chara has lived in the Kansai region before, so she's already devoted herself to the house.
But I'm so happy,
yay, yay! It's our duo.
[Music]
Greetings from my house
Yes.  It
's my house,
it's my wolf.
[Music] I
'm back, but it's the
same as yesterday. I wonder if it's
okay. I wonder if the same thing is happening. It seems like I
'm back, but I
can't trust it. This is for sure.
At Bill Sabin Ageas.  I wonder
if Ikebukuro Moment Is It's Back and YouTube are compatible with that one?
[Music]
How can this app also crash
?
But then, maybe we can use standing pictures instead. No, no, no, no, no.
That's not the only problem. It's
delicious.
[Music]
Yesterday.
After that one time, I
tested it and it was fine.  I
wonder if it's going to stabilize. I'm still a little bit still. I don't want to give up. I'm going to get my seniors back first. [Music] My OK OK [Music] I'm back. I'm back. I'll adjust the screen here. Okay.
[Music] I'm
sorry.  I'm sorry, but things have
suddenly gotten weird since yesterday, but things
may have stabilized.
So, let's get to the questions now.
I hope everything goes well from here.
What kind of activities have you been doing with Masho wa Yatcha Yatcha Ok? Yes,
uh, lately
. I
go to Aso on Monday mornings. I
always do it once, and then I
do a singing broadcast, and
that's the rest.  Well, I
also
play some kind of simulation-type games.
What kind of simulations do you have?
Oh, it's kind of
dangerous, like making fireworks explode in a residential area.  Also,
if you hit the sun with the sun, Goddess, I see, that
seems OK.That's
interesting.If you
hit the sun with the sun, it
will explode and disappear.The
sun and the
sun will both disappear.Also, the whole universe
won't disappear.This
one will disappear.  No, but the Earth is
gone. Wow,
Okeyami-san
. Someday, there will be two suns. If that
happens, you'll know what will happen.
How did Miyu-senpai find Hololive in the first place?
What was the trigger for the file?
Hololive,
um, I
was classmates with Fubuki at school,
and um,
Fubuki was my friend who played that game with me,
but recently I
thought he wouldn't play with me
.  [Music] I
was working on Hololive,
and then I saw Hololive and
thought I'd like to try it too,
so I
went for an interview
[Music] I see,
especially that
normal one.
For example, was there a reason why you decided to enter the game instead of Diary 3rd Generation
?
At the Gamers audition, I
told the shop name that I like playing games.
[Music] I
see. Well,
then, let's
create Hololive Gamers, so we joined and
created Hololive Gamers.  It
turned out that Amiyu-san was the one who started it. That
's
interesting.
[Music]
Mio-senpai was
Other than Fubuki-senpai, other Gamers were also
participating in the main live concert at that time.
No, Mio-senpai
came to see me and said he was good at games so let's
make one,
so I guess he was looking for another member,
but he
told me it was too late for that.
Our first generation debuted in the summer, and
we debuted in the winter,
so there was a little too much time between us, so we
decided to form a new group.I
love games.  That's why they
decided to include Fubuki as the leader in the Hololive game.
I see. The two of them used to be Gamers, but the two of them made their debut with just the two of them, right? Games. Ah, that's interesting.
Well, at that time, I
hadn't really watched Hololive yet, so I didn't
understand the character at all.I'm glad I was able to play
Miyu-senpai.It
felt quite unusual.It's
unusual.I don't really do things like this anymore.
Okay, I
see. Fine, I'd
like to ask you a few questions.
There are some things I wanted to convey to people overseas that I haven't been able to say due to the language barrier. There are quite a
few.
My Japanese, or rather my English, is really
bad, or rather, I end up saying strange things.
[Music] I see. I
can only speak very simple English,
so I do
n't really care if people from overseas are watching me.  It's
difficult to answer that, but I
know that you're watching, so
I'm really happy, just like all the Japanese fans, and
yes, I
can't speak English.  But  I
really appreciate it. Oh, I see.
And
English The
[Music]
[Music] I
think English viewers will probably rely on the subtitle clippings a lot.
[Music]
Also, there's something about Miu-senpai.  There are people in the chat who
translate things into English.I
wonder if they'll give up on me or something.On Twitter, I
get people to translate things into English and all those other languages.
What about broadcasting? I wonder if there are
people who can't speak Japanese when going overseas.
Either I need to rely on translation or study Japanese. I'd
like to work a little harder.
But
what is your favorite type of streaming so far? For example,
games, karaoke,
chat collaborations, or the big projects that big-breasted seniors often do.Which one do you
like best?It's hard to say which one I like best.  I
really like planning, and I
think I know because Chiara-chan also does it, but it's quite
difficult,
very difficult, and I
can't do a lot of things like that,
but I'm also really happy when something turns out to be really interesting.
Yes,
that makes me really happy.
[Music]
But I like streaming songs. Karaoke is my favorite thing. I
like singing. I like singing, so I
think it's great. OK, so
imations'
Baby Wanna Do.
Senpai
is there
[Music] I
see. Next
question is yes. I
have prepared an image. Um,
streaming.
Well, Mr.
Heart Towels.
[Music]
Nyuu-senpai. Please
tell me the birthplace of the Hatotaur, which is always on the bottom right of the streaming screen.  I want it. I'm really
curious too. I
wonder if it's okay to translate that difficult thing. It might be difficult. Please go ahead. Well, to
explain it simply, we're
planning a project
called Hololive Kindergarten.
So, we had a drawing contest at the kindergarten.The
theme was ``I wish there were animals like this.''We
asked the children to draw a picture, and
Fubuki drew a
pigeon towel, and I was like, ``
This is
what it looks like.''  Was that the one that
drew my daddy's fountain?
But wait, I
think there's the original one with the blizzard, so I'll stop here.
[Music]  It
was something like
that. [Laughs] It's so nostalgic. I
would be in trouble if there was an animal like this.
No, it's a bit erm. Fubuki
played the role of Uchimomo, the teacher, but I
see, she was
n't a kindergarten child.
This is the teacher.  But I was
trying to please
my
teacher, and I told him something like, ``I
thought the lower half of my body was a wolf, so I
changed my lower body to a wolf.''
Okay, I see.
[Music]
On my line of sight. I haven't collaborated with Nifubuki since yesterday.
[Music] It
's been on the bottom right screen ever since.
But first of all, I just wrote this, so why do I
always use it?  Did it become that?
Well, then, I
wonder if I
should say this or that. My teacher
said, ``Ah, Bodyguard.''
[Music]
Papa Izumi wrote it for me.
Then, after receiving that illustration, for some reason, the
people who run Hololive made it work in 2D, and it was really
cool,
so they sent me a GIF image of Gifu, so I'll
put it on that broadcast screen.  Well, it's
kind of
like a talisman, it's amazing,
something amazing is going to happen.
[Music] That
was back when I still had the time to do things like that.
Yeah, that's
right. I was the type of person who really reacted to material.
Ok, look at me
Action Wizard Side
[Music]
&
Is My Eye
Right [Music] [Music] What do you mean? Thank you for doing this Naoya. Tell me in detail
Subaru's ASMR was something like that, so I
sold Subaru's ASMR for 100 yen.  I
see. I see. I see. I
see. Let's move on to the next question. I sometimes hear the word "see",
but please explain what it means.
[Music]
Night
[Laughter] I
wonder if it's a maid [Music] I mean, we're vomiting. Did that become a word? I'm sure it's a painful feeling
[Music]
Debut,
debut...  It wasn't even a month ago when we
all got together for a Christmas project,
and
if we lost the game, we
had a punishment game where we had to eat cream puffs with wasabi.
but  I
lost
and ate a normal cream puff, but
then I made a noise that shouldn't be on the air, and I
saw this. I
started saying that the festival was a summer color festival, and it was amazing.
Why did I say that? And
then...
Spitting vomit has
become a popular word, ``miyoru.'' I see.
Yes, it's OK. The spawning spots that will be vomiting are:
Christmas,
Wasabi, Cream
Puffs, Savais Sunset
[Music]
Since then, there have been incidents like that from time to time.
Ah, well, sometimes, sometimes, I've
gotten angry, actually.
[Music] When
something bad goes into my mouth, or when
a taste I don't know goes into my mouth, I
end up doing it.  Yeah, I feel like I'm pretty sensitive, and what's
inside my mouth is
n't a sentient team in that sense,
but rather a warrior in its original sense.I
think that's okay, Miyu-senpai.I
want to go shopping with
Shinshu Skywith.
jepto
[Music]
[Music] I
think it's plablema too, so
let's move on to the next question.
[Laughs]
Well, let's talk about vomit.
[Applause] What do you
mean, "I'll be saved in the end." Oh, I'll
be saved.
Yeah, actually.  Nowadays,
my cat's
name is Tiger,
and
that's why Tiger is often used in that sense,
but in
the past, my cat's
name was Tiger.  I wonder
if I should say a water bottle.I
know, a water
bottle.I used to
bring a warm drink in that room with me, and
when I opened that thermos bottle, the
sound of the water bottle
made it squeak.That's
right, that water bottle.  Turn up the sound
[music]
When it makes a sound,
everyone screams at that magic water bottle.It's a
water bottle made by a manufacturer called Tiger.I
see, it's made by a company called Daika.
[Music]
Company
I see. It doesn't have
anything to do with cats. It doesn't
matter if you can't see it or not
. That's why I was told that Tiger Tiger can save you. And I've been told that so much that I
decided to give it a name.
Okay.
[Music]  ]
Nao
[Music] I see, this was my
first time hearing it.
Well, speaking of cats, my
senior
loves cats as much as I do, so I
think the topic of cats comes up quite a bit in the stream.  So, I've
prepared a clipping. Let's
watch it together. Let's
move.
[Music]
Now, enjoy.
Today, I
'd like to share with you an audio-only story of a ruthless battle between an owner who absolutely wants to be brushed and a cat who absolutely doesn't want to be brushed.  I think this is how I
want to go to war.For
now, it
starts with who's looking for it,
so I get the feeling that the cat
is the background music.
That stamp-like face is feeling something.
I'm the owner.
[Laughs] I'm
sorry to have kept you waiting. I
'd like to report on the results of the first round.
[Music]
Report on the results of the first round
This is Burn.So, my
knees are pretty bad right now, but I
still hate you.I hate you.You
hate me.I get it,
it's
okay.  My
left arm is biting me hard right now. I
'm so sorry. I'm
so completely sorry. I'm so sorry.
Yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes,
but it
surprisingly feels good, right? It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it
feels surprisingly good.
My arm is not a chicken wing.  Yo,
whatever, it's just a cat. I'm sorry,
stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it. I'll get
angry. I'll get angry. I'll get
angry too. I'm
sorry.  Do
n't try to escape, you know. I
caught you. I want to touch you. I want to touch you. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
The more you understand it, the more important it is, so that's
why this is the one. You know, I
was getting carried away, but it was
for you, too. So
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, that's
right.  My
older sister told me to
shut up and
tell me that I was a very nice girl
and that I was sorry, but I thought she was a liar. I
lined them up on my computer, but
uh, this is that. That
purple thing at the bottom is cat hair.
Well, it's going to be a tool. Well, I
somehow thought that it would be difficult to do something like this. I
see, it's
difficult. It's
like this, isn't it? But that
brush, the
brush that I'm using.  I
tried using it on my cat, but when I use it, my
cat doesn't like it either, but
when I use a different flash, she
doesn't dislike it at all.Oh,
maybe it's just too much of
this type.  I
think you'll hate it a lot.After this, I
'll send you some recommended items for your pores.
[Music]
CatsBy the way, in English, we
're called CATSready.Crazy
crazy cat
lady.Well, it's
fluffy and
fluffy and looks like an alpaca, but it's cute.It's
okay, but it does
n't have a lot of curly hair.But when it does something that it doesn't like, it keeps
following me and
pounces on me, so it's
amazing.  He
's the type of person who stands out, and he's
very
courageous. It takes a lot of courage.
[Music] Let's
move on to the next question. The
fan mark
tree.
Please tell me the
origin.Yes, umm, we have that modern one.It's
a little bit, but it has spiky hair on the side.Yes,
yes, that
's the
first costume.Yes, Caffeine's costume
had very spiky hair, and
that's for sure.  So I
said, ``The silhouette looks like that tree.''
So I said, ``Okay, let's make it a tree with a fan mark silhouette.''
Well, that's my
own
design.
That was said even before the performance
[Music] I
see, it seems OK.
Speaking of Okami Mio-senpai, some
people think that his favorite mark is a wolf, but it
's 3. Yeah, that
's it.
There's something special about him.  I
like it because the meaning is hidden and people who see it for the first time wonder why it's a tree.I really like this kind of thing.It's
not too easy to understand.  I
feel like this girl is hiding some kind of secret.It's
kind of strange.It
might make you feel better.It
might make you want to know more.But
people like that make
trees grow all over the place.  When you do that,
it's like the universe, after all, mountains and forests and
wolves, so it kind of
reminds me of my hometown.
[Music]
I see. So, next question 2. I'm going to Mew Super. I'm interested in the performance.  There are
a lot of people who join,
but how did you start taking them?
Well, I
couldn't play any musical instruments at all,
but I heard that
if you were able to have fun going, you'd become a better singer,
so that's why.  When I wanted to be able to play something, I
heard that it's easier to hold down the strings on the ukulele than on the guitar.
[Music]
That's why I
don't have any grip strength.
I see, so I thought I'd try
playing the ukulele, and I thought it would be
easier than playing the guitar, so I
decided to try it.I see, then I found out that
the ukulele was quite fun, and I was able to play a lot of
different songs now.  Now I can play it. I see.
With that attitude, I see.
[Music]
Week
Grips I feel
so refreshed by all the comments in English and Japanese.  You
say you're getting it.
Thank you, thank you.
[Music] I want to
get better at it. I'm looking
forward to it. I'm
looking forward to it. I
mentioned it a little bit at the beginning, but recently I've
been doing a weekly stream called Asamiyu.  What is the
content?
Well, Asami
is, uh, and lately it's
become more like a radio station.
First of all, the first 30 minutes are a corner where you can read letters, a
corner where you can read letters, letters, and mail.
Whose email is it?
Ah, we're looking for people on Twitter. I see. We're recruiting
on Twitter. E-
mail reading corner. It's like a place to talk about your worries. We're
deciding on a theme from time to time.
Ah, it's like I like breakfast or what kind of breakfast it is.
By the way, the day
after tomorrow, I wonder
what Asami will do if she wins the lottery. Hmm, I see. I'll have people
register and post with the north tag,
and then I'll do a section called Reading.
Yes, I see that it's happening, and in the
last 30 minutes, there's
news about the
scissors. It's been a week's news of the Hololive members, and it looks like they've done it. On Monday, they're showing off their hiragana. They
couldn't stream it, so it was
like they were acting.
[Music] It's probably
7:30 Japan time.
[Music]
Well, that's right, it's
over. That's when it should have ended. The
new time is probably Monday, Japan time.
That's why it's probably already over,
but if we can do it
properly this time, that's the key. We've been able to broadcast it like that today, so I think we'll be able to do it next time. It's
scary,
scary. I
'll translate it.
[Music]
[Music]  ]
Actually, I
have prepared that for you.
First of all, I would like you to tell me how you started fortune-telling.
Yes,
um, when you started fortune-telling.
Yes, I was the youngest junior
in the group. I see. I was the youngest member of Hololive.
At that time, I
was called senpai [music], and I
was able to say a lot of things.  I don't think so.I
see.So,
when I was wondering what it was like for even my seniors to be able to talk about so many different things, I
thought I'd like to try fortune telling.
It all started when I tried a little bit of fortune-telling.
[Music]
Can I ask you for a fortune-telling at the center? Please let me
hear your request. Now, I
can't post my card on that stream.  But, let's see if the
character's fortune-telling is
correct.The card on which that card is placed
will be submerged in water.Ah, I'm
addicted to Cat and Cat knocking over humidifiers
[Laughs]  There happened to be a
tarot card where I knocked over the humidifier, and
that's where the tarot card got soaked.
[Music]
Imagination Let's do it with our imagination
Yes, but we have cards.
Alright, Tiara-chan, what will you predict?
Please tell me what you want.
[Music]
Chiara. Yeah, I've
been obsessed with my cat for years now. All I
can think about is my cat.  I ca
n't feel any kind of love or romance for humans anymore.
Well, I mean, I just don't have any kind of romantic feelings at all, and I'm not
interested in them at all, and
that's why I'm so worried about them.  But,
umm, will the
characters be
able to fall in love again someday? For humans, I
see. I
'll translate it a bit. It
purifies the air. It's
like a purifier.
Yes, please.
Tarot cards.  The
meanings of upper and lower are very different.Yes, I
want Chiara-chan to decide whether to put the upper or lower part above that.I
see,
in the tarot deck we have,
should we put the right side at the top or the top left?
Please choose
Right or Left
Left
Then let's go.We
went to
find out what Chiara-chan thinks about love at the moment, and
also
[Music]
The future, and the other one was the near future.
Eh, that
[music]
Reality and the
future, the reality now, the
future now, the future now, I
see, and the comprehensive card,
total,
total OK,
what is a good card?
The character is that
cat,
until it dies.  It doesn't matter if you stay there, and in
reality, it doesn't matter what the result is, but if you
host it,
yes, it's true that it's
not so good right now, or rather, you
're isolated from the world right now.
[Music]  I
forgot the words
[Music]
That's right, I
'm away from the world,
so yeah,
I'm being
[Music]
Yeah, that's right, and the current card
is the
Ninja card,
right?  Hermit
That's the current card.
Hermit appears in the opposite position.
[Music]
[Laughs]
Well, it's like, you know, it's a
little bit isolated from the world.  I
get the impression that they're far apart, so
maybe it's a little
difficult to fall in love.
[Music]
Ok, I see. There are stars
in the future,
stars in the near future.  The card of "
Maybe you'll have an unexpected encounter. There's a
possibility. Yes, it's a pass.
[Music]
[Music] That
's the total card.
[Music] It
doesn't go well. It's difficult to achieve. Sometimes
people appear, but it's not like this.
Overall, I feel like there are a lot of things that don't go well,
but the future
is a star. Yes, the future is a star, so I feel very hopeful,
but I
feel like there are many things that don't go well overall.
That advice is,
yeah, the
Wheel of Fortune card in the reverse position, the shape of the
Wheel of Fortune card
in the reverse position, the
advice is so much that I end up
not moving forward.
It's fine as long as you
don't give up on love. It's okay. I haven't gone too far with love,
so I see, it's not going to go
well. Well, it seems like it's better to talk to each other alone.
I see.
[Music] It's
like that. I haven't
gone too far with it, so it's
okay.  I guess it's better not to
get too obsessed with someone even if you find someone you like.It's
okay if you can't find someone you like at all, it's okay
[laughter]  Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
it's definitely a present.  I don't know
what to say. There
are jackpot cards and what we all call SSR cards. I just got three SSR cards, so I drew four and
paused.
Since it's a good thing, it's somehow a good thing.I
mean, it's really something.I feel like I'm the type of person who has a strong and refreshing personality overall.It's my
emotions, or maybe I'm feeling
bold about doing something today.I
see, that's how strong my destiny is.  He's the one who has it.
Hoshi-sensei, I
won't plant it. I
see. It's interesting. Thank you.
Senpai: Yes, it
was fun.
[Laughs] Ever
since I heard that Myuu-senpai was doing this kind of tarot card fortune-telling.
When I was younger, I was
interested in tarot cards, so I
used to buy books and cards about them.Oh, they're
cute, aren't they?Even though I read tarot cards,
I'm not at all as good as my seniors.  I haven't been able to repaint it at all.
I still
received it, so I see.
That's why I learned so much.
[Music]
So,
for a change of pace, I'll start now.
[Music]
[Music] I'll
speed things up a bit from here.  Raise it up
Well, it would be
helpful if you could answer me properly in English. I'll do my
best.
Fighty Fighty.
So, are you ready? Do you
prefer the weather, hot or cold?
Gold Kono Gohan or Menkaan
Rise
Gust Turn Saizeria Kaoo
Gashitosa Twitter  Or
Instagram or something like that.
Apple or orange juice?
Which one do you prefer?
[Music]
Yeah, I might put pineapple on top of the pizza.  I wonder if it's
cold.
[Music] Do you
prefer spicy food or sweet food?
[Music]
Ok, do you like tea or coffee
? Do you eat a lot of coffee? Do you travel in famous big cities? I see,
metropolitan cities. Are you
naked when you sleep? Do you
cut off your clothes?
OK
[Music]
Favorite events
: Halloween, Christmas, Tanabata Easter,
etc.
Well, Christmas, no, no, I'm a
senior at the sea of Christmas trees.
Family Mart or Lawson? Do you
prefer text messages?
But all eyes are on it. Ah,
text message. Is it to
give or receive a present?
[Music] I see. I see, I'll
walk the distance of one station or take a train. Well, my
hands are on the train.
Yes, what color are my pants?
Even now, uh, I'm
not wearing them, so I'm
in this studio without any pants.  I
mean, I'm
wearing
no panties. Ah, I've taken a bath, so I don't have to wear any
punches. That's
helpful.
Actually, I have a question about that
next, so I
guess I'll
have to explain.
[Music]
What are you reading?
Tell me about the health method.
[Music]
Well, what is the
no-panties health method?
By taking off your panties at night before going to bed, you
improve blood circulation in your lower body.
[Music]
Is that all there is to it? Well, it's a healthy way of living that has been passed down
from grandma to mom, and from
mom to the house. Are you
serious,
Toshi-sensei
[Music]
[Music]  I
'm being told to
wear men's pants. What kind of pants are those? Men's material, ah. Noodles. Noodles are somen. No-no ramen. Somen noodles. Er, noodles are English. I could wear men's pants.
[Music]
Infinity with my gaze.
If there was something like that, it would be
delicious.  That's right.
[Music] I
learned a lot. Is
there any proof that this is
good for your health?
Well, I do
n't know if that's the case in our medical field,
but it seems that wearing panties is bad for marriage, and it's
constricting.
Next
Questioner
NEXTQuestion
[Music]
Wait a minute. The
way you balance games like OK Sports Day is
amazing. It's so
detailed and clever. It's like
Wolf or The
Closed School.  There
was also a contest, but I
got the wrong question.
[Music]
Also, I think you're very active in your singing career right now,
but what are your
thoughts on singing and what direction do you want to take the Congo challenge? Yes,
there are a lot of people who are good at singing.
[Music] I
wish I could sing songs that only Mio Ookami can sing.
[Music] I don't want to say that I'm
good, but that I want to be able to convey my feelings.  I
definitely
think that Howling is a song that suits Mu-senpai very well. Thank
you very much.
In the future, I would like to sing
songs in that cool style, or
even ballad-
type songs like that.
That
original song.  I want to release it as a song, and I'd
like to release an original ballad as well.
Oh, I'm going to play the future that I gazed upon. [Music] Hey, I'm
sure. The
cover of Senpai's Sparkling, Sparkling Roker Park, and Sparkle Spark is really great.  You
said in the comment that it was good,
and I'm sure I've heard it before,
but your voice sounds like it would be perfect for a ballad.
Yeah, thank you very much.  I'd like to
hear your thoughts on
that song, too.I wonder how you feel about that song or how confident you are about it
now.When it comes to
singing, right now, I
'm going to voice training, going to voice training, etc.
But,
you know, after all, this is what I
want to express, and I want to
sing.I feel like I'm still lacking in both body and technique for singing, so I
see, from now on, I want to fill in that part and do my best.  But I
want everyone to feel the impact of that.
[Music]
So
now I'm going to go look at the second clipping.  It
doesn't matter at all, but look
Let's go.
What kind of cutout should I make? I
think it's a cutout that shows Myuu-senpai's mom-like side. Mommy, please. What if Mio-chan says, "If Mommy leaves me," Soba-chan
goes looking for her new one.  I can't help
but burst into tears at Lamy. I'm already
preparing some spares. Do
n't be rude to the hairdresser. Hey, we can't
be friends if we don't do that. We can also be friends. Well, that's it.  There
seems to be a movie with that kind of relationship. I
want Mio to be my mom, but
Mio says she wants to stay friends. It's
just her mom. That's delicious.
Please, Subaru is a bit crazy. Isn't that crazy?
Welcome back, you're crazy.  It
makes you feel sad, right? I
didn't say it, but it sounds so funny.
[Laughs]
[Applause] That's
crazy. It's weird right now.
[Applause] It
felt a little good.
[Laughs]  I
wonder if it's okay to be happy even if someone says something painful to me.
[Music]
[Laughs] I wo
n't just leave it like that. It
's a lie.
What should I do when I'm caught in the middle? I'm not a
mom. No, I
'm a mom.
No, I didn't give
birth, so
that's a lie. I
may have given birth, but my
memories are being bought out.
[Laughs] Ah, you looked
down diagonally and laughed, your eyelids twitching.
[Music]
[Applause]
When you're in trouble, when you talk, you just quiet down and
sit down. You're enjoying the reaction, aren't you?
If each of you said that you were bullied, you'd
wonder which one of you was really bullying me. I was
thinking about a lot of things. I
can't do anything wrong.
[Laughs]  ]
[Laughs] That
's brave, isn't it? It
's TT.
This isn't Mama Mama. Well, that's
right, I made a bit of a mistake.
Rather than that, I want
everyone to see this gathering of these four people.
I also wanted to get an explanation of the group.
But let's change the room a little. OK
[Music]
Google. I
'd like to know what kind of group this is and how it was formed.
Ah.  But originally there was a group called OK FMfams, and
yes, that was the initials of the six members,
but
somehow the four members of Smog
ended up collaborating.
When I was thinking of a team name, I
used the initials of the OK Fams and
rearranged them, and I got Smoke.
Hey, I
wonder if those four people are particularly good in the middle.Oh yeah, of course, those members of the OK Fams.
We're really good friends, but Kokoro-Korone
and I get along really well, and Subaru and I often hang out together,
so when the two of them became that set, I
feel like they go well together in Smog.  I see. That
's right. It's
Kayu-senpai. This is Senpai.
[Music] It's
Fubuki-senpai.
[Music] I'm
looking forward to hitting you with all my might. It's
natural.
Now that we've seen that, let's
move on to the next question. It's a bit
long, but
um, what are your scores at the sports day?  His
method of distribution and game balance is
exquisite, and he
has worked as MC for many collaborative projects that do not rely on digital games, such as Word Wolf and Haiku Contest.  Is there anything that you
need to be considerate or secretive about?
[Music]
Well, I think the biggest thing is definitely the
casting part.
Casting the members.
Yes, that's right. I guess you could say it was a
struggle.
Well, after all, we didn't
talk much at all.  I'm not saying I don't have
any, but I'd like to have a group of members that I've talked to a
certain
extent and are
good friends with,
rather than members that I haven't had much contact with.  It may be that
each member is working hard to make a point where they can shine so that they
feel glad that they participated in this project.  I
was really inspired by what he said, and I
thought it would be better if we really thought about that kind of balance.The members bring out the
best in that girl in her everyday life.
I think there is definitely  The
more I look at it, the more I think about it, the more I
think I wish I didn't know
that.
As far as preparation goes, I'm pretty much like this except for that drunken feeling.There are quite a lot of
projects that are new to me, and
rather than doing the same project over and over again, I
create new projects all the time, so I guess
it's true that every time it's the same program.  It sounds
like it's a lot of work to make something from template 1 for a project.The
preparation is already quite a bit.It might
be the most difficult thing.  I
heard a lot of people saying that they wanted to do it again because it was a mess because it was so good, it was so good, and I think that's the case too.
Thank you very much. Can you please
do it again?
[Music]
Yama  I
have a plan that I would like to do more, so if I
can prepare a template for that, I'll do it again if I
can.In my
opinion,
[Music]
Since the 6th graders have arrived, I would like to ask Hololive to set up a kindergarten.Well,
kindergarten
Kindergarten Yes, kindergarten Kindergarten Okay,
Kindergarten is the best place to prepare.  Seriously,
if you're going to do a kindergarten, I'd
like you to bring in a character too.Because
there's a bubbly pacifier in the casual clothes.It's a
kindergarten, not a nursery school.
So, if
there's anything else you'd like to talk about,
please go ahead and move on to the next question.Okay, let's move on to the
next one.The next one is
also related, so I'm
proud of my favorite area of the projects I've worked on so far.  I'd
like to know what project you have in mind.
[Music]
That's right.
[Music] What
I like is
this. I don't know if I can translate it, Chiara-chan.
[Music]
There's something in the pot.
There's a fairy in the vase.
So, what kind of plan is that fairy, me, Subaru, and the shrine maiden? I
once did a project where we confided our worries to that fairy in the vase. I see.  I
wonder when it was? It feels like it was quite a while ago.
Last year or maybe last year's
face, or maybe last
year. 2020 will
be a sweets teacher.
[Music]
[Music]  It's like
the fairies are giving me advice on my troubles. Oh
yeah, that sounds interesting.
[Laughs]
That's um, I'm
glad it's crazy. A
natural 10-part special is
crazy. It
's morning.
[Music] I was
curious about this.  I think I'll go check it out. I
read that my senior's role as tsukkomi was good. It's
really
a little bit of this, a little bit of this, and I
found it. I'll post the URL so you can
see. I see.
Thank you for your interest
[Music]
HELLyoufingDS How do you come up with ideas like this?I was
sleeping and suddenly couldn't think of
anything.Also, Subaru and I talked on that Discord, and I was like, ``This project looks interesting.''  It's
like it's escalating, so it's
called a play story, right now.
[Music] They're a
good match,
Bi-priority and Subaru-senpai.
Maybe it's a good thing that we're both good at different things.I see.That
's true.Next
question on OkOk.It's almost the end
of our 1st anniversary, and Nyuu-
senpai is broadcasting, ``Eh,
get taller.''
When we talked, Oporium-senpai was Mu-senpai.
The scene where you encouraged me by saying that you look like miso soup touched many people's hearts.How
do you feel about your height now?
Ah, at that time, we had
only been active for about a year, and as
new and new members started coming in, I
felt like we were losing out in terms of individuality.Hmm,
in terms of structure, I felt like we were losing out in terms of individuality, and
then...  There was a part of me that
wanted to be more unique,
but I couldn't be as unique as I wanted to be,
so I
guess that's why I wanted to make an interesting broadcast.  I
was really worried, right?
[Music] I
understand, but when I talked to that rice porridge, I was like,
Yeah,
Gomi Mio-chan is miso soup, so it
's like miso soup.
After he told me about it, miso soup always
comes with rice, so it's an
absolutely necessary part.  Even
if I eat steak all day, every day, it
's hard,
and sometimes I find myself thinking that miso soup is the way to go.So
it's good to be taught that being like miso soup is your individuality.That's
right, right now.  Well,
even though I'm not unique,
all the fans who support me still
like us as we are now.  I
don't worry about it or try to force myself to change,
but I think it's okay to have fun and dress in a way that suits me, so
maybe I won't
be in a hurry like I used to be.I see, that's fine with me.  That's what I thought at that time, and I
still do now. Well, that's when I
realized it, so I'm able to
do it peacefully and happily.
OK, and then...
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
Sorry for the long story.
No, I think it's a good story. Seriously,
when I saw the cutout of the character, I
was really moved.
[Music] There
was a time, right? I see,
Miu-senpai. I
know exactly how you feel.  It really
resonated with me.I
think it's understandable that there are people who are in charge of MCs, like Kirara-chan, or the caterpillars, so I think it's understandable, but I wish the
MCs would stand out a little more.
Because the guests won't stand out,
[Music]
There are times when we'll hold back a
little. I see. That's the kind of thing where you
want to stand out, too, so maybe there's
something going on with the gym group.
[Music] I see.  I'm
sure there are people among my fans who like that kind of MC, so I guess it's a bit
like that.I'm
going to cry.So let's
go ask questions.NEXTNEXTThere's
still one more
[Music]  That's
it. Congratulations, Mestermio-senpai, for recently achieving your 3rd anniversary. [Music] Masde. Eh. What plans or goals do you have for the coming year? Well, this past year, hmm. It's
difficult, but we've
been doing it for a long time.
Yeah, because I've been doing it for a long time, I want to remember to have fun and stream it. I see. Yeah,
Shiseido seems like it's good, and I've
been saying that for a long time, but yeah, that's it.
All of Hololive
wants to go to Budokan together, but Makuhari
Messe is already there. Well,
Hololive Japan is going, but
Makuhari Message is already
big enough. I
mean, Makuhari Messe is probably even
bigger.  I've
gotten to the point where I think it
depends on the hall, but
which one is bigger?
[Music] If it
's just the hall for live concerts, then...
Budokan is
different,
right? There are a lot of stairs and things like that, I
see, but the
concerts for me and the 3rd gen members are also
held in an arena like the Super Arena,
Tokyo Dome Tokyo Dome City
Hall.  I
think it's getting to the point where it's a little more affordable, and I
think there are a lot of Japanese idols who are very famous, even at the Budokan.
As an idol otaku who knows how to feel, I've often
heard of it.It
's a huge martial arts hall.
[Music]
Makuhari Messeim Legran
Budokan I
want to go.  I
think Makuhari Mess is pretty big, right? It's
true, but up until now, we have
n't been able to accommodate a lot of customers.
But even so, there were a lot of
people who wanted to come and visit us in person, and I
guess that's when they realized that they were so supportive.You
know, the management always has a little bit of a
goal.  I'm not setting this up, but there were a lot of things like, ``It
sold better than I expected,'' and ``
Tickets were early.'' Maybe that's why I
had the courage to rent a big venue this time, so it makes sense.
That's
true. It's not tragic,
is it
?
[Music]
Um, there's actually a song at the end, but
before that, the last question is yes.
For my seniors, I
think of Hololive as a group of friends who can run together to the end.
Hmm, I see, that's an OK attitude.
[Music] For
people who say things like this, I
think this is the first time I've heard it, so I think it's fine. It's
cool, it's cool, it runs all the way to the end.
But it's also a little howling.
[Music]  I feel
like I'm going to run all the way to the end. Yeah, OK. I hope we can all continue to run together like this. That's great.
Finally,
let's advertise before the promotional song public. Please promote this.
Thank you very much. This is
Waku Waku Every Day.  Well, the
trailer for Fubuki and Mio was
announced the other day, and it's currently
being distributed on Apple Music, etc., so
please give it a listen if you'd like.Thank you in advance.
Yes, that's right
. The
other one is here.
Here it is. Since it's the 3rd anniversary, the
3rd anniversary goods
are on sale at Hololive's official goods shop. Ok Google
[Music] It
seems like the deadline has been set.
1  It's only available until the beginning of the month, so
if you buy the whole set, you'll
definitely get a postcard with a handwritten autograph
[Music]
Action
So at the end, I waited for a moment to say hello.  Is it
better if I don't go back? OK, now let's say
hello. Thank you everyone for watching today. I'd
like you to tweet your thoughts. Everyone,
how was your day? How was it?
Today, I spent so much time with that Chiara-chan.  It
was a great pleasure to talk to you. Thank you. I'm
also happy. You said
that you got really excited when you
talked about cats at first, but I'm sure you're really happy about the cats you were talking about. With
someone who understands what you're talking about, I
'd love to chat with you again and collaborate with you again.
That's what I thought. [Music] I'm going to say hello in German, but I think I'd like you to say it with me. OkOk. Well, to make it easier to read, I'll write it in the chat and in the disco. [Music] Something like this.
Yeah.  Ok, I'd be happy if you could watch this with me and let me know.
[Music]
Well, tomorrow
we'll see Chiara's
new product, the
new watch, so everyone, please take care of it.
Yes, please.
Miyu-senpai
[Music]
[Music]  The
landscape flows
majestically, and
in the sad days, the
hand that was extended to me is gentle, and the
slight fever that
drips with my heartbeat seems to defy the wind.Because I've
lived so long, when I
meet you, I
realize that I'm no longer alone.In the
future,
[Music]
Because I'm here, I won't get lost. I'll
follow the shining path.
[Music]
Because I'm powerless, I'll
seek companions.
Because I'll spill out. I'll
light a fire and
evolve with my underachievers. No
one will do this flickering.  I've
decided that I believe in you, so I can overcome anything and
everything The
only flower that blooms in this darkness,
whether out of fear or admiration,
I run through the night sky, fighting for it.This
story that you hide and hide is forever in the future.I don't want to lose, but my
passion is
in this love.  Let's ride
[Music]
Even without wings to fly, we could hold hands, so we
chose this fate
[Music]
When we freeze, our memories echo silently, and we confirm each other's wounds over and over again.
You are the only one who is afraid of the realizations and echoes of the
road that echoes in the darkness.The night we mourn together with the silver-colored village.Morality is
transmitted through the radio waves.Thoughts are
in the heart.Let's go there.With
you next to me, I
won't get lost.Light
by light, I walk down the road one by one.
[Music]
Yeah, my hair never stops