foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
gosh it's loud
okay
one
[Music]
thing
yeah yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
hello welcome everybody to the first
Fall Hollow Tunica
[Applause]
it took some time but we're finally all
here
my name is
be kind thank you
Disney
yeah
just humans
anymore
yeah second up is me I I am the first
real real bird actually in whole life
history
[Music]
I'm from the first round of whole life
English
I am Phoenix not chicken Phoenix
[Applause]
look at my garden phone picture it looks
like a phoenix doesn't it
[Applause]
[Music]
and next door
yes I'm raining from hollow life
Indonesia generation
I am people not turkey
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
please introduce yourself
hello
from the second generation of hollow
life English I am an owl not a towel
never happened I'm not a towel OverWatch
um
United
[Laughter]
okay okay
at least recently we have another Hollow
bird cycle
is
JP 6th generation
Horror
Story new member nice to meet you
yeah
today is what what kind of bird this car
hook yeah
exactly really cool
um
thank you
that's not even so bad
yeah so beautiful
[Music]
[Laughter]
so guys uh today we are here with these
total Tony members and by the way if if
you have not seen it yet
[Music]
I requested for the sake of hurricane
do you guys have it on the screen
yeah thank you for putting it on the
screen I got it because I've just felt
like oh we were such a cute lovely group
we need something to connect one another
group
[Music]
please make use of it okay
[Applause]
this is so cute thank you
still the steps on the bottom so cute
right yeah yeah you're so cute
I also think so um
[Music]
the Japanese Horror Story members are
actually pretty good at English so it it
will probably be no problem of course
yeah
English no problem
[Music]
[Laughter]
just sell the sweat
oh
[Music]
positive positive thinking positive
thinking
I hate coffee
[Laughter]
I think we should start uh with normal
normal mode but we can try other modes
too later maybe okay and just a reminder
uh the prompts please write in English
um
first round first round midnight jumpy
okay
[Music]
normal turns or whatever let's just go
with the basics
okay
um
hello Birds
hi everybody hi Chad nice to see you how
you doing we're finally doing it we're
finally doing the collaboration that
everybody was waiting for did you like
the opening
I was waiting to use the opening for a
while yeah finally finally originally
that was only
um Subaru Reina and me but they updated
it to move my character
what uh they updated it so that there's
more
um all of us okay uh dear Lord
um big mouth
and
the May
who wrote this maybe maybe it was Elena
I feel like mume wouldn't uh write that
herself how much time there's actually a
lot of time
uh she has something here
there's so much time I am confident
in making this work
uh uh how do I look like what do I look
like
I'm just gonna keep it simple here I
have no body only legs and arms uh
um
give me the braids
and the the feathers
well people understand this
oh dear
um
[Music]
and does this look like mermaid maybe if
I add some color well almost half time
um
Maybe
you know the thing that you have in the
back of your mouth
ah okay and then
um
like this I really love this mermaid
coat
I love her quote
I'm not really miss playing garlic phone
it was so popular for a while
uh
and then everybody stopped playing it
but I had to revive it
um
and just make some make sounds
brownie here okay beautiful
beautiful we have the white here the
white goes uh
here okay yeah whatever I mean if that
doesn't look like her then I don't know
this looks like me now let's just add
some orange beautiful
nose
okay I'm done I had some extra time and
I'm done
[Music]
next please
all right oh
my God you did it I know they collapsed
didn't they uh very recently
kissing oh
[Music]
wow um Ruby has her mouth very open
so she's really going in for the Deep
kiss
French kissing while Mumbai is just uh
kind of like not sure about it she's a
bit shy but it seems like odoi seems to
be really
[Music]
um the proactive one in this
relationship
okay next please move my loading ah
ah she has that
um membership icon too I think I use it
on Discord sometimes
um
foreign
by the way I was hoping for mermaid
cursed out but she said that she's using
her Mouse because her
um
her
tablet broke
that is so sad
right we need to get to our new tablet
because otherwise how are we gonna get
those
uh cursed artworks ever again
um
foreign
that's already perfect I I
I'm exactly drawing what uh was asked
for but I don't know if they will be
able to recognize it anyway
you're sure
um
[Music]
I don't know what that looks like
it is
hey yosho
[Music]
um
uh and then I want to add some color we
can add it not so strongly
yeah
[Music]
nice nice
almost too beautiful to be true
foreign
by the way before before the stream I
was setting up
um my OBS like everything of Discord and
all that and with the reactive images
and and
um then when we got together in the chat
roommate and Elena were like how are you
gonna how are you gonna show each other
on screen like uh and I was like I'm
gonna do reactive the the pop-up ones
and women was like oh I'm I'm personally
too too lazy to do that
and Reina wasn't
wasn't into it ever so I was like do you
want my health because I had all the
URLs that they can just use like that oh
oh talking about that before uh Tony
vacation
and then I gave everyone my my resources
and I taught them how to use it also the
Japan members because they haven't used
it like that before I think
um
yeah yeah everybody got my reactive
images if you check their other streams
I think you'll see it
I taught them how to use it so I feel I
feel very proud and useful now
yeah smart smart boob
and this probably comes from uh because
uh I was I was oh I'll tell you later
hello
perfect
we need more more difficult prompts next
time
yeah many birds that's okay that's no
problem
um let's look at it together okay
let's go we start with Poland starts
dancing
[Music]
I'm curious I can hear it
okay
[Music]
I will never listen to chat again I'm
saving I saved it
oh
sorry
wow look at me
yeah
um before before the stream started uh
me and Elena told uh Subaru Santa and
the other side we're going to the
Maldives to make them yeah yeah yeah
yeah and they were very excited to join
so understand if I want to come too
right
I surprised this Horror Story
yes
[Laughter]
the one that mermaid Drew everybody is
there even though the one that Subaru
Drew one is missing so good time for me
you added me again
[Music]
oh I love it
was your idea okay okay
oh good no problem
you guys all know the mermaid loading
icon the membership
okay next one ah
[Music]
it's you
wow
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm happy
thank you
sorry
I'm not good
it's me
nice
um
okay
it's fast yes
[Music]
okay uh okay we need to make this more
interesting
[Music]
um
putting sunscreen Sun
milk on Kiara I hope if this comes to
Subaru or Louis that they understand
if this came from Simba then I will take
the sign oh dear
um um um
um
I will make myself into a chicken just
for for the sake of simplicity
how to draw a duck
what does a duck look like [\h__\h]
looks like
[Music]
and only know what the feet looks like
why do I not know what a duck looks like
when I am I have often collabed with one
what is on their head ah thank you guys
I out of Camp oh yeah the cap will will
help
uh
[Music]
um uh uh oh God this doesn't even look
like me now uh here hat and
had the head okay
okay oh my God boing boing are we all
boy oh you're really only
wait unless at least no one was flat
Chester
um
Holo Tony
balloon boy
looks like balloons to me I would love
to pop those balloons
it's just Elena I think Elena is the
only one who uses that emoji what
what kind of
fun is
[Music]
heck eh
one two three four
[Music]
little time
wait why why did I make it rain in the
smallest
haha
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] wait I even
had some more time whatever I don't know
ah
at least it looks like we're eating each
other
[Music]
you rock band that's a great idea
can we stop um asking for a full holiday
prompts because drawing five people
looks like it's really tough but oh my
God I'm in the center with the E guitar
Rocking In The Middle
nice oh
that was so fast
it's so difficult you right yeah okay so
many people use holotoni so I always
have to draw draw five people
sorry stop
let me putting some milk
oh my God it's nice
on the beach
[Laughter]
on the beach I like this one that's
Elena has a nice booty
the first thing I drew nice
guys
[Applause]
[Music]
so cute
she can hold them
okay hold gently
wow that looks cursed Kauai
[Music]
a mix of a human and a Kappa and the
duck
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is we need to censor the stream yo
need to monetize
haha oh everybody
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice interpretation mommy nice nice nice
it is a bird it's bird well dear yeah I
like your
Pac-Man anyway
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's a good misunderstanding nice yeah
the Browns are so short because we are
only so first time should we you play a
different round a different mode
oh
um
[Music]
wait oh I'm just gonna draw something
random uh okay
um
[\h__\h] I can think what am I drawing uh
um I should have thought about this
um [\h__\h]
um oh [\h__\h] I don't know
I don't know I don't know I don't know
what to do
I don't know what to do
I don't know what to do it
I have so much time though
um what do I draw I want to draw what do
I draw guys
um
no I don't know
um bright empty my head is so empty
[Music]
um um
um okay so we're gonna do
um
two three four five we still have a lot
of time okay so now I'm gonna draw uh
hold on uh Tony member in each one of
them
[Music]
foreign
that might be very chaotic when someone
tries to recreate it hopefully
uh but that took too long to first of
all decide about it so mine is not gonna
be so good either
[Music]
this is Elena
um
maybe a little blue and then we do a
Subaru senpai
my tablet is sinking oh that's just
black
and then we do really
[Music]
uh
I love those Wing flaps that she has
those are so cute
and go to where we're going
oh blue big ocean
[Music]
yeah super December was saying like oh
you're going to the Maldives I want to
go to why you not invite me and I was
like super simple are you sure you would
have gone because you never have time
let's be realistic Kim sweater sound
like she was like yeah you're right but
still then we were like we should one
day do a full horror story trip even if
it's not like a full-on
uh one two week vacation
hmm
uh no okay awesome oh
that looks okay
I forgot the pink forgot it thank you
[Music]
nice
and I mean I still have so much time
this is gonna be so stressful later I
remember this this was really
really stressful
because in the beginning having so much
time we tried to create something really
really uh complicated Yago pilot but
Yago is so difficult to draw like
how do you how do you draw someone who
looks so normal
[Music]
like I don't know
how about we say
soul
neck
and of course as a pilot you just use a
normal car
um wheel what else
obviously what else
okay
um
is this what a plane looks like I feel
like I'm missing something important
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
let's add some details
[Music]
by the way this is not any more about
guessing
uh what it is but just recreating it so
no problem there's some palm trees
hell yeah and uh
fish
beautiful many efficiency I should drop
gouda no it's kind of too late now it's
kind of too late no
let's go
Zoom
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that
all right when I start drawing I can't
look at it anymore Ryan I just have this
moment to look at it is this a wait I
thought it was a chicken first but
that's looking at the Hat that's so
understand by eating a strawberry
oh my God that looks so
cursed
that looks like something Moonlight
would draw but she has only a mouse no
way she could draw that with a mouse
right
foreign
oh God the time is really much less than
before
oh there is there a feeling too [\h__\h]
there was a filling tool why did I not
just use the filling tool
oh my God
ah the Hat
um
uh
oh God
is it blue on the side and the
strawberry
it's a tomato No it's not a tomato it's
a strawberry look at this okay now it
looks like a
[Music]
H okay
uh uh this is just Horror Story together
also I think also on the beach probably
that looked like the sun and
um
um holy [\h__\h] um orange orange
yeah yeah
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
they are grooving yes uh mushrooms
mushroom mushroom uh
um mushroom mushroom Reina
mushroom mushroom Lena
I had the ponytail on the wrong side for
Elena before
wow mushroom
uh me kissing someone no whispering in
someone's ear
[Music]
laughs
[Applause]
there's no time my arm my arm hurts my
arm hurts I don't know what to do [\h__\h]
um okay
yeah that was so difficult
still restful very stressful yes
stressful
oh my God
yeah right it was it was very Speedy
yeah it's not speedy oh my god let's
take a look at what what it turned out
to be
sure yeah
I was not sure what to draw
um took me a while
I saw this
oh my God
[Laughter]
we can't be helped it's just no time
the biggest problem was
interpretation that got rid of
everything else
foreign
oh
yeah
it just looks like I'm sexually
harassing someone
why did you make them sweat
because the ASMR was just too much to
handle
um
it's so good
you need to put that up on the on my fan
art hashtag it's working oh yes oh yes
it was from that prom my my previous
problem because I failed I'll save that
one that one is precious
all right somebody said bye
um mushroom I like the Mario Kart stream
right now
um
[Music]
I missed something important I'm sorry
sorry moment yeah she has something to
do but besides
um
okay
a picture sorry I'm sorry
like memorize
oh my God
yeah depending on what you see you can
learn someone's personality
um
[Music]
wake up
no way I was like this looks like
roommate style but no way she can do
that with a mouse
oh I have the time oh nice
it's so cute
[Music]
um the mermaid one is very terrifying
though bye
[Laughter]
um
drooling is that cherry tomato or a
strawberry mummy I was going for I was
going for strawberry okay okay okay
one more one more one more okay
um think about what you want to draw
[Music]
um
holiday
[Music]
yeah
different place different place I have
an idea okay
okay what idea I can't tell you yet uh
we're doing nothing yeah we're just
knock off again one more round it was
very stressful oh dang it um and now
that we can try animation animation
[Music]
thank you
okay
okay so my idea it is uh
um
[Laughter]
can still hear you
[Music]
um
my idea was
um I don't know how to draw it though
I don't know where to start uh Tony
study at school
mmm
and now the back side let's for example
have mermaid
or we only do certain members
but now we have so much time we should
start doing this properly
yeah okay I love her feathers I want
feathers like that on the top of my head
oh [\h__\h] uh
um uh who else is easier to drop in the
back maybe Reina
uh right sides your left side
uh wait what what how how to
she also has like cute feathers here
let's make them blue
nice uh on the table maybe
[Music]
um
uh I don't know can I draw all of us at
this point
maybe ah I have an idea we'll draw
Rooney as well and then me and Subaru
Senpai are gonna be teaching because
we're the first Hollow Birds so we're
gonna teach them how to bird
yeah that sounds good to me
[Music]
yeah it's a burp class
oh
verb and it's gonna be difficult to
recreate to when you're lacking time
one oh
one nice
[Music]
foreign
a tie
and I'm gonna be there too
[Music]
what do I look like uh-huh
remind me to draw Lui
are we still good we're still good
foreign
I get a tie too I don't even know how to
make a tie
okay this is starting to look pretty
good don't forget okay here we are here
we go no wait let me add some color
first
I'm starting to look pretty damn good
Imagine Green although it's not really
green but there's no torquoise uh
there is no turquoise
um
right
we still have more than enough time I
don't know what the back of somebody
said this cap looks like right now is it
blue or red or
anyway
now
um
okay so we have
to where do they come from in the back
those wings should I just start there
okay no problem no problem don't don't
get stressed out and then short hair
relatively short hair
and just add some some color and then we
could [\h__\h]
oh my god there was an undo button
okay okay
how to be a bird
okay
okay okay it took me a while to set the
whole thing up oh [\h__\h]
can I make it green can I make it green
um maybe if I quickly
close the edges
nice
I'm proud of this
yeah wow that's a
combination of all of us no oh [\h__\h] what
it starts with chicken then I see a
peafowl uh
what the [\h__\h] what
[Music]
uh
is that like turducken but with all of
us what would you call that
oh dear so it's like a Transformer out
of all of us maybe
there were some part of movement up here
like some poop
where was the Super where was the Subaru
and it had like
was this what movie created
well what part of that was super noodle
and also there was like what Fire Red
around it
it looks bald
the base is a duck and then where's the
chicken part of it I guess okay and this
could be a duck
oh [\h__\h]
well I mean I tried
that the Hat
oh well oh well it's okay it's okay
we got we got most of it down the people
feathers were important there memories
are drawing what is this uh
okay
um
why do I start here I don't know
we will be holding hands we will be
holding hands
yeah I'm looking forward to it oh my God
it's gonna it's gonna be next month I'm
so excited for it I've been thinking
about it a lot yesterday
[Music]
what is this this is raining in front of
a screen
got you
um mm-hmm
what do I do with this
what else is there to draw I have time
left over one is there to draw I'll make
it
I'll make it better
what now
question mark
what is this I
I well I'm not even supposed to know the
holy [\h__\h]
what am I eating bread
[Music]
foreign
pressure
[Music]
what's what's her problem with bread
once you're angry at toast is this
related to a stream
great good job oh my God
wow nice smells good ones
IES
oh but God but everyone did their best
I'm sure
power power yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
apparently in order to be a bird you
have to know the ABC
[Music]
maybe someone can recreate this and make
it into a proper fan art I want to say
it is so cool um
yeah what did I draw oh
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Laughter]
because of black hair
[Music]
that's not been used enough make use of
it yes spicy yeah
[Music]
let's go
yes
um
are you rice girl face scary face when I
panic
just funny right yeah
you would think you want to portray
yourself in a cute way but no you're the
one who portrays yourself in a
terrifying way the most
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
simple art
um with even less time I drew a bit more
complicated
and I added the earring oh yeah
[Laughter]
I think so I think
I love Lane
we love Nina oh
[Music]
hey
guys
okay
it's like yeah pteroducken but everyone
together
yeah
okay what is if turd Duncan is turkey
duck and chicken what is Terry Duncan
with Hawk and Owl uh you mean Flamingo
wow
[Music]
can go
it was exciting as well
um
it's like a dating app
do you want to try animation
okay
[Music]
um
um um
okay we should keep this simple though
because
it's gonna be recreated and animated
I want to I'm just gonna use kfp as a
setting
kfp
[Music]
Mr cashier and I don't know what's gonna
happen here what are we gonna make
Happening Here
I don't know I don't know
well actually I'm in stair decision what
they're gonna make
to happen English don't go but it would
be fun if we start out on the bottom and
then the birds go up on the counter and
dance on the counter
but
that is just my idea I'll leave it up to
them
uh
[Music]
oh maybe I can give a hint
uh with like a thinking bubble
uh
uh what does my uniform even look like I
don't even know anymore
[Music]
okay so we do a thinking bubble
um
music maybe they can do something with
that
they'll probably draw the thinking
bubble let me foreign
what if we draw a speaker here
I'm the speaker here maybe then just
drop me dancing that's okay
I think I'm giving them enough signs
to do something with this
um
that's that's enough
too much
nah it's okay it's okay it's okay
they'll work with that
they will work with it
I believe now let's see what I get
mummy trying to eat us uh-huh do we get
to see it yes okay okay beautiful so
we're gonna make them catch up
uh-huh
[Music]
um
we're gonna make Muma actually catch up
and succeed
why is there
I don't know so
because she gets faster
it will it will uh the feathers go
backwards
[Music]
but we can kind of what is this this
looks like a vegetable
it's like we're fishing not verbs hold
of fish
Hollow fish let's go
[Laughter]
oh yeah this I don't know what the color
I can't see it so well I think this is
this is correct
and then Subaru sampai is
I'm adding the hats now
uh there we go
so we're getting closer
let's make some more movements signs
here
burps kiss a lot yeah there's been a lot
of like
kissing scenes today which I'm very
happy about
I like to see it you like to see it
don't you like to see it I'm done
and and they never sleeping as I'm
looking forward to our vacation isn't it
nice to to have such a tasty Vibe going
on I feels good
foreign
I must say that like
we love each other we have we all have
such positive Minds
and so much love in our hearts
and this is a good thing about the Holy
verbs that we're also very outgoing all
of us right
it's really typical for whole verbs yeah
overflowing with love and goofiness
the status oh my God now this time we
have no mumei uh think about chicken
I think and then Ruby crying in the back
or like being sweaty
now what do we do with this
um
I
I will I will uh continue this
[Music]
by actually giving her
what she wants
uh
right so she already has it because we
gotta take that step it's important
um and then is that really the fact
though I wonder
I keep the heart
um
[Music]
no I don't know why why rui would be so
worried or nervous about it
is it her
oh grab it from the foot button maybe we
can
um
make it look like that I'm just gonna
say this is rui I hope so
I need pink she doesn't have that pink
hair
um
[Music]
maybe we can
make it
explode like
wow it's gone because
[Music]
I took it
our mummy took it so we just have these
lines around it you know I think I've
seen like something like this before
yeah
you think what do you think what do you
think guys
to add some detail it's not really about
that anymore but
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah like oh wait
let's go where did it go
yeah yeah
I think I think I think good heartbroken
ah
why
is this my booba but what's happening
they're giving me too much Freedom here
oh maybe
I realize that I'm naked
and cover myself up
and be very embarrassed about it
I have to hide my
badonka donks
[Music]
uh
yeah
like that like that
and then even my hair goes like what
[Music]
what was it you kinda stop taking my
clothes
um
um and then we make me very embarrassed
all right can I change
okay
just realized you could change the color
here
foreign
but I do wonder how this started out
maybe it was supposed to be something
completely different
[Music]
yummy
help
oh still so much time maybe I'm giving
myself some no I don't want to change it
too much like if I give it skin color
it's gonna look like different from the
original
oh well uh
give me feathers at least why you forget
about my photos offenders Fetchers can't
forget about it okay what does this look
like
okay nice
up too much time
oh yeah maybe maybe my boobs have been
inflated
yeah
more Bubba too much Bubba to handle
[Music]
Too Much Time on My Hands
there we go
now it's what the [\h__\h] mermaid now it's
mummy
um
licking
[Music]
girls can you be less sensitive
you don't really want me to add orina's
tongue to this studio
well that gave her an ear
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
I don't want to support this Elena is
mine
[Music]
yeah if it's mermaid and I'm gonna say
you are a little pervert
[Music]
God no we can't
what's happening
so now
I cannot support this
[Music]
Maybe
but that's
not not good enough maybe that's not
enough what's like change not enough
change
um
what else could I add
make it
no that's that's mummy
I don't know
um
maybe maybe we add suddenly it turns
into like a like an animal
oh God
it's like Hello
nice to meet you
[Laughter]
alien tongue
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
what's going on why is everyone drawing
such sensitive scenes huh
fantasies
which one are you talking about what are
we talking about yeah
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
did you get my idea
let me do it yeah
cute stuff oh you guys added who's who's
joining who's that who is that yeah
oh my God
so scary yeah why are you so angry I'm
downloading it what station
[Applause]
originally was I want I was um working
at kfp and then music was playing so I
wanted to start dancing dancing
oh
I thought it was someone else I thought
it was raining
[Applause]
[Laughter]
this looks great in animation it does
nice animation
until I got closer too yeah and the in
the end it turned into a little snake
what what what is that but it's not
happening it's originally supposed to be
me really yeah
thank you
I'm naked I need to hide my boobies
oh my God
exploding oh my God
[Applause]
oh my God
oh
ah is that is that
who is that in the back though
I do I think
oh I made it into it please
I think
um
I when I look like a picture
[Music]
thank you
[Laughter]
nice why are we fishing
I didn't
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
I stood what was happening this is the
best animation cycle
[Music]
do we taste good mermaid you ever so
sweet
[Music]
I want to try uh wait uh do we still
have oh do we still have time can we do
one more animation one more
[Music]
maybe afterwards you can have breakfast
or you're gonna go back to sleep
I'll do both or I'll just eat more of
you guys okay
I'll give you some substitutes from kfp
okay
eat kfp
okay okay let's go
[Applause]
what should we draw
um how about
a shopping scene
uh
who was who's going shopping chat
foreign
so someone can like go shopping
and go in there
and uh then or maybe I've moved that
over to the side
is shopping Dana's shopping for
swimsuits maybe and I need to change
that though
let's have banana shopping for swimsuits
who knows if she already
has done
[Music]
this looks like look like swimsuits
it looks like glasses
uh
like bottoms and tops oh God we have no
time
uh
okay
swimsuits
okay and then Reyna
stands here
and thanks
oh God oh God
and takes takes both of them okay
oops okay
we gotta keep it simple
how to keep it simple
um
okay
I think
I think that could work
[Music]
maybe maybe I should get rid of that
part completely so they don't have too
much to draw
what we had before uh
that looks like really
um so Savannah is trying to explain the
situation from before maybe
somebody was crying because there's no
chicken because he really ate it so uh
Subaru takes the phone
and order some chicken herself
hmm
her hair goes the other way
yeah yeah yeah yeah that works
[Music]
okay let's add some brown sugar some
crispy fresh crispy fried chicken from
kfp who who wants to be eaten myself
who's gonna be the one
[Music]
me me I volunteer nice you guys are so
cooperative
Sasuke I'm so proud of you guys you
always put the others first to other
people's hunger yeah
[Music]
um
please
[Music]
and then let's make the phone red
or it could be a banana phone if we made
it yellow oh well
okay I hope I hope they can work with
this you know
he's out of the picture now
she ate she ate the chicken so
no somebody has to take care of herself
um or I don't know I don't have time
I don't know like what is she doing oh
my god wow it's cute
is that um
is that a chicken or a duck
and the big sun the big sun is taking
over the chicken
there's an arrow here
where is the sun no it looks rapper or
scared
so duck
[Music]
um
how about we make the sun explode
how about we make it explode
ah wait uh
[Music]
let's make a big
all right where's the there's no bucket
is there no bucket
hmm
[Music]
foreign
that's also that could work
[Music]
oh God I don't have much time I only
have lunch time
[Music]
so promising to me Piada
foreign
um
make it look more like me by adding the
hair
it's a man
hi
[Music]
ah
okay I'm gonna eat you up no don't worry
I'm just gonna give you warmth and and
love and light yes and son
um Sun
[Music]
what is this everybody thinks food
Elena about to eat
what is that is that
what is that a magnifying glass or
about to eat
um
a mirror
no Nani
it's a steak though it's not even
chicken
um
how about
[Music]
I have an idea
uh
[Music]
trust me guys
trust me on this one
[Music]
we're gonna push her away
and because someone else wants to eat
the food
oh yeah
we still have time we still have time
is this supposed to be a spoon
so maybe how about someone because super
Senpai really seems to want to eat some
good food right now
go away
go away my food
it doesn't really look like her hat
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
no she's just not the she's not the
police in this moment she just wants to
have some food you know
[Music]
huh whatever
I like the energy thank you oh this is
uh and Louis becoming uh Super Heroes
with the glasses from Louis
um or they're about to start boxing each
other
foreign
[Music]
Fly Away
oh oh yeah oh yeah
oh yeah
oh
foreign
a lot of aggressive art that I'm doing
here but um don't worry about it
[Music]
welcome punch
wow your hair goes to the side and there
was no pink hair originally but we're
gonna add some pink here
um I'm gonna give her some bangs
actually
okay what does it look like okay nice
maybe add some pink here so it looks
like she got punched
Hawk punch yeah not Falcon Punch it's
Hawk punch or Louis punch
um
[Music]
trying to add some special effects but
foreign
oh well
okay
hmm
I ran out of liquids but this is
probably the last round anyway
we really gotta give props to a movie by
the way for waking up really [\h__\h]
early I don't I think it's like
I don't know what exactly time but what
exact time it is but I'm probably like
what
four or five six a.m I don't know
ah oh it's already done hello hello
hello hello
[Music]
wow hi hi hi hi
um
[Laughter]
this is the last last round let's see
what masterpieces we have created
yes please yes let's go
okay
shopping for a swimsuit
oh
yeah
oh boy
where will this go
okay what what turned into person
Falls over
wow I don't know she got stopped for
eating after eating the bikini top she
becomes a person
[Music]
[Applause]
I just wanted to see you Dana try on
some cute swimsuits but okay this is
fine
I got my phone animation for you
okay all right
next up yeah
oh
what situation is this
button
[Applause]
slowly punch moving
leave it to me it ain't it to read your
mind
wow
I like it thank you
he likes it it looks really lucky he has
an animation too good job
[Music]
a little confused
I thought it was a mirror
[Music]
comes pushes away Dana and wants the
food for herself
who's trying to get me to eat something
suspicious
[Applause]
this steam looks really nice though the
weight goes up it's really nice it was
supposed to be a single hair but that's
how it ended up
[Music]
next up next
oh
kfp
[Applause]
[Laughter]
a
oh my God
[Applause]
I am a creature this is
so good amazing
yes
because because
[Music]
um
food please
yes yes last one last round
oh
uh
it gets bigger
getting bigger surprise
boy
okay okay thank you
[Applause]
everybody
[Music]
[Applause]
it's a bird eat bird World After All
yes it's tough out there that's why no
we have to we have to be strong together
each other strongest bird wins
well the strongest bird is is me because
I am a phoenix and and I will revive no
matter what
hide in trees if you get eaten where do
you revive Yara
oh my gosh where do you revive that that
is a that's a different story I cannot
say that
but you know because the bird eat bird
world you know what we should collab
someday I mean
Super Smash Brothers
I want to punch punch Birds oh
[Music]
did you play Super Smash Brothers before
I have but I'm not good at it
that's good because
yeah
we're gonna be bad together but yes
we'll smash each other that's okay
you would like to see that in a
different meaning too no
I was talking about oh yeah I don't know
no we are playing together yeah okay
just playing together we're just playing
smash
I'm glad we finally got a collab out of
all of us yeah
[Music]
thank you
yes
we're the biggest group of something I
think in hollow life really yeah
maybe maybe we can do more stuff
together but getting all of us together
for this collab was already very
difficult so yeah
yes
thank you thank you thank you everybody
for participating
[Music]
thank you for invite me
my lottery number one yeah
captain
thank you
Hoshi
[Music]
story
that's simple enough I think we can
remember that our ending greeting will
be
okay okay okay
everybody thank you for watching today
and in holotori we say
three two one
bye
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign