uh-huh
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
sir make sure
is
[Music]
do me a favor
human nature
[Music]
is
human nature
[Music]
is
nature
[Music]
is
all right
[Music]
foreign
kiara's here too hello everyone
you're gonna go to my room say hello
me yes volume test
hello good morning
[Music]
you're the perfect rooster so thank you
very much i appreciate it drinking
wine right in the morning oh i'm not
it's just it's from last night i forgot
to put it away
okay okay i need to go i need to go wash
it afterwards
okay okay
that the ping-pong just came and i just
i just got breakfast so i'm i'm in
i'm in a good mood now dead beats kfp
crew
oh we got a job to do today yes
we are playing a way out again
didn't i always end up being on the
right side of the screen
am i did i miss it i thought you were on
top of the chat because you made some
kind of weird comment like
oh chad do you like me on top of you and
whatever i think you moved to the chat
again for me
back then here let me let me move it
then
i think we are both a little bit tired
just a little bit here come here because
don't get too close
i'm out coming i'm coming yay
okay here you are you just give the chat
back to me give it back to me i want to
check back
no you only you have to you have an
important choice to make
well actually you know what you can have
the chat forget it
i don't want him i don't want him i mean
i do want
i want you chat but just not in that way
oh my gosh what is that strange white
block doing
here let me uh move it away it makes me
feel uncomfortable
oh it's part of the chats you know i
need that i need the block too here we
go
interesting uh composition you have
going on there
what me yeah with chad i mean
yeah chad just gets to be a little bit
you know
just a little chat you can see that you
can see the basics you can see the
basics
you can see what you need to see okay
chess general reaction
your chat is the game modes are so cute
i just got new ones i just got new ones
they're very cool
did you make them no no no no i
commissioned a very cool artist
um
um i need to put the link to them um i
think
i'm not sure if they posted on twitter
yet their link is in my members only
i'll do it after the stream but uh check
the link in this in the description of
this video uh after the stream is over
so that you can go check out their stuff
um and you're actually gonna remember
that i will i always do
i always do listen
all right so let's see i think the the
volume should not have changed
we may need to adjust it though because
i feel like it's low in my ears
um so let's go ahead and get started
you're ready i'm ready
very much ready but i don't know how
good my reaction time is gonna be today
that's okay um i'm pretty sure i forget
how to play the game
um but hey finally i have my i have two
monitors
up until now i never had two monitors
with a way out
oh my gosh you only had one monitor yeah
for
like forever what i was streaming with
one monitor forever it was such a pain
sometimes because i had too many windows
if especially when i
when i was streaming i just had way too
many windows
oh my gosh that sounds like here we are
again in the car
wait why can't it's like why is the
audio not playing
it's picking up discord but it's not
picking up the game oh
that's weird hold on i'll figure it out
okay okay
i can voice act to though that's great i
appreciate that okay good we have uh we
have a decision though
um oh do we have to make it now
is it gonna make it for us hold on let's
just show you here
she's very strange i don't know what's
going on
it's only picking up your discord audio
well let me see if i can go ahead and
add
another audio source i know you can do
it cali i know
you're you're better uh at this kind of
stuff than me
oh i appreciate that oh okay it's
picking it up now
i had my i had my other desktop audio
disabled so
should be fine okay now let's see
vincent takes the gun
leo keeps the gun um
how confident are you in your shooting
kiara
uh um
i i think i might be better than you
but we're both bad we're both bad that's
true
i did get a little help from amelia but
you know what i think you should keep
the gun
kusatori i think you're the you're my
action man i think it was about them
having different theories about how to
go about this but i'm not
i don't i don't remem remember it was
too quick and the stream literally just
started so i didn't listen much
so yeah let's just i'm gonna keep i
guess i'm gonna i'm gonna
uh wait how do we how does it work oh
there you go there we go
okay we use the was it was okay
there we go to make sure nobody gets
hurt oh he put his hand on his shoulder
they're friends that's awesome i'm gonna
make sure
no one's gonna get hurt sure sure sure
and i'm the driver as always and i got
my action man
how does this game work again every time
every time
start robbery okay start robber
control uh shift shift
shift gotcha this is also something we
have to figure out every time every time
every time it's always how do you run
how do you oh hang on wait
leo hold on a minute leo it needs to
chill
don't hurt this person
do something to you wasting your time
one more word
yeah i i got him i'm your i'm your
i'm your your not your action man i'm
your guy that does other things
yeah she gave him like free coins and
that's it we gotta find more money
all right sounds good let me in here
other f words
i'm a master at finding cash oh no
[Music]
man oh no what about the other lady
leave it to me we need the combination i
don't have it
liar you seem smart i don't want to hurt
you
um let's see is it two five zero you
seem smart
ma'am you seem like a smart lady
is it daddy yeah i just got it
everything
yeah i told her that i thought she was a
smart lady i just gave her a compliment
it didn't open
uh oh pop over here okay satsu mr
omawari sans here get
time for uh chase party time okay
step on it
how do we drive again
we just pushed the speed paddle he he
has this wasn't
what an idiot yeah that was not very
smart on you
not very smart on his part can't drive
either
the eurobeat remix was very fitting i
thought yeah i got some shoes
you should play that during the next car
chase
got it all right
so we got away so easily what the hell
nice it's because we're a good team i do
yeah
that's not good you could really pull
off a robbery oh this is just fine
game audio low they saying really relax
mr perry
i trust her okay besides she owes me one
now let's go get those guns all right um
i'm gonna add a filter
filter add a gain filter
now if this hurts your ears deadbeats
big apologies but i want you to
oh it's a desert
whoa pretty we're gonna get some more
guns i think
if i understood correctly yeah party
time that's a nice place to live is this
are we still in texas i'm not sure i
think
we're in green all right
partner hello
you look like a smart lady jasmine
i like your high-waisted pants who's
this guy
the t-shirt is funky too oh he's with
you
here i'm gonna turn it up a little bit
more just the inc when you see bit
how nice to meet you oh she doesn't seem
like she likes you
[\h__\h] oh what
why don't you bring your whole family
next time i'm out
hey wait a minute madam you seem like a
smart lady what's wrong with me
what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you you
think i'm vending ice cream here
listen i told you i don't do
business with strangers and this guy he
looks like a stranger to me
yeah but i'm not your stranger
yeah i got a problem with you
oh [\h__\h] um handle it vincent's way or
intervene leo
i trust you okay you seem like a smart
lady
just tell her she seems like a smart
we're no strangers to love you know the
rules
and so do i yep you can have it back
we're cool we're cool it's fine does the
gun not work when it when the
when you take that off let's just get
this sure i don't really know anything
about
uh firearms okay that's not my preferred
uh weapon of choice
gotta you gotta ask comment about it
money money money
in the end it's all about money true
facts
we could actually pull off a robbery not
saying that we should or anything
just i'm just thinking you know thinking
out loud let's see
oh shoes and try weapons okay
you kind of got in my way there sir i
was kind of i was right in front of you
and then you pushed your way in front of
me
okay the one that goes really fast it
goes like
i think oh we can test it out right my
turn
let's see what do i want what do we got
here
i like this one this one looks fun m14
punch from
you really gotta shoot me down like that
all right
i'm just trying to have some fun game
what if i
throw a bottle for you try to shoot this
ball okay try
yourself let me reload let me reload you
gotta be related
oh okay gotcha three two
one what you're aiming at the rocks oh
my god okay hold on
try again try it again
it just oh okay all right i got it try
to try it
[Applause]
that was very forgiving though yeah it
was a little forgiving huh
listen i just want to feel proud of
myself i just want to feel a little
proud of myself
let me try a different one oh let's see
this bad boy looks super fun hold that i
mean that that one looks fun too oh it's
fun let's try that one the poison
is that one of the slow ones or does
this go like
let's find out would you like me to
throw a bottle for you kiara
oh no no no i'm fine for me okay
all right throwing free wait hang on how
do i aim
i was ready for that yeah
i'm too excited my limbs are shaking i
can't i can't shoot the bottle my limbs
are shaking i'm so excited
[Music]
this is fun it is fun let me get it
can i how do i do it
let's see give me this pump action yeah
is anyone from coming at you
yeah you just blow them into four pieces
nothing i tried i tried
i tried yeah i'm fortunate i know i mean
she seems like a smart lady
i just i should say okay i should stop
that only
all right hold on let me oh
that's a strong boy i like the stronger
you like that one more myself i feel
more like getting uh though those the
fast ones it goes
okay well then we have some balance that
makes
all right let's get out of here can we
just take all of them ready
you want to drive please yes it's also
go
as per the usual
oh my my my my tiredness has
left me now yes i slept four hours but i
feel fine
right now it's not good yes excellent
hmm can you believe that today is the
31st
and 2020 is ending i was thinking about
that
oh insane and we're still so busy
yeah we're doing so much stuff what the
heck um
but yeah it's crazy it does feel like
the the year kind of flew by
yeah for the people who don't know we're
on the hololive official channel tonight
uh in a few hours from now uh actually
uh eight and a half eight and a half
hours from now both of us are on the
official whole
life channel so check us out yeah we're
gonna be
looking at things you'll see you'll see
oh oh
wait a minute is something fishy going
on oh
[\h__\h] are you a b-word no
it's me i got some information about leo
[Applause]
she's a b-word give me his location
don't worry about that is the b word
does it mean betrayer
yeah that's mm-hmm good job yeah sure
let's go with that
what a shame i like how you censor it
even though i said the word two seconds
it's just it's just my personal code of
ethics you know all right
gotta follow my personal code i found
him good
make sure we put our best guy on this i
want him dead
you got it you guys suck well at least
she gave us guns
this wannabe mob boss ass looking piece
of human garbage
um i don't like him i hope his death is
most painful we're gonna have fun
killing this guy
nice is that my wife oh that's your wife
yeah
hello wife oh
now what does she think about you
escaping
oh no the baby it's baby time
[Music]
god we baby someone to bring her to the
hospital oh no oh gosh it's definitely
baby time
it should have been me i should have
been there me calliope morty should have
been there
oh and i think i'm going into labor
and i'm all alone
i should have at least had an ambulance
i should have been there
oh no i would do it still be fine she'll
be fine
i hope ah chat's right i am a dad
oh god ah damn it
daddy
maybe colliding where he shouldn't be
there with her at this
are you sure you can get us point plane
maybe it should be venison i sure hope
so
why i'm driving i wanted you to drive
with me yeah i'm thinking the same thing
too what the heck
game the game makes me drive the calm
before the storm
oh ironic
oh are you gonna try to call your wife
but she's like not picking up them
did i just see a car a mouse i saw a
casper yeah
dude a little casper scampering you got
any money leo
i saw you stand on the other side of the
square maybe i could get some
change there i want to let my kfb
friends know by the way because i got
them really worried last night in my
stream by telling them that i haven't
heard casper for 48 hours
i want to let them know though casper
casper and i did hear him in the night i
did hear him so he's still
feeling but i don't know why he's so
quiet recently sorry
he's not dead yet not yet
all right what do you recommend he's
alive
well hello there i have some top-notch
girly magazines
no i don't want those i don't want those
hmm
give me some swords filtered do i really
look like
sure i'm fine why would you say that
that's just an awkward thing to say
you're welcome
thanks okay all right all right that's
just gonna be helpful
good luck he's trying to be helpful of
course yeah no no problem look good
looking out man good looking out
all people are happy that casper is
alive i said casper just yet i told
everyone i don't handle animals
that's not my idea
okay
leo's kind of my dude to be honest
[Music]
speaking of ring is your wife not
checking yeah i'm fine
thanks is that you what i need to fly
somewhere
wow of course he doesn't call his wife
what can you make that work
if innocence okay great
you gotta call to check up on your lady
yeah
what what oh he just found out he's dead
when
what oh now he's real interested
oh no he found out that your wife is in
labor okay okay thanks
oh are we gonna check out her first
because
you obviously have to see your newborn
child i know that's what i'm thinking
too you gotta explain
yeah yeah i did but i need to go
oh good dad what are you talking about
are you okay
i need to be somewhere else right now oh
um hey you can't just walk away
i'm not walking away but something
happened and i need to be there just
tell him you're
dead let go of your pride my dude
he's your homeboy i'll be honest
you need to talk to me yeah yeah yeah
yeah come on man
homie's a dad he gets it
tell me tell me
maybe it's maybe it's hard for him to
talk about the fact that he has a son
because if someone hears he has a son
they can use the the child not not a son
the child as leverage right he's just
trying to be smart about it
cal i this dude wants to kill us it's
fine we'll just kill him first
no problem i'm not worried okay okay
i have a baby he's my wife
she's oh [\h__\h]
he's here party time oh no
all right let's run ah
[\h__\h] the guns are in the car there's no
time for that
we have to go come on wait didn't we did
we not bring our firearms goddammit oh
no i guess not huh
let's go okay
where are we going here this way hold me
okay hold on i'll help you barricade the
door
okay oh push push this
it is
nice yeah
all right here all right you got to
climb up
uh the stairs oh there should be some
stairs oh
oh my god oh god can you see where the
stairs are okay
oh dear oh dear all right you got this
all right get on the boat my boy
okay i'm on there man's gonna take you
oh my gosh this man is this man is
almost i think he's figuring it out oh
no
very loot oh yeah i don't want to see
that right now
what we're trying to say
very good is safe
you know what does this do we need to
move it
all right we'll move it with us oh oh
hell
with me my man work with me
we got this this guy's so lame what an
idiot yeah what a dummy ha ha
ha easy you loser oh next one from here
come behind me all right next one
oh nice oh it has to be only one okay
okay i got you man
all right here we go oh my god what is
that red light what the hell i'm good
you're good
you're good my man just keep moving
keep moving my man
as long as you stay behind my as long as
you stay behind my wall
he's insane
that guy sucks all right ambush
it's fine you got this it's up to you my
action man
you dummy let's kill him now let's beat
him up oh double team
there are two of us in one of him
action man
yeah yes again let's strangle him
together oh this is so clutchy
not often we get to kill someone
together kiara yay
high five
that was cool i feel content yeah
we're doing a good job done i sit my
latte after a crisp murder
i don't know what's going on with you
but we need to finish what we started
harvey's gonna keep sending guys like
this um yeah
i know do you i have
then why the hell did you want to leave
all of us tell him my name is my wife
she's in the hospital what's the problem
what do you think
baby that's great news congrats man
oh friend sure it's it's great
thanks you don't seem too happy about it
he's not hit trust me
i'm happy i think he's just worried
about the fact that um
it's really cool he's he lives this
crazy nutso life and now he has a baby
child look after
you gotta go see a kid oh whatever is
going on between you two
it's still your kid i know oh you know
is the real guy go there
it's interesting because i wouldn't take
leo for like the real dead
you know yeah but family is important to
you
when you go to the hospital you're going
to see your kid and then we go get them
oh that's so sweet
you're with me yeah
my boy priorities you knew look at my
boys
i need to trust you on this one you can
trust me the future people are going to
be a bit shocked when they come in
and see this mess yeah maybe a little
bit
oh well that's uh not our problem i
wonder if they have safety
safety cameras though security cameras
uh potentially
in that case we're kind of boned well i
mean everyone's chasing us already so it
is what it is
that's good you could yeah
back at the hospital the way you were
holding your baby and [\h__\h]
you're resolving his dad's skills i i
didn't
mean it in a bad way you know but yeah
anyway it's a great thing watching your
kid grow up
yeah i can imagine it is
what's wrong man what's the problem with
you and your wife
look
carol is the love of my life you've
always wanted to have a child
oh he tried for years
every time we failed it was like a
part of us died
[Music]
and when it finally happened a day
when we found out
we've never been so happy
then everything went to hell
and i ended up in prison
how what's what happened in between i
don't know i guess we'll have to find
out
something bad didn't you get like framed
or something like that
oh yeah right i guess um that's it
wasn't really
clear about exactly how or why he went
to prison
oh man they finally like get to a point
where they're
happy in their relationship and then
he just has to go and it's not even his
fault that's really sad
ah fine carol let's find carol
let's go see my baby cause i'm real sad
hello where's carol do you know carol oh
ma'am good evening sir
how can i help the maternity ward my
wife just had a baby
here to see my wife i need to see my
wife please
okay do you know which ward she's in my
problem
she has a newspaper with our faces just
i threw it away
oh my god leo good eyes
they say birds do have good eyes you
wanna play board game hey look connect
four want to play
yes oh yes all right let's do it
i play boy game here i'm just trying to
sit
all right here we go
this is this is where it is uh this is
where the real
this is the real challenge of the game
yes right here that's good
tell me what you would what you can do
i'm red my favorite color
hmm
doing a big funk
i don't mind if i do
don't mind if i do
don't mind if i do i think i think i'm
gonna win this one
nope oh pretty sure
nope don't mind if i do
callie you're sometimes i'm suck
you were helping me build that what if i
was i was doing it on purpose because i
felt bad for you
i wanted you to win so far
oh it's so easy no
thanks for helping me with that i really
appreciate it no
it's very sweet of you no
i'm the winner winner chicken dinner
you won't win so easily kusatori i know
you think you will oh
[\h__\h] you're not gonna
play that same trick on me maybe i will
no you won't
no you will not you will play that same
dirty trick
maybe i will maybe oh
no you won't
you will not uh-huh interesting
interesting you will not i will let you
oh okay still good still good nope
i see a csc no no no not happening
not happening that's not today
[Applause]
maximum concentration here
that's right
i will stop you at every point kusatori
we'll see about
[Music]
ah
not this time not this time
[Music]
oh no oh no no no no no no no no no oh
yes yes yes yes
yes yes oh yes yes yes yes yes
you didn't see me what you were about to
win
oh no i mean like i mean maybe
i know this game's hard you had two
opportunities i blocked one but i didn't
block the other because i couldn't but
there you go
and now it's all all good still all good
just make your move einstein
my man venison for real
let you win again no no you can't do
anything about it
it's going to happen it's inevitable
no no it's not yes
god damn it are we playing tetris and
trying to fill up the
the left row to make combos coca-cola
combo
that's why we keep do i hate police
einstein just make your move einstein
just make your move
make your move make your move
ah
just make your move no
there we go
i
no we have to go back i'm gonna be in a
bad mood for the rest of the gameplay
oh my god wait hold on hold on time to
get serious
yes hang on that man totally recognized
us
[Music]
you guys seemed familiar have i seen you
before
i don't think so okay
whatever i mean even if you have seen us
before maybe it's in a positive way
a lot he looks so
so familiar i'm sure i've seen you
somewhere
i think talk her way out knock him out
yep yeah that's the easiest way
he's getting real shady that we agree
there we go
now what do we do with the body though
well he's just uh having a little nap
yeah he's taking it
tonight his hospital is like
like not busy at all like taking risks
no people here is this
is oh no you excited to see your baby
i'm more nervous how hospitals is
balance balance what does that mean how
hard can this be
sorry but you don't look too good you
okay well aren't you prince charming
yeah that's kind of rude leo i'm done
wait hold on wait stop
what oh it's a game we can play this
game
lung cancer too much smoking
and you continue smoking very smart
they say a lot of things this time all
right
all right so share realizes you're right
everyone stop smoking
it's not not good for you should i die
you want to do this huh you want to do
this
and i will win at this this is what well
i came
later yeah i'm really good at it ah
wait wait okay it's just how many
seconds
i will win at this
ah you shouldn't i i thought i had to
tap it oh my god this is difficult
i'll fight you till the end of time
kiara
that's our that's our thing i'm timeless
and you are eternal yep i will sit here
together balancing in a wheelchair
against you until the end of all days
literally into eternity thinking you can
do better
right wow i think you can do better i
can't i can't sure
you really think you can do better you
really think so tell me
the only thing the only way you can get
me down from this chair is by seducing
me
hey kiara unzip your pants oh my god
no no no no no no
uh uh nope nope my throne my throne
again no we can do this until the end of
days
oh my god my heart is going doki doki
doki doki
it was it was more to leo than to you i
don't think you have a zipper on your
pants kiara
i can't oh cause i i actually really do
don't
but yeah oh my my head my head is
pounding
this is difficult it's not even it's not
even that easy oh my gosh oh no oh no
bye bye [\h__\h] on peace
[Music]
can you play with me meanwhile i can
all right well you know what i'm content
with this so we can move right along
i know exactly that uh this is gonna be
drawn into a fan art this scene
fan arts tomorrow gonna be up right away
us balancing in wheelchairs until the
end of days
probably yes hello so
what's happening here uh the bulb's
blown out
is that you're watching this week um no
she is still pregnant no no the wire is
fine
my child has been born i think it's a
ghost what
it's a girl ah don't listen whatever
shut up
it's not a ghost are you serious are you
serious
i really think it's a ghost well no i'm
not
think about it people die down here
every single day
there has to be at least one ghost
floating around in here i guess
oh yeah so why is this ghost breaking
bulbs
because he's trying to tell us something
hey give us a second i'm serious
maybe it's just like there are two
murderers here
you need help maybe
it means you drink a lot of alcohol you
get super drunk
i thought it just literally means like
putting your face into [\h__\h] i know
yeah yeah i mean well you might you
might as well when you get drunk can you
trip and you fall your face will
probably fall into something at some
point
it's like that no no no no no no just
follow me sir where's my wife thank you
please show me where my wife is
she looks sexy huh i mean
yes priorities
i like the nurse outfit okay
it does look nice on her thanks and your
i like her hairstyle
pretty cute yeah i would say so wife
i apologize baby
you okay it's my baby i'm fine
oh she's not happy vincent what are you
doing here
seeing my child i'm dead
[Music]
she's my daughter too oh daughter so not
son
no
this is uh leo he's my homie he helps me
kill peace nice to meet you ma'am
yeah uh baby girl huh
um i'll leave you guys alone oh come on
supreme dad help me wait outside
help me yeah no you gotta do this
and on your own dad extraordinary don't
drop the
baby don't drop the baby okay
i'm nervous we already saw into the
future apparently he doesn't hold the
baby very well
wait but leo you didn't see me hold the
baby how would you know
i can imagine
[Music]
can i get a doctor pepsi come on dr
oopsie
get me dummy hello baby aggression i'm
your father
oh she's so beautiful
she is
[Music]
you know it's because the mom is so
pretty
i was gonna say i'm so beautiful just
like you vincent
please i love you
so much i just have to finish this
you have to trust me
carol just a couple more murders please
just a couple more grand theft autos i
probably wouldn't really support that
quest even
yeah i mean things will be different
you keep saying that but you're gonna
get yourself killed
i can't live with that i'm not gonna let
that happen
i promise you have to trust me carol
oh carol please
uh so am i getting my doctor oopsie or
not
thirsty boy uh oh oh [\h__\h] oh
sorry baby gotta go daddy's gotta go
commit a couple more murders
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] but you're
probably going to go outside
out the window this is so sad bye bye
baby off to go commit some more crimes
that's so traumatic too yeah
oh baby's gonna forget it hopefully go
eat the baby why it was just born
that's my child i'm a dead all right
time to go
oh [\h__\h]
oh you're not under arrest
kill him i mean uh knock him out
die whoa
got some reaper instincts coming up
the stairs
bye-bye no freezing no freezing nope
i don't feel like giving up run run you
guys don't want to get hurt right oh
okay that was kind of chill
go leo go and i'm good at running
because i was supposed to be the olympic
torch for the olympic games this year
this year this is why i came to the time
to become the olympics the olympic
george
canceled and my pizza is running out so
i can't beat uh the torch this time
i'm kind of frustrated about that that
is a shame
i gotta say that is a shame first of me
hearing about that
yeah this is why i came with my running
shoes you know
i'm wearing my running shoes the whole
time sorry i'm eating a donut right now
in honor of the
police amore son
will i ever be able to become the
olympic torch will my dream ever come
true
see this and more in 2021
yeah good luck with that
don't know how smart
donut parties he's some kind of magician
oh my god not a very smart guy
i'm a very smart guy just because you
tell me to freeze doesn't mean i will
nice box yeah this is what uh chat
wanted to see
next up back to my action man we're
really
getting good with those vents maybe we
should play a manga we should give it
another try except
i'm terrible with that game what am i
doing
olympic points now you're shooting me
oh let's go i messed up the first one
you got this you got this
this is like a like a fighting game now
mm-hmm what the heck what the hell
what's that boy oh that man flew in
there
gotta ask him how he did yeah he's got
some mad skills there
that's the move over there oh oh oh
oh oh
nice improvised the donut that weaponry
eating right now couldn't you kind of
like seduce lure them into
your like you would think so you would
think so
except this is a video they like donuts
that's what i heard in on many tv series
it's true that's why i'm eating the
donut in their honor
i can't give it to them though because
um they're fictional and i am not
[Music]
there you go that's what you get for
that how does that feel huh
feels great now it's my turn
back in the saddle
damn we don't talk about the fight club
first room i never saw that movie by the
way never started really
great you should watch my watch along
check the window
i'd rather just watch it review like
yeah
i watched it too recently though i don't
want to watch it again
it's okay i don't want to watch it
either hey wait a minute it's a good
movie
i don't know if it's a chiata movie but
so where'd he go
all right i guess he jumped down and ran
out yeah that's right that's exactly
what i did
i do want the experience of watching
someone some
something on your huge tv screen oh yeah
yeah definitely we'll come over sometime
yeah
what should we watch what should we
watch uh
shrek yes
yeah definitely we wanted to do that
anyway but can we do the watch along
while watching it on your huge tv is
that even if we time it correctly maybe
we can figure out a way to do it
um it's possible it might be difficult
but we can figure it out
track you're coming with me freeze in
the name of the law
oh oh oh you got to do it my action man
you gotta
now if you want to be nice you can get
them in the legs or in like i don't know
the message
am i actually supposed to shoot them i
don't want to shoot them we're in a
hospital
that's all i know this is the only words
[Music]
someone will know someone in the chat
open someone in chat knows
every time someone is dropped out
collected
hi it's dance and queen what no way
incorrect that's a meme that can't be
right
anyway i'm just gonna casually walk out
of here
and he's dancing like he's never done
before
i'm just a guy good evening officer i
mean i wouldn't think that you would
just be sitting there
randomly and chilling i wouldn't think
someone called me these two guys in the
paper
yes you seen them at all no no i'm just
a guy you see them you make sure
let me know if there's anything else i
can do to help sure
we'll be patrolling this wing for now so
we'll be close by if you see or hear
anything and we will be long gone okay
okay
situation
what are you gonna do what are you gonna
do should i leave what you're gonna do
when they come for you
bad boy bad boy what you gonna do
what you gonna do when they come for you
stop running just walk be normal yeah
oh there's someone crying what a shame
it's probably something really sad that
just happened we are in a hospital right
about here
this place feels familiar
yes there is right over here
yeah my man oh didn't expect that oh
that he definitely broke
some something he broke something is
your back there's my action man
oh god are you [\h__\h] me come on
oh no you can do it [\h__\h] surrender
sir yeah
why don't you just scoot me dude she
could have just shot me
it's true he really could have but i
think you didn't kill anyone yet so it's
like they're like
we should take them in i'm
i i wonder if that's really how they how
they operate i also want to see what you
know oh
i got your back don't worry
[Applause]
wait hold on hold on hold on hold on
hold on i'm just practicing
[Applause]
yeah you jerks give me my friend matrix
oh my god
show me those moves yeah what's going on
where am i
i'm gonna ah this is the time this is
the time
this is the time i gotta do some matrix
one shot one opportunity seize
everything you ever wanted in one moment
did you capture it
his palms are sweaty
we can't continue we can't continue
because i'll get the mca string
oh no what oh my god you have such great
ideas as well
i know it's i'm not even playing the
game it's the only time that i can drive
well
it's not me controlling the game
eurobeat intensifies
come on man you know what i'm about fan
of heights don't worry
emily's a great pilot she was
practically born on the plane
oh we reached the plane oh wait what oh
my god we didn't
all this time we made it huh
[Music]
long time no see vincent how you doing
good
hey leo nice to meet you you too
oh she's nice nicer than the other
woman's friend right
yeah i hear you're a good pilot
well i don't watch that no more donuts
thanks okay
emily does this thing fly what does it
look like a [\h__\h] bike
i like your style mexico yep mexico
you've got to be kidding me that's way
too far i'm not flying to mexico
emily pretty much i always pay you good
if you want to you can have like a
vacation
in mexico just take us there
double huh how about triple
good for that vince yeah yeah hmm
where are you going what do you think
mexico
let's go all right now we're talking
now we're talking holiday vacation
yeah it's doing me moon here we go i can
use the vacation
i'm telling you the truth i would never
say anything i i would never do that you
know oh he's super dying
they tried he said though he had some
children so that's the [\h__\h]
you know that you know you've got to
trust me harvey i promise
he doesn't have to do that in fact
wait is he actually letting him go nice
of him
that's uh we need more men he's coming
got it wait really oh what surprises me
he's recruiting i guess so
are you sure
see i knew i knew that that's what they
meant by let him go let him go to to be
with me
what the [\h__\h] yeah let him go to come be
that's what they meant hey here you go
let him meet callie i'll take care of
him he had some children
i'll be nice to him
you ready yeah i just need to fill her
up
help me out sure the gas tank's right
over there
um what is it what do you think
is this a good landing spot let me see
wow dad
with you pointing the signature i
totally know what you mean
that's fine you could also remember
very informative closer very detailed
no thanks i'm not good with heights oh
leo
wait emily do you have parachutes here
ah are we gonna skydive hello vincent
are you crazy oh come on leo i'm fine
that would save us
i don't care i haven't even seen a
parachute before we'll have fun kind of
hard i'll protect your kill accord
right emily well technically you're
right
okay that's easy sounds easy
land the plane i want to do that in is
life one day
right would you would you do that yeah
sure we could probably do it together
that'd be fine let's go
you know you want to parachute with me
i am stupid
i want to do skydiving one day i mean
how hard can it be right you'll figure
it out
yeah you will have to figure it out
because otherwise you'll die
relax leo just has to actually channel
his inner accusatory because you can fly
right are you being cocky now yes
if i unleash my true power and become a
phoenix
in my human form it's a bit difficult oh
maybe yeah maybe a little bit
just needs to channel his inner cusatory
yes
sorry that's just it's it's it's coming
just get it on the plane okay
what is that our weapons or it looks
like a body or something
can you please find one why would we
take a body with us i got it i got it
uh first here it is i'll just give it to
emily
we want to play again look what i found
let's play
let's play he says in such a family
voice
let's play a real men's man move that
game
let's see what you got there's time
plays grenade brothers
we are true gamers what is that i didn't
jump
oh i get it i get it i get it now okay
this is a hard game
that that did seem kind of like be weird
that did not seem like it should have
happened
okay there we go
none of us are good at this game i guess
not huh
oh nice nice size
it's a guaranteed battle cry real your
show hours
yeah really shot hours for real
yay hey look hey hey hey listen you got
connect four okay you got connect four
yes
okay i did indeed oh we can play darts
again
okay okay just game and it's mini games
hey i'll take you out
oh can i can i bench press work out hang
on one second
before i throw some darts i'm just gonna
put it put in some more yeah i'm just
gonna lift a little bit
yeah bullseye
oh
oh it gets harder and harder let's find
the master tapper
i know i'm the best oh i'm really good
at tapping
those uh those coin games at the arcade
and arcades in japan
we have to tap a lot um i'm really good
at those
where are you
what are you staring at that's it that's
it for your boy
i'm done i need to give it a try i'm
gonna throw some darts with my
my newly worked out arms okay these guns
to use
how does this work ah 87 not bad
that angry cursing how many did you do
uh nine uh bullseye bullseye baby
what callie you're good at dart how fast
not that difficult it's only because i
just worked out my guns
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h] let's go
no not fearful open hangar doors
we gotta unplug the fuel line ah and i
gotta give her a logbook
thanks chad i thought that was an okay
around two
it was decent callie got those muscles
only because of those new games i can't
move this please unplug the fuel line
that's i just did that oh you mean from
the plane
gotcha no problem no problem
i got you right now where'd you go
thanks that's open i think and
now we are where we began the story oh
you're in the point okay oh my god this
is this is so we came so far callie i
know we sure did
we did a lot of stuff
i'm ready to go let's go skydiving
together
yeah i guess so huh how are we here we
are
open the hangar doors i guess i didn't i
did goddamn it is that not open
come on
as if that wouldn't fit come on there we
could that was one centimeter
i've been nominated all right let's go
let's go
does the chat now how much longer they
think we need
because uh we we have no idea what do
you guys think
if it's like maybe an hour 30 minutes to
two hours
maybe we can play till the end i'll just
move my asmr stream but if it's more
than that
we'll no probably stop most people say
one and a half or two hours just enough
some even say three hours that's good
that's gary
i think most people say two hours okay
i wonder what we should do
you know i've been thinking about your
situation with you
two hours max i might have a solution
for you
this can't be a stream but cali has an
asmr stream yeah
i can move it a little bit but i wonder
if we should maybe play one hour and
then play the last hour on your channel
look
okay yeah but i see a similar situation
with linda
so i decided to write her a letter and
it worked
i laid it all out and she gave me a
second chance
you know i'm just saying that writing a
letter really helped
leo's such a good guy of course yeah
it's up to you
i mean i'm just saying that worked for
me but it doesn't have to
you know anyways look i'm just saying it
was a good thing
that's all you feeling me
yeah well i'm not really the writing
type yeah yeah i mean
it was just an idea it's just anyway
congrats on the baby
i'm really happy for you thank you
[Music]
people say it will ruin the experience
if we stop now because we're so close to
the end
okay well i'll just move the asmr stream
then people will have to understand you
have to understand
you and me can do another collab on your
channel
okay remember spread your arms and legs
all right time to fly
leo channel you're interesting you have
experience with that interesting
yeah i guess so i wonder why he'd have
that i'm gonna regret this
oh god bye-bye here we go
take my hand
come on go dummy bye-bye
thank you see it's fun you're phoenix
your phoenix fly
look this that looks like a nice place
to spend your holidays
yeah okay
all right the ocean looks nice can i
fall into the ocean
yeah that could be kind of fun you'll
definitely die but you know oh hey
hi i mean the water hitting you is
it's going to really slap you you know
not yet no okay oh i pulled it anyway
oh gosh oh my god
oh no leo leo
i got you i got you homie i got you help
him help him
help him
you're not going to die i'm here i'm
here hold on to me
that's adorable that's adorable hey
friend
okay
why not time is perfect i'm your baby
now
callie i'm your baby that's kind of cute
i'll pat leo's back but not yours
did you
doesn't look like you're landing at the
landing spot cali but okay
close enough close enough don't [\h__\h]
drop it
i'm so cute okay just hold on
i see a fan art coming of this scene as
well same
it's gonna happen that was the last time
i listened to your [\h__\h] ideas
it was fun come on i'm live aren't you
yeah i almost died
no you didn't let's get going no i did
and you're back almost died
i had your back oh we're liking them in
the middle of nowhere
what makes you so sure about that i
don't know a gut feeling i guess
and it's not like it's easy to sell
something like the black arlon
i still don't get how the hell you pull
that off well i'm actually good at what
i do
cool looks nice here
it is i like the
the nature that's going on here where
are we very nice
she's in beautiful she said
it's here after all i guess gotta do the
thing with the stepping on shoulders
again
that's fine we're praying at this point
now
step on me kelly
this is just so lewd this game look at
it
oh my god i can't even
can we just like chill at the beach for
a little bit
we have time for playing guides and
playing that
that arcade game and all that just relax
it's relaxed and why don't you have time
for going for a swim
good question i'd like to ask people who
made this game too
okay so we're going to hurt them now
right now
yeah hang on you're going to get really
alarmed well then
we'll see who should we hang out i just
went for it
someone's asking i'm playing vincent and
kiara's leo
yeah i'm playing the bottom
i'm not good at shooting is this i hope
this game is gonna be a little bit
forgiving with that
he literally hit that man so many times
you gotta give him a headshot ah jeez
okay
come back
there we go y'all got nothing on me
i'm going let's go let's go
can i get closer to him i think that'll
be helpful
i am indeed going to kill you
it's a very polite way of letting him
know that you're going to kill him
put your head right here please
not close enough
now now you got it okay now you got it
congratulations oh look at them they're
all super dead
they're really dead amen would be proud
of me
are we going up again since they would
definitely be proud of you
yay let's see
oh
no problem you'll get in my action man i
can't shoot but you can
it's it's probably actually good that we
chose um like you you chose this
truth actually no didn't you did end up
shoot
choosing the the one that goes i did
right
huh it's not it's not the slow one right
the shotgun i swear i chose the shotgun
oh yeah yeah but maybe we should have uh
chose oh god
oh god okay maybe we should have chosen
uh different types like you you do the
slow one i can't even speak anymore
it is a slow one though okay it should
be
okay i don't think i can do that one
jerk kill you oh yeah
okay we're together now oh my gosh
wait
[Applause]
probably should have ran a little
quicker oh god it's fine don't
die on me kelly i won't i won't that was
a fluke i'll die i mean i won't die
again next time excuse me
we just gotta time it really well
because there's no way we're hitting
them from here
you can roll by the way if you press
space yep that's nice i didn't realize
you could do that
[Applause]
roll again roll again okay here we go
that's my dude
[Applause]
yeah now we're chillin
or maybe there's no there was no way to
kill that dude
yeah probably not from here where are we
oh god inside he's still trying to shoot
us even though we're inside
listen get over here i'd like to but
you're uh your buddy's in the way yeah
there we go oh my god
i don't like shooting games but it's
okay
i'm gonna i'm gonna destroy them oh my
gosh i saw that happen
how on earth ah
god damn it leo
oh you opened the door and a bullet flew
right into my face
it's okay it was also my fault oh my god
what that was hilarious
that was loki hilarious oh my god oh my
goodness
they are really good at shooting these
guys wow
okay and okay it's kind of easier to go
over the top
and go for the side i think
hold on hold on hold on don't get shot
again gallie
i won't nice one yeah
okay
it didn't seem like an option yeah
okay i'm going to wait for you
let's not get killed this time
all right action man check him out leo
take out that sniper yeah it's up to you
homie oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] you're missed
counting on you is that a sniper oh my
amber sniper okay i get it he doesn't
know i'm coming
okay let's go
yeah all right i'm coming out
oh it's easy i got a new gun too the
sniper rifle
i'll stay up here and keep you covered
oh my god
all right well i'm doing good shooting i
guess oh my lord
i just want to hit one of you please
yeah that's my action man
there's three more four don't worry i
got you i need you
i got you
you're having way too much fun with this
man oh my gosh
i am having a lot of fun no get off of
there dummy
up close up close and personal that's
the way to do it
are we done there's only one laptop
thing but he's hiding in a spot where i
can't reach him
oh i can't see him
maybe i'll come out if i if i stand up
here maybe there's no one okay
i think that might be all of them yeah i
got him really
yep they're doing four they're all
tested
ah darn it
oh my goodness we are really having fun
there huh
no what you still oh that's another one
okay
[Music]
and you bye bye and you yeah
wow i guess i'll just leave it to you
thank you bye-bye
where's the next one come on come on
give me the next one and
oh you got oh my god don't worry i can
do something
i can kill someone anyone who wants
a little bit of this fun that i have to
offer oh gosh
i don't think they want it per se okay
it's not you can certainly give it to
them anyway
oh no oh no oh no oh no oh no i'm done
for
hang on no get out of there
we're fine don't worry i got you i got
to kill you i'm not gonna let you die
nice not bad not bad thank you
you're welcome that was fun yeah that
was kind of exciting huh maybe i
maybe i like fps games i never really
gave him a chance
yeah maybe you do you make a good sniper
where am i going um i'm not sure
there's so many dead bodies here there
you are where do all these dead bodies
come from
you i get it it's a joke
i gave you a lot of offerings a lot of
sacrifices
for that i eternally appreciate you
all right now where to next oh
going down
i think a cut down bridge is going to
stop us
indeed that's right no one can stop us
you and me
we just go down and we go up again it's
that easy oh
it's not that easy no problem now
what have you huh oh the ocean looks
amazing
wanna go swimming i didn't know me yes
let's go
let's just take a dip i want to
i wish i could the game says no
back flip into the ocean and hit my head
and die
yeah perfect that sounds good to me
nice vacation leo come here i'm in my
room
[Music]
wow we have no problems you gonna go
right i go left or should we go the same
direction
um let's go in different directions okay
this is better
they haven't noticed us yet so just
let's keep it low profile for now
probably take them out
oh my gosh oh
oh wow he's still hitting me huh do you
need some help
maybe a little bit
that's fine it's fine
i need the sniper rifle yeah
it was powerful watch out
oh just kidding that answers that i
probably should get a little bit closer
i'm going to get up on higher ground
dead no not dead
[Music]
just die dude it's not that hard he
doesn't want to die what the hell
rude it's not that bad
oh god idiot
i'm gonna come for you i'm gonna get
closer oh no there's more
watch out okay he's dead
i'm in a bad spot i'm really in the best
part all right i got you
hi you're welcome
i'm gonna get that guy in the house yes
oh someone here
oh
watch out get covered
you gotta kill them quick
no [\h__\h] you know you're not gonna do
that
[Music]
oh not doing so well
don't hurt yourself it's fine i got one
of them
there you go yeah okay nice
okay i can get out of cover now okay
clean your clear okay
seems like it how can we open the skate
i guess we can't we got to take the
stairs
all right fancy
all right party time help me with this
oh what are we gonna do with that
are we opening the
all right that works i guess i guess
always a winner word force it's a good
rule of thumb i gotta say i agree