[Music]
woohoo
oh
[Music]
me
yes meow
what is it what is it what is it um
would you like to say something
[Music]
huh
what is it
my baby that was jonker's
danke what's up junkers
well hello everyone i didn't say it yet
hello i have yet to
uh come back to my old self i am still
this version of myself this
absolutely thick version of myself
i took this streaming time for my
japanese viewers and my
you know s e a viewers
[Music]
[Laughter]
since today is a mario kart stream and
today is at a good time for japanese
bros i'm expecting some
pagoda fans to challenge me once again
the nosagies are
somewhere in there i feel it they're
always there
when it comes to mario kart they're
always there uh
i it's one o'clock here i woke up like
40 minutes ago i was like i want to
sleep more
can i can i move the stream to later
yeah but then i
i woke up anyway
partially because especially because my
cat smoothie she's like
always like oh my god recently
i spilled her too much with with wet
food
so now she thinks she gets it every
morning even though that was not the
intention
and because if i give it to her every
morning you know what happens
i told you guys before but now she won't
let
she want leave me alone
until i give her wet food every [\h__\h]
morning
um
is training you ah don't worry i've
already been trained i do everything
that my cats want anyway
by the way i realized i where's my
steering wheel i forgot my steering
wheel
well the only thing that looks like a
steering wheel that i can come up with
right now
is this
or what i could i could also
stare with a ramen bowl here
should i orange or the ramen
[Laughter]
where is my where did i put my steering
wheel
i had one and now i don't know where it
is
orange is cuter what's your problem with
ramen ramen so yummy
but sure if i if i stare with ramen you
know it will be spilled everywhere
and this makes no sense still for people
who come in later
looks like i'm holding it actually with
my all my fists
oh
[Music]
well i guess i guess you guys like the
the orange so
i guess we'll go with that pizza pizza
would be good too yeah
and you can bite it off while you're
driving mmm pizza while driving don't do
it don't do it guys
i mean i don't know is eating or like
being
fed while driving is okay right
like i've i've seen that before but
feeding yourself maybe not so much
no it is not being fat is not okay
like someone you know pushing the pizza
in your mouth
yes but actually no okay then i've seen
a lot of
lot of people go against but you know
might be different in other countries i
don't know who knows
well well well well wow
mama anything that distracts the driver
isn't great uh yeah makes sense you see
i actually
to contrary believe because obviously
everyone thinks like watching my mario
kart
races up until now i think it has been
very obvious that
um or or everyone would think that
i am a very good driver i must have been
a race car driver in my previous life
i know you can get that kind of idea i i
understand it
like i can relate that you would get
that idea by watching my streams
um obviously you also probably feel
very much challenged and endangered when
you see me
drive because i'm just so good but i
have to be honest actually i don't have
a driver's license
and actually i have not really ever
driven a car on my own
yeah oh my god is not unbelievable oh
what
well today we will play we'll play
and don't play this game again
i don't know which which one to use
sometimes we use speed sometimes we will
use
kusutori and this one is from lamy
senpai from her stream
which one should we use which one did we
use last time i think we used
kuso
[Music]
what's that what difference was there
between those two i used both right
i think i one bug so i switched to the
other or something like that
well uh by the way this oh here you here
we go oh [\h__\h] i should write down the
code though
uh okay someone did someone write it
down
it's currently closed wait when it's
currently closed
then i can take my time to write it down
right and uh
i can take my time to write it oops wait
to write it down right before p
people cannot join until i open it right
okay one second
[Music]
uh
mario so i'm a bit slow right now
because i just woke up
okay four zero
six zero hopefully when i join this will
not be full
um
[Music]
okay when you guys try to enter now does
it say it's closed
why should i put that wait a second
i think i'll probably take a nap after
this because i got i got
i got a whole talk today like for some
people it's tomorrow for some people
i mean it's kind of tomorrow for me as
well it's after midnight
i'll probably take a nap or so and
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait can
we do uh can we do um
can we do our outline
[Music]
oh my god i'm so slow i can't think i
can't think that fast right now okay
there we go here orange outline easier
to see
and now let's put that here
okay now everyone wait let me add that
actually join
only once
okay let's let's have fun let's let
everyone get in
we'll probably play for like an hour
[Music]
huh oh
oh there we go and then please
leave again uh i still don't know about
these cards
ah whatever
if you played with me once they never
played with me ever again just kidding
uh
that sounds a bit wrong and if you
if you wear in in all of the other
tournaments up until now you might want
to be nice to not be in this one
but it's okay like at least for this
stream only once
does that make sense welcome everyone
the person on the bottom right who is
that supposed to be looks really weird
oh my god i i i need to warm up
which one which one do we warm up with
which one is the best warm up bush ah
i knew that was a japanese bird i always
have weird
as always with the weird faces
ah what no i didn't i didn't mean to
have to say they got weird faces in
these what do you call those mess
oh god hello speed
okay [\h__\h]
well i did not get that okay that's fine
do i have the thing on right now i
wonder
[\h__\h] i didn't get an item but i gotta
climb
do i have to think on where
where it doesn't push you off the edge
or do i have the edge thing on
i don't quite remember you give me items
yeah
i do how do you know
okay this is just warm up this is just
warm up but i think i'm doing okay for
my warm-up
no banana no banana
oh there's two people who started and
one almost ran into me thank you liam
for it
hopefully on purpose uh
being careful and not running into me
guess you're doing good oh well thank
you you guys are being too nice again
you guys just don't want to get fired
[Music]
okay
isn't that the sound of the sound effect
of something
what is that sound event are you
i'm sure you guys know you're trying
cara that's all that matters
yep i'm always trying my best
now don't leave mario kart
[Music]
looks like i wrapped just in time yeah
welcome
[Music]
hey
is that the australian map uh uh the
fake australian
flag yo
fake australian friend
[Music]
you like my new look should i keep this
on forever and never
and ever and never or never no i would
not be
wearing it for a whole taco
[Music]
wow well that was just me warming up
obviously next time
i'll be doing much much better
i forgot what kiara looks like now oh my
god me too
bye bye thank you everyone thank you
arena
i saw the masa well
i feel like i was so far in the back i i
didn't really have
any fun with the people in the front it
doesn't even feel like we played
together
oh what do we got now i don't know which
one i like i don't quite remember
anything at all let's do donkey kong
jungle that one's fun i think
my my brain and my
arms i see no saggy
oh i looked at the key
that that must be no saggy they got that
they got the
the light blue twin tail so that one
will be strong
they're they are trained in uh
[Music]
they are trained in destroying bakura's
senpai so they're really good oh hey
everyone likes donkey kong
uh road everyone likes it
which one will it be which one will it
be yeah
i don't know if i'm happy about that but
i don't know whatever
blue crowl okay it doesn't really say
anything about no no
sagging
maybe it isn't monkey map return
reject race car driver return to monkey
oh [\h__\h]
guys be a bit kind on me please beat me
oh
no already 12 oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
we're off to a rough start but this is
just you know this is the technique
that's out this is the technique that
i was told taught by aqua senpai
be the last and then be the first
that's that's that technique yeah that's
how you do it
wow
oh my gosh
two eight oh we got a good one okay
whoever is
at the very front
it's not a good day for you girl
[Music]
wait he's still so far away from
everyone else did it hit him yet
[Music]
i think it just hit him because he
stopped nope that was maybe just a lag
hey why is he so far in the front number
one even though he got hit by my blue
shell
what the hell 50 dots oh maybe he dodged
it oh oh my god
oh wait he's so far away is he a
professional
oh my god
wait a minute what's going on what's
going on
number three okay where's number two
then
i'm there skype is go away reach the air
be considerate you don't know how to do
that
[Music]
why do you have to do this to me
oh my god did you wait for me
why didn't you get a boost from it and i
didn't huh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
of course that was a japanese viewer
what is it what in real life though
in real life i feel like
australians are pretty good at race car
driving we have a lot of famous people
for race car driving don't we but who's
like the who are like the good countries
when it comes to race car driving
i don't think he was i've never heard of
japan being so good with race car
driving
who's like the typical country who wins
uh
yeah i would say australian australia
germany finland europe italy
japan is great at drifting
well it's in lee italy america
it must be the americans who are saying
america
cause i don't think so
[Music]
americans when asked which country is
the best at
anything ever it must be the americans
sorry sorry
that was sick burn
okay let's see let's see which one do we
get
[Music]
yeah australians because we got like you
know the famous people
which are race car drivers
in there if it's the real one i don't
know
let's go let's go total
obviously will know that he has to let
me win
i'm not the one
and it's over it's over it's over
the happiness is already over
oh is this a good place to throw those
shelves maybe
[Music]
that's that was quick you started
absolutely absolutely useless they give
them to you
if you're one of the one of the last
ones
and they think they're helping but
they're not helping at all
[Music]
oh i need to drift more i need to drift
off i used to drink the log now what
happened to that
maybe maybe it's because i'm using an
orange as a steering wheel
[Music]
yes
it's unfair
[Music]
i will sue you come on come on come on
come on come on everyone's pretty close
here go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go go go
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
[Music]
okay everyone please leave have you
played in the race thank you
see you next time
sally wow i think that was the best
total was number one
wow i think that was the best straight
the best
the best game i've ever had thank you oh
everyone's leaving you guys got manners
nice
did i ever reach number three ever
before
in a fair game where i was not forcing
everyone to stay behind
what is that face behind me i want to
take weight i want to take a screenshot
how to take a screenshot again
oh [\h__\h] now how do you take a screenshot
again
i want to take a screenshot of the crown
okay did you guys take a screenshot
[Music]
oh wait i always have the crown when
everyone leaves oh
hey i just thought i
didn't think right now
for a moment i was like i got the crown
because i was number one
no i wasn't i always get the crown when
everyone
leaves hello everyone
i see some familiar names welcome
welcome welcome
someone from sweden as well sweden
hmm
hello let's go the
the square button which square button
what the hell is that donkey like why
was he so fast right in the beginning
that's not
normal great [\h__\h] what is that that one
going on
number one last one oh yeah but that one
i think
that must be that was it i didn't look
at the the country this time but that
must be
a japan girl because she's already
number one and he got a weird face
japan rails with weird faces always end
up number one
[Music]
you stole my thunder which is funny
because that's a that's a phrase you say
sometimes when things happen you know
i hate this game
[Music]
this sucks
i need to drift more i need to drift
money to drift more i need to drink
money to drink
months
what's my problem what's my problem why
did i drift away from the items
why are you cleansing me out
who loves it
it you hellion stupid australians i love
you guys so much
[Music]
me
wait for me
i didn't even get to the [\h__\h]
finishing line are you kidding me
team
number one always
but you are welcome you are welcome to
stay
it's fun having uh people from all over
the world
playing with me
[Music]
what do you mean searching for players
you're all waiting there are like
millions of people waiting outside
[Music]
hello i think we're getting kicked out
or something by the way i'm using the
adapter today to get ethernet oh
what did you tell me to
watch this race i went and didn't get
into my own race
yes i think we're joining a different
tournament now
it's no time to hide this because i
probably won't be able to join my own
anymore
it's probably full well opening up
crusoe 32
two eight four five eight four one four
six four seven five right
and let me put some oh
is that correct two eight four five
eight four one four
six four seven five okay sometimes it
happens
the sequel let's go
sorry to the abandoned ones yeah
very sorry we're also looking at
the last one nice it's that's romantic
it's like we're looking at it together
[Music]
isn't it i feel like the blinking it
looks so cute when i blink it looks so
cute
isn't it so cute oh my god tell me i'm
tell me i'm cute how about anything
[Music]
where is we're in guys oh my god there's
inna and it looks exactly like inna
wow oh and there's a nosaki
she got those ears and everything oh
wait are we going
where do we go where do we go i don't
know i don't care
look as ugly as possible with their
avatars
[Music]
wait this is my first time i've ever
been on this race happened
[Music]
i don't know
what's my first time on this one i don't
even know where we're going wow
wow that looks like fun what game is
that
modeled after wow
hey hello
stay behind me
[Music]
what i heard it like electrically
loading up i was like no way that that's
really going to do that mario galaxy
music is nice too i heard that mario
galaxy music is really nice
oh it's really pretty is this what the
game looks like
obviously we will have to try to play it
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] what what what
i wasn't even trying there i lost my own
fault
[Music]
where is mario galaxy though most recent
one
almost
[Music]
only seven galaxies years old oh
obviously it's the newest owl
look at the nozaki number one so far
away again
it's unbelievable maybe we should
implement a no saggy band
just kidding dad getting ah nice
[Music]
is
number one
[Music]
[Applause]
oh yes my cats are going crazy again
why did he not wait for me ah
everyone leave leave the race okay
animal crossing let's go it's beautiful
love animal crossing
thank you give me back my crown everyone
leave and give me back my crown
i guess that's a good sign that everyone
left
would be that that i have to crowd at
the end wait i don't have a dough why do
i not
why does no one have the crown are you
guys new now you aren't
you're still thinking what to say to me
you're thinking
thinking bye bye thank you
about you huh also where is it oh my god
where's everyone where's everyone where
is everyone
where come on come on come on come on
come on
come on come on in
come on come on please
oh [\h__\h] did i get disconnected because
of my internet or
what happened it can't be that
bad wait that's
okay it can't be that bad right
my internet can't possibly be that bad
i'm streaming and not lagging
so must be nintendo
oh no not that one again let's let's go
oof i don't know
julia who the [\h__\h] is that right next to
me with that weird ass
face we got no time quick oh my god
there's two people with weird ass faces
the green one on the very left looks
weird as hell
too oh wait the one at the very right is
from the office
no the the one on the very right
don't send me foreign i won't accept
them the one on the very right from from
looks like looks like looks like yeah
dwight dwight oh my god someone
recreated
why what oh my god there's so many
people's names that i
know oh my god it's
white it's [\h__\h] dwight that must be
on purpose right
oh my god that's so funny where's the
light
i love your face
oh my god that's the gorgeous face
what a gorgeous face you have i looked
white
okay i'm drifting i'm drifting nice
[Music]
i mean two items never number two that
is a dream that i
that i will never be able to fulfill it
seems
okay okay oh no no you get you get paid
back that was misfaced wasn't it
[Music]
whoever threw that red shell at me oh my
god i'm number 11 oh my gosh only that
green shy guy is way behind me what
what's what's up with that green shy guy
oh my god
well let's choose everything we got here
take this
what why am i so [\h__\h] so
okay oh my god it didn't get me with the
star
but once it was useful but [\h__\h] star
needs this one
much better
[Music]
a green guy wants to spam i wonder if
there's trolls out there like that who
stay behind on purpose to get the
thunder like a million
times are there people like that who
actually do that
[Music]
is
weird faces oh my god i thought that can
only be japanese people
ah there we go the thunder
well well
[Music]
well the music is nice now what is it
what is this one modeled after
wait that's already the end
i didn't even see that coming
but congratulations again japanese
braille japan bro
judas was last one what's happening
wait wait what where judas was a green
shy guy
what
[Music]
what is that [\h__\h] face style next to
me
both of them but the white oh my god i
love the twice face
well thank you thank all of you thanks
thanks thank you that was fun
oh my gosh how did you get that ring
on oh my god
oh man
[\h__\h] that looks like ammo
oh my god where are the rest of the
people come
on everyone come in
please oh oh there we go okay
oh i see it oh that's
famous no saggy oh no
this is wait there's still two two spots
missing ah okay
it's wait who was that again the one
with the crazy glasses
[Music]
pickle
all right there's no way we're gonna win
against those
those people no way
or there's one called rhizolica oh my
god i didn't even see
is that motion
[Music]
let me drive is this because of my
internet connection or could this be
because of other people's internet
connections
come on please oh
[Music]
i'm so many nice people who are
all not letting me win i hate all of you
so much i love you
i hate you i love you i remember this
speech episode it's where i said i'm
gonna stick a banana
in my ass right oh no i'm gonna stick a
banana into your ass no
what was it again that's [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] yeah
oh my god
that that that beach episode where we
played mario kart before and i said
something
here oh yeah what what did i say
what did i say i i don't remember
i have memory issues memory problems did
you just wait behind me so that i could
not
be number 11 thank you
[Music]
here
[Applause]
song
[Music]
oh he's back he's back yeah i got
oh so many stars behind me oh my god oh
my
[Music]
oh you waited for me thank you thank you
oh it's so sweet that's the second time
that person waited for me
oh man
oh manson cave cave paint pickle
i love you wait who won who won was was
it colorful
daddy
[Music]
wait that first one was a i think was a
rammy fan and
it was a freaking funny pun you don't
have a word for
kiana oh my god i love your name that
says
if it's you you can do it oh my god so
so the japanese word for drunkard
is uh yo and you know how dummy is
called
ami right so that person called
themselves yo parami like drunk
drunk like did they combine those two
words i love it
good night no no no don't sleep yet we
gotta drop we gotta drive
so good night
[Music]
eight i can't count i think we'll
complete
yesterday i watched a really funny clip
of subaru senpai
no survival
her being lonely did you guys watch it
being lonely on the minecraft server
running around
oh i love these names wait kiana yay
kishi
what these two people to japanese people
who have
my name in their name
a lot of people watched it where she
went to uh
in canada and was like
and she was always scared of those
noises
oh yeah that was a really funny clip
that was cute and how i got that little
kitty looking
did i just see another fake another in a
real australian
wow that music here is a bad girl oh my
god
what what what
[Music]
oh yeah hey
let's see how
[Music]
race car driving right
right
what's that zero again yeah yeah that's
it oh my god we got the plan because
obviously i'm a professional race car
driver
obviously we have to play it i feel like
i might have
waited around for a long time right
already three out of three oh my god
like
i feel like i maybe played it like when
i was younger
[Music]
i wanted to be nice to you because
you're from where i'm from
oh wait i have to finish
[Music]
oh
what oh that's just how it does
a zero what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
you could have waited behind me
kiana
[Music]
oh no rainbow road oh no but this one
this one was the okay one this wasn't
even that bad wait there's f zero mute
city again
thank you thank you
i want i want the grumble volcano
are you guys leaving or or did you just
join
i wish you could move around on this
globe
thank you for the membership
task now
everyone enjoyed look at that person
left nice
the one behind me was he there before
well sometimes they're trying to leave
but i guess it's just kind of delayed
anyway
[Music]
ah opening it up again
let's go
join cause they're 32. we're keeping the
same one
[Music]
see i'm drinking this smoothie which
tastes hella good it's from from
innocent hashtag not sponsored
it's a breakfast movie that has like
apple banana
and cinnamon and cereals i think and
vitamins inside it's got all kind of
no i'm not watching people again am i
so white
[Music]
it's really yummy because of the
cinnamon it tastes like you know uh
porridge
but i don't like porridge but i like
this smoothie
don't send me friend requests
should i wait
matsu should i wait or not
should i go out
wait okay
know the song they know it
[Music]
is
i know a lot of old japanese songs a lot
of them i'm not always saying only only
[Music]
only
is
oh
[Music]
what is that where oh my all those weird
faces
why why do you make yourself let look
like dad
let's get a sweet
[Music]
then i know that you would be surprised
that i know
what was that one uh
[Music]
my kfb employees welcome
thank you for making it in
simple and clean i sang that one before
did not
[Music]
here and i love this place i want to eat
everything up
wait one hour already past 12. it feels
uh
i'm enjoying this today
give it back
[Music]
come here
[\h__\h] i'm so slow
[Music]
angry german noises
is
[Music]
sorry i wanted to send that to the
german ones
it got to the wrong guy
angry germans
[Music]
is that the character to play when you
want to win
come on now
money money
by the way i would like to officially
announce i have now uh
oh this is already still waiting for me
i love you too thank you
oh wait for once it's not a japanese
person winning the race
what oh wasn't that
was that finland was that finland's flag
oh my god finland has destroyed japan
[Laughter]
nice one i mean there were not many
japanese people in this race to begin
with oh wow he's got an interesting
face really cool face the one with the
nose you gotta leave too thank you
thank you
um i officially have now
signed my contract
for uh
[Music]
my new home hey are we still missing
people
so if you're sex act yeah we're missing
one person again i think
is this a bug i sang my thing for the
new apartment
i was a bit problematic they
they wanted proof before you know that i
can pay the apartment
and they wanted to know how much i
earn monthly but the problem with this
kind of job is
i don't know like there's no fixed
number that i earn monthly so
[Music]
they i i just told them what i earned
like i showed them an official document
of how much i earned the last
few months which is obviously enough to
pay for the apartment
but they didn't accept it
[Music]
so it's actually a bit difficult to get
an apartment
with a job like this
kind of difficult i didn't accept it
and uh yeah i had to
offer them like they offered me um
that i paid not only the security
deposit
but also four months of rent
for like in in advance so the security
deposit is already what three
three months of rent and then another
four months
the seven months of rented on things
yeah just to prove that i can pay it i
mean i could
i offered them to just show them my
savings but they didn't want to see that
one either
i don't know it's difficult
they want to make it complicated huh
it's okay i mean four months of random
it's okay i mean in the end they have to
pay it at some point anyway so whatever
um
[Music]
[Applause]
stole my [\h__\h] item in other housings
where
like the maybe it's like private like
because this this was
through a realtor i guess if it's like a
like
like they they privately rented then
maybe it wouldn't have so many
issues they maybe wouldn't need me to
send them all that those proofs
[Music]
hey everyone thank you thank you
i didn't really pay much attention in
this race anyway
how much longer should we play i'm
having fun here right now
and i'm actually also done with uh hello
talk preparations mostly i got the
questions done
i just need to uh put them into the
little graphics and that's it
thank you baby daisy looks like yeah
ah what if what if i
am stacy
what's that face again is this like some
kind of there's another inado
is there some contest of having the
weirdest face now that homes need some
henna
again one person is missing how long did
it take you to learn japanese well
in in total up until now i've known the
language for
like oh well many many many many many
many years span
like it took me about half a year to get
fluent which is not a normal standard so
don't use me as a you know
what what why is there so many
australians
what they might be my neighbors you
never know australia is pretty small oh
my god they might hear me outside
[Music]
all know each other
we might really know each other who
knows
this looks like australia too by the way
this this place looks like australia
australia
oh my god i'm so bad again look at this
horrible driving
also this reminds me of my hokkaido what
[Music]
whole kind of holiday where i
almost died
oh my god what's going on why am i so
bad oh my god speed come on come on
how am i still only tempo
[Music]
okay i didn't have anything right now
anyway so that's okay
[Music]
okay you'll be my test object for all
these items take them take them
[Music]
it's offended
eat this eat it
eat it
[Music]
skiing skills
[Applause]
[Music]
why are we so bad australians we're
supposed to be skiers you know
we're supposed to be the best ones in
the whole world when it comes to
winter sports why are we all of us the
last ones
oh my god
[Music]
steak today how about that
let me win good out oh my god it really
kind of looks like good
but i'm not sure if they want to look
like gooda because of the glasses it
might not be
uh
i mean it looks a little bit like
[Music]
wait that person wasn't wasn't the one
behind me was she not already in here
before
[Music]
oh well i'm not sure
i feel like she was that's not a man
i don't think they want to look like
omni you can do a much better job if you
want to look like i'm in
let me win
[Music]
wait we got two npcs in here
something is uh wrong with this room
ah hear the beach waves
can we stay here and listen to the beach
waves
so nice oh vacation
look look ah
sticky okay okay let's just be here uh
last one okay i'm doing the lucia
lucia technique and a question by
technique
i don't know how to do it
well that was not the item that i wanted
okay okay
[Music]
no that's not the ones
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
i needed that bus or that uh what do you
call that again
oh i took a shortcut that i didn't even
know that existed
i'm still number 12. hello npc
thank you fbc oh it's
called trap tram in english as well okay
let me go here yeah why are you stupid
automatic
steering what the hell
[Music]
oh yeah come come still number 12 still
got the chance for
no that's also not it that's awesome
meanwhile everyone else is just chilling
at the very front of the road
[Music]
oh my god
good combination for a faster car but i
don't know what to choose
[Music]
okay last round this is where i will
become number one surprisingly at the
very end everyone will be like
what how did she do that
[Music]
oh there we go that's what i wanted okay
okay another one would be nice
huh okay but that's okay too number one
[Music]
meanwhile they already ended the [\h__\h]
race
gotta be optimistic you know
well i gotta be optimistic
well oh well
ah
[Music]
well i mean what i need more speed
give me more speed
[\h__\h]
i don't know they all look like pretty
much the same to me wait i wanted to
change the thing though
how do i change i want to get yeah there
we there we go oh no
and what's that what's that automatic uh
steering i want to turn it off
was it why the middle one
no okay
okay
i don't know i'll report one two three
four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven two oh we're full again
finally
i'm not gonna do much more i'm gonna do
maybe two more races
let's see
try your best to get in takamori
oh my god it's a takamoti
dad it looks more like uh
uh that that anime go there danny isn't
it your second time in here
it looks like um what's that anime grill
called
[Music]
we already see how good i am doing with
oh that oh
no
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
oh i'm gonna double him down okay okay
i can do it i can do it i'm i'm not
so bad at this oh
i thought that was a shortcut there
maybe i was wrong oh my
yeah ah
have some mercy on me will ya you also
suck
that fake australian also sucked he was
driving against the wall
one day that was on purpose for me
number 11 oh come on
[Music]
very good very good very good
yeah okay
okay okay
[Music]
rainbow
kelly is kelly number one
okay all fake australians are
and have to
and have to wait for me
[Music]
please
this is so bad he don't
think oh number 12 really wait for me
please did you guys wait for me
[Music]
three people waiting for me i love you
wait why does that person have like a
golden wheel
because he was using does he use like an
actual wheel instead of a controller
[Music]
wait is that tilt controls
now why did he those last three people
yeah those are those are the best the
mvps
no why did that person have a
one huh
why did that person have a golden
steering wheel
next to their flag
i mean i think you need some practice
without the system
no i don't
i don't know what you mean another chica
fake or a cali fake we will never know
which one you were going after
wait does no one know there's no one to
know
ah wait that person actually used tilt
controls
oh people actually use it
from sexting we're missing one person
again oh well
[Music]
okay no this is a new this is a new uh
cali fake the eyes were different
but i don't think it's cali fake it
looks more like chica but maybe this one
oh yeah okay [\h__\h] that is not her
okay
but okay i see
kelly okay okay
our mission is to whatever place
doesn't matter we just gotta be like
next to each other okay
unite tangomani so for example i'll be
12 and she'll be 11
or something like that by the way we
will know if that is the real calling by
looking at our driving skills because
she also
sucks at mario kart
[Music]
9.
oh no i regret i regret turning on the
turning off the the assist
i need it oh no
this is torture
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
no
[Music]
so far at the top that's the fake cali
that's 100 fake alley
[Music]
oh my god i'm so bad um
i think he also turned off the says
[Music]
this is just me racing against the last
three ones
it doesn't matter who's who is like at
the top it's just me and this japan
first oh thank you for waiting
i think that was a italian case me buddy
i know that's not italy what is that
flag
thank you guys who is that australian
at number four what the hell
mexico ah mexico
okay last one cycle everyone bye-bye let
the let the last people the new people
in
last doll last doll what that's the
water pack yay
[Music]
let me turn back on
yeah welcome welcome to the last race i
hope we're full
numbered one two three four five six
seven eight nine ten eleven i think
we're all yeah
yay let's do the last one
let's let me win let me win
let me win okay guys
you know what's up right last race
you're gonna let your boss win
please no no that's not kelly that
if anything that's a really weird cali
let me win
[Music]
please please please
beat the last mickey winner please
please
that looks that doesn't look that's a
cabbie and maybe cabbie yeah
not cali
[Music]
why why me
what
oh really bad
it's really bad
[Music]
okay now he's my comeback look look at
this
[Music]
she says while passing by in the
australian
[Music]
driver
oh
[Music]
yes
speaking three languages today as we can
see international phoenix
eat this eat this eat this
[Music]
oh
go go go go go go go
[Music]
me
i dropped my controller uh
bye bye bye bye
bye [\h__\h]
thank you everyone for participating
with me
super chat reading let's go
[\h__\h] what a mess
uh
super chat reading
let's go proved
[Music]
hey
did i get my point across
i'm not sure what point i was making but
whatever
uh it's because
i think i think i know why i did so bad
today
i think i know the reason
i know it it's because and only because
i didn't have my steering wheel and i
used an orange instead
that's the only reason
because you better shut up
shut up it's not because i'm bad i'm
really good at driving
well we will be reading super chats from
now on
[Music]
um
driving into walls yeah because of the
[\h__\h] orange
because of the orange
all right i'll go read the super chats
quickly because then
i'm gonna finish my last preparations
for holo talk and maybe take a nap
maybe i'll probably probably even if i
try to not take a nap i'll probably take
a nap accidentally
okay
[Music]
thanks
all right hot wings please oh thank you
for answers
how how did you see gamers tweet
it wasn't that good nobody at you you
panicked ten of you little chickens are
lagging one tweet and i'm afraid of two
hundred well she's so cool
i saw you all panicking and spamming me
adding me like how did you how did you
find that tweet like
millions of you added me like wow
that was just like
[Laughter]
okay so actually there's a simple
explanation
i um sometimes sometimes like
in my in my when i go for my replies
when i go maybe i shouldn't tell you
maybe i should leave you in the mystery
[Laughter]
no okay okay it's not like i'm stalking
you
well so sometimes when i go like if i go
when i go for my replies
uh it shows replies but it doesn't show
uh quoted
retweets so sometimes when i remember to
do so i go for the quoted retweets
manually and then i found this one
quoted retweet
that kind of caught my attention so i
i opened it and then i saw the whole
conversation
because there was a quoted retweet in
that thread
that basically tagged me for the for the
quoted retweet
i don't remember who it was but you
might you think you can find out
yourself
i i just needed to you know
know the context of that quoted retweet
and then there was a lot of interesting
things written
in that thread so i scrolled and i
scrolled and i scrolled
and then someone was like haha if only
he had a sawdust and then i liked it
[Laughter]
aren't you happy that i am looking at
you tweets
you should be happy
don't you feel like more connected to me
i mean if you don't want me to see it
then
do it in your dms or like i don't know
on discord or whatever
or twitter is uh
my rain because i'm verb and twitter is
a verb too
it's where i belong this is my reign
i control everything this is my hood
[Music]
don't think you're safe between birds
the twitter burden and me the firebird
don't think you're safe
i have a good control system
can i just i mean you guys can you can
also private all of your accounts
and then have a conversation among
private uh privatized
locked accounts
if you don't want to be seen you gotta
put in more effort and also don't
don't don't quote retweet me although
mostly like really it's uh
mostly i don't look at the quote for
tweets because they don't show up in my
normal
reply thingy sometimes
for this specific case i wondered what
people were saying so
nothing but the fandom coefficient hello
coefficient was here thank you
you made me laugh kiara ggs what does
ggs stand for
good girl xavier
good girl sexy good girl sexy
oh wait nothing but offend as well
i must be good girl sexy good girl sexy
wow
well yeah you don't need to be so
oh it makes me a little bit embarrassed
stop stop
stop good girl
sexy no
no no no no no no no you can't say that
so directly to me
[Music]
okay anyway
thanks thanks thanks thanks you too
good gravy sauce oh good gravy that's
basically the same thing as good girl
sexy good gravy sauce it's just another
way to say that
what she couldn't support me oh man
too bad luckily my twitter is safe how
is your twitter saved i mean because
there's nothing weird written on it
hey kickstand gasoline
thank you paying for the gasoline
thank you very much thank you hey cake
how are you doing here
geek how's it going do you like the new
kiana
thank you for the red super dab i
think i've i need more gasoline maybe i
ran out of gasoline
maybe that's why i was so slow um
i need to can you guys send me
recommendations for like good
combinations like i guess the thing is
also that i haven't played it much
privately so i don't have all options or
card options and all that
but can you guys send me recommendations
of good combinations of of
of like carts and and and wheels and
the the thingy please
please turning off honesty is a good
start you saw me turning off
all the steering i don't think it was
good at all we've seen what happened
small wheels best wheels depends on how
you drive well then
you have seen me drives many times then
analyze
that and please send me some help
[Music]
okay i i promise
you one thing if i
get number one in mario kart against you
guys at some point
then i will at a place one
first place then i will organize
whole hollow yen holo id holo id second
gen
mario kart cup tournament
i'm not saying that
it must be a natural win you can also
let me win
no but it should it should be a low-key
natural win
so that i have the skills you know to
actually win in the mario kart
tournament
as well so you should teach me you
should show me
what is a good combination
of a wheel and cart and all that
send it to me on twitter next year
driving with collabs because people love
the collabs they love them
thank you you're at school
i'm counting on you
patrick what it
your name is korean
let me translate that but i feel like
you're your avatar i know your avatar
did you change your name
to korean so that i can't character
aren't you jindal
ah
[Music]
he changed his name to korean and it
reads as jin lo as well
oh my god i
i recognized him even with a different
uh alphabet
that is jingle
how did i know what two things
first of all general always sends like
small super chats in the beginning of
the stream
now this was a small super chat us
dollar in the beginning of the stream
and
second thing the other avatar gave it
away
i remember you guys
[Laughter]
thank you for the pinky
hey okay i live in ca so maybe i can't
attend your live stream at 4 8
home today i hope you have more fun with
everyone best wishes to piano no i
totally got that
i mean who the hell would wake up at 4am
for my stream
wait did a bunch of you wake up at 4am
for me
because i did see some americans some
americans there
what you guys are crazy
you guys are crazy
oh my god
thank you thank you
why why did you do that
just watch the archive thank you i
appreciate it very much that's crazy
damn
okay that's very sweet of you that moves
my heart
thank you
oh good girl sexy
[Laughter]
yeah sleep is for the week
kiana more important than sleep archive
is not the same yeah that's true but you
can't catch
every string gino is even in the chat
were you surprised that i recognized
your name before i even translated it
why did you change it anyway did you
change it to bamboozle me
you were the first thing that is
priority oh thank you
so sweet i can catch every stream nice
odds maybe
can't catch every stream are you
challenging me yes i
challenge you i specifically
uh ha um scheduled this stream at this
time
for my australian and and asian viewers
over there at
sea
a can you speak german for a second
nine that was literally a second so
[Music]
gonna step on the gas tonight's
potential fly
and cali will be your lover yeah yeah
yeah attention will be so quick as
a flash what song is that
[Music]
i know
by the way i have this uh you were beat
version of hinotoni that i think i
let you guys listen to at some point
um i feel like that would have been
really perfect for today but
but
the game already has really good music
so
wait where is my where is that version
again
what's this one see i don't bury the
remix what was that again
what's that one
what are these
where's mine where's mine
i want to find the eurobeat version
someone sent me though i can't find it
is it is it here i found it
oh shh
i let you guys listen to this before
right
oh sure
[Music]
uh
[Applause]
[Music]
hey
wait wait wait
[Music]
if we're gonna do that i need my glasses
special life concert
for you guys who stay for the super jet
reading
you are the mvps
[Applause]
[Music]
so
hey
[Applause]
[Music]
um
me
[Music]
day
[Applause]
[Music]
trying to find my destiny
if i go wrong what awaits me in the dark
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
i promise i will find you
[Applause]
hey
that was very improvised and never tried
singing along with that before
kiana's first original song
hinotori you're a beat version
this was that
actually uh that was fun
now i have a i have a jazz version that
i sang before
i think you guys uh remember that uh
this was the european version i think
there's yeah there's a 8-bit version as
well
i love all these versions so nice
uh the credit
it's uh it's on on soundcloud
if you guys want to check it out and
download it
there you go
go download it two million views yeah
thank you thank you all for supporting
hinotoni
i have a problem i cannot raise my arm
one second
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay anyway back to super chat reading
uh where was i why did i
ah because of general except the song
and i was like oh i have a song too
wow okay
that was absolutely necessary
[Music]
no message written but still thank you
thank you so much for your support
[Music]
red super chat morning from the east
coast u.s center another one who woke up
early for me
thank you sing something in german oh i
already sang
he not only in german before there is
that there's a german version
because i made it german i wrote a
german version of it before
so many hinotonio versions
uh esd was ah yes it was 7 am and psd
was uh
4am well 7am is still
manageable i guess
uh thank you for next time anyway for
waking up early honestly for me i would
never wake up at 7am for anyone thank
you
hope you enjoyed it
[Music]
subscribe you were also in the game
today congratulations
i really appreciate the fun we always
have with you we know you are doing your
best for everyone and we love tanjo
thank you for destroying inside
thank you thank you also for you know
trying to communicate in english for me
personally you can write in japanese
that's totally fine but thank you
hope you enjoyed today's stream recently
i'm not streaming at very good times for
japanese
fans anymore unfortunately but i will
try to you know every now and then
have a a a stream in there that's at
prime time for japanese bros as well
um
[Music]
today i got my six month batch
i finally grew up and became a full
chicken i wonder what i'll be in six
more months oh no one knows no one knows
an even bigger chicken yeah yeah yeah
yeah
maybe a majestic phoenix like my boss
i'm sure it will be something amazing
there's no escape from my brand future
yeah exactly don't worry you you'll be
on fire like a phoenix
you you'll be on fire i can't i can
promise you that
look forward to it it's a very bright
bright future like a look at my next
film
hoping that you will stay until then and
even longer
thank you
[Music]
that not letting them to win is
absolutely justified grounds for
termination you will also before fate
all employment unemployment benefits
including your favorite spring
uncle biv you are one of the
[Music]
how to say in english foreign
how do you how do you call that again
oh you didn't get in what was that my
imagination damn
bootleggers know what the [\h__\h] now
someone who does their their job really
well
and uh others can learn from that person
ah excellent exemplary employees
model employees yeah yeah uncle biff is
a model employee not only because he's
sexy
but also because he does uh his job very
well
[Music]
super burger time thank you
us is good at racing unless there are
corners
roast bike drop
petrol
you made a complete turn around and
learned alchemy at the mirror you began
to master news combat we can only hope
that in the future the same thing can
happen with your mario kart gameplay
what do you mean what do you mean i'm
already good at it
sir but yeah i
i think that day will never come
skittles thank you
if you press the drift button when you
go off a ramp you'll do a trick and get
a speed boost yeah i've heard of that a
bunch of times but i
i'm not yet good enough to focus on
those kind of things
uh you mean the jump ring
jump when you're jumping off something
oh
have you seen the hino20x space jam
mashup b-ball tony it somehow works
really well as well as a remax
maybe i have not
[Music]
i've heard one remix of i think it was
hinotoni
where basically they used
they used one one syllable
of of my singing like
like one second only and repeated it
for the whole remix and then they were
like this is a hinotoni remix
and it sounded nothing like hingo
and and it's yeah it was just i
i don't remember quite but i think it
was just like me saying
tata like something like that something
that that short and it got
like repeated and repeated and repeated
and people in the comments were like yo
this is fire and i'm like
i mean it sounds good but
what part of you know is left in there
i remember that one oh you know which
one i'm talking about
maybe it's not he know tony maybe it's
heart challenge yeah i'm not sure what
it might i don't know it was any song of
mine was that maybe it was hard
challenger
[Laughter]
sounded really good but use more
use more of my singing please
ah maybe next time
uh i was it was it was heart challenging
oh did you see the usual room seashell
you asked yes i did see
it that was so cool ah the french remix
yes yeah
oh my god
it sounded really cool and i like the
sound of the remix
very much
[Music]
there's a french linux no it's like
french house remix i think that's what
it is
that's what they call the genre
i just hopped on and missed mario kart
yeah don't worry the archive will be
there
for you
okay continuing uh where was i
want it oh judas
oh dude that says i just see when the
race started it was a [\h__\h]
oh i thought you were just you know you
know
being bad on purpose
because you lost the race i was like
what's wrong with judas is he having
like a
a good day where he just wants me to win
whoa what's going on
he would never oh it was the same for me
too
no well at least at least on video
oh in my stream you were racing with me
you might have not been able to control
it
but you were racing with me
seems the opposite seems he had a bad
wink oh no
my honor it was not me who would use the
red shell on you i was framed still
easily got four of them
you were framed but you mean you got
framed how can you get framed on mario
kart
leo
[Music]
and kurosaki
what is the approximate amount for me
with kfb hundred
ten dollars or a hundred dollars
a meal like caffeine
uh a full meal with burger fries and a
drink
you can get for uh eight dollars
just a realistic price
yes
just realistic yeah
i'm not a ripoff we want to be a
worldwide fast food uh um leader
we want to have a monopoly so obviously
we gotta
offer some fair prices
aren't the meals free it's just working
that has a price yeah
did i ever say the meals are free i
can't imagine myself saying a thing like
that i mean you
the people who work at kfp can get free
food
but the people who don't work there they
have to pay obviously
obviously
revolutionary
have to catch up on the stream later
painting the fence because weather is
good
listening to history while painting his
motivation could you painting a fence
that sounds like that sounds so
random yeah i hope it turns out good
thank you yellow cake thank you
uh it probably is larry thank you
thanks for always being so chill and
upbeat the positivity is always needed
and we love you for it so never change
the rabbits offer a nose wiggle wave as
well
the rabbits you mean
what do you mean the rabbit's offering
those do you say that because of easter
or do you say that because you're no
saggy says easter tomorrow isn't it i
never
um ever since i've grown up i never
really celebrated easter when i was
younger i remember
um i mean
not i remember
having eggs
and chocolate hidden
in the park and in the garden
and then i would go hunt for them
uh i actually really liked easter when i
was younger
it was fun yeah i remember my heroine
they make like probably maybe in other
countries as well but they make like
little nests
and like easter nests
where they put in like like
uh some chocolate and some eggs i think
and then they hide them and then there's
also as an activity we
we would at um we would paint the eggs
the empty eggs like where no egg is
anymore inside but only the shell
we would paint the eggshells and i i
know i said i wanted to um
do something for easter but
that would have been very my idea kind
of came too late
it would have had to be tomorrow but
with holotac and kelly's birthday
it's a busy day so
uh unfortunately no easter celebration
this year maybe next year if i'm still
around
maybe we can do something like that next
year although cali's birthday would
again be on the same day next year
i'm about to wait easter
easter is also oh every year on the same
day though right
wait eastern moves
ah eastern because it's always an easter
sunday
huh oh well then maybe next year or
doesn't
clash with cali's birthday it shouldn't
nadoo hoda it would have been a fun idea
it would have been a cute idea
to paint some eggs that would have been
cute do you guys do that too
like at least as children
[Music]
is
yes yes yes it's been a while i did that
too
water cold eggs yeah yeah yeah
one day just before callie's next year
oh
yes yes yes only once
thank you eric thank you
i used to paint some naughty stuff as
again what on the eggs come on have some
decent scene
still do it for your kids i think it's
really cute like i
uh i think like okay many of these
holidays and many of these celebrations
are
religious but even though i'm not
religious i still like celebrating these
things i think it's really cute
so
yeah i i mean
i think all of you almost all of you
probably also celebrate christmas
it's fun traditions yeah well i believe
i believe in
the church of takanawa
and you should too
don't apologize what the hell let me
continue
uh
uh i think if i remember correctly your
me was absolutely disgusting
but i'm not sure it might have been
someone else
i'll try no wait wait wait wait the well
both of these are pinkies well i'm just
gonna stop thank you thank you for
the pinky i i need to thank you
specifically for that thank you
hey what hey wasn't yours ugly
i guess it's a it depends on
what you see is ugly and what you see is
beautiful but i think yours was ugly
wait i don't remember if you asked me
like that i just assumed that yours was
one of the ugly ones
[Music]
ultra new thank you also for the pinky
australian friend hello
kiara we will watch your racing career
with great interest wayne are you trying
to tell me something with that
w w y r c
w g i i don't know you you're
capitalizing every letter every first
letter of each word
are you trying to tell me something
there's a star wars reference
oh oh i am watching something with great
interest
i've heard that before
thank you for thinking ultra new thank
you thank you it's a meme
did you guys realize that i actually
have a meme in
my in my thumbnail
because race cars that's a race race car
meme
did you guys recognize that i was like
okay what funny thing can i ride in
on my thumbnail and i googled
i googled race car means
uh and that's like the one thing that
came up
it's like pictures were
of cars where they asked why did you add
this and death to your car and then the
answer is like because race car
yeah i didn't even know it i just used
it because it came up on google and i
thought i would be funny and cool and
and edgy if i would use some kind of
meme you know
even i thought people would be like oh
my god she knows her memes wow
she knows a freaking race car meme
dammit didn't get it
unfortunately i know nothing
[Music]
wow i can't believe i actually managed
to beat you for once you're usually just
way too good for me
i stand no chance be honest let you let
me win didn't you no way i could have
won otherwise
be gamer
i sense sarcasm
in your super chat
[Music]
not cool
but thank you for participating nice to
have you there
thank you thank you
okay have some fun
yeah yeah
i'm just a teammate i i really wanted to
watch a youtube live stream so i became
a member but now i'm forced to work for
kfc i'm scared please let me go
no i will never let you go but that's so
nice thank you
i'm glad you joined because of the
ukulele wow thank you
because race car now you can never leave
never you're here forever
and i welcome you in this family but you
will never want to leave
the people here are so nice so welcoming
so warm so sweet
finally sound concerned happy easter for
tomorrow attention loving the new
wealthy model hope this helps to
replenish your rent money
it's okay i got enough i got enough
savings it
still just seems ridiculous to me that
they didn't accept like i sent them
a document stamped by yago
himself where it states
my income from the past six months
which if you think logically
must i must have saved some in my
money to to pay for the rent
but i don't know yeah i it was really
like i was really
because they're they were like stressing
me out and they didn't even give me
like they didn't answer me like i i told
you guys this before
what is it with these realtors who don't
answer me don't they want to like sell
me their [\h__\h] apartment
i'm just renting not buying but yeah um
so i asked them
well what do you need for me to
show you you know how much uh
i earn and stuff what do you need and
then they didn't answer
for like three days and then suddenly
i i get two emails at once from two
different people from that company
being like we give you we give you less
than 24 hours they said uh they said
something like 12 a.m of the next day
and they sent that to me
pretty late like it was not even it was
barely 24 hours
uh until you send us uh
proof official proof of how much you
earn each month
and now you gotta think the time when
they sent that to me
was out of the office times in japan
and 12 8 and 12 p.m i guess 12 p.m right
12 p.m noon what's the deadline in my
time zone
uh so yeah i don't know suddenly they
rushed me after not answering me for
three days
so i rushed to my manager
and i'm like please i need something
official
and i organize it in less than 24 hours
officially stamped by juggle
and then i gave it to them and they sent
me an email back immediately and they're
like now we can't use that
oh come on
[Applause]
oh man that sucked
no it's not because it was a japanese
stamp or so
it's just because it's what i earned in
the past few months and they want to
know what i earn
in the following months which i get but
i can't i can't
i don't have a fixed salary
so that's uh the jaguar has no value
ah no yeah i needed
what i own what i earn in the future i
get that i get that
but if i can't say how much i'll
earn in the future
oh well print out the superjet and show
it to them
that's not enough they said
i must earn at least double the amount
of the rent
well per month for them to give this
apartment to me
oh wow wow
anyway i have the apartment now so it's
all good
it's all yeah double them i don't know
it's because i think move this so this
apartment
the the realtors and the owners just
seemed very very
uh you guys are so surprised about
double wow
but they seem very strict about this
apartment specifically
to just make sure that well the person
who moves in can afford it
but double yeah double seems a bit much
having an income double the amount of
the rent
i think in the past i used to earn like
1 1.5 the amount of my rent
maybe something like that i think that's
like basic
a little bit less than double
but yeah for me it's fun triple
whoa whoa we're not talking about
security deposits now you're saying
triple they they want you to earn triple
the amount of what the rent costs
in your place what
why not buy instead of rent because
right now
um i wanna i wanna buy some
something in the future but at the
moment
um i wanna live
in this city but i don't think i want to
live here in the future
um i want to i probably want to live
more in the countryside in the future
so i'm not ready to purchase anything
yet but at the moment i don't want to
live in the countryside
what i so i don't i don't want to buy
anything now
maybe at some point in the future i want
to buy
an apartment or i don't know a house
on the countryside or like maybe
i was thinking to get a house at a lake
because in australia we got some really
beautiful lakes you have no idea
we might have no ocean yes australia has
no ocean
we might have no ocean but uh
we have beautiful peaceful
serene lakes and
i think that's my goal we also have
beautiful mountains
and but i'm not much of a mountain type
of person
also i would probably need a car if i
want to live in the mountains
but i think i wanna yeah i wanna get a
lake house
and live there once i'm like done with
living in the city
um
like i've i visited like um
a lake house like a lake
lake and says i say
it's lake lake sounds so small
it's funny how in in english
the ocean you call it sea
but in german we call the ocean
no we we call them we call the lakes see
it's so similar so sometimes i mix it up
but yeah i'm talking about
yeah a large larger lake large lake
so whenever i go to large lakes i see
these people having these
lake houses and and doing like barbecue
dare and stuff and i'm like wow that's
so
nice that's so nice
[Music]
i think that's a good goal
to have
[Music]
looking forward to that
i was also for a while i was also
thinking about living in germany
a little bit but i don't know
germany and australia are like
pretty similar anyway
especially because the language is the
same so i might as well just
stay in australia because at least here
uh i have like the the benefits of being
a person
that comes from this place don't come to
germany
why not i visited germany a lot of times
though
i've been there a million times because
it's like right next to our
uh to us yeah and my friends and my
family
they live here too so yeah
i know i know they'll steal your phone
they did it already
[Music]
oh
okay
they'll do it again i think i'll steal
my phone again
oh man
[Music]
some japanese bros really think i'm from
australia which just makes sense because
i prefer live yen and i keep on saying
australia
so it just makes sense
but i explained it a little bit for them
uh oh my god there must be so many
people so many japanese
fans thinking that i am like not even
fans people who just like
whole life in general and just have a
superficial knowledge of takanasikiyara
they must think that i'm from australia
oh no oh
[Music]
no not australia but australia
what if you also bamboozled the japanese
little members
it could have could be possible
anyway i should be reading the super
chats
best awesome accent i've ever heard
frank smite
that sounds more brilliant i actually
can't like
i i hear a difference when i hear a
british
british person speaking and i hear an
australian person speaking
i hear the difference of the accent but
i cannot impersonate it
unfortunately when i try to sound
australian i tend to
sound british or scottish
this is so difficult for me so difficult
for mine
what did that sound like
they all sounds guys
so difficult for my
that sounds british now
ah mate
i just add mate everywhere okay okay
okay
sounds harry potter yes and british
yo what mate
are you what night
bloody well mate how how you doing
kangaroo
tuesday tuesday
or may i might
sounds like a pirate what oh you wanna
go
mate
this is speaking the language of the
gods maybe ask hatsuma for some tips
see i she
she speaks good english but she doesn't
speak australian accent
does she okay anyway where was i
dk drift king duncan can you drift
obviously not today i was really bad at
drifting
thank you cat fluff duncan
thank you
you are you quoting the game kooky yummy
cattle fluff
letting a boss get 10th place on the
last game somehow or other
dot dot dot consider it that sounds like
a quote from the game
i like i like how you reference other
games that i played on stream in other
games yeah you did ah
there we go nice one
savage step strap pitting what are you
trying to say
not upset at all i'm not upset
no i refresh and i'm scrolling
um got it
where did we stop where did we stop
where did we stop there well
now
love this model but the other model is
hotter what you don't like mine
i guess i i don't have any hips and any
boobs
in this model do i huh
don't worry it will be back in hollow
talk
yellow cake thank you soon rice all
three duncan
don't pull your hair out denture it's
hard to model them already i don't want
to do that for another week again
oh what you model what like 3d models or
2d models
james maxon
thank you for the red super chat james
wow
anyone else have the desire to pinch
angry ball fees chiara's cheeks
and that's kind of cute but don't
don't pinch my cheeks
same as me not liking head pants i also
don't like
having my cheeks pinched okay
am i okay i mean if if you send a red
super chat i guess i have to
accept it
your australians accents great can you
please show us the accent of the phoenix
as well
it's just the way i talk right now
no touching no
thank you thank you james thank you
i suppose you're calling me cute because
you want to pinch my cheeks
i'll take it as that thank you that's
really sweet
douglas bracebo is duncan and for
unfortunate did
get well unfortunate did get you racy i
think you were trying to say
you did not get to raise me but have fun
watching have a good day thank you
enter 0
[Music]
uh mr cat big sun pudding
thank you for the pinky kiara
good girl kiara thank you you'll always
be number one for me oh yeah
update on epic games she was very sad
that she couldn't support your last
silver game as food that's okay i had
more than enough other food
and thank you for letting me be your
number one
thank you thank you
motion swamp flyer thank you please
wait for you at the finish line i can
truly call myself a simp now yay
that's that's the way to go i haven't
seen the super chat in a while because
i've been broke i still am broke oh no
please it's okay don't don't feel forced
or anything please
it's okay i will i will not forget you
even if you don't send the super chat
thank you for the thing
[Music]
just catching up to the stream white
scanner bribing viewers with collapse
ah i'm not bribing i'm just offering a
good opportunity that everyone wants to
make
come true and i said i don't i don't
want to
get number one no just like that
easily next time because because if you
guys just give let me win number one
which by the way i don't think you guys
can coordinate yourselves well enough to
really make me win on purpose like that
i
i don't think you guys can do that
uh but yeah i wanna that tournament i
don't want it to happen right away so
i would wouldn't mind getting number one
more later rather later than earlier are
you challenging us is that a challenge
yes well i will challenge you yes
you would be surprised oh okay
very psychology
i didn't even try but i guess yeah that
worked
he did get number one one time when i
think everyone disconnected
don't say that i still believe in the
fact that there's a possibility that
they did not disconnect
[Music]
for the cleaning company we are proud to
say that your usual room got finally
cleaned and we found a weird puzzle
piece under the 1 million legos and
brought that
to you in your office so it doesn't get
lost
but i'll destroy it i'll burn it i i
i hit that one how did you find it there
thank you but they're not supposed to
have that uh puzzle piece
no no no no no no no no it's burned
already
it's gone it's good i need that piece
please
the last piece no no i
ate it gulp
thank you doc maha for cleaning though
uh
usual room needed some cleaning there
was a lot of
weird red stains everywhere not sure
where those
stains came from
but good at so good that it's gone now
so that new people who joined the usual
room would not be so
you know confused about it and stop
asking questions
and yeah it's just silly chicken
spilling ketchup exactly
musty ketchup yeah obviously
why are you guys bringing ketchup to the
user room
want to hear a joke yeah not me joining
the last room after so many connection
errors and finishing the
race dead last oh that's
it's not a joke that's a good way to
battle against me congratulations on
getting in though
nice one black friction
[Music]
stayed up till 4am to lunch gotta keep
my never miss a single kiana stream
record going strong chicken live
oh my god please don't force yourself oh
man
i mean i staying up to 4am is not much
of a problem for me
but oh my god do you have a job is that
are you okay
job what is that
oh man you're worth it oh thank you
crispy
that's so sweet that's so sweet
a saturday oh yeah this weekend i guess
yeah the weekend is manageable
i guess so wow job is here
only job is kfb yeah okay i forgot about
that
working from home is easier absolutely
worth it thank you that's so sweet
well if you're working for home i guess
maybe you can
uh manage your time on your own then
okay okay
just iron duncan
[Music]
okay
is it jojo reference man i'm so outdated
did i just rotate that i must have been
enough
oh you must spin kiana in the golden
rectangle there must be an infinite
i don't power of super don't get it even
in english i don't understand it can you
give it to me in german just kidding
i don't get it do you guys get that joke
i'll spin again
instruction unclear
is is this is is this what you want
[Music]
it's hard for me to stop once i started
thank you thank you though thank you for
the rest of you and the pinky
i'm washing my teeth
jacob
[Music]
she looks stiff when spinning with a gym
mates while collabing well that was
that was that was a different reason but
now i'm
spinning smoothly you know will be
six nine seven eight thank you for the
pinky nice moves thank you
got those dance moves there's a lot of
moves that i can't do
in my normal uh look
in my normal model i wish i could jump
and spin like that as normal kiara
but yeah this this is the right the
right outfit
for doing some sick ass dance moves
like a nightmare no
no
it's very close to free yeah we're
getting closer and closer to 3d
[Music]
yesterday was my birthday i happy late
birthday
oh a live piano tony from small
attention is the best gift ever here's
my birthday bonus as per the cafe
contract
keep being awesome and have a wonderful
day well thank you so much
have you had i hope you had a lovely
birthday
yeah hope you got to eat lots of cake
and drink some
some of your favorite beverage whatever
that is
thank you very much for coming by
jump up zero zero zero eight sanctions
thank you for the pinky
uh-uh rabba kun here rubber the rubber
wants me to come back fine you have more
money and better chicken to steal the
jfp
plus your security is easy to grab
because you don't pay them
makes sense if i was good at making
decisions i wouldn't be a robber in the
first place
welcome back rubber i guess so yeah
ah cool to have you
back wound me set six nine seven eight
thank you
so thank you soon
i was framed because you played before
rachel while i was in front of you it's
funny that you know me well enough to
surrender me
you weren't no it's because you are
behind me and then you for a red shell
at me and then suddenly you were in
front of me surprise surprise but okay
maybe that
maybe that's not what happened but
that's what i thought happened at that
moment whatever
vlad my inhaler donkey shooting eric
kidd
looking for the top thunder
i can't have my sleep and missed the
game part of the stream oh no
good morning looking for the job my one
size relief though i wonder why well
thank you
and thank you for coming even if you're
late that's okay
[Music]
you spy duncan thank you pretentious
apartment well thank you
thank you for the red super chat pinky
spy
[Music]
i'm looking forward to um getting like
completely new furniture everything new
new new new because i have no furniture
right now
and make the new apartment my own
yeah that will be fun to make everything
my own style because right now like my
roommate
basically uh owns all the furniture in
the living room and everywhere
in this apartment and even though she
has a great taste and she bought really
nice furniture
it's just not this is not mine you know
new cats no not yet i don't know
um i'll be keeping an eye out on the
shelter
whenever i see something that i think
fits also i'm nervous like i
i'm not i don't know i just i just
uh i'm not sure if my cats would
if they would accept a new member
i want i want them to accept it that
would be nice
but they're really spoiled and they're
used to just being
you know those two
ah
well um i feel like
i feel like chunkers would be kind of
sad
and jelly and smoothie would
be like you know that [\h__\h] over there
she would be like a mean girl maybe
two is enough no you can never have
enough cats
[Music]
but i think if you do it right you
should be able to
make the existing cats welcome the new
cat
if you do it right and if the synergy
the synergy is just good because
obviously there's just some cats that
just don't go with other cats because of
their personality but
good but um
get three more to bamboozle 10 cats
get them used to smells yeah yeah yeah
like keep keep the new cat in a room
let them smell each other through the
the door
and then slowly introduce them to each
other then switch rooms
put the new cat into the other room and
the the other two cats
into the one room stuff like that you
know transitioning i've
seen videos like that before
yeah needs some patience
no cat in the usual room
and not pink donkey shim good afternoon
buzz you look great recently
unfortunately have not been able to
watch all streams online and watch
reruns
reporting promotion of kfb in eastern
europe is going well kfb gsg
thank you and you don't worry about it
as long as you still check in every once
in a while and watch the archives then
you're
you're a good employee thank you
skydiving
carlos gonzalez thank you thank you for
the pinky
hi thank you the american stream was a
lot of fun could i get a happy birthday
for my birthday today
happy birthday also you sent two pinkies
which makes one red one which makes me
happy to sing for you
i've become a level 39 furlock today i'm
looking forward to another year of
watching you your streams have meant a
lot to me during a year where i've lost
some very important people to me
it helped a lot at the time even if it
was just a little bit
also i know it's late but my name isn't
for luck it's
fur luke
like the olympic sport what what sport
is that
i know you're going to sculpt me no no
no no
for luke is that is that it
no okay is it for luge
is it for luge for lunch
closer
lucha for lujan
for luge for lose purlins
froot loops
no no [\h__\h] well send me a freaking voice
message on twitter you can send voice
message messages
if you didn't know sent me a voicemail
i'm surprised people didn't already sent
me a post message oh no please don't
but i'm not gonna listen to your
millions and millions of uh
voice messages if you start sending them
to me now i will not listen to them
but if it's called if it's cold if it's
like the same as the sport
then i could i guess look up the
pronunciation of that sport
[Laughter]
anyway
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you
happy birthday dear fellows
really happy
[Music]
was that okay and we got we got way
closer if i sat
for furlough before that now we made a
big improvement
can't get it perfectly i think
thank you thank you for um watching my
streams all this time and i'm glad i
could help you a little bit
through some tough times
it must be rough to lose important
people
to you and i hope that um
i can feel that hole a little bit
thank you thank you so much please enjoy
your birthday
there will be better times
thank you stay strong
[Music]
another refresh
someone other stuff duncan crispy duncan
glad when one duncan your australian
accent is great oh thank you
[Music]
do you have a photographic memory your
ability to recall things
uncanny ah because of me recognizing
ginger
no i definitely don't have a
photographic memory but
some of you guys send super chats in
every stream so it's easy to remember
some of you
guys it just automatically got imprinted
into my brain
i wish i had a photographic memory
i wish i had
miami compost refined
lemon pepper phoenix or phoenix covered
in lemon lime grapefruit
ginger chili garlic what the heck
lemon pepper phoenix if you mean like
you know what's good like pasta with
lemon pepper sauce something like that
and chicken it's really yummy
and maybe with some asparagus
i can recommend that asparagus
chicken lemon pepper pasta
is so yummy obviously the
chicken would be vegan
ah what was that
nothing i wish i could
i only ate that in restaurants before i
don't know how to make that sauce myself
i want to learn how to make it
a chicken died for that chia
i tried to make me like be more
respectful
and shake and die for that kiana be more
i love it
ah
junior campus thank you for another
pinky
trying to explain to me that joke or
meme i really need to really need to
catch up on on
recent memes and recent animes i just
don't get anything at all
thank you though for trying to explain
it to me and trying to
educate me hope to see you in holo talk
too
hope you'll be there i mean it's early
in the morning
but it's at least not in the middle of
the night for japan
no one important
uh black friction dankeshen shorter
state of late flame monster hunter with
some of my dudes lol
hope to see you play too at some point
have you seen the weapon types and which
interests i haven't seen on the weapon
types i've
i've peeked into some of the monster
hunter
rice uh gameplays of
the whole live girls it looks really
good i really wanna
one thing that i really enjoy about
games is character creation
and monster underwrite seems to have a
good character creation
so i just want to create characters
this is like me when i play sims i just
create characters again and again and
again and then i never play family again
and i make a new family
again and again and again
and then mmrpg is the most fun part for
me was also
creating the character and then later on
buying like like um
like like like like new custom outfits
in the cash shop with real money
that was like my goal in mmorpgs in
anime mmorpgs my goal was to have the
cutest outfits
to look cute
but back then when i was playing all
those mmrpgs
i had no money i only had
my weekly allowance of
i think i think at some point i had a
weekly allowance of
10 euros
[Music]
i think that was the most
but so that i couldn't buy many outfits
from that
so i i just tried to
get rich in game and then buy those
items off
of the people who can buy stuff from the
cat shop
buy it with in-game money which is
absolutely overpriced
ah yeah
i got an allowance but i left
home pretty early
uh and therefore i like got
no like i left i left that kind of like
financial support pretty early on
your sugar daddy what the [\h__\h] how do
you come to that conclusion
out of everyone you know who do you like
the least what kind of question is that
are you asking out of all of the whole
live members who do i like the least
first of all why do why would i answer
such a question second of all
why do you ask such a question but you
know what let me let me just say
since you didn't specify her life even
though i think that's what you meant let
me just say
the person who i like the least
because you didn't specify is mario
manis
thank you grab a couple of coolies and
meet us at the billabong for a barbie
love your heart yucca
good on your shella you're a ripper what
a mario is dead
i heard this joke because
i was saying that because you know of me
you know doing some stuff to demo are
you saying this joke because
they took off um they took out the
the 3d collection out of the store at
the end of last month
so people have been saying mario is dead
like nintendo killed mario
because they took out the game that's
why you guys are saying that i heard
that too that's so funny
why did they take out i don't understand
why that was time limited that's such a
good game like
for me like i don't have i used to have
a gamecube but i don't have it anymore
and all those other games like for
example for the wii i didn't i don't i
don't have a wii anymore so
for me personally that was a really good
game collection
they should have kept it i think even in
the future a lot of people would have
bought that
i'm glad i bought it early enough
huh i don't get it i'm gonna get it
huh um well well but
but but games like animal crossing
are one of or are their number one
best-selling game and that one is not
limited so
um it's not like you have to make it
limited so that you will get more sales
whatever
anyway p one two three four i'm done
amazing for the model attention thank
you vegans to rise up woohoo i'm not a
vegan but
i of course can't be only sounds vegan
chicken yup yup yup yup
and downstairs danke shin thank you for
the pinkie is it weird when people tell
me
uh your mama joke i get mad because they
call you and my other mother
no that's not weird thank you for
feeling like that that's very sweet of
you
i love you thank you
if they call you mama fat show them a
picture of me and be like
what which part of that looks fat to you
huh huh
huh say it to her face send her a super
chat or whatever
tell her fat tell her she's fat directly
while looking at that sexy body
challenge that
[Music]
oh
oh you want you want you want waffy frog
where's my easy
okay the cut out for the feathers
doesn't work because i don't have the
feathers anymore but
it could work if you use it for the hair
but whatever
so
i'm wrong
i also have a this one ah
i see i see i see that's how i did it
hope you're happy ggs frog our good
girl sexy frog bonsai
we have a new a new phrase good girl
sexy
thank you glad you're happy with that
yay i'm frog
mobius thank you
thank you thank you
my my throat is starting to hurt uh
mario's tunnel of a doom i'm not dead
i'm lurking
i'm i'm i'm not dead i'm lurking in the
kv series chat to me against me to love
it
thank you thank you
thank you mario ah
why are you why are you dead why are you
not dead
please leave me alone
ah stuff some meatballs in your
throat and then we'll see what happens
do you say you're not fat while your
waist looks smarter than your shoulders
now
shut up
[Music]
this is the end i think i've read all
the super tattoos
cool i'll go prepare the rest of uh
what i need to prepare for her attack uh
for me it's basically on the same day
but you guys might want to sleep before
i don't know whatever
i know when i
eventually because it starts for me at
one o'clock
i think but we will have
akirozin senpai to the uh today
tomorrow and hello talk i'll make the
reservation soon
very soon and really looking forward to
hearing a lot from her because she also
has like honestly when i was researching
i mean i already knew about a bunch of
these things but i realized once again
how
how much of a like perfect entertainer
she is she has so many skills
she has so many charms
her songs are dope she's really amazing
yeah
and she also went through some rough
times as well
and it's going to be interesting to talk
to her and hear those stories and
some background stories as well
[Music]
it will be very early in the morning for
japanese bros and for
aki senpai but yeah i'm looking forward
to talking to her i also heard that
she's like
she has a very healthy lifestyle and
stuff i want to talk about that too
because that that's really
interesting to me because i feel like
most whole life members
have a really unhealthy lifestyle like
staying up late doing no sports at all
and but like i kissed if i understood
correctly someone told me she
she uh streams with a with a with a with
a stand-up desk like she has
she's standing up uh uh how do you call
that
i don't know if that's true someone told
me that in twit on the twitter replies
she's and she likes to go camping and
all that kind of stuff it's really
interesting
a standing desk yeah i don't know if
that's true
one person wrote that she's using a
standing desk i don't know if that's
that still applies but it's very
interesting
like what she's so fit celery man
thank you for the super chat can't wait
for the hotel tomorrow morning
thank you i'll do my best
okay okay okay thank you guys for
watching
and in german we say auf wiedersehen
see you later
hope you had fun i had fun
bye
[Music]