[Music]
n
ding
[Music]
ch
ding
D do do do
[Music]
oh
so many
members thank
you thank you
[Music]
membership
[Applause]
[Music]
he
hello
[Music]
k k get it
I am in a good
mood for now for
now how about you
guys how's it
[Music]
going finally finally we play we played
the Diablo 2
resurrected about one week late but
still I mean I tried it's not like I
didn't try last
time H thank
you what server I don't even know so the
thing is I don't know how the online
mode works on Diablo I but for me
preferably I would que qu Noir I would
like to play alone uh for now until I
don't I don't want to play with randos
I'm so sorry I want to it doesn't matter
whatever right there's like if I
understand correctly you can like open
up a
Lobby and
uh hide the top right game and oh I did
you mean the thing that shows up uh on
the map see I I did deactivate that in
the settings will I be fine
then I only want to play online with
like you know the girls and maybe my
mommy uh yeah online it's just single
player game but you can invite people do
I understand that
correctly I tried playing I don't even
have to open up a
Lobby I don't even have to open up a
Lobby I can just play uh normally but I
just have to have the character on
online uh so that I will be able to have
a Lo have a Lobby later
yeah maybe brother
toy but he's busy right now with Tales
of arise I think cuz I gave him a I gave
him a
code the ads are so long what what ads
you mean this right now you think this
is an ad this is not an ad this stream
is not
sponsored uh what do you mean are there
ads in the
game there shouldn't be any ads in the
game
oh all the YouTube ads you thought I
thought you meant me I'm I'm the end
thought you meant like get into the game
for God's sake stop talking kada kiata
with ch kada with q or tiata so I was
thinking we played in Amazon last time
because sorceress and assassin just were
not available anyway um but I personally
I really like the Amazon oh why am I
there we go I personally like the Amazon
on because um I am able to uh do close
distance comat and
uh uh uh not close distance
combat both of them and I like that
although it sometimes it was a bit
stressful to switch
around now with assassin I assume that
it's mostly close
combat oh yeah Mele and ranged yeah
I thought Amazon Amazon is pretty
versatile yeah and for sorceress I
assume it's she looks hot though I
assume it's uh only uh only ranged
combat assassin is tricky is that so I
think sorceress could be a lot of fun
but I also when I think about the future
I think about you know maybe cie playing
this game and I feel like she might go
for sorcerer or I feel like she might
even go for barbarian or Necromancer she
probably doesn't care for the looks W
she definitely likes that I mean she
doesn't care for the looks as in she
doesn't care whether or not she plays a
woman or a guy oh if she she has to go
for the Necromancer summoning Undead
minions and cursing his enemies are if
cie doesn't go for the Necromancer then
I don't know who she is
anymore yeah I'm I'm expecting Cali to
give this game a try I I know she wants
to so all right then she probably
wouldn't even go for the Sorceress I
wonder what ban Senpai would go for what
did she what did ban Senpai go for in in
the b in the alpha does anyone know cuz
she played it in the alpha uh the thing
is though that in the alpha there wasn't
there wasn't endless choice she couldn't
go for all of them so who knows she
played the
Sorceress
oh I wonder if she would still go for
sorceress L me play today
what wait did B Senai already play uh
the official version now Lamy plate what
the hell what did Lamy play
Diablo a ly is going to play tomorrow
okay L me played earlier which one is it
l me plays in 21 which one is it
some of you guys live in the future and
some of you live in the past maybe L we
did play today which which no no let me
place
[Laughter]
tomorrow why why are some people so
certain trting girl slaming why are some
people so certain that she already
played and some people are so certain
that she's playing in the
future did you guys have like a vision
from the future are you able to look
into the future is that it
could have played Diablo 3 wait there is
no Diablo free
right I'm a mess what is going
on what's going on so you can't tell me
what what class Lamy chose because she
didn't play yet right is that
correct
uh wait Diablo free exists
really oh wait really
me let me look it up wait really I mean
could be Diablo 3 Diablo
3 oh it does exist oh it came out
oh was it good
was it good wait I think I think I
remember
there wait a
second the app
three shouldn't have asked that question
well nothing nothing can beat Diablo I
so we are playing Diablo 2
resurrected all right now um I think I
personally I would like ban to play the
bararan I think or or drew
it but but I feel like she's more like
the type that that would play a tank I
think Bon is a tank she has to be a
tank um and Ramy I think Ramy would go
for the
Sorceress
yeah yeah and then Cy will play The
Necromancer and then I know I know know
of some other people or one more person
who wants to play the game and I think
she would actually suit the Assassin but
these are all my fantasies and I don't
know if they will really come uh become
reality are you the he normally I would
play the Healer but wait Diablo doesn't
even have healers does it so we'll play
the I think we'll just go for the Amazon
again if that's okay I like your fancy
thank you pick what you want inste no I
mean I do want the on it would be a
perfect balance if everyone else would
go for what I just
said yeah I I was just kind of hoping to
go for something else so that it
wouldn't be so repetitive because we did
play the closed Alpha um as an Amazon we
already finished act one and now I have
to redo all of that but I I like the
beginning of the game it's very
nostalgic it's the only part that I
really ever have seen much so um I guess
are you okay with it seeing it again
with the same
character are you okay with that are you
guys okay with
that yes yes yes okay I think when I was
younger I did give Sorcerers a try um
but I think nowadays my current fighting
style fits the Amazon better so let's
go let's go good day good day should I
stay a while and listen oh greetings
stranger I'm not surprised to see your
kind here many adventurers have traveled
this way since the recent troubles began
no doubt you've heard about the tragedy
that befell the town of Tristram I heard
heard Diablo the Lord Of Terror walks
the world again what that for
that but a Dark Wanderer did travel this
route a few weeks ago it was headed east
to the mountain pass guarded by the
Rogue
Monastery maybe it's nothing but evil
seems to have trailed in his wake you
see shortly after The Wanderer went
through the monastery's gates to the
pass were closed and strange creatures
began ravaging the countryside your head
dude until it's safer outside the camp
and the gates are reopen I'll remain
here with my Caravan
Caravan I love you Caravan the shadow
that fell over Tristram consumes us all
if you're still alive then I'll take you
Al I'm a phoenix I'll never die you
should talk to aara too she seem to be
the leader of this Camp maybe she can
tell you more all right tell me more
tell me more how do I run again not here
what do you mean not here what is right
click all right click is attack right I
got to get used to this again this is a
click can I run with w
no all right okay yeah this is a move by
clicking aara you're in the same spot as
last time I feel I am a Cara a priestess
of The Sisterhood of the sightless eye
oh dear did I stap that eye traveler to
our to run afraid I can offer you but
poor shelter Within These rickety walls
it's pretty nice here you got a cow can
I eat it our ancient Sisterhood has
fallen under a strange curse indeed it
has Mighty Citadel from which we have
guarded the gates to the east for
Generations been corrupted by the evil
just in the beginning I want to listen
to it I still can't believe it but she
turned many of our sister Rogues someone
stop the rain please it's so noisy from
our ancestral home now the last
Defenders Of The Sisterhood are either
dead or scattered throughout the
Wilderness oh dear I implore you Strang
Sisterhood please help us find a way to
lift this terrible of course of course
and we will pledge our loyalty to you
for all time all time that sounds good
to me there is a place of great evil in
the wilderness oh where is ita's Rogue
Scouts have informed me do I have to
fight that beach again and
dares beyond the gra I was I was
panicking so much last time I remember
but for an attack against our do well
right does anyone remember did I do well
or is that just me the dark Labyrinth
and Destroy messing up my own memories I
did well last time great eye watch over
you man the great eye watch over you
wait what does that remind me of what
does that saying remind me
of um under his eye from the handmaid's
tail I I downed her rabit easily nice no
it actually does I mean sour run show
for sure that I watching but but
actually reminds me of uh something
else okay wait so what are we doing
anyone else who wants to talk to
me uh this actually I know that these
maps are random right the Caravans are
aligned randomly chicken oh it's
partying it's
like so excited and I just can't hide it
he's looking forward to being fr
hi
a I know I know I know I know I know I
want to become a nugget
C all right uh what do I have to
activate this there you go I don't know
if it was already activated do we just
go
fighting how do I open inventory again
there you go I have I need to get into
this again it's it's surprisingly it
feels like it wasn't that long ago go
cuz time passes so quickly but at the
same time I feel like it's been a
million years cuz now I shall Purge this
land of the Shadow yes Purge it girl uh
I don't remember how to do things at all
how do I attack red click right how do I
how do I do
anything how I can't run anymore oh
there you go where am I going how do I
turn on the mini map so many
questions I have so many they they
previously said just follow the path I
remember that left click is also
attacked oh dear wait I don't have a
weapon give me a weapon also why do you
not pay that pick that up uh on your own
oh my God bare fist let's go my nail
just
broke W oh I pressed the um uh by
accident got rid of it huh all
right attack stop
stop is there no I I know that she
collects money automatically what about
about
[Applause]
items oh what was that again armor
Shrine give
[Music]
me me me oh this is so cool I love I
told you to Auto collect the money are
you stupid
I love this press out to highlight items
aha out out out there you
go all right I'm just having fun
stabbing monsters but I should probably
go somewhere what's I should look in my
quest
log what does my quest log say look for
the den in the wilderness outside the
rose cam is it so this place looks
exactly like last time but
it's it's supposed to be random random
Maps right how do I look at my map oh
that's not it uh undo undo undo how do I
look at my
map how do I look at the map oh that's
not it either oh but that's that's
something tab oh bring up the Auto map
uh toggle between oh yeah right uhuh
uhhuh F to zoom the game camera in what
I can what is hostile I can
[Music]
zoom
enhance enhance I think I was able to do
that last time too oh there we go okay
let's go that
way oh I love playing this right now
pick up the
[Music]
money oh this is all I want to do all I
just want I went past it the
Cave the
Cave the C is where I need to
go I wasn't sure what what the den
is what what
run
[Music]
run God she's
slow alt now alt alt why
stamina run out
yeah okay I'm I'm just going to wait for
my
stamina ah the den oh it does say den of
the evil I hear foul creatures
about kill all the monsters in
the oh I would gladly do
that I will do that thank you you didn't
even have to tell me to do
that level
up and what are we what are we stting on
what are we what are we going to do
dexterity yeah right
deck all on deck for
now
uh all
right Javelin and spear passive bow and
crossbow jab attacks with a series of
Rapid FR well we want that of course
right for now okay oh yeah that's right
you can only really select two skills or
a normal attack and a skill right that
was that was it that's the thing
crossbow is better that's and bit R most
important okay
okay Dax and v i will St on Dax and VD I
don't want to just St on one thing
no weak as hell one hit oh there's a big
big
monkey
ah oh we got to kill him first kill him
first kill him
first okay
nice oo he looks so fluffy he looks so
soft like his his fur is so
shiny do I have to kill Bales too I
can't I don't think I can oh we have a
we have a
club all
right monkey a floofy
boy this is beautiful I love playing
this game so much already I just
realized my screen is not perfectly
balanced as things should
be just realized that let me fix that
can I even fix that
oh I love the
atmosphere there we go it's more
supposed to be like that all
right
uh's not B they have a similar name I
don't even know who the hell that
is okay I think in this area we're done
let's go up everyone keeps on talking
about B I don't remember who that is I
only remember and darel is B like the
last
bus oh oh wait I need a Mana Shrine
please uh he's bow Lord of destruction
oh nothing here so quiet where all you
friends dude where are they well let me
switch
this
ooh ooh
Act five boss oh okay no more spoilers
necessary Now kill
die don't run you can't run from your
destiny clicking on the enemy sometimes
really is difficult isn't
it oh did you guys miss me I didn't oh
my God there's a lot going on here here
did you guys miss me yesterday I uh what
did I just activate holy yesterday
I wasn't die kill
him yesterday I wasn't online after all
I I had my day off kill him first kill
him
first oh my God I am about to
die no no all under
control hold shift for
what oh
oh we got a
bow I can use that did you guys miss me
yes thank
you I had a good day yesterday though oh
wait I'm running faster
noise bolts taking
that all right we're zooming shift full
shift makes you attack while standing
ah wait
what
what I don't wait where's the
difference ah I can ah like even if
there's okay okay I think I get
it ah ah okay okay okay okay to avoid
running
aha
oh
oh no no no you little me minions they
all need to die oh Mana potion bolts I
can't carry anymore yes I missed you
saying that so much nice to hear that
again I missed that that's such such a
nostalgic good
memory why is he
blue what the is going on here why
are they not dying
oh finally he was just very strong he
was buff I can't carry anymore you
going to carry that otherwise I'm going
to quit the game I'm going to make you
carry it let's see oh that's it I'm done
perhaps now the sisters will trust me I
cleared it will they trust me let's see
throwing knife
I inventory okay let's see eat that
eat that
uh oh wait uh a
cap can I wear that I use this yet Bo
unident oh yeah I got to identify thing
oh I could identify it
now shall
we plus one to energy well that's worse
than what I have re you
cap of
energy Lea
gloves that's something I want to use
press W equip the B oh
yeah o uh yes yes now I can
shoot ah and then I keep on Switching oh
yeah right I got to get used to that
let's get those potions why is it
picking it out cuz I have the inventory
open pick it up like this and M which
one is makes more
money all
right uh yeah we're going to do jab and
bow combination sounds good doesn't it
are you okay
buddy cracked dagger I'll take that all
right new stats decks vit decks
done easy new skill bow oh fire arrow
yes so if I switch then I can change
this to that all
right I feel
it it's all coming back to me of course
I'm going for the fire what choice do I
have I don't have a plan for my stats
I'm just going to be statting on deck
and
V uh which should be fine should be good
good H F1 HT
key what F1 to f8 what not right now it
doesn't do anything let me out can I
Port out of here
yes let's go I'm back need some Str to
oh okay Str
strength I'll put a little bit on
strength as well then aara wait not you
oh yeah here hello you have cleansed the
den of evil I did it you earned my trust
F1 on the restore my faith and Humanity
your reward is training in the skill of
your
choice thank
you huh what you gave me another skill
point is that
it I'll take another one then thank you
the order welcomes you
H wait what am I doing now got I talk to
the dude oh
hello I never expected to see an Amazon
in these lands you're very to have come
here many of my fellow sisters have
fallen under some dark spell and if
you're not careful you may fall prey to
it as well Brave is my second
name my rogue Scouts just reported an
abomination in the monastery graveyard
apparently and is not content to take
only our living blood Raven one of our
finest captains in the battle against
Diablo atth of first to be corrupted by
andariel now you'll find her in the
monastery graveyard raising our dead as
zombies cannot abide this defilement I
killed her before why is she alive again
you will help us destroy her all right I
have no choice
oh I have no
choice uh the T is done quest number two
look for the blood Raven in the burial
grounds next to the cold Plains you
speak in riddles to me Raven what do you
mean bual burial grounds that's a nice
fire
mate look at that
wow
wow not in town what do you mean not in
town you need a hotel room or what
should we put anything in it wait I want
to sell I want to sell not here yo Char
I'm charie the blacksmith here in Camp
it's good to see some strong adventurers
around here it's good to see you too
many of our sisters fought bravely
against Diablo when he first attacked
the town of Trish wow they came back to
his true veterans bearing some really
powerful items seems like their victory
was shortlived though them are now
corrupted by don't worry I'll take care
of that and then I'll take care of you
and your
chickens and Tra okay we'll
sell um this and this and we don't need
the throw knife
right and this and this and this all of
it all I want is
javelins and bows and arrows 350 oh oh
oh
oh o oh oh oh I'll keep that I'll keep
that I think I think that's all I want
should we buy some
armor identify them to ah yeah right
yeah right good day to you p a good day
sir I'm g a good day mate and I can
already tell that I'll be your best
friend in this for not sure about that a
spare weapon some gold a small gem is
all I want in exchange for the equipment
you'll need on whatever Quest you might
undertake n n n don't all of my items
are guaranteed for life and come with a
two-day warranty wait two-day warranty I
don't remember that two 2day warranty
Greetings oh wait no no no show me what
you
got
uh should we buy
something
could buy this one no wait I can't I
don't have enough money
byebye I'm off to my next mission God
there's so many
chickens let's
see where do we go next this looks
exactly like the map I had during the
alpha got a Bel for more potions oh okay
maybe next
time it's okay we're going to be fine
you're looking gorgeous as oh wow thank
you I look the same every day though
don't
I does that mean I look gorgeous every
day wait where's your
master you don't have a
master
flirt where's your
master cracked sash wait does that count
as the belt experience
Shrine my experience what does that mean
do I get more experience now to have an
experience
boost burn zombies burn fire was very
effective bonus exp
nice ooh skill what does that
do what does that do should I act wa
will it uh cancel the EXP boost cuz then
I don't want
it got no oh almost took it don't
replace
okay smart I didn't do
[Music]
it oh you're welcome hope you're having
a lovely birthday oh I see your house
Mana man
man there you go enjoy your
Mana W level up right that's what just
happened right yeah level up I'm level
three now I
think
chest nothing's inside
nothing
man I'm so curious I love exploring I
need to go into the house though let's
go into the
house
oh oh you don't have a master either
small charm
hello how do these work again ah just in
the inv just keep them in ah ah I should
have bought uh the Scrolls God damn it
it did automatically
uh uh do the sash equip the sash though
which is good
what are the purple ones for again for
stamina no for the oh life and
man now
hold buy some Scrolls shift click on the
potions a ah to put them in there
quicker it's all right it's all right
all right let's see what's in
here oh yeah baby bulls alist
y
are there items that come out of chests
random too since the maps are random as
well by scroll book yeah yeah yeah yeah
I need that oh hello who are you beware
Beyond lies mortal danger for the likes
of you should I go
here is this where I need to go oh oh
entering oh yeah cold
ples
activate oh nice now we have the portal
burn
W the dark Hunters oh
no oh no what the
no kill him kill
him don't run
away let's kill him with the
javelin okay what do we have
arrows level armor ooh
Chate is it better
socketed oh 6
16 get out of here I need a key I am the
key key
an am I not good
enough oh I cornered them Warrior
strategy that you can learn from me
Corner your enemies where is this man yo
thank you wait that's so
little you for
real ah my
stash wait I got a stash Town
portal no need to buy things just pick
up everything you can find uh I should
take a look at my
skills
um I've one one skill Choice should I do
magic Arrow or should
I do do another well I did it it's too
late oh I like the effect when they die
how like their soul leaves their
body very cool left or
right oh my
God so many
enemies I
see that's a
[Music]
sapphire money arrows I'll take
that o or made no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no that's it's not
fair I'm supposed to be the only one
with a rival skill all
right
stamina all
right loot Goblin are you calling me
loot
Goblin in a is that in a bad way or in a
good
way nice can I wear that no right I'm
amet
nice in a bad way then don't call me
that only in a good
way oh what did I find
oh the cave wait should I go
here no I need to find the blood Raven
in the burial grounds next to the cold
PL this is an extra
cave that you can use if you want
to
should
I a side dungeon all right now hold on
in that's that's nice of them to
offer
[Music]
hello just filling out my map don't mind
me nothing in
there looking ooh a dead
one where is you
here uh
uh I feel like yeah I should have
followed the path
right I'm so off path right
now it means you loot so much that you
never leave any for your team oh oh that
reminds me of you know when playing mm
RPGs when people vote on like the rare
items when they say like yeah uh like in
some games in some M RPGs you get the
option to vote for it and then it um
everyone who voted for it has a chance
on getting the item and then there's
always those trolls who vote for
everything even though they don't really
need it and even though it's not for
their
class but they don't give a
they don't give a
they roll for literally anything
ninja
looters um
I I play the problem is I played a game
where an mm RPG where you can have more
than just one
class and uh obviously like you you want
to you know you want something for your
main class but you maybe also want
something nice for your sub class why
the hell not what's wrong with that
maybe I was maybe I was the one that I
just complain n nah nah no
way nah
[Applause]
or or or even in games that where you
only can play one um character even in
those
games you can have like a second
character so you're like a that's for my
that's for my sub character my second
character uh-huh that's for my second
character I have that other one right
yeah I need something for my second
character forgive
me you understand don't you not enough
Mana yeah I will totally use that item I
will not sell it no no no no no
no there's a portal ah no go
oh ah wait that's a is a well for oh
yeah give me that yummy yummy
Mana I am overburdened overburdened with
what the game has just begun are you
telling me this is already too much for
you stamina
Shrine not enough Mana God damn
it oh I I know she means the lot I know
I know where did you guys see a
portal I'm totally off off oh
D and drink your Mana ah
[Music]
stop who wants gorilla for dinner huh I
can't carry anymore I can't carry
anymore no you can of course you can I
don't take
excuses
uh
uh yes Can I stack
no should I go home once this was the
thing like I had to learn to accept
during the when I played the Alp I had
to learn to accept that it's okay to go
home in the middle of a journey of a
town portal and just to sell stuff I
need to buy the freaking book oh my
God let me just killed the
an shipped Emerald I picked it up that's
that's all
right okay I'm going to go home
once home as and I'm going to go back to
the
[Music]
Caravan I am over so
many hi doesn't run away from a
fight what is that I can't carry
anymore
I I will bring that key with me no
matter what I am
overburdened I can't carry the ah who's
doing
that who's doing
that wait shut the no I'm out of here
One Moment One Moment One
no no I just want to quiet place where I
can place my
portal well good that they can't use my
portals right hello I need a book not
here of course you're
here uh selling this selling the scepter
selling this selling
the
shoes I can't I can't
use this yet because un
unidentified is that
why should I sell
the dexterity should I sell
it buy
book buy second
book Emir looks good
right keep all oh yeah yeah yeah I think
you guys told me that before
too what about that wo 1,200 what about
these should I I should I should
identify I should identify I should
identify
yes wait I need to get out of the
shopping
window wait what H oh that's the wrong
one where's my I ah here no oh it went
in here ah
plus two dexterity
[Music]
nice let five to
life
[Music]
um heal stamina plus 10% ooh baby
looking
good
okay to
do we sell this one
do we sell the small charm of
life not worth a lot of money s okay
then we keep this one for
now equip oh oh oh I thought I just
needed the needed it to be in my
inventory all right all right all right
uh now these I put into my secret
stash and this go in here this goes in
here nice looking looking good again in
my
inventory maybe we don't need that
many okay but how many do I have inside
quantity one we need more identification
Scrolls can I buy more than one at once
no okay for now this looks good to me
yeah I'll I'll put the gems in my
[Music]
chest okay let's go
back shift buy to fill ah oh okay next
time next time hello I'm back bambooo
were you waiting for me than
you how kind of
you oh no oh no no no
Reviving
y I feel more skillful but I also feel
like I'm completely off path so maybe I
shouldn't really be going this
way should I go up
there need
coconut
stay while listen wait Stony field I
don't need to go to to the Stony field
bural is the area called burial
grounds is there actually an area that's
called
[Music]
that okay well then
ouch let's go that way
maybe
yeah up up oh no my
stamina my
stamina you you coward you always hide
behind your
daddy but you can't run from Mommy
Ki unless when I'm out of
stamina low quality
scepter
I think this might be the right
direction are you guys playing Diablo I
resurrected
2 anyone in the chat playing it as
well yes yes oh a lot of you
guys nice playing Necromancer ooh necrom
is very very
[Music]
fancy
nothing still have my original copy oh
you're playing as a paladin
oh that's
cool I just keep on infiltrating all
these enemy
areas
cuz I can't stop
[Music]
myself
die oh my God oh my God oh my
Gody bu oh that was like a like like a
strong
[Music]
dude okay now now it's
quiet or is
it oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God oh my
God W
easy was that is that considered like a
mini boss not really a mini mini
boss mini mini mini baby
boss ah
Elite mob I I I guess that's probably
the word for
it
money all
right
now we should try to get back on track
where did I come from from below
right follow the path
kada it might be difficult but are these
is this
better no time to look at
[Music]
anything go left yes
yes how does it feel to be defeated by
your own element huh
buddy
I'm glad that everything seems stable
now but I don't want to jinx
it not enough
Mana but looks like looks like
everything's
[Music]
stable too many
potions let's drink some Mana
potion
meeting my fans these are not my fans my
fans are much cuter than this
it it's a
masser yeah you guys are much cter I
mean just look at yourself look into the
mirror and we've just watched a movie
about you guys don't you did you already
forget what you look like
oh those chicken brains really difficult
to handle those chicken brains
sometimes baral
grounds okay can I have one quiet moment
kill blood Raven
easy I don't know what to skill
on
impale should I
do repair my gear also a good idea we
should maybe go for go
uh go back first pass fire
arrow passives are good wait what ah ah
inner
sight attacks ooh I want
that okay I'm happy with that choice
critical always
good critical always something to uh use
let's see if we can find the Portal
first and then
go oh oh it's that place ah oh I didn't
die wait is that this place where I was
like where I died yeah yeah I think it
is
didn't I die
here this was kind of more difficult
than andariel I I think I remember it
that way there is no portal here you
have to use this SC okay
[Music]
okay I need I need
Mana yeah this looks tough dead beats
listen up
give me all you got dead
beats okay well we have a lot of in
our inventory anyway
so let's
go that beats listen up it's what you
want me coming literally in the night
for you
yes wait you can't repair can you we go
to the blacksmith for
that
oh sorry to disturb you
Mrs wait should I identify that could
that be
[Music]
better defense 10 16
oh
uh-huh free
free uhhuh
sash
uh just going to
switch that out yeah
here let talk to her talk to
her s s s s
s keep the key we still got a lot of
arrows so that's
good and yeah repair thank you
bon are we ready to
go
I think we
are open the portal before you f you
mean so that I can escape
quickly oh or do you mean if I die cuz I
spawn in the main um cuz I spawn in the
main main main thingy so that I can go
go here ah okay okay but both makes
sense both makes
[Music]
sense
there's a way to change the skill points
again later right not the skill points
but the the character stats the stat
points can I can I redo that later I
think I think you guys said there was a
way to do that yes okay good ah C I'm so
scared if only this game was brighter
why is it so dark it's so scary I don't
want to go
inside I don't want to go
inside full eliminating full eliminating
potion what I don't want to go inside
wait where's my portal did I open a
portal I don't think I did I should open
a portal right next to the door is this
door open oh god oh it's not
open was that
[Music]
open is this
open yes it is okay is that him no okay
open portal there we
go
uh wait that is it that is
him don't destroy me
please kill kill kill kill kill kill
kill kill kill kill not enough
Mana what you mean not enough
Mana wait I have to I have to pick up my
my my items right
we're off to a great
start oh at least we have the portal I
remember last time I didn't have the
portal right away HH wait no no this is
not fair this is not fair let me go get
my
things I have to like I have to pick it
all up it doesn't pick it up
automatically right and then I have to
equip it that's like not fair join my
Army wait where is my things where are
my things I don't see them H oh no she
did pick them up automatically okay okay
okay okay wait I'm not ready wait no no
no I'm not ready I'm not ready I'm not
move move move
move I'm not ready I'm not
ready what did she say join my what I
need more Mana thingies
does does she have full or he does he
have full HP
again oh my god let's
go my Army will
destroy the
give me potions holy
why am I so
weak
bye oh freak I have no money I don't
want to sell you
Dad can I buy now no I bought the wrong
[Laughter]
one one
more
[Music]
yeah is it good to to lure them all out
first join my Army no no no not joining
your army not joining your army not
joining your army wait I need a moment
to put my shield together put don't
stand still okay okay okay okay okay
okay oh I lared them all out it's so
smart it's so smart it's so smart but I
have no healing
[Music]
things
I have no
healing potions but he's almost
not enough Mana oh we'll see about
that oh I almost got him he's running
away from
me no no no no no no no oh oh the SCU is
real the scope is real I'm winning I'm
winning I'm winning I'm winning I'm
winning oh
slow I'm slow poke oh oh ah Kiana is
under control Kiana is under
control I'm dying okay I have no potions
oh no I do I do I do I do wait I can't
click on it I have to run I have to
run
hello uh nice to come from you to come
to see
me stop ring my
[Applause]
yes yes yes yes yes
yes last
one you stop running stop
running where is
he he's so
hyperactive wa we almost got him he like
he knows he can't win this
even though I have no no health potions
left he's
panicking
P
[Music]
baby rest in peace sister rest in peace
sister why you dropped crap only is that
all you
got yeah a with no health potions
left oh y anything here that you're
hiding no so
boring let's kill
them not enough
Mana
[Music]
nice I I think I got a good feeling for
this
now and I'm I'm I'm I haven't died yo
get the hell out of
here oh wait oh there's a there's
a there's a secret extra dungeon here
but I'm not quite in the condition to go
there I'll take this to
sell and I'll be on my
way where's my
portal
what didn't I put a portal
here do I disappear after
well I didn't open one this time oh I'm
stupid did I really not do
that all right oh thank God I didn't
die can I have healing from someone good
day Casia please I can hardly believe
that you've defeated blood Raven wait I
got I got CL friend welcome tortured
Spirit remains banished
forever you have earned my respect thank
you and the allegiance of the Rogues I
have placed several of my Warriors at
your disposal is she really your best
she's like running away already she's
not concentrated
enough okay I thank you that we are
facing an evil difficult to comprehend
let alone compat there is only one Herod
Sage schooled in the most Arcane history
and lore who could advise us his name is
deer K Deer K go to Tristram and find
him my friend our BFF I pray that he
still lives go to Tristram where was
twistr
again I don't know where that is but
I'll go
there
I'll buy this and
this
and this and
I need some potions at
least huh where are they going ah up
here okay okay I think I'll pick up a
lot on my way there so I don't I'm not
going to buy anymore uh three and seven
how did I how do I buy how do I fill
them up again
shift
oh wait no no no how do I fill it all up
oh I could have given it to my Ally oh
oopsy shift and right
click ah now I ran out of money God damn
it ah but hey I can sell you this AER
o uh what that was so
cheap oh
no all right we'll find better items for
my friend not in town we'll find better
items here take
this and yeah should I
repair if I have enough money charie
please can you give me like a discount
friend
[Music]
discount okay we are now going
to that feels so
good go for the under ground passage to
the Darkwood search for the tree of Inus
and recover the
scroll underground we're going under
ground okay doco oh girl don't don't get
distracted follow
me underground underground
Doo dark wood
doo
doco do there's nothing else down here
is there does it stop there is it all
fenced in oh no maybe not is
it yeah know it is it all it's all
fenced in I wasted my stamina on
that the place to the north
no the area is it is it in the direction
where I went
first where where I went wrong
first I where did am Amor Anor where did
she
go there's another way from cold ples
[Music]
okay wait how do
I entering cold ples okay so we go we
walk a little bit where the hell is
Anna good
where is
she what do I do I'm not going to run
back to pick her up what the hell what
the hell is her
issue follow the road okay Ah that's my
problem I I never follow the
road will she teleport to
me
when oh man and when you play online
with a group of people does the game
difficulty adjust to how many people you
playing with or or are you basically
overpowered when you play with
friends which way do we
go it it does adjust oh oh that's uh
that's good and at the same time
[Laughter]
[Music]
bad all right are we going this
way the Stony field was this where I
need to go Stony field doesn't say
so we get more exp
oh enemies get harder oh
n all right let's look for a portal here
ah this place I
remember oh wait this would be nice to
have my ally with me what the what
the
oh Oho you I don't want to die here
alone
no no hell no oh hell no oh hell
no I'm out of
here where is
she there she is where the hell
did you go why did you leave keep me
[Laughter]
hanging
my not in to she didn't even die she's
going to probably die quickly but um
well um I feel like I have
to I ran right into it
[Music]
you invest on it so you won't die easily
all right is the girl coming with oh
holy
ah no no no no
I left I left
town 120 why am I so
broke why am I so broke also I used up
my Mana potion I wanted to press on
health potion no no
no I'm so
broke
oh
oh my I have to pick up my is
there something cool here no
oh what where's my body where's
my oh there's a there's an overpowered
mini boss there I don't like seeing that
yeah holy they're following me oh
yes yes it's exactly what I needed right
now oh please give me
something no
stamina a shrine let's
go
oh don't pick up stuff I have
to
no give me give
me
oh wait let's hit them drop me some good
item please drop me
something oh drop me
potions oh
hello oh they make good noises when
they're killed I don't need the
Strangling gas
potions 22
gold oh 12
gold it was a cursed chest I see I see I
see how it
[Music]
is all right all
right we're just trying to get we're try
just trying to
survive
uh what is this
maze did someone try to build a maze
here
ew
disgusting can I kill
it
oh I can oh this is where all those
flying monsters come
out or he might drop something good no
he dropped
[Music]
nothing okay well go pick up your body
yeah but there's chaos
there oh there's a
well don't really need
it why is there never anything in these
chests did someone come here before me
is is old
kiata has she been here
before Oh remember that way I'll try
it's on my map at least
should I pick up my body then quickly
report uh teleport back sell some things
hi rehire my
help and yeah then come back where's my
body where's my body where's my body
where's my body where's my body where's
my body where's my body where's my
wasn't it somewhere here is that
me I can't
even
I'm getting over here real good
right
now I I got
Stu what am I supposed to
[Music]
do we have a problem I don't remember
being this stuck in the
alpha
I was like overloaded with items I
think okay got to be quick here got to
be quick pick up the body click on the
Blue Book pick up the body click on the
Blue Book pick up the body I wish there
was a shortcut for that there's no
shortcut is
[Music]
there oh my
God pick up the body click on the blue
book no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
a no no what if I drop a second body is
the first body still there no no please
no no I beg
you not
here I can shortcut it oh really do you
mean see at least I got my
heel this was my
plan I know I'm so close and maybe they
won't notice me if I suddenly go for the
portal
[Music]
now
my mom is probably laughing her ass off
she said she'll be watching the
stream she said she'll be watching she's
probably laughing us I need some snacks
I'm going crazy I'm hungry I'll be right
back need some snacks I'm mad I need a
Snickers
[Music]
that is not a
sneakers
[Music]
what do I
do what do I
do I feel so
helpless the Bonnie returns to town if I
quit
is there any disadvantage to
that I lose my gold
[Music]
oh my map too
what every time I log in and log out the
map is gone what the hell
no should I sell something in my
stash how do I have these
things is that is that my body's
things okay
um let's sell let's sell one of
these and then get some more um healing
potions and then don't go I'm not going
to go
directly
to the body and the
enemy not
immediately I'm going to try
to get some more potions and stuff
although I feel like normally if I if if
everything would was like if I had more
potions I would have been fine just back
then m
which one should I sell which one is the
worst you're a bit too low level really
the green potions are they really not
worth that
much sorry guys I I'm really hungry I
need to eat some you potato chips I got
sour cream and spring onion potato
chips oh w
that is a lot of money that is a lot of
money uh
no mhm
okay maybe one
more for now did you not eat before I
did I
actually Rec recently I can I can teach
you something that people say in
Japanese even though it's
English I have this my boom my boom they
say that in Japanese to anything like
that they're currently very much into
that you are currently um hyped and
stoked and addicted
to H that's my boom my boom and that is
Peaches my my boom is Peaches
peaches are really
nice M my
boom Oh my right clicks yeah that's
right oh or you can do a shortcut like
that
H now you know why paches are
nice there's nothing weird about it
should we go into this little dungeon
there's nothing worried about it because
let's go into the
dungeon the
cave
hello
um so I don't I I love fruit but what I
what I don't like much about fruit is
that many fruits are like either a pain
in the ass to like peel and open up and
all that and cut cut
open um but peaches they're so easy I
learned that they're so easy to cut like
they just fall apart once you like
slice uh into them with a knife yo and
they're so yummy and they're they're so
beak they have lots of Flesh you know
how grapes are so they don't have much
flesh to
them so you put one in your mouth or
cherry even the cherry cherries
especially and it just it just feels so
unsatisfying because you wish you had
more of that
flesh
right you wish you had more but then
there it's annoying because they also
have like 50 or 60% of a cherry is is
the is the core the the the seed the
stupid big thing that you don't
eat yeah not enough Mana it sucks you
can't enjoy it fully when you keep on
being interrupted at the pit you keep on
being interrupted by the
pit N I don't like that so Peach I
realize peaches are super easy to to eat
and to slice and super uh satisfying to
eat because there's a lot of meat to
it
so yes yes that's how it is but
yesterday besides now eating peaches
yesterday I made my lasagna and I wrote
I wrote about it on Twitter a lot of
people were really really surprised uh
about my
choice of how how I was going to make
the
lasagna I don't know why like some
people were like oh yeah that sounds
good but most of the people were like
what
what what how are you so wait can I use
the well one more time how are you guys
so surprised by that cuz I said I'm
going to put
pumpkin
into uh my lasagna how did it turn out
it turned out really good you want to
see a photo I took one and I didn't
upload it on Twitter cuz I wanted it to
be
exclusive it really just looks like a
normal lasagna though but this is the
second time I made the lasagna by myself
and and uh I made it better than last
time I didn't burn it this time I mean
last time it was just
like um for me personally it was a
little bit too dark but you guys said oh
looks nice looks nice looks perfect but
for me personally I didn't want it to be
that
burnt
so H
wait that's the lasagna see that golden
cheesy color
M
yes I actually I was so close to messing
up the bamel sauce the white sauce and
here here's
a here's a a slice of it you can see the
pumpkin like in the front the middle
that's
pumpkin and I think that on the right in
the corner is also pumpkin I just put
like tiny tiny tiny pieces of pumpkin in
there and it mashes really well
with the rest of the like tomatoes and
stuff
mhm and it tasted really
good if you like pumpkin I
mean the pumpkin taste wasn't like that
strong at
all I just kind of wanted to add some
veggies to it and I was originally
thinking I'll add and I went into the
supermarket and I was going to buy
zucchinis but um then I saw that
pumpkins are in season and I saw this
package of already cut freshly cut uh
pumpkin nicely cut into some
pieces and and like already ready to use
so I was like
hm why the hell
not why the hell not pumpkin in lasagna
to me personally I didn't think that
sounded so weird oh yeah y
y
y wait wait I I I don't have a javelin
oh yeah
[Music]
right oh my God oh my God oh my
God what the why is she so
strong why is she so
strong there we
go you they're waiting for
me what that to do again
uh should I try
that I I
can't whatever oh wait can I like
equip one to six
can I like equip that oh wait I do have
crew javelins all
right okay so if I switch here uh I'll
put in the jab again okay let's
go into the
battle no don't revive no where is the
Reviving
guy
ah
oh she can teleport
yo oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh wait wait wait wait
wait no
HP
oh let me take care of these
first oh no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
no
a wait
wait okay uh shipped skull
interesting oh there's a chest and
nothing inside of course nothing
inside N I need health potions why am I
constantly out of health potions
[Music]
now half an hour hour ago I was throwing
them away I can't
heal wait does life uh does HP heal
normally after a while like on its
own if I just oh I could teleport back
oh yeah
right we'll
do
okay we are recovering
slowly on money and Equipment greetings
m is that is that better than what I
have
no
okay so
anyway I made
lasagna
and it turned out really really good I
liked it uh better than last time when
in terms of um how I how I um baked it
in the
oven
that that was better than last time buy
potions oh yeah right oh yeah
right the the
pumpkin it's I think if it fit really
well
mhhhm next time I do want to try lasagna
with zucchini though I think that's a
good
idea oh
sure I think that's really natural KF be
r
oh yeah cuz people keep on asking me for
recipes it's nothing special I just use
the normal lasagna recipe and then I cut
small pieces of pumpkin and put it into
in in there it's nothing special I mean
there are some um there are some
recipes not enough Mana uh
[Applause]
yes there are some recipes specifically
for pumpkin
uh
lasagna not enough Mana
die why are they so
strong and some uh recipes even
apparently have like uh instead of the
tomato sauce pumpkin
sauce really interesting that is
actually a thing
apparently
so I killed the boss of this dungeon
what now are we done
here we done there's still a little path
here Revive Body yes will too
[Music]
soon oh there's still a lot going on
here all right all right I clear this
part even though this has nothing to do
with a quest if I kill them all do I get
some kind of
reward or is it just like for my own
[Music]
satisfaction not enough Mana who tasted
tomato sauce and thought said they can
do better are you doubting that uh
pumpkin lasagna could be good oh hell
yeah level
up no but you gain XP all right yeah we
got to level up y let's get some
vitality
and maybe a little bit of
mana and that all right and a
skill what's that Dodge passive you have
a chance to dodge aele attack when
attacking or standing still does is that
automatic or do I have to press a button
it sounds like it's
automatic
M why
not
okay good because I don't like pressing
buttons any more than this oh wait
there's two
more but wait there's
more are there people who play on Amazon
but don't use the javelin at all and and
just use the the
bow is that a
thing yes I did oh
it's very comfy I like being
ranged B bow Zone oh it sounds like Mia
bosen H I wonder if am would be
interested in playing
Diablo cuz she did play like Skyrim I
don't know the the the the atmosphere is
similar
no I don't know maybe
she doesn't like grind oh man is this
grinding I don't feel like I'm grinding
yet no actually no wait what I'm doing
right now is
grinding I know it's a different genre
but it's a similar
aesthetic m
this dungeon is bigger than I thought it
would be oh there's another
dude he barely moves oh he gave me lots
of
[Music]
potions
yay L lot of
potions oh my
[Music]
God
St thank you what a nice nice
guy I so kind of
him and so much
money
I
no I wanted to run but I was so
slow
no
no I'm going to retrieve my
body oh man sad
[Music]
crunches this one
right do do the enemies respawn when I
re-enter the
dungeon oh God I hope not no go go in
no
no they don't respond
oh
okay I will not leave without my body I
worked so hard on
that m
oh no bat no
problem we'll get
there m m m
m i by the way I
was I
was I saw that again uh while I was
sleeping there was a Minecraft party
going on again and then I woke up and
hey actually during the time when I was
awake of Minecraft party was going on
again of B and and cie and Iris and
there was actually a time where I was
awake but I had to record
something and uh take care of something
so I couldn't I still couldn't oh
God take it take it take it take it oh
my God you
idiot I almost pushing
it oh man
oh I'm
mad give me my
body cold Crown cold
cro I'm barely I'm barely
surviving but at least I made a portal
oh oh that's tough oh that's
tough
no I'm using up
everything what the are you
doing I can't I can't I
can't it's death
inevitable no no no
no
a I don't want to die I don't want to
die I don't want to die
[Laughter]
I no I don't want to I don't want to
leave
though
I used up all my potions
again my
Bo she better she
better oh my God she better drop some
nice
things okay we can we're fine we can buy
things this is
ridiculous this is
ridiculous oh nice stuff not for me
though
4 to 10 4 to
10 it's the same
thing
okay we need
more okay ready to
go find many more food
okay I've come to bar potions again now
let me finish that little grind dungeon
but let me open the portal as
well I uh I don't trust myself anymore
where are
they o
o oh I hate that I hate that what
they're doing there I hate that is that
that b better oh it can be socketed one
to
four well I have nothing to socket
now um mushy
mus oh there you are there you
are
[Applause]
die heal faster heal
faster heal
faster
oh
God why is this so
painful hit and run but when you move so
slow it's quite difficult I ran out of
potions again oh
no oh my
god oh oh there we
go that
hurts there's anti-freeze potions
Yoo once you get that moment where she
doesn't she doesn't like stun
you that's where it's at oh
man thank you chat that was
unnecessarily
painful
M wait this better right
oh defense s
yeah okay is there anything else here no
right this is
it
nice any Hidden
Treasures no wait where's my portal did
I not open a
portal
oh my
god oh I don't want to be
blue
die
okay
so now
hello I think now we can finally try to
go back to a main quest
[Music]
oh was that
unidentified should I have identified
it yeah uh socket the bow I will do I
will
do not
here yeah sorry oops
and let's do uh wait weapons plus 40 to
attack
rating 10 poison damage oh I can put
three in there right one PR damage yo
and attack rating let's put all three of
them in there how does that
work how does that work do I have to go
to the
blacksmith or should I put three times
attack
raing put the golden ah yeah good idea
not
here
uh place it in there
oh
oh nice bow nice bow that's strong can I
take them out as
well don't put the purple oh
is it too late was that a special
one I can't put all maybe I shouldn't
have put all of them in don't worry I
got I got more purple ones we'll find
more oh
e I'll get more
gems
town thank you m okay
that that's I'm way stronger than before
though now should I go for the portal or
[Music]
for yeah I'll go through
here and we'll walk out on our
own and then we will attack who are we
going for again I forgot the blood Raven
no we killed the blood
Raven we're going for some dudes the Kan
Kane cane
dude oops
my body oh yeah my body is still
there nice that it doesn't despawn how
nice I miss playing necro well how about
you do that right now go play
necro what stops
you
oh
slow
so going to Tristram oh yeah right now I
remember there's a portal there isn't
there and then you go into this weird
area where everything's burning ah
hello
hello oh look at all the holy
that's some good damage
yo is that stronger
no I melted them with poison and cold
and fire everything all at
once oh one
hit one
hit can I use that
well
yes what is
that
skill okay let's go I'm I'm well
prepared thanks to the
well let's
go I don't see my body on the
map
huh where is
it did I go that
far two bodies
oh oh
oh I need
Mana oh bad I did
oh go go
[Music]
cover
that yeah that was more than one enemy
Elite
[Music]
enemy
help what was I what was I supposed to
do that cold cold magic oh man
what is I supposed to
do what do I
do what I
[Music]
do what did I
do hit and run I was trying to hit and
run
change left click into
walk but
then I I will either always attack
normally or only fire
[Music]
arrow oh wait I can't
walk it's not even an
option not by
what
[Music]
yeah
o pick up body and exit Game run back
the way you came
[Music]
what
I don't know I don't
know take it take it take
it oh it's a dead end no it's not
okay okay oh my God oh my God oh my God
Mommy
Mommy that's where I need to go
no oh that's it I don't even need to go
to that stone
Place
huh but I want my other
bodies I want my other
bodies I am
overburdened I can't carry anymore oh I
can't pick it up cuz I can't
carry yo rast I'm
die
Revenge
iore you better carry the on
ball I need
Mana Oh wait we're rocking this
out oh yeah yeah baby yeah baby
yeah
[Music]
baby we're out of the freaking endless
Revival
cycle
hey I can't carry anymore I want that
give me that where is where is the
Revival
bastard oh my God oh my God oh my
God where is
he oh there you are there you
ring okay we did
it re zero intensifies oh my God look at
that loot let's see let's see let's see
let's a
ring never had a ring before 21 attack
rating let's
[Music]
go
CH I want my hunter's bow I am
overburdened
no fire Shrine
oh
uh well
uh wait I can put this like
that Hunters but wait I I socketed so
much there is that going to be useless
now
is that
better 1 2 4 2 to9 plus three maximum
damage plus 11% damage to Demons 35 to
attack rating against
demons o hold
shift fire resist sounds good I can't
socket it
though there's a gas potion near but do
I are you saying that because I I should
get it
oops
what just put it in
there I like them both ah put them on
your merch ah good idea that's right I
had a mercenary
somewhere oh my God don't you do this to
me
now go go go
go oh oh go hit her
a I am
overburdened I am
overburdened this
one I just want to clear this stupid W
worth it when I clear this stupid area
oh wait you're also a boss
monster no more no more I'm
overburdened kill it
how was she not taking
damage okay I am overburdened L Manana
Manana healing
healing all right I am overburdened blah
blah blah blah blah blah I I guess I I
can come
back short bow I want that though how do
I can I like reorganized everything here
it looks bad I don't think I
can
okay I'll come
back okay should I give should I give
the here I need to Res resurrect her and
then
oh uh should I give her this one if she
dies what happens to it
though I can't use that oh she doesn't
need
arrows does she not need the
arrows
over she keeps it oh okay okay that's
good that's
good uh you can wear one of those I
suppose I'll that to good use yes I
would hope
so now let's go to
anara not here don't need to provide her
arrows ooh
nice
okay
and H this
one now we will put the
diamond in
here and deposit oh wait w we could sell
the the the Strangling potion
too not in
town okay wait the key as well should I
bring the key with me I'll bring the key
with
me come with me oh wait I for got
potions forgot to buy potions well
hopefully we'll find
[Music]
some oh level
up what level am I
now
yeah okay
[Music]
what are your recommendations guys oh
the skull cup yeah tell me tell me tell
me though tell me tell me tell me please
where's the schull cup
there
uh how do I open open the skill window
again
[Music]
uh skill
window skill window T thank
you should we should we should we put
one more into fire or should we go for
cold Arrow
or passives are best in my opinion early
W more crate oh good
idea
okay okay a bunch of people said
passives are
[Music]
good
uh ohuh I'm handy defense and energy
faster hit
[Music]
recover 6
14 you can have that a good use you're
welcome short
bow ooh 41 damage to Undead six wow it's
really good for
Undead that's pretty damn
good well Undead but I think I'll sell
it I think we'll go back one more time
to sell everything
no and then we'll finally go into
the into the page I can't carry
anymore this you can carry not a
hold anything else that's important
here oh a cow what what a poor cow in
the middle of nowhere left with all
these mon
monsters whoever did that is a monster
too
yo where is your
buddy
[Music]
M oh she doesn't know what do I not
know minor healing potion thank you for
dropping
that wow refilling Shrine and money and
a healing potion
nice or this fuing
mate oh there's so many
revivers I need
Mama
du
oh
ah I've heard about the I've heard about
the cow level yeah yeah I've seen that
when I was
younger it's one of the things that I've
seen when my mom played uh
Diablo but I barely remembered I just
know it was something with
cows a lot of
cows just a lot of
cows
M ooh yes fin finally finally we're
getting what we
deserve damaged boots
not all right should we go into
the let's go let's go
towards H let's go towards
the actual place where we're supposed to
go but first
first I will sell again you're going to
come back to the car so
often make sure you're ready for a fight
is there a fight right
away should I keep this in my stats or
in case I die again I really need a
bow oh wait maybe I should have worn
those boots not sell it
okay
okay looking
clean uh what
identification how do I do that again
what you guys said I don't
know whatever I'll just do it like
[Music]
this wait how much money do I have zero
okay ready to
go oops oh
well who are you
fighting we're busy come with me a nor
you have a weird
name refilling
Shrine all right we're really
close what but what was that with uh was
that fena you know that that that Stone
Circle I remember when I played the
alpha I went there first I
think
should I go there first or is that for
later we go to okay all
right ooh it's dark in
here oh we're so
strong we're so strong especially now
that I finally have someone to come with
me wolf head
ooh burn okay oh that's so many
y y oh the loot is really
good on I don't know which direction to
go there's so much to choose
from oh hello Miss
happen that's a funny name you like a is
that a is that a joke about you looking
like something that's wasn't supposed to
happen you Mish
happened you failed at
happening
oh yo my chat
died in OBS it still moves but not in my
window OBS is so small I can't look at
it a Miss shape
oh I read it wrong then all right I like
I like Miss happen too I like it that
way oh miss shap it's to S
huh combat right I am ready ready ready
to
battle where are
they not enough
Mana no one can stop me
now
I'm going to fix chat soon hopefully
when I got time maybe if I finish the
dungeon where is your Reviving
friend oh my God oh my God I shouldn't
stand in the middle of all of
this I need Anor I dare you to die don't
you die on
me
I wish there was just like an extra
option to play the game with W
ASD but I guess that would kind of
destroy the game what do you guys think
would that destroy the
game cuz it's just like too easy
then I'm so busy with my mouse
though
a
controller there's a control pad option
what a controller as in like a PS4
controller
really I am overburdened as always I am
overburdened how oh
dear
uh
H nothing okay
okay should I go back
[Music]
once
hold H what are you
doing should I go back I'll go back or
should I uh
uh wait I think I should be able to pick
up something I can't carry
anymore this for sure this for
sure oh I almost wanted to kill my
friend sorry about that
Anor I'll go back once drop the stuff no
but I want the money I need the the
money I need to sell everything
M as we've seen
before I really need the
money oh my God that was quite the
struggle having no money for anything
Droid only Barbarian
only not for me either not for me either
not for me e not for me e and the
javelin
uh oh 4 to 10 6 to 14
oh well then okay wait can she also
carry Jaelin now I I mean I guess she
can
but uh we will choose not to give her
that also so my private stash deposit
there you go now you guys are happy
aren't you wait I forgot to sell the the
other the green
potion sell this
and now let me fix the chat really
quick got to fix the chat here it's
effing
broken there something this always
happens
o my YouTube browser is
dead
suan okay
now now I got it it's loading and open
the
chat come on very
slow all right welcome back Chad nice to
see you
again
without you I feel so
uneasy I need you guys by my
side I need
you so I'm just going to quickly buy
some blue
potions and going to
uh place them here
okay okie
dokie time to clear that
cave
watching you play this is fun oh thank
you I'm glad you're enjoying it thank
you very
much what is
that resist fire Shrine H should I take
that
now I hope it won't be a
waste come on shoot fire at Me
Now oh my
oh wow oh he was dead
fast
easy hey you you you killed him Anor you
do the job I pick up the items
[Music]
I but what this teaches me is that it's
definitely worth to uh not immediately
go
to um the next main quest
dungeon but instead like go take a look
at the optional
Dungeons and and see what items they
have there and get the
EXP yeah a little bit of grinding in
between and it doesn't really feel like
grinding just yet maybe it will in the
future but currently it just feels like
it's like fun time exploring so I don't
mind it at
all I don't mind
it mostly act three what
grinding oh my God I
I
oh
guys if you by the way for Hol talk if
you have a question for Cho Sensei ask
it now on the community post because
after the Diablo stream I'll
probably uh collect the
questions I'll probably work on
that
and
yes
there already have been a lot of
questions at least on Twitter though
from what I've seen I don't know about
in the community post I haven't checked
it
yet got these track
ladies they're so
sexy track
ladies that green really looks good on
them I don't think I could rock that
color that
well now I want to watch a Shrek movie I
need a Manish right now another help
Shrine oh
wait what was the button again to
quickly put them in in in there what was
that again I need
M sneez
some just by me mentioning sherek hold
shift left click
potion ship left click
potion h
no no it's not going
in shift and left shift and left that's
what I'm doing why is it not going in
there
shift shift and right click now I drank
it
C no that drops
oh it has to be Mana
there um but if I I can place it myself
there oh it has to be the same as the
batom in order to work with shift that's
stupid that's a little bit stupid cuz I
can I can forcefully place it there W
laugh if I want
to it just doesn't go in there
automatically what the hell
Oh what
now should I
go 9% physical damage to Elemental
damage plus
37 critical or
fire
you can always
restat is that what you mean not resp a
re resp specialize that what you mean
crit all right and
uh yes I'm just just putting it in
wherever I feel
like or how I feel like it sorry not
much system going on there
I'm still a beginner okay I need to
figure this out whatever feels good
whatever I feel like I'm
lacking big dungeon this
is
hello quilted I should go into the city
again you know no no not
yet wait a
second
uh cool the Dumber there we go should I
wear
that 11 16 no o I can even put something
in the in the socket of my armor
H little Narrow Path
here don't pick up wi items I think
right now I'm happy for any kind of
items to be honest
later on I will definitely leave more of
those things on the
ground I'm so happy that I'll have so
many different collaboration partners
for this
game I'm excited for some fun sash
sessions
sessions killing some bosses
together is this where I came
from oh no oh I reached my
goal but
well then let me first go to the
city ah I need to way point
through
Sorcerers only
oh Paladin
only very
unfortunate ah not
here let me
buy just for just for safety
net all
right
sell extra keys not
here all this extra key oh whatever I'm
going to put it in here for now and
deposit all right going back let's find
this dude oh repair arm more oops fle
gore that's okay up or
down oh dear that oh that's a lot of lot
of stuff going on I want want that money
give me the shiny
thing oh wow he just died right in front
of my eyes that was easy didn't even do
anything kill
him
okay what do we have lots and lots of
gold
mhm uh short gold identify 20 gold okay
see now I'm going to leave some stuff
here actually it also kind of look like
the the Orcs from Orcs Orcs from World
of
Warcraft with that beautiful green color
oh preserved head is good to sell right
I think that brought in a lot of
money and with that hairstyle the balls
head and then that ponytail really
reminds me of world of
warrow which makes sense because
blizzard if it has skills yes
oh oh sorry Anna you didn't see
that right you didn't see that I was
aiming at
you
oh my God why am I getting so much
damage oh because of
you what are we
doing nice I am over another one
down get rid of that get dead
that looks so
creepy
K skull cap un identifi
ooh
[Music]
yes yes you can take that good use that
looks
good thank you for dropping that
sir
I can't carry anymore and Mona potion
all
right oh man every few steps my
inventory is full every few goddamn
steps where is the portal
[Music]
here where is it did I miss it is it
like down
here is it somewhere
here there's a house here that I
missed what she must let me enter please
nope
nothing thank
you I feel
like maybe it's down here somewhere no
what is
that Ash cow the
hunter done I can't
carore head shot boom I can't carry any
sorry that should be boom head shot I
can't carry the wolfhead
though how big is it
though
wolfhead
nice who who are you
fighting did do the do the arrows get
lost when you're fighting through the
trees is that a
thing nope
stamina I can't carry anymore I can't
carry anymore
I just missing how can you miss
continuously so
often going
back
okay uh do I have something for
here
uhuh an
Cara I should I should honestly get like
a card to collect points at your
store
how much did I get 1 141 oh I don't need
this one anymore
huh
unidentified
oh how how how
how
W
cell cell cell
cell suddenly I have so
[Music]
many
potions
way too many more than I
need Discord use the axe what are you
giving me serious advice or is that a is
that a
[Music]
meme oh I should put them in a chest
that's right for for
desperate situations that's right I'll
put a couple of them in
here what do you mean fix the amon's
face she's
beautiful here I'll show
you I
mean I mean I mean with the proper
makeup she can look even
better all right what do we
got I'll ignore that I can't find the
portal
[Music]
do
she has in she has not not only inner
beauty but backwards
Beauty if you know what I
mean wait did they cover up her butt
wasn't her butt like exposed in the
alpha am I imagining
things what if
I or was that in the olds how do I go to
the
old legacy mode je oh yes yeah they did
cover up a but this is the this is the
old version from what year was this game
originally
released give me back the
[Music]
butt Justice for the
Amazon 1998
wow W 2,000
oh
h i required a
booty
[Music]
M okay I still can't find a portal
so maybe it's just ahead of
us if I go
north
hopefully
hopefully I feel much stronger now good
for you good for
you
I'll take that an know don't
die we got gem Shrine do I get a gem a
diamond
no the luck is
incredible wait I need to follow the
path
right I want to find the Portal though
I'm in the middle of
nowhere oh here's a path here's a
path entering the black wait is that
where I'm supposed to
go search for the tree of Inus is that
no they would tell me that it's in the
in there I think that's
wrong yeah that's the next area isn't it
okay what about the path
here does that that lead somewhere no it
ends
there but is there the portal no also a
dead
end
stop stop following
me I don't like that I want my
privacy I really appreciate my
privacy okay well maybe we were going
into the
right uh uh Direction after
all voice stamina came at the right time
just when I needed it I'll go hey but
shouldn't I be following a path I'll go
upwards now but there is no path
here oh oh I found
it dark I never found the Stony field
Waypoint is that for real
or did I just not activate
it I guess I just didn't activate it or
did I not find
it where am I
going not enough Mana not enough
Mana
look for the tree ah big
tree I missed it what the Stony Fields
portal or the big tree I need
[Applause]
more hello can I pet
you no never mind I don't want to pet
you an get get out of there get out of
there I need
Mana I'll give you Mana
w
oh a blue axe get rid of that ugly
spare
yes yes yes
yes nice good fight good fight my friend
is still alive I'm so
proud okay more decks more decks for the
flex and now we want a fire arrow this
time all right right all right all
right meet Shield friend ah is that the
tree that's not a very big
tree it's a weird tree though it stands
out a
lot is that the
tree the tree of Inus recover the scroll
what scroll are we talking about that's
the
tree there's no scroll
here or did I did I just pick it up
what a strange now it let me click it I
am overburdened well well how big is
this
scroll oh God damn it not hold on there
I can fix
that I got it take the scroll of in oh
that's great I just wanted to go back uh
so that's perfect for
me
nice uh I
identify
wo
wo clo
Diamond not
here
[Music]
wa ah very good I have translated the
ruins on this scroll you must find the
can runes and touch them in the order
that I have
written oh a that's where we go to the
to the stone
portal that's
them
okay oh we got so much money now yeah
D I heard an owl where is it where's the
owl I love
owls I love
M
Tom go to
the stones and the Stony field touch the
stones in the order found on the scroll
of Inus enter the portal to Tristram but
the where the D the danger that lies
ahead no no problem nothing is too
dangerous for
me what can I can I do for you I've Got
The
Power uh use now to more
chest put that money in there ooh
5,700 nice
number a very pretty
number going to put
[Music]
some of my
potions
away like this perhaps
okay ready to go ready to
rumble I am prepared you think so wait
should I even wouldn't it be shorter to
no but I don't have the portal to Stony
Fields isn't it in Stony
Fields would it be smart to
teleport I feel like
yeah
oh
cold
planes yeah it was really close to the
planes all right I will do
that right
now I don't want to go for the
underground passage passage anymore yeah
okay we'll go through here hold
planes should have sold that while
I was at it
okay this way I remember I
think I think it was that
way mhm mhm mhm what what do you want
who are you oh on my way just
calmly destroying an elite enemy as if
I'm going through a driveth through just
it to die
[Music]
through
excuse
me wait uh what is the order oh one two
three four five that's a difficult order
o left down up right
up uh are there enemies
there musy
m what I
here
oh let's get rid of that
so that no one disturbs us in our I am
over totally not crazy wi
ritual okay it was uh do I
remember no it was something like left
right okay middle down up okay
middle let me touch it what oh wait a
second
second oh wait ah wait there like ah
turned around different ah wait I start
with
two and then the tier okay two tier zero
[Music]
one and another
tier
two
zero 1
here baby oh yummy the
[Music]
thunderstorm should I really be in there
oh God that's a scary portal that's s's
ey
I
the what do you mean massive Chicken
brain what was so bad about what I just
did that was not that
bad
right I'll go back
one lum's biggest fan what are we
rescuing someone who likes
owls
[Music]
leaving uh find and rescue deard k k
Kane how do I pronounce it Kan
K ah I'm
scared shut the shut the
kai P like pain okay Kane I'm coming for
you I remember this place a great War
were fought
here no I'm so
sorry I didn't want to do that I clicked
on it
accidentally
no ew that's
disgusting I need to mark this this
stream as r18
plus oh move move
Mo by burn the m m funny
name grece wolf there's a lot of elite
enemies here too huh oh yeah holy
King
macaroni race world is
strong
oh he
slow oh you can't touch me you can't
touch
[Music]
me adur heavy boots of balance 10%
faster hit recovery Co is this oh yes oh
yes oh
yes ah
oh I didn't
H
okay not enough not
porn you got a funny name buddy but
you're weak as hell oh spear golden
spear oh Champion return they don't give
me any time to
chill oh my God that's a lot of items
I'll have to go home like million
times what do I
do I want the
spare uh wait what's the Bish how much
space Oh dear I can't pick up
anything that's going to be a couple of
trips back and
forth wait let me at least pick up the
portions
minor healing potion minor healing
potion minor light wait what is what is
what is L lighter miners okay I should
pick up light items skull cap I am
[Music]
overburdened going back
once
hello
I am really uh turning up the economy in
this
game selling selling selling
selling selling
selling
pre-identify wait what not here re
identify wait what was that yeah someone
identifies for free
right ah Kane does oh I'm looking
forward to having him
[Music]
then all
right okay that looks yes
yes f there we
go I need to save him yes yes yes yes
yes yes I'm here I'm here I'm
here I'm here I'm picking up the
important stuff should I really walk
into this ouch no regret help help okay
ow oh you were so
close go to the robes Camp without
delay byebye that was my oh that was my
character's voice I didn't know my
character has the voice oh that's it it
was so
[Laughter]
close I thought I thought I would need
to look a bit more for
you all right I clear this area any more
Elite monsters that I can
kill or did I really do everything
already
[Music]
top left
oh
cool
doco was that him just
now Elite monster a top left from from
which angle this stop
left
probably somewhere here huh did I hear a
cling
oh what what is that what is
that what is that who are they
burning was that a witch that this
person really needed to be burnt alive
probably
alive I don't see
anymore that of fire today don't stop
don't stop I don't see any more people a
member of the camp I'm allied with oh no
look for a body top
left wait I just saw a
body with top left do you mean
here I don't see any bodies do you guys
see
buddy far left left I can't go can I go
over the water
no left corner try left left okay this
left body ah oh there you
are w w wo wo w w w w w w
what is it really okay to take all of
that his leg
though wa cash
money cash money who is
that I got his
leg it's not even a proper leg it's like
a pirate
leg
oh he dropped all that
money anything I should be picking up
that I didn't pick up
yet
Plick Shady Merchant back in D1 oh
n he used to be a proper character huh
okay good to know
he took all the money he was the gacha
guy that's
funny okay I am back uh I guess
I'll wait there's a portal close by but
oh I'll take I'll take my town
portal keep leg keep leg don't sell leg
is that what you're telling
me keep the leg for when special
occasion for when I I lose my own
leg keep leg
okay cow Port
[Music]
oh
mhm
okay cow
level you have risked your life to
rescue
for that we thank you that was nothing
seek his counsel
immediately oh
okay um I have my own console though in
whole life
English can I not seek their
counsel can I use a spare
too well we're going for
javelins oh
free identifying oh yeah right
oopsie I'm not used to it
yet spars have have various bugs
[Music]
what well that's
unfortunate
okay you didn't want me to sell that
can I not buy things back wasn't there
an option to buy things
back but people say that that that
they're better
anyway don't they have the whatever you
just sold yeah this one I can buy it
back but I'm I'm using javelins and
Bows yeah it won't be the last one you
guys are always so dramatic though it
makes me worry when you're like no no
she sold it no as a token of my
gratitude I will identify items for you
at no charge
nice regrettably I could do nothing to
prevent the disaster which devastated
Tristram oh Javin and considerest fears
have come to pass Diablo the Lord Of
Terror has once again been set loose
upon the world as you know some time ago
Diablo was slain beneath Tristram and
when our hero emerged triumphant from
the Labyrinth beneath town we held a
grand celebration that lasted several
days yet as the weeks passed our hero
became increasingly aloof he kept his
distance from the rest of the town's
folk and seem to lapse into a dark
brooding depression o i thought that
perhaps his ordeal had been so
disturbing that he simply couldn't you
guys got really shitty weather here is
this playing in England hero seemed more
tormented every passing day I remember
he awoke many times Screaming in the
Night always something about the
East one day he simply left and shortly
there after trist was attacked by
Legions of foul demons many were slain
and the demons left me to die in that
cursed
cage I believe now that tristram's hero
was that Dark Wanderer who passed this
way before the monastery fell I fear
even worse my friend I fear that diblo
has taken possession of the hero who
sought to slay him what if true Diablo
will become more powerful than ever
before you must stop him or all will be
lost I will I will leave it to me I'm
the hero of the
story okay talk gossip it takes time to
master your skills and use will hone
your Technique but take care to choose
your new skills wisely oh you're such a
Gossip Girl yes that was that was not
gossip what the
hell as a token of my gratit sh sh sh
well you're not I guess because I don't
have anything to identify is that the
issue
okay well well well
well our next mission
is what is
[Music]
it you won't tell
me anyone got a Quest from are you good
to see you when I fled the monastery I
left behind the herodc malice my
enchanted I hammer you can retrieve it
for me I'll use its magic to strengthen
your equipment
okay you can Hammer me girl anytime okay
I'll bring you your
Hammer H oh that's the actually not the
next
one where do I get the next
one I'm sorry she was asking for me to
say
that
she wants me to bring the hammer she
could go herself but she asks me to
bring her Hammer Stony Fields
Tower you mean that's where this is or
where this this one
is I should set my I should set my PC
Mouse to this
one it's it's so
nostalgic so
nice the fourth Quest oh the ham no ah
this one is optional the hammer isn't
okay oh Monastery Barracks Beware of the
Smith that guards it Monastery Barracks
doo
doo the quest is optional but you better
do ah I think I didn't do it in the in
the alpha right
black Marsh oh but for the optional
let's do the optional one I want to do
it I don't remember if I actually did it
in the
alpha I skipped it oh well how would I
get the the the F the fourth optional
Quest Stony
field dark wood
first black
[Music]
Marsh okay
I'm
confused four Quest is in the black
Marsh okay wait was black Marsh over
there wasn't that the this path over
here ah there it
is oops sorry who are
you
B thank you for welcoming me to your
Marsh so
nicely I feel very very welcome thank
you so
much where's where's the
magician no
magician I'll stop picking up white
items
now cuz I don't want to run back a
million times
oo except for the for those kind of
things
obviously what exactly am I looking for
in the black Marsh for the fourth
Quest oh I found the I found the the
portal
it
not
enough a pedestal a stone tower okay
thank you I'll be on the lookout
Superior should I follow the
path is it going to
be there if I follow the path who Nice
kill
Anna nice there's never anything
here
oh not enough
Mana Tower normally spawns around the
edge of the map
who Okay Edge Edge of the
map edge
of to
to
oh nice level up
girl along the
fence middle of the map not the edge yo
okay I am
overburden middle the thing is I don't
know where the middle is since I haven't
discovered the whole map
yet
oh wait is this
it this looks like
it the Forgotten
Tower but I don't even have the quest
yet would it like activate
automatically what's that smell oh Power
Cell level I should I should go back
once though I got a lot of h no don't
use that should I go
back go
back explore first you just oh I just
got it oh I did what is it just explore
explore the cell of dungeons beneath the
[Applause]
tower all right I'll start exploring B
Tel I
I've been deceived by the barrel I
thought me and the barrel were
friends uh wait it's so
dark
ow this this reminds me of the place
where andaria Liv in it looks very much
like it
I don't like it w level
up Champion blood
Clan it's time to
die preserved
head small
Shield um
sasuga
okay I'm
going I'm going home
[Music]
going new
skill I don't know what your skill on
guys please
help power strike poison Javelin maybe
we should get something for a javelin I
barely use it
though fire arrow exploding arrow
I can't get it oh do I need do I need
multiple
shot
uh do I need multiple shot in order to
get the exploding
arrow stick to
Bow well then that means I need magical
Arrow first and then multiple shot and
then exploding
arrow okay okie dokie okay to help thank
you thanks dude cool cool cool
cool money money money Tangerine
preserved head of
fors interesting very
interesting faster cast rate
ooh that's that's not really good for me
it would be good if I had a friend who
plays like a
sorceress should I keep it for someone
else
maybe cool cool
cool wait
4,200 selling
it ah whoever CH chooses to play
Sorcerers they'll find they'll find some
something nice for
themselves yeah I never had this I never
had it never found something no no no no
no no I don't know I don't know what
you're talking
about but he does not identify inside
the horri cube what what do you
mean what do you
mean now I'm really rich
yeah oh
[Music]
an act
to oh that Cube
ah that stupid ass Cube yeah I
remember oh this is a big big
dungeon catar no thank
you well it's so noisy here
too there's so many many
rooms I don't know where to
go devil
King preserved head but it's white so
should I still take
[Music]
it where where I think I went to a dead
end it's
money yeah go to the purple okay which
one though there's
two I guess maybe the lower one
oh maybe the lower
[Music]
one
okay oh no that's where I came from of
course C
Anna was trying to show me the way thank
you
Anna you could use your voice though to
tell
me level
two
okay what do we have a
body money
what is that fancy magic around
them what what was that special spell or
something magic might or
around arrows do I need
arrows
[Music]
hello they were
buffering they probably have a really
bad internet connection yeah
yesterday yesterday I was uh privately
playing Minecraft to finish the shrine I
did finish it maybe you guys saw it uh
in any of the other girls streams
Minecraft streams over the night maybe
maybe someone showed it but I finished
it
yesterday uh I played until halfast 4
a.m. I don't know I don't know why I
played so long I kind of wasted my time
here and there by doing some other
things as well
ouch is it even worth destroying these
barrels probably
not is that a secret door
here yeah full 30 and then I still I had
some some snack afterwards a desert
dessert anyway worth it I would say
definitely worth it um but yeah I
finished it and I made a lot of concrete
and and now now that I finally know how
do make concrete I'm not I'm not scared
of using concrete
anymore um it does need a lot of
different materials which is a bit
annoying but actually actually it wasn't
even that Troublesome did I come from
here
no okay it wasn't even as Troublesome as
I thought it would be so yeah and
uh yeah I I also I made the
path I made the path much
longer oh those ghost remind me of
andario
yo that's a lot of money thank you wow
they dropped so much
money so yeah also I did find I did find
menis I'm sorry I turns out I did have
two people with mending maybe someone
else I don't remember raising two
dudes I don't don't remember raising two
dudes with
mending I need
Mana but apparently I did yeah sea menis
is
alive and I tried to move uh I can't
carry any two people into their accurate
districts
tried let me get
that
uh
no what was I get
shipped okay now it works
[Music]
okay and let's put that
here yeah but phoenixon is going to take
me ages to repair and it doesn't really
feel like something I even want to do on
stream cuz it's pretty tedious and kind
of
boring uh I don't know if I'll ever work
on that on
[Music]
stream but I need to finish it like
somewhat soon because people go to
phoenixon in the hopes of finding
something and now it's just really
really difficult to find anything at
all and that's a bit embarrassing I want
Fenix to look good with watch paint dry
if you commented the with thank
you oh thank
[Music]
you oh we're already at uh this level
now all
right maybe worth going back
once
yes oh it was so bright I thought I
spawned somewhere else not here not not
used to this thank you I would watch you
do your taxes well it's fine thank
you the order welcomes you you don't
have to watch me do my taxes though cuz
someone else does my taxes for
me
oo that's a nice
stare Maybe
I will do your taxes no thank you I have
someone to do
it thank you for the
offer
uh
deposit
okay moving on level four hopefully
we're
close think we're close I feel
it
oh no our friends they're all
dead no she went up in Flames just by my
touch I shouldn't touch
people I'm like I'm like Shon but
instead of electricity I give up
fire it's kind of hot isn't
it
o
oh my
God oh my
God oh nice his friends are
gone
nice those ghost enemies they look
really fancy a
dag okay
it's so scary oh nice
items I'm enjoying this
game I'm really enjoying playing
this Tel
SE I just sometimes I wish things were
all a little bit bigger and a different
angle I don't really like this angle can
could this be place in a normal angle
like I don't know Minecraft or like like
the angle in Tales of
aise cuz everything is so small and it's
so fckery with like clicking on
things this is just like the place
andario is
in not enough mama what I don't like
hearing
that very
Coy wa almost died
yo that was close that was very close
press F well yeah but I don't know that
that seems like too
close I feel like I need to see
more I don't know something's
wrong something's off of that angle here
for I think we have arrived oh wait
did she oh level
up is that what I'm
fighting I need money I easy easy easy
wait is she
dead run who I think we did it what's
going
on oh I was so calm with there's so much
F of the tower's Trove for the
taking W where is the hammer I know
that's a different
Quest was that it was that it was
oh
nice nice nice nice okay what do we have
oh wa what is that oh for socketing
items
[Music]
nice yeah I think I have to sell and
come back
[Music]
again uh let me take oh Mana potion
normal
size
oh I can pick up some more
potions
Miner
mace I can sell that okay I'm coming
back
once
BRB
oops nice R we have uh plus two Mana
after each kill kill and adds 5 to 30
fire damage for weapons at least fire
resist are they good should we put it
into so many people want to talk to me
should we put it in here for
now well done oh
no oh sorry I I cut you off I want to
hear that again actually I clicked on
you by accident and then I clicked Away
by
accident God damn it oh wait should I
keep
oh maybe I should keep wait get back
give
back here sell your
D
did I lose money on that it's it's
okay
[Music]
Emerald there should be a like a policy
that that like if you if you buy
something back under 5 seconds or 10
seconds you should be allowed to get it
back for free return policy have you
girls here never heard about that before
from the modern world
I got my receipt I have everything on
video
huh let me put that in there and
uh oops not
you uh was it shipped
yes okay going back to collect some no
shut up some more
items
yes buyback wasn't invented for another
20 years oof that's a big oof there long
bow I can't carry anymore I literally
just cleaned
up we'll make it
work we'll make it work
uh yeah whatever give unidentified I'll
not identify it
yet put that in
there
um maybe the maze I can't carry anymore
really how many arrows do I have three
okay then we don't need that let's take
the mace and sell
it is that it what's about what about
this area here I didn't go here
yet or this area money cting cutting
cutting
ooh all right stats
uh more
decks more
dicks okay you guys said it it's a waste
to do uh to put into v no not V uh uh
the energy thingy for Mana
right got to get this one for exploding
arrow next is that
AOE oh the Minecraft VOD it will come
back soon it will come back soon YouTube
is currently um processing it please
hold the line oh what I I almost missed
that uh oh
wait how big is that
uh there we go
Tetris oh my God there's so much money
here and I almost just walked away from
all of
that ooh ooh oh it went up in
Flames okay I think now I oh what did I
just see oh never
mind
oh I'm dager bird duck does he have the
same name in
English
oh okay well now I can leave right now
now I can leave
Scrooge Mech duck that's his name in
English oh in German he's dagle bird
duck I actually really really really
enjoyed reading those comics when I was
younger those one of my favorite Comics
I would always buy the
books always hello I don't know how
young I was then though wait I should
identify First I still
do hello
cute have you watched the show I think I
did yeah a little
bit but mostly
yeah you know I was reading that oo ah
this one is the one that you have to
keep in the inventory it's huge though
plus three to strength and maximum Stam
that's not really worth carrying around
so much it takes up so much space I
think I'll put it in my in my
stash uh uh long bow long bow worth
oh nah mine is still better I would
say yeah with all the side
effects what about this one
[Music]
oh
six plus 10 chance to cast level free
charged Bolt when
struck no I want to keep my six defens
what do you think yeah was wear wearing
gray armor
apparently should I go for Less
defense faster hit recover is better
okie dokie by the way anything I can
give to
you no no no okay all right
uh I'll sell I'll sell the
boots and the bow but she has a decent
bow I don't think she needs this one
either
okay we are doing nice progress let's
get the hammer I don't know if I can
kill andariel today though cuz I got a
lot of super chats to read and I don't
want to stay up too late today I do want
to get the hammer though let's get the
hammer um uh yes wait I needed to talk
to someone wasn't there another dude who
wanted to talk to me
here well done my friends this is the
text I skipped opportunity together have
created in you a kind of alchemy oh
thank
you that's all you got to
say
really so happy you play Diablo thank
you I'm happy too
[Music]
donk let me put that in here all right
now we go for the
hammer where do I go for the hammer
Monastery Barracks where did you guys
say is the
closest Darkwood
or way point is
faster
Darkwood black Marsh
oh black Marsh
okay
now which way do we
[Music]
go we went up there that was not it so
maybe maybe we just go straight
ahead I'll take
that
hello a little bit of exp I'll I'll take
with
me
m oh yeah I actually wanted to say when
I was talking about Minecraft that my
game was like lag lagging a lot I don't
know what happened with the server
recently good is having issues
too and it's like uh on on the stream
the other day I was just like
having uh not so many FPS I think you
guys noticed but yesterday in the night
when I was uh
playing the issue was like like when I
would for example when I would want to
fly with
my when I was trying to fly take off
with my lightra with the fireworks I
would click on the fireworks and then
then they wouldn't go off and then I
would just stand around and a few
seconds later I was flying and I was
bumping into things and I almost died I
had like half a heart suddenly it was so
up seems out of a bay and
[Music]
Cali yeah I I I said I I was hinting at
it on our Minecraft disc that like maybe
an upgrade would be
uh nice now because especially if the if
the Japanese girls and like so many
people are going to join our server now
and we have built so many new things
like I don't know how how that how
Minecraft servers really work but can
you give them an upgrade is that a
reasonable thing to ask
for can you upgrade
them what
though more r i oh it's possible yes you
can okay well I've been asking for it
but I don't know if my wish will be
granted how much does that
cost I don't think it's a very expensive
thing is
it it shouldn't be too crazy right
[Music]
not very expensive not a h all then it's
just an issue of whether or
not I will be uh
noticed got to ask Omega Alpha whenever
whenever he's not answering whether or
not he likes oil or
butter on t
got to ask him to maybe I should send
him a
marshmallow maybe I should send a
marshmallow or maybe you guys send can
you guys send him a
marshmallow okay or
them it's hard to say can you send the
marshmallow or don't send to many
marshmallows not enough
m Minecraft server upgrade
please imagine the Japanese girls all
coming over at once and then it's like
super laggy I remember the time when I
went to the Japanese server and I had
insane
lag oh my God what is going
on not enough man
although last time I went to the
Japanese server I didn't have that issue
see I don't know if they upgraded their
server or or if it was an internet issue
on my
side yeah the summer was it the Summer
Festival not only then though I think I
had issues before
too
[Music]
uh remember to say
please hey it's Christmas soon soon some
somewhat soon it's Christmas I wish for
the Minecraft server to get an
upgrade well that's really a simple Wish
isn't it no my actual wish would
be
maybe maybe I don't know getting to meet
all the Hol myth
girls what are you going to give
Omega I need man
my my my my will to work for her whole
life that's that's what I give in
return is isn't what else could you ask
for what else could they ask
for I feel like I'm getting getting
bonked uh on this let me
check no no no or is it am I getting
bonked no no
no no no no it's just a lot of DMS from
the
girls
what
interesting they maybe it's just because
management is not watching my stream we
got to wait for when they watch My
Stream then I'll be
bed this is good I work I work in the
darkness I work in the shadows they
don't they don't hear what I
say wa where the hell did you come from
returned mate you definitely did
return I'm
bat no
Birdman and Birdman where the freak is
the thing that I'm looking for where's
the hammer it's probably in a dungeon
but like where is the
dungeon where is the dungeon oh wait is
it that thing down there this
one a path Castle a
castle I'm look I'm looking for a
castle
H so I'm kind of worried about the next
Minecraft stream uh I but I'm not
playing Minecraft this week anymore
right your items in your inventory will
be deleted you got to say ah you I was
thinking you talk about Diablo oh
hello you're talking about Minecraft huh
okay yeah yeah I think they will War us
once they are actually
really making the the portal oh I should
look for the for the portal here
speaking of
portals is there a portal here cuz it
just yeah to Highlands shouldn't there
be one
here what the
still no I mean I no official date
yet but I think it's probably going to
be like 30th or the first of October or
second something like
that I don't I don't even know if that
happens like all in one day I I don't I
don't really know
so I I don't know but but our deadline
for building the portal is the 30th of
September so I would assume that they
don't want to waste any more time once
once we've done our
part oh I'm so hungry I need my
lasagna
I got so much lasagna left
over uh I've heard that people when they
make lasagna
themselves that they uh freeze their own
lasagna how do you do
that how do you freeze your
lasagna do you like where what what kind
of what kind of container do you put it
in we put it in fre up
rap
it
okay maybe I'll put like a little bit of
it in there because it looks like I
could eat it for the next 4 days but on
the on I'm thinking on the fifth on the
fifth day it probably won't be good
anymore so maybe I should freeze
it
huh okay wait there's no portal
here
oh
hello I'm
dying oh my
God oh my God oh my God oh my God where
is
here oh my
God there we go you've made more trouble
than you should have
done I'm D thank you forever no not
yet not
yet okay shall we go
into that castle or whatever it is stop
wasting time how about
[Music]
that let's go let's bring that with
me oh
[Music]
wa if she kills mobs do I get experience
from that too I haven't been paying
attention to the experience
bar oh this
place
oh yeah this place I remember this place
from the
alpha
ah oh
St it
what was the baby
here I do get experience from the mobs
that she
kills I
don't stamina
doco also potions
doco the bird sounds here are
fascinating so
melodic
ouch got to get those EXP while they're
hot found the Waypoint outer cloer
oyster the world is my
oyster yeah hell yeah the world really
is my
oyster oh thank you for the red super
chat all the recent gorilla mine you've
been enjoying them why because I haven't
been in
them and the thing is like I'm trying to
fix my sleep schedule and and that will
make the chance of us meeting one
another even even worse even
L um no but uh I think like if they
stream more like today like when oh when
cie was
streaming that that's normally a time
where I'm awake when cie was playing
Minecraft
today I would be fine with that
I'm going to go back once and get
healing
potions I
think mhm need those
pots uh kind not
here thanks
dude what the hell did I pick
up oh small
charm oh plus two attack rting I don't
mind keeping the exra gold oh if I ever
want a gold Farm that's going to be
useful hold let's take some
pts going to put them
here
nice good that I didn't sell them all I
know plus two is very little but the
item is also very little not in town
good day please swap your body and bow
and E does that matter does that matter
wait now I'm lacking arrows actually
wait did that
matter what if I'm what if I'm
left-handed I am left-handed wait does
she actually change
hands no she doesn't she doesn't even
change hand oh it's just OCD
okay
okay uh wait do you want the new
hat Defense 9 defense four okay you
don't need that huh not
here uh this this this this
this okay I need some arrows though
should I buy now or pick up something in
the I'll find
something I'll find something oh there
we go I told you I told you I would find
something
okay oh my God
Y what the
they F they don't
exist wo BL
Bang cute name you got who named you
who's naming all these Monsters by the
way who's in charge of
that
yeah all
right mhm I'll take some more
arrows light bang is cute yeah I don't
know it's kind of cute it's kind of cute
exploding
arrow explosion should I switch to that
now now or wait until it's a bit
stronger wait where is it this
one
okay we will use that in a
moment okay this room is clear there was
nothing here though and I'll go this way
now open
oh why can't you just shoot the barrels
with an arrow also what the hell are you
doing come with
me W I need
M
oh okay no boss monster here are you
sure can I hurt myself with my own
explosion if I stand too close to it
honest
question boost your Mana now so you can
use explosive Arrow
more wait wh what what did that do I
don't fear
fire of course I don't fear
fire thank you for giving me
nothing okay this was also so it didn't
bear much fruit either so let's go to
that side my fire
resistance oh it does use up a lot of
Mana let me go back to fire for
now what the
hell
no stop it at once
where's my where's my grill
here okay this a really pretty Monastery
is this where Sound of Music was
[Music]
filmed I should do a Sound of Music
K
right who would like to see that
I need Mana oh I'll give you
Mana oh my god oh kill him first kill
him
first me me me
really feel like that would be a lot of
fun oh my God stop Reviving
them oh no my friend died I'm coming
with you soon
probably oh oh oh oh I got
him I got
him
oh I'm on my
own all around
[Music]
me it's okay now I have more than enough
money to revive her
it's a small investment
for a big big girl I'm a big big girl in
a big big world it's not a big big
something if you leave
me thanks for the great ear bus thank
you w congratulations on being fried
take to school
okay okay okay okay
I'm going back to revive her
though I can't live without her how can
I live with okay I keep on singing
what's going on I'm feeling
musical
[Music]
Hello don't waste my time
K Kan don't waste my time what did I
do life stolen perit Mon oh okay
W cute Rings oh dwel of joyfulness I
want to joy joy joy
baby okay the rest I shall
sell that was a fun song
oh I can reset St points of her
now all right I'll keep that in mind
thank
you
[Music]
oh
okay just once it what if I need to do
it again inste like a pay payment option
for I don't know real money to do it
again pay to win you know can I do
that no
friend friend I forgot about
her
I hate that you could can we just do
like double click in order to get
through the portal why does it have to
be one
click I'm going to buy new new Scrolls
not here
yes Scroll of town
portal how do I buy more what else I
don't know how to buy
more
I just do it like this shift click I've
been
trying doesn't work it doesn't
work now don't forget the lady this time
casha 480 that's
expensive that's is
expensive
to
I have 27k gold well so what I got to
think like a businesswoman here cuz I am
a businesswoman who the hell are
you
oh 4 a is expensive to bring you your
friend don't judge
me you guys keep on judging
me I'm I'm you got to consider here I'm
so nice and I'm bringing back a freaking
hammer for a random girl that I've met
today and I'm going for hell for
her what what R
wife weird
extra strong ah it didn't quite feel
extra strong oops I clicked that by
accident I
jump
M mhm where's the
hammer give me the
[Music]
hammer
could have gone straight but I decided
to go here and I meet against a boss
monster
woo fun fun fun wait who keeps on
Reviving who is
it oh oh oh
oh okay
we're fine we're fine we're fine we're
fine Grand
charm oh Hammer I found the hammer guys
I found the hammer shh don't wake the
hammer where is
that is there a boss monster there there
must
be or is it
you
die I got no chance
[Music]
give me the helmet I got it I can't
carry anymore damn it I'm just going to
go back there and be like I found it but
I couldn't carry it so can you pick it
up
please oh that's a small Hammer
cute all right I'm
done it still shows the hammer on the
map do I need to be worried about that I
have it with me now let's let's go into
that one room that I ran away from was
it this are they
connecting you know don't want to miss
out on any
secrets nothing here everyone
dead
oh
not enough
M
oh action
baby this is fun I want to bring that
skull cap with me let's get rid of
that
oo other than that I'm
[Music]
good
uhuh so much loot wait it still
continues what is
that J level one is that to go back
level
one is that a shortcut or something like
that yeah I called my character K with
C get some pots yeah I I already have a
lot oh no I guess I
don't
okay uh cute name of vanu yeah it's the
Italian version of
myself I'm K Kiara fer ferar
ferar where where does this go where
does this go was I here before what
nightmarish tortures took place I
already got the helmet why would I go
here is this like
extra what is this where andar
was wait no doesn't she have a different
dungeon this is the this is the road to
andaria oh who what what what I I could
like literally just walk up to her right
now yo
oh I guess she really was also in the
monastery I was actually looking at uh
and
listen I was in Japanese I was uh ego
searching and then you know often
there's a lot of a lot of tweets about
uh fgo kiar but today I found a uh a
tweet of in Japanese about the Italian
Kiara and
um I was I was curious because it's I
don't know it was like something about
Kia on KI on Instagram and I was like H
H so I I clicked the link and I I
realized oh this is not about me it
showed a picture of Kiara a very recent
Instagram picture of her with like a see
through black
top uh and some golden decoration on her
nipples and with that she was in some
kind of cafe or something I don't know
um it was very very interesting uh
choice of
clothing yeah W what is
that
fancy
no that was not me that was not me that
is a different
Kiara you somehow I wish it was
me I wish I had that
confidence I wish can I sell that if I
wanted no I don't cannot be traed
okay I want to give that
to
141 no not
here new outfit
r
so for returning
theic you're
welcome ooh what one of my items all of
my items IMB of magic magical
powers no magic socketed rare unique or
set items no jewelry that's a lot of
rules here
girl don't use that yet yeah I remember
it was something we used it in the alpha
but very later on I
think now can I kill and andario yet or
what's up what's
up bronze ring of regeneration plus 11
to attack rating replenish
life
21 should I replace one of my rings of
this maybe this one maximum
stamina I think
yeah I would say yeah should I sell I'm
going to sell the other
ring
okay plus two two to five fire damage
should I sell this
one it's it's too big I don't want to
carry that in
my seven to eight Maps left for there oh
wow okay I don't want to I don't think I
want to do that right
now H but it would be nice it would be
nice to get Act One finished already in
one
stream s to eight
Maps store your okay I'll I'll keep it
7even to eight maps how long do you
think with my current Pace will that
take me 1 hour
I'm forcing too much what do you
mean what do you
mean two two three 40 minutes
okay 1 40 minutes 1
hour not a
hold less than 30 minutes for
andario to find her or to kill
her
oh my God it's already been full hour I
didn't
realize let's drink some more water you
with po
Alice I want to kill andario
now yeah time did fly time definitely
did fly are you guys ready to join me oh
on the path to kill
andar kfb are you
ready it show me the next
Quest why does it not show me the next
Quest
what how do I get the next
Quest yeah thank you greetings do I have
to oh oh okay now you want to talk that
we Face the demon queen andariel who has
corrupted the Rogue system demon their
ancestral
Monastery this does not it would be
really good
progress so I want to do it text that
andariel and the other lesser evils once
overthrew the three prime evils Diablo
Mesto Bale banish from hell to he
pronounces it like ban here they call
caused mankind Untold anguish and
suffering before they were finally bound
within the soul Stones wait and darel's
presence here could mean that the forces
of hell are once again aligned behind
Diablo and his brothers if this is true
then I fear for us all you must kill her
before the monastery becomes a permanent
Outpost of hell and the Way East lost
forever okay that's what I'm here
for I got it there it is
oh
scary am I better equipped than last
time I
wonder cuz I did I did the do the extra
dungeon I wonder what my level was last
time
too it's been a while I don't
remember let's go I what it
open oh my
God what a nice
welcome oh my
God
she's an is just shooting from a safe
distance now it's very smart very smart
very smart
indeed I don't
[Music]
know huh no sex or uniques yet that is
strange is it
strange oh I'm running out of
arrows we someone drop arrows soon drink
the Mana oh good
idea not strange at all okay well
done
[Music]
just as I asked for it crude long Stu
here I really have to open all those
doors for you
guys oh
man
oh nice
Scrolls if the monsters carry those
Scrolls Scroll of town portal how come
they can't use it and invade our town
game logic be
like it's not like I I need to do
anything else besides activating the
scroll don't give them ideas I probably
don't know what it is I probably just
think it's a shitty piece of paper they
can't read it's too
low oh you can go down here should I
zoom through or should I explore a bit
more kind of want to zoom
through feel like I'm
ready
RTA let Zoom for
oh yeah don't oh this is this is the
good thing about being ranged this is
why I love being ranged in any kind of
game is there a boss monster among you
no not enough Mana okay
let's go through here it's so dark I'm
scared mommy it's it's spoopy season
soon guys it's October
soon very
soon I'm a bit sad that I'm not as young
as I used to be because when I was
younger I did I did uh go
for uh trick or treat a little bit
but really only a little bit I didn't do
it that often
Tri I wish I could have done it more
often but I think in like America for
example it is
practiced uh more than in Europe or like
in Australia at
least I uh not not so
many people/ children do it as I would
say in America at least that's my that's
my impression
from oh my
God from watching like shows like Modern
Family there's literally so
many in Modern Family they have a
Halloween episode in every season Hulk
hm B
Helm you w meate Wait is Anna dead
where's Anna did she get stuck
that's
stupid I really have to like babysit
here like
that right now look at the burp hat
now a Droid only
no what the hell Droid only that's
supposed to be for
me who so
for I knew
it I knew
it uhhuh there was a lot of money in in
one room I saw it from the other side
wait I want to get that money wasn't it
like
was it is that a secret
room is this the room that has like a
secret
entrance or is there like a normal
entrance
are I think I remember this yeah wasn't
there a secret entrance
entrance ah I remember
that
mhm oh hey what does that ring do
uh I want to know
now oh poison length reduced by
25 no thank you where should I go left
or down I'm going to go left
now shiny things yes oh where where did
I get my help
to oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God oh my
god
wow Mana
[Music]
potion right let's get back in here oh
not enough man
wow feels good to level up P pulse
crawler to
Sharp interesting name once again I am
overburdened over
bbon
unbelievable so I just mentioned
uh ah wait a second
I just
mentioned Modern Family right I've been
watching I've been rewatching that
recently but I'm finished again so I
went through Netflix and I finally found
something that's that's new that I
haven't seen yet that's uh good for
um uh uh uh binging binge
watching it's called Super Store no not
squid
game know everyone's about squid game
but I don't that's not I don't know it
looks
scary o fire
[Music]
resist are you got do you guys know
Superstar do you guys know that
shell I've been binging it currently I'm
like in season 3 already it's pretty
good I I would say it's pretty
good I like
it
um it's kind of like a little bit a
little bit reminds me of the
office and
um
there reminds me of the office a little
bit and the there's a character there's
a character
there uh called Zena a f fale character
and she is kind of like a less less
sorry for saying it like this but less
peretic version I'm not saying you know
Dwight is prophetic but in a good way
that's what I'm trying to say and Dena
is like a it's like a Dwight but like in
a less pathetic
way oh my God what the
hell a strong a yeah you know what I'm
talking
about
yeah I there was this episode um of
course this show also likes to pick up
Halloween so there were was a Halloween
episode actually two two Halloween
episodes there's so many Halloween
episodes and Christmas episodes
everywhere H kind of getting sick of
those but anyway the cool thing about
that episode was that even though she
she like normally in the show she
doesn't have
like the sexy Ro like she's definitely
not the sexy
character in the show but for Halloween
they put her in this super hot police
outfit and she looks so good in
it
oh even though she's all about that b
about that
Bas you guys got to watch
it
oh it's it's a very nice police outfit I
must say
what's in here what are you
hiding nothing really
nothing brooklyn99 I already tried
Brooklyn 99 but I honestly I did not
like it oh I'm back here where the hell
is the I went everywhere where is the
continuation
do
I mean it's definitely not as good as
the office but it's at least something
to binge through while I have nothing
else I should do my
stats should I do energy now or not
wasn't a fan of Brooklyn either at least
I'm not the only one I don't know the
the main character pisses me off so much
I
cannot like ignore it I can't parks and
wreck I've seen that one of course
really really good should I do energy
energy not worth it never energy
H okay I'm spreading it Andy I suppose
that's his name he's so annoying like so
obnoxious in a bad way like for example
in the office Dwight is obnoxious but
like he doesn't piss me off on a human
level
you know what I
mean like why do someone who I don't
know I feel like it would be funny to
talk to him but that Andy dude or
whatever his name is in in Brooklyn 99
or the main
character he's just like g a type of
person that I don't want to be friends
with or I can't I literally can't be
friends
live in
RL so
un he mad like so so over over the top
like the way he acts
obviously an
ah okay I found the next level J level
fre a which level is on Dario 5 6
78 we're going
deeper I still have a lot of space in my
inventory language Tal
four wait I'm so
close I'm so close
then all
right oh my God oh my
God oh my
God killing he's right in front of
you what is that g
trap go
trap go come
on
an no now she went around the
corner oh I didn't know you were smart
smart enough to actually go around the
corner can can they attack me yes okay
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
help I need somebody
help give me somebody
help oh and her down Ander down Ander
down oh help
help is she sucking my Mana or what's
going
on oh I almost got it almost almost
there we go there we go there we go
there we go there we go she
did right she
dead oh I did
it that was not a Dario though oh they
do drain
Mana all right die
please better at
moving thank you I'm
trying
uh should I get her back
now I want to explore a little bit more
before I go back I want to fill up my
inventory and then then I'll go
back I hope I won't regret that
decision
C oh I'm running out of
arrows what is this
ooh not enough
Mana man Shrine
Doo I'll take it
though who's
shooting I'm scared I'm scared I'm
scared I don't want to be all
alone bolts I need I need I need
arrows please don't help me run out on
arrows oh wait hav I been in this room
before
oh let me
go bottom
right take
that holdal and buy arrows
no I want them to give me arrows
open
door I am oh there you go I told you I
will get
it bottom ride where you belong no no no
no top right top right
always
whoever says differently doesn't know me
well
enough my foot hurts and I'm sitting on
my foot
ouch ouch ouch ouch I wonder when my
chair is coming I bought that irone
chair I was actually I I finally found
this uh website through my
friend um where you can buy AO Herman
Miller
chairs
o but they didn't have sorry they didn't
have the new one in my size there's like
a re
B version I didn't have it in my size I
wanted the smallest
size and I think if I invest so much in
a proper chair then I want it to be the
A fitting size you
know I think that makes sense to get the
proper
size uh but I I ordered it anyway no
wait I think
I'm not sure but I ordered a chair that
I was only half happy with cuz there was
like nothing better available on the
website but then then the customer
service messaged me and told me yo we
have this chair we have the newest chair
in your size the newest aor chair in
your size in the smallest size so if you
want to go for that you just got to send
us more money kind of sounded like a
scam but I'm pretty sure it's legit
so now I'm getting the the actual size s
with the
newest newest uh revamped
version I was about to to buy the old
one which apparently even though it's
from when from 2000 something or so or
even before
2000 apparently it's still like a pretty
damn good
chair yeah I I I I interpret to to as
well as in order to have this proper
chair really work Wonders on my back I
have to have it in the right
size I'm looking forward to it they're
going to
apparently
uh uh deliver it already like all
assembled together it's going to come in
a huge box oh
hello
me is this where I came from nor way
inner cloer
oh oh yeah getting
closer here we
are well does that mean we went a level
higher
again oh
portal find the Waypoint found
it
easy I am overburdened should I go back
yes okay if my inventory is that full
I'll go back what I didn't even need the
portal the portal is just right there
I'll revive my
girl horrible weather here is always
600 oh wow so much
money two
two oh yeah let me talk to Kane
greetings
greetings also let me greetings
greetings repair
bulk selling this to you
and can I like combine them oh I did
okay the boots are they better than
mine
no
nope fire resist plus 10 sounds good if
I had nothing else waa those are
cool I who uses throwing
axes had the inventory in DIA too is
very tiny yes a barbarian oh well those
are
nice those are
nice unfortunately I don't play
Barbarian why thing resist 7 to life I
think I'll sell
that getting magic i ooh
W should I keep that in my inventory
sounds
nice should I keep this in my inventory
keep keep magic find 9%
yo
yes I should sell this
one done
ah oh
okay was there anything I wanted from
anara greetings greetings maybe
portals no no no need when are you going
to sell bigger potions though in act too
or
what oh I I have to wear
it amulance oh wait what is my current
one oh oh okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay I put it I put the other one
in my
stash okay
uh
okay ready to go act two cells life
potions that's still tiny as hell but
okay oh that's a big door oh my God Is
this where and darel is no I don't think
so this is not where and darel
is who's uh even deeper than
that what the
hell I see it why is he hiding behind
this there you
go really difficult to aim when I don't
see him see
him this looks like where andariel is
kind of but I guess yeah tatom's level
four I'm on level
fre but like not in the catacombs
anymore I don't
know what is everyone's Class of choice
in Diablo
assassin Paladin Paladin
sorceress oh what barely any Amazon
what's
up assassin lot of assassin Necromancer
Paladin
Barbarian sorceress why is why is Amazon
so
unpopular and Drew it no one literally
no one said drew it
how
sad where do I
go
oh no don't hurt
[Applause]
her
nice
oh golden
armor no my girl is dead
[Applause]
again we were too close to the
enemy oof big
oof oh I want to
identify
W oh but my defense is much higher it's
double but this one has much more fancy
effects oh but also low way lower
durability what did you guys say
okay enhanced defense is same percent
and fast hit recovery is also same
percent give this one to mercenary
defense doesn't do oh okay then I'll
take this and give the other one to my
mercenary
maybe effects over armor all right all
right I run around a little bit without
my
friend
I am
over
how
yes tomorrow I have an early stream by
the way are you guys going to be there I
was actually hoping that I can get
people from different t zones from like
sea time
zones tomorrow you guys are going to be
there too how early look at my schedule
and you will
know there was a body can I pick that
body up no I'll be there thank you I
will this place is Eerie is she here
wait which level is this level one oh oh
my God it's still a long way to
go
n
zooming if only I could be like hen in
Henry Stickman collection where I
randomly always choose the right
[Music]
path but I also I don't want to anymore
I don't want to skip too many rooms
because there's so much items so so much
money everywhere literally
everywhere that was epic I don't know
what how I did
that 4:00 a.m. for me oh well you can
watch the
archive you're welcome to watch the
archive archive is always an option 7
EST easy you'll be my
alarm I'll be like K that's literally
how I start my stream so it's a good way
to say good morning I am stuck
that was not the right
way how
about how about
here and then
here oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God oh my God they're fast they're so
fast oh
wait why is what the did you guys
see that not enough M wa where
is okay okay chill chill chill chill
chill chill chill I was trying to go to
the other room to chill for a moment I
am overburdened goblins or
whatever the hell they
are
ratman
I can't carry any give
me wait a second let me rearrange what
is with him what is his
issue now I should be able to pick it up
oh uh okay uh wait second shift shift
shift shift shift shift
shift okay uh I should go back
though going
back sorry I let her die again The
Sisterhood welcomes I know coming quite
often
recently and I apologize for letting
your people die so often it's not on
purpose I promise what is this
she's getting used to she likes seeing
me right oh wait I was going to give uh
my friend oh yes she still only has
white armor here this is for you I'll
put that to good use I trust you I trust
you with
that yes yes yes yes yes yes all
right going
back level four
is oh another
one kill him kill
him I need
M good good work Nice cleaning
up
nice it's
way what was that sound ah you level
up should I go this way no
ouch
I'll go I'll go top right and hope I
hope it's the right way there's a help
shrine at least
something it looks like it could be the
right
way woo yeah
baby
next next
level and we'll scale on exploding arrow
again KAC comes level
two I feel like I'm missing out on a a
lot of cool items makes me feel
bad energy is not the right but the work
it might be a good idea huh the way I
play the game energy might uh energy
might be a good idea is that what you're
saying everyone else says no though wayo
on this floor oh then I have
to I'm going to try to look
properly everywhere until I find it
thank you for the
hint or non try hards energy is fine
Vitality is the most
important
okay am I try
hard stop stop man burn
no okay we
are going this way
buffering no you two please come
back we're back oh that was a short
buffering actually yesterday while I was
making the lasagna I was watching ena's
stream the whole time and then at some
point you guys maybe were watching too
at some point her uh YouTube YouTube or
like everything YouTube crashed on her
and then she could move her body anymore
it
oh I kept on watching though cuz the
lasagna the process of making lasagna
took me quite
long I I I didn't mind that she wasn't
able to move because I wasn't really
watching anyway she's nice to listen
to very nice to listen
to what do you think of Bastion well
actually yesterday was the first time I
kind of like watched her Bastion stream
longer but I wasn't really watching I
was really only listening so I don't
know I like the Aesthetics of
it what low quality the Dirk what who's
Dirk who is
Dirk I like the Aesthetics of it
e
disgusting keep
know how streate that
dog another Hawk Helm I get so many of
those
what a type of dagger
oh I see let me get some more
potions
it looks like a cute game and apparently
it wasn't very long
either so if I ever ran out of games I
might consider
it but there's many games that I'm
considering so so I don't
know
MH where is the portal I'm not finding
it ah there it is
ha I just was talking about it
me all
right all right but it's a dead end so I
suppose continuing on the other side of
the map Oh wrong room way point
nice
nice Orie yes I'm planning on playing
that at some point because I mentioned
it before but there the game is made by
people from my country and there's not
many games made from by people from my
country especially not like good ones
and ay is very very well known actually
for being a very good
game and I would like to
proudly show you guys that game if you
if you don't know about it yet but I uh
I think it's really well
known
did you guys play that anyone here who
played
Orie Orie I know a pretty sad game has a
nice
story yes yes I played it me me
oh Kenna oh I do want to play Kenna but
wasn't Kenna um PS5
only and I don't have my PS5 yet but
once the PS5 arrives we can do
that
I don't know though if it's a good
streaming game though think K is f PS5
oh yeah it sounded like an
exclusive K is all platforms what what
all platforms as in PC as well
or a dead
end
[Music]
last Garden Oh
Ohan thank you
free pretty much free Super Chat blast
simulator is apparently Australian
what what
really am am was playing a game from my
country and actually enjoyed it a lot
and it was a hit is that
true is that true I almost can't believe
it also apparently this was not the way
to
go it was all just a big dead end how do
I
here oh my
[Music]
God
lots of great games come from y Kaza no
no no wait you mean is there a game
Studio that's called your Kasa what you
mean from my what what was that
teleportation try carry anymore found a
special
one going back
once what you mean my Kasa or
suasa first Trident
hello
hello besides ory I don't know of
any actually good games that are worth
mentioning from my
country I would be surprised 7 to love
can I sell
[Music]
this
heal
stamina cost level free charge
oo uh
no Gothic but Gothic is
Germany I wouldn't really count that as
one of
mine oh BL and play yeah that was that
was a German speaking people but I think
wasn't that
Switzerland
thank you John sell it what about these
did I wear
them
St I read 10% faster chat
rate go chat 10%
faster so
okay
Zoom let's
go okay we'll go here
chat wait I could sell that I'm not a
Caster let me sell that sorry chat good
evening you're already fast enough on
your own is my thingy
full
oh
going to sell that
too don't want to waste my space here
haven't died in a long time in this game
huh I'm getting
better let's
Panic let's
go oh oh yeah now the Trident there's a
trident here
this yes Trident let me look at it
who wait is that for me wait which class
uses a trident is that like a jab like a
spear C Str 38 W who would use that
me
yes
Amazon uses right
oh oh oh well it's just
oh what did I get myself
into holy
kill him quick not
enough what the what the
what the
how are they all in such a tiny ass
room damn
it oh
okay oh my God it's a
massacre oh my my finger is tired of
clicking the mouse well you be go
wow
wow M oh Mass Massac how how else do you
pronounce
it Massacre Mass Massacre
M don't make fun of
me
oh I found the next
level level three next level is andariel
O Crystal
Sword oh the ghouls they say uh the old
time I looks so pretty but it's just
white almost there almost there almost
there almost there almost there
guys oh
hello steals life no no no
no no no no
[Music]
no I need arrows
soon if if if Anna has like
endless arrows could you give me some
please please pretty
please oh there's a lot of fire over
there
oh thank you thank you
soon oh no no no and that hits hard oh
did I oh yeah I saw an elite
monster I
can't what what can you not what I can't
I can't what do you
mean impossible what what what what do
you mean I can't I can't oh I got no
Arrow can't look be more clear
lady God okay I need
arrows there really no arrows
overburdened
mag mag
sh let me take the breastplate with
me
[Music]
for I can do that I can arrange
that there you
go oh wait there's uh normal ones
healing healing healing I am over
burdened okay yes I'm going
back every so often stay a while and
listen thank
you
uh going to sell some
stuff greetings no no no no no no
no
5,000 cell
value
wow
wow oh defense is worthless wa should I
sell it sell an act to why act
two sell
it
really
why do I wait until after I get more
money for it
then
okay is
that probably not better what she's
using Crimson
Trident sounds
cool okay I'm going to put it in my
stash
but I need
arrows wait are you selling
arrows good to see
you
oh that's pretty
cheap
DK why do I get more money in act two in
infl inflation inflation inflation
inflation
infl in infl infl
inflation inflation my right c as always
why do I do that why do I do that let's
do should I go for explosion I'm going
to still go for that
one economy
hello love that you are ESL what does
that even
mean English Second Language that must
be
it why do you love that I'm glad you
love
it I'm
glad
o I think there's
a many people who dislike it but hey my
English is not that bad that I
understand that like I think I would
probably react the same way if I would
watch someone's stream and they're
speaking whatever language that they're
using in their stream really really
like badly I think that would put me off
as
well but if it's on my level I'm sorry
but my English is good
okay I don't think my
English is that
bad every now and then I might forget
some words
but I think it's
decent why did I change
weapon what the happened with fire
arrow stop
running oh I wouldn't say it's better
than ative speakers you're complimenting
me like a like a Japanese
person too
kind why are you running English is
native thank you you know what it's not
native but it's pretty damn
close I would also say my pronunciation
most of the time is also nothing you can
complain about right
right right
right right I can't I can't complain
about
it sometimes there's some funny
pronunciations but like stuff like biomi
and page I'm doing on
purpose other things maybe
not yeah I wouldn't have gotten into I
live English if my English was
thankfully see my my uh me being a
good student in English classes in
school it paid
off
I wouldn't be in whole life at all cuz
there is no whole life German that I
could um be in instead of whole life
English there would be no place for
me so good that I was a good stud and
more useful than math you know what yes
when I was younger and was really bad at
math I was hoping
that that that wouldn't you
know backfire at someday no what what
it's not really backfiring this like I
was I was
expecting that it would have some kind
of negative effect on me but nope nope
nope not at all being bad at maap had
absolutely no effect on me besides not
being able to finish the school that I
wanted to finish okay that's a pretty
big effect because if I would have
finished at
school I would have been on the on a
more creative path of life
now God damn it I feel like I'm really
far away from the next
level damn
it
oh at least I got two two * two right oh
the
uh I haven't tried I haven't tried to
say the I'm my for a long long
time yo it better be on the right side
don't disappoint me
yo Next Level please somewhere
here
please oh this level is
huge what the
oh amulet always
open the caskets always open them oh I
told you always open
them nice item Kaman
oh found it
y will she be right there immediately no
way oh my God okay yes that's my plan is
she right there no I'm looking
out two rooms first oh yeah B
quit am I ready for
this wait maybe I'll rearrange this
here
I don't feel like I'm ready poison
damage open
portal
okay wait we did so well last time time
we did so well last time I should just I
just need to move around just need to
move around a
lot and I might be getting a level in uh
level up in between so that will be some
free free HP and stuff
antidote should I go by an
antidote really weak to fire
okay did I use an antidote last time I
think I
did let's go by an
an but that takes up a spot in my
potions right
o the order welcomes you oh I need to go
to an idle
[Music]
meeting uh anti anti
do yes yes
yes
yes should I go
now
no stop
[Music]
it I don't know how often I will need it
okay I'll go I'll go real
quick
[Music]
for
I'm back
you
sure okay
okay well the worst thing that can
happen is I'll die and I'll nail it on
the second try good
day
but I put my money here
and
uh that
there wait so if I drink one antidote
potion take my CHS oh good idea I guess
the amulet no wait the the
ches fire
resist let's take
this if I drink one does it let
does
the do I have like a resistance for
certain time amount of time or oh fire
damage fire resist I don't know does
that make sense probably
not it Stacks 30 seconds of resistance
and it Stacks
oh
it cures
poison
uhuh
what poison resistance for 30 seconds
okay it Stacks resistant duration but
still gets poison
what drink it before it Buffs your
poison okay drink if I can drink a
couple beforehand and it makes sense
then I'll buy a few
more uh
yes
okay how much is maximum
stack does someone
know this Overkill yeah
probably it's probably a little bit
Overkill
H I'll I'll once she uh drops items when
she dies and drops items I'll have to um
go back to the city to clear my
inventory anyway there's no limit on the
stack like 10 oh okay let's go
okay oh I'm scared is she right
there
is she is she there should I drink it
now is she like
there leave a portal oh
yeah not
yet
oh clear the first round
okay
hello ah nervous but I can do it she was
she was surprisingly easy last time I
think I think oh level up nice good
timing for a level up good timing good
[Music]
timing ew that's disgusting who wants
soup who wants some
soup
all right during the fight would have
been a little bit better for a boost of
HP and so on but at least now I have
time to stat so should I put it on fire
arrow
or cuz I'll be using fire arrow during
the
fight or more crates yeah that's a good
idea maybe
too okay because I do I I do like the
idea of more crits okay okay this is
where she is should I drink
now should I drink it
now boss fight let's
go yes okay I'm I'm nervous y okay okay
okay
that knock knock who's
there
oh oh
oh oh my friend is
dead
I wish they would automatically go back
into the the the
sash why don't they do
that
I is this
multitasking this this
multitasking I hate
this she's a walking the park she's
taking her out for a little walk yeah
B
stop
no let me
[Music]
move this
made is there anything cool
here what is that I am overburdened what
is that I think I only got that I
can't use
but a sash sash is nice what is a smoked
sphere I can't use that Heart letter
armor all right all
right
y sash is unique
Y is that
good that was
very wait if I go for that portal what
happens to my old
portal oh what what no no don't don't
make trouble now you trouble maker
trouble
makeer what happen will still be there
Old Port says okay let's
go a he surely wants to talk to me of
course he wants this is a great Victory
indeed but many more battles await I
will accompany you on your journey thank
you what assistance I hope my chat will
accompany on more battles in the future
as well there seeking something in the
desert I'm afraid that this nightmare
will not end until you find what it is
that he seeks what could it be I don't
even
know all right identify that what
what is a sash it's green why is it so
ugly Lenore l
l it's like poison grein makes sense
maybe because she was all about
poison uh plus 152 Mana regenerate Mana
all right I do have a struggle with
Mana or resistance is five plus one to
light radius okay that sounds like
something that's probably better for
like what sorceress or so but I'll take
it that's better than what I had until
now
y regeneration plus 30 that's pretty
good that's that's pretty
strong a good
sash put all that back um
ooh oh it is also better than what I'm
wearing now enhanced defense plus two to
life cold resist uhhuh repairs one
durability in oh it's similar actually
my old one has more effects it has a
fire
resist where the armor no I'm selling it
the old one actually is better maybe
it's just the defense is better on this
one but you guys said defense doesn't
matter
[Music]
surprisingly Rejoice Rejoice we owe you
a debt we can never repair that's true
indeed in time we will be able to
rebuild our order all our thanks go with
you my friend
yay I will give to friend but friend is
dead cruel picket
vlge what is
that what who wears that me who wears
that uh me is that a spare
I can't use this oh I can't too
bad I'm going to keep it for mercenary
yeah the the Hat cruel
song well I what you guys think about
that ball did I do well I didn't panic I
was very calm I was very cold collect
it calm and collect it as all things
should be yes shut up which one is
mine
Kiara which one is
mine I'll take this one that was the
wrong one but
okay I'm just here oops I'm just here to
pick up some it
nothing here special stuff is here oh oh
my
God money cing cing
cing it went well boss was surprisingly
that's the same thing that I fought last
time
yeah oh Sapphire anthy balanced axe
tripped
Emerald that's pretty much about it on
cool stuff
wa more money here cing cutting
cutting aist special what does an
amethist do 10 poison damage you no wait
that's an
emerald ah attack rating plus 80
nice ah I guess uh cuz this one isn't
chipped it's like full it's perfect a
perfect amethyst cold damage nice nice
I'll bring with me a wor plate can I
bring over
no okay leaving check top
wing top wing of the
room did I miss
something top Wing oh wait you mean the
dead broke
oh
wait oh
wait
see there's not much here though is
there
no nothing really I
think I think our work is done
here nice nice fight noise fight mate
I can't carry anymore I'm out of here
good
evening you want to talk to me to sorry
for killing hers killed kind of for
andariel wasn't me mourn the L of our
dear sisters but at least now we can get
on with our
lives I may have Miss Jud cinematic yeah
we're going to watch the Cinematic when
we go
to and testament to the noble Spirit
which has inspired our order for
Generations he Farewell My
friend okay thank you for talking to
me return to R to take the Caravan e
what about this one why is this not oh
this won't be really completed until I
IMB something huh return to Ravi to take
the who is r who is
that who is
war daddy oh my God what is this with
the chicken
what is it with the
chicken where is
war the
camp he didn't show up the Caravan is
prepared we may now Journey Eastward to
loot Golan loot
Goan go
east act
two video
time last time this was a I think an Old
Quality mountains and into the vast
deserts of broken
lands as the days passed my companion
told me of himself that he had once been
a great warrior is this revamped and
that a
darkin burden now waigh heavily upon him
looks pretty looks like Star Wars we
traveled for an eternity across that
Aron Wasteland how oh my God it died no
I couldn't say he died always a dark
cloud to follow us just I like that game
finally the journey ended we climbed the
last
Bridge there below us lay
our
destination The Shining
Jewel
pretty with a great sea
Beyond with so being we made camp that
last
night perhaps it was the warm Desert
Wind or the sound of the ocean but for
the first time in many weeks I
slept however the dream dreams return
but these were clearly not my own I
beheld a vision of a great man the Mage
T Rashia you were there too tyel I
remember you this Dre his Brethren had
caughted a great Demon baale Lord Of
Destruction had been set loose upon the
world they attempted to imprison the
demon within a sacred stone
[Music]
yet when their attempts failed tashes
selflessly B he just closed the door
with his wingies
that's tentacle
Wings he instructed his Brethren to find
him within tomb very
unad there to wrestle with the demon for
all
eternity
now you know what I seek Marius don't
this is my
brother sleep now we set out with the
dawn the next morning we walked over the
hill toward lot
gain I had no idea then
of the horrors that were in store for me
I think I remember during the alpha we
were watching the old cinematic so this
is updated
noise
M greetings greetings and with that for
today I am done I'm glad we cleared the
whole act one today very productive it
only took me 5 hours and 20
minutes not very long at all no no no
all right save an
exit good job T thank you level
15 I didn't plan on playing for this
long today but yeah once you're right in
front of andariel who can stop no
one Justice needs to be
served can you play the ACT once in a I
didn't I didn't even get to see that I
don't know how do I play it when how do
I ah here a this
one we didn't watch this one let's watch
it I missed it
too
Marius Marius sounds
[Music]
familiar
speed
cute so
fluffy what it looks like real life is
this
CG that looks a bit more like
Sig yeah W it looks so realistic
though
real than real
life wo it's so crisp the lightning is
so
good oh who is
you are you Soo Marius at last oh those
are the two who went for the desert
no oh
is
yes yes no it reminds me of a Smo
you I should have known you travel in
the
SKU there they're always
watching I've been searching for you for
a long time
mice I was rather beginning to think you
didn't want to be
found oh forgive me darel please he has
similar Vibes wasn't my fault really
desperate not your fault sad lonely man
tell me mes how was it not your
fault it The Wanderer is this a path yes
it
was
wer my days Rogue Citadel seemed so long
ago I sought Refuge from my memories in
the company of other outcasts High the
mountain complicated the Eastern
Gate he
dead
good job carrying the the F sleep for
days at a time waiter for when I dreamt
the memories would return oh my God
memories of the
monasteries and the
evil which you claimed BR memories I
couldn't tell the difference
anymore
oh I wouldn't want to go to sleep if I
had dreams like
that nightmares evil from my
dreams followed me at my
heels how had he found me
here how could this broken shell of a
man barely able to carry the weight of
his own
sword be the burning
teror will drove me to hide here thanks
for the membership
welcome oh he's
mad he seemed to why you mad bro to have
Demons of
his struggled to
contain now funny
e
what think that's really
funny he was
[Music]
losing
e oh that's the protagonist of the first
game the one who's going insane toing
that the terror the destruction need the
evil I witnessed how else could I
explain
them were these the demons from my
dreo were they
born within the
[Applause]
wonder I don't know what's going
on am I supposed to know what's going
[Music]
on only if I played the first
one
[Applause]
okay
wow
wow why did that just remind me of this
game where there's this child uh what
was it called who who lets everything go
up in Flames or so um what was that
called called that
game that demon
child you know what Lucius yes yes yes
Lucifer Lucius
Lucifer why did I
follow
my why do things happen as they do in
dreams all I know is that when he
beckoned I had to follow him him and
from that
moment we traveled together okay
okay
always into the
East
W Diablo
resurrected very impressive cutscene SL
cinematic very
impressive I didn't even see that one
during the alpha I only watched the a
journey the other one I I didn't even
realize I don't I I don't know if I was
able to see it if I wanted
to really cool oh look at me being
strong and being in this new place with
which name I
forgot wow those character names what's
what what what's the
problem it's my my Italian other uh
self yes loot Gan m
I think um there was a funny time today
where I was struggling a lot and dying
constantly and having no potions and no
money but then later on it balanced
itself out and things were going much
much better yeah thanks for the stream
it was a treat thank you for watching
act two and three are much harder well
well don't worry I I plan to have
collaborations for act two and act three
Final Bosses whoever we will be fighting
I do not
know um but I think it would be nice
from now on it just really depends like
how fast the others play and like uh if
if like they will have to catch up or
I'll have to catch up catch
up uh yeah it's going to be a bit
difficult to adjust
that
[Music]
speed but I'm surprised Lami is playing
the game maybe I could join ban Z and
Lami Senai in a session if they're going
to play it
regularly
is anyone else in h life Japan saying
that they're going to play Diablo
2 or only ly and ban Senai so far thir
wheel let's go wait shami and takam
actually works cuz like Callie said she
wants to play
it
yo that's a good idea and we can all
like Ci and I speak Japanese so we can
communicate
properly
oh
then then I'm not F Wheeling then I'm
not F
Wheeling okay okay okay okay I'll think
about it I'll discuss it thank you guys
for watching we'll read super chats now
I don't know if I can finish them all
though it's already half 11: p.m. oh
dear let's go to my
[Music]
office
wait a second let me exit you don't hear
the music do
you uh do we hear it
now let's let's play this
one okay oh wait the chat need to revive
the
chat come back to
me Triple now double okay then I mute
this finish
away okay okay okay um I stopped at a
really random place
somewhere H does anyone remember the
name where I stopped last
time I wasn't feeling good so I had to
kind of quit it
abruptly uh uh
uh Jim Tracy oh thank you oh okay okay
okay scroll scroll scroll scroll scroll
we have to read the members only super
chats and the Minecraft super chats and
the last little little teeny tiny bit
from uh where I left off that's a
lot you guys went a little bit crazy in
the members only
stream
oh wait microphone microphone what's
going
on
placement need to fix it sorry are you
okay now
microphone H JY Tracy I guess in the
arft K right is that where is that where
I left
off there we go did I but Jim Tracy oh
might have donated more than once did I
leave did is that one that I that I read
before that story Corner does someone
know didn't you stop in Minecraft
it oh the bank
cab
oh
oh I was still reading oh not not the B
collab the mama Tony
collab the mama Tony collab oh oh oh I
was so close to finishing reading that
let me try to find Jim
Tracy is it this
one does someone know what was before
Jim Tracy you gy still weird
e
impossible I'm fine
okay that's a oh thank you okay then I
know where I am Jim Tracy thanks for the
pinky wait let me put up the thumbnail
one more
time
okay reading super
chats ignore whatever you just
saw I'm
reusing font layers so that I can keep
the specific
formatting all right thanks for the M
Minecraft Trilogy it was awesome Fenix
stand is looking so cool now you two did
great work while having a ton of fun
this was definitely a legendary series
with a pair of legendary vers thank
you yes I'm very glad I got help from my
mommy otherwise the Phenix would look
very boring and I don't know when I
would
ever if I would have ever tried to
renovate it on my
own not sure if I would have given it a
try probably not at
all thank you Jim C for the pinky cotton
D opportunity D FR d a primate brain D
black Chan D Sly M Dana
pet opportunity d g thank you for the
pinky do you have any plans to add to
your list of macra songs you sing
including original macr
uh you mean for the for the Kad that
came after
that sorry I didn't sing I only sing
lion I did sing at least one ma
song I do want I do love the Delta maros
Delta songs so next time I'll try to if
I don't forget I'll try to put in some
Delta songs
yeah sorry for not enough
m
I want to sing some some of the Cheryl
songs as well though an official game a
Dan motion danoo Dan and Dr hell d l Kur
thank you for the pinky it's been about
a year now since I discovered you my oi
oh and the rest of H during this year
you've given me so much joy and
entertainment and I'm looking forward to
season 2 and beon thank you I'm looking
forward
too thank you for staying so long and
and continuing to stay with me thank you
I appreciate that very much I'm glad
you're part of the journey yeah hope we
can make many more memories together
thank you
Lucy
H Korean Super
Chat
Korean
k p come thank you black FR and D for
the pinky hey you want an entrylevel
horror game try Spooky's House of jump
scares it starts off easy and has cutesy
art style that will ease you into the
JRE please don't be scared to play with
GAA you don't have to beat Outlets just
one stream oh yeah I mean I wasn't
planning on beating
it I have I have a feeling if I try to
play that I'll probably lose my mind
after half half an hour and ended after
half an
hour never heard of that game though
Spooky's House of jump scares I don't
like jump scares can we
play what the hell I'm I'm not even why
is it so un
[Music]
un
stable um I I think I would prefer a
horror game that's not focused on jump
scares but just like
being all or generally
spoopy but I just looked it up and it
does have a a cute uh what is that ghost
she looks
cute oh then there's something that
looks like
Sak yeah it looks it looks very
uh
simple kind of
cute
thank you for the
recommendation looking for the top D
black and D
lone naivity
d g l navity squiggling must d pbn
k lone navity I don't know how to say
your name than Luigi's mansion that's
not a horror game but I love Luigi's
Mansion
but that's not a horror
game not really
G why is my window so laggy my Super
Chat window did I load too many
messages Mo Lo nity
D it was hard to Luigi yeah okay so poor
Luigi Mario Mario where are
youba
y my God this window is so laggy what
the
hell meme dude than M 87 than soon L
naivity than soon meme dude thanks for
the pinky and Henry Stickman chat pick
this trct K why it wasn't the right one
sh
no later on Chad pick spirit for K I
haven't watched JoJo chat
F oh the disappointment of me not
watching Jojo I guess I need to catch up
everyone loves JoJo everyone loves
JoJo I'm
[Music]
sorry
it would be weird if you had watch this
really
opportunity you for the red than you
soon so it's true kfb is getting shut
down by the help and cuz rats are
infesting the F
uh
no
no there are no rats at can of
te no no rats no
no
no here the rat is being eaten by frogy
Ara
no she's not there she's too small you
can't see
her thank you m nice to see you thank
you so
[Music]
much spank dly D JP d m
dudos
motion m cat song for K okay sorry I
read that too late huh that is that
profile picture James
Cordon he looks so nice looks so small
in that picture okay I'm dazzled d lion
Quinn D Smokey winds D Ginger Ranger 13
D meme d d l navity d GD D me dude
thanks for the pinky okay your hat
doesn't fully match your head's rotation
and now I can't and see it all what do
you
mean
you what do you mean I think it fits you
mean but that was when I was wearing my
new outfit with this
hat you mean it doesn't rotate properly
I don't think
so I'm not sure what you mean
though he's right no he's
[Music]
not I think it's done pretty
well H Vincent Dan M Dan Christopher d
lity d and Ty D thank
you now we're going to why did it go all
the way back to the top why we are going
to read the kok Super
Chat
y let's read the K super chats from when
was that Sunday
Saturday love the K so much thank
you thank
you I I just realized I also have to H
still do holot talk stuffff
so I really shouldn't read too
many okay motion Jacob
Dominic stupid
lag stop
laging D Elvis Anthony pill NEX 604 D
green W thank you for the pinky honestly
I kind of love how every K of people
ever is a 50/50 split perfectly balanced
as all things should be it's quite funny
yeah it just doesn't help me with
decision
making it doesn't help
me but in the end it it lets me you know
make decisions myself instead of relying
on you guys so in some way I guess I
guess that's cool
too
[Music]
deoc
democ
um barley is that
barley
[Music]
barley yes
Bary finy
come thank you so
much hi T thank you for the red super
chat big kiss for you tyy you left no
comment with it for still thank you for
watching my C out okay I hope you
enjoyed it and my song
Choices yes yes it wasn't all around the
K at least in the unarchived portion so
I hope that was something to enjoy for
everyone kak D
Jif D story cor Dy D captain and d d pbn
k dang Outcast D happy belated birthday
J Monkey D memo D Mr cast B bigs than
for the
pinky say it with me Kiana you are the
best Idol around in deut you said you
wanted to save Yo's Dream well let me
tell you that his dream's doing better
better than
ever thanks for giving everyone a fun
cheerful performance George Queen you're
welcome let me get
a a cough
drop this time I'm I'm not going to spit
it out
[Music]
though he and Yago hung up what when
voal
where
okay Eternal happiness upon your bird
body keep being you and thanks for
making out day thank you thank you for
being here watching my streams Mr
casic thank you for being so # woke #
Yol you play Mario Go
every couple of Saturdays wow you got
those collections
huh nice can you tell him to give our
Minecraft server an update next time
you're going
golfing please
please Lan naivity than M
[Music]
than nauta come San thank you
and happy belated
[Music]
birthday thank you for the
pinky
p d Sean 314 UK D spanking thank you for
the red super
chat thanks for wonderful weekend again
love listening to you sing we are having
our vegan drumsticks in support and
we're raving oh thank you totally vegan
thank you for waving your drumsticks I
like to imagine one
day maybe something like a something
like a concert again like a to meat
where I actually saw everyone with their
with their hands and their light
sticks that was wonderful I want to
experience that again for
sure
oh have you guys seen that um D Comey D
Comey is happening
again and so far Callie and GAA and Ena
got
announced no way that I would be missing
right but I can't
spoiler
I just did know I didn't no
no no no no
no yes yes yes
yes no no no no no no no
no I said yes by accident but no no
no I said nothing I can even confirm nor
deny
yes but it's going to be an online
convention that anyone can see again
like last time so you guys can hang out
with us on Twitch us sorry I I mean with
CI
and good uh you know I say us because
it's you know we're a family I say it uh
representing
them okay I'll continue read reading
now and night Andale thank you for three
pinkies thank
you and the long message let's read hi K
thank you again for your streams I love
your voice I hope your headache from
yesterday is gone oh yes that is gone my
living situation update I managed to get
a r and PR oh oh you were the one who
was like who didn't have a room uh like
an apartment and was just about to
move oh y that's great but because it's
on such a short notice I have to share a
bathroom with a guy Etc it's not ideal
since I've had bad experience with men
before especially after they
accidentally found out they like other
oh oh you go that way oh yeah
okay please keep holding your thumbs
down for me oh oh h
h n
hold I'm I'm I don't know like what how
the guy is like but I'm sure he's he's
going to be a a guy who can respect
boundaries and and uh you guys can you
know hang out with one another on a on a
cool friendship
level without any any anxiety or
whatsoever yeah just got to got to be
open to it too I think I understand your
concern but you I'm I'm I hope I hope it
will be fine I think it will be
fine please keep holding your thumbs
down for me the Australian way since I
am a bit worried for my own safety
commuting takes 10 hours I'm looking
into other OP 10 hours Oh you mean uh if
you weren't taking that room in prag
holy well yeah that's not an
option I'm going to work hard toward my
dreams are not only me but also other
people can be proud of me even uh though
some told me I let them down by being
born different hope your dreams coming
come true
to oh thank you well first of all it's
great that you found a place um you
don't have to stay there forever so just
keep an eye out for other
places and I'm sure I'm sure you'll find
a better living situation I don't know
how the how it is frag if there's if
it's difficult to
find apartments
but yeah med school Med schol that
sounds amazing so good
luck good luck for everything I believe
in you yeah
F thank you for your
support if anything happens let me know
I'll go there in person and Bonk Bonk
anyone who tries to hurt
you yes I'll be your parttime
Warrior Ty thank you for the pinky just
the usual declaration that you're
amazing your singing singing is amazing
and this stream is amazing as always
thank you the here to the best boss best
Idol and best Fenix kfp does offer the
best benefits package makes her
amazingly generous
BS mhm
yes yes very generous boss I am
indeed
uh thank you for acknowledging it you
sound very loyal good good hasht woke
good hasht Yol I I can feel it you pray
to Taki Ki every
[Music]
day everyone's getting benefits
everyone who joins the membership at
least membership
benefits not a cult not a cult I'm glad
you enjoyed my K I always try to choose
songs that I like but can also be
enjoyable to you guys preferably songs
that I I think you guys
know every every once in a while I
squeez in some songs that you guys
probably don't know to have a good
mixture to be educating and enjoyable at
the same time educating and
relatable yes need to educate you guys
on Idol songs and stuff
yeah thank you tyon Isel Ram thank you
for the red super chat sending lots of
love because you are great and you
deserve it thank
you I have received your love
I send it back
double
pun thank you for the pinky sticker
D
[Music]
sh app D Fri screw Dan KY thank you for
the pinky sticker another
sticker thank you thank you thank you
thank you feel
[Music]
Le Mr par naked chicken d d VI D thank
you for the red super
chat your voice is so insanely good
thanks for singing good oh yeah finally
sign that song K is always a highlight
for me thank you for doing more of them
since recently my oi is the best idle ha
thank
you I practiced so that I can finally
give you guys some new songs
that one that one was difficult I was
actually also trying and practicing the
um your name songs Kim
NAA uh but but I couldn't
sorry yeah very
difficult
[Music]
Co
red wh's range is a little tricky yeah
and I don't know I just had some
troubles with trying to learn it I
couldn't learn it that quickly that's
for
sure and yeah I think it was also an
issue of key and then I I found a
different Kad that was a different key
but uh I think that was like uh like a
piano version
only and I didn't really want to use
that K
version red Wims red red Wims very
difficult
[Music]
will there be a German again oh in the
future sure but the thing is like I
already last time I already
sang a lot of the Like official ones
that already like that officially exist
because they were made by um the the
actual um you know people in charge and
that not fanmade um German openings so
if I were to do it again I think it
would have to be a lot of uh fan-made
German openings which I'm sure is still
uh
interesting there's only a couple more
that are not fanmade that I haven't sung
yet I feel like
H uh but the rebroadcast from the last
one will be next week during my little
break I will be rebroadcasting
here in English there probably more
official opening versions in English
more than German ones I
suppose
MDM R
[Music]
pbn and looking for the top py for the
pinky God knows cover with pomu funds
you can just put that yourself together
you can download both audios and then
arrange them together I love this by the
way your idol talk the other day was
hella cute K Nikki aren't as much of an
idol turbo wee as you calling me a turbo
weeb wait he changed
it he changed it back to spanking
ham I didn't
realize I'm a turble oh my God
we
no no
I'm not an Omega we if anything I'm a
turbo
we or or Delta
weep whatever that
means as you H but where is the fun in
only having friends with matching taste
plus you get cute and nerdy in those
moments who are you calling a nerd you
nerd you're a ner
looking for the nerd I found him I found
him right here
police I would like to file a report
this nerd called me a nerd even though
he's the
[Music]
nerd yeah we're all we're all kind of
nerds are
we no you
no
e
[Music]
da
[Applause]
[Music]
I love that even though I hate
mathematics I love this
song and not Lou thank you for the red
super chat with four red hearts are you
giving me your big red heart you your
big red heart
thank you
notl I appreciate it thank you thank you
for the generous
support I should sing that song in my
Koka
sometimes I want to do another K that
focuses on whole live Originals at some
point to also sing g song and Ena song
yes yes yes
yes then we can do the we can do big big
red height red
height
yeah Alan JL D oh Alan kjl that's
probably how you read
it happy belated birthday Sky D flaming
pants d d j swack
D lone navity D what's a d GD thanks for
the pinky love you're singing as always
all songs are rippers is that how you
say that over
there in the land down under is that how
you say that something cool is a ripper
or do you also say that in in the lands
that are not down
under you found the rat
congratulations hi from Spain hello
thank you I want to go to Spain again
haven't have only been there once I
think to
Valencia what was the word Ripper never
heard that in the US oh okay never heard
that all right then it seems to be
Australian come back to Spain whenever
all right I want to go I want to go
maybe next year
[Music]
where was I for the okay thank you
should I
sing VI sometime huh I kind of wanted to
sing it in that K but I couldn't finish
practicing but I heard am sing it in her
K and I was like hm I think I'm going to
put that on my list of K songs to sing
in the
future next time next time next time
there's always a next time we for and e
thank you for the pinky thanks for the K
T you always love hearing you sing thank
you I'm glad that I have an audience who
wants to hear me sing and
appreciate my singing and my voice thank
you thank you so
much oh I'm a to do it
M maybe I
should love hearing you singing thank
you you singing it's awesome thank you
you're amazing boss thank you love you
guys I love
you
for Pap thank you for the red super chat
you're
crazy Tano CYO I love you singing so
much and don't go Tano don't worry I'm
not going
anywhere thank you for your
support Papa
sh thank you from the bottom of my
heart chocolate in thank you for the
pinky we love you too K don't say
goodbye to us so soon I guess right oh
because I was singing that song you guys
are so
dramatic so
dramatic H thank you for ging strength
from your voice today
oh so dramatic I was singing such a nice
cute song and everyone's like crying in
the
comments oh man
danal L navity what's
AIM
[Music]
M want to look at your profile pict show
what aim what is you changed it it's
really a Cy salt and Peppa
dispenser wait is
that but that's a keychain over me in
front of that did you actually take a
photo yourself of a salt and a pepper
dispenser and put my keychain in front
of
it I thought it was just a Google p but
there's a
keychain from me
you must have taken it yourself
maybe wait you uploaded a video called
Ki Kik key alarm 2 weeks ago that's
me let me
listen you actually made an alarm
for that seems to be my own
music
Ki that's a nice alarm open your
eyes
[Music]
Ki get out of your
Ki wake the up wake the
[Music]
up
get
out open your this is so
good I don't even remember when I did
this I remember like like doing that at
some point but I don't know when that
was that's
funny that really fits well as a as an
alarm especially with that music in the
background I need this well you have to
look for k k kittyy alarm but it's not
written correctly how it should normally
be written it's k i k i r i k i
k it's written incorrectly Mr salt and
pepper dispenser but that's
okay that's okay I
forgive that's a great alarm yeah if you
want to be uh awakened by my voice then
this is the way to
go is he here now I wonder I didn't see
him I think
now I didn't
oh oh no that's
[Music]
not thank you for the pinky thank you
for the Blissful time T thank you as
well I appreciate you being there thank
you I hope you had a great time M I hope
you'll be there for the next K as well
whenever that one will
be I want to do one maybe once I get um
my new outfit maybe then or like a
Halloween themed K or we can combine
that new outfit with Halloween themed
[Music]
Kad hold and scroll different Zoom
levels I didn't know that
what
what any news on the out uh I I probably
should stop giving news on that not like
I I have been bonked
but
uh it it keeps getting later and later
than what I'm saying even though every
time I've said something it seems 100%
sure that it's happening and is not
happening but I'm just going to
I'm just going to uh not not say
anything anymore not getting you hopes
up but it should be
soon or not so
soon
yeah waiting
waiting waiting and waiting and waiting
soon
TM
yeah DM
no it won't help it won't
help every time I mention it it get it
gets delayed another week it feels like
it
yes
candle
big and that's it for the K party
although I'm wondering should I read
should I start reading the members ones
or end here and read
tomorrow uh cuz my stream is going to
start early
tomorrow end it here end it
here you guys are in synful ones it's
been 6 hours
now better to
[Music]
stop
the question is though how long will the
gaming part of tomorrow's stream be will
I have the energy and
voice to read
after uh uh trying to save eggs for what
5 hours or
so and screaming probably a
lot it's it's supposed to be an
endurance
stream
but I wasn't really expecting to play so
long today either
yeah yeah I I don't think I can take
that game for longer than 5 hours I will
go
insane my personal goal is just getting
through that first
room cuz I've been so close so many
times but yeah in the in the one mil
enduring stream I tried reaching it I
tried getting through that and I was so
close but then because of time fress
wasn't was that the last thing I was
doing in that
stream but I couldn't do it because of
the time
schedule oh it was the last thing yeah I
was really forced to end it there
although I did feel like just starting
another stream right after those 12
hours to finish it cuz I was actually
pretty motivated and pretty
energetic oh God damn it I think if we
would have gone a little bit longer I
might have gotten through that first
room but tomorrow since it's been a long
time I probably have to find my Grove
again I heard that there is three rooms
three
levels and the last one is
insane well I'm not planning I'm not I
don't think I can finish
four four
[Music]
okay endurance let's go maybe I might
start uh change the starting time to 1
hour
later
yeah I hope it's
okay 1 hour later maybe I missed the
first hour will perfect for you cuz I
might change it to 1 hour
later y good for you good for
you I kind of set it to that hour
because I wanted it to force myself to
get up
earlier
now I originally said it at that early
time because I wanted to get myself to
wake up early but yesterday I stayed up
so long
again
[Music]
we'll wake up before the sun rises to
watch the stream but I do it for love
thank you do it for
her you know that Meme everyone knows
that meeme where did that come from
where did that Meme come from do it for
her come thank you for the
[Music]
membership The
Simpsons
what do it for Maggie was that like part
of a of an episode where they showed
that a really touching scene
a
a it was for the baby
a that's
sweet had to download my wife alarm you
downloaded the
alarm you're really going to use it
that's so
cute that is so
cute old Simpsons
oh
oh I tweeted it too we'll use
it a don't
forget
oh some letters are covered is that how
it ended up as supp post to the original
says remember you're here forever homewo
cover with pictures of Maggie and it
becomes do it for
her
aw how does that become do it
remember there's no do there you're here
I can see how here Becomes Her and four
is from forever
oh another
H I
understand thank you for teaching me on
the
memes okay I got to work on whole talk
and eat food
[Music]
and
why did I decide to have Hol talk this
week it's so
busy it's so
busy I don't know I read the rest
hopefully maybe the rest of the super
tense tomorrow maybe maybe maybe we can
maybe I'll do a real good job tomorrow
and we finish the gaming part early so
that I can write super chats
and yes
yes
yes don't know a lot about choco well
then you have to come to holot talk to
learn more about her yes yes yes all
right then thank you guys for watching
today I hope you had fun watching my
playr of Diablo
I I think it was it was all right that
we um played it from the beginning again
it would have been a lot of work for me
to play through all of that privately
especially cuz I wouldn't have your
guys'
advice would have probably taken me more
than 6
hours yeah so good that we did it
together
thank you thank you thank you ask for
advice oh I don't need any advice just
yet I'm doing fine
[Music]
still it was fun and we had a lot of um
possibilities to chat in between
chitchat in between noise all all good I
even was able to show you my
lasagna Beach
Las okay then I'll see you tomorrow and
enj say
[Music]
Al coming for you oh by the way I
thought of this word listen k
it works perfectly in Japanese cuz r a
is the same as L A what do you mean
me
K Divine
Exquisite stunning
Heavenly I'll eat my K not catchy y not
catch
it shut up it works better in
Japanese M you made me you made me
angry Platinum mad I am Platinum mad
now
[Music]
K open your
eyes
Ki get out of your
bed
Ki wake the up wake the up a
smoothie came into the
room
SM smie woke up smoy was woken up by the
alarm open
your
k