[Music]
n
a
[Music]
n
a
[Music]
n
K
oopsy oh are you hearing the bgm
[Music]
guys
I was thinking we're going to have my
bgm today cuz I mean I only streamed the
S game
once
K but I feel like other
people like you guys probably have also
watched other people play it and now um
we don't need to listen to the same
music anymore probably at this point cuz
I'm late to the hype so you
guys are probably bored of
[Music]
it unfortunately that means we don't get
the nice droppy
sounds you know the fruit popping
sounds but that's okay maybe I can make
the
[Music]
sounds
you're
welcome you didn't watch anyone else
play before me wow I like the Loyalty
you're
showing I like that very much but other
people might be you know at this point
sick of it cuz
yeah I would personally understand
it making brain
mushy no you can't turn the bgm off and
the sounds on there's no no settings at
all in the game
menu me
personally I I am fine thank you I would
have liked a
nap
[Music]
um but I also didn't oopsie I didn't
want to move the uh streaming starting
time I do that too often and I thought
well some people
probably uh you know especially the sea
people probably are you know like you
know not
Tas yeah it is a bit of a
problem
hey uh it's hard it's hard to know when
you plan out your week on the schedule
for you guys how things are really going
to
go it's hard to
know things
happen sleep the Rival
happens and other things
happen just
[Music]
yeah did you guys see m stream I was uh
I recorded something for that I don't
know when long time ago but this time
apparently she used it I I mean I
watched it so it's not apparently I know
it I know she
[Music]
did oh thank
you I I was like you know when she was
planning things out I um I was like you
know trying to help her cuz like she
didn't have like a lyrics
split so I was like girl do you not want
to like do a lyrics split like cuz I
think it's more interesting should I do
it for you I don't know if she did it
for anybody else but um cuz there was no
lyrics but I I just made it for us and I
made her do all
the
parts because well
well
because she did it so well and I wanted
to yeah she hit that those notes I I
knew she could do it so I wanted her to
do it to impress everybody with those
notes hell
yeah hey what a good Senpai trying to
show oopsie trying to show her cooh
strengths trying to showcase the
strengths I'm such a good
Senpai yeah her new song yeah I love it
is so
wow quiet the Bob and the music video oh
my God like oh wow it's so beautiful
it's so cute so
interesting uh by the way I realized
just because I had to buy the game
with a Japanese uh shop account doesn't
mean I also had to like you know play it
with that account so I switched from the
one I used yesterday to the one I
usually use so my record is different
wouldn't it be funny if suddenly I hit
you with like 6,000 would be so funny
but no but I think H what was my highest
one yesterday something like
2,300 I played a little little bit today
and I got up to
2,400 once I think that was the first
time I played today
actually so I already cracked my old
record let's
[Music]
go new new record a doesn't count it
does I feel I even took
videos wait when you press the video
button where on your switch it records
everything that just happened right not
what's happening
onwards right had some funny
moments right that's what it does right
let's watch
it
wait I mean wait let me just mute this
you won't hear it I guess but no I guess
let me play it I think you can oh sure
so what happened in this
one oh
ah this was a good score I was doing so
well I was about to combine two melons
into one big melon and
then I don't even remember why I
recorded
this uh I think something will
fly Pro or or not
oh oh I noticed it's moving I'm like
oh yeah it started moving and then it
just but it was it was probably not
going anywhere
anyway um
unfortunately and then
[Music]
this again nice fruit oh oh here it's
about to touch it become a peach it
became a
peach and then something's going to fly
I'm telling you now
[Music]
n oh no it's a close one close
one what's going to
happen oh ah yeah something
flew something didn't need fly
there
I it's always those moments and there's
one more probably also
flying again with a big melon and a
pineapple and you know we're going to
places but
then going so well going so
[Music]
well and then oh oh oh oh I'm out I
think I just wanted to flex that I got
the the watermelon yeah this actually a
positive
one isn't that
nice all of that suddenly turning into a
watermelon this might have been the one
where I got my high score
maybe yeah let's say it again cuz it
felt so
good what what exactly happened what
touched what I need to
[Music]
see
oh so the the right side uh pair wasn't
even
used so that's
that
out
let's I would say I've been doing quite
well you
know but other people don't believe
that I want to sleep I always want to
sleep sleep I love
naps I I don't like the
judgmental
Vibes behind you
know taking naps as an adult I don't
like
it naps are
awesome naps are
good I'm an
adult move to Spain
ah uh what what was it um
Siesta Siesta
Siesta
[Music]
meaa
right
hey yeah I like that
spirit
[Music]
sorry I I will I will wake up oh I just
you know I stop don't do that
hey I just no I wanted to push it over I
notic I just when today when I like was
just after breakfast which was a sweet
breakfast I noticed wo I have like no
energy I I feel like
so but I figured it might be because of
lack of you
know proper food
intake so I've been drinking freshly
squeezed orange
juice very good and I had a good
sandwich a good sandwich
woo
nice now I think I feel a bit better
than
previously nice and healthy kind of yeah
kind
of also you know what I was
doing partially
today I was like looking up on
YouTube YouTube
this
and at the
time the
famous holder of the record of
7,300 was
streaming I was like oh isn't this the
person that has the record yes they
are so I thought okay they were like
doing a a stream where like he was
trying to break his own record again or
like get two watermelons again and I
thought oh I'm I'm surely I'm surely
going to learn something from him
but turns out he also like basically
really struggles with getting to that
point that's like really Next Level [\h__\h]
you know that's next level also this is
not looking so nice go on touch
it it's warm up time guys it's warm
up but you know I thought oh the person
who has that record surely must have
everything figured out
I mean they seem like they they know
what they're doing they're like doing
things very calculated but at the same
time things also often go very wrong for
that person too it's not that
different it's not that
different
so made me feel a bit
better and also um you know it was uh
interesting to
watch he did indeed he got close to
getting ooh the melon the second
watermelon again
unfortunately then
yeah something didn't go so
well and he didn't and then he gave up
for the
day yeah I want the paches to
touch but they're so far there's so much
[\h__\h] in between because of
me it's okay we're going to have better
runs this is not the
[Music]
run I need four peaches anyway yep true
I mean the more the merer
[Music]
anyway maybe easier to build another P I
guess so I guess that's what we're
[Music]
doing well not even the grapes want to
touch so
rude um well this will become an apple
too so oh there we
go oh Cherry do where do we want to go
with a cherry maybe
here okay
well more
rudeness so
rude guess we'll make another
Apple can never have enough apples here
this this could go there there we go and
then
push no here I'll help you okay that
also doesn't want to touch the other
pair great great not like I care you do
what you think is best for you I don't
think it's very
good maybe one day you'll see the things
that I I see Ora
hello I recorded my voice
pack that I said that I had a deadline
for I recorded it let's go this one's a
bit longer I think than the last
one oh oh These will touch this will
touch
[Music]
this man well well maybe it's just you
know this way we don't we're not wasting
our times on a bad run what happened I
don't know don't ask
me things
happen things just happened hello that's
not
[Music]
nice you
blinked are you saying you made that
happen cuz you blinked don't you have
superpowers when you blink or did you
not see it I should have maybe I should
have recorded it for you guys watch
everything in slow motion but you know
what I'm I I record my
vods obviously this is YouTube so you
can watch
it
afterwards grape showing no mercy yeah
what's with that grape man feel the
grape is the worst fruit out of the
bunch not because I don't like the
flavor
no it's just because of its behavior and
and how it's like the most difficult
to you know
position like it's too big and it's too
small both at the same
time it's
just a a big problem with your
Apple yeah that's what I like to see oh
just rolled over like that
[Music]
noise the game still treats it as a
circle I guess so you know it I realized
something that it really bothers me
we're putting things in this like
supposedly threedimensional
container um but if you think about it
whatever everything we're putting in
there is flat and it's only filling up
the front screen the front
panel there's actually so much more
space that we could make use
of and it bothers
me it bothers
[Music]
me you know when it's like filled up to
the
brim and you think about it like all the
fruits you know these cherries for
example They Don't Really block so much
path there should be more space behind
all of this where is all the
space
Illuminati put on the put on the tinf
hat guys it's
time it's time that we say something
it's time that we speak out
fake Dimensions man thank you thank you
thank you thank you
soon
Adamas also I watch super Senai play a
little bit
today it's actually fun to watch other
people play this I don't know why it's
so much fun just because I'm really into
it as well I guess it's fun to watch
other people play something that you're
into
wow
science who would have
known genius wah
wa I'm
feeling
just real today like I'm not I'm just
being real today you know what I mean I
don't feel like sugar coating things
today what's happening why do I feel
like
this
[Music]
M
[\h__\h]
shitty shitty
[Music]
selections wait for it there we
go
[Music]
uh all I don't know what this is I don't
know I was not fake the other day no I
never am I'm always
real oh
pineapple I'm
going one two one two
three peach peach time
baby touch no touch the Other M
H oh
well okay fine
apples there's um too too many grapes
down there AKA to but that's already too
many
tou but my fruit production is going
well so far I
think pen pineapple Apple pen
touch nice why why must you go that
way is there a
reason is there some reasoning behind
that
huh wait wait for that wait wait wait
wait before you go there thank you thank
you can we like switch all the places
please hi tento
hello go some somewhere
else oh shitty fruit everything's [\h__\h]
just pessim pessimistic
today oh oh hey okay maybe go
down go
down it's fine I'm not
mad I'm not mad I'm
happy
oh pineapple
Bon all right
cool
nice hey Google Play pineapple by
takii hey Siri play pineapple by
takana I need to make a melon song
next can we push it down go go go go
go close maybe
later oh
oh it's actually going well somehow
weirdly I feel like it
shouldn't but it's just working
out my on
[Music]
song
oh oh sometimes just got to be
patient oh things are happening oh the
apples might touch and the oh okay we
cleaned up there's not even that much
trash
around but the apple is stuck in a
position where I will not reach it
that's
okay I'm not really going for double
watermelons so whatever oh they're still
moving did you see that
bounce so that was in that was cute
bounce apples and tats wow I'm so
[Laughter]
productive
oh what it's really clear down there
[Music]
oh huh
why
[Music]
what why is this going so
well huh
huh is what I'm doing good yeah
go wow oh peaches what are we going to
do about the
[Music]
peaches don't jinx it what I'm not
jinxing it people people are so
like up like
uh like man you can't Jinx things if you
don't believe in
jinxing just don't believe in it um I
don't know if I really want to throw
things there man I don't want to because
then I can't move things anymore so I'm
going just going to I'm just going to
try to build here you
know just going to do my thing here up
here
what do you think about that choice
[Music]
H I like my
choices
wow how did
that
what huh did I'm confused did I just
make two apples I didn't even
[Music]
realize
wow
wow I'm doing things see I'm doing this
now look at that
oh um but I got to I got to tell this
peir to to go cuz I need space for
another
Apple I don't think I can push it with
the with the grapes can
[Music]
I got a combo on the right side and
unstuck the peaches
m
you want me to throw things in there
but but
[Music]
what yeah we'll we'll just throw the
grape in there and then I want to
balance this here now ideally I want to
put it here but it's really
risky but I'm going to do it and then we
push
this but it won't move that's okay
that's
okay and then we make a grape
here
oh it has become
something but this will never move will
it and then I messed
up maybe maybe I have no choice but to
build
here until everything changes into to
something uh Big Chain
Reaction but my points are already
pretty decent so far
[Music]
W what the [\h__\h] there's no tomatoes here
this is fruits okay fruits only no veget
oh right people say tomatoes are fruits
right still that's an apple do me more
Apple but okay I'll try building
something here
beep I don't want this
strawberry can
I can I push it probably not right can I
but if I push it won't it go too high
anyway if I get to push
it
okay well let's put it here
oh no no no yeah yeah yeah stay stay
stay yeah stay stay stay stay push push
push push push push push P puse push he
this is gonna go bad it's GNA break
everything in three two no okay that's
[\h__\h]
strawberry hi that's it that's the
end
unless what but good store good score
good score for our first game
today even I wasn't even trying that
hard wait same score as before oh
yeah same
[Music]
number all right let's
go let's go all in
[Music]
now I had the comfiest snuggles with
smoothie and with chunky wonky and I
fell
asleep so quickly last
night I couldn't
even I couldn't even go to idle meeting
before sleeping so I was like forced to
go like I I F I fell asleep accidentally
but still at a good
time but you know I don't like it when I
don't when I fall asleep
accidentally it was like sleepy time yes
but still not really how I intended to
fall
asleep
but I will choose this
over like you could almost call it the
insomnia that I had back in the day I
wouldn't really say it's insomnia cuz
it's all caused I guess no I don't know
back in the day when I wasn't used to my
fiber mialgia that much yet
falling asleep took
me minimum 3
hours I
like average three hours four
[Music]
sometimes for many years it was like
that and so I'm like so
happy
for and it hasn't been that long but um
for maybe I don't know a year or so I've
been able to fall
asleep way
quicker no I had my I would have my eyes
closed no nothing like going on like no
music no um TV for distracting no but I
would try it out sometimes you know I
would try all kinds of
things m
it's cuz like my whole body was in such
weird
pain by like my
my my that's what for a while I thought
I had restless leg syndrome cuz it was
especially my um
coughs and I just felt like they were
feeling like maybe Ting tingly
[Music]
Maybe
M but not in a good way like and kind of
in
[Music]
pain you have versus leg syndrome oh I
don't know if I really have that I never
got diagnosed with that I don't think I
do cuz like I never got diagnosed with
it
um but anyway I've had that for years
needing to uh needing so many hours to
fall asleep no matter how tired I was so
now I really appreciate falling asleep
pretty quickly these
days such a
blessing yeah let's have it be stuck I
prefer
that gives her a lot of trouble for your
mom had the same
problem Oh
interesting did she ever get a
diagnosis
it's called getting old oh sure sure I
was old when I was 10 and 11 and so on
when I already had the issue
mhm
mhm no young people can have big health
problems
[Music]
too
my mom got diagnosed with fibro same
simp oh yeah
well I heard and I agree with this that
fibro is just um the diagnosis doctors
give when they don't know what else to
give
you when they are out of
ideas and I don't even I'm not even sure
if I believe fibromyalgia is a real
thing but when you're like
experiencing so
much weird
unexplicable pain for your whole life
you want some reason for it you want to
know what it is you want to know why you
have
it so any kind of name for it
is a a blessing to
me but then again for me the fiber
mialgia is very different from
my um other pains that I
have and that's what I've been trying to
explain to the
doctors I I'm always like yeah I mean
people said doctors said I have the
vialia but I don't think this is the
same thing cuz this like started
separately it feels different you know I
I I try to explain it but I I don't know
if they are
listening is there meds with fibro well
that's the
[Music]
thing it depends on the person
apparently and the first thing they put
me on is anti-depressant because there's
something in there that makes you feel
less pain or like it's it does something
with your pain feeling and I was taking
that for a little while but I noticed it
didn't help so I I stopped taking it but
when I was taking it is when I went to
the uh
Lanza cabin attended audition
audition interview where I was just you
know I was just testing it and I was
going to stop anyway soon after but I'm
too honest and at the medical exam I
told them this is what I'm taking and
they were like M okay they sent me
letter a while
later and
yeah that was it that was the end of
my upcoming cabinet attendant career
sad but it's
okay didn't need
that found something even
[Music]
better
M what could have been it's all
connected everything is
connected
[Music]
no stupid strawberries
no okay so many apples so many things
what a mess
[Music]
hey careful
now everything's like so far away from
each
other I don't know about this oh we got
two
pineapples mhm
okay weird
consolation you got your fancy armor
let's
go my Peak advice is to listen to good
doctors while
finding the right one with the right
answer is
[Music]
difficult I don't want to imagine a
timeline where there is no kahua well
kiaha always was
there was just about you not you're not
you would have not found me and that is
indeed sad
so
sad oh bye-bye
strawberry was nice knowing
you oh oh
a nothing will
touch
[Applause]
ah
ah I
this nothing wants to
[Music]
touch I don't think I would have really
been able to show off those traits as a
flight
attendant and honestly I would have
probably not been a flight attendant for
that long anyway cuz it's a damn
difficult
job
tiring ah it's so
over it's so over
end it
already ah let me
go what are you trying to do what you
trying to do 24 Kat magic in it it's not
over the
to
okay next
[Music]
please
do you like the bgm guys oh [\h__\h]
distracted myself if you don't like this
one anymore either then let me
know but for now I think it's
good
donkey it's good
classic it's one of my favorite bgms
that I downloaded from audio stock AIO
St oh thank you I'm also H really I'm so
[\h__\h] blessed #
blessed do you have this job
man man for real for real such a
[Music]
blessing # plus
oppa get there
[Music]
go all I'm also by the way I'm trying to
have like small things on one side big
things on the one side but it's just not
happening at the moment I don't
know oh haa nice okay just flew over the
moon wait for
it big one win big
[Music]
win you make me believe wonders are
possible
oh yeah definitely are I've had like
many times many oh it's still moving
many instances in my life
where I would say I I I made things
happen that were seemingly impossible or
or where people would tell
me people would tell me oh it's not
going to happen like I I legit recently
I
remembered because somebody
tried to like contact
me when I was like really
young I don't even know how young I was
but this was so early
on I was like in this group chat with
weeps was before Discord times I don't
even know what Messenger application we
used um but I was so I was like so shy I
was still so shy and
WEEI um I oh I was small small
[Music]
W I don't think it was teams speak cuz I
remember mostly we were chatting via
typing
so I'm not sure what it
was
m i feel like in may have been like a
self-programmed chat
actually cuz I remember it being very
different from all the other messagers
at the time I
think mhm I think so IRC oh wait yeah
that was a
thing yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah wait
what was that again I haven't heard that
in a while
that sounds very familiar that sounds
right that sounds like the right
answer
[Music]
oh internet relight
chat wait so that you could make your
own chat rooms with that oh my god let's
go for Internet
history peaches peaches peaches peaches
peaches PES PES PES PES
[Music]
PES oh so anyway this was the uh a group
of
weeps
and I was so young and I started
thinking
about you know I want to do this I want
to do that I want to live in Japan I
want to do this and that
and they were
like they were not like mean or bullying
me or anything but they legit were like
n you that's not going to
happen like they legit didn't believe me
cuz I was really smaller smaller and
yeah they didn't think it was possible
and then I actually did it
N I actually [\h__\h] did it all of those
things that I said I would do and I know
they sounded kind of like very ambitious
but I did
them I
foring
[Music]
yes yeah I showed
them dreams dreams don't have to be
dreams guys even if they sound
ridiculous and even if there's a lot of
hurdles to overcome in order to become
do the thing
[Music]
I do think I defined the odds I do think
so even things like me getting into art
school I may have dropped out of it but
me getting into that I still see that as
a huge accomplishment for
me I'm still so proud of myself for
getting into it because there was like a
test to get into it and it meant that I
was you know good enough for
that I'm proud of myself for getting
into
it and
me uh dropping out of it in the end led
to other things like me now being in
whole life more or
less more or less led to that
so
H hey
pineapple was there a peach somewhere in
between I didn't even see it all all
happens so
[Music]
fast going to try to stay up there for
as long as I can and there it goes but
that's fine actually that's
[Music]
fine po hey I didn't want you to go go
there pineapple hey people always want
those watermelons and I I'm just happy
with my
pineapples all I want is
[Music]
pineapples I was trying to make it with
grapes another one like I can't really
put it there I don't think it will land
where I want it to land I could push the
grave away maybe I don't know if that
works I should still fill it with grapes
okay then I guess we're doing something
else down here there is the
grape oh no tou really come on yeah push
push it push it pushed it a little
bit I'll just it it will happen it will
happen just got to give it some
[Music]
time oh now it's going more
apart oh you're moving to Japan thanks
for working
holiday how you found out about it
because of
me wait what country
oh oh
England nice I'm so happy for
you to be like you know making use of
that it's a very really really unique
ooh uh uh a
chance things are
[Music]
shifting I'm not yellow I'm
Orange
your number one thing to do in England
leave hey it combined I didn't see that
coming thought we were going to have
problems combining those now it's kind
of in the middle what's my what's my
trash side currently looking like the
right side although there is a
[Music]
pair go trash
left
really I guess ah there's enough like a
lot of space here to build
things I don't see the grap is trash
right now so but now I do now I do in
hindsight I
do Mama
Mia cuz then I'll be blocking the grape
and the grape will be lost
I'll put this here for
now oh my God there's
more sorry trash side is somehow the
right side now but also the left side
it's both oh oh
nice we take it we take it we have to
adjust to how times
[Music]
change
hey trust the process what the [\h__\h] I
was going to put a strawberry there you
little
[\h__\h]
okay where does the strawberry go maybe
it can push it hey was oh
okay I was going to push it through
underneath the right side of the
orange um here take
this oh it's working it's
working
go Cherry go
Cherry
chadad chadd
bum T is strawberry trash it is right
there's so much trash Oh my
[Music]
God it's not moving though anything that
doesn't move the melon can we really
consider it
[Music]
trash ch Chad Chad
bum
Chad
[Music]
bu that's from caddy Pomo Pomo
hey hey you're not welcome
[Music]
here
uh well I just felt like it fits well
there uh uh where grape
go you watched to perform that song Live
recently
what in like an actual life venue
IRL and maybe key
[Music]
over I'm thinking here I'm just going to
do whatever guys now because it's not
looking so good and at these
times you just go with the flow like
this like this who said it's ski
over I mean
still looking pretty bad with all the
trash down
there if only they would touch maybe
they will guys maybe they
[Music]
will oh things are moving oh things are
shifting yes yes sir getting rid of the
trash a little
bit
[Music]
M yeah weight balance weight shift all
oh
pop popping like a
pimple
sheesh does the other strawberry want to
go there no
okay I'm putting trash on the left side
now but also the good stuff everything
everything anything
really
[Music]
anything
goes I can make anything
[Music]
work I want everybody to feel useful in
this
[Music]
environment H hey would you not like to
go a little bit more to the
left no no really
you
suck then let the Cherry through thank
you really really W
really what are these Life Choices Wawa
I don't
know I don't
know things are the way they
[Music]
are
this is
fine this is
fine this is also fine everything's
fine see this this looks beautiful not
so
[Music]
oh look at that
Pomeranian in the right moment and
actually you came to the stream where
I'm using your Papa's art for the
thumbnail M all my wives are here let's
go all my
wives in the chat let's
[Music]
go say hi to each other be nice to each
other pom say hi to pom this is Nest
ravencraft Raven craft is rain
puff oh your names are your last names
are kind
of
matching feels
good hi pomu
uu pom be
nice be nice don't
bark oh nice I nevera oh sweet they
maybe maybe they can go hand in
hand why are you girls watching why are
you so sweet why do you love me so much
why do I love you so
much love love is Beautiful Love is
Blind
trash yeah good stay
[Music]
there
la la brush I feel it every every
day even in the dark times I my hand up
right to
the I see you and you see
me
eternally
we without
you feel
undone you gave me what I dream
mom you're my L I can't give up don't
say it's over it wasn't over last time
also anything I'm happy as long as I
have a watermelon like there's nothing
to complain about there's no end to the
game anyway is there
so I'm I'm constantly winning there's no
state of
failure understand that would just
building here it's a nice building
area stupid Cherry stupid
Cherry why do you got to do this to me
why you got to be so complicated I see
it you're acting like a somebody else
makes me
frustrated fall C and you break and
[Music]
take can we get this
through move
move [\h__\h] get out the way get out the
way
[\h__\h] I'll just
wait maybe I will pay off your 30th
birthday congratulations oh it's moving
see
M wow the
genius move Peach get out the way get
out the way Peach get out the way I
didn't even why did I not realize I
could change the lyrics to D
we have no trash side by the way
again we don't need
[Music]
one we don't need
it
ah ah
[Music]
sneeze good
sorry I'm just uh screaming for
[Music]
fun it's shaking everything's
shaking no I was doing so well it was
Happ
happening
why why can't put yourself out
there new high score though good
[Music]
good real BR
moments was feeling the the tenseness of
the fruit they were shaking and ready to
set
off I beat your high school
ooh I thought I was doing really badly
yesterday but then I saw uh like all the
hollow life members uh Point
rankings and I wasn't even the last
so I wasn't even the last and I
definitely am
more now or less less less of a loser
now all right nice even Nik
nikan it's Japanese funny
number it means
smiling
cuz well you know the
N but it's like you know the two you can
pronounce as NE and
the five is ghoul but it will turn into
a
CO and then nik nik you can say somebody
is really Ni
no really
Smiley we have a LIF off let's
go I was like in my head right now I'm
thinking like who's that guy again am
not Amsterdam that's the country
Armstrong kiaha armr
strong but my arms are not very
[Music]
strong so I'm not Armstrong I couldn't
be I literally couldn't be
Armstrong so funny I'm so
[Music]
funny kiaha arm
weak no that doesn't sound good if
anything call me kiaha noodle arms that
at least has a nice ring to it nicer
than the other
one my neck feels like so stiff today
what the
freak I can't even crack it like what
the
hell let me crack my
neck hey you were supposed to merge with
the last
one hm
[Music]
let me make an apple
here nice that was fast
ha I say a thing and then I do it and
then I achieve it that's just me that's
just
me so much
confidence have
confidence see all the confidence in my
gameplay I feel like you can really
taste
it smell
it is there a reason why YouTubers are
playing this
[Music]
game um
no it's cute
it's in fact it has infected
us it's just it just happened you know
wo hey
move
lame why YouTu play
game why why rtu
why right com so
true
I can't put anything there oh
[Music]
well it's isn't that a beautiful meme
that pomu
created okay I didn't think there would
be another strawberry right away so I I
could have put it there why B why so
true Pomo you created something so
beautiful AKA our baby
what sorry narissa don't
listen narissa AKA no no Lissa because
she ain't listening because she has to
close her ears because I'm flirting with
[Music]
pulo I'm on a
roll bars
pulling out the Comedy Central
but she's crying no there is
[Music]
a where do I
build what's my where am I am I really
asking this question this is waa after
all it doesn't matter
whatever I do is the right thing to do
see it works whatever I do works it
always works German always works W
always works I always
work the wa way is the only way I do
miss the the am way though am way is
pretty good
too and St B hot but the grapes though
I'd like the grapes to meet h
so many
grapes this is why I said the grapes are
the worst absolute
worst
[Music]
H
Peach hey that I made the meat oh my God
I'm such a genius I'm such a
genius
so good
[Music]
m double pineapple D I'm a Genus e
there's only one pineapple right now
let's make it
more I would like it to be
more nice
[Music]
one M don't need this grape right
now can I gently place it on the
peach I don't think it will land there
huh half a pineapple on my head yeah I
know I
know but I'm not considering that one
it's only
um empty
Holo it will definitely roll yeah all
right W away it doesn't matter I'll fix
any
situation positive
thinking see this is why I don't
understand the trash side because in the
end it becomes something that's not
trash so it's not really
trash nothing is this this is all
good good
[Music]
stuff
mysterious
ways ooh this is not so good though I'll
leave this
here yeah thank you I was hoping for
that wow
beautiful
[Music]
H oo
nice one man's trashes never one's
watermelon
little late but here now
[Music]
welcome I'm I'm building here
now Ki the Builder can we do it yes we
can
no
the
byas
I'm I'm I'm having a good
time you guys are probably constantly
shaking your head like why did she do
this why did she do
that I'm so
sorry don't worry it's over
soon the
Cherry oh the Cherry oh you little
[\h__\h] be
careful that was
dangerous
[Music]
oh
n
[Applause]
[Music]
NY
no why did you no
hey it's
okay go
away what happens oh
sheesh wait wait wait for this one
[Music]
no cool cool stuff
okay okay okay okay let's try
to make it very
clean good run thank
[Music]
you Peach those peaches
man okay okay clean so
far pretty clean so
far strong early game
waa showing you her strong late game
also
today
impressive skill
Showcase of the one and
only truly
Godly truly Divine
takiki see
[Music]
this is why they call her the myth
speaker of
[Music]
Ian some people don't get
it then you should maybe watch my
streams more
often if that's the
case
[Music]
um I love you too Chad I I love you
too can can you not like display it so
publicly I'm getting a little bit
embarrassed
[Music]
cute okay um trash side let's go right
side I need a trash side right now I
need to be
organized but at the same time I'm doing
the same thing again I'm building on my
trash
side because that's just how it works
right now that's just how it
looks left side trash light I've changed
my mind
wo okay see times change in early game
very
[Music]
fast I want to put this there anyway oh
it's it's actually going there let's
go left side T
side
touch
oh I Cara thank you I didn't know there
was taxes for snorts
[Music]
hey what do you want
here not your
[Music]
territory oh not
now
more public affection no
[Music]
hasashi the other day there was
something that made me really once again
realize something that was just normal
for
me but when I'm in Japan I rarely ever
notice it because it's hard to notice
things that are not
happening but
um the other day I saw some really
really affectionate people in Japan they
were like like the the guy was like
pinning up the girl against the wall of
some store and like wo sming and
woohoo my Japanese friends were also
pointing it out
like and that just made me think oh yeah
this never happens in Japan but like
outside of Japan this is just
normal not a big
deal but I actually I like that
it's just not normal cabon just
public uh kissing this was some intense
kissing too it's not
common in
Japan and I kind of like
that cuz
like explode I want I want them to
[Music]
explode get a
room I'll I'll do it here otherwise I'm
going to make everyone
mad fine I'll do it
[Music]
here Caba don't yeah maybe Caba
don't depends on places country yeah but
Japan is one of those places where it's
not common and I really appreciate
that oh okay see suddenly we're on the
left side again I can't help it
it I just can't help
it it just
happens hey where you going where you
going sir where you going hey stop hey
back up back up back up back
up hands up in
here yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah two
Pineapple pineapple that will never
touch unless I push him around a little
bit oh it stopped is it did it stop yeah
it
[Music]
stopped we'll make it meet someday
somehow good safe thank you I'm a
pro hey oh oh oh
oh okay but how do we get the pineapple
to the other side or do I just have to
make more pineapples and combine them
with other
pineapples and have a big swinger
party
H questions questions question oh what
it's going
there it's not on Steam no it's um on
switch but Japanese switch only Japanese
Nintendo shop needs Japanese payment
methods
too all right don't don't make the Apple
fly thank
you okay uh I think I'll try to build
something in the
[Music]
middle when you stay here I said stay
here
Sasa
sasuga all right I'll work with
that hey
[Music]
yeah thank
you go there all right go there all
right go there all right all right all
right all right all right all right all
right all right all right all right
right um uh okay
um
uh oh
[Music]
M
fast not looking good there
boss just you just you wait just you
wait
[Music]
touch touch
it push
it touch it something will fly oh no
free
pineapples free
pineapples
[Music]
yeah I'm
cooking
okay I don't want to block the middle
but it will most likely Fall
Down I don't think I can balance it
anywhere
yeah it's just how it
[Music]
is
not nobody will ever understand the WWA
strats
not even
Wawa
oh
uh-oh oh oh oh
oh uh it's over I will admit it's
over it's so
over
I was in a pickle jar take me
out so T
over it's okay GG I think that was
better than the previous
[Music]
one I have to cook today cuz my hadle
fresh order is coming but you know what
I did yesterday my mom left me some
meatballs
but I realized there's no sauce I was
like H what do I do so I took some of
the um the the
Indonesian uh noodles that they gave me
they always every time I meet ID girls
they always give me so many Indonesian
noodles
ah in Indo India
yeah and then I I made the India and I
made I added the fried egg and the
meatballs sounds genius doesn't
it was the purple India by the
[Music]
way let's go India let's
go wow aggressive
[Music]
aggressive
renang yeah
renang I feel like the others might be
more up my
alley but this one was fine
[Music]
too I'm the only person who pronounces
the E what about the ID girls do they
pronounce the
air I feel like you know in English you
wouldn't pronounce it but in many other
languages you
would why did you turny
to I'm personally like still okay with
listening to it but I thought others
like the viewers who also watch other
girls play this game might be sick of
hearing it it's not weakness from my
side it's part of the
experience yeah yeah that may be true
look at my high score niik
ni isn't that
nice I know it's not a 3,000 but it's
really aesthetically pleasing I would
say oh did you see Dad
oh nice p p action me likey me
likey Kelly you you don't want to watch
me play this game what I'm doing is like
really painful but it kind of
works very cash
money oh my fruits are so aggressive
they're so aggressive calm down calm
your fruit
tits fruit fruity fru
tits where do you want to go Cherry
should we do right side trash cuz
there's not so much space
[Music]
actually fruity
o
fruity go in there come on I know you
want
to okay you little
[\h__\h] see
everything's everything's
my recreational space I am a fruit what
fruit am I if I were a fruit what fruit
would I
be and why is is it an orange I don't
know why why I would be an orange that
just doesn't make any sense to
[Music]
me or pineapple yeah
pineapple
yeah not the
Doran or are you saying that because I'm
so
enduring
M grap I hate grap
grapefruit kiwi I like kiwis although
I I love eating them but uh yeah my
stomach doesn't like it that much but
it's okay I'll eat them
anyway
enough what did I say oh
enduring genius such a
genius such a genius should be
illegal
[Music]
I would be a
mango I don't know about
that mangoes I would put oh in the
avocado category in terms of like what
kind of
people are mangoes and avocados they're
like the same kind of
people you'll never
understand
it's like just like
popular popular fruit these days too
fruity to be just one kind of fruit okay
I am fruit
salad I'll take
[Music]
it I am ruining it let's
go
oh
where do the grap
go
oh oh shifting
shifting everything's
shifting
woo see sometimes maybe it's good not to
wait sometimes it's good sometimes it's
fine to not wait but all the trash down
there who said this T over again you
little [\h__\h]
[Music]
cuz it's never really really
over uh yeah yeah that's fine I actually
want you to move make some space
[Music]
for
yeah for your
[Music]
friend w
all these aggressions
again
oh too far
though but
okay we'll just got to make another
one that's fine I can make another
one
this is one of the few games where I
like the building
aspect No you little [\h__\h] you
suck
oh all right
oh look at the pro game
play display here by yours trly Takashi
kiaha we combined the
[Music]
peaches yeah no gameplay sound because
you can't only have just the the popping
of the fruits unfortunately I wish you
could and I thought it would be nice to
have my own bgm today cuz I saw superet
by doing the same too
ooh
[Music]
shifting feels good
man where trash go trash go
here a little bit of
trash wa
oh I'm so pleased with what I'm creating
always I'm just so pleased with
it no
trash mukashi actually we could get a
watermelon if only we could move the
pineapples I can't really this will fall
down
probably
no here it can
[Music]
land
I I don't know this situation is kind of
difficult not going to lie oopsy I
should have let it
move that's
okay I'll fix
[Music]
it uh I'll just make one one more
pineapple just make another
one
hey not so
[Music]
nice
okay
okay oh ranking in again oh p Peach I
made a peach look look look look
chickens I made a peach isn't it
pretty I'm so proud of my
[Music]
peach
H I won't
touch oh
oh why won't you
touch it's looking like uh the end even
though it could be so good if
only the constellation wasn't so bad we
could we could have have a
watermelon we could have more than a
[Music]
watermelon oh man I was trying
to how far can we push
this why so why now why now you spamming
with me with grapes I was hoping for
more
strawberries oh Mama Mia
2,000 okay
you're doing much better today than
yesterday really am
I it's because you know how like when
you when you learn something new I get
this with uh choreographies as well
dance choreographies but also
with I would say partially also with
things that like are more like text
based or so but when I learn something
new
um
even when I feel like on the day where I
start learning it I I feel like it's not
really in my head
yet like when I go to sleep often like I
will go through it like I can't help it
I don't I don't even do it on purpose
but I I go through it in my head a lot
oopsie and then when I wake up and I try
it again I'm like so much better like I
literally practiced in my
head and it
worked it literally had an
effect sleeping over it alone already
helps I would say yeah but then me just
thinking about the dance moves over and
over imagining them makes me
remember isn't that
fascinating
t
yeah visual visualization technique
helps a athletes too
oh I do it a lot like I think about
dance moves a lot like even when I'm not
trying to to learn something just when I
listen to a
song do you guys have this
too cuz in my head when I listen to a
song often I will have like I'll think
of really intricate dance moves like
choreographies in my head and when it
the problem is like in my head it's like
really nice but um it happens so fast
I'm that's why I can't really do
choreographies when I actually try to
act it out with my body I can't keep up
it's only good in my head
I can I can imagine it in such a
detailed way in my
head but yeah trying to do it IRL for
real for real
[Music]
musuki you ALS you imagine moves that
you're not capable of
doing you used to do art and animation
works for a lot of things kind of
like I will come up with a new MV for
the song like listening to lovers I
imagine something else in that oh really
interesting I'm good at this with math
computer science and other subjects I
don't know about dancing oh
Nar what do you imagine yourself to draw
is 5 years ahead of your current skills
that's a really interesting thing to say
from
[Music]
Ena you used to make Coral oh can I hire
you let me hire
[Music]
you easiest job interview
ever oh join kiwa's Angels
today kiwa's
angels we we're
literally a
click
nah we're we're cool people
though we're pretty
cool we're pretty
dope why noi why why why why why why why
why I like this constellation oh okay
but not this can the pineapple just go
up and the rest be
flat
[Music]
no
n n yeah yeah that's what yeah thank you
thank you just like I asked thank you
and there goes the Cherry in the middle
perfect okay but I'm getting so many
tiny ass baby fruit the
[Music]
[\h__\h] have to work with
it
nice such obedient fruit it literally
hurt me it was like okay we we can't
make the Wawa
mad can't make her
[Music]
angry I need to drop him more gently is
there a way to drop him more gently
because they keep on popping
off in a not so nice way
[Music]
that's not where I wanted it to
go
okay
uhhuh oh how
H how to scoop those things out of the
way guess I just got
to catapult it
somehow what is
happening oh yeah
melon
yes
yes yes Peach okay clean baby I have a
clean
slate
ooh
[Laughter]
ooh you think this is a freek run oh
watch me mess it
[Music]
up
M it will bounce off I'm so
sure ah
stay it's okay we have to make something
big anyway this this will also bounce
off that's my
problem oh
well that's
fine oh ooh hey I scooped it didn't I
what what
[Music]
happened Scoopy
whoopity all
right all right scoop maybe I'm trying
to transport it over to the other
pair I don't really mind you can you
know we can also just make two more
pairs pairs of
pairs I guess that's what we're doing
[Music]
[Applause]
anyway oh there we go now they're
meeting now they're meeting oh yeah
fruit
meeting cleaning up my
Mists
[Music]
I hope you win the video game there's no
winning in this game it's very
depressing what if I just rest this on
top of
here well at least we have another
[Music]
Peach
oh
[Music]
M
ma
hey okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay and and okay and okay and
touch touch touch touch touch
touch not
[Music]
fair not nice this fruits shouldn't be
so
bouncy pineapples are really hard melons
too apples too the only somewhat soft
surface thing is Peaches and the grapes
and stuff there's no way it could like
be realistically bouncing like
[Music]
this ever see orange in space me when
putting on Amelia's space suit Orange in
[Music]
space I really want am and gura to play
this I mean maybe some of you don't want
to see that but I feel like they're
missing out on this beautiful beautiful
game one of the best games of 2023
[Laughter]
man right I just H isn't literally
everybody else playing it I need them to
play it
[Music]
too
I did see like
fans I saw several versions of like
fan-made sua games already and they're
working on it maybe there will be one
that we could play instead in the future
who knows they got to make it they got
to make it aesthetically pleasing cuz
this is like really cute uh visuals that
I think add to it
you know I should hey that's not where I
was going to
go
[Music]
hey but that's
fine whole life mask oh yeah cute round
mascots that would be cute but like 1 2
3 4 like it wouldn't need that many
variations so which one which on are you
going to choose right to be in the
game 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
[Music]
11 some really round
mascots typically round mascots a lot of
mascots are really round though what is
this I don't like
this
but I'll make it
work like I you guys are pretty round I
would say
so maybe
H bird birds birds only not only honi
even if it's like you know bird mascots
then there's more actually than just
[Music]
honi like we could have lapas BP in
there too and nissa's
B game and then we call it not sua game
but we call it t
[Music]
game oh yeah for also has a bird mascot
so I'm sure we can get to
[Music]
I'm such a
genius I am such a genius genius Wawa
strikes
[Music]
again
oh
no call it fruity fowl oh that's cute
but but feel like it needs a name that
Japanese members will understand
[Music]
too why why wouldn't you touch you
little shits you for real
[Music]
now
woooo copyright I don't know
I don't ask me about
copyright
I mean we did fan games of other games I
don't know how how that worked how how
was it acceptable to make such a similar
game to
vampire survivors or whatever the name
was of that
game I don't
know must be
some
creative freedom thing I don't
know
uh what's going
on why is the grape in
there I want to save the
grape but one might argue that this is a
favorable position in general with the
lineup here like an
[Music]
l oh hey
o o la
la
oh are you going to join the grape I
don't no I don't hey okay not
[Music]
really wow oh so where are you
going
MH yeah go back go back to oh they will
touch they will touch they will touch no
they will not
touch should I add something here oh
wait it's still moving oh it's moving
back
interesting interesting movement hey oh
oh it touched with the other pach that I
just created also and P
H melon I
mean
yay all
right good
stuff why is it moving so much can you
[Music]
chill so much
trash o
[Music]
huh
M
okay there we go it's calming down I
think yeah just send it all to the
bottom we'll deal with it
later oh yeah you too you too
bye-bye
what rice said what did rice
say what oh you can copyright the art
assets but the idea of a game dropping
things down a space where things will to
move around is not something you can
copyright all right then fan games are
go let's
go really really should I try to push
it it doesn't
work you did not
work this way then no no no no no no no
no no wait not the Apple to no no no no
no no wa
no why do you have to go that way
[Music]
yeah literally so
many stones in my
[Music]
path
rude that's that's what I'm talking
about that's
[Music]
nice this run is like constantly
moving interesting
hey hey where do you think you're
[Music]
going no no no no no no no no no no now
maybe that's good that's fine actually I
guess that's fine cuz then um I can make
a another Apple that will touch that
then the pear will touch and then PE
Peach yeah it's
[Music]
okay
M oh hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
so we already have the Apple but now
this stuff is in the way so I guess
we'll make another
[Music]
Apple okay I'm so sorry it keeps on
happening we'll make an another
[Music]
Apple just make another Apple a no don't
go
[Music]
there here's another
Apple V
why
[Music]
I should have waited I
know I apologize but it's too late to
apologize it's too
late it's too late to
apologize
it's too
late no patience Jo yeah I really just
generally don't have a lot of
patience cuz I'm not a
doctor why would I have any
[Music]
patience
but hey what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm so
funny
oh what why would you feel pain for that
that's that's well not my problem cuz
again I'm not the doctor go to the
doctor tell tell the doctor you felt
pain from that not me
not my problem sounds like a you
[Music]
problem
hey pushing it works it just works W
always
Works Unlimited W
works the is going to look at be
funny when I tell him the orange lady on
the Internet is giving me pain
no no he will he will just not
understand he will agree but he will
just not
understand
peaches yummy beautiful
[Music]
peaches when is peach season I saw in
Supermarket I saw swet now what's fet
again uh plums it's plum seed why there
no plums in here plums are yummy I love
plums plums are
good is the game creator or Plum
hater what's his
issue
[Music]
oh wait for
me and
me I'm a great I love the skin
especially I saw other girls discussing
uh especially Japanese girls I know they
don't or like in Korea
too I think in a lot of Asian countries
you peel the
grapes I wouldn't do
that oh it's normal in Europe to just
eat them like that some people even
don't even spit out the
seeds just chew those too chew them down
we have strong teeth after all the
evolution has granted us strong strong
teeth thank you Evolution
[Music]
Senai yeah it just seems like so
so annoying and it's not only grapes
I've noticed that Japanese people just
don't like eating fruit with any any
skin in general like they peel or also
also Koreans though again they peel they
try to peel everything like apples
apples
too I mean okay some will still eat them
with the skin but then I see a lot of
like peeling going on all the
time h
okay no certain things like kibbies and
bananas I do agree should be
peeled they don't find the skin
appealing
[Music]
the skin yeah that's also the thing skin
of fruits often has like the most
nutrients
so I think I if it wasn't such a mandai
annoying thing to do I would maybe peel
apples too but it's it just takes too
long it's annoying and then yeah it's
still very edible with the peel so I'm
fine with eating
it the skin with the peel
peel can you say that with the
peel is that a
thing you don't even peel them for pies
[Music]
oh oh wow that was an instant
relief you see that you see that you see
that see
that it all just came tumbling down
trickling
down the trickle down
effect he's
real
[Music]
M oh
[\h__\h] all
right Apple KAG
nomics just bam here's a melon take
it wait to get political
sheesh you ever ate a durian I did I
tried one in uh
Indonesia uh but they were like Frozen
Frozen durian like normal durian and
then Frozen durian
pancakes Mauna got them for
me and well of course as expected I
didn't like it very much cuz I also just
didn't what the [\h__\h] grow up with
it
um um
okay so the flavor is
not really common to
me where do I put this
grape why would you put this grape maybe
here I can build I can make it into
something cuz it won't land on any of
the
sides yeah
[Music]
no whatever I don't understand what you
guys are
saying
[Music]
uh okay okay
oh
[Music]
okay
uh no oh
[Music]
well
Apple score still under
[Music]
2,000 why won't you
touch why what's your problem what did
the other pair par do to
you why are you mad at
[Music]
them what did you do to
them what I don't know no yes I know all
on purpose oh according to Kaku I saw it
in my
dreams
I planned it all out as I told you you
know the visual Vis visualization
[Music]
technique tactical genius thank you
thank you thank
you why didn't your kako include the
pineapple
stetching
cuz
[Music]
cuz um they
will but if I do too many things at the
same time people will accuse me of
cheating cuz I'm just so
good so I have to go
slowly I'm just going to make several
pineapples as we said
[Music]
before
oh I I hallucinated I
thought I thought there was something
there literally hallucinating
now that's
[Music]
okay see we have this situation
again but it's
fine it's
[Music]
fine okay how is this going to work is
something going to
fly no okay okay okay okay okay
your
[Music]
um I'm close to a third
pineapple let's put that here oh oh okay
but I'm
building but then the they won't
touch they will not
touch I just got to give it as many
options as
possible o I'm running out of
space can I put it
here
yes um
[Music]
um
um left or right depends on what comes
next you
know I'm going
to It's Not Over You little
[Music]
shits where is my
orange where the [\h__\h] is my
orange but you thought it was over and
it wasn't it was still
going okay okay okay pretty good pretty
good broke another record of
myself yeah new third I'm
improving yesterday I was like
struggling to get 2,000 right now I'm
like constantly over 2,000 so we see a
big
Improvement mhm
[Music]
I can see you getting over
3K yeah I mean I'm like always like
really close I just need to like be
better with my placement
but I feel like a lot of it is just RNG
you
know pray to the
rngsus but if I get better
placement then like I always have more
than enough material to make the
Watermelons like everything's like in
place we have like millions of
pineapples millions of peaches and the
melons it's all there just it's just
never touching that's a whole life
record uh like 3,600 I think from Su
second is like a p sandai somewhere up
there
[Music]
too I don't know how addicted suici but
really is did she even really need to
really practice because I feel like
she's just naturally good at
[Music]
it she did practice a lot
oh I just thought it comes natural to
her with all the tetris
experience
oh
[Music]
Nan she's a god
gamer
peaches again
not being
[Music]
compliant should we tangent a little
bit should
I oh yeah I wouldn't even mind you going
down there saying hi to the other orange
I feel like I'm creating a nice pattern
here
look it's orange grape orange grape
orange grape Orange
grape it looks
[Music]
nice it's colorful it looks like graphic
design is my
passion it might
[Music]
be oh
oh
she get scored by how artistic my board
is thank
you I agree she get points for a beauty
and
[Music]
cleanliness more cherries I I'm getting
so many of them might as well for down
here if there's already such a huge
mess
yeah we'll deal with it
later this bjm is from me but I think it
suits the game don't you
[Music]
think do you like Cherry I love
cherries who
[Music]
doesn't
all you're welcome guys you're welcome I
did it for
you doing it all for
you
[Music]
oh w why why do they hate me so
much no BM I'm at peace finally you can
dream of something else besides
fruits growing teeth like The Annoying
Orange chasing you trying to get a bite
from you fruit vampire Annoying
Orange
don't don't you love that idea in your
head I know what I'm doing in this run
this
is I don't like it I'm not just not
feeling it it's like uh
disgusting it's disgusting what's with
these free apples and all the
why you're disgust me it's another Apple
this is however really aesthetically
pleasing
graphic design run how about that it's
oh there there we go it it ruined it it
was so
pretty now it's all
[Music]
ruined
I ruined
it no
no don't say
[Music]
that all right we have once again two
pineapples
[Music]
wow I don't know it was so really messy
still not
very
hopeful smug
Cherry at least I'm cleaning up at the
[Music]
top hope this game isn't killing your
not at all I'm I'm like so chill right
now I would like to tell you guys a
tangent though I know I know I
know I know I know I know it might ruin
my concentration but I want to tell you
tangent do I have something let me check
my my
[Music]
tangent
oh uh something weird
happened spooky do you want to hear it's
October spooky season let me hear tell
you a a Horror
Story IRL happened to me for real for
real Horror
[Music]
Story this is
it
okay okay so I was staying in a
hotel um and my hotel room was at at the
very end of the
hallway and I I generally I think this
hotel was pretty good you know I was
quite
satisfied had a good
time then this one
night I'm falling asleep I'm sleeping I
I would say I was like deep deep sleep
status and
I had normally like I was like actually
locking double locking my
doors just this night I only had the one
lock on
it um the one that you could probably
open with a key card I don't
know now I'm like the room is like
really tiny room really really tiny like
Japanese tiny hotel room and and my bed
is like taking up I would say 80% of the
room not if you if you if you count the
hallway if you don't count the hallway
then the bed and the table takes up 90%
of the room there's no there no place to
move um but the bed is like positioned
in a way where it's like behind the wall
so and and facing the window so if I
wanted to look at the door I would have
to like kind of crawl off of my bed and
look around the
corner hard to imagine if I explain it
like that maybe but so basically I can't
see the door when I'm normally laying in
my bed is what I'm trying to say okay so
I was sleeping I was in deep
sleep and I wake
up
from this is at 4:20 I checked my clock
I woke up from a
loud noise that sounds like a really
heavy
door being opened that was really close
to me it sounded like it was my hotel
room door
oh because it was so close it sounded so
close and I was like woken up by it so I
was like really confused like what the
[\h__\h] the first thing I thought was like
I was scared I thought
somebody is trying to enter my room I
was legit scared cuz I was like what
what was that and I was too scared to
look around the corner so I was like
waiting but the the the noise was really
like short and it made me feel like
somebody didn't like completely open it
but just like opened looked and close it
again really
weird so I'm I'm taking a while to make
sure that I don't hear anything anymore
and that it is safe to take a look I'm
just I'm just being a little
chicken
so at during this time I'm also
Gathering my senses waking up more and
more my mind is waking up and assessing
the
situation and
then I look around the corner and make
sure okay there's no one there door is
closed at least at this
moment and then I'm like I lay down but
like it bothers me like it's like what
the
[\h__\h] what did somebody really just enter
who was it why why at this
time you know and then I realized oh
yeah it might have to do with them uh
like every every third day of not having
my room being
cleaned they give you a
message
and cuz you have it in the morning you
could guess they uh they let they let
the night
shift
um uh give out those papers through the
door on the bottom so that in the
morning you see it hey we need to clean
your room
today
h and so I was like okay it's probably
that let me check if the message is
there and then I I I turned on the light
and indeed the message was there but I
was think thinking well they put it
through the door there's not really a
need to open the door right but I was
thinking maybe maybe the um they had
troubles getting it through the door so
they tried to open the
door to get the paper through maybe it
was like stuck or something I don't
know right so that's that's the only
explanation I had in my head cuz it
really sounded like it was my door that
was being
opened and also I just
I at this point I just got mad because
it scared me so
much I don't want to wake up in the
middle of the night and be terrified cuz
I thought there's a burglar entering my
room I don't want that
experience so I call the reception and
I'm like
hey it seems like like I just woke up
from the like sound of somebody
seemingly entering my
room I it really scared me it sounded
like somebody was entering and I thought
I thought somebody was maybe robbing me
because I was so sleepy I was like not
sure what was going on so what's up with
that oh and I also mentioned did you did
you guys do that because you were giving
out the
papers is that what just
happened and then the guy on the
reception he like
explains that yeah they give out those
papers but they
don't um they don't enter the room and
I'm like yeah but I'm I'm like I heard
it I'm pretty sure I heard something
really
loud and he's just
like just not really like giving it
any you know benefit of the doubt that
maybe there was something weird going
on he just like shuts
down my concerns by saying no didn't
happen and then I was like too stunned
to speak cuz I worked in a hotel and
when you have a a scared
concerned uh
guest then you might want to even if you
know for sure like I had many instances
where whatever they're saying I know it
didn't happen that way I know there's a
lot of iCal explanation and this and
that but you want to you want to make
the guest feel safe and you want to make
them feel hurt and want to help them so
I was like stunned that he was not
trying to do that at
all and I just um I was like waiting I
like I was speechless so I waited a few
seconds and I was like well thanks and I
hung up and then I was like upset and I
cried cuz I legit scared being woken up
or something like that and then
um uh I try to calm down and sleep and
all that but here's my solution okay
here's my solution if for for from
someone who works in a hotel who handled
many situations like this before if you
want to make a guest feel better about
this even if you know what they're
talking about is like [\h__\h] you have
to give them the feeling of being
understood and heard how you going to do
that well you can ask them for more
details about what they heard then you
can offer or actually do it you can
check the security cameras see if in the
hallway somebody really did something
there on your door then all the locks
there's usually card readers you can
read the lock did this before you can
see which card tried to enter the
room yeah can do all of this and even
more
M so many ways of trying to to to help
no check the like send someone up if you
don't want to check the camera cuz it's
too annoying you can just send the staff
to the hallway sometimes I would do this
if people U complain about noise you
send someone up and you
check what's going on does it come from
a different room where is it coming from
it's not that difficult yeah don't just
dismiss it yeah that's what I'm
saying
now I woke up again that night by really
loud uh spooky wind noises that I didn't
hear in any of the other nights and that
made me realize one thing I think in
that moment I think I found out I I'm
not sure I never I never really found
out what it was but I I think I know
what it was because I was at the very
end of the
hallway um that that's where the like
emergency stairs were and now what I'm
guessing is that this guy who put out uh
put the the papers under the doors he
went to the very top floor and uh with
the elevator but then worked his way
down with the emergency
stairs floor by floor put it through and
when he was opening the emergency stairs
because it was seemingly a very very
windy night the the heavy heavy door
from the emergency stairs which which
was right next to my door right next to
it made a really loud noise he didn't
enter my room probably I can believe
that
because I tested out my door and it
actually when I woke up it wasn't
actually that my own door wasn't that
loud um can I want to do a rerun I don't
like
this oh
well H and yeah so the heavy emergency
door was in combined with the wind
probably what was so
loud I figured it out myself once again
I am the
[Music]
detective so yeah but you know what I
mean when you're like when you just wake
up and you hear something spooky you're
like what the [\h__\h] is happening you
don't understand you can't assess the
situation
immediately
scary genuinely smart the that
smart thank you yeah first instinct is
panic also genuinely because like I I
know many Hotel stories like I've had
this before where
like
somehow people when people are checked
into a room normally you wouldn't like
give out any c uh uh key cards to any
other people for that room
there's really really rare cases where
for some mistake it does happen some
weird mistake and I it happened to like
uh a colleague of mine before and then
they sent them up and then they entered
a room that where people were already
inside and was just like really like
what the [\h__\h] why are you sending people
up to our
room yeah it it happens like sometimes
people enter rooms that they shouldn't
be entering
happens
[Music]
sometimes but there's an explanation for
everything
[Music]
supposedly there are more keys for room
but no you can always code new
keys usually when you check in they code
the key cards according to the room
number and then they only work for that
room
but you can always quote extra
[Music]
keys why is this an O
moment is this so
fascinating did you guys know here
here's a hotel
tip um something that I didn't know
until I worked at a hotel but it's
actually you could figure fig out
yourself some hotels even let you know
about this you know like the in in most
hotel rooms they have like the
electricity going through a little like
thingy card case thingy where you have
to put in a card and they they tell you
to put in your hotel key card
normally you know you can put any piece
of paper any any like paper in there and
it works you don't have to put in your
uh Hotel key card and the reason why
this is so important is because when
it's like really hot wherever you're
going you don't want to take your key
card stop the electricity and the AC
sometimes you want to keep the AC
running you know so that when you're
back in your room it's nice and cold
right so what to do you take your key
card but you put something else in there
and it keeps it
running
woo life hacks by takanasi kiaha you're
welcome hotels don't want you to do that
um some hotels actually uh do it like
when they know someone important is
checking
in they will prepare their room by also
turning on the AC and all that so that
then when when they first enter their
room it's nice and
chill so some people actually do it for
the guests oh
[Music]
M and then uh the hotel I was staying
at in the other day not not this one I
just told the ghost story about but the
other one from the wedding
trip um actually had like a separate
piece of some paper in the slot
basically telling you hey you don't need
to put in your uh Hotel card in there
cuz we got you covered this this is this
is for this very purpose was already in
[Music]
there we don't get AC in Britain
what what even in Austria the hotels
have some kind of
AC the apartments don't but the hotels
[Music]
do
ah
hey why you glitching on
[Music]
me been to some that have depends I
would say so too
yeah but to
me Japan is like the land of of
the welldeveloped
AC's I love Japanese AC's man I don't
know they know they know how to make
cool toilets and they know how to make
cool
AC's
pineapple
Next
Level I mean I never use those special
functions from Japanese
toilets but at least you know what what
I what I do appreciate is like the seat
opening itself when it senses
someone and the Warmness of the seat is
very conforting to I you know I'm an
idol so I don't use the toilet the same
way you guys do I just I just sit on it
and and just enjoy sitting on it of
course of
course I just sit on it like that's all
I do and I imagine oh wouldn't it be
nice if I had those bodily functions
that normal people do have so I could be
more like a human being it's like you
know like Ariel was wishing she had legs
it's like that
[Music]
I I just I don't know it fascinates
me the thinking for yeah just go there
to
think
exactly
okay is it allowed for me to have such a
clean space with one
melon may I really experience
this is this okay also should I throw
the trash on the right
side I may
really almost 1,000 points and so little
in
here yeah I don't think it's trash
either but you
know
[Music]
wow no
we keep it going we keep keep
adding to the
[Music]
beauty
no what should I keep on the best seat
should should I keep on adding to the
red side now the orange because now
there's a tangerine in there
[Music]
or should we put it left now yeah oh
no the St between no I'm going to ruin
my life if I do
that the pair is on the
left yeah let's build
it or ah the reason why I didn't want to
do that is because I do have a grape
upcoming and I could have put the grape
on the grape oh well ah
you're supposed to land
here
stupid put this
[Music]
here it's okay we'll figure it out
look oh my
God so so
[Music]
beautiful oh okay
I I like where this is go no okay not
anymore cuz the Apple oh okay no it's F
it's good
actually good it's decent it's
[Music]
fine
okay
what this is this is
good I don't know if I maybe I actually
should put the cherries here in this
case Barbie movie watch along why I love
the Barbie movie but I already watched
it in the cinema it's my best run it
kind of
is still on the r and the snap
back unbelievable see it would have
worked it would have worked but okay
this is fine
too
the the fruit selection was pretty
good make sure not to let the melon get
pushed too far up M
okay pit perfect too watch long ah we
need to think about what to do with a
melon a
melon melon watch along no no the
members watch
along no it's not going to be a watch
along basically I want to do not a watch
along cuz we did um watch
along
before okay pineapple here we
[Music]
go
okay those sh if the if the Tangerine
goes down it will become an orange I
don't know if this is good or bad cuz
they're like pushing everything
up
you got to kill the grape it's going to
block kill what do you mean kill you
mean drop
it I'm I was trying to build on
it middle on the grap oh yeah okay wait
we can indeed make something out of this
but where does trash go now still right
side what do you
think yeah okay
something with hand
[Music]
cam yeah I don't know what to do is this
trash I'll put it
[Music]
here
uh
[Music]
n
she the sooner you match the oranges the
less likely it is to push it
up and
[Music]
why you think it's so I was actually
also thinking about the sock puppets
like should I make him early but I don't
really think it's the season yet to make
the sock puppet it's
already it's not the season
yet
[Music]
Apple it's like teasing me it's it's
baiting me to build on the right
side what the do I do should I combine
the pair or should I bring it over
here
left
okay but this one this one has to
[Music]
go oh
okay nice
[Music]
combination it happened guys it just
happened I didn't do it it just
happened
[Music]
I'm
not
okay okay fine
[Music]
ah
what I
do so sad this was the Run don't say
that it's still the
[Music]
run myi I was going to put something
else
[Music]
there it's still fine it's still clean
it's not even that much
trash
[Music]
I want to put the grape there but
okay I'm going
to actually okay if I would have known
it was two
grapes I should have known it was going
to be two grapes I should have known let
me put it let me put it
[Music]
here where did I put the
orange
[Music]
I know I know that's what I said what I
me left but not far left
[Music]
like above
the yeah maybe
here what's with the
cherries
okay
[Music]
we just going back to the Wawa way cuz
it's looking
complicated
oh lots of material to work with at
least just going to make
another two two here to
here
it's it's fix it's not
bad it's
good now I wonder if I should put this
here and wait for another
Tangerine or if I should put it
here left or right what do you
think might
work free pair is perfectly space
perfectly so that they so that they
won't touch each other too late for left
left left left left
left oh who would have thought that
there would be an or orange
upcoming and another
one there we
go kick
it okay let's see what what's happening
maybe something's going to
jump
[Music]
oh M comfortable oh hey who said it's
over you little shits who said it's over
you little shits who said
it it's not over still getting the
points and good fruits good big fruits
okay I'll be I'll be careful
now um I'll ask you guys more what do
you think we should
do um
trash I mean we should probably
build I don't know we should probably
finish the Peach on the left side like
we should make another pair on the left
side but should we use the Cherry for
it a trash on
left you guys want me to build on the
right side
okay let's see if that will be our
downfall see I might just with the trash
be automatically building
stuff oh no
doio
ah thanks for the
raid yes Peach on right is sua
oh uh troop
[Music]
okay I want to
push the Tangerine
over but I don't know if it will do it
should I put the grape on the
left
oh welcome welcome welcome we have a
good run right
now they wanted me to give up but I
believed in
it maybe on the pineapple I'll try
yeah y the double
orange the double orange hitting me with
the double orange for real now
they're never going to touch if I put
them if I put the oranges on there
[Music]
now should I should I just put it away
for
now maybe a miracle will
happen like what I'm thinking is the way
to salvage this is adding another grape
onto the grape so the tangerine these
two will combine then I can drop another
orange another Tangerine probably
eventually here and then they'll be big
enough to touch hopefully I don't know
you know yeah so put this here for now
oh there's the
gravee there's the grape oh there it is
this is oh this is
perfect
yeah
now now
oh we need we need oh we still need so
much to get to the peach
[Music]
guys you want me I was thinking if if I
could push it
[Music]
oh it
worked I was I was wondering if that if
I could do
that w
so we need another pair but spacewise
it's it might be difficult anyway we
could
build we could try to block this part
and build it in the middle I don't know
I don't know I don't I don't no what it
worked of course it did of course it
did should I put the grape here cuz it's
going to turn into an orange
immediately
[Music]
M yeah
okay um yeah I don't know where to build
the the next
pair on top of here
again I
no here again or I try like I can't
really squeeze it in I can't I can't
squeeze it in here
realistically it has to be here kind of
on the on the pineapple more or less but
for it to not fall
down I kind of have to block it
off no I can't put it on the
right it will go there eventually
hopefully if we can like throw it over
again
okay
so
um here or
here I fall down
[Music]
anyway
Middle with the tangerine
what if I put the Tangerine here and
then the orange
here the Tangerine will be a way of
blocking I don't
know
yeah you like that idea
[Music]
okay
umm
[Music]
d
d but great position I
[Music]
think that was an early push I didn't
expect it so early uh great position
but the upcoming positioning is
difficult cuz like I put if I put the
torine down it's going to like tumble
over here then the Orange is going to
barely have space then I need I need to
be lucky and get another Tangerine to
make it into an apple
immediately and then the question is is
it going to touch properly is it going
to touch the left one before it touches
the right
[Music]
one you
know was it
[Music]
questions yeah we need two
tangerines
well well this one I have to place here
right cuz it's going to end up here
anyway it's going to fall
down a
cherry a a
cherry I mean
maybe I could use it as a barrier and
push the Tangerine out of the way from
the left
Apple
asop AR
[Music]
Jesus
um
uh if we don't I know you want to give
up right now but let's say we don't give
up cuz like they're small enough to put
them
somewhere I could put them in like you
know some spaces and the orange could
come
[Music]
next okay
let's put it
[Music]
here oh no no no no no
no there it is
um I don't think it can take
another like if it turns into a grape I
think it
might explode
uh not sure where to put the strawberry
it might fit
here it might work left
but but then when I put the orange uh
here I don't think the game is going to
like that even
though you
know I don't know okay we'll put it
we'll put it here we'll see what
happens whatever happens there's also a
high chance even if we succeed that
something will fly and ruin it anyway
should I is there is it important that I
go byy an exact pixel of where to drop
it like like line it up really
nicely like or should I go like sideways
what do you
[Music]
think on the side more to the right or
to the
[Music]
left
left yeah at least what we just
accomplished is that it wouldn't fall
down to the other Apple we wanted to
combine on the right side can the melon
stop shaking
it's making me nervous I'll drop it here
or more left
more left here what about
[Music]
here
okay more all
right I don't know 3 2
one it should have been more right
should have been more
right
if anything it should have been more
right maybe I don't
know I was
I it was it was it was a good run there
was potential the the the ending RNG was
pretty bad with the fruits that were
being offered to
[Music]
us
why why why why
[Music]
why ruined my
beautiful beautiful
run most people lose their way after the
first big fruit shows
up no not me not me not
me it was so clean
too such a pretty
run but you can't have it
all can't have it
[Music]
all but we go again maybe this is the
Run who
knows
Su the
flying what was it was it the grape the
flying
[Music]
grape if a grape can fly then I'm sure
you chickens can fly
too all right
peaches yeah touch oh yeah
[Music]
touchdown
hey
sexy very very
sexy pineapple hey stream pineapple guys
my my uh it's not a single but has an
amazing 3D MB one of my favorite album
songs
pineapple
hey I'm going one two one two three it
tastes so so so sweet when you go and
kiss me I'm taking the perfect
picture ooh you're stuck to me like a
sticker you got that
[Music]
pineapple
m
m n my my strawberry is bound to enter
this danger
[Music]
zone love Rush too love Rush every song
is nice all my album songs are
[Music]
nice now you want pineapple juice
pineapple juice pineapple juice is
indeed quite
nice I like pineapple juice
too
and pineapple
pizza I had I dreamed about pineapple
pizza last night I just remembered there
was pineapple pizza in my dream somebody
made it for me but it wasn't just
pineapple pizza it was a combination of
pineapple and tuna Pizza my two favorite
pizzas combined into one thing not
really something I would like make in
reality they don't even like make these
in
restaurants but I wouldn't say it would
be
disgusting it could
work H it's not a nightmare it's it's a
good dream good
dream
Doo o all
[Music]
right okay you do you my dear orange
friend
bounce
[Music]
don't ah didn't go far
enough it's so rude so
[Music]
mean it's not looking good right now but
there's always this like um time where
things just look messy and then at some
point
everything
just suddenly
transforms just big
big
big big big change of oh there you go
see it's happening see that's what I'm
talking about so that was still one of
the smaller
ones yeah it will sort itself
out oh oh that
was O uh also too much that is too much
trash that is an uncomfortable amount of
trash
okay is it
moving no sometimes it's hard to tell
cuz they're turning what makes them turn
why do they turn sometimes and sometimes
they don't is it like how they're
touching other fruits is that making
them turn is that making them nervous or
[Music]
so
H gravity
magic will of their
[Music]
own
mhm physics
[Music]
engine do you guys know the those videos
from the channel
cut I just want to share a really funny
moment that I saw
today the the speed dating thing that
they do you know
that I saw a moment today where like
this like basically it's like you know
uh speed dating uh with like a buzzer in
the middle if you don't like what you're
seeing you push the buzzer and then you
got rid of the person that's across you
and then you switch it out to a
different person yeah so the button yeah
but there was this funny moment I have
to share it this girl this like
religious seem seemingly religious
girl uh she says or I think there's like
the the MC that's like buting in and
he's like Oh I thought that would work
he's like uh this girl her name she
likes she's into Jesus or or she said it
herself I'm not
sure and and oh yeah I think the button
said it
and then she's like yeah yeah I love
Jesus and then the guy is like oh me too
and she's like yeah
really and then he's like yeah I like a
a good G or something like that he said
that and she's like what
what she's like literally like trying to
understand what he's saying cuz if even
if it's like a common word when you
think you're talking about something
else you don't sometimes you hear it as
some
gibberish
[Music]
and she asks like twice like what what
what and he's like go go ches you like
you said you like Jesus and she's like
no I meant I meant Jesus Christ and then
he was so embarrassed by it that he
buzzed himself out and just left but
that was so
funny cuz like she was really
happy
about somebody liking Jesus too wait I
think my hello beep is here wait they're
calling
H he talking to
Jesus okay whatever doesn't
matter they should just put it down in
front of my
[Music]
door hello hello
beep sponsorship
do no oh okay BRB
[Music]
ah so
annoying they used to just put it at uh
in front of my door but nowadays they
just always need my
signature always need to
confirm oh
sh why just put it there also sometimes
when I'm actually really not there they
will they will just put it there without
my signature so where's the where's a
problem ah thank you hi
[Music]
Aura they want My
Autograph it's not the usual autograph
though it's not my idol
autograph
it's my mature looking totally mature
looking adult
[Music]
signature oh the lame one yes Sara
couldn't back I stole her signature I
know it's identity theft
[Music]
but oh paches they're so
pretty all right
okay they have such a beautiful color to
them wow gorgeous just
damn
slate Alexa play pineapple by
Tak every time I create a pineapple it
should actually automatically be I
should put it on my
soundboard by the way since I like
scheduled the rest of the week already I
don't think you'll be seeing the sua
game on my channel for a while maybe
never ever again who knows because I
feel like by the time of like next early
next week it's just
over I just have a feeling it's I
already missed like so much of the
hype I'm late to the party
[Music]
anyway I feel like I'll be too late you
know oh
nice
you're fine with
that tail say is not too early wasn't
the release
November it's just the beginning of
October shelf
[Music]
life my Freo just arrived oh I'm still
waiting for my H talk merch I asked
jenma before I don't think they I think
they forgot to send me my merch merch
and now there is probably nothing left
over can somebody somebody who bought my
holot talk merch give me
some please I really wanted to holot
talk merch cuz like holot talk is really
special to me speaking of I should
probably get that nanora episode
[Music]
going especially I should do it now
before I go to Japan again
right
[Music]
totally did I not do vame
already why does it feel like I already
do did vame
[Music]
episode I
didn't oh
Oh I thought I
[Music]
did oh man what is
this no when you tumble
down and of course they will not
touch
whatever I'll make a million pairs if I
have
[Music]
to
really
[Music]
the
peach I have an extra whole tug mug if
you're interested I was worried I would
at least I would break at least one yeah
man if only you could give that one to
me damn I
[Music]
wish I wonder if they forgot about
producing one for me if they can produce
another one that peach is losing
it look at the bottom
Peach is it
[Music]
freezing it doesn't seem Dau I love the
Hol talk shirt oh yeah right so it was a
shirt and the mug and the the standy I
think you know normally I also don't
like doing acrylic uh stands because I
do think they're like overdone like as
like official
merchandise but I thought the for the
holot talk one I really like that
[Music]
one nice nice aim there making it into a
grape oh still happening still
happening
okay once again the waa proves she can
do
it
and my current score literally says
yay
IM
yay let's go
[Music]
yay the fruits were going like Yay let's
go um
no I should be building on the left side
oopsie well things will probably move
around anyway whether I like it or
[Music]
not we need another pineapple that's
what we
need oh
okay all right all right all right all
right why is it on the right side we
don't want it on the right side maybe I
should shoot my trash on the right side
so that everything would move to the
right side
right yeah that's that's that's more
like it wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait here there's another chair
here absolutely yes sorry I was late to
notice trash
trash not trash not trash Peach
baby
uh you know what I'm going to grow this
now that I made the
[Music]
peach give me another strawberry ah it's
a cherry should have left the Cherry
[Music]
then ah ah
do not block the two
pineapples what there's only one what do
you
[Music]
mean I don't know where to put things um
o o
ooh my future
[Music]
one the peach is a potential
pineapple
damn all
right
uh man it's it's difficult choices are
very
difficult this difficult [\h__\h] left or
right left or right left or right left
or right get R okay oh but say that
would have been another
one oh
man
okay I was on to
something
M the the I need to do something with
the grape because otherwise it's just
going to be in the
[Music]
way yeah don't you
agree we should be sending down the
cherries to the to the grape
[Music]
Maybe
or strawberries I don't know whatever
but there's a cherry up coming so okay I
think this Tangerine will stay up yeah
okay and giving us big access to the
grape there are two cherries that's at
least one strawberry and another
strawberry okay perfect and enough
strawberry this one I think I'll send to
the
[Music]
right there's a grape UPC com
so
come yeah
okay ah
MAA should I put the Tangerine up here
and then the grape here and then see
what comes next maybe another
[Music]
gravee right very right really see now
there's the grave
did you not expect there to be another
grape
[Music]
guys is it moving
no
um I'll put it here okay it's pretty
stable um
so RNG hasn't been RNG hasn't been good
to me lately so
yes always expect the second grape yes
yes but now we have two grapes so I
wonder even if I put them here they're
going to Tumble down so it's not even
going to be in the right placement but I
can put it
[Music]
here so
Kuru right man you guys don't believe in
the suas
in the grapes see this could have been
us but you say no to
it nice trash shoot
[Music]
though okay stable stable
AE thank God it's not
moving
um Dam I just need a
[Music]
tangerine
there that scares me because what if the
Tangerine
flies Co the
skittle I can probably land it in a way
that now even that it's kind of
difficult to land this orange so that it
touches the other
Orange
M I would have preferred a
tangerine trash it
oh well we can at least try it before we
trash it cuz if it doesn't work it will
trash itself do not wait for 10 oh okay
okay what to bigy
that it's not
coming
ah n there oh but if I put it there now
it would probably touch the bottom
Tangerine but uh the bottom orange but
what happens to the
Tangerine what do you
think it will block the Apple it's going
to
bounce okay just going to put it here
then there it is
stop
Yes watermelon oh it's it's the year
niss
congratulations nice
numbers sua time it's called sua game so
maybe you could see anytime you get a
watermelon since it's also the last
fruit that you can get as you winning
the game I would say so I would say this
is the way to win the
game now I would put the grape on the
left I
think I don't know about you guys but
now that there's another grape I regret
it of
course
[Music]
do like it it fits better down here
spacewise I want to send the Cherry down
here look for strawberry clean up the
right okay I'll wait I try to wait for
strawberry but I think I have to land it
here okay
um can I put here oh
no
dummy oh there's a
[Music]
strawberry should I put some I mean it's
not going to move right away but should
I put some weight on the
strawberry top left it's probably going
to fall down yeah
oh
well we go with the
flow let's go with the flow whatever
score I get out of this I'm happy with
it
Peach
[Music]
is actually could make another
strawberry here maybe it will go there
eventually
if I build a tangerine here it might
like the moment it becomes an orange it
could like like jump a little
bit
[Music]
possibly and make way for the strawberry
I don't know I'm just like experimenting
now yeah yeah yeah yeah see see
see oh but it doesn't reach cuz the
peach is too
fat that's okay it will maybe
[Music]
later but then it's still just a a grape
though how's that help me oh
well oh well oh
[Music]
well
M okay oh yeah that's
fine so many strawberries and
tou
uh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah good
oh it's like I literally feel like it
just hatched an
egg
suddenly Birth has
happened
I put this
[Music]
here those Shield here or
here probably here oh
touches
no
[Music]
no I mean all good things come to an end
so
yeah but why I accept losing with like
when I'm like out of space but the
moments where something just flies
off that's just not a nice way to
lose
ah it would have totally been my new
record if it wasn't for that stupid
flying was it the pineapple was the
pineapple don't thing that sent
something
flying
[Music]
man so
rude just so rude oh wow
was it a
tangerine I was going pretty
[Music]
well okay okay tangent time I saw so
much um whole Al merchandise in
convenience
store and especially actually only in
the
Lawson so if you guys are going to Japan
soonish feel like it depends like
sometimes we have some stuff in Family
Mart sometimes I think even at 7-Eleven
but I feel like Lawson is like the most
common for our
collaborations
at least from what I've
observed uh and they had do you guys
remember long time ago I retweeted some
Bai
Namo uh made whole life
merchandise and it's like the ones where
like in we're like hugging
something small small whole life members
hugging
something and I it was really confusing
as to how you get to
those cuz it was implying that it was
like gacha related I think that was the
thing I found uh some of them in
Lawson and it stood out to me so much
because the moment when I found
them uh in like they were lined up in a
way that in the very front was me and
bales
and then behind the uh us were like more
of the
others but it was us in the front so I
was like oh that's me I was just looking
for the shelf and then I suddenly see me
you
know and whoever you guys don't know
who's ba who Bales is but yeah that's
[Music]
bales
I was like contemplating buying it cuz I
wanted to rescue myself I guess you know
it's it's funny like you see yourself
your merchandise out there and you you
want to buy it just to rescue
yourself like adopting you feel like
this piece of merchandise has a soul and
you need to rescue it it's like
suffering there in the Shelf it needs a
[Music]
home I like ah you remember I don't even
remember that the black work
shooter thing yeah I did rescue
[Music]
that I
did nice nice
bounce and then I saw uh the those those
those things those like weird cracker
cookie thingies that I opened in the
Twitter space that I did
Mooney also opened some by the way that
she got from
jenma my lyric lyric writer by the way
is morning in case you don't know
wa
explosive but like I opened three she
opened like two of three and none of
them had Wawa only Japanese
members those would have like a little
like snack inside and um
stickers shiny sparkly stickers but I
figured out something guys I thought
that you know there's like two different
uh packaging versions one with me on the
front and one without and I thought that
it meant that only the one with me on
the front has the option of getting me
but turns out no that's not
true you could get me from the other
packaging
too just in case anybody's making a trip
to Japan anytime soon cuz like so many
of my acquaintances and friends are like
going to Japan like these recent
weeks one after
another one of my good uh friend no good
good acquaintances decent
friend he's also in Japan now and I was
like oh my
God if only I had time to meet but makes
no sense to meet in Japan I guess cuz we
can meet in Europe all the
time
I know it's a weird way to say it but
we're like not besties at all but we're
good friends good
friends I would hope
[Music]
so uh but yeah uh what was I going to
say oh yeah so the stickers and then the
the little the sticker crackers and the
the little Banda unle things there were
several ones but there's a bigger
selection other stores that's not
convenience stores
[Music]
apparently oh why did I do
that and then there was um one more
thing that was not with Ian members but
um I need to I took a picture actually
wait let me show you do you want to see
I took some pictures for you guys just
for
you was so awkward taking pictures of
the
[Music]
shelves where was
it which
one ah
here so just I want to just give you a
feeling of what it's
like um let me just in case
sensor everything else
[Music]
maybe it's just so fascinating cuz like
overseas convenience stores and
Supermarket they would never like have
this kind of stuff this is only in
Japan only can experience this kind of
like H life is everywhere
feeling
inan okay this is good
go oh yeah this was also there
right oh
oh this was quite
[Music]
something one moment one
moment
okay okay I think it's
good let me send it to JMA so I can
download it on my
PC still haven't found a better way of
doing these kind of
[Music]
things ah so many pictures this one two
three oh and I guess this one should be
okay
[Music]
yeah you just have an empty server a
yeah I see some people doing that what
the [\h__\h] I have N9 DMs
narissa this was like 3 hours ago
narissa says out of nowhere Ki I love
you and I appreciate you thank you for
being you have a very good day
M are you
good the Pomo also messaged me I don't I
don't think I can read this one out loud
it's
secret oh interesting
now and mix the mix is everything's
finalized for my your vision song all
[Music]
right oh I was like where is the sound
coming from oh it's my phone
probably
okay could you repeat that and what what
what what did you really not hear
me
what the fairy
doing
what she's so cute when she's like that
with you Marissa she's always
[Music]
cute
okay all right I got the pictures so in
one convenience store and this is like
you know in Japan there's like
especially free convenience stores that
are like everywhere in every street
corner lawon 7-Eleven and Family Mart
Family Mart Family
Mart so this is like really really
common you could find this anywhere so
first of all these ones
right these ones that I
opened uh by the way it tastes like
cereal it's like a big cookie looking
thing but it tastes like
cereal and then it's a sticker inside
random sticker and uh oh in this case
there's both of the same packagings next
to each other but there's another
version where I'm also on the
packaging this wasn't the same
convenience
store
wo Wawa waa and
Bales this is how I found
it but these are Clips but they have
like the same thing as like keychains
and so
on but I was lucky to find this and I
didn't buy it
[Music]
though and and this clip version you can
get non-random like you can actually
choose it but everything else is like
random like you buy it in a packaging
where you don't see what's
inside but I found this and I was like
oh it's me
[Music]
and then then I found this one I
actually bought I bought some Ito Jaga
the the cereal cookies
too but uh on a different day this one I
also actually bought cuz I love this one
when I first saw this collaboration art
I was like oh my God I love it so much
cuz I love this
artist um and and this chocolate is also
a very
well-known a popular
chocolate that even I like like I don't
like much Japanese chocolate but this
one I like it's canu Mamu country ma'
it's like uh you can see it on the
packaging little relatively soft cookies
with chocolate chips
inside and on this one I didn't open it
yet but there's a apparently a postcard
inside is sccha
but I'm happy with whatever cuz the art
is so cute and the whole packaging is so
cute normally the packaging is not like
this not this pink it's just because of
the collaboration but this is so famous
so I was surprised to see a
collaboration with country
man and same convenience store one more
thing that I found can you imagine so
much whole life merchandise in a in a
convenience store that you can just so
casually walk in into and buy things
at
TA this is also a really famous
chocolate in
Japan then
Magi uh macademia and almond nuts
chocolate it had um these four
versions I didn't buy these though but
okay apparently it also comes with it
says
uh magnet magnet
sheet a magnetic sheet maybe you can put
it on a fridge or
so these chocolates are pretty good
though I would say they're very well
known as
well so if you were to buy all of these
you would have a decent haul to show
off isn't this nice Chu oh there may
have been also sub
one not lined up in this
case aren't we
jealous I I went into other lawon and
they weren't as stocked up as this one
and also I would guess a lot of these
are very time limited so if you go there
and you don't find it it may have to do
with the like time or it may have to do
with the stop
U but in FY they would have these things
[Music]
now Shu may have been like the previous
lineup apparently according to Japanese
bro it's just so fascinating sorry for
this little break but I find this so
fascinating so many collabs and then
like all of these brands are like
snack
Brands
yeah like for me when I see it I still
kind of see it like out of a fan
perspective I think cuz like I normally
don't see it then I go to Japan and I
see this stuff and it's like oh [\h__\h]
damn that's so
cool yeah so famous like in Japan we're
like next level famous it's just again
and again such
a yeah big exciting surprise
in Japan whole life is a
lifestyle yeah you can also right now as
I said yesterday I think and retweeted
already um you can see whole live
English myth advertisement in Akihabara
big one I wish it was like one or two
days earlier than I would have seen it
man
[Music]
okay
um I decided to put trash on the right
side I don't know if that's
okay oh it seemed to be okay oh
all according to
kak always in Japan for popular
what something always in your whole life
to see when you leave oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah
trash left now gota grow the peach okay
but this is not trash right but there it
bothers me that there's a whole grown
ass orange
there bothers me what I do about that do
I just wait
for for the melon to to like go over
it
ignore unnecessary sacrifice don't let
it bother you okay okay at least it
makes a a big space for all the trash
that I'm going to put
[Music]
there
mhm
[Music]
um okay I will grow The
Grapes oh wait sorry that was reflex
that was reflex was my
[Music]
reflex
well but it's already so up high maybe I
could grow
it if I make it into an apple the
mountain will automatically push it
up why
why I'm good at launching stuff yes I
[Music]
am still
left your high score is
2,447 wow good night thanks for being
here so you don't you don't want me to
do the thing that I just suggested suest
maybe I will though let me
try M M M it will resolve
itself sooner or
later I have no space for trash right
now there it
goes
oh I am so
[Music]
sorry
you forgive me
[Music]
now okay okay okay everything's fine
everything's fine I just don't want to
land the Tangerine on here can you
please balance yourself no no
wait I will grow this
mess don't
[Music]
worry
pop pop pop pop
[Music]
you I just don't really understand the
whole trash
principle cuz it it it I guess it's it's
the
desired right then in the end the trash
becomes something good too just
automatically and you just hope for it
to go
well man it's getting tight in
here
[Music]
oh
to oh my God oh my
God
once again the pears are far far
[Music]
far
uh
[Music]
uh help help help
help
please wait let let let let the grape in
okay I ruined
it
oh this Mel the melon the melon is
shaking
nothing wants to
touch is excited for new friends for
upcoming
melons I don't know if I can give you
that if I can provide you with
[Music]
that no go down go
down go
[Music]
it will not go
down it will never go
[Music]
down it's
over it's
[Music]
over
oh it went down a little
bit only a little bit
oh
[Music]
okay maybe next one is last
one because I'm at 4 hours of sua game
now it's not
healthy wait hey
M last one for real for
real wait what time is it 9:00
p.m.
uh my brain is like getting mushy anyway
not not from the music just from the
game
[Music]
play I'm really proud of my Nik noiko
score H so if anything I see uh today is
a success
M
yeah whatever
happens it was all meant to
be and I'm
happy with the outcome
hey oh
[\h__\h] I like to be more
gentle thank
[Music]
you
what do you mean it's still over you
mean the stream is still over
right it's so over our stream is heading
soon
no there it goes I didn't want that but
[Music]
okay yeah watermelon was there
watermelon made an appearance that's all
I need for my personal
satisfaction I
think I mean the more the Maria but it's
fine I'm not obsessing with
anything where am I putting the gumy the
trash maybe
[Music]
here
okay gift memberships let's
go kfb being so nice so
welcoming
[Music]
sual after today I have a day off
tomorrow doing some stuff and then and
then there's AOE too I need to check
with
MAA how how the perms are going the
tournament
perms if that worked
out I'm not sure
[Music]
tph
oh it popped the the the
the the bubble popped the baby P pble
bubble the water
broke I saw had on well I have it too
but it doesn't mean
anything I had many things on my
schedule before that didn't happen
that is not an
[Music]
argument the baby
puddle that comes from the popped
bubble and then out comes the bubble
bubble oh my God it's literally baby
speech did I just hear
meow do you hear meow
guys oh I hear hi chky wonky I knew it
was chky wonky you see me I was like
that but you probably didn't hear
it she's doing a squid
Squatch nice squid Squatch enjoying the
squid
scatch are you happy hi oh she's saying
hello chunky want me oh she has water
drops on her face she just had water did
you like the the hydration
don't he
I caught her she immediately runs away
the moment I put my feet on the ground
but I got you I got you water drinking
girl she's moist do you want to play the
S game H oh she's purring my
baby oh
yeah this is way better than any
PGM
[Music]
oh who's a happy
baby you're happy
baby aren't you happy baby H she's a
happy baby moist and
fluffy cozy
sleepy happy baby
I'm rubbing her
belly best air
simar yeah you like the bny Ws Don't
You
O remember yesterday the the smacking
lips that smoothie
did you're not going to smack your lips
at me are
you cuz that's kind of rude isn't it but
you she smacks her lips a lot too
though she's so she's always so
happy
oh look I would just like look at
her or sometimes even when I don't look
at her but I just kind of look in her
Direction she will like start to purr
she's just any attention I give her she
loves it
should I let you
go I'll let you
go go
byebye byebye juny wony thanks for
saying
hi thank you for this little cat break
and you should be thanking me
honestly ah there go the GBS
[Music]
Peaches I want to push it to the other
Peach but at the same time I want to
turn the grape into
[Music]
something it's over
don't why you just saying this at this
point at any
moment building left launch to
okay well well you say building but this
I guess you can't really call this
building but there it
goes there it goes yep okay oh yeah
yeah it's still not touching come on you
can do it
come
on no it doesn't want
to it doesn't want
[Music]
to unfair Advantage I always start with
two melons
already push harder I can't push harder
put more weight on them okay let me try
oh it goes away I'm
sorry puss
puss e you go here
maybe oh they're doing some spicy things
they were humping each other the fruits
are
[Music]
humping okay but the pineapple still
don't want to touch cuz they hate
me and they hate each
[Music]
other yeah that's uh I just got to make
another
peit it is what it is I guess I'll
should I build it on here or here left
or right what do you
[Music]
think on the
left the gap on the right is opening
up well I just do it on the left side
but here I'm putting this here
o uh I I don't know it just kind of
turns out like this but this is fine
actually it's fine that's actually good
it's good it's good it's good it's good
it's good
[Music]
I think I will use the grape no I guess
I'm not using the
[Music]
grape
okay um will I use the grape
[Music]
now yes I will maybe I will maybe I will
yes I will yes I will yes I will and
there there we go this should do the
trick
yes okay now I'll build another
pineapple on the right
[Music]
sidea and put trash
here the apple is taking up a lot of
space down
[Music]
there it's all coming together
it
[Music]
is but it really makes me wonder if I
really shouldn't use all the
trash
pair now to pair the pair with another
pair but first an apple cuz that's how
Evolution goes and the
fruit fruit Evolution
[Music]
line there it goes there it goes we've
got a pit
[Music]
Ah that's taking so much space that's
terrible that's
[Music]
terrible m
but I'll I'll build a peach here yeah
but I don't know if I can use anything
of the things that are like already down
there probably
not those are lost
[Music]
forever or yeah I could try to make
another Apple down but wait what it will
just take up more and more space the
bigger I make
it if you make the orange down or red it
can combine with the Apple what down the
[Music]
red you mean make another orange here so
it combines with the Apple yeah but like
then it's down there where I can't reach
it anyway and it's just shooting up the
melon higher higher
[Music]
higher I'll put this here for now
ah okay I did not ECT that it would move
so
[Music]
much this is not the run but it's a run
and it's
[Music]
okay there we
go going to make another Tangerine
[Music]
hopefully
um wait one apple two
apples I guess I'll do this yo that was
dangerous stranger
danger I just want to another grape
TBH I'm going to put might put this here
I know I know I know
but ah wait I can make a
grape
uh okay I take it all
back
ah I messed up kind
of thanks for the
memberships m
I don't know like these two pairs If
Only They would touch now making another
one is just not econom economically
economically
thriving because I have to make two
apples
[Music]
first I I can't do it but I will fail at
it
[Music]
again I like your fancy words funny
waha should I try something
here then then again it will not reach
the Final
[Music]
Destination y
y commit to the peach well but how like
I'm just going to put something here and
here and here and why did this have to
no I have no space I have no space I
just I just don't have
space I'm already running out of
space
oh okay but the pineapples will
literally never touch
never they are not planning on ever
touching so it's over it's so
over
[Music]
so I'm just like building out of fun
now just just your little shits I hate
you more apples sure why
not it's
over
[Music]
but at least I got over 2,000
again it's over it's over it's over it's
so
over
man why it got to be like
that well well
well well well well it was a good time
nonetheless
tanos tanos thank you for watching guys
we'll read a few more Super
chats that I didn't finish yesterday and
maybe we can finally catch up
again because my old old
knes are too weak to be
always running after the Super chats get
it get
it don't B
[Music]
me it was
funny and even if it wasn't funny it's
like a genius moment where I'm thinking
of interesting ways of using the English
language which is not my first language
so you better respect me for
that
was my was the Shadow on my neck always
like
[Music]
this always like
this
no no no actually I think that's a bug
cuz I look at myself on my
phone and I have a different outfit on
there the dandle and it the Shadows like
all this like the same color
[Music]
actually I just noticed this
now there's more and more things just
[Music]
weird I mean when I just look like this
it actually gives maybe a nice dep but
maybe it's too
much it's not
normal I didn't notice got to check I
got to inspect maybe if if this is also
something weird I can report it together
with the blouse
transparency and then I have two things
and that might be worth
fixing okay let's put on a different
BTM
uh which one which one I feel like I
always choose the same ones
recently I want to play this one
maybe no it's too
exciting needs to be
more a bit more calm although I really
like actually it's oow bar so I can play
this
spoopy uh where do we
[Music]
go
a you didn't see
[Music]
that
Samantha fell down into the void bye-bye
Samantha it's good knowing you
[Music]
let's read Super
Chat Dam this room is so
cozy love this
room two
hat that's not the right to man for
[Music]
no Eden was like mentioning he wants to
make a Halloween version of this room I
was like okay if you think you have the
time for it
sure so that
might might show up at some point I
don't
[Music]
know okay last time I think I
remember uh uh
uh let me
just get to
Hyer and okay I think I
read maybe didn't read the Japan chat
[Music]
or oh yeah I think I have to continue
with the Japan chat mhm
mhm is that's Dan
stream I got tagged again
[Music]
no okay
okay yeah I'm almost I'm always getting
tagged a
lot okay and let me bring out the
thumbnail as always so you guys know
what I'm reading although I don't have
this thumbnail
nail let me download it from hyzer so
convenient
[Music]
she okay cute
art here we
go Jacob 47 Dan anony web Dan The Gamer
cre
Dan and here comes Yuko with a
rainbow hello K good to see you I wasn't
active as as I used to be and I had a
little break of three months sometime
ago uh first of all congratulations on
reaching 1.5 million subscribers a bit
late but better than never right a sweet
girl like you deserve twice as many good
job on endurance K I had a lot of fun
and kept cheering you on through the
entire stream next I want to say that
last week I had my third birthday here
and began my last year with number two
in front
oh so 29 soon every Crunch and crack in
my body will become lethal say same this
sucks but cannot do much about this at
least I have a very cute and talented
kosi that makes my gloomy life more
colorful with her music I listen to your
album and repeat every day keeps me
happy and motivated to work harder even
though I got into trouble a few times we
can't listen to music at work oh I will
not be stopped from enjoying your songs
oh my God thank
you I love waa forever and ever now I
will return to my hole and keep lurking
from the Shadows I will support you and
K be as much as I can stay cute
beautiful and with big smile sending
kisses mwah MW sending kisses back to
you a thank you I'm so happy that you
came back I don't know what the reason
was for your little break but I'm glad
that you decided after 3 months I I
still I still want to see some more Wawa
I miss her that means a lot to me thank
you so much also H thank you for
supporting my music thank you for
watching all the things that were going
on recently that are important and happy
belated birthday or not wait
belated last yeah belated
belated and
congratulations happy birthday to you
how do I sing Happy Birthday in
Polish happy birthday
[Music]
polish oh
God n need a
[\h__\h]
read this
guys um uh
[Music]
uh when you type in happy birthday in
Google Translate it froze confetti
anyway tell
[Music]
me isn't that crazy long for happy
birthday but seems to be a very um
polite way of saying it there's there
should be a shorter way
[Music]
right a No Way Poland
uh
[Music]
perfect
really po polish is terrifying to try to
read my God it's so
[Music]
intimidating you could just say
St
a but this is a flex
[Music]
she's
I nailed
it that's that's a lot of words in
Polish wow I hope you'll be healthy
though you say everything will be lethal
and hurt but I hope you'll be healthy
take care of your
body and survive I still need you so I
hope to see you around even though
you're saying you're going back to
lurking but I see you now and I've seen
you around these days so that doesn't
really look like lurking to me and
that's good so stay around I have my
eyes eyes on
you thank you Yuka welcome
back soon s WC Ronin thanks for the
pinky hey K you talking about taxes the
other day in your Twitter space suddenly
made it hit my brain and i' forgotten to
send in some estimated taxes earlier in
the month ooh so here's a thanks for
saving me from further late penalties oh
but you were already getting them but
that's good damn that I that I saved you
from getting more
o you need to set some reminders sir for
yourself for your own
sake you have to go now thank you thank
you for
[Music]
coming it's fine I don't really need to
reach fre fast it would be really cool
[Music]
but it's fine I had one
one reminder well seems like it's not
enough I guess I'm your other reminder
but you know don't rely on me I'm doing
my taxes at weird
times thank you thank you for the big
support actually that should have gone
to your penalties I hope you're okay
financially you've still been playing
well thank
you I've set a whole week of reminders
for the next oh okay okay okay that
should hopefully do the trick I wish you
luck with your taxes and Nathan coton
thanks for the pinky new month new supas
to start my World of Warcraft guilty you
play World of Warcraft clearly doesn't
own an air fryer could you please tease
bear for me what are you going to like
send him the clip does he even know who
I
[Music]
am
ah bear you clearly don't own an air
fryer
ew
[Music]
ew turn him into
kfp do
it Megan join I play World of work of 2
I mean I used
to not really actively but sometimes I
think about playing it again for a
stream or two or three or four or five
or
[Music]
six
sorry I felt like
it spook
J I'm going to break your
windows well that was awful you little
[\h__\h] vanu I hate
you black Ro dear s thanks for
the let's say oh
no I don't know why I still always need
to start reading the sentence until I
realize that you you are the person who
always send these
things it still takes a moment every
time k let's say that the strange glue
appears on raina's hands and she gets a
desire to seek out other Hol members she
will hug whoever she catches and they
will be attached to each other for a day
will you look for or avoid
l i mean I don't think I have to look
for
her cuz she will look for me I'm
sure certainly she will do the the
looking part and find me
anyway and then we'll be stuck that's
fine I guess I mean I don't know how
we're going to do idle meetings and all
that but I guess we'll have to for a day
um just not go to idle
meetings nice situation though this one
at least I don't know it's it's a at
least I can answer this one unlike
others thank you g
[Music]
par thank you always you never say much
in your super chats but thank you for
being so
generous of the house right Dan Nathan C
thanky for the seat of upgrade thank you
I ended up getting both seat upgrades
man don't even make me think about it I
want I just don't want to forget that it
happened it didn't happen didn't happen
my bank account is fine Dusty D soon Tas
thanks for the pinky with words o so
good that that is that is so deep such
beautiful
words yeah I got both of them one was
already enough damn
damage I should still send the complaint
yeah maybe they give me some
miles that would be
nice oh let me check my miles
now do I have a good amount now at
[Music]
least
oh oh yeah
[Music]
it says I have I still don't know the
difference but I have 16,000 award miles
and 22,000 status
Miles when do I get like a special
status again was it 30,000 or
so
wow looking
good I don't know where the difference
is e
oh one thing that's weird like from my
flight from uh to Japan it gave me the
same amount of award miles as it did
with status miles but it says for the
way back it gave me like half the amount
of award
miles and the same amount of status like
same amount as like the other trip and
Status
miles I don't understand
I'll ask someone I know someone who can
answer this for me probably imagine if
you really became a senator wait I want
to look this up now how many
miles to become a senator um this is
Miles and
more to renew your status you need a
minimum of 100,000 status miles in one
calendar
year that's actually not so
[Music]
much thinking how many I already have
and I didn't even get miles for all my
flights this
[Music]
year that's somewhat reachable for
me wait wait wait wait
wait there's some some
details the frequent traveler and the
senator status are awarded for at least
2 years each time until the end of
February if you have reached 35,000
status miles as a frequent traveler or
100,000 status miles as a senator in one
of the two calendar years before the
expiry of your card your status is
extent I know this is about uh retaining
oh okay okay okay for keeping the
[Music]
status but yeah generally you will
become a senator when you earn at least
100,000 status miles peral calendar
year and the status is valid for 2 years
oh and in order to retain it
just got to you still got to have
[Music]
100,000 why do Airlines use miles
instead of kilometers I don't know it
sounds
nice is it really like one mile per per
mile that I flew is like
literally guess you'll have to fly a
bunch more of a alens just as they plan
uh it doesn't have to be aan alens cuz
miles and more I think could probably
also has a Swiss Airlines and probably
Lanza
right but I mean it would be the most
logical to fly with Austrian Airlines
yeah I am the
Senate probably not one to
one not hold
on well 35 I could definitely get to
that
yeah maybe probably with my next trip to
Japan h no actually no because I won't
be flying business next time so I will
not get as many
miles actually yeah then it can't be 1
mile per per mile because I got more
miles for flying business than I got for
flying uh premium economy so it's it's
miles plus the class the money you spent
actually m
YouTube keeps
dying
why that like does it cut off the video
only or or do you hear me like still
while while it cuts
[Music]
off it
buffers what about about
now thank
you
b b SM
stick
hungry
nice right now it's fine H okay I hope
it's not so like this in the vault
because of the super
chats and Jeff star thanks for the pinky
as well also with no words why Jeff why
must you do this to
me nothing to talk
about tell me about your day Luka dun
morally immoral dun g c k e
dun I
a black space water G for the pinky good
luck cheering for you to get that IR
Vision spot thank you thank you I am
very much doubting it but we got to give
it a try let's go I'm going to send
in my audition soon like we still have 5
days the the
extension gave us so much more time what
the hell crazy Stark Mandalore D glass D
I'm a te D James MC thanks for the pinky
good luck T and team thank
you well all of your good luck wishes
ended up in extend
uh the deadline huh
huh it's definitely helpful for getting
a little video uh
done cuz that seems like it wouldn't
have been done otherwise in
[Music]
time a that is true
mafin looking for the top thanks for the
pinky hey W guess what it's time for a
birthday supera oh it's my fourth
birthday in kfp been a while since we
started don't you think almost half a
decade but I feel something changed
between us this years these years and I
want to rectify it with a birthday wish
okay what Chang is that you don't use
the small Chef P anymore give us the
rarest SSR SSR possible when you read
this while only wearing the small chef
hat not the
beret
and I have to take off my pineapple hat
and like it's kind of like disgusting
right now everything's like really
[Music]
slimy I do not approve of
this I do not approve of
[Music]
this wait where am I
here this is even more special because
it's with my swimsuit
[Music]
don't get used to
it this is so
stupid it's so
[Music]
stupid it's so stupid I look like an
idiot can I take it off
[Music]
now cuz I
will
no hat doesn't stay on Burp stays
on
no no it's such a stupid
hat I don't want it especially not alone
I could still maybe tolerate it with the
like
default outfit orange normal hat but on
its own
nah
no no no no no just no no no it's stupid
it's so stupid it's so goofy yeah and
especially with the swimsuit it makes no
sense
[Music]
man
what you shut
up it's spite animal I don't know it's
not an animal it's a hat okay calm down
calm your titties your manly titties
okay happy birthday though
congratulations I guess what a selfish
selfish wish that you
[Music]
had did you hear that say you didn't
hear it that was not very llik it just
came up I couldn't even control it what
the
[Music]
[\h__\h]
no
good oh thank God okay
okay okay uh that's the end of the super
chats Evans L also sent one that that's
the end of these
[Music]
nah narissa will not weigh in on the
hats she has no say over my
hats okay next is the everybody want to
switch collap which was man that was
just so freaking
[Music]
funny
wait there it is
it was so funny honestly it was already
so chaotic maybe it was good that kuo
wasn't there like so energetic and Loud
if she would have been there I don't
I I think I would have
died yeah cuz my throat was hurting I
was basically taking up the roll of Kobo
with my energy but if she was there I I
would have been even more etic I
think
and yeah that's not no not
good yeah they expanded well it's good
for a stream game but they need to make
the other
games like show up more because we G
basically had most of the games
repeating constantly maybe it is because
of the restrictions we
had but even
then that's so weird would have been
nice to rotate a couple more
[Music]
games but besides that I had a blast
this was
amazing I love these
girls I also I think um like I saw clips
of this stream and in the comments I saw
some people say stuff like like Kaa
normally not being this energetic and
this excited and so on H and I'm I'm
happy to read that actually
she did seem like she was having a great
time IRL too
so it just shows me that she had fun and
that's in an off collab just laughing a
lot and messing around I think is the
best way to spend an off
collab people said what people said that
she was more energetic than usual in the
uh off collab I saw it like in comments
in the clips so I was happy to hear that
means that you know it went
[Music]
well
soyak tror thank you for the pinky oh
just want to send in some love for the
ASMR of Noel oh really the lovely D
ladies blessed by eyes and ears oh you
must be a fan of ASMR from frogs and
sizzling chicken to hurricanes and Cat
engin sorry it was so chaotic
man H there was a lot to enjoy you had
me rolling in bed laughing one second
then nice and comfy in the next I know
you curring pretty badly but honestly I
would have loved more even if you have
to default to comedian to get Pro it so
thank you all for trying new
things I don't know I think um in the
future maybe next year I would consider
not buying the one that she has uh that
like the the head microphone um but
something more like what uh Aki Senai
used for the crab collab for example she
said that was an ASMR microphone um
basically anything that works well for
maybe using it for cooking in the
future then I can maybe do like cook not
not really like completely ASMR but at
least have like ASMR sounds in my
cooking streams maybe make it a little
bit more
calm so but not exactly like 100% as I
don't know we could do that I don't know
I have to first of all
um stop making purchases for now because
otherwise I cannot pay my
taxes so uh no purchases
for the next couple of months I'm
profusely
sweating I'm scared
[Music]
yabby
help yeah but thank you Travy I'm glad
some ASMR enjoyers enjoyed it uh
especially you know the KF the K of
people who love ASMR have been deprived
of it since the beginning of of my
time and yeah I will surely not become
someone who does ASMR regularly although
I mean I could see maybe we could do
something for members
only I could cuz like you know don't I
always don't we all always struggle
finding content for uh members only
streams I guess we could play around
with it in members only m
[Music]
but next year as I said no purchases
now it seems like in kfb because of my
influence possibly there's a lot of
people who also just don't like ASMR
just like me for real for
real but maybe I can make a kind of ASMR
that's acceptable for all of us just
give it a try if I give it a try you
must give it a try too I hate ASMR okay
but we're got to do it together
[Music]
okay I'm your Oshi so it will be
enjoyable for you whether you like it or
[Music]
not oh
I am melting off my
chair
[Music]
help
[Applause]
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay I'm back
ja for
7 VK d py d Queen Twilight Sparkle d g d
and yuk
[Music]
m da da da
da okay next
[Music]
please uh just a few
ones
[Music]
P
g82 celebrate spe T and space waterful
than thank you guys for supporting the
Vlog once
again thank you I'm glad people really
enjoyed it hopefully we can do something
like this and again in the
future and now we are at the stream from
yesterday the
thumbnail oh saved it in the wrong
folder
uh I think it's here
yeah nice
[Music]
thumbnails okay T soon 47 soon air
soon oh I don't know honestly I haven't
talked with her for long actually since
the
uh I haven't seen her around since
the anniversary collab I think well
I
know yeah literally since
then but I've been thinking of asking
her
[Music]
to okay I asked her but I will not tell
you to answer anyway cuz I just asked
for my
personal um
relief and I don't know when she'll
[Music]
answer
I'm yeah I miss her streams too first
night studio for the
pinky again thank you I receive
it I have received it the gamer
cre P Dix Le Dixon Le d d and dun donate
blood and watch R tubers dun nice
profile
picture you changed that recently didn't
[Music]
you number
one
I'm so fancy D A and P thanks for the
pinky you look cute as always p hat
looks good on you this past weekend was
my second birthday with kfp oh I love
being part of the community you helped
develop now it's a birthday present can
I get your world famous Happy Birthday
song um un normally so that I don't have
to do it too often only sing it for red
super chats pong have you noticed and
even then it's not always a not not a
guarantee but you're asking so nicely I
kind of have to do it you got a short
version a short
[Music]
version happy birthday to you Mom
love happy birthday in your p to happy
birthday to
P my Korean
bro you found me a sometime
ago now let's play some ping pong when
I'm back in
[Music]
Kore
okay short version discount Happy
Birthday
song
congratulations yay okay that I'll take
that opportunity to change my bgm
[Music]
actually hope your birthday was lovely
M happy birthday
what what why you cut it off like that
because it's only half a birthday
song it's not even for you it's not even
for
[Music]
you anyway thank you P for the support I
hope you'll spend your following
birthdays in kfp as
well
I need to practice my Korean again ma
y Lord EV eating m t's ass T J monkey
thanks for Pinky happy Canadian
Thanksgiving oh that was yesterday
here's some fun to get roasted turkey or
roasted Kar uh uh wait I made roasted
chicken maybe with a nice slice of
grilled stream pineapple and vaa
watermelons for dessert
what grilled
I prefer them just normal
fresh welcome back by the way we miss
you thank you did you really did you
really I
mean in some way that puts some pressure
on me cuz like I was trying my best to
provide content still and you guys
missing me makes me feel like it wasn't
enough but it's also sweet
so I like hearing it
anyway
[Music]
difficult it was enough It's never
enough duality of kfp we're
fine I didn't miss you what you always
do more than enough words thank you I'm
happy to hear
that I'm glad that hopefully the
majority is thinking
that
I was really busy like doing other
things like dance lessons and stuff
so it's like also the problem of not
being able to stream
spontaneously like having to reserve the
studio in advance Jemma said ideally
like
free oh did she say five work days in
advance and then things like also kept
on changing a little
bit yeah and I went I literally left
Tokyo and went to a wedding and that
took up quite some time just like
traveling in the shin conent that that
the shin conin was like what 3 hours or
or more 3 and a half hours I
think including the the smaller train
rides I think
too so back and forth that's like 7
hours
plus takes up like a a whole
day hi chunky
wonky she's
crying are you
okay
H she's just sitting
there looking
and meowing at
[Music]
me man she's a
baby well I'll be done soon baby don't
worry don't worry anyway Happy
Thanksgiving then to all the
Canadians yesterday I'm a bit late but
Happy
Thanksgiving we don't celebrate
Thanksgiving at all here
[Music]
so yeah it's kind of weird like it's
really hard for me to like relate or
even
imagine anything about Thanksgiving we
just don't do that here thankless ations
now oh she looks at me with her big
round eyes and she says
meow what is
it maybe there's not enough Kibbles but
last time I checked which was like
before the stream and they don't eat
that much it's still
[Music]
plenty every Super Chat reading is
Thanksgiving kind of
true yeah she's like panning at
me
H I want to hug her I want to pick her
up but she's just going to run
away it's an excuse to eat
food you shouldn't need to have an
excuse for food eat food every day
survive for your first Super Chat which
is also a red
one come hello K today is a very special
day today is my birthday I'm so happy to
be able to watch Ki streaming like this
on my birthday don't forget that Ki who
always streams with a smile on her face
is a great gift to all of us meow thank
you for always oh thank
[Music]
H down to soon K
congratulations your first ever Super
Chat are you here now probably not
probably
sleeping but that was yesterday sorry
for being a little bit late but compared
to all the others this is nothing this
is basically still the same day m
yeah I hope this will reach you in the
VA
though so thank you for supporting me
and thank you for watching me I hope you
continue supporting me and stay healthy
and happy and I'll hopefully go to Korea
again at some point either virtually or
in
reality and then I hope you'll be still
in kfp for that moment meow yeah what
n
baby what is it oh she's doing the squid
squat thank you Sun
[Music]
K take W thank you for the pinky I
worked in the call center for 10 years
and I can tell you that the call center
employees are the last to hear about any
I I kind of read this already about any
new programs or changes sorry you had a
bad time with it and they definitely
could have handled that better
mhm they definitely could have
yeah I'm really really upset about
this cuz we're not talking about like I
don't know 50 bucks 100 bucks we're
talking about 800 plus
bucks but anyway let's not talk about it
anymore shall
we yeah thank you doll for trying
to you know make me feel better about it
you m p thanks for the pinky at least
kfp has great customer service no
complaints of any kind here yep none
whatsoever well I wouldn't think that
the customers have any complaints maybe
you guys have some
complaints but customers I think our
customer service should be great because
why would customers complain in the
first place right mhm
mhm and your complaints wouldn't go to
the customer
service they would go to me and I would
say shut up go to usual
[Music]
room
yes 100%
satisfaction can't complain of their
fried yeah up in the fry you go AR booo
Alex ah you didn't tell them but you
watched the the Lo the Rings musical
let's go but even if they didn't talk to
you you should have talked to them and
told
them but I'm happy you saw it
ooh they're saying it's even better than
what I said about it nice maybe they
improved it
even good feedback about the load of
drinks yes yes there is one I did a
whole like review of it in one of my
streams recently ah
[Music]
thank
you I wonder if there's another one
coming no I think I'm safe where am I
nerd book Channel than Gil Roy ironheart
than
jcuz super SSG wild
B sleepy critical red
Jack
space Nathan pinky oh yeah fiscal
responsibility do I have that I wonder
if I'm fiscally respons
responsibilities what responsibly
responsibly fiscally you know what I
mean I
[Music]
wonder I will stop talking
now thanks for the pinky welcome home
and thank you for the chill stream thank
you I'm so happy to be home I mean it
was a pretty fun uh trip the reasons why
I came there in the end were my
decisions and I was looking forward to
them so
much so it was a great time I had a good
time a bit stressful here and there but
mostly because of these stupid things
that happened that had nothing to do
with the trip
really like the I mean it did kind of
but not really like the ausan Allin
[\h__\h] and then suddenly deciding to uh
make something for your
vision and I'm working on it adding onto
my
plate
[Music]
yeah we got some good collapse and then
totally not obvious thing later this
month what's what's happening later this
month oh ah
yeah for a moment I didn't even know
what you you were trying to point
out huh what do you mean I don't
[Music]
know who knows wa what do you think it
is
huh
huh why what what do you think you
know you know nothing John
snow all righty and last this k
that was from
yesterday I will now read and this you
haven't heard in a long time I will read
today's super
[Music]
chats
what
NY
[Music]
what
how long has it been I can do
that
what I am back baby I am caught
up yes I am oh yes I
am oh maybe not since my birthday oh
[\h__\h] oh my God yeah I was trying to
catch up before my anniversary but I
didn't did I [\h__\h] oh my god let's go
candy stamps feel like I'm like at the
end of a marathon and there's like
really really emotional music uh playing
and I'm like like the video is like slow
motion I'm running in slow motion but
I'm actually running really fast and
everybody's like throwing water bottles
at
me y take jaob D cany STS d py d Stone
shadow thanks with
pinky oh another one you guys are so
concerned huh hi k sorry to ask you on
your live stream how are gura and El
doing lately they haven't released
anything in a while I just want to know
if they're safe and healthy if so could
you tell us about them I will thank you
very much I'm so sorry but it's not
really my place to say anything and I
also don't really know
anything um
yeah both is very
true I really don't know and I if even
if I knew I it's on my place to say
can't ask me ask them maybe when they do
Super Chat reading they might answer who
knows
sorry sorry
[Music]
wory yeah yeah I guess I'm
a I'm sure that she will be back soon
amyy you I'm sure she will I mean I
don't know but I'm sure she
will 1269 red J D Jacob 47 Al d e d
motion D Aon D you know just got to be
just got to be a bit patient you know
and in the
meantime maybe watch vods that you
didn't watch yet or watch other whole
life
members
yeah Studio thanks for the pinky 10 oh
again thank you oh and because I'm not
reading it in hyzer I actually see the
the Emojis so
fruity the the peach Emoji has such a
nice shape such a butt
[Music]
shape nice yummy Violet myth
dun intelligence is knowing that a
tomato is a fruit wisdom is knowing not
to put a tomato in the fruit
salad well I know both so I have both
intelligence and
wisdom but what is I guess adding to
that and ignorance is knowing tomato is
a fruit but not accepting it as
one
and referring to it as a vegetable
anyway like I do
that's
[Music]
ignorance oh interesting oh Nathan
thanks to the pinky just think if tenter
had become a flight attendant so many
chickens this one included would have
never found oosi
exactly exactly like so many of you we
we talked about this before before but
so many of you you wouldn't have we
would have never found each other if it
wasn't for whole life I would be very
lonely and I would be very sad because
you
[Music]
know I would still
be very
very
well small small
C after many years still being smaller
smaller is very the presso espresso hi
chunky
[Music]
wonky for I'm a drawing that boat What
boat I'm going drew a
[Music]
boat I'm almost done chuny wony okay
almost Ricky do that thanks for the
pinky I'm moving to Japan ah this is the
one thanks to the working holiday be I
didn't know this was a thing but thanks
to an orange streamer I think that's me
I can live there for a bit thank you
awesome really anybody who's still like
in the right age
and and in the right country like the
right um
citizenship should do this in their life
working
holiday if you have an interest in
living in Japan this is like the way way
to do
it there's an age limit yes there
is or some sometime 4:30 I
think usually might depend on the
[Music]
country but I wish you the best of luck
I don't know when you're going uh but
wait this means you might not be able to
watch my streams as much when you do
that Ricky are you here Ricky we have to
talk
you're now in the English
lands now it's like easy for you to
watch me but when you go to Japan it
won't be so
easy what are we going to do about that
Ricky what are we going to do you're not
here anymore are
you ah there are you try to keep up
anyway when are you
going love find a way I sleep late
okay okay that might work if you sleep
late like if you sleep late AKA 2: a.m.
then you won't see much of my streams if
it's more like 4:00 a.m. in 2 weeks
shes that's so sudden I'm not
ready I'm not ready for
that
I you should have told me
earlier I'm not emotionally ready for
that but good luck and have
fun I'm sure it will be
[Music]
great you know uh I'm guessing you're
going for one year
too make sure to you know take care of
all the like there's a when when you
live in Japan for that long you do have
to take care of some stuff like bank
account and get uh a health
insurance I think it was a must to get
uh a health
insurance I hope it's not like too
complicated for you to set those things
up cuz like I feel like I was a bit
little bit like uh how
where got to go for some
some document stuff you know go to to
the how do you say it
municip office whatever it's called
large savings I've been working for 10
years of wow okay let's go that sounds
good you can get like more than just a
shitty shitty shitty shittiest ever one
room apartment that I
had
man mine was so
bad pretty bad like pretty like on the
outskirts of Tokyo too you know the one
where I was in when I started out with
whole
life then afterwards I moved into the
shitty house the Casper
house the the so-called
Mansion before that anyway that's
exciting I wish you good luck and I'll
be hearing from you
hopefully yeah take monkey John E
D dong d M Miss
D O R
Dan Luc l m Griffin danin lunbo D Super
Snake Mario happy
birthday to you than and
congratulations
hey much love to you need to breathe for
a minut I feel not so good
yeah but it's okay I'm almost finished
El D out run the win D Max the first d c
gaming D thank you
[Music]
oh
really do you get money for these kind
of Japanese ComEd merchand oh
uh uh
[Music]
probably I
uh Pro probably not a significant
amount but it's not about the money it's
not about the
[Music]
money it's it's not worth
mentioning small small but uh birthday
merchandise big big
big other things not all not all you
know but yeah anniversary birthday good
good
understand
and py D Clement go
dun oh it arrived I want it to where's
my FMA bottle I want my FMA bottle oh
chunky monkey is here again
hi did you guys get your fmo bottle your
frd merchandise and all that the fmo
bottle for bot F
bot
yeah give me where's mine what the
hell about a month ago you use it for
camping yo let's
go nice
nice well it should be arriving now
right cuz like that was in February or
so dumpy D happy birthday
dumpy
hey D N diesel D another birthday what
the [\h__\h] happy birthday Nene diesel
thanks for the red chat today is my
birthday and my time zone having you and
K be around make my life more kinky and
fun thank you w
[Music]
to
you
little should I say it in Japanese
accent or like
proper sounds funny I didn't recognize
it at first I thought it was Juliet and
Romeo or something like
that okay I'll do both versions here for
you NY diesel happy birthday to you you
sweet potato you cutie pouti mww m m and
your little
[\h__\h]
or you little
[\h__\h] does that do the job is that
good that sounds so
stupid that's no y seems like you are
satisfied happy birthday I guess you
said in your time zone so it's not the
10th it's the 11th now
hold
Celebration Time come on no wait that's
not what they say celebrate good times
come on right that's it
whatever same meaning I hope you
celebrating those good times
today but Jes Cruz zly thanks for CH for
your taxes no you're making my taxes
bigger the shinger
taxes
cuz they get bigger but I also I don't
know I earn more and I pay more but then
[Music]
what yeah how can you help me with my
taxes if this is just making it worse h
if you don't pay them they don't exist
no no no no no no no I have to I have to
there's no other
[Music]
way offshore
count I don't think I can do that I
don't know how to do that anyway and oh
wait no simply thank you for the red I
give you a kiss come here come here come
here that was a weird
one thank you for the
pinky yeah this is for a few seconds in
the new collab when we got the double
heartbe oh I need to listen back on that
with my headphones I have never felt
such Bliss before Oh I want can I can I
do it with my
[Music]
microphone wait
uh
no where would it
be oh I hear
it oh but there's no way the microphone
would pick that up I mean I see it like
a really really tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny
bit I saw it an OBS in my sound
thingy
but yeah you guys would have to like
turn that all the way
up or I I would have to get rid of all
the like noise Gates and
[\h__\h] but I'm not going to do that now
cuz that messes up my settings anyway uh
I'm glad you liked it but I feel so
embarrassed I feel like could have been
better I could have done better overall
I was so nervous and
awkward and unprepared a d soon oh thank
you
also oh oh another ASMR appreciator nice
and random collusion thanks for the red
super
chat happy
birthday happy happy what happy what
now thank you for the big Super Chat
just to make a
jerk than
[Music]
soon give me a number than Jacob 47 out
than soon M thanks little pinky it's
been a very long time since you've been
100% caught up congrats as for as I you
can actually do a basic binar setup with
two mics at least I figured out how to
oh so you can save money can probably
just Google how to Hope AOE to works out
thank you no I don't think I want to do
that cuz that's complicated uh I'd
better just buy an ASMR microphone but
no purchases this week uh this year also
I don't even have two microphones uh I
mean I do but like I would think they
should be somewhat of like similar
quality and the ones I have are not so
yeah interesting experiment but no
also I'm out of
[Music]
breath space wonderful
than
is I know what you're going for
but no it's bad it's bad bottom FR face
with the pinky well time to increase the
backlog no also here's a good anime
recommendation fre on be on Journey's
End it is a story that takes place in a
fantasy world following a Long Live
female elf who goes on an adventure to
learn more about human it's like violet
I was really considering starting to
watch it when I kept on sewing it pop up
on um I think it was on Disney plus but
it might have been only because I was in
Japan was adjusting its program to that
I have to check if it's uh even now on
my Disney
plus it looks
nice it looks
nice
yeah any yeah yeah when I was in Japan
my Netflix and my my Amazon Prime and
mind Disney plus it was all filled with
anime I was like I should use this
opportunity to watch some anime but then
I didn't feel like it after all and I
kept on falling asleep after 20 minutes
of Home Improvement and
[Music]
Seinfeld okay but I'm interested I watch
it I might actually give it a try cuz
I'm Legit interested and I wonder if
it's on purpose that the word
freen literally sounds and is written
like the German word for being cold
freezing I wonder if it's on purpose or
if it's supposed to mean something
else I I wouldn't know what else it
would
mean all the names of people and places
are German proper nouns oh well okay
then it is on purpose huh hauh ha so
it's speaking to me it's literally made
for
me baked turkeys Dan no the IRS ma go
away go away to the usual room and un
chat thank you
D oh thank
you cleaning ears is just generally so
weird to me as a concept cuz we just
don't really see that as like something
to relax in in Austria but it's this
whole thing in Japan they have these
like you know for no senpai's outfit how
she has this accessory for her hand they
use these kind of things not not the
cotton ear cleaners no they use these
like stick
thingies and it's like a thing there's
even like Services you know how you can
get a massage you can also just go to
like MiMi Cy they call it Mimi
Cy ear the the goal isn't really
cleaning I think it's just like like
poking in your
ear they love that [\h__\h] I don't get
it freaks me
out yeah you got accustomed to it cuz
it's a staple in Japanese ASMR mhm I
would think so that you get used to
[Music]
it
okay I'm going to go now cuz I'm out of
breath and I need to cook I
guess I hope I was smart enough to put
some easy recipes in
[Music]
there okay guys byebye the j s do
in oh I hope you had fun
today see you on Thursday
I'm so happy we' reached the end of the
super chats
[Music]
yay
yes
[Music]
smoothie
yeah
she's meowing I don't know if you heard
her she's demanding
[Music]
attention
app he's so
soft
[Music]
w