[Music]
[Applause]
you
[Music]
hello kombawa
can you hear me is my mic volume okay
hello oh
thank you hello
slay my queen oh thank you i think i
will do that
well that made me let me feel something
strange like a tokidoki feeling
volume all good everything is good we
hear you loud and clear
hello kalistama wineglass and skull
it's funny that you say that because
hold on just a moment hold on just a
moment
i want you to hear something okay one
let me lower the bgm volume so you can
definitely hear this but listen to this
[Music]
do you know what that is everyone that
is the sound
of not a 200 yen wine bottle which is
2.50
not a 300 yen wine bottle
a 450 yen wine bottle
which is about four dollars and fifty
cents
can you believe it that's right
for a special occasion your boy
bought a wine bottle for four dollars
and fifty cents
we're moving up everyone ladies and
gentlemen we are moving up let's take a
swig
[Music]
ah yes tastes absolutely terrible
i love it can't get enough of it
huh all right guys i know right
moving up moving up well anyway
let's head over to the hangout spot one
moment
basically
[Music]
yay here it is now you can see it that's
right living the high life now everyone
when you get super chat enabled will it
all go to wine
that's a good question and i cannot
confirm or deny
[Music]
but the likelihood is at least 40
percent
maybe possibly
[Music]
let me just lay back a moment so anyway
i released the new song and my apologies
that it came out
10 minutes before um this stream are you
surprised
because i'm not surprised i actually am
really not surprised at all
that that happened it's not that i
procrastinated it's just that
how do i how do i say there was so much
work to do right
last night was a trip it was a trip as
they say
ah man i actually the reason that this
stream is
is titled girigiri af
a f stands for as f word
so so very very girigidi
which means it almost it really kind of
almost didn't happen
right um i recorded the song a while ago
and i had it ready to mix um
actually i'll bring this up now because
someone asked recently
um what do i use to mix well usually i
use cubase for track making and i used
it to mix vocals back in the day
but cubase has since betrayed me
i know but i'm not surprised uh so now i
use reaper
which is a free program um and it's fine
it does what i need it to do
because cubase won't put my effects on
my files
um but yeah so i've been using that
and i was having a hard time you guys um
before debut things got so busy right
and all of the songs that i had
prepared for my ep got put on the back
burner in favor of getting debut things
ready
right um fitting right yes that i would
use reaper i thought so too
well the first thing that drew me to it
was the name
but then it turned out to be um
[Music]
it's i as a program
like it's fine it does what i need it to
do right
it's like that let me grab another sip
of this wine before we move on
to the story because the story gets good
[Music]
and by guess good i mean it's really
unfortunate
so actually i was working on the mix up
until last night
believe it or not thank you everyone
saying that it's so good
i'm really glad you like it see i
remember distinctly i was kind of like
not really
able to sleep but see that's not such a
that's not such a big problem because
let me tell you guys a secret very
quickly i see a lot of discussion on the
internet these days saying
um do you know like when maury goes to
sleep or
or what her sleep schedule is and that
kind of thing people trying to figure
out
my sleep schedule or um where like what
time zone i'm in or that kind of thing
or
or yes my sleep schedule well i think
that that's very bold of you to assume
um that i sleep at all
yeah yeah
sleep
sleep is for the week i see that often
uh people say that often and i don't
not sure if i agree i feel like without
sleep
i become weak but i can't i can't i
can't do it
i'm too busy i was kind of tossing and
turning trying to see if i could
right the other night and it got to a
point
um last night because actually i've been
having
um having someone else um
a very dear how do i say uh collaborator
of mine uh mr case kokorovic he's the
guy that made
um the [\h__\h]
song track yeah that was him and he
mixed it
and he offered to help me because i kept
thinking to myself
i'm having a hard time making these
mixes sound the way that i want them to
right um so last night i was preparing
the mix
um and i did it into the morning
and it went on for a long time right and
then i had streams to do
and i was quite busy right well i hadn't
slept for
a long long time and um
i actually dozed off with my headphones
on
and i i awoke to the sound of the
program actually crashing in my ear
so when the program crashes it goes
something like
and yeah something like that and i had i
had fallen asleep
so when i woke up i was like ah
and i thought i was having a breakdown
like an actual mental
and i recall just being so exhausted
and i thought to myself i have to finish
this mix oh my gosh
oh my gosh we are so late what am i
going to do
absolute terror and you know what made
it worse
i had scythe swinging lessons in four
hours
and i still needed to close my eye
so at the end of all of it what i did
was i just
i just i simply reached out to mr case
and i said
listen man i can't finish this
can you and he said leave it to me
and so i sent it to him and i passed out
for two hours
and he finished it it actually made it
sound good
the hook was super flat before there
were no harmonies or anything and i was
just
i was kind of losing my mind you guys so
when you say to me that you enjoyed the
song
that's a huge relief to me i mean i know
that my music and my rap isn't going to
be for everyone
but but
i feel like just the fact that some
people i mean i've seen so many kind
comments even people saying like um
i don't really like rap and i can't say
that i'm a fan of your music but i see
how hard you work
and honestly that's that's enough that's
enough for me
chad
[Laughter]
please check him out please check out
tama onsen's music if you like touhou
dojin music they do hip-hop
and yeah keys is the leader he's just
phenomenal just an incredible track
maker and
and i'm trying to learn some from him
but you know death sensei says don't
fraternize with the humans so
it's kind of been like just when i have
time i suppose but anyway the story
continues story isn't over
let me go ahead and take a drink of this
wine because it gets
it gets worse well it doesn't get worse
but the story continues
let's take a step
maybe it does actually get worse um
so anyway i close my eyes for about an
hour
i feel a little better knowing that case
has the track
but i realized that i'm going to be late
to sight swinging lessons
now here's the thing i am a reaper on
hiatus
but if i simply stop swinging my scythe
around
here let me show you my size a little
bit wait nope hold on
wait nope hang on what i'll get it to
work
here allow me to move my body excuse me
chad i'm probably going to sit right in
front of you i want you to see the
scythe though
[Music]
sorry chad i'm in the way for now but i
want you to see it yay
um so science swinging lessons
uh i have to continue taking them with
death sensei right
because if i don't then i'll get rusty
so when i go off of my hiatus as a
reaper
um what that means is that if i haven't
been
swinging my scythe around my muscles
will not be strong
like they usually are believe it or not
because i do have a human body now right
um so i do have to attend sci swinging
lessons and my side swinging lessons are
actually
i have to take i have to take the
underworld bus
the underworld community bus now any of
you who have taken a community bus
in the real world know exactly how how
uh dodgy
the underworld bus might be the
underworld community bus
can you imagine i want you to imagine
for a minute
what the underworld community bus is
like and it's about it's about an hour
right from my place of dwelling
to um death sensei's death dojo
[Music]
if people are spamming f in the chat
what does that mean is hold on
hold on is the is the is the stream
buffering what's going on what's going
on
huh what's happening what's happening is
it okay
[Music]
thank goodness because i'm so sorry but
but you all scared the so-called [\h__\h]
out of me
we've been having issues right with uh
with underworld wife
it's fine it's okay it's okay okay i'll
continue with the story
so anyway was taking the underworld
public bus and it's about an hour ride
with um all kinds of super annoying
creatures
on the bus right the really skeevy
goblins and demons and whatnot
yeah not my favorite but i don't have a
license so i can't drive or anything i'm
death
imagine death being able to drive can be
kind of strange right
huh f means respect are you sure
if it's buffering you'd see okay okay
thank you thank you i'm very new to all
of this so
you guys are very helpful thank you yeah
so anyway i'm gonna move back to my seat
um anyway so
i take i i get up and i i just feel like
i feel like death actually
you guys which should be a good thing
but in this case it wasn't
it was not a good thing yeah
and so i got on the bus and i went an
hour and then i walked
it's a 30 minute walk from the bus stop
you have to go up a mountain to get to
death
sensei's death dojo so i went
i climbed and i got up there
and you know what sensei said to me
eh nanite
wait now is it buffering
[Music]
gosh dave you can't you can't wait
still good okay nani no
hello mike muted oh boy
they're just trolling all right i'm not
gonna look at the chat i'm gonna keep
talking
and if i if i go if i go offline then
excuse me
i'll make it up to you guys in the
future i promise but
i'll continue on um so
i arrive where were we destiny's death
dojo i arrive and i'm ready to swing my
scythe just kidding i'm not i feel like
absolute garbage
and i show up and sensei isn't there
why do you think sensei isn't there well
it turns out everyone
i went to the dojo an hour early
usually i arrive at least five minutes
late but no
i was there an hour early i've never
done that before everyone
and that is a true fact that is a true
fact death sense they showed up and was
like what is wrong with you
why are you here and i said i'm ready
for scythe swinging lessons
and he said you're an hour early
and and you know what he made me start
swinging my scythe anyway
and this is a true story everyone this
is the truest of the true
you can't make this stuff up
[Music]
and then i came back home and i just
worked on the music video
until now and guess what tomorrow it'll
be the same
in fact after this stream it'll be the
same i have to finish up the mix for the
last song but
the good news is the last song is
actually pretty much done already
and i actually don't feel bad about it
like i did about this one so
[Music]
you need sleep i know i know this
weekend i promise
i'm really looking forward to our big
our big celebration stream of the first
week
hey wait a minute guys are we close to
um 200k
subs i wonder
[Music]
because last i checked we were almost
there
[Music]
i'm so excited really
oh we're so close yay
maybe i'll just stay streaming until we
reach it so we can celebrate together
awesome awesome yay
i mean i would say let's just do another
stream right um
but gosh tomorrow tomorrow i also have
two streams
it's a review it's a review stream with
ina um
and then after that i have a drawing
stream wait which comes first i forget
i'll let you know i'll let you know
but yeah i'm actually i might also draw
with ina as well because drawing with
gouda last time was so much but was so
much fun
but this time i've actually prepared an
outline
so we can talk about tomorrow's song i
was not very prepared when when
i was celebrating with gouda and i felt
terrible so i was like oh gosh
i actually don't know what to talk about
so in the end i was just like ah screw
it let's just draw
and it was fine at the end of the day
chico shokai wrap is pretty much just
my self-introduction right not much is
to be said about that but with that
being said maybe i can speak a little
bit
about the deadbeats rep
[Music]
well i'm really happy that you guys said
that you enjoy it
i worked hard on it the beat is pretty
simplistic
but that's kind of on purpose because i
really wanted to highlight i guess the
wrap
i'm a big fan of like rap tracks that
sound very simplistic and kind of goofy
or comical
almost and then really emphasize like
the rapper's speed or flow
yeah you are so talented you're very
sweet
thank you
what was that ending by the way it was
my inner s
that is what it sounds like inside of my
brain when i'm debating what to say to
you guys
what should i say on stream i wonder
that's what the conversation sounds like
you get a little sneak peek in there
also
there's a there's a little clue about
death sensei as well
i'll give you this hint in the middle of
the song there are some hints that death
sensei might just be
a get mower like me but i can't confirm
or deny he'll kill me for confirming her
benign
well he wouldn't kill me for denying if
he could kill me
but he can't i'd like to see him try
this sensei is scary though i will say
quite frightening much less cute than
the um abbreviated version that
ina draws draws him as
gap melee well there's i don't know
about moe but he's
quite gap i suppose because imagine
death sensei
well he's very strict and very
straight-laced
but on occasion if you catch him at the
right time
anyway you might find that clue in the
song
death sensei is you go no not confirming
or denying
but definitely can't confirm anything
we need your new songs on spotify i have
to figure some stuff out first but
i would love that
oh no my face is getting red
a death sensei t-shirt or chain that's
such a good idea i feel like
if i ever were to roll out merch someday
i feel like that would be
pretty swag cash money
if we had that kind of thing i feel like
that would be cool
i want to think about all kinds of
creative goods
name of the weapon of choice what would
have to be my scythe but after that
medieval flail
i think i talked about it recently on
the collab stream
i would buy in an instant i ship mori x
sleep oh you really shouldn't
you really shouldn't sleep loves me but
i do not love sleep
sleep is unproductive
whales are badass i would have to agree
are you good at rhythm games nope i'm
terrible
i used to there is an arcade in the
underworld that i used to go to that was
pretty fun
i played some game called choo choo nice
them
chin of them something like that and i
really enjoyed it because they had a lot
of tam onsen songs
give your scythe a name i'll think about
it
[Music]
maybe it's ricky
no no no no no i i can't i can't i can't
i can't i can't name my scythe after a
freaking meme
ah no way no way no way i refuse
i refuse
would not be happy but then again that
is the goal isn't it
[Music]
no don't actually take it seriously
no no no oh man
is death sensei from castlevania well
they share some similarities
i always get excited at that part of the
game and point wildly at the screen look
look dad sensei he just grunts because
that's death sensei but you know
yara yeah she's all right
[Music]
oh goodness
listen connie
[Music]
can i even say i don't have a problem
with
that man but let me be real with you
for a moment his shoe is whack
sorry meng your shoe is whack
[Music]
oh man can you speak tai unfortunately
not
can't sorry
don't tell him i said that if he ever
wants to collab in the future i'm toast
which will definitely happen by the way
we're almost at 200k subs can you
believe it
a collaboration with that man is on the
horizon
big kusa oh
no this is the effect of the
450 yen wine over the 200 yen wine
can you play the song on the stream sure
we can bob our heads to it
um i'll put it up
let me see if i can find it
i i won't rap to it live because there's
just nothing left inside of me
um but i will go ahead and i'll give it
a little play
oh for those who have yet to hear it
okie dokie
[Music]
found it found it fine i found it
here we go deadbeats lurking now
[Music]
honesty a blood price to be paid but i
promise it's worth this on demand
homicidal circumstances
benefits will be best friends adrenaline
i think i like you wanna feed my five
months
leave it all to us
uh
that's for sure
[Music]
thanks for enjoying it it was fun to
make here i'll have it on in the
background it's some bgm but yeah
eminem's been real quiet since you
dropped this well he's probably working
on on some
some stuff that's kind of how he does it
right works and works in the shadows and
then drops something
super fire one of these days i'm going
to wrap
the godzilla third verse for you guys
we gotta get the rights though i think
that that we must become
friends first but i doubt that he will
see this
if he does maybe maybe he'll let me
i'm so tired maybe he'll let me rap
godzilla just a capella
acapella it doesn't gotta be like wait
huh
did we make it
[Music]
that wasn't even left and right actually
i got it i got it twisted
i got it twisted time to add him on
twitter i don't think that he'll see
oh man we're so close maybe 500 uh
collab with eminem someday i should have
put that as one of my goals and dreams
but
eminem death sensei wouldn't that be a
plot twist
rap godzilla i wish i could i can i
really can i promise you that i can
but i can only do it in two breaths i
mean i can
i wish i could do it in one but i can't
it's got to be two breaths but i can do
it it's just that if i do
um i mean you guys already know that um
giddy giddy possibility of me
getting monetization that's the price i
have to pay for making the music i want
to make i guess but
if you guys noticed um the songs have a
lot of censorship
especially in the japanese lyrics it
might be a little more noticeable
some of the kanji like um the kanji for
it's my favorite kanji but we have to
censor it
she has to be censored um
so yeah you know you know
yeah well that's the price i got to pay
i suppose
but to a certain extent i don't
i don't want to completely censor myself
you know
make your own rap god songs
yeah congratulations for many subs i'm
blown away
i've only had a body for what four days
why so many i think it's really
wonderful though
that me and my girls are getting so many
so many awesome
really kind supporters and it's been
really great
i don't know i mean it certainly has
brought on its uh
stresses i suppose but i think the good
things
probably outweigh the bad things at
least so far
do you like death core sure
i think it's good it's just that rap is
my favorite especially when it comes to
um
moments of human annihilation i'm trying
to find it
content-friendly ways of saying
the m word
i won't say it youtube [\h__\h] please
have mercy on me grim
shady
let me make a promise to you guys and
it's a promise but it's like it's like a
greedy kitty promise that's not even the
proper usage of that word it's a promise
that i don't know that i can keep
but i will try okay and that promises
if i ever debut in 3d i would love to do
some kind of eminem song especially a
slim shady cover
but i can't promise it it's it might be
too difficult
but for 3d debut i want to do just the
most
yeah something like that would be
perfect
grim shady non-stop music
[Music]
i hope you guys keep enjoying the songs
and and the the last
main one will be out tomorrow it's um
it's actually
the ending theme uh to all of my streams
from here on out
for now right so i hope that you'll
enjoy it
it actually has a lot of singing in it
there's like
like some there's some rap but there's a
lot of singing
quite a bit at least so i think you'll
get to hear my singing voice a little
better
and then after that instrumental and
acapella of [\h__\h] shinde kudasai
is coming out um on friday and
we're doing something really fun that
everyone can participate in i think but
i can't give any more details
so it'll be cool i want a freestyle
dance to your new song go ahead
just make sure that you at me and use
the tags and stuff
[Music]
are you a fan of castlevania um so
here's the deal i'm not gonna lie right
and pretend that i've played every
castlevania game
i'm a really big fan of castlevania
symphony of the night
so that's the one that i've played most
um
i've played a bit of super castlevania
64. that's it
i want to try more though because i
really do enjoy
the the style of gameplay but the thing
about symphony of the night that i
really enjoyed was like the rpg elements
that they mixed with it
so i'm not i'm not sure how i would do
with the other games
but i certainly am open to giving them a
try and i think i'd like to after we
want to rerun through symphony of the
night together
it's your go-to me too yeah i love
symphony of the night classic and and
the ost is just
amazing one of my favorite osts ever
play on stream i want to but
unfortunately it's a little more
complicated than that right i
i have to wait to be allowed to it's
complicated but
don't worry i have requested to play it
and i already have my thumbnail prepared
for it i got so excited just thinking
about it and i think you guys will think
it's funny
oh yeah bloodstained actually i do have
that one i need to check really quick if
i'm able to play it but i did want to
give it a try because
i heard that it was good uh same creator
and whatnot so
i'd love to give it a shot yeah arya of
sorrow is pretty solid
200k yay
i wish i had like some streamers or
something maybe let me see if i can play
the sparkle
oh no i don't know if i want to play the
spark
the sparkles are just as bad as the
smoke everyone
congrats patchy it's all thanks to you
guys
i can't believe it
freaking sick hell yeah
it's all thanks to you guys
thank you deadbeats thank you for
lurking now
and always
[Music]
i want to do lots of fun live streams
from here and
i feel kind of bad because i haven't
really done any like games
like game plays um but i am i am playing
mad father i believe it's fr
it's either friday or saturday it's an
rpg maker style horror game
uh and it looks really fun so we're
gonna play that
um rpg maker games are a little easier
for me to be
able to play so maybe i'll do some more
horror rpg maker games
good content eventually will be rewarded
congrats thank you
i'm glad you think it's good yeah yeah
mad father
it looks super fun and i love rpg maker
games
it is insane awesome that's what i like
to hear
oh yuma nikki that's a classic i
actually have played that one
yes maybe maybe we can make it like a
regular thing right
maybe i can play like weird rpg maker
horror games
like what like once a week or something
that sounds kind of fun maybe we'll do
[Music]
that
rpg maker games have you played all
right let me think
i feel like i've played a lot of the
classic ones i played um
wada no hara which i loved that's a
great one
um and eve of course is super classic
and i've played misao
as well which is why i really wanted to
check out mad father and witch's house
but it's been a long time since i've
played witch's house so maybe we'll play
it again together that could be fun
yeah it's been a long time since i've
played it so i forget about all the
deaths but i would love to see them
again
i remember some of them really like got
my heart rate going in like the best way
huh amazing taste thank you
wasn't ohara classy yeah i really liked
i really liked that game i still haven't
finished grey garden but i think
deep sea prisoners games are really fun
[Music]
let's see what else what else to the
moon of course i played i played to the
moon and i've played finding paradise
those aren't really horror games but
they're nice they're definitely nice
like
story-based rpg maker games i do
recommend and the osts are very nice
and really good storytelling yeah
what are they like you've never played
them before um
maybe i'm partial to them because i just
really like games with pixel art i
suppose but
there's this classic feeling to them i
don't know
it's hard to explain i mean hmm
how should i phrase i mean even
many many years ago when i played them
they still hold like a nostalgic feeling
you know
well for me time is spread out a little
differently than you humans right
so like a hundred years is to me what is
probably a second to you
right i think that's how it works but
i'm not sure i have lived for eternity
but there's a nostalgic feeling to them
right i don't know
aoni
that game is a trip i have played it but
i couldn't finish it
not because it was too scary but because
it was too it was too difficult
i could never run away fast enough from
the blue guy
one second has passed yep that's a
hundred years
ah yes corpse party i have also played
that's a fun one
i mean just from the name alone you know
that i'd be interested but i actually
really did enjoy the story
and there were some moments in there
that were super yumbai and i was like
huh no way i love games that have super
yaw eye moments
ya bye meaning oh my god
in japanese very yumbai
i've also played the crooked man and all
the games in the series as well but it's
been a long time
yeah super yabai
off is quite good ah yes i've been
meaning to play that one
oh i really like the the lisa games
i played two of them not the first
friday the 13th game isn't that a 3d one
it does sound fun though i must say
there are so many games that i want to
play that i think would be super fitting
for me
maybe i'll do do maternal or something
[Music]
it looks like my kind of game but i'm
really really really bad at shooting
game
[Music]
i like action games though and i'm still
crossing my fingers for ghost of
tsushima guys
i want to play it so bad on stream but
it's just taking a long time
yes do maternal you guys want me to play
it
if you want me to i'll get it and then
i'll schedule a stream for it
i'll try my best i can't guarantee that
i'll be great
at least definitely not as good as
amelia is that fps's though
because she's super good but i'm
terrible i'll try my best
demon souls remake oh i want to i want
to play all the from software games
but yeah again just kind of kind of
waiting to get the okay
right need to make sure it's fine first
okay cool yay i'll get it then
the multi is the multiplayer out yet
i actually haven't had any time to play
the game
i really want to do you like eve cali
yes i do that was the first rpg maker
game i ever played
and bloodborne bloodborne is my favorite
game of all time actually
and i think that ina and i were wanting
to play it together
i think co-op um but yeah again just
waiting for
the okay sorry to keep you guys waiting
hopefully we'll have a nice list of
games that i can play in the meantime so
yeah yeah i'll play doom for sure sencho
is drawing me
really
i want to go see mitai mitai well we'll
probably close up in four minutes anyway
because i only wanted this to be about a
45 minute stream
and then i got a mix but anyway have you
played touhou
i have tried because i've mentioned
before i'm a huge fan of tamaonsang
um but it's tama onsen come on
tama onsen which is mr keys's group
um so i tried to play toho um
i'm just kind of bad at it i think the
girls the girls are super cute though
oh yeah my favorite is marisa and i also
like nitori
as well yeah the girl the girls are
really cute but i'm
i'm terrible at bullet hell game soho
stream when
tom onsen is amazing do you like tom
onsen
i love tamansen marisa gang
she's so cool you play persona that
would be fun
actually i asked i actually went out of
my way to ask
if i could play persona 3 specifically
i know that a lot of people like 5 or
think 4 is the best
but i love persona 3 and it fits with my
theme right
momento you're mori i love persona 3.
um but even that
older persona game was a hard no for now
at least
it's just hard to get the okay
[Music]
the most complicated game of all roblox
i can't say i have
sorry to disappoint you persona 3
[Music]
whoa really persona 3 supporters in the
chat i didn't know that they existed
or maybe that's persona 2 fans
no no more roasts no more roasts against
the persona phantom
all the persona games are fun in their
own ways
[Music]
persona 3 remake let's go i would die
for a persona 3 remake
oh your favorite too sick ah
mass destruction oh yeah did that at
that
i'm gonna stop singing right now because
even that in itself
just those just those four notes man
they've got my number
they're coming for me
never played persona i highly recommend
it
baby baby babe all right enough enough
enough enough
no i can't i can't
i know i wanna i wanna go see sencho's
drawing of me well we're gonna
we have one minute left on this stream
so
copyright strike and there he goes
all my hopes and dreams maybe all
because i couldn't resist
the urge to sing a lettuce juice song
[Music]
oh man devil may cry bayonetta
i've played bayonetta before and i
enjoyed it but not devil may cry
does seem fun though congrats on 200k
again thanks guys
where are you from the underworld my
entire existence
one minute left one minute left do you
listen to tyler i do
big fan of some of his earlier work
actually youtube look away
play devil may cry i'll consider it i'm
hollow knight actually i did i did get
a hollow knight i'm checking to see if
it is okay it should be okay though
congrats uh
[Music]
yeah thanks
do you have to can't you just say
congrat
can't you just say congrats and let that
be
[Music]
alrighty guys well
one more swig of wine big celebration
for 200k
that was nice okay guys
all right well that's it for today and
i'll see you for tomorrow's streams
please keep uh playing the new deadbeat
song as well as some of the new ones
that i've released
uh show me support by subscribing and
i'll see you guys around
have a lovely day and take care of
yourselves
okay don't go out when it's too hot
outside or whatever
it's always hot in the underworld but
i'm concerned about you humans though
alrighty guys bye-bye see you have a
lovely day
bye-bye peace
[Music]
i'm your more i hope you remember me bye
you