[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this is Pomo can you hear me
who is this
kept you waiting huh I'm at the
warehouse and it's filled with guards
what's the mission how did you get this
number
why do you keep calling each night
age hasn't slowed me down one bit Ah
I swear to God if you call me one more
fighting time or because of police oh I
see through the warehouse and make sure
no one sees me got it sounds easy enough
with a one-hour deadline never contacted
me again you freak
[Music]
so then I said
nacho cheese get it not your cheese you
mean not your business oh bro you make
me laugh
what a deep slap
oh oh
[Music]
what was that a box
did it did it just ooh
nope bro I was gonna say did it always
exist there but I couldn't move it's
just a box derby oh my bad
um what the heck is a Gigi Saji
never heard of them before
I kind of like this box
it's pretty solid I think it's pretty
solid like your smile oh bro
whoever made this thing they must be
pretty good
just like you bro
so how about we uh
how does ice cream sound oh oh bro you
know me so well
[Music]
can I get out I think it's safe
ta-da
yay I mean I mean I'm I'm still on the
mission I need to be I need to be
stealthy I'm I'm so good at that this
the stealth part
nobody
Welcome to our ultimate super uh top
secret most secret ever Mission ever in
the world oh yeah are you ready for a
crazy
time
as as a professional I have come very
prepared with many many
Goods oh yeah don't you worry I'm I'm I
know exactly what we're doing here in
this warehouse and exactly what's going
on so let me show you
just how prepared I am
let's see I'm looking for my gun
[Music]
yay
check this out this is the most modern
technology
and bye I guess definitely uh very cool
I'm legally obligated to say that this
is a toy
Trigger Discipline I want I want you to
guys but what if I did
I'm just kidding
help unless
don't don't don't turn your back on me
I'm dangerous now I can move look
maybe I can I can wave my arms I can
I can point guns at you like you better
you better watch your back
well last night we're powerful now we're
like
you know yeah well let's let's try
something else I got a few more other
weapons
let's see what I have in here I have my
my katana
oh sorry I have so much junk in here
like my dakimakura so
it's hard to like oh find it through all
the oh here we go
yeah
look at this bad boy oh yeah this is
look someone asked me how many times my
Katana was folded
two
oh yeah isn't it like one of those
things where the lower the number like
the the higher
quality you know anyway look at that
so cool right
oh gosh I can't be sneaky when the floor
sounds like this I gotta be extra
careful what am I licking
oh wait oh you're supposed to like yeah
you know like how they do in the movies
oh
what's a cool pose to do with a with a
katana I don't even know maybe like uh
maybe like a
[Music]
this weapon is for me let's try let's
try something else oh now this one
you're not ready for let me show you let
me show you give me one second to look
at my whip
I yeah oh gosh hold on okay I think I
got it
oh
yeah are you are you witnessing my power
now are you look at this don't get too
excited now unless
oh dude
yeah did you like that I don't actually
know how to use this thing really
this is nice I feel like I feel like I
don't know if I use it maybe the the
cards might get a little excited that's
not really the point of this is it so
I mean unless
I heard them talking before I kind of
want what they have
so lonely
but I think after all
I think I gotta go with the gun right
what's more what's more intimidating
than a fairy with a gun so let's let's
let's get that bad boy out
are you red oh sorry that's bad are you
ready are you ready for this
Ultimate Super top secrets state of the
art mission where very cool things will
happen nod your head yes if you're ready
come on come on no no there you go yeah
yeah yeah
that's what I thought all right let's
get going and I think they went that way
so let's let's check it out
sneaky sneaky those stealth everybody
remember don't don't squeak your shoes
let's go
whoa what's going on here
oh gosh
is this are these the infamous
I was briefed about
I was regulating this this is this is
not up to code oh my gosh
what but what if I mean my intrusive
thoughts
[Music]
oh
they're fake
they're kind of cute when you look at
them
maybe at your place oh oh who are you
Who Am I who I'm you what we working
I work here too oh
okay just kidding
actually I feel kind of bad using this
you guys don't have weapons so maybe
I'll just you know put that away
[Music]
[Laughter]
you're gonna regret that little girl
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait okay let's let's let's do this
fairly okay okay I'm just a tiny fairy
all right you guys are okay this is 2V1
yeah you know I know I'm right yeah all
right let's let's do this with a classic
game of rock paper scissors yeah yeah
winner winner winner gets to kill the
other two
all right
we go on
Rock Paper Scissors Shoot
paper for
paper
all right the best two out of three
that's two out of three all right she's
not getting with no matter what Rock
Paper Scissors Shoot
all right last one this will determine
it off
yeah your little hand this is 3D
technology I can do whatever I want oh
sorry all right last one foreign
let's do something else something that
involves not thought
because I don't have much of that does
it involve using my booty
yeah get down oh okay anything for you
madam
whose side are you on what's going on I
don't know but I kind of like this yeah
this is my my sub I really like what you
guys got going this is my little can I
also oh my God oh my God I think my
voice just turned into a female for a
second
Hollywood
I think you knew though I think yeah I
saw it in this group
all right ready ready
how are you so fast I forgot to mention
Ed
oh nothing
you this isn't fair okay last this is
the last one all right all right
watch this brother
this one's for you oh yeah me too I'm
living the dream oh man what is going on
I don't know and this boy okay but but
serious all right
I got the power over here bro giving you
the story
one more
keep it thinking
okay all right the last challenge the
last challenge will include brain and
Brawn the double whammy
are you ready yeah look at these guns
look at look at that I look like I could
Bend those in one
[Laughter]
come at me
oh
[Applause]
foreign
what's happening oh
oh
God
[Music]
I
like me yeah
[Music]
foreign
tonight
[Music]
daddy daddy
foreign
[Music]
God yeah
what'd you think of that yeah
I think it was pretty all right yeah you
were doing the little legs really pretty
good but yeah enough to not get me
kicked out right oh no yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
I can't believe I can't believe I
screwed that up so much
I took everything from me my guns my
whip they were on rental
[Music]
I have to I'm gonna have to leave town
I'm gonna have to change my name
[Music]
buff isn't taken
look it looks so good in there
no no I can't afford anything I have to
go back home to the forest
what will my mom think
I have to see my grandma again
I guess uh I guess it's time to put my
fists up
God she's gonna lick my ears there and
she oh Grandma see you soon
[Music]
hello
everybody here we're here in my Forest
oh my God isn't it so beautiful
yeah let's forget that old job whatever
that was yeah screwed that we're you
know this is this is my home this is
where I this is where I belong
oh it feels so good anyway
um I actually have some
special guests that I want to invite I'm
nervous so I'm really nervous oh gosh
um but I'm very excited to show them my
3D baby
so
um yeah please welcome everyone warmly
and let's start with our first guest
hello
hi
oh hello
[Music]
you look so cute
thank you for joining today thank you so
much I want to cry
[Applause]
[Music]
oh it's so cute
wow do you have any any like special
poses or anything that you you know I
have so many of them I wonder what
should I do but today to celebrate your
3D I have a special request for you for
clothing okay something really cute
right something like
yeah yeah it'll be perfect it'll be
perfect for the day like this okay yeah
okay okay well I want you to do uh
find a push-up
are you sure
yeah I have a date for the workout right
oh that's true it is it's a lovely day
you're so right
yeah anything for you
it's faster yes
no one one
two
three why
[Music]
five five
oh my God
[Laughter]
it's just perfect you got you got 3D so
now you have to do the push-up look at
my arms I'm so strong
[Applause]
I feel I feel so tired now
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you thank you
is there anything else I could you know
like a like a
okay so what about you give me a coat
the cutest kiss you ever gave okay okay
only for you
only for you because I'm only for you
oh I couldn't forget that y'all
thank you oh my gosh okay now we're
married right
yes we're married now
everything
thank you bye-bye bye bye
yay
my heart oh I'm hearing hearing the
kettle laugh it just fills me with so
much energy
I'm so glad you could join now we have
another guest so I'm going to bring them
in
hello
[Music]
thank you for joining today
of course I had to I was so happy that
you wanted me here anyway
but yeah I am takanashikara from Whole
Life English myth yay
thank you of course I would want you
here of course
it's only it's really fresh here that
the air is so fresh yeah ah
wow yeah how do you make this air so
fresh in here it's it's you know anime
girl magic it's just bam
yes deep breathe be brief and maybe that
also helps you in case you're nervous oh
yeah yeah I do I mean I'm very nervous
nah don't need no need so is there
anything I could do special for you oh
yes yes okay I have I have a couple
ideas oh um well let's start easy okay I
don't know if you already did this but
how about uh a big heart with your arms
over your head oh yeah
this one's for you
and now while we do that turn around oh
One One 360 turn oh yeah okay a flip
a flip
how do I flip
okay
thank you okay how about we um spell
your name
with your body yeah okay that's a p
indeed oh
hello Emma okay
you're hard to use more of your body
more m is
I'm sorry my arms are still so it's cold
because the m is just an o oh
it's easy
I heard you have a gun is that true it's
true I do have a gun
would you like me to bring out my gun
yes show me the gun I will show you my
gun
[Music]
one second
I gotta pull it out of my anime space
oh it's like a Spacey gun all right yeah
I wanted to post like that like your
secret agent oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah yes
some cool angles yeah
now you're gonna shoot my heart no I'm
already fallen for you
okay okay how about we put the gun away
okay no gun and now we want a close-up
okay
and then put your hands on your cheeks
and then smile
like this
oh guys
I'm too close no oh okay how about we do
foodie mookie poser you turn around okay
and then you very shy
you oh yes
the other side other side
[Music]
because she
is
oh I have I have another one oh okay
last one
my ones are pout with your arms crushed
um like this
yeah and you press your arms for one
another
um why why are you poaching for more did
I make you angry no this is this key are
you you have so many girls around you
and it makes me jealous a little bit
sometimes you know
the last one is the last one this will
make everyone happy
okay now please I'll go I'll go lower
camera
[Music]
okay
Kiara
[Laughter]
oh my God I love you I love you thank
you only love me that was amazing thank
you I feel so revitalized and refreshed
yes I'm a new person
congratulations
[Music]
oh my God
I'm so glad you could join me
oh she's so cute now she got me that
whip one though I felt and I'm I'm
embarrassed I'm even more worried about
the next couple of people what they're
gonna what they're gonna make me do but
um you know
it's it'll be fun yeah I do have a
couple props so
um I've been I've been kind of like hey
let's let's let's do fun stuff so let's
call in the next group
all right the two of you
hello hello
congratulations on your 3D days
so cute
thank you
I'm here um
thanks give us a nice bro yes please yes
this is this is it oh it's so cute look
the background as well yeah it's like
Boris
so so pretty how can you fly though
putting me on the spot kanashiro
okay all right I'll do my best
okay here I go I'm flying
[Laughter]
are you levitated for like less than a
second
I've used a lot of my energy today okay
so like you can't you can't blame me
it's just
anyway we have more things to do for you
oh you do okay I'm scared okay
can you do the MLP using your body or
arms but can you make sure that you zoom
camera man Zoom it on the armpits
okay okay
um
I can't hear I can hear this oh
[Music]
a heart
oh that's so adorable
yeah can I do a heart like yeah kind of
oh you can kinda kinda
the thing is formal okay uh-huh
enough with you enough with the cute
stuff cute stuff yeah all right
can you
are you as mean as you say can you beat
us up oh
yeah come on
all right
don't wait don't look
oh my God Millie
please
yeah
and can you put your the Tomodachi and
squeeze squish it using your thighs
like crushing
I don't know if I can
wait I feel like you're welcome they
don't they don't deserve that kind of
fan service you know
you're welcome
I thought I thought I was actually
worried I thought you guys were gonna
ask me to do weird things
oh see you went with oh you want weird
things okay Emily okay last one though
it's not weird but it's kind of like
funny okay okay can you do a Watergate
of Jin so fire fiber
like I don't there's no like Watergate
too you want me to just say it yeah just
do it just sit on the spot so we can
dance it next time okay okay improvise
okay improvise I can do actions okay if
you want that instead or
[Music]
okay I'll do I'll show you I'll show you
like a like a easy waza to do okay all
right okay this is called Thunder snake
you go
to Guru
that's amazing
[Music]
are you
okay
[Music]
we have another group
another group of people I've been so
social you guys I do just really nervous
about asking people for this but I was
like I should be social I can talk to
people anyway let's welcome the next
group hello
hello hello
can you hear us hello yeah I can hear
you
oh my God you're so cute okay so you're
3D but you've been 3D before so exactly
only MVR chat yeah
move without a bulky headset on you know
oh my God you know what that means oh
God do a jump do a flip okay yeah do
that first I told him yeah
was that your
[Music]
young lady how can you be showing your
undergarments to all of these people
today watching sorry Mom I think they
want that though
oh you're honest baby what about the
order of Sanji Ian okay what other stuff
do you guys have
all right all right all right all right
I got the perfect pose for you so scared
of you so bad okay so can you do like
two peace signs okay
and yeah yeah can we have a close-up on
that oh yeah yeah can we get a a heart
eye expression oh no heart eye oh yeah
yeah
it's so yeah cute cute's the right words
so cute
yeah
yeah it doesn't mean anything at all
okay
oh you do the splits bubble I heard that
short people are flexible like they're
nine centimeters so you gotta be really
flexible who told you that
you're nine centimeters yeah but like
who told you that short people are
flexible God God I'm not I'm the least
flexible person I know
wait can you have the other angle again
that was really funny
I can't
oh God
your pain is so much fun
oh anything else anything you guys I'm
your doll today I can do can you Naruto
run for me
um okay
I waited my whole life for this now you
do oh my God as long as you zooming
I'm like I'm like an onion Hedgehog
[Laughter]
all right did you have any poses because
I have one more oh okay I mean I like
you to blow kisses at us little
okay come on you can do it think of me
when you blow your face okay I'll think
exactly of you
I don't think she's thinking of you
[Laughter]
you're so cute darn it
I can't even beat you I hate you Nina
yeah
she's here so you can beat her yeah
exactly meet me in the boys
like me like give me a little bit of
time okay I will get my ass into that
Forest yeah all right oh my God and I
can watch yeah
like if you sell the tickets for our
fight but I get how much what do we
split in here you know wait I'm
splitting no
I'm doing it for capitalism
all right what's the last pose now
what's the last part can you call me
call me ha for me oh okay
yeah yeah
say it too
[Music]
okay
you cut out could you do it again
we missed it sorry uh thank you guys for
joining thank you get out of here
I can't wait
okay and we have one last guest
um or two
welcome to the stage
one last
guests you forgot about me
the way that you just assume it's new
why do you think it's weird it's like
last night as a unit is the best yeah
one last me
look at that aren't they cute
oh crap I'm not using my Chad voice
banging no look at it oh yeah they
bounce yeah they're so bouncy
so stiff just like her chest
speaking speak for yourself
oh yeah actually look I'm in 3D I can
bring this is the forest the boy is
chemiston
what is going on beside me
it's a chest bump chest bump oh yeah you
wanna wait actually
oh my God
oh my God the nips touched
wow now that you brought us to your
Forest what would you like from us what
do you want us to do or else whatever
you guys want me to do oh
yeah
oh no
well let me first of all get a zoom in
on my favorite
um
part
besides the assets okay
you gotta get him down there because I
know it's so damn small
oh my hands are in the shot hello me
now let's try okay should I be on my
back
oh okay oh I see
she's become one with nature
okay does that feel good it looks like
kind of like a massage yeah
yeah get in there
this is so wrong
how are you feeling
[Music]
the camera
oh
look at her ears she's gonna overhead me
I wanna touch it
[Music]
she's just so cute
so cute
[Music]
this is so cute what other what poses
can we make her do I didn't think this
I'm like a rag doll
can you death drop oh I don't know what
is the death drop for your leg
you end up oh
don't look at her do not perceive I'm
perceiving respectfully
are you safe now I don't think I should
try that
um don't test drive at home yeah
hahaha
this is so silly how does it feel to be
3D whoa what the hell is this on the
ground oh you know what that is I was
just standing there medicine
this guy
throw him on the ground
like a soccer ball it is
it's just it's just a little guy well
where's his face there
all right do the best kick you can are
you ready
that was a good one yeah
oh my God look at home when she's so
cute she's so she's so fine She's So
Divine
hey baby that's my line to you this is
true it is I feel like I'm a mute I'm
immune because I I'm so used to doing it
to you
if you say I'll be like yeah what's up
I'm Hima let's go
[Music]
I'm just showing off the poem
what more do you got planned after this
what's going on what you what you doing
where you at where's you going where are
you what you doing I have a thing what's
your name
I have
a concert mini concert
I thought that was what we were doing
we're not in the forest anymore
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
tonight
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
it's always been my dream to perform on
a stage like this so I'm super duper
happy hey thank you for coming I really
appreciate it oh God I'm out of breath
now
um yes so before my uh final song I just
want to thank everybody I want to thank
the staff I want to thank everybody
watching I want to thank uh oh I did the
wrong order
I want to thank the tattoo monkey people
for coming and you guys of course
um I'm so nervous because the next song
my final song is actually my original
song so I really hope you like it I hope
you've enjoyed uh the stream I hope that
you've been having fun and yeah I'll do
my best so
oh okay let's go
alrighty music start
you find the magic
[Music]
dance
no fantasies
[Music]
believe me believe me let's go together
yeah we are bubbles believe in magic
powerful energy
[Music]
if you're feeling lost you can find
yourself here there's anime games
[Music]
foreign
the universe or metaverse no this world
is
[Music]
[Applause]
no fantasies
[Music]
electric fairies
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign