[Music]
A
Go
[Music]
DET
[
Music] Ko [Music] ã£
[Music] Ko [Music] L
[Music] ã£
[Music] [Music
]
Ko
[Music]
Haiki
Oichinya  Hello, Pikiniki,
hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, halo, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello,
hello, hello, hello, everyone.  I
can't tell from this, but everyone,
Nyan Hello has started. It's
going to be an amazing event as usual Holo
Live Grand Sports Day 2023 All-night Festival.
Thank you very much for joining us today.
[Music]
[Applause] It
's an amazing number of people.
Today, we decided to enjoy the all-night festival together quietly, so we
all decided to play together and practice a little.
Thank you very much for your support.Thank you very
much for your support.Thank you very much for your support.Thank you very much for your support.Thank you very much for your support.Well, I'd like to say
hello to each person one by one.Isn't it okay?Is it okay to
take today?Can I ride my dog?It's
okay.  Let's move on.
There are a lot of people today, so the
people who are participating today are Eko.
Everyone, just press the tab button. That's
amazing.
11123114+14 is.
20 years ago, 27 people are planning to come.
[Music]
Okay, so today we're
going to play in the newly renovated fir tree for the first time,
do some Holmen hunting, and have a little fun with 27 people.  That
's what I'm thinking, but
today I'd like to talk to all of you listeners who have
n't seen me play with you yet.I've been
thinking about doing a little bit of holomen hunting since then.  Let's do it,
please. I don't feel like it's too late.
Well then, let's do it right away. I'm going to go to this place.
Please follow me. I'm going to have a
great time today. There's fights going on all over the place.
Stop, stop fighting, look at everyone.  I
know what Subaru is saying. Let's get along.
Let's
get along. Let's
get along.
[Laughs] We're getting
along.
[Music]
Oda.
[Laughs]
You say you have two nipples, that's great, Nemio-san. You
have two nipples,
but you can't use them properly. You can
press them properly. Why are you being
made to do this when everyone is gathered together like this?  I really want to go without shame,
stop it, stop
it, you're not pushing me, delete it, delete it, it's
fast, it's not really good, but I can delete it.Even
though I was in a state where Sasu-chan left it behind.
No,
just delete it. No
matter what I tried to do, I couldn't delete it. It got
stuck in the system.
Something happened. So what are you going to do?
You should put out a button,
everyone.  So, let's start with the red team, and let's
play with each other.I think there's probably a good
balance between each of them.I think the number of people
is gathered.Yeah, yeah, in general, there are
too few whites and too few yellows.  I looked at it to see
if it was too much or too little red.I did
n't feel it, so I thought, ``Yeah, yeah, that's good.''So then, there are
people who appear with red hair.Yes, yes, there are people who appear.Ah, it's
not the red group.This
is what I say.  By the way, I do
n't know if anyone has already gotten it,
but there was a copy of the book on the table.  Let's get it over
here. Yes, everyone is here. Please
get out there and head towards the school. I
made it, so I'm
sorry that the version is not ready yet, but please
support the members.
Yes, yes, yes.  Well, Holmen Hunting
The rules are that each team will select 6 people.Yes, there will be
2 games, 3 people will
be selected, so there will be 6 people.Yes,
then the red team will play first, so it's Hunter.  I
guess I'll just decide on the 6 of us and get them together.Yes, yes, what should we do about the voice chat?We'll just keep it divided.I'm thinking that the voice chat should be divided into red, white, and yellow colors.I'm sure it'll be crowded.Then the red team will be a bit crowded.  I
asked them to stay here and go to the place where the yellow and white colors were designated.
Please, please. Right now, the white group is
a bit lacking in coordination, so Chiara is the only slot available.
So,
why are you all going to Chia-chan's slot? Please get in there. I'm
going to leave for a second.
Wait a minute.  I'm going to
enrich the frame,
thank you very much. That's right.
Hi-senpai, where should we gather?
Where is Tiara-sama? She's in front of Yoshiyoshi
. We're getting along well. I'm okay. I'm
sorry.  I'm
sorry, I'm
embarrassed, I'm embarrassed.If you don't take it today, what's the
point of my gathering here?It's
all called a pre-party.I was
worried about what to say, but I
decided to call it a pre-
party.  Chi
Tite
Gerati Um, I wonder if the members of Holomen Hunting are
all together.  I'm
not sure if it's all set or not.I
see.If you want to try it, you can try it.No, yeah, that's right.Let's give it a try.Yeah, yeah, let's do that.Okay,
okay.
[Music]
Then I'm surprised Kara-chan isn't here.
Kaela and Kuronei
haven't collaborated together yet.  It was
there, but it's
gone now, but I'm getting louder. Everyone's voices are getting louder. That's right. Everyone came to my house, so it's really
difficult. Is everything okay?  If
there's anyone, please spam me in the chat. Little one, I'll give it to the person himself. Oh yes, you already give me a small cause. Raden is tiny. Ok, Ran, tiny, tiny, oh, Ran, where do I start?  I'll
ask Miko. Wait a minute.
Thank you, Ritsuki-senpai too. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.  Nice to meet you Nice to meet you Nice to meet you Nice to meet you Nice to
meet you Nice to meet you I don't have any hobbies Hey hey, are you an arranged man?  The
arranged match has started, but the yellow one is
going to be on the hunter side first, so we'll be on the hunter side first,
so we'll be on the run, so we'll be on the runaway side,
so which one should we
choose, all the fugitives from Class I?
Yes.  This purple fugitive, fugitive,
right click on Teb,
please, please.  That's
funny. That's funny.  The
white team was on the run for a little while, and the white team turned yellow and yellow. We'll
run away. We'll
do our
best. [Music] On the other hand, if someone who isn't the target gets caught, we'll lose time, so let's get caught.  If you don't have enough time, you can try to catch him
, but he won't get caught.It's
possible to take the place of the person in question.The more strategic you are, the more time you can
buy.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.What's it like?It's
a bit of a road.The topic for the actual performance is
a little different today, but yeah, yeah,
isn't it someone from Yanicus?People from Yanicus?
What is Yanicus?Smoking
Smoking Ki, Rabelly Berry Hard
Smoker Hard Smoker Ko
Raden, I won't protect you if you don't protect me
Olive
Smoker Hard Boiled Smoker
Nikas Oh come on, help me, I'm not doing anything
No, I didn't do it. I'm
completely innocent.
What about the red team's red team members? Well then, it might
be red. It might be red, it's red
. Oh, wow, wow, wow, wow,
wow, they got caught.  The
door is
being secured, it's
secured, it's secured,
more and more people are being arrested, it's
amazing, it's so
interesting.  No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Please help me. It's stopped. It's not
doing anything. Wait, it's not here. It's not here. It's unexpectedly
anti-anti. It's here where you can escape from anywhere. It's here.  If I
stay here, it's too bad. It's so bad. I ca
n't help her. I can't help her. I can't help her. I can't help her. Oh, that's
amazing. 6 seconds and 5 seconds to lead. [Music] 42 You're strong, aren't you?  There are
no yellow people or yellow people.There are no yellow people,
right?Do
your best, Una.Do your best, but you're a demon.  I
got caught.
Wait 15 seconds. Next topic. Next topic.
[Music] It
said that I was captured. But for
some reason, I was forced to go to the responsor.
Responsive, if you catch someone who is different from that Maodai, you will
be returned to the responsing point, so you can come inside me.
Nesaasaasa Asako was quite anti in her first book,
no, she's anti here.  Seriously,
even if someone with that string approaches me, I
can easily run away, right
? I have gray hair, but my hair is white,
and yet I returned to Spon.  The
next time I come back, Red
is on the hunter's side, so I'll run away again, and either way I'll
run away again. I
wonder if my dad has finally turned out to be a fugitive. Is it a bug? Nayoshi, he's running away, so he's running away. I'll ask Miko-senpai later.  I was able to enter this and
that. Thank you for your hard work.  There are
people from the yellow group who try to catch people from their own group,
but don't worry about it, people like Dekohama,
people who are a few centimeters taller, and
Holomen who debuted in 20,000 years, it's easy.  I
enjoyed it because it seemed like there were questions about people like that or the whole Holomen group.Thank
you very much.As for cup size, it's
really difficult.I have to look at the official website, which is really dangerous.
Even though it's written, I haven't ridden it. I might not be riding it officially, but it
's written in my private memo. I'll
paste it in my private memo. I wonder if
it's the G I want. But if it's JP,
I know chocolate. Leave it to
me.  I've made all the progress in the measurements. I'm
having fun.
It's a gorilla G. It's
not a gorilla cup. I don't
like it, but that's a G cup person.  I was
put in a prison, and I would
be sad if I went back to the spawn point.
[Laughs]
Since I'm a baby animal, I can't
help but worry that I'll be thrown into a prison and play ping-pong with them,
but it's definitely a
gorilla.
If you're the judge, which
one do you like? When you're on the hunter's side, the
hunter goes to take down the kids at the
top, so it might
be a good idea to have one more person waiting downstairs.
Yeah, that's right, there may be cooperation, but I'm sure it's true
. Is it
possible for people around you to give information to hunters? Well,
hunters hunt while talking on the phone,
so there are people around them.  There are no more people to
cheer for.The ones to cheer for probably aren't on the phone.Ah, that
's right.Well then, it's like showing your age, and your age is red, red hair,
red hair, red hair, ah, red hair, red,
ah, Lily's plan, sled project, soriso, sorry.
Sorry this is Lee Big Sad
News Sorry Leo Timely Chosa
Miko has been arrested.
No, Harting has
failed.
Unfortunately, this is how failure comes out.
Yes, I see. It said that you
didn't apply to the topic. Oh, I'm glad you got
caught.  I was freed
and surprised me,
Yabaya Yabai Ah, I
don't want to help people in the group.
Oh 200 oh 200, you are so crazy, you're a
playful, you're a playful, you're a playful, and
you are
both of you.  I
guess no one came. I
'm white. It's
okay. Sumiko's life is fine. Miko caught me just now, but the
subject had changed. I'm barely safe.  It's just
barely, it's just so safe, I think I'm
going to escape, I'm thinking about it, and
maybe that's it.I feel like I can definitely earn
about 10 seconds by going far away from the prison and hiding there.
Oh, that's
better. Let
me out right away. Help me out. That's
nice, but surprisingly, the prisoner's girl was behind me. I couldn't find her. Hey, nice, nice. You're
too strong. Maybe that's a good thing, too. Yes.
So for the last time, there are three people from the white group, who have
joined? Now, it's Team Leader Team Leader and Team Leader Ra, and it looks
like it's going to be a good one. Also, I wonder if it's going to rain. It's not raining. It's raining. Let's go!
Where should I press this?
OK, you don't have to press the button. White team,
don't press the button. Just press the hunter, just the hunter. Good luck to the
hunting
guys. Do your best. Yes, that's Raden-chan, the
hunter. Well, the hunters are Ame-chan and Kato.
And Kiaraden, hey, hey, who's there today?
Among the people, one of them is going to take a break.I wonder if that's
possible.Okay,
look at Raden.Who's watching?Is it okay?I'm rooting for you.It
's okay.I'll definitely do it later.
Do your best with the leader and Chiara,
enter, do your best, right click,
right click, right click, right click,
right
click
[Music]
Oh, let's do it, let's
do it, let's do it.The other members are like, do your best, yes, yes, do your best.  Let's
do our best, let's go, let's go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go,
Lego Red Team
[Music] The
Red Team was against the Red Team.
Mui Ate
is also Athenois. I finally got Nice Ope-chan.
I'm getting it, right-click. I'll
take it in front of Roya. Nice Ope-chan.
Do your best,
do your best, Zhang, do your best, try your best, next white, waiaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa sori
Amaun Berry Sorry Okay Choco Sensei
Choco Sensei Come with me in front of the cage It
's the white team.  Don't
hold on to the
rope you've been caught in, right-click, and
be careful, Raden-chan.  I'm
glad I put it on, I practiced it, right-
clicked it, and dug it out.That's right, in the run below, you
can't do it without using the rope thing.I
feel like I'm going to go here, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no.
Oh, nice, Wow, that's a good character. Reiyo, oh, Mizuo-senpai, that's great. Let's
catch it with Nedo.
Come on, Ririka-chan. Oh, he's
catching it. He's catching it. It's amazing.  You're
really catching me, you're such a mess I
'm
catching you but I don't have time Leggo nice Nice nice I couldn't catch Aston at all I feel
like I'm in front of the prison Left
click ah right I wonder if it's right or right Yeah yeah maybe that's right Shin is
kind so kind  Is there something I can do to fix it? Should I
face that sign and go to the right? I see. I see.
Okay, okay.
Well, it's the first time, so let go and turn to the right of the sign.
Click Yeah, it looks like the actual performance will
be difficult.If you don't catch someone by mistake, you'll always be on the right.This is the
right one.If you
catch something weird, it'll be on the left.Who
told you to do your best right now?
Angel, thank you for your hard work.  Let's do our
best, everyone, let's do our best. There's surprisingly a lot hidden under the yellow mountain.
It's ok to ask Mio-chan to do it in the middle of this game. I
can't do it right now. That's
right. Well, yeah, ok. Let's
take a look at the instructions now.  Please
take a look at the explanation.
Yes, I'll watch it. Yes, I'll see. I
think we'll get together for a while, so please
come to channel 4. Ao, yes,
number 4. Yes, it's here. 4, number 2. 2, yes, I understand.
Wait, wait, one more time, one more time,
one more time, one more time, one more time.
Cross is too strong. It's really reassuring to have someone on your side.
It's helpful. Why don't you do it twice? Well,
this time the theme is the same one,
but the actual game feels like we're going to go around this again. I do
n't need it.  Well, the
topic is completely different, so I'd like to think about it a little bit.
Let's do it together, three of us, and one person to
catch it. Let's do it with some teamwork.
Well, maybe we'll
take a look at the balance a little later.  Hey, that's expensive  Please
understand that there is a possibility that the building may be slightly scratched.
Yes, it's difficult. They would have been
captured even if I didn't do it. It
disappeared. Yes, it disappeared. There's no anti. So, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Please don't
come.  I
can't move, I can't
move,
let's make it better.  If you
have a partner, you might want to practice with someone. It
's true that some of the seniors have a partner. Listener
, we always already have a partner. That's
right. Yes, we have already decided, so each team has to
decide.  I'm giving it to you, so I'd
like you to do that with your partner.If you're a fan, please
touch that signboard.Only people who are superior to you should do that.I
made a mistake.  It's
okay to be on top of my senior. I
don't have anyone for the first time. Let's take a
look today. I don't know where they are.
Wait a minute. I
haven't decided who's going to be above me and who's going to be below me.
Well, especially for me, I'll be the one below you. Of
course, it's okay. He's
running really
fast, but he's got an aura.
Thank you very much. Miko-senpai's picture
book. Can you use it? Awesome. Let's take a minute and press the start button.
It's okay to go back to the start and start.Yes,
thank you.
But-chan, I
thought that
would be a good idea.Chato-chan, today, it's going to fly. Oh okay, fight fighting. I see. Can you press the fighting button? Kana
Fai. This is a really cute game.
Cue
Ah, it's time to release the true power of the leader. Today, it
happened at the leader's sports day, so I was on top.
So, I did it. I did it, so I'll do my best. Leave it to me.
Remember those days. It seems like it's at its peak. If you
defeat it, you'll get points.  You get points for defeating the ones that don't have many.
If you have a lot of guards and defenders, then go to the general.
And now the team you're chasing is a different team. Ah, the
red team is chasing you. This is their first fight.  It has
n't started yet. It hasn't started yet. It
hasn't started yet. It's like a sword. If you
don't do it, the countdown will
begin. I think it's easy to understand.
Protect,
protect, protect, oh, this line of
watermelons is great. Yeah, yeah, I want to take a picture. I'll
take it. Should I take a picture? The baby has become the general.
Cheesy me, I'll save you. I'm sorry.  I
can't see each team's rulebook right now,
so you can ask them to give you a quick explanation.Okay, I understand.I've
put up a spreadsheet with a summary of the rules at each team's place, so if you
could take a look at this as well, I'd like you to give me a quick explanation.  It
's the same content. Okay, I
'll explain. Yes, please.
Yes,
please wait a moment. This is the
summary of the
rules for the competition.
Yes, the older person fights with a sword and shield.  It became a competition
Well, the knight's physical strength is 3,
so the person above him has 3 hearts on his head,
so when he
gets attacked once, he gets 1 heart.  It's
going to be gone.
If all the hearts are gone, you'll
be respawned. You'll be respawned at the initial position. You'll be respawned
at the initial position in that field, or rather inside the tree field.
Well, when you respawn, you have 3 seconds of invincibility.The
time limit for everything is 1 and a half minutes.Yes,
can you please explain this in English?  It seems like the more
kills you
have, the better, but I
feel like it's even better if you defeat the general, by the way.
1st place
gets 15 points, 2nd place gets 10 points, 3rd place gets 5
points, etc. Oh yeah, it's
starting
Go hey hey hey what are you doing?
[Music] It's
better not to know. I'm not going. I understand. I'll
protect you.  But when it comes to people,
hey, oh, oh, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's
coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's
coming,
it's a huge attack, it's good, go go go go go go
After the defense of Stegos, this is the general, let's go, let's
go, let's wait, let's go, let's go, let's go,
nice, nice, go-go
jumpin, nice, nice, nice, nice, wait a minute, we can go first.  It
's coming, it's coming, it's coming,
it's coming.  It's
dangerous, it's dangerous, what are you doing to the general?
Stop it,
stop it, stop it, it's dangerous, it's dangerous. No, no
, eggplant.
White is a very good protector. I
can't accept it. I'm thinking about it. It's amazing. I got
10 points. Oh, Ki-chan and Ame-
chan, 8.  Awesome kill, amazing 8 kills, but 2
kills, chocolate. I
wonder if he's participating in the battle. It seems like he's participating in everything over there.  The
yellow one has a two-way advantage,
so it's amazing, it's amazing, it's
amazing, it's amazing, it's amazing, I'm going to participate in this in the actual
race.
It's possible to break up with someone who kills you.That
's right.It's a big deal.I want to
forgive you.I want to forgive you.Okay
, I'll go back once.Boy.
Yes, Ooicha 2 is here, yes, it's coming, it's
coming, it's coming, the management didn't say earlier
that it would be okay if the person on the Kiba Line touched it.Yes, that's
right.
Yes, there's probably one
yellow player overflowing, but yellow team is supporting us today,
so we'll do it, so you can ask the red team to come too.  It's
a little bit different from that day,
so I'm going to be on the lower side, and I'm going to be on the higher side, yeah, yeah, you
can do it at all, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yeah, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
let's
do it one more time, let's do it one more time.  Kana Teja
Matare
[Music] Let's
go in one more time. That's fine.
One more time. Let's go. Let's go. I guess it doesn't
have to be different from before.  The
whites above and below the members are probably weird, and
since they're so drunk, it's okay to ride the horse.Okay
, then I'll ride Chancha, I'll ride Rane.I
had 0 kills a while ago, so
let's go a little more aggressive this time.Okay, Ganga.  Let's go, Oooh.
If we attack, I'm also curious if the General will be defeated. Can we
go? Well, we should just keep chasing the ones who are getting close to the General.
Oh
yeah, that's right.
The general has been staying in one place for a long time,
but I'm a little curious as to what will happen if the general goes with him.Let's
all stick together as much as possible.  It's
fun, it's fun, it's fun, it's
fun, it's
fun, I want to do more, more, more, more, and more.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's attack, let's
beat it up, let's beat it up, let's
destroy this world, let's destroy this world.  I'm
knocking it down, go go go, na
ya baya ya, something came from behind.  I
might be able to
kick it. I'll kick it from behind after I've
knocked it down. [Music] No, it's bad. [Music] I'll beat it. It's coming. It's
coming. It's coming. It's coming. It's coming. It's coming. It's coming. It's coming. It's coming. It's coming. It's coming.
It's so yellow that it's so
surrounded
[Music] It
feels so good, it's so good,
it's so good, it's
just like that  The
general hasn't died even once, but the
fact that he's earned so many points doesn't mean the general's points aren't that great.Maybe that's
true, but it's true.  1
kill is possible, just 1 kill, just 1 kill.
Well then, I don't care about the general's life anymore, so I'm
protecting him. Isn't it better to just attack without defending?
Need is more like that because there are so many of them, right? It's
true that they have a lot of physical strength, so there are 5 of them, so
everyone, please gather at number 02.
Will you deal with it?
Or will you change?
It's Konemiko. I see that you're looking good. I understand. Thank you. Thank you. Seniors and seniors can't run away from each other. I'm definitely going to become a Riki leader.
[Music]  I
wanted to practice with different teams,
but since we can start like that on the day, let's hear it.Yes,
everyone, let's listen.Yes, the
person who plays the knight can press the start button, so it's not
at all.Even after this, the teams will practice separately.
Even if that's the case, it's okay for you to do it.Yes
, I think I've pretty much figured out how to do it.I just have one question.What is it?I don't
understand at all how many times that general will kill, and whether there will be any benefits if you kill him.  It
wasn't, but if the general is defeated once, you
get 1 point, right?
Yes, this point
doesn't matter in the team points mentioned earlier, but the
number of deaths of the general is
in that overall specific number.  If it's added to the final
score, that means it's the same as the winning points for the first match.It
's a bonus point that is added regardless of the points from the first match.That
score will be tallied at the final stage.  Yo  The
person in 1st place gets 15 points, the team in 2nd place
gets 10 points, the team in 3rd place gets 5 points, and so on.  Even
if you get killed, it won't be added to the previous place.I see.For example, if the team in 3rd place gets 5 points for the grand prize and kills 5 times, yeah, yeah,
that's right, but it gets 10 points.I see.
I see
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's such an interesting
rule, but if you
can't keep up with this and it's going to turn into a rhinoceros in the rest of the time, you'll be able to
aim at the target. Yeah, yeah, that's right,
please be careful general. Yes, yes, yes.
So what
do we do next?
Isn't it a good idea to check it out once? Daebak,
debaku, voice? Do you want to do the voice?
[Music] I'm
saying English
[Music]
Hit me!  It's very
difficult. I
still have the equipment for the bar line,
but I still have the equipment for the bar line,
but don't worry, I'm playing the game so I think it's a good deal.  It looks
like we're entering. Let's split up into teams.
[Music]
Please.
Yes, that Calliope won't be doing this event,
but what should I do? I'm
not going to watch it because Iroha-chan isn't there.
So I asked for two knights, a
knight of Raden, a knight of Raden, and
a knight and a knight.
Commander
: So, where are all the Captain Knights? In the middle,
in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, dangerous. I'm going to become the Red Knight.
Dangerous, dangerous,
unexpected spy is a spy. Do your best. Ahi looks good
on you. You look good on a princess.
I'm a stubborn princess who looks like a princess. I want to beat Hanahime I
want to beat a little. I want to hit a little aggression I
want to do a little aggression.
Fufufu By the way, the
knight was
talking about that
place with Iroha-chan and the others, and Amu-chan
said it in easy-to-understand English.
So today, I'm going to
go and do something like that, like the top right corner of Jou. Holding chopsticks, I have
such basic understanding, this is the first time I've come to Earth. I just came
to Earth the other day. Please say hello to Earth. I wonder
if it's going to be more and more knights. Of
course.  Yes, of course you can leave it to me. I'm a
cheerful knight. Okay, buy it. The
white team wins, we win, we win, we win, we win, we
have no choice but to win. I'm all confident. Speaking of Minecraft, I
heard Kaze for the first time.  I'm
going, I'm going, I'm going, I
'm going to protect you. I haven't done anything.
[Music] I
want to ride on everyone's head.
[Music]
I'm riding on the white one.  Right now I'm
riding on top of Raden
Oh yeah, now I'm white A-chan, this
is it Chan-ah I'm riding on top of the leader Right now I'm riding on top of the leader Masu
Razu-chan is good oh yes yes yes Yes, I'm
riding on top of the leader Oneisnai
Pa, I'm going next time. Well, then, I'll go. Well then, Captain
Raden, ooh, it's good. Shizu-chan, Captain. I'm
riding Rade. I'm riding on A-chan. Captain
Raden, hey, one more time, one more time,
one more time. I'll be back. It's okay, it's okay, please ride. I
'll ride. I'll ride.  It's
not Captain Zuzezura, it's Captain Raden, A-chan. Hey, hey, Captain
Raden, Azu-san, hey, Captain Raden.
Zu-chan is fine. Yes, Raden, hey, Captain.
Ah, okay, I
did it. Gogogo, ok, ok. I wonder if you'll give it to
me.
Well, please
leave it to me. Please press the ``please'' button and press the ``OK'' button to get the material.Ah,
ok.  What is this?
Oh yeah,
yeah, that's it, that's it. This is important. Please help me. Help me. Oh
yeah, it's a lie. No, it's a lie. Hey,
this is a bit of a tomato, or this one right now.
Here it is, here it is, this color here,
this color is good, it's good, it's good, that's
right.
Raden is the director, good, good, good,
that's right.  It's like a pig. Yes, the hourly
wage has increased. Yes, Azuki-san, Azuki-san, the
hourly wage has increased. It's a little different. This is that.
Naechie, the leader. The hourly wage has increased, one by one.
So, it's better to have one. If it's a little too long, it's no good.
Oh wow, what was that? Another cat, Cat.
Now another
cat? Oh wow, this one, this one, and that one.
Isn't there something easier to understand?  Kanae,
no, no, but what did I do wrong earlier? I do
n't know, but I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got
it, I got it wrong. I
mistook it for paprika.
Well, first of all, I want to eat grilled mutton.Okay,
yakiniku.Okay, what's next?The other thing is, I
want a special hamburger steak, so
please couple the raw meat with Kawa.Also, I'll do the hamburger.I'll
have the lamb.Yes, I'm going to eat it.
Cut the raw beef,
potatoes, and carrots. Potatoes, carrots,
potatoes, and others.
After that, I cut up the ground beef on a griddle,
then roasted it with potatoes
and carrots.It looks like it's done.I cut up the carrots and carrots.I
can't imagine what it would be like as a dish.Here,
lamb.  Yes,
it's lamb. Yes, I'm grilling it right now. Is it beef?
Beef is raw. I'm going to cut it. Yes, it's raw. I'm going
to cut it. Yes, it's going to be raw. Cut it on a cutting board.  I
got it and grilled it with ground beef, cut potatoes, and cut carrots on a griddle.
Thank you very much, Raden.
Amada Fight
Naietto Top Left Pink Top Left
Pink Top Right Orange Bottom Left Red Hatena Pink Orange Red Hatena
Pink Pink Pink Pink Pink
Pink Pink Pink Pink
Ona Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Okay, good let's
go Aisuke Customer, Customer, please stop. I can't go. I can't go. Customer, please stop. You're so weak, Princess. Please use your grip strength to come somehow.
Dead, dead, where,
where, where,
where is this?  So, he
's burning,
burning Nice Nice, and I'm not
approaching to Nahi, I'm not approaching to Hi -kun.
There's a pig.
Yes, there's a pig. Oh,
no, this pig. Oh, this pig. Oh,
save me. Please say it one more time. It's
okay
. It's the last round.
That wizard on top is the scariest.The magic
user.That wizard on top.That's
dangerous.He's a magician.Please use your grip strength to do something.He's
trying to make everything work with his grip.The
wizard is scary.I'm scared of wizards.Yes, I
'll use magic.  I've done it and I
'm a magician. Is there a demon or something? Everyone has recovered too much. So,
everyone,
hey, hey, let's go. Princess, please. Yay,
5 minutes. All right. 5
minutes.
If it weren't for that one that fell on the way, it would have
been nice. But yes, everyone, please come together.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you, Ama team. Niwa,
here, here, here. Yes, the princess is on her way. Hime
says.
Oh,
Hime, ice cream was a princess and I was in a good mood, so I was
called Princess, and I had a
hot dream.Everyone had a new
cooking menu, I
think.But
Subaru's difficult fried chicken.Subaru's fried chicken.
Fried chicken, no, I was surprised, wasn't I? I
ate a hamburger
that
tasted good. That's how I ate it. I ate it. I ate it. I
ate it. [Music] I was surprised when it was moldy. My
voice went like this.  Yes, you
can do it, but
please take a close-up of it.I want to see it.Do you want to
see it?I want to see it.  I'm
going to the place where I'm at.
What's going on? What's wrong? Everything's fine. It's okay. I was
wondering if they'd make me [ __ ] again. I was waiting. They suddenly told me not to look. It's
not like it's my house.  That
's no, that was me, that's
wrong.I want to do that with the people who practice sorry.It seems like they want to do
some replay too.Practice,
people who want to practice, practice.What
should I do?  Is
n't it okay to play upcollop? It's fine if you only do it
once. Right now you
can do it with unlimited players, right? Well, I'd
like to try it once. I
think there's only one red player right now.  I can't do it today I
couldn't do it now I can't do it, so there's three of us Yes, there's three of us
Go Chiara Let's go now, um, Chiara
and Su, this is the same as the actual performance, right?
Please give it a try.
[Music]
Please, Tiara and Bi go to that other server.
Okay, I think it's okay if we split them up into groups. I
feel like if we cheer, it'll be a mess. Okay, let's open a group and
play that member match.
I'm a member who wants to do what I want to do while listening to it, so please move me to No. 6. Is it okay if I go to No. 1? I
can't hear everyone's cheers, so I want to do what I want to
do while listening. It's
okay to be a team, but to be a returning team. Please, yes,
yes.
Well then, I did my best.
Yesterday, when I practiced in the middle of the night, Miko-senpai
told me that Chiara was the best.
Even today, that's not the case. When I saw the visitor and Mizuo-senpai today, I realized that maybe
that wasn't the case.  I thought,
Oh, I'm losing it Ah, do your best. Believe in
yourself. Believe in yourself. Oh, try your best, do your best, be persistent.
I forgot how to do it.
Oh, oh, B-senpai, that's amazing. It's
okay to fall. Calm down, calm down. Finally.  It's the
last point. I don't know how to do it anymore. If I
fall in the middle, I'm out, so that
's totally true. I don't know until the end. Even Sui-chan is
falling like this, and I
think I won't really understand until the end.
But here I am.  So, I'm kind of
nervous. That's right, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm definitely nervous. I'm a
senior. Oh, it's
over. Someone cut me
off and interrupted. Hey, did I press it? Did I make a mistake? Pressed it. Pushed it.
Pushed it. Pushed it.
Lister Sometimes things like that
push you, sometimes you push them.On the contrary, they help.On the other hand, they
help.Reverse help.Let's
reorganize things a bit.Yeah, do your best.Good luck, bugs, bugs, bugs,
bugs.I wonder if anyone can
push that.That's why.Anyone
can push.Maybe.  The more I
understand, the more scary it is to make a mistake and get a bug.
Hey, are you okay
? For, oh, oh, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, the
pressure is on.
Yao, do your best, do your best,
do your best. If you do your best, I'll make you something you like. It's
really a
book. People other than me want to eat la and la de. Eat
hamburger, hamburger, hamburger,
ha.  Nice nice character nice scanner Ai
Okay, let's do our best, try our best, it's finally here!
Serious senior hamburger is waiting for us. Hamburger with
chocolate right in front of the hamburger.
Teacher's hamburger with handmade hamburger cheese.  I want you to
put it in. It's okay, it's
nice, it's cheese. That's good, it's nice. Let
's eat a hamburger. Oh, I'm so
happy. I'm so happy. There's
one person who's greedy. I want fries.
Calm down.  Nice
checkpoint Nice checkpoint My heart is
pounding, but it's good. So the
checkpoint is important. Oh wow
wow wow wow, it's gone. It's okay.  It's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay.
That's right, wow, wow, wow, this is a great battle Yo
Tia-sama, fly, fly, fly, fly,
fly,
Yo-sama has wings, it's okay.
Nice checkpoint
Nice Omai
Gao Maga OK OK, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry I'm sorry. It's
okay. It's okay to practice.
If it's too good to be true, there
's a chance that they'll take measures, so I thought so.That's right, that's
right.There
's a possibility of starting a fire, so let's go slowly.Let's go slowly.We should be able to
do this in an atmosphere that makes us feel nervous.
Yeah, yeah
, okay, oh yeah, it's okay even though I went. There's still
100 seconds left. I wonder if I can make it to the top. I wonder if I can make it. I wonder if I can make it. It's delicious, delicious,
and salty. I
seriously fell too far, but it's okay. It's okay. There's
still more than a minute left, so calm down.  It's
totally okay, but it's okay. I
can do this, but I'll do my best. Do your best. Good job. Good luck.
Thank you for being late.  It's going to
take more than a minute, I
can go, I can go, I can go, I can go, I can
go, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay if I fall here It's okay, it's
okay, it's okay I can
only see the top of the checkpoint, it's okay, go,
Tia Ato  I can go a little further. I'm
done. I'm done.
Hamburger. It's not a hamburger. I
'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Good job.
Even if it's just your first time, it's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's a lie. I'm more
nervous than the broadcaster. It's
okay. I can't climb a single mountain. Thank you,
Senpai.  I
can't see it, I can't catch up with you, you're so kind, oh
my gosh
, I don't want to do this anymore, go home, tomorrow
is tomorrow, tomorrow is tomorrow, tomorrow is the real thing, today is the
real day.  It's
better than not being able to reach the goal, even if it's a week or so.Even if I don't do it, I have a goal that I have some margin for.If I fail or fail, it's not at all.As long as I calm down, I can recover.In the end, I have some margin.  If you reach the goal, you'll
get the goal. If you don't, you'll get zero points.
Sorry, but if you reach that point, the
points will be different. Ah, okay, huh. Hey, Mio-chan.
Yes, there's another Saano on that team.  That
holo-up person you praise isn't there.
No, he's not here today. Okay. I'll
ask Yellow, too. Wait a minute.
Yes, yes, on the other hand, don't you want to decide that number one who can't climb?
This is a terrible game to think of.
Yes, it's German, but there are some highlights.That's not good, but that
's the thing about the first part where you can't climb up.That's
right, that's right.
I'm a bit of an adult and can I ask one more person?
There are members who would like to try something.Anyone is fine.I'd
be happy if you could just leave it alone.  I
can't climb it, but it won't end forever, so I'll try to do it for about 4
hours,
but maybe no one will do it
anymore.
Well then, yes, it's better that way.  I'm in trouble,
Leo! It's okay, my
heart is pounding, Kia-chan has a heart. It's already my second
time, so maybe things will get a little better. Nice,
nice, nice, nice. I've done
this once before.
What do you think? No, I haven't done it yet.
Since I haven't done that today, I'm
thinking maybe I'll tell you some rules and tricks after the broadcast is over.I see.
Thank you, nice Bo,
Senpai
[Music]
Has that, Senpai, are
you kicking around
? Can we do it together? There's no horse, but there's no horse. We
can do it, no, you know, we shouldn't be able to do it at the same time.
But what the heck?  Once you get the debug item, you
can practice somehow. Eh, that
item is that debug item on the far left.
Hmmm, I can't do it right now. It's being played. It's no good, it
's being played.  I
guess we can't do it unless we ask him to stop doing this or that, so it's something that everyone wants to do.I think I'll ask Miko a little bit about it.Yes, yes,
but I
'm currently in the yellow area, so I'll have to talk to her for a while.  I'm
listening, yes, that's right, now
and then. Yes,
tomorrow's microphone check, etc.
After I'm done, I want to practice, etc.
Yes, let's do
it, let's do it,
please leave it to us.
Wow, you have a different spirit,
after all, you're a newbie. Yeah, if there's anything you don't understand, just
ask me anything. I'll answer anything,
so no, I can't answer. I'm the newest. That's
all. Thank God, it's okay. I
see. It's okay.
Tomorrow.
For those of you who are coming, oh, oh, oh, oh, I'm going to hit you, can you please take me out? Yes, yes, yes, yes, my life is already being targeted. But the little Sui-chan, the Sui-chan, is floating and talking about everyone with a trident.  I'm
aiming, I'm going, I'm going. Maybe the
debugging guy is doing it. The
debugging guy is
in creative mode, so let's
bring out the trident. Oh,
Kiara-chan isn't in it. That's
not in it. Aoi-oh.  Well, it's
here. There's a lot of Tridents placed here and there. I could
climb like this, I could climb, I could climb, I could climb. Let's go.
Wait for me. Let's go.
No matter what happens, I can't go to the lottery anymore. Keoisho, I'm no longer excited.
It's funny
[Music]
Naoishoya, stay here, do your best.
Hold on, it stinks. It's
omelette rice. Omelet rice chocolate. Choco-sensei's omelette rice. Oh, no mushrooms.
So,
please, it's been added, but it's true. I'm
happy. I like yakisoba,
but the most delicious one is fillet cutlet.
Fillet cutlet Fillet cutlet Fillet cutlet is good Fillet
cutlet is
good Fillet cutlet
is delicious I would
like fillet cutlet, please.
Ah,
I know, it's expensive, but it's going to come back to the fins,
right? Ah, you understand. Oh, okay.  It's
so smooth. It's so smooth. I wonder
why things
were like this earlier. Well, the two of us
were a little bit nervous just now. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right. Yeah, there was a lot of
pressure on us,
and besides, it was the actual partner.  I'm
sure I'm nervous, come on up, checkpoint, I
hope you're doing well. Let's
buy a nice bar here and go to the winning rhinoceros beetle.  It's so
difficult that it's the strongest. If you stop, you
'll laugh.
Even that tiny beetle can win against a
stag beetle or even a large beetle if it gets into the habit of winning. It's
too much. It's too much. You said it last year. It's
true that it's a beetle. That's a little bit.
It's a lesson for the leader after all.
He's the leader, so
it's okay, it's okay. He's close to the leader, so do your best. It's going to be difficult, so it's time to leave.
Ki-chan is amazing because normally he's
good, he's kind, he's kind, and his
seniors are a little kind, he's quick here,
but he's almost there, he's doing his thing here,
and he's going to go here, or he's
in the middle of the corner.  Let's keep our spirits up, let's keep our spirits up.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Okay, faster than before, it's really fast.
Just
in case, we've won in a row. It's crazy!
I wonder if there's a lot of loss if that part falls. That's right, it's amazing because of that last checkpoint. Yeah, it's definitely calm, but it's not at all. I was able to make a comeback from here, so I can afford it. It's so fast.  Okay, just try a little
harder, thank you. You
can go, fly. You're a woman who can fly.
Mix it up with fins and a little.
What's the
unnecessary thing to mix in? The
idea is delicious. Darkness is okay. Delicious.
Yeah, I'll try my best, and then I'll
do a little more, but as expected, Tiara, I'm still nervous. It's good, I'm a little nervous. I'm
grateful to see you so nervous. Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you. I wonder if it's rare. Yes, it's amazing. No, no, no, no, no, no,
even in practice.  During practice, I was already able to
walk around, but even during practice, it's
amazing. It's two goals in a row. Yeah, it's so
kind. It's
amazing. It's so kind. As
long as it doesn't hit, it'll be fine. Yay.
Nice, nice, the results of the practice are showing.
Thank you, do your best, Eiko. I want to see Eiko's turn in the actual performance. Let's get
1st place, Kia 1. Let's go. Let's do it. Let's
go. We're the woman who can take 1st place. You
can go. Nice.
Inaba. What's next? Nice.  Nice
po, nice I guess that's it at the end Are we going to do an obstacle race?
Relay
Ralis Relay Relay Relay Relay
Hey, please leave it to me Rele Run let's get off!
Karari yay yoi shon NEXTI
thinkIthinkObao bar
teleportation
Baba teleportation teleportation
Aiina Uber teleportation
I LOVE
LOVE
Kakao
Enribe I wonder if I'll just watch my house Good sho
There are some members who aren't there so what should I do I don't know
what to do 8 people  Is it an entry?
Wait a minute. If it's just a matter of time, we might have to get
8 members or all of them. It's true that there
won't be enough entries unless everyone is present.  Is it
okay if I ask you to do it for me? There are
8 of us, so maybe it's all of us. Let's
put them all in. Yes, let's
do our best. Let's do our best.
I'll do my best.There's something like an entry button.Oh,
something like this book would probably
let me enter.It's not that cool.I hope
that's the case.It's okay.
There are up to the 9th person to havetoate, but I
wonder if it's the last general.Oh, I'll
make him general, then he'll be the 8th general.No,
but there's one person, Isuka.That's definitely one person.That's
not enough.That
's 2 laps, 2 laps.  Wait a minute, it's the
second one, so let's do it.The last one
will be the same course, but this is it.Each
person can only enter once.  It's
talking to me, yes, yes,
yes, please, please, that's Lale-chan, please.
Yes, I haven't made an entry. Is it a book entry?
When I open the book, I click on the right, oh yeah, right.
Right now, it's only 6 or 8.  I understand that there are no
vacancies, then I'll make it 6. Nice, okay. I've
been waiting for you. I also ran away and wasn't here today. It would
be nice if you could tell me what it was like for the members.
Well, that's right, that's half a lap, right,
so we decided to do it with people, so 8 people, 8 people,
uh, okay, this is fine, I see,
thank you, oh, thank you,
each person runs half a lap.
Okay, so the odd numbers here
are the odd numbers, right, so the odd numbers are here, so
135757 or here, then you can go over there. Hey, this is a
really difficult book.
What should I do? Oh, what should I do? It's
over. I can't go without practice. Is it going to be real? It wasn't there. Well then, I
wonder if it's okay. I still don't know what the shortest route is.  I
want to take the course, but if it's a
different course, then Chiara-chan, it
's the 4th race, so even if I ask you to take over, I'll
definitely take the change.
Yes, it's done. It's not done. Wait. How do I
change? If one of us presses number 9, we
can run away. Well, we
might do that. Well, Ki-chan is number 3. Cue
number 4.  Nice,
nice, thank you for your help. That's good, that's good. Oh,
oh, oh, oh, it's starting. A-but-starting.
Suddenly, it's all gathered together. This is probably a format where things are thrown out on their own. That's
amazing.
That's right, do your best, do your
best, when it's your turn, you'll probably be forced to stand on LINE without permission.It's so artistic that it's
too graphic.May,
early bread,
fly left click, left or left, oh, I
have to eat.Maybe I should eat.I'm
hungry.  I'm hungry,
so I'd better eat. It's so
fast. It's so fast. It's so fast. It's so fast. It's so
fast. It's so early. It's
so scary. It's so scary.
Left click, left click, feel like punching, punching,
punching with the left, okay, left okay,
okay, I'll hit you, Ashiko-sensei, you're fast, it's so fast, it's so fast,
it's so fast, it's amazing.  That's
right, oh yeah, it
's so fast. Even the bubbles are pushed back. The bubbles are also pushed back.
I see. Let's have a
hamburger. Let's have a
hamburger.
It's strong
[Music] It
might be better to pull fast and pull it in the middle.In the middle, yeah,
left click on the cloud, right click,
how much is enough?Okay, one by one, go,
run, run, run, do
your best.What will happen if you don't give me the fast bat?
Robato, that's such a
scary
thing,
oh
no
,
go, do your best, do your best,
do your best, you can do it even if you're not.
Kekea, it's hard here, seriously, don't fall down, long,
and that vine is long, space above, that's
dangerous, long press, hold space, press and
hold space, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, oh, oh, it's good, it's good, this pool here is
Surprisingly, it's at the top.  I think it's probably good, so
if you do something like jump when the top bubble comes up, you'll probably be able to go all the way.  Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, it
feels good, it feels good, do your best, do your best, go go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
do your best [Music] Do your best, do your best, leave it to me.
I'm going I
'm going I'm going This is this
Larade I can see
who's running from a distance Raden Good luck
I'm Raden, I'll do my best. I
can't go here. I can't go here. Please help me. I
got on this first ride.
[Music] I
did a jump. I can do it
upside down. The space is going to be long. That's right. I
can
avoid it, but I can avoid it. How do I avoid it?  I do
n't know what's going on,
but I like you, I
like you, confession-chan, I like you better
[Music]
I'm scared
Hey, I guess that's right. I feel like I get caught quite a few times on the far left,
at least, and I
always seem to get caught by other people from the middle, so that's
a bit strange. I'm looking for a machine to try this one out.
Mogumogu is
good, it's nice, it feels good, it feels good, it's really fast, it's nice, it's nice, it's a book, it's nice, it's nice, it's the last one.  It's
really fast, it's really good, it's really good
, the general is fast, fast, good, good, good, calm down. [Music] [Music] I was losing ground, but I caught up, amazing, I caught
up.  Hmm, I'm not going to
appear. I'm not going to appear.
Emiyu Senpai, I'm not going to appear in the
actual performance. If I don't do the actual performance, I won't appear in the actual performance. I'm really excited.  It
's just Mase, yeah,
who's the only person here who's going
to be in the real race? Ikuzu-chan is the only one. Wait, wait,
1st place. I ran 1st place, and the last one was the fastest, but neither of them
showed up.
Hey, come on out! I'm so excited. It's okay to have fun.
Let's have fun. Yes, it's fun, it's fun, it's
fun. I'm so happy. It's fun. It looks like it won't be fun, so I'm scared.
It's crazy.
Yes, yes, there's a bumpy sound, Deka Miko,
yes, this is it. The system is quite
confusing and it's easy to play. No
matter, I'll try waiting for a while. Oh,
wow, you can do something like that.
For example, if you mix it up, it means that you can do that fang line
while also being a hunter.
Does that mean you can do it by mixing up the members of different Lilles? Yes, you
can do it by mixing the members of Rire.  amazing  It's
amazing, it's amazing, so for example, everyone
touches the entry signboard, and at first, it's
easy to move fast, and if you touch wherever you like, whether it's white, yellow, or red, you can do it,
and you can
run up to 3,279 people.That's
right.  9 But by the time there are 9 people, the
anchor person will run one lap,
and they can do it in a blink of an eye. Yeah, it would be nice if they could do that, so they'll do it next
time. But if they can't do it right now, yeah, yeah.
2  in the third time  I
wonder if I should just join in and do whatever I want after that.Well, there are some people on the other teams who aren't able to do it.I see,
there are some people who are acting violently, so let's
do it again with the full members.  Well, I guess it's
fine if the team is a mess anyway, so I guess that's the case.Then
how do you decide?The
team will have a quick story, and
then they'll be able to support each other as they see fit.  I
guess it's just a matter of cheering them on. Everyone, just do your best. All you have to do is enter once. All you have to do is just press the entry button. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right. It's the white team, the white team. It doesn't matter. It's the white team.
So, wait a minute,
yeah, I have to stop the game.Wait a minute, yeah, I'll
wait.Oh,
wait, yeah, then the red team will become the white team.Yeah
, yeah, yeah, yeah, right now.
Maybe there are some people who haven't been able to run this
team. If the whole team doesn't run, it'll be a bit yellow.
Yes, it looks like we'll have to run one more time. That's
right. There are some people on other teams who can't run, so it's going to be
one more time.  Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, leave it to me,
yeah, it's white. I
don't know. It's still turning a little. I'm
sorry you asked me. My head is
seriously not turning today. It's seriously not turning.  do not have
Okay, Kihawaha, just take the frame.
Yeah, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's good.
To the right, that's the right one. Looks like the right one will go forward.
Maybe we won't bump into each other even once. Yeah, maybe it's the right one. I see.
Well, I guess that's what happened in the second half, depending on whether you can cross those vines well
or not.I
jumped for some reason and then pressed space once on the spot.When I
first pressed the button to get to the top and then flew, I
didn't fall once.  I feel like it
That's right, even if I asked you to write it down for the first time,
okay, I'm sorry, but I can't help it. Okay, uh, it's
raining here, uh, it's not possible.
At the white group, I'm eating Lil' bread. ``I see.
Okay, yea, I feel like I understand.''
Tips for forgetting 1  That's right, the first
one is creative, so it's on the right side. If
you
fall all the way down, it's going to be difficult to come back.
[Music]
Hey, everyone, I'm sure that once you get to the top, you'll go.
Easy everyone, Kia is
going to Japan next week, so please come and play with me. Well, welcome
to Japan, welcome. If you're serious,
even if it's against Chico, you'll make a fillet cutlet
and fillet cutlet fillet cutlet won't be there.
That relay.
Yes, this is the one that allows you to practice without using the system.Yes,
this is the one where you can
practice freely without using the system.Yes, this is the one that allows you to practice freely
without using the system.Yes, I see.  We have to
do it one by one, so let's
give the command. Those who want to do it, I see, okay.
Well, for example, we're going to play
Holomen Hunter one more time, so anyone who wants to play should
come. That's right.
People who want to play should come.  I'm going to give a command like, ``
Ten,'' and then I'm going to say bread, but I had a question about this, so I'm going to share it with you.
But if you don't
do that act of taking the bread, it might be
faster, but if you
do that, everyone will just dash without taking the bread.
Yes, I'll take the bread because it's a
must-
do, and it's definitely a rule.Then, if you have to take something, you
have to take it, but if you don't eat or not, you have the
freedom to go along.Yes, I
understand.Okay, now that I understand that, I'll do that competition.  I
'm going to say a little bit when I'm going to say ok. Yes, I'm going to reach that point. Okay, I'm practicing a little bit. That's what we're practicing
. It feels like it's practice time. Okay, hoops
time from I did it.
Thank you. Let's practice lots of relays.
Okay.  I'm sorry, I'm not sorry,
I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I
'm waiting, but it's stained, I'm still waiting for it, but it's stained, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.  If
there is one, it's like I'm going to rush in. The
member who feels the possibility of running into me is the first one. Yeah, I'm the one who's going to
rush
in.
Is it okay for Ruen-chan to rush in?
Yeah, my luck right now isn't good.  Yako,
I was so busy with you last time,
Ran-chan,
thank you so much. I'm sorry for barging in on you so much today. I was wondering why you were apologizing.  I
was so happy, but I'm so happy. I'm so happy. I'm
fine today as well. I'm energetic, energetic, energetic, and the source of my energy.
Alcohol. I'm feeling energetic today as well. I don't know if I'm
drinking alcohol or not, but I only drank a little. I
'm writing about this here, so I'm going to jump in here.  I don't know what to do.
Well, first
of all, I'm not asking you for the tips on theory. I'm
saying I can't write it down.
If you go with that space jump, you'll be able to
go really fast.Okay,
that's what I said.  Yes,
that's
true.I'm grateful for that.As someone who's only been playing Minecraft for a month,
let me tell you that.After all,
all you have to do is throw some money,
right?
Oh, who is it good for?
Why are you throwing it at me? It's really
starting from 1,000 yen to 1,000 yen,
but it's a little expensive. Isn't it
okay to start from 5 yen?
5 yen or 1 yen, that's a terrible option.
There was a single yen on the ice, ice dash, dash, jump. I
see.
Oh, it was just, it was, it was just, was
there any competition that we didn't do today?
Today, I did everything. I
did everything. Oh, I did everything. Ok, I
did everything, but I want to practice something like this.
If you have something, please do it. I see.
Yeah, I'm doing Holomen hunting. Ah, oh, I'm going to
do it.  Oh, everyone, the lid is
on the left side.  I
finally noticed it Yeah, I finally noticed it Yeah, I'm going to move the
ivy on the left all the way to the top of the ivy on the left.
Yes, there is white, but
there is something written there, and there are always red players
entering. Are you a hunter?
Should I put it in? I forgot, Raden,
that's right, I didn't do it earlier.
Oh yeah, let's do Yellow Hade. For now, let's run, run, run.
Yellow, uh, other uh, uh, members
should also be included in White's Hunter. That's it.  Is
n't it okay?Are you a fugitive?That's
right.That's right.We did it too.This
time, we ran away.A
fugitive.Don't run away.No, it's okay to run away.  I'm
going to run away, I'm going to run away, it's OK, I'm going to run
away, I'm going to go to the bathroom, so I'm going to go to the bathroom for a little while. I'm going to go to the bathroom, but I'll be back.
You have to
run, you have to run, you have
to run, you
say it like a curse.
Evangelion,
Evangelion, you can't run away, you can't just run.  I
have to run away, I have to run away, Misa-
san, I have to run away, Misa-san. It's
also great that we don't look alike at all. We
don't look alike. That's weird. We don't look alike. I thought it was really funny.
Naewaaaa1  A hunter with only people left
This is the person from the red group ooh the person from the red group is rehearsing the red group Oh, it's
only white He's
already screaming so much Zeta-chan shakes me even though he's
still red I'm
getting beaten up
No, that's not right
. White, I'm bored. You're lazy.
Run away.
Power lare-chan, come on, let's go.
Raden-chan, there's the English you learned the other day.
Nil's
nipple on one side and nipple on both sides
No, no, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's good, that's good, that's good. I'll
be happy if people think it's a skill. There are so many
people in yellow. There are so many people in yellow
. I
don't know what they're doing. There are so many bugs, bugs.  It's
just a bug as much as it's a bug.
Bug testing is a
little bit of a bug.
When I thought I was there, no one was there,
but I was surprised to find out who
was hunting Mia.I was feeling
a bit relaxed, and then I
noticed that it was the same guy from when I was in the mobile classroom.  I
'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but the
members of the red team in my house still don't quite
understand how to do it, so they practiced one more time during the first half of the game, and
only during the red team's theme.
Can I let you go?
Yes, yes, O. Yes, I'm a fugitive. Yes, I'm a
fugitive. A fugitive has been released.
O The high place is disappearing. It's disappearing. I
guess it's something. It's yellow. It's something.  Mikara:
Yes, yes, it
certainly looks like poop, and I
can see it, and I can see it.  Is that
what you mean? That's why it's only honey on the top. I noticed that. Yo, there was such a sense of playfulness. Poo. Don't say no. No, no, no. How do you say that in English?
There's a pattern,
I see, there's a pattern of not teaching it. That's amazing. It's a stupid, good decision.
TE
say, if you teach it once, you're going to say it a lot. That's why you say it,
so yeah, that's what it's all about. Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Let's see where you are. Red
people, red
people, this is this, this is this, it's solitary, it's solitary, it's
solitary, it's solitary, it's solitary, it's
solitary, it's solitary, but
I'm at the top. Me, me, me too.  Me,
me, me, no, I don't have a place anymore. I don't have a
place anymore. I don't have a place anymore. Have you
seen the movie Titanek? There's no place. It's so small  It
's a small space, isn't it? The red team is looking at us. There's
someone behind them. Be careful.
There's someone out there. Do
n't hit the target. It's not a hunter. It's not a hunter.
The hunt was good. It was a dangerous place.
People should run away.  Run away, they're coming, they're coming, they're
catching, they're catching, they're here, they're here, they're here, they're in trouble, they're in trouble, they're in trouble, they're
in trouble, they're going to get
caught for practice Oh
yeah, I see.  It's
not going to fall easily, so I'll run if you don't, but come on, come on, come
on. Hey, the subject has been changed.
Slow, slow, hey, there's no point in trying to catch me.
That
's why I said that I didn't do anything like that to my senior.I won't do it.I won't do it.That
kind of thing will cause a flame attack on my senior.  I
won't do it, I'll try it, I'll try it, I wo
n't do it, I won't do it, I don't want it to start a fire, I don't want it to start a fire, I don't want it to start a fire, I don't want it to start a fire, no, I won't do it, I
won't do it, it wo
n't start a fire, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
funny.  Oh, hey, hey,
hey, hey, what can you say? Hey, hey, say something, it's
you, yeah, is it me? Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, don't say, don't say, stop, this part is
cut out, this part is
cut out, stop it, stop it, please stop it
, you're too impatient, no, no, no
, it's already gone, right?
No, I
went to the blue one, right? I
can't keep up with the developments.
[Laughs]  I was
about to burst into flames, but the white team is also a
pigeon. I'll do it. Do I want to do it? I want to do it. Let's do it next to yellow. Yeah, okay, then I get it.
Even when the white team was that white team,
those who ran away could become other members of the white team, so yeah, yeah,
yeah.  Yeah, that's right, please
try it.Yes, yes,
that's
not the next one.Raden was taking a break
earlier.So Raden is better.Please go ahead.Please go ahead
and run away.Everyone.
No one has free time because you get used
to it.I see,
it's like what was explained in the chat.Raden-
chan became like a Yankee to Kana-chan.Raden-
chan became like a Yankee.That's right.
Yankee I got tangled up with a Yankee. Oh, hey,
just jump a little. It's a
Yankee. It's scary. Try
jumping. The jump is offline, so it's
offline. I see.
Okay, okay, oh, jump! Hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, chili, pay, pay, pay, pay,
pay. Don't say pay, pay, it's not going to end up in your pocket. Give me the money now. Don't do that. I'm scared.
After all, cigarettes and Yankees.  It's the
Showa era of Yanki and Leverage Tobacco,
but the harmony is gone. It's
like it didn't come out now.
Tsukkomi doesn't have many tsukkomi, and
when you act like a stupid person who doesn't have a lot of fun, you're going to be taken for granted. Hey,
people in the red group, people in red who aren't red. Popi-
popi-po, popi-
popi-po, popi-popi-po,
popi-popi-popi
[Music] It's
so nostalgic.  After all, the back of the prison
is
the place where you
put me. I don't know
what to do about this.
Hey, this is good, this is good.
Kanami Senpai Senior Prisoner A
back of the prison that may be the back of the jail
that's really good. It's really good,
this is definitely a yay galaxy brain.  It's
okay, I found out, Senpai found out, it's
okay, it's late, it's over, it's over, it's over, it's
good, it's good, it's good, it's
good, it's good, yay, yay, yay,
yay,
yay!
No,
no, no, I'm not drinking. I'm yellow. No, I'm not drinking.
I'm white. Oh bije.
Even if there's a lot of people, I still want to catch them. I'm going to
catch a lot of them. It's
fun to be in a cage with a lot of them.
Ooomo-senpai enjoying the inside 7
Matsuri-senpai has caught a lot of people.
Even though he was caught, he won't run away from Matsuri-senpai.
Next up is Hunter and Oraden. I
'll practice a little on the day too Hunter-a.
Well then, Captain Raden Gun and one more person will
work hard if they join. There are already three of us, right? Well, there are three of us.
So
even Chiara-chan is not the
senior Raden-chan who can ride Ame-chan Noel Raden.
Really, it's okay if it rains. Then,
yeah, yeah, okay, just give me a minute.
Really, of course, the rest of the members except for Tsurugi
are fugitives, just like before. Okay, I'll do my best.
Right click on the rope Yeah,
beat up everyone and do it Why don't you beat them up like
that There's no need to
beat up like that I got lots of kills
got lots of kills Goal yeah Goal I'll
become platinum Platinum Hey, I don't
want to do it anymore.  If it's a group, I
can't handle it unless I'm a Predator. Which is
better, Platinum or Predator? I do
n't know about Predator, I don't know.
Predator, let's go, let's go, let's do our best. Good
luck, right click.
Right click Right click the person from the Red group
Click right click Red group
Red group Rare-chan Where is this, oh, white and blue-
chan is here White is
really here.  There
's a lot of red guys at the entrance.Aa-chan has already caught
them.Ame-
chan's really delicious.Let's go
!Look at them and use them.
Who, who, okay, oh, nice, nice, nice, nice, keke,
ok, ok, nice, nice, nice,
keke.  I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
but I'm
sorry, you can't catch me, Senpai, I'm sorry, I
'll try my best to catch more of you.  I wonder
if A-chan can't do this rope.Yellow
Yellow Member Yellow
Yellow Yellow Member
Yellow Sora I caught Suba-chan who has a senior.Here,
this is double the score.Tasore.Let's
solve it.There are a lot of people under the yellow here.Okay,
let's go.  I'm hiding, I'm hiding. I'm so nice. I'm
going to catch you here. It's
the end. There's no room left here.
[Music] It's
fun. It's a cute game. But it looks big.
Yes, everyone was able to practice the controls.
It's pretty easy. It's perfect. It's perfect. It's a
fun game even for beginners to Minecraft.
Raden-chan, I can do this. I
can do this. I can do this.
E-
mas. Yeah, I'm aiming for platinum.  Platinum
APEX
[Laughs]
Kasou APEX I'll
do my best Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
for my senpai is gone Mio senpai
Well, let's do some holmen hunting. We've
done all of them. I
wonder if it's May or not. They
ADD
Light is nice. And we've already practiced on our own. Oh
Himegoshi
Oh Himegoshi Hime Hime
Hiami I've done it once.  We
got together at 2 and played all over that once,
so I'll close it once, but after this, I thought it would be okay to practice and
stream, so I
went to 2 once.
[Music]
I'll do my best
Low, nice greeting. It's
wonderful. I'm not sleepy. I'm not sleepy. I'm not sleepy. I
'm energetic.
Motomoto Mimiko isn't here. It's yellow. I'm on the team. See you
soon
.  I'm sorry, but Subaru has a question. I ca
n't
make calls anymore. Or maybe I can't make calls anymore.
Hey, these guys are weird.  I
was angry, I heard the
voice of an acquaintance for the first time
in a while. I'm sorry, I said it wrong. I made a mistake.
I love you, I love you, I love you, all of you. I
'm sorry, I spread the rumor that we're acquaintances. It's
over, it's over. Thank you for your hard work, disbanding, disbanding. Thank you for your hard work.  It was a
gross senior that
was dripping.Gross.Gross.Gross.It's no good.It's
no good.It's no good.It
's no good for a group specializing in real music.Yes.
No, no, I was told no.
Dekari-chan is a miff, so it's not right. I
want to join too.
[Applause]
Everyone,
48 people.
[Music]
Hey, we're looking for 42 more people,
but it's early.
Good
morning.  Hello!
Project? I heard that there were some fans of Hello! Project, so I came here,
closed it once on the way home, and left the slot as it was after that.
People also felt like it was okay for them to do that, so I guess it
stopped once they closed it.
Yes, yes,
Ospor is missing, is
n't he? I'm back, so that first time is okay. Okay, yes, everyone.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you.  I
'm very happy, even though I'm a bit hesitant. I hope we
can all have fun while supporting the members who couldn't make it.
Please, from now on, I
'll call out to you, and it's okay if it doesn't matter. I'll call out to you like it's someone who wants to play with you, and you
can ask them to come at that time. Is that the
same as the fang-gag line that activates?  It's the same with uploading, and I
can't do everything at once with Higo, so I'm
thinking of doing it in turn, so I'm
going to gather only those who want to do it and have them come.  You
can close the frame after this, or you can leave that frame,
but I'd like to thank you very much. Thank you for your
hard work. I'll see you
again tomorrow.
Thank you for your continued support.  [
Music]
Thank you very much for your
wishes. I
'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Yellow is number 5 for now.
Yes, what should I
do? What should I do?
Connie, Akata, I don't know what to do.
Yeah, but
there are some people who have already left the channel, so it's Raden. Ah, Raden is here too.
Raden. After this,
there will be another broadcast from 11pm, so I'll excuse myself here.
Ok, thank you very much for your
time. Thank you for your hard work. I'm tired. I'm
sorry.
Hey, I'm a little drunk around here, so
don't push yourself too hard. Tomorrow, we'll go to the actual bar, and we'll
have some practice, right? That's
right, in the chat around here. I get it, I get it, I get it.
Thank you, thank you for your hard work, food.  Let's eat, what
should we do, what should we do, what should we do, what
should we do? We have a meeting after this, so
thank you for your hard work, thank you for
your hard work, then there are two of us.  I'm
so pissed Oh my, it's the two of us Hey, my heart is pounding
Hey hey hey hey hey hey hey what are you
talking about talking about it here here here here here here
talking about it I was really surprised.  I
was surprised. I was really surprised.
Moreover, they debuted in 3D right after they debuted. I
don't think so. They're 15
years old. They're 15 years old. They're young. I mean, they're young.  I
can't keep up with you, but you look like an adult.
After all, even at 15 years old, you look like an adult. I'd
like to collaborate with something like that.
No, I suddenly started singing a song aimed at Kiara. I
want to do it with the three of you. It's a dream that I want to do.  I don't know what to do. I don't know
what to do. I don't know what to do. I
don't know what to do. I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do.  It
's nothing, it's a lie, then let's do it.
Let's say something or something. As a vtuber, we're seniors, so I'm really worried about that, but yes, as a vtuber, I'm a senior.  Honestly, being in that kind of position makes
me so nervous that I can't do it, and
even though I'm thinking that I can't do it, I'm
different from Maki Goto, who is who I am now, so V Sesame.  I
'm a different person, Goma-chan, I'm a different person, I'm a different
person, I'm a 15-year-old Bugoma from the past,
so I'm going to talk to Hamata about that.
Yeah, it's just a dream, isn't it? We're the
number one Hello otaku on Hololive,
right? We're probably the top two. Ha
, yeah, yeah, it's a little airy, sorry.
Who was he? Who
was he? Who did he know? Yeah, it's me, Eriri, Erin. Oh
yeah, I loved him too
. Yeah, I already had a photo book,
too.  I have a lot of photo books by Risako and others,
so I'm
going to buy some photo books, but I
'm going to look at things like swimsuits, but that's not it, that's not it.  No, it's
not there, it's not there. It's not just
that, it's not the only thing that attracts me. There's a lot more
to it than that. Yes, she's just cute, so that's fine.
But the truth is, the reason I bought the photo book was
because I wanted to shake that handshake.
That's right, in Shinjuku, we
used to do that in the basement of Shinjuku.We shake hands, once at a time.Juice
Juice comes to Sunshine.Sometimes, we
shake hands just once.We buy a CD and shake hands with everyone for a moment.We
live in a different world.  That's what I thought
Seriously, I'm 3 years old, God, I'm already a head. I
got a flat tire. Tell me to do my best. I
said things like "please" and said I didn't understand,
but I tried my best.
Haha, thank you for supporting me.
Sunshine City was really cute,
and I've already seen a lot of Hello Polo, so I really
want to do something there, but
how do vtubers do it in Sunshine? I'm
sure they'll have to get a slightly bigger monitor, and then they'll be able to do it
with Wato 3.
Let's sing and dance. I'd like to do something like that in a
place that's famous for Hello, like Nakano-Sa Plaza
or Nakano-Sa Plaza.
Chiara: I've
been to a lot of places, I'm sure.
Well, I'm a stay-at-home otaku, and I used to be a stay-at-home otaku,
so I've never been to the Plaza.  The
best seat I had at Nakano Sun Plaza
was probably the third row. It's
not that bad. It's amazing that something like that could happen.
Basically, I was a useless person if I didn't do that one time at a time.  I'm
sure the sweat will be flying off of me. It's no one else's sweat. Maybe it's the people around me who are sweating more than the idol.  Because it is  It
can't be helped, right? I'm
sure we were flying it too. I'm sure we were flying it. It's
sad that Ekana-tan never had the chance to experience something like that before,
but he doesn't say that, so it's sad.  Well, after
all, I'm not going to watch old Hello! Project DVDs or have sleepovers, even if it's not related to the collaboration with Saa, or the DVD of the live concert,
or the YouTube video of Saa.  I've got
a lot of stuff at home,
so I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to
it. It's been a long time
since I've seen it. I'm really looking forward to it. I've got a lot to bring. I'm
really going to go there.  Let's go, let's go to the house.
After all, Rival Survival
is a bit necessary. Rival Survival. Oh, it
's the oldest and strongest, so it's a little rival. Let's
watch Survival. Let's watch together.
Also, do you have any of those Hello! Project
year-end ones?
I don't know if I have
any.
Yes, there are DVDs of Fujimaki when she was around 16 years old.  I'm
talking about next year, right? I'm talking about a little bit ahead of time.
Yeah, that's awesome.
DVD of the future. Excuse me. Excuse me. It's
amazing. I'm really looking forward to it. So, stay with that video. I
'll have that T-shirt.  It's coming, it
's good, it's good, what's going to start, me too, and then the
movie is about to start, ah, we're all doing it.
Wow, is it okay if I don't participate? There's
not even a princess, a knight, or a white warrior.  hey
There's Noel-senpai over there, but the
leader got drunk a little while ago.The
remaining long knights who haven't fallen down are
probably resting.So,
about that DVD sleepover.  I'll
get back to you.Okay, I'll be waiting for you.Thank
you very much for your support.I'm
sure I can't
handle my broadcasts anymore.It's
like, ``Okay, I'll get back to you.''Kira, I'll do my best today.''
Thank you very much, I'm so nervous. Thank you. You were so good. You were so good. You're a genius for getting both goals. Let's have fun tomorrow too. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you to everyone who watched. I'm
sorry.  It was just Chiara, thank you.
Hey, thank you. Let's hang out again tomorrow.
See you again. Bye
bye.
Maybepeople
Watchpeople
Watch.
Maybe everyone wants to see the archives of people who are late.
[Music]
NEXT
generallytheysaid
anybodycanSTREAM
their
puv
butIthinkTheylike
probablyPreferredto
nothaveLikeamillion
PVSbutmorelikeafew
BIGonesSoIknowsaid
SheSTREAMpovIknow
whattheSTANCEreally
isI
askprobablyIwas
planningtoSTREAMbut
honestly I was
planning to take the slot tomorrow, but maybe
someone else will take it, so it's
going to be really early in the morning, so instead  There's a
saying that you won't be nervous if you don't take it, so you might not understand.The album I called out in English is the word distribution point of view.That's
a pun, so please listen to the album in English.No matter whether it's
in Japanese or Japanese.  I do
n't get it IImakethe
jokeofSTREAMPVin
japanIknow
howmakethe
Joss Apov is from a point of view, uh, from a
distribution point of view, or your point of view,
and my album uses that word.
I may not have a point of view for tomorrow,
but that's the point of view of the album.
Please listen to the point of view.
Just let me just EXPONE.
youhaveany
plansofcourseWhydo
something
knowthere
about
inanhomeandwasting
fromHomewatchingDVD
andstuffSoISaidOhmy
godmissedOUTHow
about
WeDVHow
noabjustlikestaying
OverStayOverParty
watchingAllTheold
HelloProjectdvds
buseIalsoHavenbeen
watchingthemfora
longtimeandiikindof
wantedtoForceyou
guystowatchwithme
butyouknowlike
HowbutYeahShesaid
ShehasSoManySowecan
doStayOverwatching
oldoldConcertdvds
Togetherisextingwe
gnado
that
guys
[Music]
see
DeshiyouguysknowI
perform
wellperformbadly
knowthatgirl
isingfromtoostrong
andshakingIfeltMy
HEARTBEATup
myseIf you're really depressed tomorrow so you don't
get nervous, that means you're nervousAun Bye
Bye Guy Bye [
Music]
Bye I'll do my best
[Music]
Ah
[  Music]
DET