[Music]
so
hello kitty
[Music]
welcome to the stream everyone
how are you
first things first uh
first things first um i i did
i did get the the the restocked peccora
senpai merch
because
[Music]
get together
but actually i moved um
uh this this stream okay i think some
people don't understand don't some
people don't understand
um i'm a big decorah senpai fan
and uh bakura senpai's mama artist
released some not whole life official
merchandise on horoketo which is a whole
life related
whole life related event anyways
i wanted to buy those things but they
were sold out so quickly so i could only
buy one thing
and i thought it was over i thought
there was gonna not gonna be a restock
but it was announced that uh
10 minutes before now they would restock
and i was i was ready to buy it i moved
my stream
i moved my stream to a little bit later
to five minutes later to buy everything
[Music]
gifted dosa
gifted those things to me how could
[Music]
i bought i bought one thing but the rest
uh hagura mama contacted my manager
and asked uh if if the if she could gift
uh the other peculiar senpai merchandise
to me
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you
yes yes i was gonna buy it all i was
gonna buy
everything i was tr i was gonna try but
i was scared if i could
um really make it in time because pakora
senpai fans that know
sagi are really fast
and if you guys remember when i did the
crane machine thing
i also got a decorative
so i'm going to be sitting on decorah
senpai
and resting my hand on the peculiarizing
by mousepad
he
yay perfect combination okay anyway uh
today
i am doing a manga stream uh
but have you noticed this thing here
down here
[Laughter]
hey no dirty release next week
26th november don't forget don't forget
mark your calendars
we're playing a mangas today
it's been a while it's been a while
and this time i'll be reading out the
code for you guys because there's some
people who maybe don't
don't uh write that quickly so i will i
will say it out loud
slowly and then you can type along
i know
[Music]
please go easy on me everyone but the
rule is
one play per person okay
one bed per person and
don't check the chat while playing but
also
i think last time i mentioned
uh give the people who were
not in the previous streams a chance
uh so i'm very sorry
but if you participated
in the previous among us stream
would you please be so kind to not join
today because we want to give more
people a chance
i'm sorry to all those people who want
to join again
i'm sorry but um maybe you'll
you will get another chance i'm sorry
i want to give more people a chance you
know there's there's only like 10 people
per game so
uh and i'm taking up one of those spots
maybe i shouldn't play because i've been
in all of those games maybe you guys
should just play with each other and
i'll be watching how about that
which server uh doesn't really matter to
me but
should we do any
[Music]
we create the game concern
let's see okay
the code is
okay
tea i like tiara t
t t o
like orange
uh p like pineapple
oh like orange
okay like
and what the [\h__\h] f likes
like france france france i don't even
think it's got that
okay i'm gonna say the last letter
faster next time
yo why are there people with uh question
marks
why do you guys have question marks
hello rules
okay
is this only 7 out of ten uh i think
there's probably trying oh
there we go one more
we're still are people trying to get in
or is it
is it a glitch again
still hello more people
why does this always happen why does
this always happen
okay well i mean i guess you're just
gonna go with eight out of ten
okay showing that oh well if you want to
see it there you go
t-o-p-o-k-f but
i will change the room next time so
after this game
you don't even have to try to join the
room
at the end oh there we go hello you
don't even
you don't even have to try to join the
room at the end after this game is down
because i will be opening in the room
okay
are the tasks okay because i didn't
change from last time so it shouldn't
have changed right because it's my
settings
it should still be the same right
already full oh really did you count 10
people
uh okay everyone
uh please be nice to me
it's been a while
all righty
yeah thank you judas for understanding
thank you thank you
all right everyone i guess ready
oh yeah there's two reds well that's
really weird
but only in the chat hey that's so weird
okay whatever
weird game let's go close the
close
do i remember how to play this game well
this map is fine
but um i i don't i hope you guys are
okay crewmate i hope you guys are okay
with me playing the normal the most
popular map again
okay so what do we do how do i see the
how do i see the map again what's the
key for seeing the map
um that's so fast it's so fast
what tap okay okay
i'm running i'm running
i feel like it was someone that was in
the same room as me just now
okay there we go yay okay tab
tab okay
i'm running against the walls oh
who called there's there's a pretty good
i feel like that impostor has quite some
practice
uh let's go oh my god
um well i don't know man
electrical damn two people saw the body
oh there's the the question my guy also
okay that's that guy oops oopsie no no
no no
wait the red guy is uh which one
the great wait this is so confused on
that one okay okay
uh-huh so in electrical almost everyone
went there after
react electrical
oh the room there where only i did not
go
oh i went somewhere else
and so everyone saw that buddy
oh well why don't
i'm size of brown and green who
reported red aha
the the grey and red okay
what do you guys think am i allowed to
check the chat
am i green well you cannot see colors
green who hung back while we went to
react
well uh skip photo
i think wait a second skiara
we don't need to vote yet but keep it in
mind
i just thought of that
okay very well very well just stay safe
don't kick me i don't wanna i wanna play
the game it's not funny if i'm not
playing the game
okay we i have to do something here okay
how do i is there a key for doing the
task what's there
a key for that did you
come on wait give me
let me get my point thank you okay
shouldn't one person go down should one
person maybe go down
we're so busy here oh okay
there's one more thing
oh my god do you guys remember there was
like um i used to play world of warcraft
with my family
uh with my mom and my brother
and uh that was like that's like ages
ago i i played it like around the time
when world of warcraft came out
and um i didn't play it for too long
maybe
i don't know i don't remember maybe half
a year or something like
how [\h__\h] dead
i'm telling a story i guess you're not
watching the stream
okay well ghost still gotta deliver the
point so
okay so what i was talking about
what i was talking about so we we were
playing world of warcraft
and then there was i don't know if this
was a if this was a world of warcraft or
hello wow can someone report for [\h__\h]
sake
what about my body
so the story uh i don't know if i i
don't know if um
i don't know if this was only a world of
warcraft
meme back then but one thing i remember
very strongly
about what a warcraft back then was a
song called
the internet is for born the internet is
for born
you know that one
[Laughter]
i know is that isn't that only from
world of warcraft or did that come for
something else
[Laughter]
did that come from something else
because i know i i remember watching
that video uh where like world of
warcraft characters were without dancing
oh it's evan you cute it's a musical
yeah
i thought that was like fans originally
making that
up or something how did you know okay
wait which red one was that which red
one killed me
this is confusing maybe there is only
yoda oh wait no which word was it
oh the nameless one
he's not
is he is he uh protecting himself well
like i was telling my story
a stage full of muppet characters in
broadway hey
they had such a song
or is that like a song with changed
lawyers or whatever what was that so
interesting
uh that's a that's a childhood memory
hell yeah
what are we doing i still don't really
understand this one i think
is this the one where you just go away
and come back later yeah go do something
else interesting
let's go here
that's complete oh [\h__\h] this just
imposter
knows what they're doing i can't help
with that right
so i'm gonna do something else what can
i do there we go
hey those were actual legs on broadway
what what they allow such a thing
on broadway what
there's one more thing that um i was
like
oh my god i remember i remember amazon
very very a very young phoenix when i
was playing
what no
oh no well opening in your room
thanks for playing i didn't do much i
was
i didn't do much in this this was a
quick game
i know how to okay
thanks guys bye bye a little game
what was i talking about oh yeah that
was uh i was like super young
uh young phoenix
and i felt like nobody would take me
serious
so i i said i was older than i actually
was to everyone
yeah i was one of those people
don't trust kiara
okay so let me tell you the quote
that's normal okay
[Music]
i like uh
i like railway i can't think of anything
else
i like railway
uh x like
x q like
[Music]
welcome there's a one missing maybe one
more
come on come on come on come on come on
one more come on don't bug
this game always bugs
they are really fans um
one two three four five six seven
oh i wonder if one more person
was gonna come in because in the other
game we waited a little bit and then one
more person joined as well
it's na server america
america oh there you go
[Music]
10 people for 10 years
okay everyone understood
the rules right
uh-huh uh-huh okay and no bugged out
names this time oh
no one bugged out name what the hell
last time i played this this wasn't that
buggy
weird okay
now let's go next again
wow let's see when i i'm not a good
imposter please don't make me impossible
i wasn't busted so many times last time
[Music]
please
ah one person left goddammit grumman
yeah
i'm too scared to be an imposter i wanna
do
good things for the people i don't want
them
i don't want to kill them you know
this reminds me of uh cali playing among
us
with some people wait don't kill me
uh
and uh in that big collab where i was
not in
and she was i was watching the stream
she was pretty hello hello
hello
i'm not supposed to do that one yeah is
it because the lights are out
yeah she was pretty um she was doing the
same tasks over and over but even those
tests she didn't really
complete them and i was like i was like
sitting there
and trying really hard not to back seat
i was trying really hard click in the
middle yeah
did you guys watch that collab i want to
do um
i want to do one more among us collab
with the
with the fifth generation i want to do
that again
california imposter right
wait what what the hell
oh my god
free people holy [\h__\h]
oh wait no two because one one got
kicked out
where was it yeah i was i was going to
the shooting game
uh i don't know these are people
wait where was the where was the where
were the bodies anyway
black was in the middle of clums so i
guess they didn't see the other body
whichever it was wait how you can't even
see which one was killed and which one
got the seat right you should
you should be able to see that it's kind
of confusing
south report how how do you even get
that idea
oh my god oh i know it must have been
gura she's not even here but it must
have been gura
skip since double kill
what kind of reason is that
well okay be careful
[Music]
ah yes i forgot my own word again
did everyone who's watching the stream
right now also watch the announcement
stream
no one was addicted did you all watch
the announcement stream
i hope you did yeah of course you did
thank you i i i hyped you up very much
but it was worth it right
some people even said it was even more
than
like that it was worth even more hyping
up than i already did
yay i really wanted to make sure
everyone comes
that's why i hyped it up so many times i
wanted people to understand
wait where's the task out there i wanted
people to understand
that it is really important that
everyone comes
i didn't expect it to be that big ha ha
i'm not going to say what i'm thinking
but yeah it was very big
uh blue to blue yellow to yellow
did the door just close
but wait there's more don't get
your piece of [\h__\h]
[Music]
ten toes they killed me quite early this
time
they used to let me live quite a long
time in the previous games
uh which color was it i don't remember
who killed me oh
who killed me
i i have a small
memory space purple
paint baker it was you
i feel betrayed and you're
oh
cereal killer i don't have to
ah maybe the guy who just signals the
other imposter
oh that could be
oh then then he's still doing a good job
alone what is this
who dares to kill me
[Laughter]
you guys should have protected me you
did not protect me well enough
it's okay though i i'll take one for the
team because i'm a phoenix and i can
just revive it's okay
it's okay
[Music]
i'm not a very vengeful phoenix i'm i've
lived
millions of years stood me like
wait you are
in are you confessing in german and no
one else
um understands
wait what the heck why was why was why
is why was brown and j
he just confessed in german and no one
else understands
he said i'm sorry kiana
wait why where why was brown injected
who voted for brown
what is going on
he even i kind of confessed in german
now no
what the hell what a madman okay got to
help with the task
i'm gonna help i'm gonna help come on
we can do this
oh my god oh emergency meeting
what is what is what is happening did
you see something sus
what's wrong green what's wrong
what's up bro we're still powerful
oh yes smart
yes you did oh yes you did oh yes
yes believe in yourself have confidence
my friend have confidence believe in
what you're saying
yes
don't dump yourself don't doubt yourself
[Music]
you guys understand why i'm singing that
wasn't a group called uh
something with it wait you understand
why
because the group is called isn't it
isn't it called wait wait does this not
make sense
no yeah no doubt right so yeah
no doubt wait now what is going on are
they believing each other or
no don't skip
yeah i was singing uh no doubt and don't
speak
so something oh yeah please be careful
please be careful
[Music]
again why would you do that
just believe in yourself is this a is
this a task
what is that what is that what is that
map it's just a is that
is that just another i map
go up
let's go up there no damn
please don't lose i'm gonna do my best
i'm gonna help you
come on you guys uh i've been
i watched a lot of netflix and uh
one thing that always bothers me this is
very random i know this is very random
but one thing that always bothers me
wait there's still something up there
that i can do one thing that always
bothers me
oops sorry what is that ah one two three
four
five six oh god no green
oh no
it was blue [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
don't believe him anyway one thing that
always bothers me is
you know how how in these uh in this in
like sitcoms
mostly sitcoms but even in in serious
uh serious serious
uh it's like when people are in one room
and like the room is
fairly small but there's like one group
of people
on one side of the room and the other
group of people in the other side of the
room
and the like they would talk uh in a way
that
supposedly the other group wouldn't hear
them like
it they they this script-wise they're
not hearing them
but you would obviously hear them
especially because they always talk
so loud but they're in the same room i
just
this this is one of my pet peeves i hate
that
i hate that you know what i mean
when they're all in the same room and
then like their they don't hear each
other
like there's no way you don't hear each
what are they doing visual tasks are off
i don't numb
wait what happened no
are you guys stupid or what are you guys
stupid
oh no there's only three people left oh
we gotta help we gotta help we gotta
have
this is they're too stupid my crew is
too stupid
my crew is too steel
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten completely
guys you gotta be more serious about
this
ah
okay new room guys bye bye
okay
[Music]
do you like dangerous do you like
dangerous
w like water
m like mother said like
dude that like two f like f
there we go what's this hello welcome
welcome everyone are we complete not yet
we need
one more welcome welcome welcome
can i put all the song damn nice yeah
you gotta watch the announcement stream
if you missed it because there's much
more to that announcement it's not just
that i'm putting out a song there's much
more to it so please if you missed it i
had an announcement stream today it's
only 40 minutes or something so please
uh watch it
the censoring
hello um uh
rules okay i'm talking as if i don't
speak english
something something okay
oh yes
yes
close your streams
and we are not 10 out of 10 yet though
maybe i weighed a little bit more
or is the number wrong i wonder and it's
just act
it's actually 10 people
huh
ah come on give me ten
what is the what is the matter with the
bugs man
what's happening cold please
oh oh you guys is are these the only
people who manage to listen what i'm
saying
i don't believe it but here's here's a
oh wait ah
there you go there you go
d w m z f
it's full eh all right
all right then let's go there's only
five ew
no yeah i said
that for dude come on in
someone someone help i need somebody
help
no okay bye-bye let's start the gotta be
more clear
huh you gotta listen better don't put
this on me
i'm cruel again
[Music]
apparently i like being killed that's
why i'm in a relationship with kelly
i'll be maury
i'm coming for the kite swipe yeah why
are they always so fast these days
why is the crew at them the impostor is
so fast these
[Music]
i'll go up oh oh okay
i was too late eins
[Music]
sex stephen
very good very good
um i wanna uh to talk about something
with you guys regarding my stream
schedule
um
scheduling oh
um so i've been doing
with this stream i've had uh two
gorilla streams this is spontaneous this
wasn't on the schedule and there was
another one the mario kart one was also
not on the schedule
um but i have to uh prepare some
more stuff for the talk show and
something else that is secret where the
deadline is tomorrow
would you guys mind if i move the fire
emblem stream
possibly to the day after tomorrow
uh after the talk show
sometime after the talk show is that
okay because tomorrow i would have a
fire emblem stream but i need to work on
some things
but i'm gonna move it uh it will still
be this week i hope that's okay thank
you
thank you thank you so
much
thank you yeah i need to uh also talk to
marine senpai and check all the
questions with her
and maybe uh i need to prepare some
other things as well
i want like a a clapping sound i want to
play in
do you think it's weird if i have like a
clapping sound board or something like
that where i
if if mine is if i say something amazing
i'll turn on the clapping like
like a crowd clapping like yeah
maybe i'll just record myself clapping a
million times
wait skip skiada
okay
coughing my cheeks oh yeah maybe oh yeah
clapping audience
but in reality it's not hands clapping
it's actually
a kiada slapping her employees
chiara slapping her employees
compilation
oh my god
don't have a dad scared yet
okay that would be that would be uh
beautiful
but in the end it's actually just me
slapping myself so maybe not
we don't want we don't want uh kiara to
show up with a red cheek
on in the talk show
[Music]
let's go
hello let's pour some drinks
bamboo drinks yummy
go do something else but okay you're not
my mom but okay what are you doing
why is he just standing there is that a
task is he getting a body scan
damn no no no
don't follow me no no no no no nine
yo welcome why are you not doing
anything
soccer
purple my um oh i wanted to say amigo
but it's amiibo
my amiibo my amiibo
what what who ricky okay
uh rest in peace rest in peace
awesome i was
top right um it's not top run can you
call that top right
[Music]
ah yeah jaxa was a safe
i guess um
top right i am not no
no no you guys have no idea what you're
talking about
hallway next to the admin well i mean
who is not telling us where they are
pink
pink where were you
gotta be active in this one
interrogation
huh talk to us talk to us you carried
hello green and pink not answering
oh i'm at the columbus now what area
comes
what what is that anyway
i forgot where i was uh-huh sure
sure how can you you shouldn't at least
like
i also never know the name of where i am
but at least i put
uh a direction on scala
yeah very sus very susque
keep an eye on the green stay away from
green
people with no keyboard
why don't why does that make you say so
kiana but from our bottom right why did
i say something smart
did i did i say something smart what did
i say that was so smart
i will remember it and say it all over
again
why am i says you guys know that i'm not
sus
okay ah ah that was not the shootie
shooting game
big brain moment you got promoted
yesterday
yesterday you mean uh today for me
yesterday for you
you mean i got promoted for my song
announcement and my holo talk
announcement
well i knew that i always deserved it
i will [\h__\h] kill you yeah he he saw
that right he saw that come on unless
that was also the imposter okay
wait a second didn't
marshalls myself marcel's
um yeah blue saw that no blue kind of
saw that
wait he's self-reporting
blue come on say something blue unless
blue is also the
imposter blue voice there
blue ran by while
from came coming from the direction
where white was running away to
right and blue
didn't come back but uh white came back
but blue saw
oh wait did blues out my body wait did
blue not see my body
he just saw white
oh god damn it always blue is the second
imposter
i wonder
oh it's white and green you think so
it did blue not see my butt but blue
definitely ran by
wait the color the one one more color
that ran by where
there was one more person that ran by my
body was that not blue
it green that ran by my body
i'm so confused i don't see colors
[Laughter]
was it
it was a greenhou
it was a ghost eh
apparently my eyes are bad but actually
no i have quite good eyesight
doctors like to tell me they're always
like wow chiara your eyes are so
good wow
hey upload
i don't need glasses but
i feel like you know how recently when
when uh
uh whole life girls get new outfits
pretty much
every of the most recent outfits why did
i go here
pretty much every one of them got uh
glasses as an accessory
so i feel like hookah papa
might want to give me glasses as well
because it seems like a trend
but i don't know if i would look good
with class
what what
why emergency meeting
wait leaf was here lifu also uh
suspected white correctly
yeah yep yep it is it is pink
do you have any new evidence though why
do we have to vote why do we have to
vote now
what's what's happening why do we have
else we get doubled what do you mean
with double
why do we get doubled
uh because one more body dies and then
there's more imposters
i don't need glasses what the hell a
double kill ah
ah yeah please believe pink you got you
guys have to have confidence
with your suspect suspicions
come on come on
but who is the second i wonder who is
the second one i still don't really know
maybe blue blue or green
i think pink and red are definitely okay
cyan has been quiet no siren hasn't said
anything
oh that's kind of sucks
don't you think we should give every
member of whole of glasses
it would look cute for my for my fairy
tale reading
uh series right or maybe i'll ask my
papa to make glasses for me because
they would look they would suit quite i
mean i don't need reading class
glasses my eyes are superior
my eyes are obviously superior did they
vote on white
yes good job good job
good job i'll find you
poke poke
i'll help out
what i'll wait this one how do i do this
i don't have any tasks left
i'm done with my test yay i'm a good
girl
i'm a good ghost can i do something here
no well
but who is the who is the second one
what wait how many people are left well
these are yeah it's obviously
these three are fine right where's the
other one wasn't there a fourth one
oh god stay safe
okay it's green that one
they understand yep yeah yeah
it's obvious now okay we win
nice nice
yeah whatever still takes lot of it
yeah you shouldn't have closer doors and
free people
thank you for the red super chat wow
i'll tell my papa
in the name of you i will tell my papa
to
give me some glasses
wow a proposal
a confession that's a different kind of
confession
but i'll take it thank you
[Music]
thank you very much for this awesome and
that was a good game i would say
new room i'm making a new room everyone
japanese bro also very welcome to join
if you want to
let me tell you the code are you ready
guys
are you ready and you're ready
[Music]
um
i'm just repeating sorry only one only
one n one
n okay uh why
like york
be like boobies
t like tencho
and like november f like f
friends so fast why is f always the last
letter
welcome oh we already turned on the ten
perfect you guys are hella fast
damn speed um
what was okay well it's okay
she had a glass of sponge thank you
ah okay clocking in denture very well
very well
you better work your ass off oh there's
again one person with no name
okay
okay let's go
let's go let's go let's
i have only been uh crew the whole time
but i want to stay crew can i stay cool
please i don't i don't know how to be
impossible
yes uh well i hope it's not too boring
for you guys if i'm always cool i'm
actually happy about that
it stresses me out to be a
imposter stresses
perfect card swipe don't worry we just
love you
thank you i'm not not worried about that
do you guys have some um
did i really have to be your first kill
am i all alone
my my dude my egg friend
reported thank you i'm all alone
these idiots keep kicking me out but
okay that's good because then i have
some time
to talk to you guys
do you guys have any questions um
about i think they
i was reading after my announcement i
was reading a lot of
questions here and there online like
twitter reddit
and so on uh some i think some people
were a bit unclear about the voice pack
that i'm releasing
uh because i think for many of you i've
seen many people
who never heard of that before it really
proves that
many people are completely new to holo
life again because you guys don't know
what voice packs is
so let me explain you there's a
different kind of voice pack some people
thought i will just be saying like some
single words or something
like or a good night or whatever
or good morning for your alarms or
whatever no no no i think there's those
as well but what i'm doing is called a
situation voice uh
it's a bit of a longer one it's several
minutes
and it's um it's uh
i will not tell you what it is about but
it's a situation boy a voice and it's
about
uh i said i will not say what is it what
it is about
but it is uh kind of something between
the kfp employees so yeah
did they vote on skipping okay
uh it's not asmr some some girls also do
asmr for their voice packs
but it's not asmr why am i i only own
the only dead one goddammit
it's not asmr however uh i did
i did one small thing that's maybe a
little bit like asmr but uh
but it's not asmr in general it's just
me it's just me kind of like you know
uh doing doing my thing with you guys
talking to the person who's listening to
this
yeah um but it's um
these voice packs are i think um
aimed to the people who really want to
support
uh their uh girl you know
yeah and also there's the instrumental
and the thank you voice in them
leaves ah isn't it isn't it nice like
recently it's fall
at least uh in most
countries it's autumn i i really like
autumn but i like every
i guess i like um luna
yeah so many people dad oh my god i
really like autumn
it gets so cozy i like the colored
leaves
the orange leaves hmm
very very pretty where where where where
where were they like birds like where
what where where where
where one of us wants one of us
is that that's not the real munna right
is it you it cannot be
sorry i stole peko peko wait is that
mono
it's okay i have plans with her
oh
what
no no
no oh
oh we have plans for you too
wait what do you mean what the hell all
three of us together wait is that
hey wait you're not
muna right
what time is it in indonesia right now
is it a zing character hey that's not
it it's not it's not
yeah she'd probably say something in the
chat by now unless she really wants to
troll me
um anyway anyway
i will you guys know do you guys know
who i am
who i contacted today to ask for a
private date
lucia say bye i just saw i messaged her
out of nowhere
ah i just asked her who she has senpai
do you want to go to a cat cafe with me
sometime
soon and she's like yes let's go
and i'm like okay hell yeah this is how
you invite girls
on a date it's that easy it's that easy
oh oh that's quite a good time oh
they're only they're two hours behind
japan huh so she she should
she she could be uh awake
yeah because russia senpai likes cats
and i also like cats
you just have to you know have
confidence
okay who is that who killed me by the
way oh the pink one
who's the second one i wonder
wait a second the white one
am i imagining something or was he in
the previous game as well
what did white rip am i imagining
something
ah it's white
it's i don't think it's white it's pink
and black
no don't vote no don't vote right out
oh no it's black and pink
white no
no i don't think the organ is just my
my mind playing tricks on me okay
okay so anyway yeah lucia senpai likes
cats
i like cats i miss my cats
i think lucia also wants to meet cats
again
so it's perfect it's just perfect
what do we do here wait this is my first
time what is it
no
[Music]
okay well but can you guys um
one request one request to just say hi
no no no i'm making a new room one
request
could you um i don't want wanna
i don't want you guys to like give me
special treatment but in order to me
also being able as a streamer to play
the game more
would you maybe not kill me like right
away please
like not not so fast like i think it's a
bit too fast you you are allowed to kill
me but maybe not that early
is that would you please all cooperate
with that
like please okay
the the code
please come on i don't have so many
stories to keep on
talking to you as a ghost
oh thank you thank you thank you
jacqueline
i appreciate that but you you at least
you don't only get the voice back you
also get the karaoke
so you can you can serenade someone with
that
ok
japanese viewers also may join you're
welcome and
american server so
oh like orange you
like ufo
m like music
v like video
jay likes j and f like f
j f this is so [\h__\h]
so fast oh my god
oh that that child the blue child is
like
suffering thank you okay cali
egg wait is that egg from before logical
there's so many eggs here
okay what
[Music]
yes
now pure idol
song there are no swear words i wouldn't
put swear words into my song
it's actually um the japanese lyrics for
this one are
quite uh quite difficult words
um like really fancy really fancy
japanese words it's not the words used
in my song are not words that you would
use in normal japanese conversation
right one she doesn't get it
as foul a word for some kind of bird
i said it's supposed to be a pun oh oh
sorry i didn't get it
okay oh it means bird ah
okay i laugh laugh now kelly i know it's
not you you're fake calling
ah they're not using no more characters
oh okay anyway
new rule don't kill me
in the first two rounds at least
okay everyone ready
don't kill me yeah kill blue kill blue
kill him
skillful drop yeah whatever
okay me on stream
mhm
okay are you guys ready they're not
saying they're ready
talk to me conversation is important
communication is important
answers or i fire you
i miss your voice already
stop learning with your
boss
a comment
you know
[Music]
yes i have a wife already undercover
taco
let's go please oh yeah don't kill me
uh-huh so much for not killing me okay
i hope they all have this dream mutant
wait i don't know what to do my other
imposter better be
better be caring wait oh oh oh i was
like why can't i do the task
i was like why can't i do it hey it's
you and me
bro i don't know how to do it can we do
double kill should we drop a clue
is that too weird is that too dangerous
okay let's go let's go wait a second
what if we kill him
okay never mind too indecisive
[\h__\h] egg should we really be following
each other like that
and maybe we should um oh
god suspicious me i got black
black is definitely suspicious of us now
do something you gotta carry this game
now tamago
why she's just following me when we can
do a nice scale together okay
how about you sabotage
uh oh i can't okay
could you please at least sabotage
when did you do that huh
we were all together what the heck
let's see how logical the logical egg
can be
you didn't even notice but there was a
body there
what where is the body what
outside security where is security
how did he did do that while following
me the whole time
she's an assassin
here because the tory is safe to say so
the kill
true thank thanks
life
my wife is protecting me this is real
love it must be the real cali because
she's protecting me
and also cali is the only one who is
allowed to call me kusotori
so it must be here no one else would
ever dare to call me
kusotori i'm sure of that
who thanks elijah to say what for me i
don't want mental
what he doesn't even know which color he
is
sus sas
wait like blue what says
oh man i like this game it's a funny
game
oh yellow voted for yellow interesting
interesting choice let's see if i can
kill someone this round i will try
without messing up i hopefully don't
mess up but with egg following me the
whole time
it's like um
it's kind of dangerous
now like if i i feel like eventually
that would uh
mess something up if i die first and
then it's only egg
left and egg was always with me
i don't know i feel like they would
suspect something
can we kill him no probably not everyone
is always in this room
there we go i did something oh wait
is he sure oh totally doing this one
like we should actually do it probably
right because otherwise uh five
oh okay never mind let's go
okay did you close the door on me aren't
we supposed to work together
let's kill someone is someone here no i
need to kill someone
oh
yes please
wait why is flynn saying to vote him out
oh he was just checking if someone died
oh smart
brain must be a bird brain
damn i didn't i wouldn't think of
something like that i wouldn't
just call an emergency meeting to
egg that's it's true right now
yeah egg is safe kind of says
no that's it yes yes
yes i don't know how you would think
that but i indeed did not kill anyone
and i have been a good girl a very good
girl
yeah i would never know um that i should
call an emergency meeting in certain
situations yeah i probably saved
[Music]
must be killing them
that doesn't make sense um
uh who who can we
um and shouldering who can we
answer it i can't think of the english
word
okay i got them yeah that's that's true
who can we frame yeah who can we blame
or frame
nice to meet you thank you
hi wait this is good right i was gonna
help to tell them to accuse someone but
actually it's good for me to not accuse
someone so yeah that's actually
good i was hoping i would accuse someone
but that's not how wait but actually how
the hell does x do this while he's
always following me i didn't see him
kill anyone
what yay party
party
oh let's go somewhere egg let's go
[Music]
she's an assassin for real
i don't know how to vent i don't know
how to end i don't know i don't know how
to make
it
[Laughter]
uh electrical
they were shocking oh shocking are you
fun
i just saw someone
no okay no no no no no very electrical
top
of electrical
la la la la i am innocent
i am innocent
what what
no
i don't know
hey i feel so hot i'm sweating
have like no idea
oh god thank god
oh thank god i got away with that i got
away with it oh my god
oh my god oh my god i got away with it
okay i killed that one right at least i
killed someone yay
okay okay
okay i can't do anything anyway oops oh
is there someone there no okay
wait i i think though i should i
i was trying to click on the vent
thinking that makes me vent but i have
to
click something else excuse me what is
it
that's not a task oh god oh god um
but no one saw that right what do you
mean i'm finding kiara what
keeps on following me
yeah let's change the topic to something
like that so they don't talk about who
it could be
i know i'm scenario with my students
yeah that doesn't sound like cali
that does
not quite sound like something she
would say publicly
says
pink sass
she is indeed the pasta i
actually like for real though
yep i think i guess i i guess i got a
vote for kelly
voting for cali i think
oh wait this was emergency we didn't
even find the body
oh yeah it why was there an emergency
called anyway
what was the reason for that oh yeah
that's not mode
i guess
did someone vote for kelly okay cali
voted for kelly
white voted on cyan why
hey there did an emergency to find me
what what what a simp
oh my god why does he always close the
door egg open the door
lab is an open door
[Music]
hello i'm here for the swipey swipe
this is okay i'm done with the swappy
swipe
la la i'm just
when did that happen
i did not kill that bunny
yeah well he's a [\h__\h] simp
what does how does that give him away
he's a symph after all
he saw him killing
wait who reported oh pimple did
wasn't purple just i know
oh oh green got killed while we were
buffed
oh oh
oh
[\h__\h] i gotta help him but i don't feel
good lying i don't want to lie
i think i can mind being awesome
but he never killed me
so i don't know i don't
want him to leave
i'm protecting you here i'm protecting
you
[Music]
la
what song is that anyway task queen no
no
no okay i need a kill to go
i don't care i'm just gonna kill the
next person i see but i don't see anyone
hello i couldn't kill those
how could i
[Music]
oh that's a smurf song
come on kiara how many people are left
is no one here alone are they staying
together am i the only one who's walking
around alone
oh god oh god
[Music]
no they're doing tasquen no no
hello hello everyone how you doing
hello
who doesn't have their task finished
asking the real questions
me too it's me i was the rip oh yeah
well maybe really maybe it really was
kelly
could be a ghost eh why
ah a ghost who has not the task finished
all right
could be um
[Music]
wait could it really be a ghost
could it really be i guess it could
really mean
well oh
oh my that's this part
yes okay sounds good
[Music]
what a good idea yeah let's just uh
let's just party you know
um um everyone fall out
wait if we're all together isn't it
possible that they just don't see
who is killing do you don't see that so
clearly
right if everyone's together like you
know in a
in a bunch yeah right stack
it's party time come on kelly vote
yeah that's german i'm not gonna
translate that german
i'm not gonna translate that
turn up the light okay okay i don't know
how to do that
parting funny what what is that
uh is that electrical
[Music]
thank you what about the party though
what about what about the party
no
shut up that wasn't me it was not me
it was not me
[Music]
that looks rude okay i'm sorry i i i
hope you're watching i'm sorry
[Music]
you can use any to vent oh thank you
oh okay okay okay
japan only game i don't think many
people will follow
that rule okay okay the code the code
hey like apple meanwhile let me drink
something why am i feeling so hot it's
like my
why is this room so hot
a like apple right that was the first
letter
a second letter
um
cute like cupid oh no that's
wrong that's written with a c
cute anyway kill yeah
um s like
snake
w like w
we like victory f like f
g v gamer welcome
is it your first time if it's your
second time if you played with me before
you gotta leave you know that right
welcome everyone welcome to another 10.
yeah do they always end with f because
up until now
it always ended with f
it always ended with f is such a cell
always f
shut up no one says kick that ricky or
so anymore
don't say that anymore because i'm
afraid
oh well thank you okay everyone
mute the stream don't
kill me before
uh third round
and be nice to me
thanks i can't count
game of three well
that's just the way it is if you play a
game with potential life is just not
fair this is how it is you you should be
used to it by now
let's go
it's so hot why is it so goddamn hot
[Music]
i'm so relieved when i play crew thank
god
thank god
okay i'm gonna be a good girl and do my
tasks
by the way everyone i i wanted to clear
up one more thing
the biology what is that what is that
oh it's a task that i don't have i guess
i do
i never had that before i think
ah one more thing
don't kill me one more thing uh
the because uh this one has already been
teased anyway so i'm just gonna say it
but
people think people think that me and
kelly are doing an
uh a song together they think i'm doing
sorry they think i'm doing an original
song no
we're not doing an original song okay
that's all i'm gonna say
hello blue is dead
yeah i said cover well there's not much
other choice but yeah it's a cover
i i am it's gonna be on my channel
because i asked kelly
if she wants to do it together and i'm
planning everything so
it's on my channel but i'm still not
sure when i will release it
because i don't want to release it too
close to my original song
you know magnet
i don't think we have the rights to
magnet because um i saw that uh for
example marine senpai
and russia senpai sang magnet before
as a collab but i think it got deleted
because probably they got like copyright
issues or something i think that was
before
uh cover started to ask everything and
everyone for
uh permission so i think
probably if their cover got deleted
because i did i only saw a re-upload
if their color is deleted then it's
probably not allowed but i know it would
be really it would be a classic it would
be such a classic
of like two girls singing magnet
together it's just absolutely
you know meant to be
[Music]
what do you mean by instrumental well
it's a it's the it's my song
but without my singing
so for example you could use it to um
make a song cover if you want but also
i just think the instrumental sounds
really good because
there's a lot of egotis in my song
i'm busy
[Music]
okay let's go where is it
i'm coming why is that other person not
coming priorities
oh it's over okay hello
hmm
oh no the voice pack
is it does not have the actual song in
it but it does have
uh a voice a situation voice a thank you
voice
and instrumental but there will be uh
details on that sometime soon
it's not me that's all i can say
what does someone is everyone skipping
already
are we scared
dark green bad person dark green sauce
we say we murdered well how if you're
not the imposter
you saw him kill oh okay
i trust i will actually trust that
because uh wasn't uh black running
together with me
and yeah i think black is safe
bye-bye hopefully that was really
everyone even he himself is for him okay
bye bye
she manages to talk more than text
excuse me
i'm stealing i'm still i'm still doing a
lot of tasks okay
more than cali did when she played this
game
[Music]
i dissed kelly
new
phoenix energy is all back now
hello everyone
did you guys fix the lights or something
oh i have that one again i usually never
have that one
the door closed on me hello
hello hello hello hello
this seems familiar yeah oh yeah do i
have to do that one
kiara get out eh who do you guys think
though the second imposter is
could it be italy
so funny i'm so funny i'm so funny
black you think it's black
why
double kill really oh you were scared
oh oh it's okay i'll hug you
no need to be scared it's so okay it's
okay don't be scared
no need to be scared i'm here for you
as long as i am here i will protect
my employees
with my life
until i die and rise again
and then repeat
are we good
employees that's not a thing i love all
my employees very much
we win this game you think so wait that
sounds like something uh
it kind of sucks isn't red kind of quiet
i'm not done by the way
please follow me i don't want to get
killed
thank you thank you thank you
see i'm obviously not suss now right
because i'm asking them to follow me now
that's something that's something an
imposter would never say
i'm gonna remember that line for later
okay by the way i think the game
uh either this game or the game after
that
will be the last one because i want to
read the super chats from the
announcement stream you guys were all so
sweet and sent so many super chats
i gotta read them oh well at least
they're staying with me
keep an eye on who is not with us
okay next one come on come on with me
come come come oh yeah and after this
stream i will finally make the community
post
i waited a little bit with that because
uh
i didn't want to uh i didn't want to
i didn't want the the announcement post
to
suddenly um be overshadowed you know
thanks for following me why is nobody
else following
okay damn i have still so many tasks to
do
wait is it not here
[Music]
it's not here ah
go go is that oxen oh
red is dead red red
oh god who is it who is it who is it
chad what do you think
like did we even like green was one of
them right
who is the second one
purple or pink
how can it be me when red has vouched
for me the whole time
the whole time did you really know
purple or pink oh wait
it would be funny if it was pink
[Music]
what do you guys think pink
if the game is still on go for pink
why why could we win if we just skip
i'm not sure hey what do i do
are they skipping are they skipping
oh what do i do complete the test it's
just one task okay
i guess okay okay
oh purple did vote for pink interesting
so is it all on me now you better
protect me so that i don't die
well i guess as a ghost i could still
complete it and then we would win
okay uh electrical let's go friends am i
the only one
who has tasks left over it's two tasks
though
follow me wait if you guys are awful who
is not following me right now
oh my this is
hi rhythm game here we go ah
wait it's so obviously the person who is
not following me right now wait no
now it's everyone it must be it must be
the game gamer you little [\h__\h]
that's this is because i told him
probably
do not super chat so much i told a bunch
of my
people to not super chat so much anymore
is this the revenge
is this a revenge
is that wait did i not it was pink
did brown see that well pink is the only
one who stayed behind
why why would you kill me
come on vote v gamer come on don't make
up excuses now
it's over it's over
it is over give up
thanks
not for long
wait black has been killing his call out
what i i thought he meant that uh
he's passion he's killing people kind of
alive in myself
[\h__\h] vote
vote
[Music]
for
but yeah black was uh
being presenting and whining from the
symphony
black collected uh quite well he had
black had much confidence
this is how you have to live your life
this is the lesson for your life
everyone
[Laughter]
bye bye okay this means we won right
catchy
[Music]
thank you thank you okay
one last game saigon
what
thanks again last game
let's go you guys ready for
last round with the phoenix kiara
i shall tell you the code i'm sorry
we're only playing on this map i hope
that's not boring
because i don't know the other maps very
well
okay it's a g like
gold
set like zebra
w like watson
you like universe
d like dinosaur f like f
welcome that's so good yummy cannot eat
you
[Music]
it's a austrian german food
awesome amazing
did one more person join even though
we're morty
should i call kylie kusama it actually
sounds like
perfect well i would never call her dad
because she's my wife
[Music]
what
yes okay let's add a little kid
if he keeps me alive okay okay okay
don't kill me too soon
close stream let's go
okay last round everyone
ready okay
let's go or mute stream don't call
stream give them give me those views
you'd stream don't close
[Music]
did we got one japanese beer
into the game no oh
okay
[Music]
let's see what i get i feel like it's
going to be imposter no okay yes
that's a much less stress and pressure
on me so i'm fine with that
i wonder who it is please date me
what a simp card swipe everyone always
always goes to this one first it feels
like
i always did it so well and now it
didn't work
where's my next task let's see probably
something here i'm not even checking the
map right now
i don't have time for that let's do a
task queen everyone shall we wait a
second
wait a second wait a second my nose
feels itchy why does it feel so easy
yeah it was definitely not me
anyone's doing tasks in
electrical shut up cousin morning
i don't like bottom left i am top right
i know
he had the courage to ask me to date him
via
his name and yet he has died
what do we learn from that everyone
you first have to get to know the girl
i mean i guess you you all know me
better than
i know you so that's that
bottom left engine um
dark green was an o2 aha
don't try to date idols simple life is
hard
sounds about right okay
[Music]
foreign you know in japanese there's
this word for now
um it's called tori eisel
and it has the word bird in it
well that's a long task holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
i never know where to go that's
obviously very subs but yeah
okay
let's do this thing
color by color
[Music]
torii
why am i going here oh shields am i
suspicious to you sorry i know that kind
of looks suspicious but i'm going here
what yang
good
[Music]
they had so much time to kill so many
people so it actually surprised me
there's only two now
um where is this uh not sure
where i am
uh oh
i still don't really know the names of
the places
someone was following me but i
have short time memory
so i don't know who was following me
who's green
eh
it was you know yeah okay dark green
dark green was following me
yep
was he following me or was he running
away from the body
10 joystick yes very safe
of course i am don't question
my integrity see i'm using smart words
i'm
smart verb using my vocabulary that i
usually forget all about when i
stream
[Music]
we still don't know i have no idea i
don't have any idea but it's getting a
bit dangerous i think it's brown
[Music]
maybe he did he was alone with me and
didn't kill me but that was maybe just
because of my rule that they should not
kill me until the third round so
now it's dangerous okay let's see
let's go 202 oh god don't follow me
don't vote on me
this this okay okay everything's cool no
no
don't kill me don't kill me don't get me
oh okay not killing me
don't kill me a lot of suspicious people
are also
are all together here let's do this one
download download
that kiara voice back gotta download it
did any of you ever uh get like a voice
pack from a whole life
talent before
did anyone ever do that
or will it be your first time chiara
voice back
nope never i'll get yours thank you
thank you for the support
it is a cute cute little voice pack
okay science seems safe
not sure yet about labor cases just
because he left me alone in the first
round
doesn't mean anything oh
wait a second
hmm kind of sauce i would say
i have to do one here
uh eight zero five three four
there we go fixed
why is my nose so eating
what is it
what is it are you scared did anyone die
no okay oh
[Music]
seems fine let's go
never tried voicepack before yeah i know
many of you
probably are also new to this whole
thing so it's gonna be
a new experience that we will share
together
pink seemed to be waiting for someone to
separate from the group interesting
interesting very interesting
interesting
thank you for the super chat no problem
don't worry about it
which is what i say uh publicly but once
once
uh this stream is over you know what's
going to happen
don't think you're safe just yet
don't think you're safe after killing
your
boss it is a sin
it can never be forgiven
one does not simply kill takanasi kiara
right oh
i'm a um scared alone oh i have only one
task left
oh follow me everyone follow me
follow me follow me
i only have one task is that my final
task
hey tasks done yay okay let's stay in
the main room
and wait oh
one more on the lights or something
yeah bye pink nowhere to be found
what do i see what do i see i was able
to report something
did you guys say something
eh what no wait no wait
okay listen i just saw the
uh report button pop up but
uh i didn't see a body
yet so i was uh
not sure
if i can push it
does that make sense
you guys know it's not me
and but but
is it because you just pressed to kill
thanks us it is not me
it looks like no no what the heck i
didn't see
anyone eh
pink sauce
you're not gonna vote me out guys are
you
it really isn't me though
do they think it's me
it's not me
[Music]
wait am i orange yeah idiots
that's what oh
i understand i understand it's youtube
everything makes sense though
they were both ganging up on me
i thought kusamuri was safe though
but who i wanted to i didn't see who
voted for me i wanted to see who voted
for me
besides those two who else fell for that
stupid trap
eh what the hell they totally framed me
how dare they
how dare you frame me
[Music]
well you're fired that's that
thank you
idiots idiots
oh that's not getting sensitive
[Music]
punishment is watching my super chat
stream
until the end actually that's a blessing
never mind okay everyone thanks for
playing today
thanks for joining me on a manga stream
it has been a while
um it was fun i had so much fun this was
great
thank you everyone yes you should i
never
when i'm the imposter i'm quite bad at
lying but
when when i'm actually i'm also i'm also
bad at defending myself whenever
i'm not imposter hype
hypo bye bye
i'm gonna do the super chats now so if
you want you can stay along
people people super chat readings
on yelp have been reviewed as very much
fun and they say they are the best part
of my stream so you might as well
say and watch it right right right
bye bye okay i gotta
update the chat there i forgot that
that's right
yeah yep reviews about my super chat
readings they say it's so
super positive
[Music]
for
the super chat rating text
and some advertisements at the top maybe
a little bit smaller
okay okay
[Music]
it's 2 am now i did have quite
quite a long nap before the stream so
i should be fine though even though i
woke up early but i brought i had a long
long long nap so i will be fine
[Music]
amelia just messaged me for something uh
about the video
that she's working on right now
you had fun thank you
thank you ah
gosh why am i feeling so hot
why do i feel so hot the whole day
actually i even turned
off my air conditioning which was set on
heating because it's getting a little
a little bit cold
okay so i'm reading the announcement
stream to protect right but before that
i think everything that was before that
i already read so
only announcement and a manga stream i
suppose
do you guys have a question do you guys
feel like my english pronunciation is
bad because sometimes
i mean i understand myself but sometimes
when i watch like my own stream or clips
or something
to review something sometimes i feel
like
you guys probably don't hear me
as well as i would like to hear me
is it okay because i think sometimes i
do
slur my words a little bit
no
no you don't think so
okay
but if i tell you stories is it easy for
you guys to follow my stories i try to
um like work with some
extreme intonation by making my
sentences
sound not so monotone
scala the super chat i did not see me
oh you don't don't you lose like a
concentration while listening to me and
stop listening to my stories
is it easy to follow really okay do you
notice that i tried to speak
not monotone but uh what's it what's the
opposite of monotone
do you notice that
asking you like for so many reviews
polly tone multi-tone
okay it's way too hot in here
okay
i'm gonna take a shower after this off
and sweating
[Music]
okay oh
i may have a good idea for the for the
intro
they okay the talk show is so soon so
there's so many things to do you know
sorry about that i'll i'll start reading
the super jets
should i make some tea
chat
[Music]
i don't have a academy i don't have a
cup up here right now so okay whatever
i'll have to live with my cough drops
okay we're starting to read the super
chat now
[Music]
let's go everyone
this is gonna be wholesome i already
feel it i feel it
thanks for the super chats everyone
thank you let's go
get my 311 thank you for the red super
chat
thank you my official guest oh here come
the guesses
my official guess is that you're
announcing your excitement over the
failure
over the fact that you bought a snickers
bar from a vending machine but an extra
one drop
now you have two snickers bars for the
price of one and you are very excited
about this journal of events am i close
people really underestimated what the
announcement could be about
it was not about that but thank you for
the red super chat
thank you thank you for your support and
also thanks for playing
fun to have you and the team thank you
[Music]
jonathan koslovsky thank you thank you
for the red super chat
[Music]
thank you i thought i oh yeah this i
read this also
i was liking in the pre-chat so i also
read this one it was very interesting
listen to me this is beautiful the super
chat
says i thought i understood this called
tundra is this some kind of meme then i
stumbled along a pillar
that defied my sense of reason these
flames without form confused me
the radiant heat burn it's scary but
in a way it's nice softly the words
abate my lips thank you for proving me
wrong what is that
is it self worth is it is that some kind
of
like the movie scene or something or is
that his own
oh basement's too loud goddammit thanks
for telling me
ah there we go very poetic
a proposal
how poetic indeed i wonder if that is
some reference to something but you guys
don't seem to recognize it
thank you thank you so much for your
support what a beautiful plan if you
worked at yourself that was absolutely
beautiful
interesting but uh i don't understand
what it's about
thank you very much
[Music]
on the chest match you never gave it up
and you tried to not let us down oh
thank you
oh do you you heard that you didn't run
around and desert again oh
i thought you were actually
complimenting me
even losing the queen didn't make you
cry and you never said goodbye to your
king
very smart rick roll i must say thank
you
thank you take it monkey again
we're no strangers to tests
you know they're rules and so do i
a full checkmate is what i'm looking for
you wouldn't get this from any other
chat
thank you soon
has come up so i won't be able to catch
the announcement live looking forward to
catching your future streams though best
of luck i'm so excited to see you in the
archive did you see it until now
how did the exam go didn't you have an
exam
wow see i am such a good
potential i remember i remember your
real life stuff
how did your exam go
thank you and airborne cats thank you
hey girl grabs on the winning chest oh i
guess i did win one time huh
i told myself i'd send twenty dollars a
return if you'd win at least one game
thank you
what's a great match to watch hope this
becomes a normal thing as for today's
announcement i have trained can't wait
yay thank you i'm glad you enjoyed the
test match as
obviously everyone else also did
thank you so much
andre
the hype is real men but don't forget to
hold the energy until it is time are we
not gentlemen are we not kiana's
greatest let's wait for kiana oh you're
so sweet
you're so sweet thank you thank you
[Music]
m
i ran a million ideas from my mind about
what the announcement is going to be i
don't know what i'm mostly hoping for
but
but i'm so bloody hyped up
i was just going to ask if you are
british because you said bloody and then
i look at the currency and
it's actually british pounds
bloody thank you so much my bloody
friend
look thank you david
who wants to be this is just what who
wants to bet this is just an
announcement for the real announcement
and that she's
just been announcing the announcement
for the announcement yep pretty much
no i have definitely delivered right
i would say so
i confused amit
[Music]
um
sorry gotta clear something up with with
amelia
watson
sorry something else many things going
on
behind the scenes
[Music]
many things are going on behind the
scenes
okay okay
oh let's make myself bigger by the way i
feel too small
there you go say hi to ahmed
no how about you say hi to amit
oh i'm i'm in right back
ah okay okay okay
okay let's continue sorry about that
guys
because i said you say hi tom
[Music]
another speech everyone listen
ladies and gentlemen of the kfp it is a
destined day
a faded day a day of the big
announcement arrives now
we shall show our undying love and
support to kiara
onward to 500k glory to the kfb people
lucky
i love these peaches i love them
[Music]
thank you again general pickering
and air vancouver
thank you the
[Music]
thank you
and i can't send you flowers but i sent
this for you to get somewhere ah
yeah that was so sweet i did see that in
the pre-chat as well
try to get something that brightens up
the room as much as you brighten up all
our lives actually i was really thinking
of buying some flowers uh
i have to figure out where the closest
flower store is around
my area i do like flowers but
every time i get flowers they die so
early
i can never really keep them alive that
long unfortunately
can you do another among us with viewers
during the thanksgiving break
what do you mean thanksgiving break
what do you mean with that
what what is a thanksgiving break is
that the weekend that comes afterwards
or
next week a weekend
oh a school break oh
the whole week is off
the whole week americans get the whole
week off for thanksgiving
eh so that means all the american
students will have so much i know
oh you don't yes yes you do not everyone
whoa
[Music]
interesting
again thank you so much thank you for
the flowers i really like flowers
i'm gonna get some thank you thank you
[Music]
stop spamming who is spamming who are
you who are you guys talking about
uh maybe it's because i have the top
channel and i don't see who you guys are
talking about
ah i'm not gonna be too cheesy but i
would like to say thank you for
everything you have done for us you have
been
my pillar to get through tough times
that are happening to me at least right
now viva
thank you that was not a super chat but
i caught that
i like long messages so thank you too
i'm glad i can like have a positive
impact on someone i'm happy about that
thank you
[Music]
this is by your host for your future
500k the talk show the announcement
and everything this is special so thank
you for existing and thanks for being
here since the beginning
be confident we're all here we're all
proud and love you for the person you
are
thank you that's so sweet
thank you so much tiara what's your
favorite game
the tales of game series
thank you um yeah i uh
i'm really um sometimes i feel like uh
being myself
so much is maybe uh
it did um cause some problems so
because i was just too emotional and
some people did not like
me being emotional and even claimed that
i
like you know faked my emotions or
whatever but i'm just an emotional
person and i do realize that
i was quite emotional in the beginning
there was just so much
there was so much stress and pressure in
the beginning there were so many people
watching and
i had to fix so many things on my own
um it was it was kind of hard to
figure out everything uh and people kept
on
also like criticizing the fact that
everything is going wrong and the fact
that i'm
not reacting well to it but you know if
you have so much stress and so much
pressure
and so much people expecting everything
to be perfect
it's just hard sometimes but um now
recently everything seems
somewhat fine i mean there have been
some issues
with my pc as well when it comes to
certain games that are
a bit tough on the pc but
i did buy a new pc which should come
probably maybe next week so then we can
also
then we can also get that thing solved
and then there should never ever be
problems ever again
i have to say it is um
the phoenix's era has come to us
i think we all have seen if you look up
here
the phoenix era has started it's here my
friends
holotalk and my first original song
what else could you ask for it's my time
to shine
i'm a proud phoenix i'm proud of myself
for doing all these things
i've been uh i've been really preparing
a lot of things behind the scenes people
some people think that youtubers
that all they do is just the streams
like for example two hours or
three hours or whatever per day i mean
that can be true partially
depending on the person but it's not
it's not just that
like we prepare things in the background
we have to
not only these things that i just showed
you not only things for myself but
sometimes there's other things that are
like
general for whole life some things and
there's something that i have a deadline
on tomorrow
which is also something i do behind the
scenes so it's really not just that so
some people don't quite um understand
that there is more than just the
streaming time yeah
this is correct it is a i mean if you
want to take it easy
then it can also be a job where you
don't invest so much time but i
i am investing quite some time into it
at this point yeah sometimes i do six to
seven hours
uh streaming time quite often actually
but that does not mean that that is the
only thing i do each day
but it is fun it feels like even though
i
prepare many things
and work quite a lot it does feel like a
lot of fun
it does not necessarily feel like a real
job
at the moment to me it's just something
i'm very very passionate about
something i just really enjoy doing and
that is really a blessing i'm really
really really lucky to have such an
amazing job right now mm-hmm
[Music]
i was really hyped for this announcement
whether it's releasing your new song
hosting your first talk show or
potential merchandise we are all very
happy for you so high for you
thank you well there was no many people
thought it was going to be merchandise
but
i think like physical merchandise takes
quite some time
to prepare but i guess a voice pack is
kind of something like
like a digital merchandise in some way
so
is there a secret to be positive
honestly i have to say i'm generally a
very negative person
so
[Music]
the only reason why i can be positive
right now is because i'm enjoying what
i'm doing
yeah generally i'm very negative very
negative
[Music]
so i hope you can find a way to be more
positive about things you know
pessimistic yeah i guess i guess you
could say that
elephant elfian thank
[Music]
i know it's like a really simple name
right it's one it's like pretty much the
first thing that came up
to my mind when i thought of names for a
talk show
it's such an easy name i really didn't
put much thinking
thinking into it but i think it just
works fine uh
it's simple it was not taken so i was
like okay why not it just makes sense
it just makes sense right there was a
one more name that i was thinking about
but i think that was taken
what was it something with holo but it
was taken by something else
i think if i remember correctly yeah
it's it's very simple but
i think it's easy to remember as well
why does that ring a bell i don't think
that that was the thing that i was
thinking about but it's rings of bell
for some reason
why would i think of that
how often will there be an episode um
every two to three weeks
um although i am quite busy in december
as well so i think the the next whole
talk
will not be two weeks later but three
weeks later
which means oh when would that when
would that be
11th
i know wait 12
no wait what is with this cow ending
very confusing a 12 barley that would
probably be a 12 for me
i have to think about it because i
already planned quite a lot
of collabs for december i have like so
many collabs set up already for december
it's a bit crazy many collabs that
the other side asked me to collab
god for your personal yours sure why not
go ahead
am i now my nose is so itchy
also thanks for the membership sketchy
sammy
[Music]
the other one had a different writing
interesting
mouse familiar ducation theft
jacksworthy
william lisa thank you thank you
thank you thank you
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
i like that show worth watching yeah for
me it's not late night and for my guests
it's also not late night it's actually
gonna be like what 11 or 12 or something
like that
yeah but probably better because um i
think um
uh the the japanese talents are usually
busy in the evening time with their own
streams anyway so
probably a good time for everyone
involved
and i'm gonna try to always have the
talk show on the same
day and same time so it's probably gonna
stay
a friday night for you guys and a
saturday morning
for me quite for a while
engineer gaming duncan why is my nose
toy to do i have an allergy or something
i don't know about
make sure mine doesn't sleep in oh yeah
that's dangerous indeed
please ah
i should probably not never invite shion
senpai
to my talk show because i heard she
oversleeps
i'm so excited for this talk show yay me
too
although i'm getting a little bit
nervous now i'm feeling quite
uh the expectations uh i'm getting a
bit nervous i hope i can
do it well it should be fine if i just
do it
uh my way it should be fine
i hope four hours
by steven and marin eh martin as well
marlin has such a record of oversleeping
that much
oh dear oh no
i will remind her
i will remind her to not oversleep
[Music]
now
thank you jesus and thank you for your
support i hope
you will make it to the stream and watch
it live
[Music]
if the talk show starts late
don't automatically think it's my fault
it might be someone else's fault
the motivation to seriously study
japanese your multilingual
prowess was really inspiring so i put my
money down and got lessons oh
thank you so much keras and you're the
best oh thank you good luck with that
i hope you can remember it
well i hope i hope those lessons will
help you
try your best to if you only have like
um
like lessons once or twice per week you
should still try to
practice every day i know it's hard to
sometimes find
the motivation to do it every day but if
you don't do it every day
you're not gonna make much progress
marry abby
[Music]
subtitles for archive talk shows too the
taxes are gonna be one hour
um i don't have the time to do that
it uh would have like if a staff member
will would do it for me then it's
it might be a thing but it probably will
also take time and
uh but one hour is quite long
like uh i know there is hotels for asa
coco
but you guys have no idea how long
subtitling takes and i don't have the
time for it i'm sorry but
this is this is why like some people
when they heard that i'm live
translating my talk show they were like
no please do subtitles um
no i don't have time for that
and i think it's more fun if you
actually understand it
live and not afterwards because i also
think that some
people um they watch the stream live
and even if they know that later on
there's going to be subtitles i think
many people just don't come back to the
video
and watch it again so i i want to give
them the opportunity to understand it
live at the spot
yeah and i'm gonna try to be as detailed
as possible anyway and also
like for example the questions i'm gonna
already prepared
like a graphic of the questions in
english so
uh there will not be so much lost time
so on the screen i will show the
question in english
i will ask her the question in japanese
but it will be in text
on the screen in english and then her
answer she will answer in japanese and
then i will
repeat what she said in english and i
think someone again
was like oh is that not going to ruin
the flow gave me some flashbacks but no
it's not
this is a not like a normal collab it's
like a very structured
a very structured collapse with decided
questions
the flow is literally like planned out
so there's i don't think there's gonna
be an issue
just believe in me also
that person who said that definitely did
not watch the among us collab
where i i was in with the fifth
generation
did i ruin the flow i don't think so
just believe in me
believe in me trust me
hmm i actually i didn't even i didn't
ruin the flow i actually
people say i i gave it more like a
structure
i i was i took like the guide
the leading role so believe in me
i believe in myself so you should always
also believe me
yeah i'm not being i'm not being like
uh how do you say i'm that did not
uh affect me in any way but it's just
like
believe in me have have confidence
in me kfc
[Music]
0x4e454b4f
pancasion spicy pork bulgogi duncan
[Music]
this talk show is a genius idea that
fits you perfectly but what happens when
you run out of polo members interview
i don't think that's going to happen um
because
if i do it every two to three weeks
and there's uh how many members now
i don't know enough but
there's also gonna be new members right
so i don't think it's gonna happen
and even if it happens i can just
re-invite
someone right so if for example
one year let's let's say i ran out of
guests to invite
one year later i can just invite marine
again and start all over
she probably has some new stories to
tell by then
will whole size be invited uh yeah i do
see it as a possibility but for me
definitely the
the girls have a priority just because i
personally
uh really like the
but yeah we can also invite indonesia
talents eventually
if we want you know but for the thing is
like for the indonesian talents they
speak english
and this whole holotalk show is about me
translating
what they say what you would normally
not understand
i would translate that to english but
with indonesian talents they already can
speak english so
and we can we can totally do it uh and
still have a talk show and i will still
interview them
but it's uh it's not exactly the concept
of the show
make them talk in indonesian well i
cannot translate indonesia
but yeah it's definitely definitely an
option
[Music]
but eof could come to my show and
instead of speaking english
she could just speak japanese and i'll
translate her japanese to english even
though she already speaks
english fluent what a good idea
invitiago oh one day maybe if he
if he would um accept my offer
my invitation i don't know
um the
make sure to ask maddie about your
physical ability
phenomena and aliens i found your
thoughts
very interesting you want me to ask her
about aliens did you talk about that
before
[Music]
uh
that's that's a good idea
widget dog thank you sure thank you for
the red super chat
thank you thank you so so much thank you
did you know that
pigs won the first outfit wars what are
you what
what pigs with
a number one as the eye outfit wars what
is this about
did i did i miss some joke
who is that who is
pigs you sent me a red superjet and i
don't understand
i really hope to see hollow stars in the
show at some point it could probably act
as a popularity pose for them
yeah first the girls ladies first
i don't understand the super chat but
anyway thank you for your support
[Music]
and frosty thank
i don't know the i think
it is gonna look it up
nope it's not i think
[Music]
congratulating me for my original song
even though it's not even out there
but thank you thank you thank you
everyone
yeah the guests have to be in whole life
i'm not gonna interview
uh non-homo life members it's called
hauler talk after all
[Music]
here's a down payment on the great music
metal is the genre obviously
no but thank you so much
um you paid a little bit too much the
song is not gonna be that expensive
and also it's gonna be released on
youtube first where you can basically
listen to the whole song for free
and afterwards it's gonna be released on
spotify etc
but i still hope that you will be able
to wait for the uh release on the music
services and then support me there as
well that would make me very
very very happy
i am releasing the whole song on youtube
for free as well but
if you want to support me boof
and the later on release on the music
services
which helped me very much thank you
would you invite philippe of course i
would
of course that's so so obvious
of course i would thank you dilla thank
you so much i'm glad
i'm glad you liked the music i'm glad
you like inside of kiara i was so
excited
um
looks amazing looking forward to hearing
the song right it looks so
good you look at it uh
closely you will notice that i mean
you don't you don't even have to look
closely i think you all notice that
this art and the other art that my papa
did for me
uh like around the debut time looks very
uh different
from the style that he drew me
in in this bunny
i i really think it's amazing how he can
draw so many different styles
so the one the artworks that he does for
me like this uh
this artwork there but also the arts
that i use for my twitter profile pic
it definitely looks more like his
previous works
for like steins gate and black work
shooting
[Music]
like especially the eyes he draws so
differently
but i like both both ways he draws both
of the ways
he draws the eyes i like them very much
like my eyes look like the universe but
in that artwork
they look like how just
how to describe it looks like psychotic
is that
is that the right word i feel like i
mean look at those eyes
do you know what i mean with that
look at those eyes
so interesting and then look at mine
look at those eyes look at that can you
believe the same person drew this
door
so talented i love all of his styles i
respect artists
that can draw in more than one style
i cannot do that i can only draw in one
style
at least like if i even if i tried to
draw in a different cell i guess i could
do it but it wouldn't look so good
like he's so skilled but he's been in
the business for a long time so he's a
legend
[Music]
let's continue thank you thank you for
the red super chat thank you for
supporting
jeremy
thank you high fructose corn syrup
function
x-men wolf function
[Music]
how do i say your name again salvius
thank you
headstand to elemental congrats and
finally achieving your idol dream now
take it forward and go beyond towards
what you want to achieve
i look forward to your beautiful singing
good luck to talk show too thank you
it's definitely not gonna stop at one
song so much i can say
don't mind i can say i want more than
one song
i don't know when i will have my 3d w
but i want i want once i have my 3d w i
want to be able to
perform some original songs so
i have to have at least like two or
three songs
let's see if we can get that happening
um i think i'm even gonna
for the three day debut i'm probably
even gonna like prepare some kind of
choreography
and then you know it's probably not
gonna go so well with my asthma
but i do want to add some choreography
i don't wanna only stand and sing i
wanna
[Music]
what have you done thank you for the red
silver chat
thank you
thank you for the support can i really
do be going all out for us i really
did
and there's even more things that i've
been preparing you know the cali thing
you know
yep i'm trying my best to deliver you
with good content there's some weird fly
frying around here i'm gonna kill you
i didn't catch it
it was really close to the microphone
yeah that was why it was bothering me
but now it's gone
i didn't kill it
ouch slap
nansu thank you
james burns bronx also
thank you for the red super chat thank
you so much
papa's art is amazing much love from a
fan ooh you're a hooker papa fan
well who wouldn't be who wouldn't be i
need another cough job
you should take up the limiter on your
belt for the pretty darvier
no no
papa says no i'm not allowed
foreign
drop down
you know what i ate a whole bowl of
strawberries today
i saw strawberries in the supermarket i
was like what
is it strawberry caesar what the hell
i ate the whole bowl actually i bought
them because i wanted to make pancakes
with the strawberries but then i
realized i'm too lazy to make pancakes
so i just ate the strawberries the way
they were
really good yeah i love strawberries
mood but it's so easy i even have a
normally i make pancakes from scratch
but i i even bought a pancake mixture so
the only thing i have to add
is egg eggs and milks
even though i can do it from scratch so
but that will make it even easier and
i'm still too lazy
i saw my in my kitchen i currently have
uh one of those um
one of those
things with the with the fire
a gas a gas uh gas
gas something
you know what i mean yeah glass a gas
stove yeah yeah and
uh gas range whatever um
and i don't like using that i'm too
scared to use it i moved in here
how long ago
oh one and a half months maybe and i
still didn't use it even one time
because i'm too scared to use a gas
stove
i'm too too scared to turn it on so
that's also why i'm not cooking pancakes
normally i would
do it but i'm just too scared to turn it
on
i don't know i'm used to uh kid
to stop stoves that are not gas so
i'm just too scared that my kitchen will
explode because they always say i have
to be careful of gas and
i'm just scared that everything will
explode and then i will die
phoenix is afraid of fire that is not
normal fire it's not about the fire it's
about the gas and everything exploding
i'm so scared i don't want to use it
that's why i'm not using my kitchen and
always using ubereats
[Music]
but i did i did buy my
my small microwave size oven so i can
make pizza now
and yesterday i made pizza in the oven
and not in the microwave like i did it
before so the pizza was actually crunchy
perfect perfect
ah finally crunchy pizza finally and
today
in the morning i put a croissant into
the oven
and warmed it up and uh gave it a light
a slight a slight crunch
and then i ate that with nutella mmm
warm crust oh yes
you did pizza in a microwave yeah
because um
many people in japan have a small
kitchen
where they don't have an oven and they
usually have a microwave but sometimes
the microwave has an oven feature
because they usually don't have a normal
oven
but my microwave didn't come with an
oven feature but now i bought a
microwave oven as well
anyway um i know overseas
it's you would never put a pizza in the
microwave but here uh
i had no other choice and it does say
on the pizza package it's like a small
pizza
they don't even have many big sized
pizzas they're all pretty small
so that they fit into the microwave
it's it makes it very soft
but it does work somehow if you're very
desperate
just like me go for that
i can't breathe well the whole time
oh yeah this is this is gonna be fun
when i do a 3d live stream
this is going to be fun
i didn't want to be one of those people
who
lose their breath at the beginning of
the stream
now i'll be fine
it's not it's i've seen much more than
that
everyone everyone's is just so used to
streaming at home every day in front of
the pc
it's just uh i don't think many of us do
work out
i don't think any of us do work out
besides the
once in a while uh ring fit adventure
stream
i don't think any girl in her life does
any workout besides the
occasional ringfit adventure stream
kelly says she runs
i'm not sure if i'm not sure if i
believe that
i mean she does look
fit uh but i don't know is she really
the time to go jogging
is she really does she doesn't even have
time for that
gouda does run really did she say that
gruna runs and eats a whole melon well i
know about the melon didn't know about
the running
corona does boxing what
like we clear it
could have started running could have
swims
with floaties i wouldn't call that
swimming
[Music]
that's interesting
that's very interesting
she did
[Music]
thank you so much this is all p-o-g
hype ngl what
i'm so looking forward to everything
you're talking about in this stream
i have faith that the song will be
amazing always love your karaoke streams
here's 100 chicken nuggets for all the
hard work you do
thank you that is so
kind thank you so so much oh p oh
a pog
i didn't i didn't get it
thank you thank you so much for your
support
i wonder if that super chat was before i
gave the preview of the song
but thanks for believing that the song
will be great
i wish i could already let you listen to
the whole song it's so good
oh yeah one more thing i want to clear
up because sometimes i said if you
listen
if you listen to what i say correctly
in stream then you would not
misunderstand this
but for some reason people still manage
to
misinterpret misinterpret
what i say even though
i probably even said it twice
my song
is mostly japanese with english lyrics
i never said that there will be an
english version
of the song
but people did take it that way some
somehow even though i said it very
clearly
that there will be english lyrics in the
song
that i wrote but it is a japanese song
there is no english version
you said the opposite i did not
what do you mean when i said the
opposite what is the opposite
yeah there's another meaning why do
people not listen
why do people just not listen to what i
say
[Music]
oh i did say there will be no english
version and there you go
people just don't listen
thank you thank you lord robin thank you
so much for the chicken nuggets man i
haven't
eaten chicken nuggets in a while i feel
like i've tried um
in japan i've tried chicken nuggets
from literally every
fast food restaurant in japan
and they taste so different from where i
come from
they taste so different i don't like it
i don't like them that much they taste
better in my country
i don't know why
i have not really found any chicken
nuggets in japan
they that taste the way i want them to
taste
yes of course in australia
yes although i do believe that actually
australia probably also has
yummy nuggets
also they have different sauces they
don't have my favorite sauce
in in japan for the chicken nuggets even
though in my country it's such a
basic sauce such a popular sauce
sous and salad salsa sweet and sour
sauce
and it's different from like you know
the sweet and sour sauces that you use
to cook or whatever
it's different from that there's like a
specific sweet and sour sauce
for chicken nuggets in australia but
they don't have it in japan
they don't have it so i usually go with
like barbecue sauce they don't have that
much choice somehow
i don't know man and sometimes
i was so shocked can i just stay
a certain fast food restaurant with
three letters
in japan has basically
no sauces for the for their chicken
i am absolutely shocked how am i
supposed
to eat all of that chicken
with no sauces yeah there's no gravy but
even in my country
there's also no gravy for uh that
specific
that specific restaurant uh i think that
is like
i think that is only like something
american
i think gravy sauce only comes
in countries like america or canada or
whatever
wait i think there was one sauce
there was one sauce that they have in
the japanese uh
version but it wasn't it's not
particularly a good sauce in my opinion
there's really not much choice but i
feel like um
they really need more choices that's why
i am opening my own fast food restaurant
and as you know we're getting a lot of
those sausage
sauces we're getting all of these sauces
we are getting sauces
that have never existed ever before
k f
[Music]
if you if you beep out the last letter
it turns into kfp i just realized
if i beep out if i censor the last
letter it just turns into my own
restaurant chain
can it be
[Music]
me
a
[Music]
tonight
japanese people just seem to prefer to
eat their chicken
without any sauce
tonight
i'm surprised they're still japanese
beerus even though i'm speaking english
the whole time
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat thank
you
[Music]
a voice pack i'll take your entire stock
thank you it is not in stock yet you
still have to wait a little bit
but i hope you will enjoy it my nose is
still so itchy that's why i'm moving so
much
trying to trying to make it unity
thank you
oh yeah the book walker thing did you
see the tweet
people were like oh kiara set out i hope
you guys are joking
you have to be happy for me
[Music]
there might be a book walker related
stream in the future
where we read something together
what do you think about that
yeah i was thinking of reading a yuri
manga
i was thinking of that
what do you think about that
but the good thing is that unlike the
the movie
watch along for the manga read along
you would see what i'm reading you would
be looking at it
with me i think i'm pretty sure about
that
no i don't think they have anything to
do with that that
connection
yeah i mean i would be showing it on the
screen and i would be reading it along
making some funny voices
but yeah i i i usually don't read manga
um because of you know
time and motivation issues but if it's
like a stream i think i would enjoy it
when i read uh
i never
a manga that does not
um where the characters are not naked
let's just say that way
does that one get naked
does this one get naked
it's pure really
yes no it does not okay okay i actually
already uh
looked up some manga that i want to read
for you guys i already looked some up
to be honest but i will not reveal it
yet
i was also thinking of reading
uh it's together with
cali
wouldn't that be absolutely perfect
[Music]
all right let's continue
where was i there i missed singing again
thank you for the support thank you so
much
one more week to go and then you can
enjoy all the goodness
of the kiara voice pack thank you
thank you black knight
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
but wait there's more yeah there was
much more there was so much more
thank you thank you so much for your
support
i hope you enjoyed all the announcements
i hope
you're excited for what's to come in the
future
thank you for your support
[Music]
um
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you for your support even though
you wrote nothing with it
thank you so much
smack him all right i guess
i guess so i guess it has to be done
jonathan
sorry but if you use this red super chat
and you don't write anything that's what
you get
that's what you get
yes mommy
john smith thank you let her fly thank
[Music]
thank you so much
very true very correct statement
always has been wait
kiara is an idol always has been
thank you did you just realize it now
how did you not see it before
i know it is so itchy
where is my nose
the way you wrote that is funny
[Music]
many of you said it sounds like an anime
opening
actually um the the producer
[Music]
is uh from the touhou project
arrangement scene
some people thought that i got to him
via cali's kokoro beach
but that is not true i have
i've known him for a while i really like
touhou music to be honest i
actually know a lot of
touhou music i am a fan of the whole
project
so yeah it does have that kind of sound
if you wanna if you like touhou graduate
music you should check
that producers toho which is called
sync arts check it out
it is quite uh it was it is one of the
if you know two project circus
it's one of the well-known
toho project circles if you are if you
know that scene
then you might have heard about it
before
[Music]
hmm
maybe also
but i also like uh
what's her name again oh
what's her name again um
[Music]
the frog girl what's the frog girl's
name again
i also like channel and i like all of
them
god damn it
continuing
to fancy thanksgiving
kiana is a masterful sales phoenix the
best boss anyone could possibly ask for
you're doing an amazing job kiara
thank you so much thank you vibratio
thank you
your local hollow fangirl thank you
i did read that super chat uh while it
was sent
i'm not gonna read it out loud but thank
you thank you i'm glad i could help you
i hope you're feeling better
[Music]
shaking with excitement wow
that song is definitely getting blasted
hard enough to vaporize the speakers in
my car
look kfb
this is my first ever time giving a
super challenge of course it had to be
your attention thank you
thank you for everything you do you will
always be the best girl for me
thank you i'm so sweet thank you
my stomach hurts
[Music]
my world will be crying this month but
it will be worth it it's just the course
for now but i'm loving it personally it
reminds me about your personality
and upbeat exciting and majestic phoenix
i will be uh
waiting with a baited breath for the
full release i don't hype
thank you thank you
[Music]
i'm i'm happy you are all as excited as
i am thank you so
much i'm glad you also enjoyed the
chorus
it will get even better if you listen to
the whole song so stay tuned
[Music]
thank you for your support as always
thank you for the red super chat
congrats on everything to our queen
but you're donating with australian
dollars i think you have a different
queen
but i shall i shall accept this
james thank you
[Music]
foreign
bad right now
[Music]
i'm done with the super chats from the
announcement stream
but considering stopping here
stupid fly
dead gotcha
[Music]
my stomach hurts and i can't breathe so
well right now
it's my ear sorry sorry
i think since we already got to the end
of the announcement stream
super chats i think it's a good spot to
stop
and again i i said this during the among
us
play through but um i will not i will
move the fire up livestream from
tomorrow
to uh probably
the day after tomorrow after the super
drive for the american views it's
probably gonna be in the middle of the
night
but uh yeah that's gonna be that
sorry i think i need some i need a break
for one day to work on other things
[Music]
actually last last week
last week was it last week
yeah last week um
i had like one one day off
in my schedule i think but on that one
day off
actually i was recording again i was
recording the song
so actually i didn't have a week off yes
uh last week
and uh
it was fine though i had my fun
definitely
my calendar is acting weird
ah no
so even when i have a day off in my
schedule you never know
i'm probably working on something as as
tomorrow
i might move the fire on blam stream but
i'll be working on something else
for the talk show and for something else
that is
secret thank you all
for the support today thank you for
coming uh
and thank you also for coming to the
announcement stream that was that was
very very
very nice of you all to come by to
support me thank you
for always being there for me i'll make
it worth it
i'll make you all proud
so that you can say i am a proud
employee
of kfp hmm
i'm already proud thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you that is so
sweet
thank you
kind of sad to leave you all now but
i gotta go maybe i'm gonna make some
pizza
for dinner
[Music]
thank you all i love you all so so so so
so so much i love you i really
hey i'm so sorry oh my god did you
oh man you know what that is oh my god
oh
so sorry
you know what that is this is my [\h__\h]
stream labs
i'm so sorry i saw i didn't hear it but
i saw it go
right into the red that was mine that
was my obstruction i'm so
awesome so sorry oh my god i was
i'm so oh my god
oh i'm so sorry i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry i'm so sorry oh my god oh
my god
[Music]
everyone who watches the archive has to
be warned how do i warn them
i'm so sorry oh my god i'm so sorry i'm
so sorry i wanted to turn on the echo
in my filter and tell you how much i
love you
but when i the filter i don't know i had
that before
off stream when i turned on the filter
suddenly i don't know why but it bugs
out in the microphone like i don't know
what you guys heard but something
happens there
it's it's crazy until i turn it off
again
i don't know i gotta switch back to the
normal obs and not use streamlabs
anymore oh my god i'm so
sorry why are you giving me why are you
giving me super chats if i hurt you
oh my god i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry is it safe to unmute yeah
i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry oh no
it was it was like someone wrote that it
was actually like really painful
i'm so sorry i'm
i'm so sorry
was it really like really really really
really bad
i didn't mind okay did you wear the
headphones
here it did hurt a bit oh my god
oh my god i'm so sorry
ah maybe i should edit out that part of
my
of the out of the archive but then the
live chat will be gone
and it will not it probably won't update
until 24 hours later
should i no leave it in what do you want
pain for the other people who watch the
archive
you just wanted to be painful for
yes we do everyone who watches the
archive hello i'm very sorry but the
decision was made by the viewers
to bring you pain i am sorry it was not
my decision i wanted to protect you
but they decided to hurt you
so oh well i i will say it again you
might not believe me
anymore but i do love you
guys they can replace your drums really
can't you mute in editing without
calling oh i wonder
[Music]
oh my god it was a loud robotic buzz
right i can't
imagine i can't imagine
i still rely i'm sorry
keep it in it's funnier
i don't think it's funny
speaking louder i can't hear oh my god
okay guys i'm actually in pain as well
so i'm gonna leave you guys now
i'm sorry i'm sorry please forgive me
you need you need those ears to work to
listen to my song when it comes out so
please go to the doctor and fix your
ears now everyone
they have to work on the 26th for
thanksgiving
[Music]
just sent me the bill
give us a paycheck no that's not how it
works
that's not how it works
bye bye
[Music]
uh
i love you all i'm sorry i'm so sorry
i love you bye bye
hmm
[Music]
huh
and now i went down
the ringing is gone oh god
there was a ringing
[Music]
can't hear the outro thanks
i can still feel it in my ears
oh my god
[Music]
is she muted bye bye
one hour loop of the noise
you are a mad lad you are obviously a
muscle
kiss guys
[Music]
bye