[Music] I'm saying that everyone has a role to play,
so maybe I'm not good at anything,
but
if anyone did this to me, I'd
be devastated.  Little by little, the flames are created, and the
heart becomes
huge.
Even though we are all ragged with our weapons, we can't resist anything. Good morning, hello, good night.
The door in my chest is the key that opens. I wasn't afraid of dying alone,
but I still feel
sad.  Hey Hey, he's hated Hayia
Hayia,
hidden in the back, hidden
in the back
[Applause]
[Music]
[music]  Let's
build a home for our hearts together.
This city will surely
become the biggest star that anyone can build. Let's put the feet of our hearts on the ground. As
if we were born wherever we are, the
vomit that comes out from our birth,
as if the world is shining on us, is a beast.
[Music]
etil