a
[Applause]
[Music]
oh e
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
K hello thank you for the raid
MAA I saw you raiding so I hurried up
over to the screen but I'm still
finishing my sandwich my grilled ham and
cheese sandwich
I
can three arms oh it's just because I'm
not on
[Music]
closeup say it again about my
arms say it
again if you dare
oh the whole one hour before the stream
I was
playing the
game so uh like oh my God that time
passed by so fast and then I realized oh
my God the stream is starting soon I
have to make a quick lunch so I made a
really quick ham and cheese sandwich
oh but it's just like two more bites
okay okay did you guys see ID's new
outfits they all look so nice they have
like like idolish outfits performance
outfits that are all matching in life
2D
M so
nice especially
[Music]
Mao reminded me
of um macros
Delta because of her purple
hair and the style of the
outfit but it's nice when they're all
matching like we we started out in myth
trying to have the themes matching but
eventually you
know also simply because the the artists
have very different speeds and not just
the artti artist but also the talents
the members so some artists are like
they throw uh design at you in like one
week some need a bit more time but also
then if the talent says Okay I want this
Chang and this and this and this changed
or if they just reply L then overall
like there can be very varying speeds in
how fast an outfit can be
finished thus Us in myth following theme
is uh a thing of the past although I
wouldn't mind doing it again in the
future but it's just
like you
know we had a
fee first it was casual which is obvious
everybody needs casual
outfit and then we had the fancy outfits
which is also very useful everybody
needs uh fancy outfits maybe once in a
while and I think and of course the
kimono which everybody
gets and I think that's kind of when we
stopped because everybody just wanted to
do different kind of things uh
yeah at different times which is fine
you know like you you may think you need
this kind of outfit more often than
another different
[Music]
one
smooy is lying behind my
monitor which she rarely
does and especially when I'm talking
to the monitor I wonder why she's still
here maybe she's apologizing for being a
[\h__\h] all
morning because she stole 3 hours of
sleep from
me because she was terrorizing me
endlessly even after I gave her a
breakfast she ate her breakfast and then
immediately
continued to meow
endlessly and not only that she would
like go around my place go to the living
room go to the hallway go
to my room Etc sorry the Coca-Cola is
coming up my my
throat I don't want to
burp yeah and she would like I I hear
her I literally hear her jumping up
doors trying to open them and jumping up
the like my coat uh closet
thingy uh and then on her way down
bonking all kinds of things over and she
was just making a lot of trouble while
meowing
endlessly and I was like what the [\h__\h]
is wrong with you I gave you food what
do you want
n she just wouldn't stop and then she
every once in a while she would come
back to my bed and meow Yow Yow Yow Yow
Yow Yow she would not come down for
hours chers of course she was just
chilling next to me trying to
sleep I don't know what her issue was
and then I got up after three hours of
listening to her and like zoning in and
out I gave up and I got up and she still
even when I got up she was a little bit
a little bit annoying still and now
she's calm behind my
monitor tell me what is your issue
should I touch her let me touch you
touch soft okay I can never be
angry at least not for too
long a
[Music]
okay if you want to be there you know
last uh Yakuza
stream in the middle of it she uh jumped
on the on the guest bed and was just
chilling there for like the rest of the
stream and I was like oh oh why why is
she being
clingy she doesn't like me like talking
in the same room oh squ Squatch chunky
wonky doing a squ
Squatch sorry I'm having a little bit of
breathing issues right now cuz I was
like rushing to make a a sandwich before
the stream and rushing to eat
it
okay okay but so as I said I was playing
for about an hour before the
stream um I did almost all of the heroes
quests in this area and then I went up
and I I did a couple like around here
too I mean there's still a bunch and
also did there a couple of reminition
and a couple of uh Bond
conversations so I got I got a bingo
with Satan and a bingo with uh
Namba and uh I got uh a level up only
one level up for all of them even though
I did a lot of fights but some rank UPS
as well and
uh our beloved kidu should have I don't
know can we see this
here uh wa uh can we see it
here I don't know uh his like circle
thing should
be upgraded where where I wonder where
can you see
no idea the
uh the the thing that gives him four
different stats you know what I mean
right I I worked on that a little bit
through the hero quests and gathered a
little bit of money but now I was kind
of shocked a moment ago cuz I remember I
went up to 1.5
million
yen and then 5 minutes later I was down
to 800,000 and I literally don't know
what I did to lose this much
money uh I bought some food in
restaurants and that's it was it that
expensive I don't think so
taxes wait I'm probably too big and I
probably shouldn't be here I should be
around
here
some okay so since I did some pre-work
right before yeah I'm a little bit
drunk because I went to the restaurant
and I just ordered
everything can't imagine that it would
be so expensive though but I guess um
now we can go straight to the story
because I did a little prep work
although one level I guess is not really
that much prep work if you think about
it but was one hour of
gameplay yo one full
hour I'm still straight edge trust me
I was hoping to at least get like two of
free extra levels but I only got
one kind of shook it maybe the hero
quests aren't the best way of leveling
but at least it also gave me a a bunch
of money and some Bond stuff or like
whatever whatever that is that kidu
gets levels are a dungeon yeah I didn't
know where the dungeon was in this city
I forgot so I was like whatever I'm just
going to do I'm just going to run around
do every hero Quest I come across and do
all the BNS on the way as well and all
the remin I I didn't get this one
though but yeah yeah not unlocked yet
see okay makes sense so what was I
supposed to do I just went to all the
hero
quests yeah I leveled some useful stuff
I leveled enough with the her Quest I
did them all oh
okay so all side quest today no no no
we're doing main
quest
um I I don't even know anymore what side
quests are are they on I don't even are
they
marked I don't see anything that looks
like a side quest to
me I wouldn't even know what to
do but yeah I guess we can go I also
topped up on
items which maybe maybe that was the
expensive thing h no way 700,000 Yen can
get lost that
easily no way
maybe maybe we go here I do one more
hero Quest hero Quest I also noticed
those hero quests they're really
unbalanced in
payment some pay 10,000 20,000 some pay
500,000 and I thought oh maybe this
one's more difficult but no
no it's
just please ignore me ignore me ignore
me ignore me no
no okay this one is 10,000 but that
doesn't mean that they're so much more
weak than the others it's uh weird so
this was really cheap it's not even
worth it but we'll do it for those stats
anime girl and what oh my God I want
that
sausage Mr America you got a nice
hat wait okay
so I like to start out with a flash
grenade I hope it hits the pretty wait
wait ah it's pretty
Cure but without the
e pry
oh my God and right he's like oh it
looks like almost like wait what I
wonder it's so green and turquoise it
makes me think he's a p o m u otaku but
no wait his shirt shows someone else who
is this
cute oh this one's weak against
guns but you know what let's leave it
to our gunsling a
girl
nice what are you we are you we against
water water he does not like the
water but water is so nice I didn't get
the buff are you for
real I was spamming Square as much as I
could
[Music]
okay we love sub
birs uh wait wait who was weak against
guns him no right the the picure girl
should
[Music]
I I should just finish himim off I
guess H Tony attack I'd grapple him
first well you would do that but I don't
do
that you mean yeah cuz he has a guard I
see that I see that don't worry but
uh ow ow oh
oh he's doing allu
moves okay here here's your grapple
it's like we're in a wrestling
match so I wonder what we can expect
today from this from the
story last
time we found out the
obvious that Pana is a cult what did you
see her Zoom by did you see Sony soon by
Zoom
by we found out the office that Pana is
a cult and the somewhat obvious that the
blonde dude is
evil s this
there a
[\h__\h] game audio could be raised
oh
[Music]
okay it was absolutely
shocking yeah yeah I know you're
speaking
sarcastically finish him otaku
being taken down by two beautiful
[Music]
women
cute
okay now that we have saved them I think
I'll go to the I look
it was way less last time when I ended
last time I was like at what level one
or something for all of
these having awakened his soul to level
four keto's perfect guard has been
enhanced in the brawler style
successfully performing a perfect guard
against an enemy's melee attack will
trigger a counter oo well brawler style
was the the right one the heavy one or
however against attacks which hit
multiple times you must perform a
perfect guard on the final hit timing is
crucial oh [\h__\h] the final hit how do I
know which one's the final
hit kind of hard to tell if it's uh the
first time I fight that particular
Enemy at the blue one so the main one I
guess right cuz the other one was red
the other one was yellow I think I think
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh
uh ah we're supposed to take the
taxi yeah where are we going good
question Kaz
grave
o are we going to start off sad today
[Music]
M smells
good nice Graves they look
nice that was fast
[Music]
is
right there you go
[Music]
fore
I don't know him
right
foree
fore okay
okay byebye W so much taller
than let's go
yakas number one detective uh what's his
first
name
d what's the first name you guys know
Mako oh
Mak yakas number one
detective
Mak there you go
e
foree yes
yeah I
cannot same model
[Music]
L is
Siri
[Music]
foree
fore well
[Music]
fore
memb thank
you for
[Music]
yeah we were lucky that we met at the
grave so
randomly got to go to
survive I have some conversations to
do
for
sister a
cute no let's go to survive
no hit the sack no I don't want to I
don't have to it
seems cool knife
attacks um survive
do
survive I Will
Survive hey
it was probably somewhere high no
actually
noive ah isn't that here
yeah we got to go we have some
conversations and
allinis here as
well goodby it's a great bar but it
doesn't hold C Serena
I let loose a little too much last time
it sang like
crazy a yeah I ought to thank n my the
others for hanging out with me and so
this is a new
remines but that said K is really a
mysterious thing it's nothing like
working up a sweat from fighting or
hitting the batting cages sure you still
feel exhausted but in a pleasant way
what's really fascinating is how you
might even catch a glimpse of someone's
True Colors depending on what song
that all right I was the only person
singing back then I'll have to listen to
everyone else pick next
time
yeah they better get up there and sing
next time not just me and then they
don't even
listen you got to
listen yeah and wait so uh I also have
some flower bouquet that I could give to
them I can only give it to them here
right begin drink link let's begin the
drink linku drink dinku I feel like I
even got two levels of
no I'm just here for
[Music]
you I pet the cat while I listen to
this
[Music]
fore foree
sorry oh he lik me
[Music]
when I when I pull back my my hand she
like cat punches me and tries to bring
me
back
uh yeah just use my real name around
friends
[Music]
yeah can't
stay forch
[Music]
yeah like
not to mention any names
but
yeah I guess that's not about each
for we
she really oh she's really aggressive
right now
aggressively
cing fore
[Music]
fore
what why is there a jelly
answer I think we should ask for details
I wonder how she will tell
it
for does not spill the beans
[Music]
do
not
maybe yeah but
still it's the the bro code
she's purring really loudly
but she's too far you can't hear
it oh she's
so psycho's B of the team has enhanced
her skills she can now use Tag Team kok
fever let's go nice I think I have one
more
number let's go more cat col L behind
the
monitor have you ever thought of the
option of drinking water or ice
sweetened tea
like oh there you go it's so popular in
Japan anyway I was going to
say totally
[Music]
acceptable
for
Fore
foree
fore fore fore
H do his Juniors not show him
respect you are a man of good character
N I love
you he means not showing
respect that's not
true
for
[Music]
Fore
for love with someone
besides
foree
fore
fore for
[Music]
going to hear from
her we going to find out who
uh life is hard let's drink I don't like
that sentiment I will not support
[Music]
that
for nothing wrong with that
oh my God she's purring so
loudly toast I just
toast different kind of
toast yam and cheese
toast come
by you know you use Taxi team fire
breath let's go do I have another one
cuz I feel like it was double for number
no maybe it has to be like on another
day but oh I got one with her too let's
[\h__\h] go I got them
[Music]
all more cat
cuddling now he's back drinking just
have
that's
good wow that
look God back what happens with the
tea
for
speech
fore foreign
how old is K now
again I think I already heard it before
and I was
shocked
[Music]
fore
damn Grand
the thought of Y of like bent backs and
like walking sticks walking canes and
maybe some pushing each
other
chairs
cute
very why did my life to stop moving
there we go
uh I'm not worthy of your presence damn
of course you are do you know who you
are
[Music]
fore
for asserting
dominance
[Music]
for ah
for
fore fore
he's
[Music]
fangirling fore
fore
[Music]
for uh
uh please don't take any risks for
me wow
so she trying to kill me
for squeezing her paws
well thank
you women with power
pot
[Music]
yeah okay
now maybe we can sing
K I didn't see that she was waving she
waved for
nothing
foree she's aware
you're pretty awesome too
[Music]
son yeah someone's got
competition do will impact
okay free bonds
done now it's time for a little bit of
K so you there's something new which
one's
new this one seems
new it sounds good
hi
[Music]
okay
W wo wo wo W wo wo wo nice back up kid
wo wo
wo
for
[Music]
Fore my head
oh
[Music]
joh
he wo wo wo wo wo w w
h no
Miss
elf we love it oh oh
[\h__\h] oh black hair
s wow nice she looks cool oh do you
right white and black version
[Music]
yeah I didn't do a miss it was strong
let's
go not
bad ooh we got another level up wait
every level up means uh a a bond
conversation
right damn but probably not in the same
night
um is this you
singing is that new I wish I could see
which ones are new
[Music]
this probably new
wait like a
butterfly K is also carrying a
microphone
[Music]
H that's supposed to beo or r
[Applause]
[Music]
what do you mean M I [\h__\h]
you I want to
redo oh pretty
[Music]
a [\h__\h] I [\h__\h] hello what's wrong with me
but sounds so different like a different
song what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] fly like a beautiful butterfly play
like a beautiful butterly
fly fly like a beautiful butterfly fly
like a beautiful
butterfly oh my God I had so many more
misses and I'm still 91 on the score
that's kind of
crazy God damn
it so ridiculous I love
it thank you for the red super chat
Super Chat Super Chat
this one I know I
[Music]
think I know I guess we should do this
one we didn't do
[Music]
theak yeah I also was feeling evanesence
Vibes really really really low
key h
[Music]
indeed oh you seeing
higher he hey
[Music]
for I love you
what hey hey hey
hey
[Music]
hey no woman in this life what about
me damn that one mistake was so
unnecessary but when I sing along I
can't I can't
but I had to sing along a little
bit but there
no he hates
me well number another level up wow can
I give give gift again ah there we go I
have so many flowers only flowers in one
self- bought ABC Store gift set like
what I do with all these
flowers did you ever see say what's her
favorite flower whatever we'll give her
a
hibiscus what do you mean ah there we go
okay and now holy [\h__\h] that's like so so
many level UPS
today will
you I shall give you the
lies I like receiving flowers
yeah but um ideally in a situation where
I can take him
home but if I account then I still like
looking at them like you know the
situation with uh you know the flowers
in in Bangkok in the flower stand
obviously I can't take it home I wish I
could but I really appreciate it it's so
beautiful and it's like a nice a nice
little surprise I didn't expect
it okay here's some some pansies on
maybe no you know what how about this
ABC store store gift
set let's
go
okay and good we'll probably be back
again for some more
conversations but
now we got to go sleep a little bit also
I can't believe this smovie is still
here like this whole morning I was like
oh my God she hates me because she
Terror she's uh terrorized in
me but maybe she loves me after all CU
she's so
Cy you guys know she normally wouldn't
stay here when I stream because she
she's bothered by me
talking but the fact that she's still
here and purring and
sleeping maybe maybe times have
changed maybe times are
changing as movie is growing
older maybe she's on her way to becoming
a lap
cat instead of a lap dance she will give
me the nicest lap
nap I could ever imagine
who needs lap dances when you can have
lap naps from lap cats huh dream come
true okay he wants to stroll around
town smovie lapat AR well not yet don't
don't jinx
it I I knew he was going to say
[Music]
that
for
Fore
fore wait C
rose
blossom rose blossom wait it's right
across the
street there it is okay wait where's the
entrance oh
here right across the street how
convenient a this is the place let's go
inside kka
[Music]
damn
it J she's going to do some detective
work
she really wants to see it or another
level up damn
[Music]
okay right away another one we got some
cute
where are the
women he got all the women he's talking
them
[Music]
for that dude is a boy he
raised ah
huh he looks like him
[Music]
indeed is he rich now or how can
he so much service
[Music]
sure you're just saying it to himee
probably or he doesn't
[Music]
mind yeah what the [\h__\h]
how would you not notice
[Music]
though a long time
ago
for
[Music]
True good night
but you want to
[Music]
right
for
[Music]
fore oh
yeah for
real
[Music]
fore
for D
it got a hero complex she's got to do
[Music]
something oh
fore going to show that he's taking out
the
for step
in there we
go or maybe he won't no this
he's on the
floor never
mind he can't even see what sorry he
can't even see properly oh but he's
fading out oh
[Music]
bye-bye let's
go my gang's not here I guess oh do are
okay thanks for coming over so
quickly I guess that was only possible
because we were stay by
see ooh really
low why is there one dude with a much
higher HP
bar guess he's the boss
[Music]
yeah that was good whoa everybody wiped
out except for that main
dude yeah catch me outside how about
that is what K
said she cat me outside
[Music]
uh what are your weaknesses do you
have nothing I can
[Music]
tell older meme you know I got to rely
on those older memes that's all I got
man also did you guys see how perfect
our HP for number and K are
7500 wow full
numbers I missed again but that attack
is so so strong I love using
[Music]
it oh level up level up two level UPS
finally let's go it only showed
one oh we we brought the bodies back
inside how nice of us don't want the
streets to look dirty
well that'll be easy to convince him
when he's awake that kitty was not
indeed there
[Music]
yeah littering human bodies is also
wrong no no no no
imagination
for was never
[Music]
here a would be nice if he could
speee fore
let me try to put on a
little sheet on my shoulder no not
snck of
me
for
[Music]
foree
fore for
[Music]
you call me again does that mean I'll
meet more of his kids
[Music]
he so many
kids and none of them from his own blood
Lally The
Witcher just more characters
[Music]
okay he
is why dare
uhhuh low grumpy
voice little
emotions he's The
Witcher
[Music]
okay
o as Kido raises his Awakening level he
will trigger life Links of dat and his
older friends other old friends
lifelinks can be initiated by speaking
to dat at the Harbor Light in 's bar
District after K receives a phone call
awaken the dragon within and see things
through to the
end diet has been added as a guest of
Dono Island try inviting them to stay if
they make the trip
what wow level up bond with
myself sorry for the wait uh oh good so
did you get to chat with your friend
yeah our talk made me realize something
important actually oh yeah glad to hear
anyway where to
next good question
kumako the legendary dragon to think
you'd return restaurant R I'll be
expecting you come alone okay but
when I hate these like really
undetailed like invitations in like TV
shows too like and when they invite each
other to a date and then there's no
mention of location or or time
whatsoever no exchange of uh telephone
numbers or so NOP NOP they're just
no they just
know I'm not just in TV shows in games
too something the matter there somewhere
I need to be mind taging alone oh we're
supposed to go alone it's so
vague can't say I'm not curious restant
R huh maybe I should drop
by Okie
doie
oh what the hell oh everybody
except the son gets a really nice number
for level 30 look at look at Satan she
also has 500
HP um so
[Music]
this wait if I go to survive bar now I
could do another drink link right but I
feel like it's been 1 and a half hours
and everything has been pretty slow so
far cuz it's mostly like pretty slow
dialogue so let's see if we can get some
action over over here I'll do more
drinklings later I
suppose you're mostly
talking yeah no I it's supposed to be
main story this was also main
story just
now at least it was unavoidable dreamy
signature C an idol idle
signature temp trip whip a whip that
inflicts Unforgettable
pain wait I don't think they can use
that right I did find a cool equipment
so I had to switch out one of the uh
insoles because this is only for her
class for Assassins it greatly increases
drop exp so I'm just going to wear it
for a little
while um
but I wonder I don't know should I
change glasses I still don't know what
to do
I don't know what to do with
them dominatrix
weapon that wasn't that a class that
existed already uh in the previous
game yeah right so in theory we
could do that the dominatrix for one of
them
supposed to go here no no no no no leave
me alone leave me
alone oh I think I remember this
[Music]
place n taking classes to level 30 is
usually worth it oh okay that feels
reassuring thank you I've got some to
take care of real quick mind waiting for
me no problem I'm sure you'll be okay on
your own no one go to tag along nope I'm
supped to go
[Music]
alone oh a yeah I remember going here
too before in the previous like a
dragon the M said they'd be waiting
here yeah
hello spinner well
you who are you Ammon
Amon Memoirs of a dragon new found
strength the Ammon Clan believes they're
the strongest in the world is made up of
skilled Fighters we've clashed countless
times long as I can remember they kept
hounding me to fight saying that me
being the legendary dragon hindered
their CL Clans claim to strength you
haven't forgotten about us have you how
could I when you this persist the and
how did you guys know I was back after
your retirement we targeted ichan kasuga
who had been making name for himself as
the new dragon in town but while we were
keeping tabs on him and his flunkies you
showed up right out of fer surprising
really to think the dragon would resurge
couldn't keep yourself awake could you I
didn't return because I wanted to not
that it's any of your business why of
course it is in the past you've insulted
the Ammon Clan at Time After Time Time
After Time the fact remains that you are
but a forign in our side
okay so I guess you want to fight
basically Ammon is the secret boss in
every Yakuza game usually you need to
complete every sub story to fight him
whoa
okay
damn and now we get to fight him so
easily if you intend to making a
comeback we won't let that slide besides
having you roam the streets and your
weakened State guarded by your allies
only tarnishes our reputation it's like
talking to a wall just like old times K
ah
didn't I tell you guys to wait sorry
we're just worried about you who is he
who is he this guy picking a fight with
you K son no need for kosan to bother
with him if he wants to uh beat us up so
badly he'll have to go through all of
us so these are you little friends how
weak you've become
kazak you want show everything yourself
and F alone to think you'd have allies
looking after you now ew
disgusting you think strength means not
relying on others well putting your
trust in someone else takes real courage
quit shoving your ideology down other
people's
throats stop running your mouth about K
and I'll show you no mercy okay let's
go show Amon Amon
Amon oh [\h__\h] I just did that wait what
the actual [\h__\h] I blocked it and I'm
still I what level
54 e why did I stumble into this at
level 30 this was kind of
a the main main story know
like I cannot win
here can I
lean is this
uh yeah I I unlocked the counter I think
I just did it but he only got one one
damage
okay I'm meant to lose but don't take my
money if I'm meant to lose I don't need
to put that much effort into it oh
okay wa a triple six on
16 I tried my best man I try my
best okay just a normal hit
then oh hey he's on the
ground
oh
oh I pressed on the last moment it was
too
[Music]
late nice heat yeah what the hell I
didn't
know there he goes now
[Music]
out save
that okay okay okay this time I'm
ready this so fast holy
[\h__\h] one
damage it's over no no no not so
awkwardly in between
what
[Music]
the you're weak CIA too weak both
physically and mentally is this all you
can
do I told you I'm not the same man I was
before well boy here how about this say
I killed one of your precious comrades
would you would that awaken your old s
huh our Clown's line of work is
assassination you know it'll be easy for
me to sacrifice as many lives as it
takes to revive the legendary dragon the
[\h__\h] what's wrong with
you don't you dare lay a hand on
them looks like you do have some fight
left in you it's time you take this
seriously for your alies sake I guess
some things never change now show me
your true strength show me what these
bonds of yours are made of you better if
you want to protect your
friends n
no what what is this
what when his hype meter is full ketu
can now use dragon's Resurgence a
powerful skill that allows him to move
freely on the battlefield hold R2 to
activate it then use blah blah blah to
attack until the timer at the top of the
screen expires oh you can increase the
duration of dragon's Resurgence by
strengthening K's bonds with the
party okay so
I'll just be able to like hit several
times
W where are you where are
you I can take
him it's over no I'm back to one damage
for person oh I can do it
again oh they're so
nice Okay we get an easy way out after
all oh 500,000 there we go there's my
money O level
up up nice nice
nice ah is it a reference
to from when the yak the games were not
turn
based I won't let you hurt
them that just that hit just now felt
just like the ones from the past uh left
the mark too no doubt about it looks
like the bond you share with all your
allies is what gives you strength now
still raring to go no I'll leave you be
for now if you were just a Jer gezer on
the decline I would have killed you here
and now why
why why is there a need to kill him when
there's like that's what you wanted to
achieve to be the strongest so just
don't bother with him
anymore
oh oh thanks for the lore I'll read it
properly but I yeah already already
learned this info roughly thank
you uh but you've still got some growing
to do with this Bond you and your allies
have do or what whatever call it what
you will should you develop your bonds
and grow even stronger I'll return to
find you once more okay I'll keep in
mind I probably have to be at least
level
50 I'll be the one to take you down not
some illness and I'm sure I'm not alone
in that sentiment Don't You Dare Forget
that oh thanks I
guess the strengths of our bond huh Can
you okay yeah and you
guys we're fine somehow that was a tough
fight sorry for dragging you into this
mess oh good we're used to getting mixed
up and stuff not like it wasn't any of
our business
anyway they mess with our friend they
mess with us
[Music]
right he used to break the forth
W and talk to the play directly oh what
would he say
[Music]
creepy all righty then that takes take
care of that come on let's get
going yeah let's do some actual main
story let's
go and Memoirs of a dragon oh
oh wa holy [\h__\h]
what holy [\h__\h] so many bonds level
UPS we're going to have like a million
conversations four St equipment C just B
steam has enhancing
skills D want it oh come on that's so
mean want to check our
gear frear frear
three star fre
star oh she oh she got some good stuff
actually Four
Star oh do we not have anything
better on the other ones perhaps U no I
got to buy some stuff I got to buy some
stuff but where there's a place right
here I don't know if it's
appropriate at this place M I don't
think they so armor
let's go eat here although I've been
here
before time to spend that 500k
immediately
true
[Music]
um let's do the DI some course
wait it doesn't even heal them
completely now need to
F another
one oh yeah yeah one one four plus four
star armor that's just
one this
one
o pretty strong need more where that
came
from so we
got Welcome
[Music]
Pharmacy
no where do I get like good gear
maybe what about this place dancer
equipment H hustle
Boutique ah yeah they got four whoa one
million for some festar
shoes okay well we just need four star
they got some hats and some embroidered
jacket the other places with a loafing
marker oh this
one holy
macaroni that's uh nope that's also
still way too
expensive C an anklet a four
star a weapon for the
breaker no need okay then I guess the
only real place that we have is this is
this one which're is close to the
survive bar so we can do another
drinking equpment is a bit grindy for
real and then and then you go into a
dungeon and you find fourar equipment
there and then you're like man why did I
buy
it I Wast my money
why there present here gi gi
ah thousand yen for something casual
fashionable
sophisticated
H maybe
s yeah I don't
know definitely not
number could have been Sony too though
don't know if it matters really
okay we want two
hats uh one
more oh my God it's so expensive I
already spent half a million
yen what the
[\h__\h] okay one jacket for number
uh one pair of shoes for
you maybe we can
keep like cuz I think K is wearing
something
that's
decent they're they're free star but
they have extra
agility I mean I think you can keep
wearing
those buying shoes in this economy
we're going to walk Barefoot it's good
for your feet or your skin I don't
know they Honestly made cash a lot
harder to get early in this it feels
like it yeah I mean grinding those hero
uh quests gave me quite a bit of
cash but yeah it disappeared so fast
again I literally have a drink link with
every single one of them again
I might like zap a little bit faster
through it uh but I'm still like reading
along so you guys pay attention Okay
read with
me just D oh really H
oh the
other mhm yeah oh we keep on drinking
tea with him
[Music]
let your emotions
out oh every 10 levels
okay get to the point
yeah it just a half an hour
ago I'm here for you bro just Hur
up the one in the middle
[Music]
that
fore
yeah you you're too busy
anyway yeah yeah no that I get it we
drink until you talk he's talking right
now are you listening
K be honest with me that sounds
cool
fore fore
[Music]
nice
Ka good talk good
talk
na I'll take this opportunity to give
some
yes now but you want also one your
flowers for
you he likes them lies well so you guys
would you guys also like to receive
flowers
sometimes flowers are
nice W almost level up
maybe not really only from
me of course yeah aren't really my thing
I think maybe RAB
flowers what's what might be nicer to
receive both for you guys and me is a
plant because flowers die right
away and you know are maybe look a
little bit tacky but a plant is a nice
decoration for your
home and almost like you know a bouquet
of flowers or it could you know it could
be
flowers a flower land take care of at
home yeah and
I like to get more and more plants
whenever I can but I Al always have to
check if they are uh cat friendly if
they're not toxic for cats my cats don't
even try to eat my plants thank God my
my family is cat when I still lived with
my family that cat always was like
nibbling on the plants
um but I wasn't in charge of buying the
plants so I don't know if those were
safe but I when I'm in a plant store I
look at every
single what blue icon what I look at
every single plant's name then I Google
it and then I check if it's safe for
cats and even if it's just a little bit
toxic I won't buy it which
generally it it's actually quite
restricting
my plants are made of
Lego
what H getting it ready yes so I maybe
you guys saw I was building chairs
yesterday and today uh I got some more
stuff like a table it arrived today but
I didn't build it yet I feel like I
could probably build a table on my own
too and I got like a nice lounge
chair the lounge chair I think I might
wait for my mommy because she's coming
over either on Monday or on Sunday she
was saying for like one or two
nights um so I'm probably going to take
off at least one of those days just so
that I'm like a little bit
available and yeah maybe tomorrow before
the stream maybe I can build the table
the chairs the first one I was still
like pretty slow I was looking at the at
the guide the whole time and then
several steps I had to reverse because I
thought I was looking really closely at
the guide but then you realize in the
middle that oh something was a little
bit different like one part being the
wrong way around it still works you can
still screw it in but then later on
you'll notice something is a little bit
wrong so I had that happened several
times but that was only the first chair
and then I had to make three more and it
was so easy chairs are really easy I'm
confident now I can make my own
Furniture I I mean I say make but
obviously it's just assembling but still
for me that's a big step because for
most of my furniture or pretty much all
of it I I have to ask people to help me
don't have confidence about
it yeah but I felt quite com uh
confident no yeah confident and
motivated yesterday when I was making
the chairs and I felt so satisfied yeah
when I finished one and two and three
and four and ah let's
go and the the reason why I got it is
because it's getting so nice and warm
these days and my previous furniture for
outside it flew away or it
broke both
happened and I had like one chair left
but
you know that chair all alone doesn't
match with anything so I just bought a
full new
set yeah um it was really really cheap
plastic anyway that's why it was lighter
and that that's why it was able to fly
away and this time I got uh like wood
wooden
stuff why four CH why not because it's
like nice to maybe have but if I ever
have people over I can like say hey we
can sit out side you know why not
for I was I was really thinking hard
about it too maybe maybe two is enough
but no what if I want people to come
over it's nice to just in case have
more
yeah four it's always the best
yeah like if my brother and my mom or so
come over or my friends you
know got to have enough
chairs yeah can you fold them no but
that's okay I don't need to fold them
for nakisha cheria my favorite
woodpecker
stream oh yeah maybe tomorrow before the
stream I'll try the
table I'll
try otherwise my mom will come by even
Monday or Sunday
evening and I proudly sent her pictures
like hey look these are my chairs that I
made oh look I made another one look I
made another one she was like good job
waa so proud of
you don't stress yourself out too much
before the stream yeah for real like
especially if I can't sleep because a
certain someone under my monitor wants
to terrorize me for the whole time when
I'm trying to sleep
yeah to is going to be so happy
yes yes also I'm raising some strawberry
plants from her now um they're doing
pretty well I see some green
strawberries tiny strawberries already
they're growing but only because she
gave them to me at a really late stage
already yeah so I got them in on the
stage where there's already flowers and
uh strawberries growing on it so
hopefully I will not ruin it from here
on
out yep I'm excited if I if I can pick
my own strawberries I I would be so
excited see it's me got it I'll be right
over did you get the
picture the s that picture or what
probably not something came up I'll have
to return to K will you be all right
yeah yeah byebye come again later
byebye yeah I feel a little worn but
it's no surprise All Things Considered I
after all have
cancer maybe take a [\h__\h]
break yeah Birds I hope they don't eat
the strawberries do they do that
hey yo who the [\h__\h] is calling
me why does he sleep like
this maybe wear the dress instead over
there is a
pajama might be more comfortable
oh she just going to expose that Kido is
still alive
right
[Music]
[\h__\h] for
I don't remember
this it's been too
long
foree for
[Music]
huh see I like that there's like a
little bit of a delay because they're
having this conversation over whatever
Zoom or like whatever TV stations
use why are you exposing us
what's your problem man
what
whate foree
[Music]
strings
you poor poor little men or you were so
frightened and felt so endangered by
kidu coming
back that you are showing here on live
TV on the channel of tatara Hoka that
you have really really tiny tiny little
peees
[Music]
congratulations um no don't
mind your own [\h__\h]
[Music]
business I am
flabbergasted this girl is unbelievable
I just started to hate her at this very
moment
who the [\h__\h] is
she it's probably
[Music]
ay dream
sucked Bad feat
K is that
R's used bunk bed that they left behind
did you buy it off of them just
kidding oh my God I must
inspect it's ichiban's place right so
ichan must have bought it
m
but it's just creating evil where there
is no evil and actually supporting the
evil
that yeah cuz the those two dudes were
that were sitting there are the ones
that she should actually be
exposing really biased but okay
fore fore
fore
foree
spee
for
mm probably
we should make our own vtuber and expose
her
fore
foree
[Music]
for
indeed fore
for Fore
okay
okay since I just started in a Super
Chat uh about whole talk so girls talk
is happening next week but whole talk I
asked both uh what I do nothing but but
the dates the scheduling just didn't
match up so it won't happen in that week
that I said might need another extra
week or so sorry both of them couldn't
make it
oopsie yeah a girl talk is happening
yeah who am I inviting this time oh you
know what I want to get these
two conversations really
quick probably skip for them
anyway
[Music]
signature another
Bingo wait that's like my third bingo
with him holy [\h__\h] n on me we're so love
N I should teach that to Good Eye I feel
like that could be a good one similar
kind of Menace
feeling as
professional as a c sugar you could
combine it perfectly
fancy business card let's go from
whom don't don't don't look at me I'm
just here for the walk
away something here to pick up
no would you mind walking away or do you
want to fight H okay they're
walking that's going to be nothing but
very aggressive not not just to her fans
but with any slies she
collaborates let's
go oh I guess level 20 means we have a
maybe a yep we have a conversation
unlock I'll talk to you soon
more fan Girling from her oh the
expensive cotton
ank
honestly it might be worth like looking
at a guide at what nice items are in
what locations unless it's
random I wonder if this anklet for
example was like always said to be there
or if it's
random cuz if it's not random you could
like look it up and and be like okay I'm
going to go here to get this instead of
wasting
500,000 Yen on
equipment not
random yeah there's a bunch of stuff
everywhere but if you want to look for
equipment specifically I'm sure there's
a guide for that kind of
stuff
right yeah some weapons in specific
places for sure oops
uh oh I was going to say maybe I should
eat or heal but where
are in the cut you're going to ask me
something though right if I want to go
in if I'm ready oh hi hi
hi break his Fu phone in
half
[Music]
foree foree
he hurts
me take his phone and drop it in that
what do you call it
g next
to by
accident thank
God thank you
oh he's had
enough
fore fore
fore foree
I thought he wanted to frame it the
other way around but I was hurting so
much
[Music]
the times of nice K are
over fight fight fight fight
damn that's a lot of
people all right
[Music]
uh let's see
[\h__\h] oh the ones in the back don't count
oopsie they're not
fight my thing is active
did I use
[Music]
that I'm all over the
place yeah this a strong holy
[\h__\h] wow
okay only three
[Music]
left yeah you can just
uh give out a lot of punches and you get
a punch and you going a punch thank you
Michael H and you going a
punch I mean normal hit is fine actually
cuz he has water on his umbrella
what what's this camera thank you that's
what I was
thinking
nice yeah not
wor want some more
H get that ending on camera it will be
your ending
end of
life flash
grenade
[Music]
Miss jump a little bit of a
refresh
W easy easy easy easy easy
he finally put his shitty phone away
thank
God we have been
freed that [\h__\h]
[Music]
idiot all right kawakami and
katayama left on the battlefield
[Music]
wa oo good damage I didn't expect this
much actually cuz the
attack oops feels pretty weak at this
point but no it has 14
itself
Nery umbrella you mean is that a Naruto
reference
okay Overkill
[Music]
son she's also
like so sick of their
[\h__\h]
wow no I've heard of E before
[Music]
you always miss timing and not move I
didn't miss it off stream that much but
here I am once again missing all the
timings at least I manage to block the
enemies
sometimes level up level up job rank up
rank
up so now maybe you you can tell us a
little bit about
t
[Music]
mhm
mhm thank God finally some intimidation
thank
[Music]
God okay how the [\h__\h] did she know it
was she just assuming it or is it
someone from our inside like
Soni who's been no way right Soni
wouldn't do that that then I would I
would even say maybe Satan cuz this
whole time remember when I was saying
Satan in the beginning cuz like she she
uh after the whole marriage thing Satan
left us and then right after that the
Tatar Channel thing happened and I was
saying back then that I think maybe
Satan is the
vtuber yeah and I don't know man I don't
want
to say this but like she might right she
might be backstabbing us want to be
wrong
[Music]
though n can't
be can't be
her yeah maybe at least the connection
but we're not even pointing out right
now that they already knew we were
coming
interesting
oh I believe you even accus pyo that M
up it was just like really weird timing
though suchan
disappearing
and then this vtuber shows up who's
trying to mess up Ian's
reputation while Satan was really pissed
off at Ichiban but then you know it's
like she has no beef with kidu right
so she's no real reason to do anything
against kidu but whatever
[Music]
it how long you going to wait huh Can
you a wow
Fury oh suuki it does say Suzuki oh [\h__\h]
oh oh
Uh Oh chapter end let's
go that was the chapter
what what the [\h__\h] happened chapter nine
Uso the LIE hardheaded woman oh
meanwhile back in
Hawaii they're all just
[Music]
chilling so
sweaty
for oh yeah we made a video
what that's actually actually really
good
[Music]
he's
Bing he's
[\h__\h] but it's for it's for a good
cuse
foree fore
that comment just
now
[Music]
but
but supposedly she didn't even know
ichiman yet when we were not in Hawaii
yet put on
your it did feel
uncharacteristic for
her
for oh more membership thank you
he didn't even say Target he said like
old
lady he was offended by that not by
saying she's a
Target um but yeah
uh sorry Satan I mean
it it would be weird a weird
decision to kind of drag her into the
position of a uh villain right
definitely
uh so you know I had my
doubts I never was serious about my
suspicions that never was serious about
I never meant it um
but but but yeah you know it it's just
because she was a a
positive heroine in the previous
game a big part of it she played a big
part there's no way she would do that
now from a from the POV of the creators
of the game hopefully um just would be
weird a weird Choice uh now for Chan
I still want to think she's good because
just like Satan it's just kind of weird
decision to have a character who's so
involved in our
team actually be backstabbing us but of
course it's a good old well-known
pattern So Tan could probably be it Kimo
500k thank you thank you thank
you wait saan does have a twin
sister now I'm kind of like going back
to
[Laughter]
sa
nah
nah it can't it can't be anything with
that no I need to stop cooking yeah half
a million thank you please keep on
listening to it and if you haven't left
a comment on the MV yet I think most of
you did it has a lot of comments but if
you haven't by any chance go ahead and
leave one to boost the algorithm yeah
yeah yeah yeah but it's doing pretty
well I'm pretty
happy it's
clearly
for interesting soundtrack
[Music]
Choice
weird
hey
for man in this part of the game there's
so much
resting what the
hell can't believe K channel was Channel
all along it was me
me I am a YouTuber
indeed we've got to find something on
aanan soon oh yeah say would you would
you um do you do you happen to have like
an iPhone or what's your phone
hm no just just just
asking what do you do you uh do you have
like a PC H yeah and how much how much
time do you spend on a PC every day H H
you have like a cool microphone setup or
so H hm
H H nice microphone uh I just wondering
maybe I I was thinking of maybe
recording a song or
so do you have like a good recording
environment at home that I could borrow
to record a
song by any
chance yeah no you don't want me to come
over or I wonder
why yeah can't let Pana get to her let's
see if that old tattoo knows
anything Ulta two lady Bryce's influence
has brought the barracudas and the Gansu
to grade their levels of aggression
enemies roaming around honol Lula have
become considerably stronger o they were
already
strong o and look how low their levels
are they're still at 28 to 27 so sad but
okay then let's switch some gear
again this is fine
wait can
[Music]
I going to switch because they're not
here at the
moment that's all
right no gear are you for real
probably nice to have both souls for her
combat knife is
fun that's a three star let's get the
four
[Music]
star four
star we need to sell all these things
too and then Tommy
he's using the decreases MP cost item
okay could have
this
unless it's probably fine and then some
shoes number shoes Tommy and number
sharing
shoes oh wait it one no uh no
[Music]
switching I wish I didn't have to do
this each
time but it is what it
is not going to buy a set for each and
every single one of
them wait do I even have in my team
actively yeah okay it's completely split
4 four
uh this one you can
have and then is there a pair of shoes
left
over yeah oh yeah wow we have a we have
a five star pair of boots those are
really expensive in the shop I was lucky
to get that
one yeah better than buying a whole new
set for
Real uh what do you want to wear
items
[Music]
obtained job
exp but for some oh yeah he's a samurai
right that is exclusively for him so why
not give it to
him
okay ready to go maybe we can go to a
shop on our way to wherever we're
going oh we're going right over
there where are we going
oh now we going here
they're coming at me so fast what the
[\h__\h] I think I have to fight them ready
for non fight okay I see what's
happening all right look at my funky
party this looks way more exciting over
here I haven't bought them in a while
um need to
remember how we
do is this how we do
wa wow she that's so
strong not the be it looked like
butterflies to
me okay well they better be weak if it's
several little fights after each other
ouch so guys I'm almost finished with
the third season of The
Witcher it's been pretty good but I
don't worry I'm aware it's not accurate
to the books but apparently there one
scene that got me really excited in the
sixth episode it does happen in the
probably like different here and there
but the the whole thing and
happens now I just wonder like what
parts probably towards the end of the
season is probably where all the things
get really messed up I
guess but it's been pretty
exciting don't fight
me I really like it
and it's so funny to me because I
recently got into the
Witcher that's why I wanted to buy the
game and then also got it for cie and
then I was in a call with Cali telling
her I'm buying her The
Witcher and right after it was fauna so
I think she was
listening and then uh I was made aware
that we might not have the uh PC perms
for
it so I uh for cie's sake
applied for Witcher PC perms really
quickly and now we have
them now's playing the
game I also want to play it
soon um but I don't know when
I but there there's no rush but I
[Music]
think I think what I might I want to
do
is finish watching the third season
which I'm I'm in the last episode
already replace Dragon but I have a code
I need to play it at least once I don't
have to but I want to as a as a thank
you at least for giving me a
Cod he resist it but I want to take him
down
no I
will I
will you can't stop
me grapple do grapple no [\h__\h]
[Music]
grapple what's wrong with you you're a
samurai uh but no what a what I'm
thinking
[Music]
is
like I I can't
really I shouldn't really be starting a
whole play through right now
anyway
so fre SL listen to the audio book a
little bit
[Music]
make you guys
happy
and
bridge that how you say it the time
between me watching the Netflix show and
me playing the
game Run on home to
M what is is it nice I brought two
groups
together I bring
together wow do your worst oh my God
she's
overpowered yeah thank you for pointing
out the thing that I already
said a minute ago yes
yes don't
I have a
[Music]
grapple no knock back doesn't do the
trick does
[Music]
[Laughter]
it oh man ichan don't
[Music]
what what where the [\h__\h] are all the
grapples here all the way down here for
m
Overkill
okay what
by the
way uh wait what over
here D
ding
huh yeah I know it's really
strong I one hited him literally what
you looking at what you looking at what
what you looking at what you looking at
what what you looking at what you
looking at what you looking at guys
speaking of new jeans H Las seraphim
actually the seraphim is at Coachella
Coachella
what
fighting can you believe it I don't even
think this is the first year but hsik is
at
forella and she performed a
song that k wrot what you looking at
what you looking at what what you
looking at what you looking
at my
producer you know yeah he worked for uh
voal Lord basically before they had to
make a
song called highlight which is really
[Music]
good really good I like it and and yeah
I saw a video of it being performed at
Coachella and like no matter what your
opinion is of Coachella that it's for
Zoomers and whatever I wouldn't feel
comfortable there
either I want to pick up the
trash but it is quite an achievement to
have your song performed at
coella that cannot be
denied but performing at Coachella what
are you staring at I mean it's
definitely overall more welln than whole
alive but I wonder maybe it's not too
far off I feel like I can see I can
see a world where cie gets to perform
with
Coachella I can see such a timeline I
suppose
yeah Co is the New Year
Vision
what Kelly said she would never do
it I don't know once like those things
that you say oh I would never do that
when the opportunity is given to
you you might
reconsider what was I going to do I here
also if
uh what not United Universal Universal
tells her to do it I don't know if she
even has a
choice but I don't know getting into
Coachella I think
possibly the music
lab if you could just pain get in then
anybody could be in there they get big
stars I wonder if
coella probably but not always maybe
maybe some there's some cases where the
artists
Wonder really pissing me off
I mean even Miku
being kind of out of place right do your
wor it just feels
weird
[Music]
but she still seemed to have a big
crowd see let's
go she's not even real she's virtual
screw you don't screw
you come on whole life would feel more
natural do you think
so us being real might make it more
cringe not being a real person might
make it less
cringe I'm real make
Israel you meet her ow what you think
I'm stupid my wife for
real IID doesn't fit
the I mean I agree so honestly by
music the genre I would maybe fit in oh
Smoothie has decided to leave the room
goodbye think she might just go to the
toilet or
byebye
um but obviously I I don't even have
close to the amount of popularity that
it takes to get in there you think I'm
stupid but they do have a lot of K-pop
performers these past years my songs are
very
strong I do think it's
um not far off in terms of mus vibe
[Music]
but yeah if anything I'm still thinking
about your vision because your vision is
made
for just weird performances stupid
anything weird that stands
out really one third only
you [\h__\h]
cars I've seen bab metal when they
opened for Red Hot Chili Pepper so
anything is
possible yeah that is um overall a very
[Music]
interesting turn off
events I mean not even the right word
Mak sense but if you think about it it's
interesting
that such a
cutesy thing o was accepted
into what are you st by fans into
something like that they make great
music so and they're just like
interesting high energy performances and
stuff
people appreciate how much H life puts
into the live shows really feels like a
stage and not a on a flat screen
TV
a uh yeah uh I watched a video of how to
make with Coachella and I wasn't sure if
they were actually using the invisible
screen again or not because it looked
actually like they were using a normal
LED screen again but honestly that whole
drama I I was like okay I feel like
people are kind of blowing it out of
proportion like I understand like that's
how they had H Miku shows until now and
and that's kind of what you expected but
people are acting a little bit like it's
the end of the
[Music]
world and like trying to boycott it and
that's a bit too much in my opinion
um
yeah but sure of course it would have
been nicer if it was an invisible screen
for the hsik concerts that are going
on what they asked me for my TV
con they used your TV screen for
it yeah for just one act I don't know if
it would have been too much effort it's
a big um showcase big
opportunity small LED screen
bad Nar Nar yeah cuz ours are
big
big yeah well you know what made me more
sad is like although it's there's
nothing sad about it but it felt sadder
with seeing the
insane um
instrument people the band behind cages
in the
back get ready for
this while they were rocking
it but it's not like you know it's not
like it's an inhumane thinging or that's
just how they do it they're just back
there maybe for acoustic reasons or
whatever but people are like oh my God
they're so cool you need to let them out
let the band out of the cage they're
[\h__\h]
amazing yeah they are [\h__\h]
amazing free range musicians yes we need
to support free range
musicians wow nice block
[Music]
W wasn't not for safy I don't
think what's there to be safe
about I think it might have just been a
b or
whatever just attack
normally think I can take one of these
down why are you moving like
[Music]
this
Miku Miku is
dangerous no but anyway I just wanted to
let you guys know that k
he has
music perform that
Coachella does my producer is a
Coachella producer
officially yeah what a flex weird flex
but [\h__\h] she's
[Music]
insane C
close
close it's a huge win
yeah oh he kicked without discretion so
now his defense is lowered
[Music]
it is
rad Grand that's why surprising that
they're going well they must have had a
reason what the [\h__\h] why is she so
insane why is she
so what's the word
why you
so not OP I'm looking for a word crack I
she so cracked
busted
broken all of
those where are we going now over there
why don't we just take a
taxi we could just take a taxi but okay
gift set I should get that gift set on
my
way got to always think of the gift
guys pineapple
Maracas sorry the pee is strong
[Music]
today
pineapple wait who wears them Maracas
again does anybody even wear them
anymore oh I don't think they do I think
we're done with the
Maracas we have a new axe it's not
upgraded but it's already
stronger I hope we get to upgrade our
weapons at some
point you looking for a beating no ele
I'll sue
you I mean
fine it's a lot stronger at
least 188
522 Mama
[Music]
Mia why bad
Warrior guys one question I had this
idea for a EUR
trck I wonder if someone did this before
even if they did doesn't matter I'm just
curious I'll do it
anyway oh
um your truck
simulator driving through
Europe and at the same time unarchived
K so the whole stream where it be
unarchived it's basically an unarchived
Kad with your truck simulator in the
background more or less or the other way
around however you see
it singing fitting songs for long
drives like I'm on a high way to
Hell High way to Hell stuff like
that has nobody done this before because
it seemed so obvious to me like such a
obvious
choice thank you for stopping by
goodbye did you have terms for that I
mean I think it's fine I have terms for
the
game I going just sing No I me it's fine
it's not like I'm playing two games at
the same
time take me home yeah
that one I could sing honestly in this
case I will sing
it in this case
okay they're all
scatter only that yeah but we can
rebroadcast it too and uh I just think
it would be a nice way of doing anarch K
slash another
shill uh EUR truck Sim and the good
thing is about Euro Truck Simulator
there's no story or so there's no
lore you don't really you're not really
missing it's just you know we're
chilling chilling on the AO bound
you're telling me now now that the game
is loud
now guess it
is W the great stream ideas thank you I
thought it was
so
Unown been telling me for 30
minutes are you
sure I think it's in your dreams I look
at the chat all the
[Music]
time something yeah maybe just the the
fighting bgm is uh like
more in
Hawaii freaking
no I don't have a grapple on
him oh it didn't help him
much almost
dead sometimes there's no need for
grappling I guess yeah cuz magic attack
was that considered a magic attack so
to do with uh the defense the thingy
blah blah blah
whatever I don't know what I'm
saying
smovie you coming back
oh
me what do you
want what do you
want
no
no just looking out the
window I'll CLE you
in okay guess we'll fight
I pulled her up so you have shortcut now
you can go behind the
monitor you want go go go
go come
on yeah the German NE truck simulator
stream yeah or honestly I was thinking
also of other stuff for the German
Channel I just don't know
when to do
it I want
[Music]
to do
your but then again I'm wondering
likeed to see that in English too is
there a demand for
[Music]
Gothic Gothic two I
think let's
go people want to see it
remember well it's
like to me right
now although it makes no sense it's in
the same position as The
Witcher
because it's like a European
game our
both has cult
status oh yeah this
attack is
mad absolutely
mad watch my streams are always
scheduled for European time I don't know
what you mean
come play in the normal Channel but then
we could play anything here in the
normal Channel what what would we play
on the German
Channel that's that's that's my issue
too you
know what is interesting enough to have
on a German Channel but
like taking away a
stream on this channel in a
week worth my time you know for
that but not worth putting on my main
Channel
cute cute it jump so
high it's just it just feels uh
contradictory to me
me making a German Channel kind of was a
curse leave me leave me leave me leave
meone you can't run for
me do
your you think I'm stupid what
more important than a German Channel
perhaps is me starting to do the Dual
streaming the
simultaneous streaming
thing
[Music]
what but VMA has to set up an account
for
uh I would say pretty much for all my
streams once it's set up it's
really automatic I think and
uh why not just do it streams to just
always
be you always have a present
[Music]
work and especially cuz I'm aware that a
lot of viewers are just lurking on
Twitch
so I know I should have done that a long
time ago
[Music]
chat would you see I mean I could have
both on I don't think especially in the
beginning for a long time I don't think
the chat will be that on the twitch side
anyway
mie so don't worry it's not like they're
going to overpower the YouTube chat by
far I don't think
so my main viewers will just continue
using you
[Music]
to
think game is very loud I already made
it
lower okay even lower or what don't know
if I can change bgm during fights I
don't think that was a thing right cuz
it's always just louder during the
fights I'll Follow You wor ra thank you
s of X gets loud okay
okay it's always the freaking
sfx oh more okay I'm going to put you in
your
[Music]
place that's loud
[Laughter]
yeah it will always be good as a backup
too whenever YouTube is being like wonky
you guys can go over on Twitch and then
First Watch like a 30 second or one
minute ad or however long Those ads are
over there and then jump into my stream
by that time maybe the lags are over and
you can go back to YouTube but at least
you had a little a little outing a
little trick a little
walking little
refreshment
[Music]
hi holy [\h__\h] 762 I thought the guy in
the back would get hurt too damn it
[Music]
you want to have both
open at all times I mean sure you want
to what are you why looking why are you
looking around here movie
they're all weak to
guns thank God we have so many gun
skills what do want
go here let's go let's go go go go go
go under the
monitor
yeah I put her in front of the Monitor
and now she's squeezing herself
underneath
cute okay go movie has been secured
in her seat I need to make a chair for
her no no chair she wouldn't use
it doesn't need a chair the world is her
oyster I will have both on then I will
start conversation on chat between
YouTube me and twitch
me big
[Music]
brain big brain
oh oh [\h__\h] all
enemies beseech the gods to strike a
random enemy with magic damage at the
start of your turns for a few turns with
thunder that that sounds like what
yennefer did and not to
say what was that called
again that was pretty insane
too W on Twitch would also yeah we can
have animated
emot that you can use only over there
but I mean that's still
[Music]
cool just attack
normally help me Chan or shoot say t
he's
so chicken twerking
emote that's that's why you guys should
maybe use the twitch chat watch on
YouTube but use the twitch pop out the
twitch chat but watch on YouTube and
just use all the twerking chicken emotes
and stuff
that's definitely worth the
investment is there several versions of
it oh I was I thought I read 3 million
but it's only 3,000 bucks what the
hell at least they dropped some good go
up up rank
up me stream's going to work obviously
those are not going to be streamed on
Twitch what do twitch YouTubers do do
they just not do membership streams I
guess so thought about that
and I'm here what what am I supposed to
do oh next
Point all
right can I use
my can I use this
thing surely I can use it and I could
charge it right here while I'm
[Music]
here a small charge is okay
ah subscribe only streams oh see I know
nothing about twitch
wow oh wrong
side the way I am absolutely clueless
about where this at this way I'm
absolutely clueless about
money so
this way I guess across the
river oh the
algorithm smokes you we're using sub
only really
I want to pick up the trash but I can't
do it on my
scooter hero sword Boomerang
Brees M panties from the trash yeah that
sounds like a good idea to put on my
body rainbow geod the
M bird
food for you
guys oh double wait you want no I have
to free the doll
[Music]
twitch streamers don't reward their subs
really like I like we reward our
members I guess that's just how they do
things over
there interesting they're just happy
being subed because I guess a lot of
them can have free Subs through Amazon
Prime and stuff like that
I
suppose I suppose
hey I just learned the other
day someone sent me a
video that the English version of is I
suppos
hey I watched the whole
video it works surprisingly well the
English version of that
hi hi hi hi go hi hi hi hi what should I
do what am I choosing I'll just punch
them normally how about
that I
suppose oh cat hairs in my mouth
[Music]
your
ouch mie left your what no what what do
you
mean no grapple what's this Pine bamboo
Plum
interesting but I have a snack in the
fridge I should take out at some point I
have um honeydew
melons cut and ready snack
on I think it's
honeydew the ones that are like yellow
whsh mostly white on the inside
[Music]
very strong still yeah probably I
figured so
much as
much no no not calop is the orange one
no maybe yeah I think so do your
worst yeah it's
Hy I like calop too but honey do way
better for me
but you can easily notice like I don't
know if it's a difference in quality or
just in ripeness or whatever but every
time I eat a honeydew it tastes
different
basically it can be either really mid or
pretty
amazing I need do when it's cold usually
you would want to eat it fresh from the
fridge cold
chilled I have
dog
dogle you're so welcome dog you seem to
have an owner right next to you but I'm
the one feeding you I wonder how the
owner feels about
that you need to feed my dog I my dog
very much by myself thank you
y there's dogging me go
away
[Music]
no that bananas true I have a banana too
I should eat the
bananas once again we're stopping
traffic but honestly if you're in your
car driving through the city wouldn't
you love to see something like this okay
maybe not but it's kind of entertaining
but if you see it IRL you probably also
really get concerned and scared that
people are having a really serious beat
down right in front of you like this
it's pretty
hardcore what would you do guys Florida
it's kind of
normal
Florida just Florida things I'm going a
trophy a for reaching level 30 I
guess what is all the Cru I don't get
it oh no and he goes to the goal on his
own I guess okay what do you mean where
am I what I'm
lost this
way no no don't look at me car people
don't look at me don't look at me don't
look at
me oh we're here wait can I not make a
wasn't this a place where you
can where you can make a like a fruit
[Music]
thingy while I'm here I should make it
yeah I'm talk to the chicken I saw the
chicken chicken you look like
a wait you look like a p
Exemplar the most beautiful example of a
chicken aren't you look a
cow what the [\h__\h] am I supposed to feed
you milk no you make milk
I guess you can have a
coconut I know but that's I don't know
it's like
whatever have a natural Earth you like
grass yeah I
know no I'm talking to the chicken right
now wait it's called
Phoenix I
mean that cannot be a
coincidence do not yeah the makers do
this on purpose because they have
vtubers in this game and they have a
certain person in this game may they
might very well be aware of me and
father we should name a chicken fushi
cha
Phoenix this might be a reference to
me you never
know we must become best of friends okay
you and
me run run run run run run run
run wait I wanted to make a
movie than refence this
cover welcome to the Discovery
Channel oh nice
opening whoo whoo whoo whoo
she's so
strong yeah W has many game death fans
how come how is
that
possible Easter
egg Al so that sounds ironic to me as
well
[Music]
I know he's
guarding I don't
care attack is raised but you're only
living for one more
turn sorry you don't look so cool to me
dude you think you look really cool when
doing that
move but it's all in your head
it's all playing in your head just like
a VN so you Mr Pana zeelot are not very
different from
ichun I think we might have to keep this
class on her until the end of the
game I don't think there's anything
better for her she's
cracked she's literally the cracken hoha
okay yo perfect I really want some of
those for everybody healing
items oh
yeah
yeah I wish I could have made more of
the fruit but I'm missing some mango
thank you can I buy
[Music]
mango do you sell mangar no you sell
watermelons I'll here sold out okay
well we gained something nice at
least oh shark to long
sword Maybe samai
yes oh but it's
worse it's
worse no what for real how much it's
both four um
stars mine is already a little bit
upgraded but
still
sad oh yeah I should shake oopsie I
should shake some trees for
real which trees here are are
shakable not this one not this
one I don't think any trees here are
shakable it's only the palm trees I
think oh wait it's a lemonade girl what
are you the same as the other one I'll
buy your whole
stock
yay 19,000
okay it's a different
one I welcome lemonade on every
corner no no no no no no no no no no I
don't want to fight you oh but there's
the the spot is right here okay next oh
we I have to stay
here for a moment it's not a short
and
now and
now ah we're almost there at the volcano
volcano tattoo place do you guys have
tattoos I
don't I don't think I'll ever get one I
have no problem with it and I kind of
like the idea but if it's painful and I
can never get rid of it unless I go
through some stupid
procedure doesn't sound like a good idea
to me
personally I'm not that passionate about
anything that I feel the need to have it
on my body but I think people's tattoos
look pretty awesome most of the
time I never looked into the
[Music]
price but yeah for something permanent
it makes sense for it to be
expensive I even well yeah me neither
that's why I don't like it when people
think that my feathers come from
piercing no no they're growing behind my
ears for real people don't get
[Applause]
it the be the birds and the
be wait the bird at the
Beast the only number was here we could
bring the birds into the
[Applause]
game one the one St the start the start
is like a a
clip you want some of this extremely
painful to get a tattoo style I can
imagine it takes like you can't even do
it in one
session a tattoo that big that's several
session
takes a while that's a lot of pain to go
through
but I mean 18 B tattoo for sure
is kind of insanely nice how should I
have blocked that tell me
game I did not see the
attack so C again and uh what the [\h__\h]
camera I think I will have to sue
you the
[\h__\h] you get banned from on yeah but
honestly do you think I care I don't go
to
on there are a few that allow it so if I
really wanted to go to one I could go to
one that allows it
[Music]
what if you want to take niss to one
again I don't think anyway I said I I
I'm not planning on getting a
t oh this discussion doesn't make any
sense
teleported through the
car I did look into ons sense before
that
um allow or so to say even encourage or
need swimsuits there's a few special
onsens that are made for you to wear
swimsuit
[Applause]
I think one was even like some kind of
specially themed Evangelion
one I wanted to go there but I think
something just didn't work
out now I'm getting more and more over
this feeling thanks to also me going
with
Nissa some don't feel comfortable so if
I find one yeah EV the water was
red if I find one again I might consider
going usually they are just something
about them is really
[Music]
special you you know which one
are you sure that's not
blood it might be
you one shot okay easy
with aachi's
bow and any attack from
chich Roy Wawa Roy waa is forever
gone
frogy oh ultimate T oh finally Kasa has
finally learned in the last what third
fourth of the G last fourth from
probably at this point of the game how
to do ultimate tag team this colossal
killer move can be performed together
with up to four party members whose
hyipe hype meters are
full I don't like this word hype
meters right now because it reminds me
of cringe Tick Tock uh get togethers the
hype house whatever they're called makes
me cringe
oh it's only three of us oh
sad not that I consume any of their
content but I know of them
through that was only a like a
bird for c
c ouch holy [\h__\h]
okay you want
trouble is there something you're weak
to what is
this doesn't seem like to be any of this
at
least I'll
[Music]
just maybe we should try to par
wait can this kind of big enemy even get
paralyzed what I need to
[Music]
heal
uh one person
heal okay for now it's going to be an
item just because
is looking pretty pretty y maybe maybe a
bit more than
200 maybe
300 there you
go oh is it because of their bond with
oh
[\h__\h]
what oh that
sucks maybe a little bit of a
[Music]
I recommend you a pescatarian diet from
now
on if you want to become
stronger those we should go for this one
maybe but multiple maybe not so good for
one
enemy medium medium
heavy
um area heavy
Al do Shadow is he bleeding he's not
bleeding but he's actually confused
paralyzed confused or something like
that greatly the action promp yeah I'll
try I'll try
this yeah
St good on one enemy
oh
shees super no no no no no
no
wow nice block unfortunately I can only
block it on the character I'm
on I
think but okay you
dead you dead
anyway you're not getting another
turn
[Music]
ouch I like how they say that
always like oops I got strong again
hey so cute
[Music]
sorry Ring of Fire is also a song we
should sing during the Euro track stream
[Music]
the only problem
is I'll need to be looking at the lyrics
while I need to be looking at the
street otherwise I won't be able to
drive well uh sing well
I'll definitely Drive worse than
usual but it's not not about
driving distracted truck
yep we'll be getting a lot of bills for
not going in for weighing ourselves
yeah depending on how the next week how
busy it looks I might already do it next
week I don't
know hey excuse me I'm looking for some
people they were last see nearby sorry I
didn't see
them what about people working at the
shops maybe they start something yeah I
was already going to ask
them it's kind of a challenge
her truck simulator challenge mode oh
you oh yeah you probably didn't see
anything
right
byebye I expected as
much what what are they selling here H
oh wow things are way cheaper oh but
that's H just because uh we're talking
dollars here I was like well we earn and
we spend way less money over here
because the currency is different but
here we have Mystic shoes for
[Music]
177,000 yeah maybe
not wait uh oopsie no no
no the rings of fire thanks for the pink
Super Chat by the way
challenges what everyone else does on
the road when me specifically is driving
on the road
MH you're free now meant to do it in
January but mobile didn't have an option
to member TOA ah so I forgot until I
managed to do it on my Xbox for my
what do you not have a
PC
Bia do you not have a PC or
why that's
funny no no no
mercy oh she knows
something you know what I think I have
days ago
though let me see they stuck out since
it was late at night it was just around
here were they okay I mean they they
seem hurt at all sorry it was dark I
could tell they were clutching each
other's hands do you know where they
went toward the feto building I remember
that F building damn that's where y's
Cabaret is
at thanks a lot I got to go she's
fashionable
ball good
looking oh
need wait was there an answer just
recently got a lot of so for real you
didn't have any other
means oh then that yeah
damn makes a lot of
sense mobile would randomly not let you
M for random people that's so
weird oh by the way apparently YouTube
has a new uh
testing for now a new layout but thank
God I don't have it because apparently
it's really [\h__\h] doesn't show up for me
yet
yet hey check out the club boys they're
scotting guess they haven't met quota
yet you mean those are recruiters mhm
and if their job is to scoope out every
girl who walks by they might be just who
we
need we already got some hints though I
guess if one of us is going to have any
luck with that it would be CH hey but
look she's coming back
already no D said they haven't seen any
old women then they offered me a job I
think they all work for yum
screw it this time I'll take care of the
talking all right I tried to tell you
don't send chetos in alone against guys
like
that what but they're not here they were
they were just a
hallucination
oh it's pretty trash you got it I'm
sorry for
you your
it doesn't even let you like the stream
unless you close the chat
box
[Music]
what everybody's looking up
what's
[Music]
happening I was so
casual oh how concerned he
is you
oh come
[Laughter]
[Music]
on you need to calm down and let out
that anger elsewhere my God
how do you get this angry and this
aggressive what's wrong with him what's
wrong with these kind of
people they need like a boxing sack at
home oh you're kind of close
dude
wa actually fight on the
team oh my God
he's on my
[Music]
side I'm
feeling complicated weird
feelings what is this feeling
guys I need to look cool for him I need
to look cool in front of
[Music]
him I need to leave a good depression
okay where can we get a
couple I could get
free I'm
here don't
Mo oh we did get four nice nice nice
y standing right here I eat the fire of
my St
board he's so
cute I can fix
them nice at least two of them
come
on oh
hey don't hit a lady from
[Music]
behind that's some
decency ouch
bsection bye to that section of my body
I guess bye-bye he cut it off
[Music]
who do we want to kill they all
resist wonder if I
[Music]
can is joh the way I mean
collateral
damage wait they're fighting on their
own did I turn that off on it did
I I turned it off again I think
now wait no I guess I turned it on
what's
Happening Now I turned it off
again what's happening when is it on
when is it off
[Music]
well I mean now it's
just yum
fighting okay there we go something
weird was happening I swear it was the
same setting now as it was when Ichiban
did something on his own but maybe that
was just a followup attack for
yumay
confusion I
yeah yeah I see the bottom left
thing I don't know if you guys saw it
properly cuz my head is maybe in front
of
it then I got confused and I I because
now it says Auto on even though it's off
like it's like the other way
around but because I saw itan attacking
I thought oh okay maybe I pressed it
accidentally so I turned it the other
way and then it says Auto
off so I was like okay but there wait
what's going
on
confusion I feel like this happened
before
[Music]
you think I'm
stupid he resists our attack but I feel
like we could make it y do you want to
help no oh we couldn't make it
interesting should have thrown in a
skill I guess
[Music]
Overkill
sheesh Y show me what you got
he's just kind of [\h__\h] cool but he
also scares the [\h__\h] out of
me I don't think his personality would
be anywhere
near something I could work with though
I
roll
someone so hey hey oh okay someone so
like monotone and
gloomy and
sarcastic that just sounds like a recipe
for
fights hey
all right I think we need a little bit
of heing for
everybody it's the Bromans now
tick
tick coconut shower oh yeah thank God
here in this team we have a Healer
but where's
everybody
uh hurry up let's
go so scattered these suckers
that's all you got I can try to
get don't think don't think maybe I have
the tippy toes of
ichan NOP only me
okay yeah
B yeah I thought you didn't need it I
guess damn it could have gone
closer to
[Music]
let's
go nice block today I'm honestly pretty
good at blocking even attacks that I am
seeing for the first
[Music]
time oh thank God finish that one
lock okay I think we need something to
heal call the whole Squad because we're
growing like V big time it's for
yourself and your P awesome and they
don't need to be close no they have to
be close
and he is far far far from
saving all the way over there can you
come closer buddy eyes
on H up let's go oh wellow should I
still do it feel like I
should Tommy is next on you let's go he
could heal himself if we feel like
it how
fun Should I heal him I think we should
just do Soul Capture
[Applause]
yeah
nice he's a do it myself kind of guy
Tommy isn't that right
Tommy that makes the timing even more
strict but you dodge instead of block
and negate all the
damage oh
wow but if the timing get it's even more
difficult to hit I don't think it's for
me when I hit it I hit it though I feel
like I
do time to take this bastard
down an arrow to his
heart hell is coming down point
you it's so
over
sheesh by the way thank you guys for
letting me take a break
yesterday besides making those chairs I
did take a long naap that was probably a
little bit too
long and I took the
opportunity oh clean a little bit
and change my sheets and Chang to Sumer
blanket and changed also the pillow
again I have several different pillows I
switched back to an older one and I feel
like it was more comfortable than usual
this time with this older
pillow so I might use it
again sorry I didn't sign the PO Awards
I will sign them next week for
sure I think I'll have
time but yeah I think last week I was uh
this
week I was feeling a little bit low
energy because
just trouble of sleeping whenever I
sleep I have nightmares and then and
then it's so uncomfortable I wake up
with like really s sore body
muscles and just
generally wasn't wasn't in the
best condition not too bad either but
just felt like my body needs a little
recovery
period
know I figured one thing out
though I figured out how to stream with
my accent to I
think so most likely next week's member
stream will be the 3D dancing stream
yay I I'll learn dances on the spot I
was thinking the nity uh uh kaaa
dance and and the S say s by B DEA
dance and uh for Miki her new song I
want to learn that dance and whatever
else we can think
of yeah
giraffa giraffa fan meeting that one is
so cute if if you guys remember any that
whole life members uploaded recently
that have a dance to
it let me know more recent ones though
not like dances from a year ago
ideally actually we could it doesn't
have to be from an MV it also could be
uh like the Coro could be taken as a
reference from one of their if if they
had like a
recent uh birthday or anniversary life
or so I could look at that too
yeah just send me when I put up the
reservation you guys can send
me of whatever dance you want me to
learn I'll put it on my list and we'll
see how many we can learn and record I
cannot do Kon
[Laughter]
flip then we record little YouTube
shorts or at least the motion data will
be recorded and I'll send it to check
and check it can fix it up for
me make it look
good I think it will be a nice
stream if there's no
scuff wow okay thanks y
uh we're into
scuff to be permanent
not
companion not colleague what's the
word I do think like it makes sense if
he becomes of like a more permanent Ally
because the game while throwing him at
us as an enemy so many times I think the
game knows the game creators know that
he grows on you even through all these
negative
um
confrontations he
just somehow something something about
him you just like seeing him you're
happy every time you see him
again that makes sense
cuz the reason why he was looking for
akan
and why he was like fighting Us in the
end it was just because like he had this
order but he doesn't really like care
for it he just like you know he's just
doing it because because he's doing it
but he might as well join our side
doesn't have a good reason to be against
us he's got so
hard and that's a good thing being a
[Music]
real
for yes yes that's the best we
have
fore foree
spee on
wait what what what I thought
what wait why must we F I
thought wait
what when we about to like hug and shake
hands and say yo welcome to the
team oh I provoked him okay so if I win
he's probably going to help us out but
like well that's that's not really what
I expected what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay this this I like this skill cuz it
does big damage but it's kind of hard to
find the right position as it's like the
weird shape
like where does this start it starts
like behind the enemy that I'm
selecting like
what where is y my uh all the way in the
back
whatever epic music
JoJo PO is very
necessary he's weaking as water but I
should take off the the smaller ones
first huh is this does this have grapple
no merciless Mele has
grappled all
right oh it doesn't even kill
[Music]
boy's
go you my mama
my you are my mama
my
nice yeah ichiban's attack reminded me
again of this song because there's a
boogie boogie
attck he's so shiny he's so sparkly that
effect is the same effect we used in my
Chima
MV that one scene where there's a right
before the idit makes it big
entry you know in the black background
with the with the this kind of effect
that's also one of my favorite scenes
pop threee
he's following
me yeah the
particles look so
cute use your best attacks
okay Mor scales to to enemy area ooh in
a line
[Music]
is it worth is this worth it we'll
try oh makes them
sleepy W they snore so
loud wake him up they're
loud I don't like the snoring
sound no
stop
snoring we should choke them we should
choke them while they're sleeping oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh I I mean same attack so
I should have seen it coming but not
sure at what time you have to
press little bit earlier
probably Boogie boie b
b let's go
[Music]
should I
heal what not going to help anyone but
me
[Music]
probably maybe one more attack on the
minions do we
[Music]
have no weird
awkward this one perhaps enemy
area pretty big this could hit yeah yeah
yeah and if we focus it on
yamay he's weak on it wow okay there was
a lot going on
there I hit at least three people
right look at that person at the sushi
bar limbo over there just standing at
the entrance there hands
together
look are you having fun observing this
or are you just like
man why did I open up shop here this is
the worst place there's always some [\h__\h]
going on
outside always so much trash on the
streets because of these
dudes just come here and buy some
[\h__\h] Sushi and calm the [\h__\h] down
Sushi makes people happy I'm sure
why did they open a store on fight
street right next to the fight
club all right all right all right
[Music]
right yeah let's try this
one [\h__\h]
missed
one cuz it's really
fast a new one again cych and we still
have so much MP damages a wave of
enemies main flict
bleed appli your weapons ATT I don't
know if it's worth
it maybe just burning arrow is
nicer he resists
fire I don't know this is worth
it like this one I mean maybe this I
don't
know let's try this
one oh [\h__\h] I wait those so fast first
time I saw
it everything's happening so
fast ouch
well I she at least was a better Target
than ichan for that thank
you for having
Mercy okay okay okay not bad not
bad ultimate take team
time only two
[\h__\h] I should have checked how many
people already
oopsy the way they walk
away ah only only
uhoh oh
man what's this Bes the god to strike a
random magic damage at the start of oh
that one's pretty cool
[Music]
probably
heal um
ichom
but I wonder if I if it's okay to just
use mask of
fertility how big is the first heal that
they
get or it's just not happening yet
uhoh
uh-oh okay okay okay okay he resists it
and he was the best Target he could have
chosen cuz he still has the most
HP yeah yeah you're just charging
something
okay
[Music]
fine m
I don't
know I think even her simple attacks are
really
strong when I look at the other ones I'm
not sure what to
[Music]
do H okay
okay agility stack
okay okay maybe this time I can get it
right oh W is free
okay two out of three damn damn
we only have 45 MP left on him and yamai
still has so much
HP maybe I should not only go for the
high MP
attacks want to do something fun like
this though at least once it's only
power light damn but every round it
might be fun it might be nice
yeah should be good extra
damage yeah boogie boogie B bang a
[Music]
aloha aloha to you too
sir
yeah h
[Music]
a you guys said I should follow up with
this
[Music]
one oh [\h__\h] four times wait was it only
two times last time because I missed
them I feel like they were less last
time who I hit them all this
time y yby yby
Abby no
prompt
uh
yes should be
good get stronger ah when you have more
agility
Buffs makes
sense my [\h__\h]
God we got burned CLE got stunned
Al is also close to dying oh no please
don't
what oh thank God ichan is not in that
line of attack
OMG ah I think I have to use one of
those uh everybody heal items because I
mean it's really only Ian and AD
but uh you don't have a healing do you
yeah I think I need to
use like a smoothie or hand mixed fruit
cup but
4 I don't know it's only two people
really needed what if I heal ADI on his
own and then itan separately on his own
you know what I mean CU it's not like
Yama is attacking right
away maybe that's
acceptable yam is judged from
above is it my chat's
judgment h I will use his turn to
heal ich
bomb and then hopefully he's not stunned
anymore he probably will be by the time
of his turn
[Music]
let's stack him
up
again okay he's stunned he gets a little
break I
guess uh-oh don't stand in a line don't
stand in a line I
said I saw that
coming
ouch
ouch oh oh she's not doing so
well she has a heal but she has no MP so
let's give her a good item that has MP
and
HP maybe the egg
[Music]
or stamina XXX X X XX x x x x x
x x
little do damage more or
[Music]
less no no no I wish we had a water
skill on him
[Music]
too do we have a good debuff maybe or a
good buff boost our defense
[Music]
Can I stack the healing no right
probably
not attack item yeah good idea good
idea good idea actually water ice ice
damage yeah yeah yeah we can throw the
modified liquid nitrogen spray
or yeah let's throw that
or no the healing run out is it not the
plus plus
plus that I
[Music]
see oh that's actually less than
300 is it up to 300 I was hoping for
300 no don't be
stunned yeah it only ran out on Cheo
interesting
[Music]
no he's not bleeding
H let's maybe inflict bleed oh wait is
he ah he's wait we need a
grapple what do you mean he has no
grapple why does he have no
grapple
whatever we'll try
anyway apparently I have no grapple but
that doesn't suit a
samurai bleed bleed
[Music]
bleed oh maybe one more or yeah one more
what who he's zooming around he's
showing me his own abilties
[Music]
I can't believe I blocked
that ooh counter
St but what was it magic does not get
countered
or but these uh probably gets
countered attack from the
distance yeah I guess I have to
shoot let's just throw some
shoy I wonder if that's fine yeah I
could also heal her cuz she does need
healing again wait should we do coconut
[Music]
shower oh
maybe need
[Music]
the don't know if it will hit
ichon that's
okay oh yeah I can Target them but it's
okay I needed it the most
for
um but he's still in the counter stance
right
he's still in it
yeah let's do some magic oh no stay away
wait does this get countered no right
okay he got scaringly
close that I want to do my my tuna
attack but that will get
countered anchor to the blinker perhaps
or oh wait there's a few new ones
Preston
[Music]
Carver I think this is my best
option only 160
lame can we shoot I like the dreaming
Arrow 600 yeah yeah
yeah that's what I'm talking about is
there Jil
gone but does it just go away what all
at once
NY so you didn't count get countered by
anybody how you like that
huh that one's kind of crazy it's hard
to oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh sh oh
sh please leave me
Al
who holy [\h__\h] the burn how much damage
does the burn
do I need to heal
him come on
[Music]
Mom otherwise it's game over
my
skills but we could do ultimate attack
team now where does it
say where does it say who is ready for
it how do I know how many people are
ready for it ah wait the the endless
Circle thingy never mind that's it so
it's only with Tommy now it's not even
that strong with two two people but now
that I can't use a skill this is
probably better in that case than just
attacking normally
maybe
maybe might as well use
it add the infinity time I forgot but I
found
it oh this looks
strong but last time it was really
disappointing 320 that's okay that's
okay I critical hit rate got raised as
well yeah we're almost
done wow oh wow okay we're
done 9,000 this fight was uh quite
challenging needed a lot of healing
[Music]
many levels many ranks reigning Arrow
skill
y
fore foree
oh my God we're allies now who would
have
thought that will ever
be we really needed some allies
[Music]
he does seem like the type that any
mommy would
like he comes back
she probably has some good
Intel we got to
go your face pisses me off you face
pites me off sorry I almost born with
this
face I can't do anything about it
really can we get those guys to move
[Music]
faster air
gun how
fun safey hey you there
no am I on the leveled I
wonder would be good to upgrade our
equipment but I feel like I'm getting no
break I mean I don't have to go directly
there
but feels like I'm
being forced to
go but I'm
not it feels like it
you think I'm fine okay okay same level
yeah it's more like undergeared I think
so too what do you want to talk about I
be absolutely sure you
[Music]
yeah
no yeah why you searching for these two
in the photo oh these two cuz one's my
mommy not my she
is except now it turns out the whole
hawaian underground thank you is after
her even y only just recently called off
his
search her life's in real danger that's
why we got to get to her and
fast and you one more Criminal on her
Trail what would you do if you actually
found
her plan is to together to Japan we have
people that can move her
safely look what's your
lady be straight not
European I'm yeah I'm from
Hawaii huh you better not be joking us
off here what what did you say boy yeah
same question jeez I'm sorry for him
ma'am but you must have something to
tell us
right at least one of you has some
manners okay please oh go you boss then
that information won't be free 10
grand money is hard to come by you know
that why do people charge just like in
The Witcher so much money for
Intel here we are again guys I watch
something I compare everything with
it I was also thinking um our mommy is
running around with that child right
that reminds me of yenfa with
Siri they're not
related but she seems to be probably
right now like a mommy character for
that child and they're on the run it's
exactly like with yennefer and Siri
because everybody everybody really just
wants the child Siri AKA
lannie it's it's literally The Witcher
what the whole Hawaiian underground you
said that means it's worth a pretty
penny we didn't say it like that could
have been less oh man you stupid old
sussy bucker oh look away I'll see if
the gangs cut me a better
deal you haven't offered this to anyone
else have you h no congratulations here
the
first miss you really don't want to take
this to those guys The Gangs here don't
negotiate they more likely to torture
the in yeah for
real torture the info out of you not
even Pana
trustworthy so hold on it's 10,000 you
want that's a lot but at least it's not
like six figures a lot it's doable then
uh yeah I guess I mean I already have it
I
[Music]
think we can get some money gain a few
levels all in one
goal what do you mean are you telling me
to do to go somewhere to gain more
money thaton his life at stake yeah
we'll make it doable who come on man
you're not really considering this are
you it's a risky bat I know but [\h__\h]
we're out of options here scrunching up
that kind of cash will take some time do
I not have the
money I thought I had the yeah Al I got
like n Grand just now oh yeah I got the
money she wants 10 grand
right before anyone asks I can't use my
name for a loone oh what am I
miscalculating
something why do we need a loan why are
they talking about a loan I have money I
just fought for 9,000
Grand if you were at this point in the
story you're forced to have just had a
fight where you get 9,000
Grand uh no we real find a away we just
got 9,000 Grand wink
wink canonically we're broke I guess
so we have 44
yeah we're fine but I also want to go
upgrade
my weapons I
think uh which was
where yeah oops no
[Music]
44,000 the the fs on the 44 are supposed
to be
FS it's not even that
weird um I don't know let's
see
wait uh uh gear
huh four should I have five star knives
fin now this is still only fre
star got to check if we can make a new
one for him the tribal ax I think we
should can we upgrade that but maybe not
I don't know we'll
check threee four
star
um so can we make a new surfboard are we
even staying as a surfer we cannot make
a new
one I
need can I buy a cloud board in a shop
somewhere it's a fourstar
surfboard yeah where where are they
selling that
uh wait how do
I is that what you were saying oh maybe
here no surf no life H 5,000 oh it's
pretty
affordable and there's a little chitchat
over
there what you looking at what what you
looking at
what you looking at what you what you
looking at what you looking at what what
you looking
at I'm
fearless yeah let's get that one not the
140k no
no no the 5K you're going to get that
one then craft it into something
[Applause]
cool what what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] what what are you staring
at
what what what they're just some random
blue people in a golden
car wait why am I going this
way what was that
entrance I mean golden card kind of
siake yeah
he used to
Surf Aloha me too I used to surf and
turf okay buying
this even that is already a lot stronger
thank you it will get even stronger
after I craft it something
else I might when I go back now realize
that I need other weapons too craft
stuff for the other ones but we'll see
we'll see we'll
see one thing after another we're going
to check them off one by
one serve and serve serve serve
some
Turf shark two sword ooh that's like the
the uh was it was more like a dagger
that was the dagger equivalent of the
shark tube sword that we
found
interesting look at all these people in
the Hawaii shirts you could think you
could
think we were in uh Tire celebrating
sonan okay I
guess I don't have enough electric
geod
oops no okay for now we'll carry this
one I
guess um what can we make for you we
were we would also be missing the ice
shields but we have the shark tooth long
sword we're only missing
three free ice geod and a couple of
electric
ones and okay here we just got the
perfect one for her shark to short sword
I just got that one need a few more ice
geod in the Hawaiian hun you mean in the
dungeon right you can exchange ah rob me
too yeah cuz we didn't exchange anything
previously so we might have some good
choice oh he we can make his one already
though wait isn't that what he already
has no I guess
not this stronger so I guess he doesn't
have it it looks like what he had before
but we can make it
amazing
SC out of the tribal ax which he is
using right
now okay I mean we have the we have the
base weapons for most of these things
except for the one for
ichan no
problem no problem more okay so we need
six electric ones and I think six ice
ones
the darkg food the thing the dungeon was
somewhere here yeah I remember this one
where it was oh my God for once I
remember a
location an aluminum bat at one of the
malls for each mother gets B damage but
I don't need a bat I want to stay
Surfer n
CHS oh the same
item right around the
corner if you want to do both The Sword
and the dagger you'll need eight oh oh
my God math thank you tiny
Del oh wait no I don't want to enter
sorry this never mind
oh oh cool thank
you exchange there we
go 18 ice geod
right oh I think I can get
enough
meth 18 I think ice G wait
18 ice
GE and what was it five
electric
CL I
think uh six
electric 15 per weapon wait do I need
more
ice Sonic
no I'm good
okay you guys do the maap I do the
buying the
[Music]
purchasing Okie
doie wait was there maybe a conversation
close by not
really
maybe I'll go here to have those two
bonding conversation St yeah okay
there's two down
there yep yep yep yep let's y literally
let's
Yap let's
yap yap to
win he likes
coffee okay and then I think over
here was a dog
bye-bye oh silver blade thank
you kind of useless but
okay there's another one over
here
collect what does that
[Music]
mean are there any trees I can take over
here I want to bnk some trees there we
go potato
[Music]
chips should I get my snack I'm not even
that hungry but I feel like I should go
snack
now go get that
snack cuz otherwise later it will be too
close for when I eat dinner
why is this always
coconuts you guys said I get some other
stuff too right but somehow it's always
coconuts coconut coconut coconut
[Music]
coconut Mar
bouet sometimes it has valuables that's
a coconut but I thought you guys meant
sometimes the coconut trees also I know
it makes no sense but sometimes they
drop something else too cuz where else
do you get the other
things wait that increases my base
MP X skills me do I have more items like
this without
knowing or was where did that
go I here oh I do have a couple
H I didn't
know as an action star nobody's an
action star now right my Bice
agility Bas
MP MP is really good for
everybody Tommy Heth
current
[Music]
job everybody
okay we'll see
who's um leave me
alone but okay one enemy I'll take you
down in an
instance what could be he resists
guns actually I'm thinking about this
more than I want to I'll just hit you
normally oh he's Turing his next oh
you yeah water I have no
water
yeah that always feels so good
[Music]
what's this place can I buy something
no you have thank
you 2 years and 3 days now without
interruption thank you so much for
always staying a member thank
[Music]
you our supporter I hope you've been
enjoying the members content you guys
are winning oh thanks for the poe you
guys are winning you guys getting
members streams
weekly
and cute
wallpapers and a 3D stream next week
wow wow what am I running around here
for I was going to go back here
right lost drag
wow I'm honestly a little bit too shy to
commission like
stack spicy wall papers so normally I
just go for
some pretty innocent
fee I know some members release pretty
spicy stuff but I usually I put my order
in
indirectly like
I JMA does like the initial contact with
the artists and then I tell them pretty
much directly what I want and so I feel
a little bit too embarassed to be
like can you draw me really spicy with
like you know this and
that it's not necessarily something
I feel like I need for myself either and
yeah yeah so just
um maybe sometime every once in a while
I could do it but I feel I feel too
embarrassed um but did you see we talked
the other day we talked about me wanting
to go strawberry hunting and then I
asked the members what they want to see
in the next members wallpaper and then I
had the idea of doing like a strawberry
hunting wallpaper F and so
Wawa collecting strawberries out in the
field and then now one of my favorite
artists who I also commissioned before
for a wallpaper di drew me Callie and
cobal
together uh collecting strawberries and
it looks so cute oh my God it's like
they read my
mind it's such a cute idea right I
wonder if they threw it because they
heard me talk about it or if they at the
same time as I'm planning my strawberry
picking wallpaper at the same time they
also had the idea of drawing me with
others strawberry picking picking what
is this coincidence if it is a
coincidence I love
it okay making the storm board who I
hope we'll be happy and satisfied with
this one for a while although I wonder
will we be I hope
so cuz like four
stars we've been carrying four stars
things around for a while I feel like
but actually maybe only on the other
side
in in
Japan so maybe this is
[Music]
fine
waste all my stuff
you made me buy strawberries twice
already I also bought some decent
strawberries the other day and I noticed
it's spargle
season wo it's spargle season I saw
Sparkle in the supermarket the green one
I need to cook something with sparkle
sparle and then I also saw it's be
season cuz the other day like maybe one
or two weeks ago I saw in the
supermarket
baow which is uh like a really nice herb
like basil similar but more wild that
grows wild out there all over in Austria
in the forest you can just go to a
forest and pick a [\h__\h] ton of it and
make like a pesto out of
it um what's ba of
anglish a wild garlic but it has
honestly nothing to do with garlic in my
mind it's it's not I don't think of
garlic when I eat this usually b u you
can make some really nice pesto out of
it Wild Garlic have you had wild garli
something uh like some sauce or so with
wild garlic before it doesn't look like
wild garlic I don't know it's just the
the the leaves of it oh yeah yeah you
can mix it up so maybe you shouldn't
pick it yourself but yeah I don't
know but yeah it's m there's some
poisonous plant true yeah yeah I heard
about that last year when I was talking
about it with my friend cuz we had we
had it everywhere we were you know
remember when I went hiking with my
BFF and her rbff my
rbff and and and and in the forest that
we went through there was so much Wild
Garlic it smelled so nice oh my
god oh dear an old couple died oh no but
yeah so so it's it's a great season for
many things for sure Sparger is which is
asparagus yes yes the green asparagus
please and and the wild garlic and soon
strawberries I want I wanted to buy the
wild garlic and make something out of it
but but but but then I was like uhuh I
have to cook the things from Hello
beep I I don't think I have time to cook
something extra and I wouldn't know how
but it was very tempting
y but I want to do something with the
asparagus just even simple
pasta with chicken and asparagus would
be
amazing Ro uh this one we already
made this
one
here meal Lon sword that looks like
something
a certain villain that we already
F would use who who am I thinking
of and the maet
guy KN they're
matching Den
DWI yo okay
now if we
can we should upgrade
it oh oops wrong oops wrong
wrong they're the same strength but this
one's plus
eight okay
so depressing when they're the same
strength and I just made something new
I'll make you plus eight
too I should sell the other things also
what the [\h__\h] diving knife why I not get
that earlier
huh why' you let me wait for so long
wait he's not even carrying it is
he need to make him carry
it this is
okay
yeah need to switch them out and sell or
uh exchange the I don't know if I can
exchange the other weapons I have
can
I wait let me Che H not
no yes
my plus 10 jet Sur for did I use so
much time
to say
goodbye really 15 IR ore Keep It For The
Memories which 15 IR ore keep it for the
element I don't think I'll need it
whatever goodbye
[Music]
damn actually I have so much stuff that
I don't need
um I'll keep some of these just in case
if I need
them
but yeah
[Music]
I got some good base items for all these
classes I already have the four star
base
items would be a good idea maybe
to them at least for the Japan G
H what happened to my jrpg hoarder
mentality it didn't affect this really I
I wanted to get rid of this stuff I just
didn't
really have the
opportunity just yet but I wasn't
purposefully hoarding
it oh my God so much
materials did I get a good Mount yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah uh yeah okay upgrades we didn't
upgrade his storm board
yet
maybe
mhm well I can make so much more now oh
really
being useful for me now probably
not plus
eight plus seven maybe one
more of course I'm still on you're
always welcome in the
Stream there's always a home way for
you uh wait branding sorry I'm like all
over the place brand
uh what what okay what do we have what
do we have well I can't unlocks that
enhancement level 10 oh yeah right I
need to get them all to
10hm
mhm mhm mm
m
[Music]
m mhm m
okay ooh uh wait wait what she does use
gun attack sometimes right we could we
could uh strengthen
that what should I strengthen or the
plate
attacks yeah still need 10K yeah have B
I think maybe maybe
we use both a lot I think for
[Music]
her basic attack down always
okay we don't want these too expensive
ones right now I
think dagger fro gun yeah crit would
also be good for Kuni
specifically the crit one is so
cheap I don't know 5% is if anything
than this
one shall I
invest we may have to change weapons in
a chapter or two already then I'm not
going to invest too
much then I'll I'll put the gun one in
there
[Music]
and for him
uh strengthen a bit more to
10 what do you mean I already have to
change
[Music]
again this better be worth it uh for
him
uh he has a lot of fire attacks if my
memory
doesn't uh
deceive me but this is only a small
boost I think CU it's
only5
okay I didn't look do I didn't do his
one yet I think
brand his I don't remember a specific
element in his
attacks um he has a lot of blunt ones I
think right or should I should I just do
base attack
maybe can
basic oh crit oh [\h__\h] no but then
there's only the the super cheap one or
the super expensive one no in between
kind of bothers
me did I do
yours no
[Music]
maybe I think I want to boost ice
attacks I used ice attacks a lot on him
but I just a
[Music]
five why hold back because I'm switching
apparently again in one or two
chapters magic skill wow
right now I'm wasting
money then I use a cheap one what do you
mean I'm wasting
money I'm I have to upgrade the last
fight was pretty
rough no no I'm not wasting money don't
say so don't say it is so say it ain't
so oh no no no no I'm not I'm not
dealing with these
guys uh uh where am I going what are we
doing uh I guess we we're prepared now
so we can go
here
yeah I don't think it's a waste thank
you for staying that even if it might
be yeah yeah yeah I can always get more
money in one way or
another okay me getting up now might
confuse smovie who is still sleeping
behind the monitor wow I just see her
like a part of her fluff underneath but
I'm going to go grab that uh honeydew
melon from the fridge really
fast don't alert smoothie
I'm
back it seems like chunky wonky has been
alerted and is lurking in the hall room
hallway but smoothie is still in the
same
spot I hope these honey DS are good
smells good hi chunky
walking yeahum
okay hopefully we get a cut scene soon
so I can eat
this while we're being
productive you know I hate it when when
there's like free
cut calop or honeydew melon but they cut
it way too close to the edge so part of
it is like way more hard than it should
be
and that's just not not the good part of
the fruit it should be the soft part
only yeah it pisses me off they always
cut it wrong they cut but probably
because they don't want to waste too
much but that part is not really
enjoyable to
[Music]
eat I brought the money and I brought
some extra
equipment yeah enormous Spender
that's our end of the deal time to hold
up yours one question is she seriously
ignoring me what what is it you're right
that if I took his off this offer to The
Gangs they tortur me before paying why
didn't you try to threaten it out of me
too cuz we're
cool look we may be in a race with the
bad guys and everything but let's just
say I want to be able to look I kind of
sound in the eye without knowing I
messed up some old woman to find her
yeah like damn couldn't live with that
that's insane only insane people do that
only psychos do that I mean I consider
it you know for a second or two what
Tomy what Tommy you're kind of
what more darker than I thought but
usually when he tries to do these kind
of things
he kind of
fails if you tried should have beaten
you
senseless tomorrow night the dog's near
Harbor Street what is that it you'll see
it for yourselves now be quiet and go
man she must be a big fan of my original
song pineapple look at those pineapples
up
there you really are the bossiest old
the doc's new har Street got it will be
there
ma'am
okay not all
though either we're meeting there to
have a secret talk or she's telling me
to go there because she knows something
something's going
down I want to get this talk and this
talk I'm like aiming for these bonding
stories this time have you noticed just
because I did some off
screen now I'm like trying to combine my
routes in a way that I can get some of
them done what is this uh no
where is my one is up there
okay cuz bonding is good
right no I'm not want to talk to you I
want to get this case thank
you I you yeah he needs I you needs the
bombs what the [\h__\h] ah there we go
you what what level we need him to be
10 oh cat and
[Music]
police best
Fortune okay and now there's another one
uh over
there
10 calico cat they all
cute I like all all colors all shapes of
Cat every cat must be loved just like
with doggles
really make a paper cup one oh I don't
think I ever did
that or did I maybe I did actually I
might have done it but I don't know if
it really worked
okay we are
going all the way over
[Music]
there there is a couple of chi chats in
the shopping mall but I really don't
want to go inside there now I'm going to
take a little cab all the way to
[Music]
here including bubble shaped dogs of
course doing the roving can help you
unlock a strong summon later on
what was that what did you have to do
for the RoR
thing
see o so close to
bingo we need that Bingo for the Big
Boost I like big boost and I cannot lie
are the dancer Tomy zawa tomwa okay
straight for a Tomy zawa talk H I let
you
talk these other bus can't
deny not you I wasn't waving at you what
do you think you
are please be the Bingo one yes bingo
yeah finally level
[Music]
10 Pancake House oh my God I love how
Hawaii loves pancakes
seemingly I love that that's a
[Music]
thing no
wait do I have everything
now
yeah
y time to go to the bar true
[Music]
oh I always eat this kind of
stuff that's nice
too I love FR toast
[Music]
oh pretty cute
breakfast
yep pretty much same thing
cute I wonder how people in Hawaii how
the restaurants make French toast if
they nail it because you guys know every
time I eat french toast in a restaurant
I'm
like that's not quite it I had one good
french toast or two and then a lot of
other weird ones one really bad one
um I don't know why it's so hard for
people to do a good
job making french toast it's not that
difficult come
on
[Music]
please okay let's go here and then I'll
go out
there sorry I'm literally hunting them
right
now where's are pre-made you think
so nah no way oh he's hungry you want
something does it matter what I give to
[Music]
him he loed
out yeah yeah I'm I'm trying to go to
the main story while
getting some conversations
in had some they were dog water what
French
TOS really are you looking that is a
really
unfortunate 300,000
[\h__\h] really unfortunate experience man
aloh are you looking no I'm not looking
I'm not looking I'm not looking me deny
you they're so angry I hear them bonking
everything
okay oh we're going to the
bar
awesome think we can do a drink
Ling oh more confidence
why are these people so aggressive what
you looking at honly makes me
scared how do I take a photo
again
no makes me scared of going to Hawaii
Man Down pad
okay yo why so
strong
The Hit the Road Jack don't you come
back no more no more no more no more
it's the road J don't you come back
hit the and don't come back no more no
no the Jack and don't you come back
[Music]
no yeah sexy okay nope down one was not
uh yes
haven't found one of these in a
while 25 cents [\h__\h]
yeah hello hi h s
[Music]
bries I shall use this as a
weapon here we are it is time to sit
back and listen to a conversation with
oh all of them oh my god let's
go
enjoy I eat my
melon fore
[Music]
fore
foree fore
foree uh
for maybe she's the
victim you guys like wearing your tinf
hats
huh you want to glue yours on it's C
protects you from evil spirits and from
the Illuminati
what thought there was a fly on my honey
juice maybe it's a seat what
looks
[Music]
weird we're here to share and
care don't worry Tommy
[Music]
no we should
go I mean I don't know
[Music]
foreign speech
how cool you can see the lady outside of
the window
foreign fore
fore fore
um I think that is the answer it's not
like she hasn't given you an answer
you can take it as a
no she's still waiting for an
answer
[Music]
dude he's so
hopeless he's so
okay
[Music]
mhm two more to go guys I'm done with my
fruit but I am not done with
smoothie hello m
v i touch her she goes like
[Music]
what thought she stayed at place
has a whole
[Music]
hotel I don't know
than thank you for 33 month
[Music]
who maybe her Grandpa is the
vtuber thank
you
foree
for
cutee
for that's probably a
lie don't believe
it pick Sor it didn't
happen fore
memberships oh 10 before that thank you
guys watch
[Music]
fore
come okay hi baby she peaked under under
the monitor she's on her back right now
giving me her belly to
rub while
purring in extreme
mode finally Adai
there's another drink
[Music]
link I love the music that's playing in
the background I know the song
[Music]
yes I you should do the same hair
for
yes same as me please
is he actually got a change
[Music]
ever those
spe
[Music]
what's going on guys thanks for the
members [\h__\h]
[Music]
memb thank you
Nathan who would be who if I if the myth
members were Yak
characters might be C
because of
the I don't
know I think there's two NE
overlap K
you I don't know if anybody could be
even
K wait n maybe number
number number could be good
maybe
uh who could be Ena who could
be who could
be who could be
me ichan would be good he has the fish
no that doesn't matter it's more about
personality and their
role he do for am no what are you
talking
about you I was like a little bit
feeling that too
[Music]
but you can also pick from Side
characters like
yum but nobody is y maima majima yeah
for the craziness yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah mean majima is not in this
game but
yeah is Ina
I mean what is it the Sleep the
priv fact sleep the priv fact I don't
know ah the Crowbar okay okay okay I
think there's at least two points why
Ena could be
yay Ena does say she's cold a lot
oh okay well a lot of lot of uh kind of
concern turning overlaps I might have to
put on my tin foil hat and I might even
say yay is
[Music]
Ena and
then
I would
be I feel like I have number Tendencies
too and ichan tendencies to
uh but there are already taken now gave
them away although let's give Ian to me
and let's give
son
to
cie the thing is okay actually son can
be surprisingly dorky if you think about
her um
nervosity when it comes to
kidu um I think she's hiding some
Darkness but I CI is truly way way way
way way more dorky while Soni is able to
hide
it um but at least the first if you
don't talk to them either of them the
first impression could be pretty
similar uh just the visuals are like not
because of the pink hair but just the
cool lady
type if you don't let KY
[Laughter]
talk Kelly is very
dorky
yeah and then I would
bean I guess nobody really fits
such
Nah if anything
a if anyone then
a Tommy Tom somebody could be Tommy zawa
though Tommy Tommy is kind of H
Tommy is an interesting character to
assign Tommy Tom me
is you guys think he'd fit anyone in
my
Tomy difficult me we already gave enough
out so we don't have to force ourselves
anymore Cron's Tommy how how is crony
Tommy they have that Grandma energy
Tommy and
am Tommy Gremlin a little bit he can be
a little bit Gremlin like
sometimes GAA can be Alo
happy no no no no no no if anything am
or me are Alo
happy no no no
don't think tell me fits anyone right I
would
agree so did I forget anyone from the
main
[Music]
members no I don't think I
would assign her to anyone of us
H I don't know she's still hard for me
to figure out
she she's pretty
cool but she might um be actually
backstabber she might be deceiving us I
have to wait until the very end to make
up my mind about
her Iris
oh I mean we just were talking about
myth but yeah I could I could see Cheo
say on Iris at the moment I don't know
Chito says full deal just yet but at the
moment yeah
yeah yeah they're kind of like princess
Vibe okay
anyway should like to hear that
true Iris does have a devil side so
even if cha turns out to
be secretly a
villain even D
might she can be your angle or your
Dev what do you
mean you mean my my
say tin
foil tin foil
[Music]
ification sorry I didn't want to listen
to it
anymore can stop no too much be
careful m
I have to sing
now something is calling
me please
listen this is my
dream he he
[Music]
f
it wait that's cute I don't think we did
this song
[Music]
before the lyrics are really sentimental
a I just barely like noticing what's
going on in the video but the lyrics are
touching my
heart and no mistake what I never had
such a high score
before I think oh my God almost almost
up there top
free
wa
she I played K okay yes I did one more
just one more one more
okay I think all of these are done
before oh let's do this
one summertime groupy
[Music]
[\h__\h] this is
difficult too bad there's no translation
here for non Japanese
speakers cuz they say funny things and
the lyrics are usually super funny
don't
[Music]
don't this is too
difficult oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] he's crying cuz I'm missing
hering yo towel let's go he stole that
from
[Music]
me sh
that was so
Random [\h__\h] that was difficult holy
[\h__\h] they're so bro 100% bro 70 I did
better
before ah go [\h__\h]
yourself I did just fine apparently
there another B I'll just kind of Zoom
through
it we need to make some progress
he it's
important he he saw
her boyfriend was
there oh making out on the Hulu
Beach you think she was happier when she
was with you
H need to get closer no let's not
[\h__\h] intrude anymore if she's if she
has a boyfriend and if she seems
happy you're going to ruin it for her
for
[Music]
relation when she sees him
probably want to be with you again she
ends
relationship we're going to go there
sounds
good well then let's leave her the [\h__\h]
alone yeah IRL don't do
this especially if you were involved
with that lady
[Music]
no no none of this none of
this yeah don't take romantic advice
from the
ichan oh man
yeah I mean it's unfortunate how their
relationship ended but she's she's moved
on and she's happy now with someone
else unless that relationship ends
naturally you should not try to go there
to disturb them even if your intention
is not disturbing them or or tearing
them apart that is uh Poss a possibility
of what might happen so if you find her
again she does not have a relationship
anymore then you can
try not saying that you can't be friends
with your ex but this just feels
like the girl might be like
receptive receptive of like an
ex-boyfriend coming back and being
like I want to be with him again and it
just make stupid
decisions she'll just make stupid
decisions and then it's all [\h__\h] up
nobody's happy
then I don't know maybe she's not that
type of girl but it it can be I feel
like it's really likely to end up like
that hi do you have some
food yeah I got
[Music]
buddies gu attract just how many inters
you've had friend somehow and it knows
if your bonds have deepened then it lens
your
bodies for
friendsies the higher
your okay wouldn't be rushing
oh thank
you that kisss your head in a fight when
you wear it to a
brawl
byebye
[Music]
okay
Aloha give me
food that's that's not
food uh then
whatever thank you I don't want to drink
alcohol I'm out of here wait what am I
supposed to do I was supposed to rest
oops
[Music]
see oops wasn't
me
oh what
well after dark but I head to the
meeting SP where's
she where is she is she V tubing right
now or what
oh why were you late let's check the
channel if there's a new video up H
should
we as dangerous walking around here
alone you
know I said I was sorry s suspicious
Behavior no all good anyway let's get
moving why didn't they show us her
face because it's too
sus hi hi hi it's you B how's that up
treating you come by we both again why
don't you have you ever heard K son sing
col okay it's amazing I can't I don't
know how to I'm sorry
I cannot make an impression where was I
supposed to go what do I where do I go
what is this one this is
ano wants candy well I'll give you candy
and I'll shove it up your
ass because you are deceiving us
I saw there's a conversation here
but never mind I'm not going there I
don't want to I changed my mind you
can't make
[Music]
me how do I where do I
what this park is dangerous it looks
dangerous there's a lot of enemies
there was a pink even but I think
they're probably ready for Pink by
now I would hope
so oh look at the POS
no I am not there I am not here I am
nowhere this would be a decent car
I just want a car that can take the top
[Music]
down ah my chat died Let me refresh yeah
convertible she took the money and play
us like the dumbest [\h__\h] on Earth
keep that annoying voice of yours down
so she's actually here
okay you scaned the [\h__\h] out of me I
thought you were a
ghost do you believe in ghost Tommy lady
we're done we've done everything you ask
us to where's Aran CH of all here
oh you're giving us
some all of the money
back good woman good woman good woman
she probably also thought we were good
people good people good people and thus
she thought
okay I'll be a good
woman I'm not so hard up that I've got
to explore the dumbest [\h__\h] on Earth
wow excuse me and why the hell would get
all this in the first place haven't you
ever heard of putting your money where
your mouth is just a little test of mine
guess I appreciate you being careful and
giving it
back nice that we get it back well you
want us to get in the
boat get in wow okay
[Music]
scary I'm
scared nice cut scene
maybe she just really doesn't want to be
listened
to
oh
fore is
[Music]
it is it a
PO come back from their weird island or
so is she just always on the
ocean are we actually going to get to
see
her actually kind of sick oh
it's
them
oo yenifer and
Siri found
them mommy do you recognize
me no
not
no I'm your son
what that's all we
get Y is here
too in the boat
anymore
what we brought her over
or that
is not
realistic judging by how many [\h__\h] are
all over the island
Hawaii there's no way we could snuggle
her over there but
[Music]
okay
smug I want to snuggle a
smovie shees
YouTu just kidding
no
for we go get to the
point are
you Mommy
for a moment I thought you was going to
say sorry I'm not your mommy
actually
[Music]
foree
for let's go
[Music]
fore speech
I'm know if Japan is the best place
either though but
okay the only choice we
have yeah we didn't
[Music]
know yeah
yeah looks good
though private
jet you know how expensive that is
oh she needs a stream she has a stream
upcoming [\h__\h] she's getting so
suspicious
I 100% up to something
[Music]
yo his tattoos are sicke
you yeah I'm going to get Inked
Up going to get to the best tattoo place
ever you know my
tatonis it's going
to ink all over me
and I'll I'll have you know Zin all over
me when
wait actually makes sense cuz she's an
artist but also because tackle inking
inking by
accident remember there was something
where youa Inked by accident we made a
joke about it didn't
we I'm it was just kind of
[Laughter]
cute coish ordered the K cosplay let's
go
oh amazing times are ahead of
us he wasn't there something like that
with with Ena inking on accident what
there was something like that before
like recently come on not not that
recent but somewhat
recently oh you made me ink that one
octopus and finding new no that was
Ena yeah there was something like that
some
incident what was
it the marker pen leak when you were in
Japan last
year
really myth house when when did I don't
even know anymore either I just know
there was something like that anyway car
is coming take care of whatever you need
before we leave just give me a hul when
you're
ready wa to Japan are we not coming back
to Hawaii
anymore surely we are right I think they
would tell us if we're never coming back
here because then you want to do like
all of the leftover
things I'm
ready I
will there's a clip uh if you search Ena
in I'm asking Ena do you ink
there's something that I'm not
remembering properly but yeah there's
probably a
clip you were talking about it during
the fire BL stream no I don't mean
the I don't mean no no no I don't mean
fire blam stream when she showed up no
no no
no ah you mean ah okay I was thinking
you meant the fire blam stream the early
one where she showed up uh with live Tod
you mean yeah actually when they were in
the background something happened and
they were like oh Ena in
yeah didn't am say that
likea
in she did something behind me while I
was streaming yeah engage yeah see okay
okay so now you understand why I made
that joke okay it was nothing
weird there was a a legit background to
it I'm maded what even
me I said it was cute and G am were
flabbergast what AM was the one who said
it she can't be
flabbergasted something's going to
happen pretty soon I think with Chito
cuz they're just now they're suddenly
throwing on so many
suspicious Acts towards
us of course it's cute that she
Inked because she's the lion
club what is
it what is it what is it what is it what
is it what is it okay why do you need
this just give it to them
just some random accessory you don't
need
it if they stop chasing you then just
give it to them
but palana is a cult why do you want to
have that
cult although you think you can make it
into a better place maybe it used to be
a better
place oh is Bryce wearing a fake one
spee
[Music]
for
for foree
[Music]
price Fair child is not fair to the
children of the P cult at all
ironic more like unfair child
for
inheriting a cult
yeah
MaDee for
[Music]
fore foree
foreign
spee for
[Music]
M
okay but the fact that the one thing
that determines this is the
pendant
like I
mean is there not like documents and
stuff too like yeah he has Forge
documents but she has also has some
documents and she's obviously uh from
the bloodline and whatever she's the air
like there there's the will and all that
like but in the end she's also just a
child so if she goes there and she's
like um Ry please go away um just
belongs to me m go away please like it's
not going to work
either uh yeah it sounds like a medieval
drama yeah like yeah this
[Music]
uh what she going to
do she even want to be the
sage a
child
fore fore
yeah she doesn't even want to do it
probably uh
yeah
[Music]
for
Fore he can for
[Music]
foree
fore
spee fore
man yeah that's that's what I really
wanted to hear the deep conversation
between ichan and his mommy more
please that was not enough
this whole time nobody had seat belts
on really bothered
me
for
Fore
fore
fore fore
[Music]
I love each [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] maybe he's the
vtuber CH the [\h__\h] m a minute
and she
knows and it's just about him he he's
always on the PC and he's always
observing
us it's him he uses a he uses a voice
changer it's
him oh my God he's so creepy he's so
creepy
I'm
sorry of course it wasn't the main
character
[Music]
wait did when they met on the airplane
Ichiban and him did ichan tell him a
little bit too much did ichan tell him
that he's looking for someone AKA maybe
his mom and dad like lit a light bulb in
his head back then already and that's
why he stuck with him and like tried to
find him
again I think I think he too
much or he
already of course they do
yeah
so
mean wasn't there other ways
too try stabbing his
leg daab his leg test it
fore why is he lying down there like
in
[Music]
Australia [\h__\h]
psycho he's a he's a
[\h__\h]
no oh my God I'm I'm so
mad I'm so
angry
no okay how dare
you holy [\h__\h] yo no he's a good
man no hey what the [\h__\h]
right in the
heart
ah not the support
character I wish I could show you my
middle finger right now
and poke in your eye with it so
deep then it comes out of your
ears what the [\h__\h] that was intense I'll
sue
you ah quick get into costumes and let's
[\h__\h] those [\h__\h] up what the the
actual
[\h__\h]
intense that made me really
angry I'm really
angry yeah delusion I know I
know what the [\h__\h] can they be can they
have two debuffs at once I don't
remember if that was a thing I don't
want to override them
can they have blindness and paralyzation
you know thanks for the memberships oh
my God yeah
okay where do we want it maybe in the
back cuz he doesn't have it he doesn't
have
anything they're almost dead already
W did you see how Tommy dived with
me move
Myck yo double double double
double I'm so good I'm just like so good
at this
should we go for the ones
back I'll do
it finally with anti
together that didn't did that kill
anyone at all
yeah I worked really hard on increasing
boms today I did a
lot especially off stream stream
scream see
you 235 of a basic attack damn
actually that's
okay Happ to the best of us was that a
big ass crit or
[Music]
what um I can't believe what just
happened that bastard
honestly I don't think there
were really any signs in his acts but
the fact that he was always on the PC
you know when we think about who could
be a YouTuber and I I was thinking
because there was obviously a voice
changer being used so it is most likely
a guy
makes you realize
it's it must be a guy on this PC and we
noticed that it's somebody who always
knows what we're up to so it was
obviously someone from the
inside well our dear Cho say was helping
though I'm not a guy you can hear
usually from the quality of the voice if
it's a a voice changer or not I mean
nowadays I guess
there's like Ai and [\h__\h] I don't know
how good that stuff can really be when
it's
live but like the pre-recorded ones are
certainly pretty good
huh but still I think notice you can
still kind of notice whether a person is
real or
not yeah she was
blackmailed we have to forgive
her especially in the end she was trying
to like she was getting more and more
like kitty
kitty nervous because she wanted to do
something she noticed like I she doesn't
want to do this she wants to break the
[Laughter]
cycle she didn't say what she was
blackmailed
with
quick far
[Music]
gone we couldn't keep her
safe should have stayed on the [\h__\h]
boat oh wait she's still here okay mommy
still
here at least one
thing
Min um she's not dying is she
dude don't give me that look like oh
it's too late she's
dead guys is dead
[\h__\h]
no hey his eyebrows
moved
man who
was [\h__\h]
up well you'll have to tell us a bit
more
now oh oh that's when the call is coming
in o
[Music]
oh pick
upe
fore
fore fore
[\h__\h] ah that really
hurts but we finished a chapter is a
great ending point
actually
damn chapter 10 would start
now um but we're ending it here for
today we can continue
tomorrow quite the plot
twist I wouldn't have wanted want to be
a bigger character but I would have at
least liked to like end his Arc properly
without him being
[Music]
killed H can we watch a cut Okie doie
Don't Be
Cruel please
fore
no it's because you had Cheetos in your
team
[Music]
for for real
man we can't get worse
unless it K dies
yeah okay we already know who that is
now pretty
obvious pretty obvious
maybe it is
her yeah it is her yeah
okay it could have been him cuz of the
voice changer but I mean any she would
she would obviously want to change her
voice
too I wonder if they made her start
that for all of this or if she wanted to
be a YouTuber already or
cuz she already had a big following
before all the reporting
started
oh wait it sounded way more like a voice
changer in the
video wait her audio quality is
[\h__\h] all the phone audio quality is
[\h__\h]
for
huh she's a
[Music]
[\h__\h] kous
for yeah makes sense yeah
fore
fore yeah
[Music]
foree
spee speee
h n hates it
[Music]
yeah we should just
go go
[Music]
now mhm
okay if you think soe
I guess so yeah that could
be separate
POV you might say
[Music]
o wake
up yeah I mean big leader must have
number of other big leader right
yeah maybe fooled
easily
well yeah
uh I think it's hard you you had to be
there when you talk to
[Music]
S to feel how genuine he was
that's right K that's what I always
say we have us strategy go over what we
know that way will be I'm so hungry
please stop
yapping not B idea then what do we say
do we that survive hard to think of
anywh
better if was all hands on De I suppose
I could call them in them shouldn't be a
problem the balance of V is crumbling
enough as it is who are we inviting I
don't I let you guess wouldn't want to
ruin the
surprise yeah leave us on a cliffhanger
perfect
because this
is door so Hana is dead all he was to me
was my Handler
still a lot happened between us I
suppose so this is one of the memories
he
gets we made it this far and now Hana
leave aanan and land it to us we'll see
this for you I promise you'll all you
always work so hard you deserve to rest
I'll be joining you soon don't say it
like this God damn
it
man crazy [\h__\h]
really crazy
[\h__\h] so I'll save
here and then I'll see you tomorrow for
more but I will read some Super Chat
just a little bit just a little
bit I'm hooked now yeah that
twist and turn turn of events was
very gripping it's got me in a choke
hold
yeah where actually I might know by
myself
to I'll stay in the screen cuz I'm I'm
just
lazy it's just one Mouse click but I
don't want
to I'm on the edge of ma oh well good
sorry good thing is tomorrow we're
continuing you don't have to wait very
long how many chapters are there
again I ask this like every time but how
many are there 13 14 15 16
more
14 okay maybe tomorrow and then one more
stream we could definitely finish it
next week
I think we'll finish it next week with
one more stream next
week sounds realistic cuz we're in
chapter 10 tomorrow I I was like doing a
lot of like bonding and [\h__\h] today
listening to a lot of chitchat yap yap
so tomorrow we could probably do like at
least two chapters if not
threee this is a bit of a grind chapter
ar
oh oh you think I need to
okay we'll see we'll see we'll see we'll
see how it goes how far I get tomorrow
then we can gorge how more how much more
time I
need okay uh it's I think the climbing
stream that I need to
read
[Music]
climbing
thumbnail movie is still behind the
monitor by the way what
what can't believe
it where's my climbing
thumnail
here
simple sometimes is
best
climbing
also I saw several people coming in uh
saying something about coefficient I
already saw it I already reacted to
someone telling me it the first time so
sorry guys uh we're not reacting
afterwards is just because I already
said something about it when the first P
person came in to say something so it's
not that I'm not excited it's just I
already mentioned it and we were deep in
the
story Jacob 47 dun H dun Al beo dun
roader said J D for the pinky oh oh K
let's say that you're sent to a world
where Amma refuses to answer questions
if you try to ask her anything she will
she will always say don't ask me
questions would you still like her
despite this one flaw it would just be
too
[Music]
annoying it would make many things very
very very very very
difficult very difficult
I would still like her but it would make
everything very difficult
but there's a way around it I think you
can make implying statements that she
will try or want to negate if they are
wrong you know you don't have to ask a
question you look forward to
these yeah this one's good Roa you're
getting better at these These are
finally making
like somewhat sense like it's a bit more
realistic and and and I can actually
give a realistic
answer yeah she'll try to correct me
probably even without me asking
questions so we can work around it it'll
be
fine yeah Michael H than PE K thanks for
the pinky thank you so much I appreciate
it Maxwell
than okay can you beat mum as long as am
scream 20 seconds I wonder if I can if I
try it now smoothie will probably run
away I'll
try 20 seconds okay okay
okay let me look at my
timer I'll start in 15 seconds
seconds Four 3
2 am
[Music]
that was 23
seconds I should do probably longer if I
try a few more times but 23 seconds I
beat the record yo whoever Clips this
you can include the rockard deer
sender uh question
alongside that we just talked about
yay buy buy thank you smoothie still
here I can't believe it my cat did not
mind me screaming Amy maybe she's also
Gosling cat takes after
me S well yeah by average I normally
every day spend at least 15 seconds
screaming her name so this was just a
little bit more longer than average
es coma D for the pinky which I wanted
to upgrade from a story point I really
like them and there's a cool feature
where you can carry across your safe and
decisions all the way to which you're
free oh that's crazy cool I don't think
I've
ever had a game that does that but it's
always like this thing where you go from
one game to another and it's like a
sequel and yet you start from level zero
you start with no equipment you start
with no money Etc and you're always
like game doesn't recognize that I you
know we it's not the first time we're
playing this story uh resets everything
I don't know if they
reset they probably reset that stuff too
in Witcher but uh at least the decisions
and stuff are carried over that's pretty
awesome so if you
don't play
those and you don't have anything to
carry across I I wonder if it's just
like neutral stuff then everything's
neutral but the game play is very janky
up to you to decide where you start from
I would start from free yeah um because
everybody recommends it and says it's
not necessarily like connected in a way
that you have to play the first
two
yeah you can simulate it by answering a
questioner oh interesting and also I saw
you guys saying Mass Effect also does
that that's awesome
wow that's really
cool I I can imagine it's difficult to
bring something over to another game
like that so that's probably why a lot
of games don't do it but the games that
put in that effort I
respect oh you can try talk to a
specific guy in the beginning that will
change it if you don't have a save W
cool cool cool
cool nice information thank you Esa
Dusty dun rat dun JC staff dun rice of
free
dun oh this is when I told my my
embarrassing
story space waterful than soon thank
you the gamer cre than
soon oh thank you oh my
God we're we're so connected oh my God
check your channel than you soon FR SCH
than
what do you mean with that type of
clocks you mean also analog clocks or
like military time
clocks I couldn't tell if I yeah this
one I think I
read you learned it for the driving
license test thank God good
job I first learned Am Pm digital clocks
when I was 14
oh you you're ah but you're from Denmark
right
so it yeah cuz like you probably
normally would say like also in military
time just like we do here in Austria so
that's okay that's that's not something
to be
too like feeling negative about
Chad are you live wake
up I never learned how to ride a bike
and I can't
swim
H yeah okay okay that is two big skills
in life that you might want to learn but
there's also a lot of people who don't
know how to do it
so no need to feel too bad about it
space wonderful I never went skiing or
ice skating before I cried in front of
my crush before in school I I'm scared
of big spiders I can't 10 type on
keyboards the 10 finger typing thing to
me is probably the most uh funny to me
because like everybody who can't type
with 10 fingers on their keyboards to me
looks
like a a big
Boomer or a a complete Tech
[Laughter]
idiot how do you get 10 fingers only
have
eight you do have you have none but
yeah
rude tying with two
fingies that just takes ages oh my God I
feel like I just like naturally because
I got a PC really early and you know
back in my day when I had the age that I
had a
PC at at was not normal at the
time but I really early on was early on
in my life I was a lot on the PC so I
just picked it up really
fast yeah back in my
day my my typing
speed I don't know how fast that would
be it also depends like I one thing I
get confused with all the time is I'm
never sure
about my Z and my y cuz depending on the
keyboard that I have activated cuz I
have to switch to uh Japanese keyboard
uh every once in a while when I type
something in Japanese and then that
makes the Z and the Y's change
positions and also other things like at
or question marks like all kinds of
special signs they're not actually where
they should be anymore and uh my
keyboard the
actual object
uh I think a Japanese layout right now
so but then that confuses me when I have
German keyboard on the on Windows turned
on
because it doesn't match right so anyway
everything is very confusing because of
the language switching that I do if it
wasn't for that I would probably
remember where everything
is now I'm always like second guessing
myself and like uh
testing yeah I mean I I Remember by
heart how to get an at sign for example
in a German keyboard which is by the way
the at sign is different I think in all
free English like American keyboard
German and Japanese keyboard the ad sign
is in a different position each time I
would remember how to do it on the
German keyboard but I'm just often not
really sure on what keyboard I'm on in
the moment and then I mess it
up I never REM remember how to get it
with the English keyboard though
yeah sometimes I do I am on the English
keyboard too on Windows but
yeah it's confusing everything's so
confusing it's different places on the
US and U UK keyboard yeah it's just like
H too many different keyboard layouts
over the
world
yeah so that messes things up yep yep Y
where was I oh yeah miss my greatest
cring was when I was 12 going up to a
panel of voice actors at a con and
thanking one for his role in another
game and how inspired I was but I mixed
up my generic white guys and thought he
was another person
oh well you were 12 I'm sure they didn't
like think you know like anything bad
but I'm sure it happens
to anyone who's not two extremely famous
like I don't know freaking Angelina jul
or I don't care um yeah and with voice
actors they're they're not really
selling their face so often a lot of
people don't know what they look like so
it's
understandable you CH
D thank you or original lost wolf D
thank you
[Music]
same I guess looking for the top t t I
need to ask my dad for computer advice
regularly he works in it and I just
never picked up the skills many other
people in my age did oh are we also
talking about
keyboards SL fellow than I keep
forgetting the order of months not that
bad until you have a meeting about a
project worth a few million and get
asked for a date three months away okay
okay okay actually
I think nowadays I don't have this
anymore but a couple years ago I also
still felt
like I'd mix up the order
of um September October no yeah just
just September and October I think I
would sometimes have to
think pretty
hard and then I was really happy in
Japanese uh language it's just numbers
ichu and so on somehow that is uh easier
to
recall yeah but I actually don't have
that issue anymore
surprisingly it just went
away I mix June and July quite often oh
I wouldn't mix it up cuz that's when my
birthday is July sry September and
October technically so are what
what's what means eight month that's a
10th on the
calendar that's [\h__\h]
up what why did that happen Caesar you
little
[\h__\h] used to have this oh used to have
this before I started working daily with
bills and voice and stuff that that deal
with
M seems actually little bit common
huh I think it's because I think I think
I think I know the reason so it's uh
maybe it's a bit different from German
to
[Music]
English
September October November December see
I had to think but I think the reason is
because those last couple of months they
all sound kind of similar and have the
same amount of syllables and the same
way the word ends
ER while the others all sound
individually more
special January and February those two
are similar but those are the two first
ones you're not going to you you're
going to know when January is January
February uh March
April May June July those all sound
really
unique August 2 and then it starts
September October November December they
just sound too similar and have the same
length as a word so that's I think why
people uh struggle with those in
particular that's why I struggled with
them
mhm yeah
yeah H they literally mean 78 9 10 but
then they're not 78910 what the
[\h__\h] cuz those months are m
kind of kind of kind
of oh and I guess sometimes I have to
think H one one thing I have to do is
because in Japanese language they're
numbers they're just numbers there's no
name like this like January Etc when I
have to translate a month like let's say
uh sh gotu I have to count in my head
first sometimes y febr m April that that
is the fourth
one to make sure I know what month we're
talking
about yeah not with every month like
like seventh Shu in Japanese 7th month I
obviously know it's July then 12th month
I obviously know it's December and
October certain ones are very obvious
but but maybe the third fourth the third
and fourth or maybe cuz
it's n yeah cuz then I get confused
with M April May March April
May the m the m months and the April in
between why am I exposing myself so much
huh why am I just like making myself
seem dumber and dumber to you guys
voluntarily no one knows you number one
come y I'm
unstoppable cuz I want to make you feel
better for saying you forget the order
of the month you know I also do kind of
Na thanks for the pink for the Super
Chat not pinky this one time in high
school I tried to troll my friend by
pretending I had a girlfriend and even
made a fake Facebook proof of her but
then he believed me and I kept it up so
well that people at school started
asking about her I even had to do a fake
RP on my real account and fake one then
some guy at my school figured it out and
made a calla post and taged everyone I
still cringe to this
day H High School o did you ever have a
high school reunion that sounds
rough that sounds really rough
I feel like I must have at some point in
my life probably done something similar
where I would role play as someone else
I probably
[Laughter]
did never I a time of really weird
[Music]
decisions yeah I I I I don't know maybe
there were high school re reunions from
my high school but since I never
finished it and I was never too long in
one class they probably never considered
inviting me so I don't know if one
happened if that one happened if one
happened which is sad I would still like
to go even if I didn't finish the school
together with
them I would like to know but I don't
know I don't I don't think High School
reunions are so common in
Austria I've never heard of anybody ever
doing a high school reunion to be honest
here I only ever hear about it in TV
shows that are from like America
in Italy also not really yeah maybe it's
more an American thing
mhm no such thing in UK
really not even in the
UK I inv your unit but I live so far
away from my hometown oh
no you did one you from
Austria
what maybe you had maybe I think maybe
certain classes might do it if they had
a really good
Bond but I think a lot of schools a lot
of classes don't
care you're hoty El did one what the
[\h__\h] why was I not invited
h i remember being invited for High
School Union back in the Phils
Philadelphia it's an older people thing
yeah maybe it's a generation thing like
back in the day was more common and
nowadays it gets less and less common
maybe because people get more and more
antisocial because they have small
attention span and
phone would you guys say people got more
antisocial though at the same time I
feel like Zoomers are very social but
like in the wrong ways
maybe they don't really connect they
they may be social and outgoing but they
don't really connect on a deeper
level that's the problem Alum because of
the media and [\h__\h]
Tech wow deep
[\h__\h] I'm not dragging too much Mom was
right it was a damn phone yeah it was
damn
phones yeah I mean I wouldn't want
to keep the world from such useful
Tech um we're betterle off with the
tech but times were better perhaps when
there was less Tech and it's just
getting worse the more we're
advancing some things are getting better
but now we got to a point where we
Advanced so much that any more
advancement is
dangerous giving people more power to do
evil things more and more in easy ways
they can even even figure it even figure
it out
themselves that with the tools that have
been given to them already at this point
so it's just uh really bad yeah so
robots will take over the world someday
and they will kill us all
that will
happen put that tinf hat on again you
should have been on the whole day
today for real though for real I mean
some some [\h__\h] will go
down maybe already in a 100 years or
less just got getting closer and closer
to chaos
I for one welcome our new robot
Overlord agree to disagree because it's
a double-edged sword that info travels
fast so for me I know way more about the
world than I did before yeah but we know
too
much maybe we know too
much there's too many pluses and minuses
to probably know for now the metrics for
determining
uh a true positive or negative are still
not up to date to figure it out well the
thing is like you can't just tell
scientists and tech people and so on to
just stop trying to evolve things and
stop trying to figure out new things and
better things stop trying to make things
better you can't tell them to just stop
improving and just stop where they are
in time then there's no purpose for them
and uh yeah it'll also be like what the
[\h__\h] are you guys doing and we'll get
mad for them not doing
anything we can't tell them to stop yeah
yeah they have to like find new ways of
so to say improving life
quality stop working on the damn
phones no no please improve the selfie
cameras and the outside cameras too and
yeah just the cameras you can improve
stop working on the phones as in stop
making it like into like foldable phones
that [\h__\h] is
stupid
no no just stop stop stop stop making
foldable
phones like the old Flip Flip flones mhm
the old flip flones are cute but stop
making the screen
foldable I don't like it it's stupid hi
thank you for the raid improve the
camera though I welcome that quality
improvement how do people like seeing
the crease on their I I from what I've
seen they don't even necessarily have a
crease which is
stupid get yourself a book if you want
to fold
something or or do your laundry and then
fold your pants I don't [\h__\h]
care they develop a creas oh for real oh
ew e do some origami yeah if you want to
fold something do some
origami stop folding your phone it's
getting creases just like your
skin when you look at your phone for too
long so just throw your phone in the
trash right
now uh tasim thanks for the Super Chat
oh my God I also recently had my fairy
exam for the driving license and I
passed my family was supposed to be
waiting outside for me in their car I
was so excited and it was really dark
and then I accidentally got into the
wrong car the dude in there was
confused oh oh that's um yeah
embarrassing
oh oh I hope they were a friendly person
and and and were forgivable I mean you
probably immediately realized when you
saw someone else sitting in there
oh that's awkward but funny thank you
for sharing that and congratulations on
passing your driving license now it's
time for your diving license next go
go thanks for sharing that he was all
right good thank God oh no happy chunky
bird chunky sh how cute wow what a bird
what a bird
oh I want to touch that poofy
chest he Luna thanks for the pinky H red
sorry I can't see colors today I'm so
colorblind queen of tangent thank you
that is me where's my
crown taking the crown now you calling
me queen of
tangent thank you
aluda would you like to elude to that el
el isn't that a word
elude to that does that mean like
telling me more about it right or or
telling it is a
word yes
eluder elude to it ah elude doesn't mean
hinting to something or
so oh to refer yeah yeah refer that's
what I mean and then elude is evading ah
elude and elude and
elude and then there's a
loot that's a lot of
loots difficult important to make a
differentiation
yes hey
Lo and then and then there's
UDA
elud simply D you know those dreams
where you forgot to put on your pants oh
I did that with my swimming trunks in a
public pool what you were NY thankfully
there weren't that many people around
but definitely enough for me to remember
to this day oh dear were you were
actually
[Music]
n were you a like a child cuz I feel
like as an adult it's more embarrassing
but as an adult it's more embarrassing
but as a child
you no wait I mean it's embarrassing in
different ways I think
as a child it's like Ah that's just
Child Things whatever but an adult is
like what the [\h__\h] are you
doing hello you're an adult don't be
naked I was a kid thankfully okay oh man
thanks for sharing that I love these
kind of stories maybe we should do a
whole stream like
this where you guys share your
embarrassing stories with me anonymously
of course Travis Lord
an start wearing a band like zor long
story short I was mistaken for a sick
child like charity workers at a
chocolate factory and got free Chun for
wearing a bandana oh because they
thought you had
cancer just by wearing a bandana you'll
immediately get people think you're you
have cancer that's [\h__\h]
up whoa what is this assuming you have
like a really [\h__\h] grave
illness I mean
maybe as a child that's fun because you
got the free chocolate and you're
probably thinking oh yeah [\h__\h] yeah free
chocolate but whoa that's actually
messed
up a zombie d j
[Music]
d MP
mp15 most embarrassing thing I could
think of I get to the point I I get to
the point I have a heart attack I'm
speaking my own language than English oh
I stutter slightly and forget words so I
have to use English words when I
talk I feel like that like people using
English words within like them speaking
German for example here already have
that happen a lot I have some friends
who
like or some even do it so on purpose
I've seen a conversation between one of
my friends friend and her
friend and they were just like
completely Converse in English and I'm
like this is so cringe for me this is so
cringe because we all speak German but I
think it's kind of cringe because they
they I don't know they think they're
cooler or something I don't [\h__\h] know
why do you feel a need that to talk in
English to each
other it's weird it's just
weird I told them though I think it's
weird H but then
yeah mixing English words into German
language I do that too because I just
speak English literally every single day
for several years now I speak it more
than my own language on a day-to-day
basis so uh it's not that I completely
forget words there's still somewhere in
there but it's not the first thing I
think of often so I have to replace them
quickly in English and I feel so stupid
too but it's a normal thing it's a
normal thing I would say not a big deal
nothing to be embarrassed
about I mean actually it's a flex it's
actually a flex if you know your
non-native language almost
better
and uh implemented in your day to-day
life speaking it's actually kind of
reflex because some people only speak
one language they can't do
that when they can't think of a word in
their own native language then they have
no other language to replace it with
because they don't know any other
language looks at all you only English
[Laughter]
[Music]
speakers
wink or not even only English looks at
all you mono lingual is that a word
monolingual
speakers rude
hey now I know a z doesn't count doesn't
make you bilingual at
all get dunked
on imagine only knowing one
language couldn't be
me sorry I mean honestly if like the
thing is like in Europe our education is
just like normal to learn
at least two languages um so depending
on where you grew up and what your
circumstances were um yeah also like
even even other languages I learned in
school I I wouldn't remember all of them
English is just like the one that stayed
with me and Japanese is the one that
stayed with me because I had a passion
for it and I taught it to myself but
there's certain other languages that you
learn in school that you just don't
remember so many people in Europe
learned like French Italian Etc as a sec
as a third language actually and and I
think I think most of them don't
remember much and that's pretty normal
too you just uh get forced to learn
these languages more or less and if you
don't have a big passion for it then
your brain will not keep that in your
brain so even if you had the luck to
have an education where you did learn a
second or third language chances are
you're not going to remember it
depending on you know how you feel
towards that language when you learn
it yeah and if you never had the chance
to learn a second language then there's
absolutely no blame on you if if you
never had the opportunity for it
like that's just you know the education
system that that's just the society that
we live in you know [\h__\h]
Society
um but the cool thing is you can kind
ofar uh teach languages to yourself if
you feel like it if you want to do that
there's
resources all over the world I learned
Japanese without books or teachers I had
books I bought books thinking I would
use them never used it never flipped the
page
conversation is the way to go yep yep
yep yep yep yep yep yep
yep we chat is the way to go uh I I
don't know about that but I guess that's
a world that I have not really
um uh like that kind of VR chat world
where random people meet in these
like VR chat
rooms I've seen one
video uh I think it was from Cody Co
where he did a video about going into
these like public VR chat rooms and
talking with Rand and it was really
concerning what was going on there there
were like some really young kids and
then you know there's like
weirdos just doesn't seem like a safe
place oh weird Gatherings may happen
[Music]
there it's so unhinged yeah I can
imagine um I don't even want to know
what goes on there I want to stay not
knowledgeable about the
possibilities Second Life lobbies were
stranger second
life that rings a bell I know the
name but I don't really know don't know
anything where was I
um ah Travis Lord dun no wait I read
that one
uh here Brandon dun motion
dun J dun oh real story I was super
chuni in school I submitted fanfiction
to my writing Professor for review
cosplay in class I did that too never
shut up about anime and people made fun
of me a lot makes me
cringe yeah I think nowadays there's
more openness to being into Japan into
anime into all that
culture and a couple years ago it was
not that accepted yet and more of a
bullying reason so that's
sad why did you cosplay well like for
stuff like fashing like Carnival in
school I would bring out my I think I
told you this before guys I would bring
out my M dresses and my other stuff that
I had cuz I collected a lot of ma
dresses and school uniforms and other
stuff
like a like a little Yukata goic Lolita
Yukata whatever and I would even let
some friends cuz they were some cool
friends that I had at the point of art
school people were way way more
accepting in art
school and I would um let a friend wear
a maid outfit for
example yeah honestly we were we were
like the best dressed like
honestly like in in in times like these
like Carnival in school or whatever at
Halloween like the the girls the and the
boys I guess the people who are kind of
into that culture and have like costumes
from cosplay and whatever at home those
are always the best dressed in these
situations like for real that's when
we're winning that's when we are the
cool ones because our costumes just have
like the best detail and they just look
they just look the best they don't look
like your cheap ass Amazon on stripper
outfits yeah facts spitting facts we
were
dripping uh Nathan cotton thanks for the
pinky you can do it t I believe in you
you can make that jump I don't think I
ever made it what jump are we talking
about space waterful than you thank you
I feel obligated to read all of these
because you guys were so nice to
share99 should I say this in English I
say this in English probably um so I
never studied in a university so I can't
really tell but from my
observation you have way more freedom
to
not follow up on your studies than in
school why because like in school you
like you get pushed through it kind of
you can still like stay behind um but
like it happens less I feel like from
what I understand in University there's
so much
more it's it's so much easier so to say
to like spend way more time that you
need to in University or college yeah so
it's easier to waste time cuz nothing is
there to push you so if you don't have a
really really strong Drive of your
own which I would probably not have if
it was related to school
then it's easy to spend like 10 years on
University I can totally see that
happening and that's not something to
feel too bad about because I having a
drive for stuff like
that is really tough really
difficult yeah you need so much self-
discipline so much self- discipline but
yeah at the point of like 10 years if
you're still not feeling like you're
making progress at 10 years I think it's
also fine to just say [\h__\h] this this is
maybe not made for Me Maybe maybe what I
need to do is just go get a job instead
of you know going to University and
that's fine too like I mean I don't know
it depends maybe on the country uh I
think in some countries it's more
acceptable or less acceptable to have uh
a finished degree
in Austria thankfully it's very
acceptable to not have a finished degree
it's very normal a lot of people have
finished degrees also but it's also more
accepted to not have
it it's very much not required to have a
degree to be successful in life or to
get a job
yeah
yeah so just I just want to say don't
feel bad feel don't feel bad about not
having this drive and this self-
discipline and this like ability to push
yourself every day to get something
going because that is one of the most
difficult things in
life especially when it's something that
gives you so much freedom to progress or
not
progress
now is like you can do this but you
don't have to you can spend one month on
this or you can spend a year on this do
what you
want it's rough
yeah
yeah you're welcome
yeah so
this I mean that doesn't even have to be
in like University or whatever even in
everyday life you
know even in everyday life taking care
of
yourself where was
I B Jones thanks for the Super Chat I
One Time Forgot to scan a ladies coupon
and
member and member read card after t I
told her to give me
them first so I wouldn't Forge to forget
to scan them I was a lot of money those
things would have
saved and
remember my C there's a lot of like auto
corrects
here I cannot really figure out what
you're trying to say but you just forgot
to scan
stuff coupons
and money was lost I guess what that's
not something to be embarrassed about
don't
worry I got jumbled mumble
jumble yeah I mean yeah surely you'll
feel regretful like ah man I could have
saved so much money but that's not
embarrassing Kam than you soon R thank
for the Super Chat when I was in un my
brother was teaching a classer oh
I thought I saw him walking called out
to him and waved but he didn't wave back
turns out it wasn't
him and then the same exact thing
happened later the same day with the
same
person but your brother was somewhere on
the campus right you just thought it was
someone
else you thought someone else was your
brother you forgot you sent
that yeah like thinking you know someone
waving at them and stuff that's really
embarrassing can happen to all of
us it's really weird when you're the
person being waved at though or talked
to
even Papa than than
you oh
wait
FAA FAA
Fafa are you
here
Fafa you learned to read the clock
pretty late like me I want to give you a
handshake you are me I am
you God place thanks to the
pinky Fafa doesn't seem to be here but I
appreciate the
sharing sorry in high school a girl
tried kissing me in front of the class
while I was unaware but I instinctually
dodged her kiss good job question mark
she thought I did it on purpose so she
ran out of the room crying
ooh Why did she try to kiss you in front
of the whole class did you guys have
something going on before that like an
obvious Crush from each side the teacher
got upset at me in front of ever the
teacher got upset at you for dodging a
kiss in front of the whole
class what what if you don't didn't want
to be kissed uh what what how can the
teacher blame you for for not oh my
God what also this is high school I
wonder if it's in the early high school
years or in the later
because puberty changes kids a lot in
those years
what I need more context for this super
chat this is not enough I need more
explanations
more function looking for the top
D cat
hair on April Falls a newspaper
published news as if they were from the
future when I got the paper I thought I
really had future news I knocked my
neighbor's door to tell them until I saw
the
date wait what what you what you you
were just
like you f
what what are you implying you
thought H what
what yeah you believe what the newspaper
said but was it was it implying what
news from the future
what what what you thought that this
newspaper was actually
reporting something from the
future
what
ah
ah okay
no so you knew for example a soccer
match didn't happen yet but it gave out
already the result and you thought
okay however the [\h__\h] that's possible
but you accepted it as the
result they published the supposed
result before the but you knew the
soccer match didn't even happen
yet wa were you a
child
what you must have been a
child you were 10
okay understandable then yeah very
understandable that's cute though that's
not embarrassing that's cute J Monkey D
py D I am a beep sky you are
D I asked for changing my schedule so I
can catch a bit of the
stream thank you the game for the pinky
I thought that was a I thought Lou you
were confessing something and gamer crat
is confessing something as a kid I
couldn't figure out the lock mechanism
at my school's bathroom so I ended up
doing my business with an unlocked door
one day some older kids came in saw me
sitting there slowly closed the door
then made fun of me from the outside oh
man
that's
unfortunate I wish you would have felt
like maybe comfortable to ask a friend
or so but you probably didn't feel
comfortable like oh do you know how to
lock the door by the way so random
but yeah that's unfortunate that's like
a a
nightmare I have while I'm awake
sometimes like while I'm in a public uh
bathroom to do an idle meeting nothing
else sometimes the locks are not so
clear right and then you're like you're
already sitting you can't reach it
anymore with your hand and you
wonder I hope it's really
locked while I finished super chat
before PS5 and rest that depends how
much I'm planning to read I'm at the end
of these
ones Spartan B free one to
GC
and oh the horor
yeah8 hours oh wow yeah it's almost 8
hours 8 minutes until 8
hours my head hurts a little bit I'm
going to make some simple
pasta oh oh 6 minutes ha until power
saving who
how do
I I really don't like the PS5 like
switch is just
easier switch is more intuitive in my
[Music]
opinion of course I saved and there's
auto save
anyway yeah going to leave it at that
going to make a quick Bast a b bter and
there wait should we get wake up and
smoothie she's still here I kind of want
to give
heram Lam snack and see if she mamams
into the microphone wait I'm going to go
get theam
snack as a um uh treat for staying
behind the monitor all stream and
letting me pet her
chunky wony knows what's up okay it's
moving
hello
mov look what I have let me put on my
headphones yeah oh oh oh it's chunky won
you'll get something too CH she's
holding on to my leggings okay wait wait
wait do you guys hear chunk wonkey smoo
is like she just woke up she doesn't
know what's happening let's lower the
mic
sorry okay here we
are wait can you can you
here can you
hear dony like in the
background wait here
there turn up the LI Lim
you guys will maybe manually have to
make it
[Music]
louder she's yapping so
much oh it's that
yummy waa that tastes so
good the chunky wonky wants something
too she's like why is smovie getting
everything
first he just doesn't stop
yapping yeah good good movie shall we
let chunky
wonky hi chunky wonky the only time when
they let me have them on my lap for
extended amount of
time you you you
okay here it goes wait I'm still pushing
it up there we go there it
is this is chunky wonky mm she Mims a
little bit
differently uh she's kind
too far from the mic I
think she might be liing the microphone
at this right can you hear it at all
she's not
slower might be too quiet you can hear
[Music]
here bit
more mon here there it
is oh yeah she definitely led the
microphone and we I have something left
to my finger here take
it thank you thank you thank you this
one
to thank you thank you thank you yeah
I'll I'll wipe my fingers on your fur
you'll love cleaning your fur after
this now they had a half
each okay and in German we say I'll be Z
I can't believe I never did this
before sharing a uh snack with them uh
for them into the mic
I'm so
hungry
I'll byebye oh my god oh no it's
midnight I'm going to lose my
transformation
[Music]
ah stream Cima