[Music]
foreign
you
[Music]
[Applause]
hahaha
[Music]
[Laughter]
what are you doing today we have a very
special guest um
you know the one who hosted the part one
of the thing of the recap thing uh
takanashi kiwawa please introduce
yourself
uh hello everybody um
from indonesia second generation yeah
yeah what attention please
let's go
um
hi you guys how are you guys today i was
so nervous because it's actually really
it's been a good while since i last you
know did something like a stream like
super giddy kitty you know this stream
is like a
a mini picture diary but the thing is
started actually drawing the afternoon
and then
i finished probably like
half an hour ago
yeah i was just like
i had most of it done but like you know
i wanted to do some extra what what huh
yeah
what what are you doing
what are you doing stop hiding she's
just behind are you gonna hide
um
i am marina
okay now we have a bird we have a bird
here if you guys are seeing if you guys
are seeing you know it's like a white
screen and that's where the comics are
gonna be that's where my drawings are
gonna be what
oh no you're cut off
i'm trying to find my placing any of it
i think i'm smaller than before yeah
yeah you became small it's all right
yes
a little bit a little bit closer to me
because if not then you will
make yourself a little bit smaller yeah
this is just bird things we can resize
ourselves
yeah okay
okay nice
big bed yes okay
so did you guys enjoy yesterday's recap
by kiara the photos
what no what
no i didn't enjoy it no why
there were no naked pigs
what
what not cool not cool
i was looking forward to some spicy
picks but there were no spicy pigs are
you role playing as chat right now
[Laughter]
yeah oh yeah we have to say some massage
or something something and chad's just
like you know in their own world
it's okay you know like i'm i'm proud of
my listeners because they have a very
very active imagination you know you
have you need to have a little bit of
imagination to get far in life right am
i right am i right
yeah probably not that way but also you
know you're getting there you're getting
there
very nice
so going now today i kind of look like
you're your child lena really
what oh no look i feel like i look so
childish when i'm standing behind you
low-key smaller then don't stand behind
me you can be not no
no no no no it's okay i wanna be your
child today okay
usually it's the other way around
so i guess
in the vacation it was kind of
established that kiara did have some
motherly moments apparently
apparently you really see myself like
that but dana needed a mommy and i
became mommy
[Laughter]
yeah she was so good you know like
you know squeezing the thingy and oh
yeah yeah squeezing the air out of the
thingy the what the getting getting the
ipad yeah showing you the shows that you
like yeah
waking you up in the morning
um
i guess you did kind of i wasn't really
hard to i wasn't really hard to wake up
you just like poked me and you're like
yeah you woke up whenever i was i woke
up yeah yeah exactly see our our
sleeping schedule synced up pretty much
you know but i was like if you're not up
i don't want to get up that kind of
thing you know
yes
but anyways yeah we're here to talk more
about the maltese if chiara
[Music]
today
so if yesterday kiara showed you guys
photos and like a more objective view of
the
of the where'd you get that
on the vacation well today is gonna be
you know stuff from my point of view
they're they're getting comics but you
know they're very very personal from my
point of view so there might be like a
little bit of a you know repeat story
but i guess that's all right you know
it's gonna be taken from my point of
view so it's gonna be different
baby kamala oh my gosh
don't steal my roll or are we we're
switching for the stream tonight okay i
guess so um
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah
yes yes i know yeah i know that i know
some did you know that there was an u
there's an uyu song if you look it up
there's an uyu song in korean but
anyways we're not here to talk about
someone told me before maybe yeah yeah
yeah oh okay okay so we're just gonna
okay i'll try to i'm using photoshop
here if you guys don't recognize the
cursor
ah
oh you're gonna reveal it like that okay
yeah i'm gonna review it like that
because i drew everything like on like a
lot yeah uh one paper
uh i didn't have time to divide them by
like layers so i'm just gonna do it this
way so mommy's gonna show me a picture
story yeah it's an ahorn storyboard
[Music]
i know you like demon cats so much
okay
so the first story i drew my hand feels
like they're gonna fall off by the way
because i speed ran through everything
but how many hours did you spend hey i
started in the afternoon pretty much i
woke up at like half past 12. wait you
say you started an afternoon did you not
do anything last night i did i did it
was just like mostly like you know super
rough planning like what i wanted to do
yeah
but then i started in the afternoon like
the actual inking drawing
i expected that if you stream while
doing it you're not going to get
anything of course definitely definitely
i mean partially was my fault when i
showed you some sea otters but
i mean you have to have some
self-control over yourself and
apparently you don't i do when i want to
i do have self-control all right so
the first one is on the first night do
you remember what happened on the first
night
[Laughter]
you touched me yeah
i did i did it wasn't intentional i was
asleep the whole time apparently she
didn't really she didn't think i was
asleep but i was asleep i was fasting
i thought it would be like that like
every night afterwards but it was only
the first night exactly exactly exactly
so basically
uh
[Music]
huh me
me
really this is yeah cause like she told
she told on stream like what
i don't really think i don't think
that's the case with that and then you
know
like
like even after the stream i had to ask
her is it true i asked you right like
when we started screaming i was like is
that really true did i really do that
oh my god it's so cute yeah so like
honestly the first time like on stream
when she said it like i thought she was
gonna reveal something like do i really
snore in my sleep or something you know
something unexpected like that because
me personally i'm not really good with
people who snore in their sleep you know
me neither yeah yeah or like i'm just
really afraid like oh what if i was um
grinding my teeth and she couldn't sleep
you know i was like really really
worried about that you know like what if
right
and then i was really really nervous
because like huh what this is the first
time i'm hearing about this and then she
revealed something much more extreme
she really feels something much more i
guess that is okay and you are not it's
not only touching the spine it's also
you trying to like take the whole bed
for yourself um
i only
i have a little stories apparently
family member about um about this
apparently i do have that
kind of habit if i don't really restrain
myself
i guess it was like a little bit too
relaxed on the first night so i was just
like maybe without realizing i did that
that is that you're sleeping with
someone else in the bed so
yeah
on the following days i will say again
she didn't do
she didn't take the whole bed then in
the following days it seems like she was
able to control herself while she was
sleeping yeah
yeah exactly even after the stream i had
to ask yeah it was like and then
so every night since then
[Laughter]
you were watching me while i was
sleeping no no this was just the third
panel no no but realistically you always
left first right i mean you know i don't
know you fall asleep faster which is
good you know i feel like uh i don't
know i don't want people to wait i don't
know actually actually it's good that
you fall asleep because then if i do
something in my sleep i don't know you
were likely for anyone you realized uh
if i were to do something in my sleep
normally because they're already asleep
then they wouldn't realize for example
if i accidentally like maybe grind my
teeth no i don't do that but what if
right and then they wouldn't
because that's how it
he found is like back then sometimes she
had a habit to like grind her teeth and
then so whenever i had to have like you
know whenever i have to sleep with her
for example like during vacations and
everything why are you like looking at
my back
[Laughter]
i always try to sleep first so i don't
have to hear that and i can sleep for
the whole night yeah
when i sleep with someone else in the
hotel room then i'm always the one who
falls asleep after the other
is i really i really don't like it
because then i hear them snoring and
then i can't sleep even more
yeah okay so that's good but this time
it was the other way around
thankfully yeah thankfully yeah that's
that's that's good that's good yeah it's
very normal so every night since then
i tried my best to shapeshift
why are they swimming out because you're
stoned
when we got in the bed i was just like
okay i need to lie down a certain way i
try i need to try not to get too
comfortable and roll around you know
like the bed is so soft and comfy i want
to just like roll around you know
and so i did not i did not um snore no
you didn't oh oh it's good to know
because that nobody ever tells me
because usually i sleep alone so yeah i
don't really know what i do
like yeah also like the other nights
right i always ask you like did i do
something did i do something but i guess
i never did really really did anything
right
sometimes he was breathing a little bit
stronger but no not not so much that i
would say that it's like loud snoring so
all good all good oh good i think that
was probably like the dream where i had
like a really messed up nightmare where
i had to like fight some ghosts and
stuff
one yeah some nights i had really
extreme dreams that has nothing to do
with the mall dips too
yeah oh well oh well oh wow
this is scary i know this is so cute
so cute you have to upload them on
twitter afterwards yeah i will i will i
will and then i guess
the second one
[Music]
floaty story
oh
how much do you guys know about the
floaty story i think like we told a
little bit of the story like a bit like
here and there
i think people can kind of guess by now
loki like roughly what happened but
i guess now there will be the details
yeah i guess so
so for the floaty story we finally got
floaties let's go let's use it we went
to the shop and then we got floaties
look at the price tag it's really
expensive
mine's a little bit more expensive
because it's the type that you know you
you lie on it basically that's the time
it was the bigger one also bigger than
mine it was big like yours was like the
the typical one right
nice price yeah i know yeah and then
so you were already downstairs and you
were already in the water with your
floatie
even though it was really like the the
tides were really strong and i was
trying my best to not float away myself
but what i did was
because i i knew that the wind and the
waves were really strong yeah
i walked down that ladder already with
the floating around my body so that it
wouldn't fly away and that i could have
control over it but i guess when i was
already in the water reina was like oh i
see it's fine so what you did next was
your biggest it was that it was a big
mistake wait uh give me a second give me
a second i need to are you hmm
oh
oh my god she's
always screams when she walks
basically the weather was like pretty
yeah it was pretty awesome it was like
either the first or like second day oh
basically second or third i don't know i
don't really remember
but wind was strong definitely second
definitely
yeah yeah yeah wind strong cloudy sky
but she you know wanted to swim and of
course why wouldn't you want to swim
even though the tide was pretty scary so
what i did i thought like so there was
like a little stairway over there right
and then i thought to myself you know
what this is really big like my my thing
uh the the the pillow not pillow my my
floaty thing is really big i can't do it
i can't like bring it by myself because
it's too narrow so what i did was
i dropped
the floatie
i dropped the floatie
downstairs
to the water splash normally it would
work right i eated it downstairs like
whoosh splash
yes yes
didn't you
consider what might happen if you do
that
i i no but i was like um
don't die if i like bring it i didn't
because i thought to myself like me
because you were staying in place i was
like i'll just quickly go down you know
it's not even like that far right
i could go down yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
and then it wasn't that far what
happened was
[Music]
it ran away
so sad
really fast actually really fast
for me like i feel like
there were there were some there were
there was like a moment um of panic but
if we would have reacted faster
um and if you were a good swimmer
then maybe you could have swam after it
quickly uh
but i think yeah we both
were
panicking and i'm also not a good
swimmer so
i was like
with those strong tides i don't think i
can swim after yeah the tides were
really strong it was pretty scary and
then we were panicked we didn't even
think like to contact you know anybody
like say our butler or something i mean
it turned out that you know
we could we did
somebody in front but then it still took
a while anyways right we were too music
panicking yeah
we we contacted the butler and i guess
the butler contracted like security but
they told us that they will go out
looking for it but when they actually
went looking for it it was already like
30 40 minutes later
i think even even more later by that
time i did not see the floatie anymore
in the distance it was already gone it
was gone yeah yeah we called them really
late definitely
so yeah that was the first and second
story so sad no no no but the floaty
story is not over yet right did you draw
more yeah of course i did
let's see through part two let's go
the second part is
won't happen again
so i learned my lesson basically i
learned my lesson no more throwing yeah
no more throwing no more throwing
and so
we were swimming again the other day
okay we were sleeping again like
i already went in uh because i was like
hey if she's up there maybe she can like
like like put it above my head that was
my
ideal plan that i'm in the water by the
ladder at the bottom and you put it
above my head you know what i mean so i
can just swoosh in there yeah that was
my idea
well in my head i was like you know why
not be efficient and i mean
relaxing uh-huh yes
and then so there was the stair again
the stairs so there was like barely no
wind but like you know if i roll the
floatie down the stairs there's gonna be
like there right now
there's some definitely some wind yeah
but then i thought like even if there's
some wind if i like roll it and then the
railings will like guard it from like
being like blown anyways right it will
just like roll straight to you
there was like around the bottom or the
middle on the right side there was no
railing that's the problem
i don't remember
partially that yeah only partially there
was a railing
i well
so anyways that was what was in my brain
am i exposing elena here no i mean
i'm going to expose myself anyways
so what i did was naturally up the
ladder
yeah naturally
here
roll
see rolling isn't throwing right so it's
okay
[Laughter]
but the moment you did that it happened
too fast but i already knew oh this
this is going
wrong
and then well it didn't go as you know
as i as what i visualized in my head
unfortunately
it got blown by the wind
yeah literally before it touched the
water
even before that before that
so sad
adios season two but
this time as well the the tides the
waves were really strong so once again i
did not feel up to the challenge to swim
after that
but then it's different because like
last time yeah the um the wind kind of
blew my floaty like away to the sea but
this time
the wind uh kind of like blew her floaty
towards
the resort part i guess
so through through the other villas like
underground
because they were over water villas in
the like low key in the sky yes yes it
went through to the other side where the
villas were facing the other side of the
ocean
yeah so
so
naturally
oh oh oh next page
the title's just
that was still haha for me though
it's like oh no it's on the other side
see it's like the bridge this is like
the bridge like between like the houses
yeah and then oh no call the butler this
time we were so quick to call the butler
because like yeah it's not our first
time right so it's just like
i was like oh my god i'm so sorry i'm
just i'm gonna buy you a new one if you
lose it you know if that's not ideal but
that's like the least i can do okay like
if i
lose that like it's my fault so that's
that's the least i can do
while it was floating away um i was like
thinking maybe
if only we could like enter
um if you could walk over to the other
side and go into the water on the ladder
of a different house villa but the thing
is you can't you just you have to go
through the villa so you have to go
through someone's
door and
you can't go to the other side
so
musukashi but what we did was elena ran
out first because i was still in the
water panicking yeah i got my phone
contacted and i went outside
basically next panel but an unexpected
thing happened we were
we were looking at it and then suddenly
the guys living
where you know where the floating was
like floating
but but it was like you
were like actually the butler was around
right really fast yeah yeah in the area
butler like in between the the
the houses like on that path looking at
the floatie and the butler was trying to
get him to call they took so much time
so before the the real help the security
could come yeah this this person who was
living there a lady
immediately put on her flippers her
snorkeling flippers
she was so hunky she was so serious
about it and she flew into the water and
against the really strong waves she was
really strongly like
swimming you know the swimming style
like it with the
tv series describe that
no like in the tv series like rescuing a
person drowning yeah
it's just swimming
but it looked so tight him because the
waves were so strong i know
it was literally
him yeah it was very very much
there
next
yeah they got it they actually got it
like so fast i think like you know the
butler was fast but it does take time
for them to like contact like the both
people and then for them to get it and
then i feel like you know we were gonna
get a floaty story apart to a bad end
another bed if they didn't show up and
then they actually got it
it's so good
i was i
felt really really
embarrassed and uh
like i didn't even wanna
didn't even want to face her directly
but yeah
we were like thank you like okay first
because you know our floaty got into
their territory and second because this
is the second time the butler knows we
lost our floaties it was really
embarrassing
i i was like thinking that the butler by
now must think that we're like really
really idiotic tourists like really the
stupid time
really annoying and stupid i felt so so
so so
chiara listen
um here's the thing she's really really
um she
she really doesn't want to be like
meiwaku to other people like she's like
oh no even like uh our butler offers us
to like drive us around and she's like
you know what i kind of feel bad asking
her to drive us around all the time and
i'm like yeah we paid for all this
[Laughter]
yeah we paid for all this
because some some places were actually
really close walking distance so i
didn't want to annoy her too much you
know again and again to go to the same
place
yeah she's super considerate i was like
but yeah
and then there was the rain the rain
story too so it was just like
it all happened in the same day i think
was it did it happen the same day i
remember like the second floatie was on
this uh one day later oh okay but then
this and the rain happened on the same
day
because i remember
just on that day just on that day i
remember man we did so many embarrassing
things just in one day you know yeah
yeah
so
i feel so stupid but i don't you didn't
draw the the part where
um i greeted them in the lounge did you
no i didn't there was no space but well
yeah sure of course
when they gave us the floatie actually
the like the husband the woman was
getting the floatie in the water and the
husband gave it to us on at the door
and the moment like we talked in english
but the moment he just said like he just
said five words or something but his
accent
made me think that he might be german
like i just heard a slight german accent
in there so i was always like thinking
they're probably german and then
uh on the
uh departure day when we were actually
we had the same departure day so we were
in the lounge at the airport together
and
i felt um like i needed to say something
one more time and express my gratitude
so i walked over to them and i'm like
you're german aren't you and they're
like yeah yeah so we started talking in
german and i i like
bowed several times even though it's not
a german thing but i apologize a million
times and i explained to them
we will never do it again and i don't
want to pollute the ocean i'm so sorry
about that and then they told me that
they actually also
uh saw the first floatie
fly away float away
because they were originally on the
villa on the other side next door to us
but they had a problem in the villa so
they moved to to the other side and they
said that they wanted to rescue the
first floatie as well but they were not
their reaction wasn't fast enough but on
the second time they saw it and they
reacted fast enough but can you imagine
that's even more embarrassing that they
saw both of them fly away and they they
must also be thinking these idiot
children oh my god thank god i don't
speak german
yeah
yeah yeah but i made sure to maybe leave
a little bit of a better impression by
apologizing a million times
oh man
oh yeah i also complimented her on her
swimming and i asked her if she like
like why she can't swim so well and she
said oh just because i guess i i had
like a swimming course when i was
younger so yes i guess she learned it
properly really really so good
amazing she was really good it was yeah
like i said it was really like a tv show
rescuing drunk person
yeah it felt so so useless when i was
just standing there and watching it
happen while she like works her butt off
to get the floatie for us i just i
wanted to give them money or something
for the hard work man i felt so so sorry
i want to forget this incident let's
never talk about it again
she's so embarrassed
[Music]
because when you're maybe good to them
yeah i guess i get you
oh but they're so nice though they're so
nice
they have the choice not to help but
they still did so it's like wow there's
they're they're really good people you
know really good people yes indeed
i must say that because other people
they would just chill in their room and
just watch it floating away she was
already in her swimsuit you must also
consider that if she wasn't in her
swimsuit she probably wouldn't have done
that yeah so it's just like you know
nice people and also like i mean we were
see like we were also in our swimsuits
all the time but then if we saw
something like that i don't think
i would because you know also because
like i'm not really that good yeah i'm
not i'm kind of scared also i just got
that cut remember
yeah so i'm like kind of like how
low-key like uh i don't know what if i
hurt myself again or something
if it was
low tide i might have tried rescuing
something
but not on high tide it looked so so
scary not dangerous but just really
really tight and really
difficult to
even move forward in the water um yeah
it was i thought it was scary actually
because you also don't know when rain is
gonna like come right because it's just
but you're already in the water at that
point what does it matter
if if it's raining then it's gonna be
even harder to like swim
i think
maybe i guess
i'm not sure about that but okay
anyways yeah good people amazing people
very grateful embarrassed yes but also
very grateful
[Music]
and then what is this it's pulling you
in like gravity what is this
okay what is this sing high tide
it's pulling you in
that's it
this is where the comics start getting
personal yeah honestly i didn't you know
like the the funny
there were funny stuff but like honestly
most of the time the vacation was like
pretty comfy you know no
it was pretty comfy so that was like you
know you i know you're pretty observant
but i do also observe a little bit about
you i already told most of this anyways
so
during breakfast
[Music]
during breakfast this is one of yeah i
think like our first or second day
definitely
um
yeah it's like we were having breakfast
eating so nicely
you had what was it you had
uh french toast the first day i think
right yeah the first day i had french
toast and i had omelette with turkey
bacon
just because i wanted to cook breakfast
for me every day
i know i don't know i i'm normally the
type of person who would eat like a
savory breakfast but like after spending
some time with you i learned i don't
know sweet breakfast isn't so bad after
all
yeah yeah very nice very nice
and then
so when we're in the middle of eating or
maybe like after we eat and then we
still have some time like she would just
suddenly like go to the sand
no nothing like you know she would just
like go to the sand
and they wanted to go in i wanted to
touch the sand and the water yeah she's
so fascinated with
everything with everything i feel i feel
like i don't know maybe it's because i'm
from australia you were also pretty
fascinated with things i i was pretty
fascinated but then you're you're a
different case because i guess i don't
know maybe i'm from a tropical country
so like i see a beach is nice but also
you were you were practically like
sparkling like you were so excited
[Laughter]
you were taking pictures of the hermit
crab you were like taking a video of the
hermit crab you're so excited wait now
look at that it's good i like crabs yeah
you would like take off your sandals and
be like
and then i immediately uploaded it on
twitter yeah
i was just like looking from the front
i was like oh i see
that's cute
she's so excited like man like there was
also like this tree
there was also like this tree right with
the with the river you brought it too no
i didn't i wish i did but i didn't have
enough time
so it was kind of like a cage and then
she was like hey take a picture of me
take a picture of me and then she would
like go inside like the cage like roots
and she was just like squat yeah it was
a tree where the roots were like
like showing out of the earth and there
were so many so it was like like a cage
like you say and i was like can you take
a picture of me inside and you took a
picture
yeah mangroves yeah yeah i guess that's
it mangrove is mangrove
yeah cool
it's not normal oh wait let me look it
up man
then
minecraft so mangrove green yeah usually
like in the water in the sun that's what
yeah
oh yes like that but it was not it was
on the sand not on the water but then
the butler came to pick us up from the
breakfast um and and she saw that
i told her i just took a picture there
and she said oh you might have found a
new photo spot there i didn't know about
this one
cute yeah very prison
prison what's this ah this one
yeah
so she was recording videos of permanent
crows
is that still the same hermit crab um i
don't know maybe there were multiple
yeah
but then honestly like on uh on one of
the later days when we were having
breakfast outside i i was like oh then i
see a hermit crab in the distance moving
and you were like oh where where where
and then we kept on watching it until it
like disappeared we watched it walking
away from the far right distance so you
were also pretty into it
i
it's that no that's because you weren't
into it like it's it's like contagious
you know it's like contagion
yeah and then we were kind of like
watching i think i do have the video i
was just like watching like come on get
up there's something
i did the video and then you were i
didn't draw it
i can't take this anymore yo you trying
to make me look so fascinated about
these things but can i just say there
was one thing that i was absolutely
unfazed by but reyna was so fascinated
by crows on the island and she would
take videos of them and be so excited
and watch them until they went away yeah
she would make a whole documentary and i
was like it's just a crow they're
everywhere they're not even pretty
they're just
boring what are you
there were two weird they were just like
spicily hanging out together remember
the time you're so crow you were like oh
my god look a crow
guys you would make crow sounds at them
and film them yes not only me you two
you have a bird uh fascination it's
normal cause i'm a bird i'm fascinated
by birds you know we have to stick
together right
somebody's like i think crows are
beautiful birds yeah
let's go
anyways they're not that special because
you have them too right in your
way you live right um
uh not i mean i guess like not very
common maybe we do but it's not very
common because it's not like wait then
maybe it's just that we're both
fascinated by things that are not so
common in our own country because we
don't have hermit crabs normally because
we don't have ocean and beaches
so you apparently don't have many crows
yeah but this comic's not about me it's
about my observations
exposing me okay okay i'll stop exposing
you you only expose me now okay
and then quickly
[Music]
let's go oh you drove so cute yeah so
like yeah on the second time we were
eating at the southeast asian restaurant
you were talking about yeah you know
like how cats were like
you know how cats they get stuck in the
tree and then you have to call the
firefighter to yeah to rescue them
and then like oh yeah that gecko is just
like them and i'm gonna be a firefighter
i'm gonna rescue it i'm gonna adopt it
rescue the gecko
yes
yes it's scared it's scared it doesn't
know how to get down and it went up
there but now it doesn't know how to get
down
get down
but yes um the gecko probably knows how
to get down but it's all right and
um yeah i told you like you know
i forgot how the gecko talk went like i
thought you had geckos in the house but
then apparently no you guys are only
have it in forests
um yeah like outside somewhere written i
don't really see them often i just
remember seeing them maybe twice in my
lifetime outside
yeah we have a children
we have a children's song dedicated to
uh house geckos
it's about how it crawls on the wall and
it sees a mosquito and it captures the
mosquito that's it that's how it ends
with the tongue
uh
i guess so it doesn't say in the song
but i would assume
a tropical deadpool yeah a tropical
gekko so cute though uh i also told her
like you know see there are people who
are afraid of uh cockroaches and there
are people who are afraid of geckos
they're also oh yeah they're they're
they're
great they're really cute
yeah
they're really cute i do agree um i
personally am not afraid of geckos
cockroaches though a different thing i
just got a pro you told me can you tell
me that your cat would like um play with
the gecko and like yeah and i was like
yo that's torture
yeah yeah like my cat my cat would i
feel bad for the like baby gecko and
they're like small it's not as big as
the one maybe that one we saw was like
super grown up but the gecko that
you know i witnessed was like pretty
small and then my cat would just like
try to play with it and i'm like i feel
so bad right don't torture it so like i
hold my cat and i'd be like okay gekko
you can go away now but
the gecko was so slow he wasn't even
trying to run away
come on i'm trying so hard to like you
know hold my cat here and you know what
i don't know at the end of the day i
just like you know brought my cat in my
room to play
and the thing is with cats when they
find something like that um i mean i
guess i know there's also cats out there
that go outside and kill things but i
think mostly with cats that stay inside
they they just play with these things
and hurt them but they don't properly
kill them so they're just making them
suffer yeah exactly i feel so bad you're
so sad
if you want to like at least like kill
kill them like make it swift you know
don't touch it
torture them and it's like
gets excited so easily see the gecko the
gecko on the oops the gecko on the
camera and the camera
so
cute so i mean the gecko is cute but
also like you get excited
look at that what is that i i have the
close-up version
of the picture by the way if you want
but then i guess
i guess to be fair kiara
apparently i guess i'm not so different
when it comes to animal videos
yeah
so that's the only thing that you forgot
that was that i was fascinated by was
those the seashells i was picking
seashells very specific ones
sometimes they were shaped like poop and
they were printing she keeps saying oh
poop shells i'm like whoa
[Laughter]
you keep calling it that but it's like
she said she wants to like make a
necklace or something i mean that's cool
i don't know i don't know if i'll really
do it but i i collected enough to make a
bracelet or necklace out of it so maybe
i'll make a stream out of it all right
all right all right
[Music]
it's taboo i drew towel
a dabble
[Music]
i mean i guess he does have a nose
anyway but it looks like a funny nose
it's like his mouth too it's like that
thing i don't know i try my best okay
your comics are so cute
and then yeah she said you know i was
making these noises right and then she
said i'm gonna hit you but as she says
that she hits me
that's what i'm gonna hit you you hit me
already he hit me like twice
yeah
let's go
that was when you you know i already
several times when i was like
sorry i wouldn't stop i have selective
hearing
i slapped you gently
but anyways it was an experience
it was an experience nobody else would
narrate animal videos obnoxiously
right
so it was a unique experience right
would you agree
[Music]
it was definitely unique yes
yeah that's what i'm asking unique yeah
nothing else unique right
mama mama
very unique yes
this one is
i was rushing i didn't i couldn't think
of a time i was rushing stream was
starting soon
[Music]
what smell funny this time nothing
and i was i don't know okay maybe you
can give me a better title for for the
previous comic it was called was it
called no it wasn't called the haha was
the
the other haha was the this is the
second floaty story was yeah okay can
you can you give me a title for that
then yes
miraculous
rescuer miraculous rescue okay no it's
so much better than
okay listen i didn't have time
okay i'm gonna miraculously i'm gonna
edit it i'm gonna edit it uh before
uploading it onto the miraculous
rescuer
well
okay
and then you will also help me with the
title of this one
literally any word is better than haha
what's this about actually
ah this one
remember the bathtub the thing you were
putting foam on your head i was putting
foam on my face actually
originally i wasn't really doing
anything but reyna the moment she got in
she immediately made herself a bubble
beard and i was like oh that's cute
she's enjoying the bubbles like a child
that's cute and after a while watching
you i kind of i felt like okay i guess
i'll join in
i guess i'll join in what's that
you're not gonna do anything in a bubble
bath that's such a waste you know
yeah
but it's cute what happened here what
nothing
nothing happened i was just like uh this
is for reminiscing this is for
reminiscing this is just one panel this
was really fun
[Music]
do you remember this
do you know what this is
yeah
trying to take the picture when i was on
that yeah
it was called again um hammock i think
hammock i am the big hammock yes the big
hammock whoosh what's good hand
so yeah for the in case you guys missed
it so i was supposed to be taking the
picture and she would go in the middle
of the water and get on the hammock but
the problem is it's impossible to get up
by yourself
so what we ended up doing was that i
would help her i would go in the water
and help her get up and then run back to
the sand and take a picture
we did our best but unfortunately i
guess you know the sun wasn't really on
our side the tide wasn't really on our
side but you know i told her like i you
know at least if we take a better
picture the next day or if we don't take
a better picture at least we have one
like you know for like you know it's
better than having nothing right well
that got like an accomplishment to me i
felt like that was an adventure on its
own so
it was fun it was fun
you were not so amused by getting into
the water again but you you did a great
job
oh yeah yeah i did a great job g
my thanks
an instagram girlfriend
i did i took a lot of pictures actually
yeah
sometimes
sometimes i would try to take pictures
of reyna but they're all just her
running away from the camera yeah
looking very unamused
yeah no don't take pictures of me it's
all right
but the thing is i was thinking even
though she's acting shy and and unhappy
when i take pictures of her i'm sure
that afterwards she would be happy to
have some pictures so right after the
vacation she asks me hey do you have
some do you have some pictures of me and
i'm like yeah but they're all you were
running away so i sent them all over and
then they realized maybe you should have
posed for at least one picture yes or
having some memories
okay i don't need to poke memories i
don't know i just thought like you know
this vacation is mine you know i want to
do vacation and i'll post because you
know like i'm you know i'm actually
you didn't even have to post i wanted to
take like natural pictures of you you
know like those instagrammers who look
like they don't care they're just
walking and looking so great
and graciously yes yeah yeah and i
wanted to take a picture like that but
you just you were running away no i
don't need it i think it's all because
you know i guess it's just
uh like a candidate yeah yeah i like i
um
i used to take a lot of pictures for my
um for my family too so you know it was
all right i don't mind taking pictures
for you
so it's all right yeah
i used to i used to get yelled at like
this photo like it's just doing a little
bit more like this but then i guess that
made me a little bit better so like when
i was taking her picture she wasn't
really oh yeah this is a good photo you
were generally good but there were two
things that um always happened when i
asked you for a picture oh you always
had so much of the sky like the picture
would be
i can't help it i like the sky all right
like we don't have
and then one more thing was on my phone
i guess because you're used to a
different kind of stuff yeah yeah the
photo screen yeah the camera it cuts off
differently so for a lot of pictures i
had
reina's feet
toes on the bottom of the picture
i have this a weird habit like you know
i would like sit i would like uh take it
from like slightly uh
like a
warm eye view slightly so then i would
just like lift my leg in a way like i
was exercising for no reason and then
the camera actually like yeah it doesn't
cut that far i'm like oh oh but i mean
like you can crop it anyways right yeah
yeah yeah i can crop it i won't show you
but but yeah a lot of pictures i have
brain is cute little feetsies or toes on
it yeah so many feet pictures my god
yeah
you guys don't get to see it you nobody
gets photos just me just me
you make it sound so weird i don't know
if i like that
but anyways yeah
spicy yeah say it more spicy let's go ah
this one
you were fighting with the curtains
quinoa versus curtains i think
it was uh you were trying to like close
the curtains but only halfway was it
what were you trying to do yeah i tried
to
not close or not open them completely
but every time i tried to move them they
were like kind of automatic and they
would always go to either to the very
end of one side or the other end of the
other side so they would either close or
open completely and i was so mad yeah
and i was trying to really smoothly move
it without activating the automatic
moving thingy but then like i was i was
always like oh god i'm so close i'm so
close i can do this but then it would
move away again and later was just
watching i was doing that for a while
yeah you were kind of doing it for a
while you were just like looking at me
and i'm like
i was laughing at you and it was
entertaining to watch um and then you
just gave up i guess
yeah top 10 anime battles it's awesome
anime battles stupid curtains
it was really nice i don't want to go
home at that point i thought man i don't
want to go home this was like at that
point the curtain point was the point
where you thought i don't want to go
home
i guess no i guess it was like a
coincidence because then like the
current part was like a little bit like
halfway through the vacation i think
yeah
you were you were probably thinking that
because you thought ah kiwa is so funny
i don't want to leave her
but i mean if i can see if i get to see
that kind of thing every night just like
her fighting with the curtains you know
i would live a very happy life i would
just laugh
[Music]
precious moments
precious
moments
let's go
yeah let's go
man i'm gonna like you know
i i i spent like so long drawing this
but then
we kind of go through them so fast
[Laughter]
no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no that's not it i'm just i'm just
saying come on
it seems like you are really stressed
out when drawing these i don't know this
wasn't when this was after i finished
like all the drawings uh there was some
titles that were still like blank but
then i realized it was time for stream
right so i was like
it was just like film anything is better
than this it's not this is not the
laughing ha ha ha it's the
[Laughter]
panic huh yeah
i was also like panicking so hard
earlier like when we were like doing the
crap for the stream yeah you were a
witness of it raining and panicking yes
banger titles thank you i appreciate it
what is this
oh
this was us uh in dinner we were like
looking at
cat pictures yeah the last one last
enough yeah
it was so nice yeah that's what yeah we
ate uh ate steak she ate you what did
you eat
[Music]
um um
yeah i've been i think i had chicken on
the last night and i didn't need to
start it oh yeah it didn't you skip
started because you were like the one
started but yeah it's the night with the
live music and everything it was so good
it was so nice it also took a video
actually for private use for private use
yes yes yes yes me too you're really
good the singers are really good yeah
yeah
super nice levels
and then
and then this when we walk back no and
then um so before going to dinner
that was when the star story happened
like i was like what is that is that
like a plane or something no you're like
that guy
that's a plane because honestly there's
no
stars don't really twinkle where i am
where i was right yes
as long as this thing that you see in
the sky is not moving then it's not a
plane maybe it's just trying to stay in
place you know oh man it literally can
fine
yeah i mean like okay then like later on
like back from the dinner we were like
walking back to our place and then it
was just like there's so many there's so
many and they're all twinkling it was so
good it was so nice it's like reverse
mcflurry i'm hungry now for mexico
but yes it was really nice it was like
it was i've never seen something like
that so it really really stuck to my
mind to my memory you
know actually um someone wrote a
marshmallow to us that um they like in
some of these islands and some of the
resorts apparently they have like
stargazing tours yeah i don't think we
had something like that in our resort
but it would have been nice it was cool
to know there's very stargazing toys
with some people who are like you know
they know their things about stars yeah
yeah i used to think that
i didn't know stars could twinkle like
that so i used to think like them peop
these people who write stargazing as
their hobby they're so pretentious like
do they go to like the upper battery all
the time and like look at stars
and i'm like now you understand that
it's really pretty stars are really
pretty i like stars now
nice oh yeah i recommend it to you to go
to see the northern lights you know
somewhere in europe yeah yeah yeah i
wanna i wanna go we'll go crazy if you
if you see stars and you're already so
amazed by it then you gotta look at the
northern lights yeah yeah it's pretty
really pretty actually like once i went
somewhere uh and then we were supposed
to see something like that but
apparently the weather
the weather was it was either raining or
cloudy that's why on that day we
couldn't see it and then there was
really not much time because we had to
like go somewhere else anyway so yeah
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
literally right before sana commented
someone in the comments wrote well ask
sana or something
maybe ask santa for that two seconds
later
did you get like a message
someone mentioned you in a comment
so yeah
though i love stuff maybe santa could
give us a stargazing yeah please please
how do we sign up santa
yes i want to sign up please yeah she's
been here since the start how do you
know oh did you comment before i didn't
see it i didn't see
you see
but that now reminds me that they maybe
not they didn't have stargazing tours
but i did see in one of the restaurants
they had this big big big
thing to look into the sky oh right yeah
yeah like near the
sushi place that we ate yeah and i asked
if i could use it but it was daytime and
they said yeah you can use it but like i
was like well i guess now it's not not
not the best time to use it yeah then i
forgot about it but it was so big like
huge not not like the the finn telescope
but the beak the big one telescope
yeah it was like a huge thick thick one
yeah very thick the thickest of the
thick of the telescope yeah i don't know
how far you can feel with that
i don't know i want
the next time if i have a chance then i
would wanna
so my eyes were opened that day my my my
eyes like wow so beautiful i didn't tell
you that you know after the stream we
were gonna like go back and maybe we
were thinking we could watch the stars
through the you know the balcony but
they're they're all gone they packed up
and be like oh time to sleep bye
yeah
and there were no more styes
at least they were probably stars but
maybe it started becoming cloudy
and then the stars weren't so clear
anymore
sad but another time
yeah maybe another time i remember when
we were walking back from the restaurant
to the hotel room we we were barely
looking at the ground we were like
mostly just looking up in the sky yeah
yeah because it was that pretty it was
just like
oh
fascinating i'm fascinated what is this
i even forgot oh this is our stream the
one that yeah
the one the last one the last one where
you work so hard on like doing the
parts walking lyric lyrica what were you
doing again while i was doing that
um i was
i don't know we're doing something no i
was behind you
no but partially you were also running
around doing something what do you keep
saying running around i wasn't running
around
she keeps she keeps trying to paint this
picture that i'm just like somebody who
like
this is wrong
yeah you're often very visibly running
around i guess i was like walking doing
i don't know doing something
i mean what else are you supposed to do
you were busy
yeah yeah yeah all right
but anyways
was really fun
yeah
karaoke is so fun you know like usually
yeah we made it work even though we
didn't even like have proper like we had
headphones but elena even brought her
own headphone and i was like elena do
you have like a headphone splitter or
something and she brought something that
could split things but it was like not
exactly the right thing so unfortunately
we couldn't use it yeah
we were so close to perfection i know i
had a headphone amplifier that i used
for a off collab mainly like karaoke so
you can monitor and you know when
splitters like sometimes the sound
volume gets like kind of split uh this
one is like
uh powered so you know there's unlimited
power what yeah but anyways um yeah your
headphones didn't have one
thing but anyway it worked yeah yeah
that's what matters i mean we barely
heard the music when we were singing but
reyna was like with her hand she was
making like
ribbon movements yeah
in the ribbon yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yes yes i was trying something
oh yeah i was really impressed when you
immediately like you listened to the
delay once and then immediately you were
like so and so many milliseconds delay
and i try it out and it's absolutely
perfect when i play around with that on
obs in the past
i never got it right i i took like a
million tries and you immediately
understood how much delay i should put
in there
damn
it's just uh it's just i mean like i'm
glad it worked out but yeah
yeah we were like sharing headphones
like
yeah i could hear some stuff yeah i
could hear enough it was nice i had fun
i hope you guys had fun
[Music]
if you missed it it's on my channel it's
the q a and kyokus session we sang free
songs not much but it was a lot of fun
yeah
it was more oh and then in
uh
june
probably end of june we have a song
cover coming up so you can hear us sing
again but professionally but together
yeah mixed together
i saw the i saw the works in progress
stuff it's so spicy yay the ice it's
very very spicy indeed spicy
spicy spicy
nice
okay
basically well you know the punchline of
this comic
i don't want to go home
oh
both of them end like that yeah
my god it's like no this was like the
last night right well last night it was
you know the last dinner was so pretty
and then the night sky was so pretty and
the stream was so fun and then we
watched animal videos without you
protesting so
that was like oh this is the last night
you know what i i should be nice to
i was like she's not complaining at all
what is that she was just like watching
quietly she seems like she's okay with
everything i'm like i'm so confused but
also i will take this
i wanted to make my wayne happy
yeah um okay yeah you you already make
me happy that's all right and it's okay
[Music]
it's good that we did like two recap
streams because we we're really trying
to drag it out the whole experience it's
like oh i feel like after all of this
arc is arc
people keep saying maldives aren't after
all this is done i'm just gonna think
like
what nice memories but then like
i'll just think about it in my head i'm
just gonna try to keep remembering all
the details see this is why i wish i had
taken more pictures like none of the
scenery but like i don't know maybe of
you fighting with the curtains or
something
[Laughter]
so i will have something to remember you
but i i may have not gotten good
pictures of you alone but i did get some
good pictures of us
oh together yes yes yes i guess so yeah
yeah
i i i insisted i was like hey do you
mind taking yourself being together so
several times i did get i did get some
selfies and at the very end uh i asked
the butler to take a picture of us
together at the last dinner and also at
the at the departure in front of the
dodo airlines seaplane so i still have a
bunch of pictures of us together i was
like
i know you're shy but later on we'll be
happy that we took them so please
yeah i guess so
i guess so i guess so
yeah i wish i took i wish i just wish i
documented some pictures like the funny
stories you told me i felt like it would
be nice if i had a photo or two to
remember but that's not good i guess
i don't think
we took a nap if we took any more
pictures than this then we would have
been like permanently on our phones yeah
24 7. i guess so you're already pretty
close to it so it's hard to find the
right balance right
yeah it's okay you gotta and you gotta
take some pictures in your in your mind
in your brain
and try to remember it by looking for it
with your own eyes because the problem
is when you take pictures and videos you
always look through the screen from the
phone so you don't really enjoy the
scenery with your own
eyes that's correct that's true
that's true that's true what is the
title of this one
oh wait what ha ha ha is this the same
one oh never mind uh
is it
uh
oh no
we're kind of almost done
with the
[Music]
yeah
oh no we're kind of almost done how do i
do this
give me a second yes
yes yes and
let me just
you know what i like what i've observed
is that
since both of our
main languages is not english but we're
like kind of
around the same level and
we like whenever we're missing some
words we
like
fill it with some japanese words yeah i
feel like yeah we're already always like
on the same level so it really flows
well the conversation and and it's just
like when i speak with whole live
english members i feel like they they
have much more vocabulary but we're like
similar so i don't think it feels like
comfortable to talk to you just earlier
i asked you like you know like oh can
you go down a bit but instead of just
like down like below i said like can you
go downstairs a little bit
okay she met she met and i go down like
this and yeah she goes downstairs and
look downstairs
yeah that's just like
okay
downstairs bye-bye
and then like yeah something like that i
mix japanese all the time she does too
she says things weirdly sometimes i do
too you know language is hot all right
the bread is making it into something
spicy again spicy
what you guys
we're gonna i'm gonna
i don't care if you're uranus fans i'm
gonna put you in the usual room for
being so spicy for being so spicy don't
make spicy as if it's a bad word spice
is a good one
[Laughter]
everything is spicy if you want it to be
yeah spicy very nice tori linguist
okay
so this is basically just what happened
on the seaplane fly i felt like i wanted
to make a yonko
but i don't know what happened i decided
to not make a yonk coma so
yeah so apparently
effort throwing the seaplane
so much effort let's go
wow
see what you drew i understand it
perfectly fine perfectly fine
see this is okay don't make fun of me
don't make fun of me because this is
very personal it is the last day of the
trip and then we are on the sea plane to
the main island
wow
[Music]
yeah we were like um we weren't going on
the slingslang because um on the first
on this is the same seaplane that flew
us to the uh resort right and then we
wrote the same thing
uh but this time we were on the
back on like the absolute back of the
plane
yeah so it's like a little bit different
still the same though i guess um but you
know how on the
on on the way to the resort it was so
loud so we couldn't talk so we
communicated through our phones like
writing things down but i feel like i
don't know what to put on on the on the
way back i was so sad and that i just it
was just silence we i just was
quietly cried looked outside and thought
about how sad it is to leave yeah we
didn't think about saying anything yeah
yeah yeah we we we kind of didn't talk
at all the whole ride it was like
imagine it was like a 30 40 minute ride
and like we didn't really like talk at
all
yeah
and then but we talked for actions
because then i reached for you stop
i mean they already know anyways
but it's like i looked at her it was
like she was always like looking at the
window
looking at the window yeah
yeah
and then but you weren't like doing
anything it's like i guess it's all
right you know you need your your you
need your time and it's all right it's
noisy anyways i didn't want to like talk
and then yeah i'm just like yeah you're
just looking at the i don't know maybe
your sentiment i mean we get i get it
like everyone gets a little sentimental
but then yeah maybe she just like the
window seats so much and then i'm just
like don't cry
she's not crying so don't cry i really
didn't want to be like the only one
crying it's really awkward if that's
like the case
i think many people were silently crying
or being really sad about leaving this
is like
for other vacations i may be like a
little bit sad about leaving
but i was never this sad before about
leaving a vacation place because this
was just such a dream
yeah i guess so so unreal it is it is
yeah we talked about that a little bit
too haha
oh wait you didn't draw the hand holding
oh shut up it's not done
it's so impatient
where is that loot spicy hand holding
movement no stop role playing like chad
so basically i was like oh my god don't
cry she's not even crying why are you
crying no don't be like so it's like
trying to like
like close my eyes breathe breathe so
don't cry
and then
i glanced and then i tried my best to
draw my head draw bird hands
and then you were offering your hand
while still looking at the window i'm
like huh
so i just like took your hand with both
hands so i guess i don't know
live hand holding oh no we need to
censor it but move over your hands yeah
this was like a well
uh this was like a while though like
probably like the second half of the
trip like i was just like expecting
silence i guess
yeah and then i was like huh oh by the
way guys this is like right to left
sorry i forgot to say ah
yeah this is right to left i forgot to
say sorry guys okay you guys didn't
understand i'm just too used to right to
left
yeah and then so what happened
ah
here it is and then i looked at you
again
and then you're like you you're like
wiping your face but then i didn't want
to ask i thought to myself like is she
crying but then i didn't want to ask
yeah and then
and then i don't know like i guess like
throughout the flight like you were like
kind of like moving your hand around
like you know i'm just like uh just
really really subtly so i'm just like
you know
at some point i was just like holding my
tears and like i could i can't hold it
anymore i was trying to hold it back too
but then oh man that's so beautiful i
was thinking like
this is such a dream vacation
[Music]
you know the very beginning when we took
off i like had some tears coming down
but then i calmed down after like five
minutes and then after 10 minutes or so
i saw the lady two rows in front of us
crying like a baby so i was like oh
you're making me cry again and then i
started again
yeah by the way guys this is right to
the left you know i mean you can read it
however you want but it wouldn't make
sense
pretty much so
i guess yeah i just couldn't hold back
my tears nathan became pian
also like you know i just like looked
away i just looked away i was looking at
them
i was looking at your hand but like yes
i was looking at the left but because we
were in the absolute back the seat next
to us
was
just luggage
the window was covered yeah i didn't
even see that
you cuz you're too busy crying while
looking at the window
i could have looked over my shoulder
no but i was trying to not cry
i didn't want you to accidentally see me
crying i didn't even know if you were
crying or not so okay
yeah i didn't even notice that like you
know the people like
the next rose are crying so yeah
basically yeah i ended up crying while
looking at luggage very intently like
for the rest of the month i was just
like looking at the luggage and like
yeah i had to hold you with only one
hand because like the other hand i used
to wipe my tears
looking at the luggage respectfully
yeah yes yes ended up crying
and then
i guess yeah that is it and then
and then and then
all right the drawings
[Music]
why does this thumbnail look weird hold
on let me just
let me just try to what what about the
next layer
on it
the next layer ah
there was like a ah oops oops oops
oh there's mine oh there's more ah
so basically
after we landed she let go of her hand
and talk to me normally
yeah
what was i supposed to say no so yeah so
i didn't know if were you even crying so
i was i'm the only one crying after all
i didn't know
and then spoilers apparently
from yesterday's stream i found out i
guess not
um i really i really like this drawing i
guess i don't know it's just like a
rough thing but like i just like
drawings
[Music]
you should finish one of them with color
yeah i should probably maybe i will if i
uh i look so dead yeah yeah basically i
look so damn just like and then when you
when yeah when we were on the plane you
were just like chatting to me like
normally oh yeah by the way someone saw
him like so was she crying was she not
crying
only one i don't know it is a mystery
you're thinking too much training
yeah no but thank you thinking i know
but then look is like what if i'm the
only one sad about
it everyone's sad
everyone
even our butler maybe maybe yeah we were
waiting
even sad about leaving the butler
because she was so sweet like hello you
want to be friends with her oh me were
asking do you know what game called
animal crossing
what what's animal crossing
what animal crossing gia i don't know
but anyways yeah um i really enjoyed
drawing this one this is actually uh i
drew this
um i sketched this one last night um
yeah the stream was privated because you
know as you know i was watching the
otter live cam but then
at some point
uh there was sound the lady was like yo
it's feeding time how is everybody doing
i'm like oh shoot
i need to trim that and then i will
unprivate it
yeah
yeah yeah good afternoon uh-huh yeah
good good afternoon everyone
all right i told you there was no sound
so it was okay to
unmute
and then i kind of forgot like i could
have just like you know
un like just muted the sound anyways
right but then i didn't because i let my
guard down
but yeah anyways my life is drawn i'm
gonna be honest with you it's been a
while since i actually um drew
this
so i mean drew drew stuff remember i was
telling you like oh my god i even forgot
like how to do stuff how to export
properly like the settings i used to do
this
a lot but i guess these days i don't do
this it definitely looks like you have
experience yeah you should draw more
good uh yeah maybe maybe maybe like like
a secret uh like you know you know that
like inna and money and senpai and sana
na na
there are like so many good draw artists
but then there's some secret ones like
you who only expose their skill on
guarded phone but
if you had more time to draw then you
could probably draw some really amazing
beautiful pictures so do it
but don't you also draw i feel like i've
seen you do drawings
yeah but i also i feel i feel like i
used to be better
because i i used to i wanted to be
um like a character designer for rpg
games like tails off when i was younger
yeah that was my
my my goal in life so i was really
actively drawing for a couple of years
and i was getting good for my age but
then eventually i stopped because i i
got interested in other things and
i don't know i lost inspiration and
motivation for drawing so now sometimes
i draw on my streams but i don't know
i'm not this good i'm not as good
anymore no no no motivation and time
time time time time and motivation is
the you know oh after
ah yeah this is not related this is like
10 just anyways yeah i had to reposition
my drawing tablet because you know i was
just not getting anything done with my
current setup where it's just you know
positioning such a not ergonomic way um
people who watch my stream know like i
snipped all of my cable management
angrily because i was like you know
otherwise i'm not getting anything done
so right now my keyboard's like a little
bit like messed up on the side but it's
the perfect setup for drawing
but yeah hold up
are you using a cintiq uh yeah like the
small one like the 13 inch one i'm using
uh cintiq as my third monitor so i can
also draw on it and it's a relatively
big one but it's really good to have it
as the third monitor and whatever you
want to draw you can just move it closer
yeah that's so nice yeah yeah me too me
too me too me too
yes you should draw more too maybe we
should do something yeah
i don't know i don't know i i feel
embarrassed drawing for people on the
stream because i i don't feel like i'm
good enough so i need more practice and
i need to draw privately maybe yeah i
totally get you though i totally get you
that's also why i don't really do
drawing streams it's just it gets a
little bit overwhelming sometimes but
wow we can just do whatever you can't
focus i can't focus when i'm streaming
like i can't focus on drawing like
i can't get anything done
yes yes
yeah it's all right we can do what just
anything we're comfortable with i would
definitely love to like you know play
more stuff with you i guess yes yes
yes yes was that it now oh yeah yeah
this is basically yeah that's the end of
the
page last page
[Music]
and then this is basically just uh some
collection of drawings that i did
uh i don't think i need to do this
this is um
this is you know us in the airport
watching animal videos and we realize
[Laughter]
[Music]
and then you opening the current i
wanted to draw you like fighting with
the curtain but it was like a little bit
too complicated so i ended up just
drawing you opening the curtains it's
morning
yeah good morning yes
yes yes
and then
you
[Laughter]
[Music]
because i left earlier than you yeah
no i just i remember like you waved at
me you were like looking back i remember
that was that one so vividly so i tried
like drawing it la mao bye
you should post this on on my arts of
ash's hashtag
i didn't look that cute when i was
snorkeling
nice
i'm fine you look plenty cute it's
alright even when you're um
and this one's just like thank you molly
thank you mama
[Music]
there yeah there was a lot of things i
wanted to draw but i couldn't make it
into a story so like this page i just
decided to you know just draw that's so
cute so can you finish the one where
we're looking at the animal videos ah
sure i mean i i guess i'll try yeah i
can try
didn't i when we were watching at the
airport i feel like at some point i put
my arm around your shoulder
really
i feel like i did or at least around the
seat maybe i didn't touch you directly
maybe i guess so yeah i guess like on
the last day we were like suddenly like
way touchier
i feel like it's just like
the sad mood getting to us so we're just
like you know if you want to be touchy
now's the time
[Laughter]
yeah
and then i feel like you know when when
you were like when when i went with you
in line i just like you know because
i was always like asking like you know
does your arm hurt or something but then
i guess i just didn't really care
anymore so i just like grabbed your arm
right i just like yeah when you were
like in line just like hey
the last moment oh but then but then we
were saying goodbye and you were just
gonna like
walk away but then i i pulled you back
and i gave you a hug oh remember yeah
didn't we like twice or something
we've hung twice in the airport i was
like one off i'm not hug
can't just go
[Music]
yeah big hug we got better at hugging
later so the first hug yeah we improved
from the very first time
i felt like it's just like you know
it's like it's like maybe shy but
i felt like on the last day like you
know it's not the time to be shy you
know so i yes you know it's not the time
yeah
yeah so yeah yeah
that was a sentimental last day but we
made the most out of it also with the
tour yeah yeah it was fun you didn't
draw any parrots we were so excited by
the paris i can't draw parrots i didn't
have time
the parrots this the parrot was called
naruto by the way the red one if you
guys yeah
yeah it was so weird like
there are some
i wouldn't even call them weebs because
i feel like if you if the only thing you
know is naruto then it's like so
superficial that you
you're not really a weeb at that point
but well like in the shop as you told
and in the the guy with the parrot they
both mentioned naruto so it's like is
that the only anime you know
i think it's just like very very famous
yeah like when you watch local tv for
example you probably have naruto
something you don't have yeah we all
have a channel
yeah
but it was really funny it wasn't
expected you know like you asked hey
what's the name it's naruto
also said something about like how we
sounded right
yeah yeah yeah when we were at the
counter i was like paying for my for my
souvenirs and he asked us like even if
we're japanese or if we're like if we've
been to japan or something and then it
kind of got quiet when he asked us i
don't know were you like scared of
doxing yourself or something no not
really i was just really confused
because um i don't really feel like i do
but i guess i do subconsciously do it so
just having somebody pointed out was
just like
you know
[Music]
at least i
i didn't want to like talk for years and
told them i lived in japan i guess i
picked up picked up those uh
um traits and that's right it is not the
first one to tell me like austrian
friends they also tell me
it's funny hmm
yeah it was a little there we go again
like all the time hmm
[Music]
yeah i don't even realize because it's
like nobody ever comments about that
like when i say stuff like that
okay
okay yeah i'm gonna i don't know if you
want me to finish this one i will try i
will try to touch it up and this one or
the other one
or i don't know any anything they're all
cute they're all cute i mean you know
i'll do what i can um should i just post
this one to arts and fashions like the
sketches
okay
retweet i'll retweet this this
mysterious new fan artist in my
community
who is this newcomer oh my gosh
so you must be so into kiwanis
i guess i'm her orsi oh my gosh really
i guess we do have it's because we have
some things in common what could it be
could it be that we're both birds oh my
god
or that we're both in a hole alive
[Laughter]
and i should draw you two sometimes oh
draw me draw me draw me only a few only
if you feel like it though
yeah i feel like it now now that i see
the cute pictures
but anyways um honestly to be honest i
want i really really really want to draw
more uh if not comics then you know just
just drawings like this but
unfortunately i didn't really have
enough time
it's just like really really hard it's
you know i wanted to draw you with the
floatie i remember you were
when we were at the beach it was yeah it
was fun it was a fun memory there were
so many really really nice memories that
i wanna you know make in two drawings i
thought but yeah maybe in the maybe
sometime not the stream but maybe in the
future
but yeah you did a great job i didn't
think you would draw this much no i
tried my best i did what i could i
wanted i wanted to illustrate my
feelings i want to make sure the
feelings are total cool to the chat
and everybody
yo let's go
did you not draw it i did
i did draw the stars yes yes you're too
late
too late uh wait did we actually get all
the titles for everything for all the
house the miraculous
the miraculous recipe
fresh just okay if
we forgot something i'll just like leave
it as
hot
sounds good to me sounds good but yes um
i did say that we will be asking and i
will be asking we'll be answering the
some of the questions that we haven't
answered for
you know last time
[Music]
uh where where where is it
where is this did you save them
no uh i guess we can just like read the
mouth can you read the mouth from me
pretty please i have something okay
is that okay yeah sure why why are we
making a speed run
oh cause i'm feeling like kind of weird
oh okay okay yeah yeah yeah no worries
oh
there might be one or two questions that
have been uh
answered last time or answered also in
the previous recaps recap stream but
whatever
okay question number one okay we need to
settle this which burp is the better
swimmer i think we're both like i think
we're both like really mediocre yeah i
feel like we're both mediocre like
i mean it's not like we kind of need to
swim swim right in the resort no i feel
like we're mostly just relying on our
floaties
and we also in our on our snorkeling
equipment but i think we're both
not not good swimmers we can we can
survive above like on the surface of the
water
yeah but yeah
probably not not speed swim like that
lady did yeah
yeah
the bird reverse drink was better
somebody said
you are the one who rivers
it's all right you know it's all right
it was an accident it was an accident
all right there was one single nihongo
question
[Laughter]
otherwise it doesn't enter your brain
yeah yeah let me let me read it hold on
what oh
i'm so lazy it translated for me
uh when when during the garden phone
collab
uh you put a
topic that was like uh
holotoy in the maldives and
the question is if it was already
decided that we're going there at that
moment yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
it was actually quite a bit before that
but before the stream it was just like
we were telling subaru while we were
waiting for the others we were telling
subaru that we're going to the maldives
together
so
i don't know the whole stream ended up
being um like all these topics with
the whole torii on the beach yeah
because everybody i think everybody was
like um this spirit vacation spirit i
wanna go i want to go something like
that yeah that's the cause that's the
actual cause cause we're going this way
[Music]
next question is a bit long one listen
well reina aye okay
hello kiara hello rainer thank you for
keeping us posted on how you've been
enjoying a vacation now that you have
experienced the paradise that is the
maldives what would be the attraction or
activity that you would recommend for
first-time goers based on what you have
done so far okay first answer this
snorkeling
yes snorkeling
struggle
and we didn't do it but you should dive
and maybe rent a
kayak yes yes
oh we didn't do kayaking we wanted to do
it but it's like we were watching people
doing water sports but we didn't do it
ourselves and and the guy who was like
on the board in the room with the
parachute that was pretty insane
i was laughing at him every time he fell
down into the water it's really fun
though i mean i would want to try that i
would want to try if the weather was
better i think i would probably want to
try it yeah but it looks so scary the
one with the parachute that just oh god
i'm so scared of that you because i
think you need a lot of strength in your
arms and your legs
[Music]
okay i mean it looks so tight yeah looks
like does anyone ever do that before in
the chat did you guys ever try that
thing where even even the one where the
boat pulls you or the one where the wind
where the parachute like pulls you i
guess yeah
both of them look very difficult
paragliding but i feel like if you don't
do it on vacation then you won't be able
to do it like in the city or like you
know whatever right so it's just like no
you have the chance
oh there's one person who says yes ah
two people two people
they're fun yeah but they're really like
difficult no
this looks really difficult have you
ever been on a jet ski before
no
jet ski
machine
um isn't that the same thing
no no but it don't when you say jet ski
don't you mean the person who's like
behind the scenes uh the the speed belt
being pulled on the skies
okay then both then both
now i only been on the boat
and that was already terrifying because
my my friend my ex-roommate she was like
on the front she was controlling the
boat and i was on the back and she was
like more than the
the type who wants to go fast but then
it was so bouncy because when she goes
so fast it like bounces over the waves
and i was so scared of falling down
because of the water on the on the seat
it was so slippery and i thought i would
fall down it was so scary ah
i've never been yeah i've never gone on
that but uh what have been what i've
done is um snowmobile so it's kind of
like on the snow it was kind of it was
it was nice
you told me that's cool
yeah one of the coolest things i can do
we have no snow around here so it was
nice that we did it anyways yeah
next question that is still the same
person yes also the limited number of
items that you brought with you is there
something that you do not have right now
like it means at the vocation that you
wish you did bring so something that you
didn't bring but you wish you brought it
is there something um
oh my camera yeah i um i do have one
myself but then i was just like well
maybe i don't need it because maybe i
have phone camera because like the 20kg
i had like 18 kg ish when i went you
know so i was like
really really really really really
trying to pack light yeah i was also
thinking about bringing mine i even like
i was i was like um switching the
batteries and the
the the
the film it was i was about to bring it
but but then i took it out again because
i was like i'm gonna really be getting
getting on the weight and i was i had
exactly 20 kilograms so any extra item
would have been a problem yeah but
besides that i guess
a serious answer would be um
to bring like the the proper headphone
splitter that we needed
that would have been good yeah
oh well yeah i guess so
yeah but besides that i think we both
had pretty much everything we needed
okay next question
did both of you bring snacks foods from
your home for the other to try if yes
one of the foods and what's the
impression dana brought something i
brought something i brought chips i
brought
cereal flavored chips like savory cereal
yeah and then yeah i tried them i never
had cereal chips before that was
interesting yeah yeah
and it was i mean it was nice i guess
you brought the cake
the yeah the cake cake it was a present
for you but then i i was i really wanted
to eat it too so i ate my
oh yeah yeah that was what the tweet was
about yeah
yeah i was like this is definitely not
about the dream dolls probably about
that
yes yes i brought some food too
no we i didn't bring holo me because i
feel like when where are we gonna cook
it instant noodles i don't know
yeah that's how i mean follow me is the
very very tasty instant noodles remember
i asked you do you eat instant noodles
ah
yeah you said not really so yeah i
didn't bring it too because you know
where where are we gonna cook it we're
gonna have nice dinner anyways right
yes yes yes yes okay next question yeah
are you um are you planning on trying
diving did you enjoy snorkeling and the
marine life i love snorkeling i want to
try diving of course next time yes
yes i think we are both since it was our
first time so fascinated
yeah it was so fun i was like oh so i
didn't know snorkeling was this fun i
didn't think i would like it so much but
the feeling
was so nice it's generally also like so
easy like you don't have to be a good
swimmer or anything and yeah you can
enjoy it without
being a pro swimmer i really like that i
mean i had some problems with i mean if
anyone has advice for that i would like
to
have the advice how to not get the sea
water into your snorkel device yeah
yeah i feel like on the first second day
i used to have that too but i feel like
on the third day i got a little bit i
got much better that i'm not you know i
don't really get it
what i mean it was the other way around
like when i first got like soft water
like in my goals i'm like oh my god am i
going to die
i always say that there's one thing
about dana she's so dramatic every time
something happens she's like i'm gonna
die i'm gonna die oh i need
maybe maybe your chat knows that anyway
because they watch you for hours and
hours and hours and you say that on
stream too yeah do you um not really
actually i guess i don't know
i guess that my brain is just on
vacation mode
that it just kind of slipped out right
okay
oh she's like
did you feel you could disconnect from
the world during this vacation this
vacation has been awesome thanks for the
gorilla streams and twitter updates but
i don't know if you consider streaming
on twitter
as work hours rather than relax time
thinking emoji
what about you you think
i feel like when i said this yesterday
we're just gonna answer it again i feel
like we
um
even though we were both because i think
we're both kind of addicted we were on
our phones a lot and we were on social
media a lot but just because we're also
so at least me i was really excited to
share every little moment with you guys
yeah and um streaming is fun together so
it wasn't it wasn't like we were
the whole time like in
in working mood
but i do think we still got like time to
relax definitely like if you're in in an
island like that
small tiny island with a resort with
dreamy
um scenery like how can you not relax
right it's like it is so beautiful yeah
for me like i don't know i feel like my
phone is already like sort of like a
part of me you know call me addicted or
whatever but it's it just kind of feels
like you know if you're sick and you're
prohibited from playing then you would
feel sad right that's just it you know i
didn't feel like it was nice to be a
little bit detached from like the usual
like work and stuff um i still have my
phone but i felt like i could relax it
was a really really good time i spent a
lot of time with
just talking and like chilling and i had
a very very good time
yeah and also like hearing the sound of
the waves 24 7
literally everywhere you go
that's that was really relaxing and
the water just felt so good like finally
being in the ocean again
[Music]
it was also it had perfect temperature
even on the days where it was kind of
colder
the water still didn't feel ice cold
um so it was really really really nice
how i felt i feel like we we definitely
were able to disconnect just because
we're also on that little island yeah we
disconnected from the rest of the world
everything was so different so it really
really worked out um yes
and what made you choose maldives for
your vacation she chose it was me
yeah she asked me and it just happened
to line up i've always wanted to go but
somebody's inviting me so let's go right
i'm so glad you wanted to join me
yeah maldives is like a dream
destination for many people in europe at
least very famous
i guess also in korea apparently in
korea apparently yeah
yeah very well known in korea as well
um but yeah maldives was always like i
heard it so many times when i was
younger i heard about people going there
on honeymoon but i always heard it was
really expensive so i always thought oh
i could never go
but here we are we were in the motives
yeah
dream come true
me tell me too
dream
you destination answer this one was the
weather they're quite wonky or pretty
much the same throughout your stay so
messed up so up the weather
it was basically it was just you know we
can't really let our guard down you know
you see the weather report and say oh
it's gonna rain here and there this hour
no it's not accurate you have to be like
super spontaneous you know i remember
the time we streamed uh was it smash or
something
remember the rain it was super cloudy
and rainy and then when we streamed the
rain stopped or something
yeah
and then after the stream i think it
started raining again
but i mean it's okay we decided to
stream it was fun i like streaming yeah
but also yeah that's just how it's
illustrated yeah
but that's mostly like the first half of
the vacation the first three days it was
like constantly like that bad weather
and then
but we we still were able to
have like a few hours per day where
there was no rain and we could go into
the water and then later the last three
days it was really sunny and hot as
yeah it was really really really hot
like in a pleasant way i guess so it's
just like oh finally made us more
appreciative like i said like a thousand
times of the good weather to be honest
especially on the very last day when we
were like out taking those those
pictures and it was so hot i was
thinking like this is like this is
so hot i want the weather from the first
few days back
remember like we were like all dressed
up late for pictures and stuff and then
we went over like 10 minutes and then
yeah you said so much it was so drenched
in sweat after that i tried to stop my
sweating but continuously um having the
tissues like
tapping it on my forehead and all that
but it was so hot oh my god um
so then then i wanted the monsoon the
the cold weather back but
overall um we we were able to handle
every situation
accordingly i wouldn't i still wouldn't
recommend going during the monsoon
season because honestly
it wasn't even much cheaper you would
expect that during that season it would
be cheaper but i feel like it was still
very very expensive so
it doesn't really make that much
difference if you can't go during a
normal season
go during the normal season not during
the monsoon season do it i felt like the
best weather was like the like day four
because it started
getting better but also there was a
little bit of like clouds right so it
was just like not very hot but no rain
something something yes yes yes today
was good yeah yeah definitely actually
that makes me think like if you don't go
into if you don't go during the monsoon
season but during the high whatever
season then
it will be every day like the last day
we had oh and i don't know if i can
survive that me too so maybe it's chosen
maybe it wasn't really that bad after
all yeah
we had a good mix uh next next one yeah
any thoughts on doing more 3d collabs
after the vacation like i guess he means
the vr vr i would love to do more
definitely i would love to
still don't know what yeah i am planning
to i want to oh it's fun okay okay we
can we could try to somehow reuse the
set uh from last time yeah yeah yeah we
could we could we could definitely
but i i generally i don't want to do vr
too much because it's really meant
excited for me like setting up
everything i forget everything every
time and i always have to help and then
the headset is so heavy i hate
it yeah yeah yeah i get it i get it it
was me i mean it was pretty like i was
thinking like wow
even i was stressed like especially
because of the unexpected there's so
many unexpected things that can happen
there's always there's so many things
that can go wrong
and yeah vr collab
usually like i don't know but too but
for normal collabs i usually always tell
the collab partner to meet before like
half an hour earlier and then for vr
it's like when i'm the one organizing it
then i would be there like two hours
before preparing but then
the others i would ask them to join one
hour before but one hour is still not
enough like they start coming in one
hour before because we've we've done a
lot of vr and myth they start coming in
and then yeah everybody everybody's like
ahmed this and that nama this and that
but emma can you send me an invite i
mean why is this not working i mean what
do i need to do and then ami keeps on
trying to help everybody and and it
takes a lot of time there's some fixes
that don't work and yeah it's just it's
just so much and it's very stressful
every time yeah i mean i don't mind i
don't mind showing up like two hours
honestly yeah
you know for like a peace of mind you
know
man
but you would think that maybe one hour
should be enough but yeah every time the
vr streams get delayed because of these
technical problems
you think you have it all figured out
but then a new problem shows up and uh
it's just like that it's just like that
you know sometimes it's like the room
kind of bugs out and then it's like oh i
can't join for some reason it's kind of
like uh you know
i don't see you i don't hear you well i
i can't my legs are wobbling weirdly
bliblable
is such a mvp she's so good she's so
helpful yeah
nice thank you
next one there's two more two more
questions that i have to send to you
okay
about your snuggling stories what's the
deepest you've done so far what's uh
what are the most interesting things
you've seen when snuggling
um
deepest i don't know because like
honestly like
we just went and we didn't go deep down
yeah we didn't really go like there's
there's only so deep you can go right
because yeah you have the thing
um yeah the snorkeling and the air so we
yeah we always
floated at the top
we want to go deeper with diving
equipment
yeah like remember like the one past the
coral seems interesting
maybe next time i will bring like a
better setup to record underwater i want
to bring a better set up to record on
the water so i can make like clear
footage yeah like a gopro i don't own
one actually do i own one probably not
yeah
i don't own one but that's a good reason
to get one yeah yeah yeah yeah
definitely yeah
[Music]
i i would want to go but i would be a
bit scared like what if ah there's some
scary fish but usually when you go
diving i think if you're not a pro then
usually you have like some kind of
diving instructor with you yeah so you
should be safe i guess yeah i guess so
and then if you want to if you need to
if you want to dive alone then you would
need a license right so either way i
think so yeah i think we're gonna get
you know something like that yeah yes
and the most interesting thing we kind
of mentioned yesterday i think elena
said the what was it that finn long boy
oh what was it called
the long boy
[Music]
one of two things like we weren't sure i
looked them up even with a needle fish
no needle fish trumpets
yeah needle fish the teeth are so scary
though
yeah
and then the one that i thought the most
interesting i only saw it so shortly
because it just swam away so quickly
into the dark
but it was like some fish with a with a
horn on its forehead oh yeah it almost
looked like a shark but i don't think it
was a shortcut i like
more like a relatively like mid-sized
fish with no special colors
but a horn on its forehead
unicorn fish unicorn fish it's not white
but unicorn you don't need corn fish i
saw like a flat fish that's like white
colored huh
maybe that ah but no i feel like the
horn was longer
maybe maybe it was that though it's
already been too long but it looks so
stupid oh my god the unicorn fish looks
so stupid
don't call it stupid
it looks so stupid but that might have
been it actually oh it seems like
sometimes they have longer and sometimes
shorter horns ah maybe
it looks so stupid ah it looks so stupid
it looks cute don't call it stupid yeah
if you see it you think too that looks
so stupid
it looks so fake like someone just put a
human nose on on a finger
the unicorn fish will remember that
kiara oh so funny
all right last one
last one i picked because i wanted to
thank you um
has elena asked you for a back massage
she didn't really ask me but she started
massaging me when i was preparing for
the stream oh
wasn't the voice i was so happy
wasn't the vocal smash one
i don't remember which one it was but
you started messaging me and i'm like oh
my god is this really happening thank
you thank you oh my god and i was trying
to get the most out of it and then and
then reina actually she said that i
should massage her back sometime but
before i got to do that on the next day
she would randomly massage me again
so kind i love people who randomly
massage me yeah i do that actually but
like usually i just like to like when i
pass by and people's backs are exposed
to me i'm just like
but then i would walk away for 20
seconds and then she would be like no no
i would walk away can i just quote you
this is really confusing when people's
bags are con
exposed to me i go like
but then i go back and i'm like well no
what
huh what
it really confusing what you just said
oh no no i said i said but uh you know
when people's bags are exposed to me i
massage you know i get tempted to
massage them but then i walk away after
20 seconds because i get bored
ah
okay okay that makes more sense but then
but then you were you were like no then
okay and then i guess i can't it's not
like i have anything else to do
now but at one point at the end i was
like i guess i still owe you a massage
so i gave you i gave you a little bit of
a back massage yeah yeah but you said
that you have more like lower back um
pain and more
shoulder pain and i said that i i don't
know how to massage the lower back it's
kind of difficult but you know like i'm
i i am not picky i am not picky
everything hurts so you know
upper back no problem no problem
you take everything yeah yeah i tried to
give her a shoulder massage and
but your shoulders were so katai
yeah
and yours is too
oh thank you i like it as a compliment
all right i guess so
but yes
somebody actually asked me like did kia
did you ask kiart to step on you that
did happen no
that did not happen
yeah it didn't happen what the hell
yeah i never asked you i never asked you
to step on my back no that didn't happen
but did you ask someone else before
oh yeah
muna stepped on my back kobo stepped on
my back yeah it's like it's kind of like
a recurring thing so i was like oh shoot
i should have asked her yeah
why why no no no no no no no you thought
that's scary
i feel like i would break your back no
listen it's like you know remember the
massage person they were doing like the
whole massage like what do you think is
happening they also use their limbs
they are professionals they know what
they're doing the thai massage they know
how to crack the bags and they did some
really funny moves with us
but then uh i guess that's how it is
like indonesians people who are you know
in indonesia we i guess we just like
somehow get that um passive passive
skill
of massage to some extent
[Music]
maybe you should step on my back then ah
i don't know we can arrange that next
time probably
gently though please yeah gently of
course of course i won't just i won't
break your back of course no i will be
very gentle
scared yeah it's good now you didn't do
it this time though because i have a
history of hurting myself on vacations
[Music]
yeah
yeah that was the last question oh yes
yes thank you so much for asking
to answer all your all your thoughts
also with our stories
yes yes yes yes
and i hope you guys also enjoyed the
drawings we're just gonna like go
through them like very very quickly
we're gonna go through them very quickly
ah there we go
we didn't see the beginning yeah let's
just scroll
very
wow
yeah i don't know should i upload this
yes yeah
i'm still going to question what is that
upload them all they're so precious
yes yes and so much time
yeah i spent a lot of time on this
actually pretty much
you know i'm just so good
he's so cool nick can you get right
whirling isn't throwing yes yes yes so
embarrassing so sad
i like the face on the uh
last one when we were like embarrassed
oh yeah
animal video
so nice
[Laughter]
[Music]
you know like i feel like these can some
of these can be like reaction images
yes oh yes
you don't want to go home
i don't want to go home oh and this is
the uh
last day of the trip
bad one
i think i like this one like the panel
and the bottom
i feel like
see i see that it has a lot of uh sense
sense sense oh yes
that's probably japanese right
yeah you said so yeah that's japanese
definitely
english it's an english word but it's an
english word it is an english word
yes yes yes
i like this
it's so good
i can totally imagine this is like being
printed in a book like first you have
the normal panels and then there's one
big page with a big panel like this yeah
yes yes yes and then this is the last
one
animal videos opening curtains playing
circling barfing saying bye thank you
mountains and thank you kiwawa
thank you everybody for watching
i was so fast walking away apparently
that um i lost my eyes and left them in
the maldives
[Laughter]
sometimes i see that in manga yeah yeah
don't worry i was just
joking i can draw you like the eye emoji
on your face
i left my eyes and where are my eyes
where my eyes your eyes
your eyes you're so in love with the
maldives that it's stuck there oh yeah
they wanted to continue looking at
dynamics
yeah
anyways
that is it guys thank you so much for
watching and thank you for hanging out
with me today too oh i never want this
vacation to end but you know what you
know the end of the vacation marks the
start of another plan right so i'm just
gonna call it i'm gonna cope and think
that way you're okay actually i'm gonna
be on
a plane next week anyway to germany yeah
germany oh very nice not really a
vacation but
but it's so exciting because it's an
event
nice nice day come and i
you know now that i went on a trip on a
plane now i want to go elsewhere too but
i still don't know what yeah yes yes
travel travel travel travel all right
how do
[Music]
uh thank you for watching and goodbye
goodbye yeah yeah yeah how do you say
hello
[Music]
so aggressive oh my god
thank you for having me on the channel
thank you thank you
everybody
[Music]
you
do
[Music]
bye
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
too
[Applause]
[Music]
hello
you