[Music]
does does it work does it work yo
looking for me yo yo yo yo yo I need to
ask chat oh my gosh this this mouse is
so slippery I can't
deal K Kitty
[Music]
key hello there we are here in Minecraft
toe just us just the two of us along
with the staff of
[Music]
course your rival is over there oh my
what my rice your rival oh my rival
sorry I was thinking about
food we're not offici
[Music]
my golden armor I need to where do I put
it is there like lockers
here the chat is low that the chat is
low is because the way they set the hold
on I'm gonna set the
um the volume
yeah can
I is there like a locker where I can put
my diamond
armor oh uh you can put it here is it
better wait I think that's one that
one's full
sorry let me is it better
now still
low don't worry I I'll hold on to it
yeah sorry guys it's because um I'm on a
very different setup that I'm not
familiar with so I'm going
[Music]
to does it work now
is it good
now and oh yeah the other team that is
here there was like two
okay sorry I did a little intro way okay
okay I'm going to do my little intro
alone too then I'll listen though
okay attention please I win from whole
life ID generation 2 what's up guys been
a while I'm going to do practice with
Wawa for holo ID Cup tomorrow let's
freaking go guys
w t ton tonj lima lima lima tonj she's
so smart already she's like she's like
honorary Indonesia member cuz she
knows and that's like what matters
honestly what the is this pretty much it
though are you like we uniform what is
this uh yeah this is the uniform they
told us to wear you're not wearing it oh
well I'm going to wear it tomorrow
because it's um because the real event
is tomorrow I'm going to wear it
tomorrow oh it looks like I'm going to
go to school in this I'm like a
student H
okay uh it's high school uniform in
Indonesia oh
wow wow pants I'm wearing pants pants I
guess pants were not banned
yet all right oh God I think to Welcome
to the B Bo
[Laughter]
[Music]
now me and Ru will guide you guys inside
the
B please follow us okay
you
know let's
go I have a question
yeah did did you all build this on your
own yeah yeah that's [\h__\h] we did that's
crazy I thought you guys were going to
hire
people just hysterically
answering yes Blood Sweat and Tears go
ahead literally are Blood Sweat and
Tears Who whoo whoa whoa whoa what is
that why is it doing that it's security
system
security down and then we climb down the
berries
climb down climb
down
wow one Chad um I feel like my mouse
moves like you know too fast you know
what I mean how do I change that
in okay hi hi
hi please come here
yeah when iost and I was like how again
but then I did it
[Music]
one more time welcome to
the so we have uh five games in total g
go five G okay five games wow uh Lima
wow yeah the first one is actually
called treasure
hunt um because we want to keep it as a
surprise for now we're not going to do
it but let me explain the rules
[Music]
uh no
so basically we'll be hiding emeralds in
a bunch of chest and then you guys will
have to um look for it but there's going
to be a lot of gimmicks going to be a
lot of platforming so you guys have to
work together to actually get the
emerald that's the Treasure Hunt game
that's the Treasure Hunt game but we're
not going to do it today okay is it easy
it's easy you you just need to open test
okay is it time do we have to be fast
with
it do we all do it at the same time all
all
teams so you can also hit like other
team
members oh we can hit them okay wait can
we I don't remember I I'll have to check
with the staff again
okay oh it's the flags you want it
yes here you
[Music]
go there you go
ah why are you bleeding from one of your
eyes why am I bleeding from one of my
eyes that's the Indonesian flag on her
uh I didn't see the white part oh I'm
not oh but for now follow me first
[Music]
wow wow so God who how do you wait I
want to can you ol can you tell me the
like history not history but like when
you guys were building this like who
made the plans of the layout and what
what you built it right but did someone
else make the layout or did you guys
make it because you guys are insane oh
some somebody else made the layout we
just built oh but that's crazy how long
did it take
two months was it oh my God two three
months I think I saw you guys building
the floor
here that was a
night goats absolute goats
yeah so if you guys built it in case any
accidents happen I can sue you guys in
particular for yeah sure why not causing
[Laughter]
it like if the stones from the ceiling
fall down on me and what kind of
scenario is that our building is safe
really really
no
no I sue you I sue you but so far all is
good no problem all is good jaanese
all let me introduce you this is the
Simon says um stage
[Applause]
[Music]
so uh to put it simply we'll be doing
Simon says but everything will be in
Indonesian wait you mean there's stuff
down there Simon says no no no just this
platform this is Simon
says I'll be explaining a little bit
[Music]
spee fore
Yeah so basically we'll be thank you
yeah we'll be doing Simon say and it
will also be kind of a memory game
because we'll be giving you guys
instructions in Indonesian by the way
it'll be like cons
consecutive it'll be consecutive orders
in Indonesian and everybody has to do it
so like it's not only the guest team but
the ID Girls also have to do it so it's
a memory game for
them and uh if you succeed you'll get
emeralds which is very important because
you need to collect as many
emeralds okay yeah it'll lead to a very
big event this game we will practice
right
yeah
soda I almost forgot remember anything
yet so these are the words that you guys
need to
remember K
Kitty KY K kitty kitty
Kanan Kan which is right Mig right
Mig which forward
forward OPP backwards you got to go back
J and then numbers from one
[Music]
toath empath I'm sort of anath Lima
empath lima lima Li
and then
s what
P what I thought that's
ton T is T is different but p p is like
Rand hit but tonj is like punch you know
but in the in the in the text you sent
me it says pukul equals hit SL Punch
Yeah so it's like a more the more broad
term
oh can I say t
punch okay I don't have to use these as
long as it's Indonesian I don't have to
use these particular words or do I have
to oh you just need to memorize them and
that's it but can I say
t
yeah it's just that you know uh when
we're doing the game uh the instructions
will be saying P instead of T that's as
long as you know you know what me
talking about this right now already
made me remember it I think just if I
can change
good I'm just uh can you hear my voice
clearly
actually yeah okay
cool I just like tweaked it a little bit
sh
sh J is kind of similar
with
jun j
[Music]
how can we remember all these words
until
tomorrow but I told you yesterday
[Music]
I had no time true you're
right come come come
here which one is difficult for you all
of them except
[Music]
T but
everything just the it's not the
singular words it's like the amount of
words why
speakes you're so cute
[Music]
right yeah why are we speaking three
languages now I don't know it's just the
japanish
thing
yeah how many are there I see only
one but is it that's
long
tech
so so you don't have to remember yeah
you don't have to remember wna cuz warna
is uh technically is redundant so just
remembera yeah easy right if if they
were make you remember
is there any other
colors
no maybe is it because of that red
block
maybe okay and then there's
lamp a
[\h__\h] maybe maybe a red if if red you go
to the red
stone yeah probably okay well for today
for today I'll just look at the
reference
she and uh I will you know just learn
how the game works today and then
tomorrow I will know the words for sure
but today I just look at the words I
think uh if you already played the game
you will eventually like you know put uh
you know like a priority in your brain
like which words are more important than
others like which one you have you
absolutely have remember
honestly no because you always only
said to me but today I learned Lima Ki
Lima Ki you never learned not really I
don't think I don't think I knew what
you were saying so
Lima okay andisa will be giving
instructions are we playing this with
all teams at the same time I think so
let's go there you go
[Music]
okay
s where's your
tail
I is that what goes on
India behind the curtains we eat
squirrels tail in Indonesia breakfast
and then shirt grow back every day oh
no how do we how do we test I'm not sure
I think they're still can
watch first
and okay where should we
[Music]
watch okay please listen to
okay example I will I will have I will
give you three stages got I know stages
of
grief I guess three stage so let's start
from the first
stage
St and after I set the command I will
say 3 2 1 and then you can move ah
okay okay okay let's start from the
first
command face
[Music]
it okay
okay let's
start stage
one jump one time yeah okay that's
that's first stage
wa can you see see well I can I can
really you can see well enough yeah yeah
yeah I can okay okay okay making sure
you got a good
view
that's um l
[Applause]
[Music]
three
times let
[Music]
start up
Ki 3 2 one
[Music]
oh my God you damaging private property
oh that's your
[Music]
okay
okay you can do it it's easy practice is
easy we make it
[Music]
hard
yeah oh oh sorry I'm supposed to be here
you stand where do we stand in the
beginning ah it's it's up to you uh you
just stand in the middle okay I'll stand
on red right here okay
I might not stand under red oh we should
stay on we should stand on red or what
no no no uh
don't anywhere but red anywhere but
red I
[Music]
understand okay so you guys ready there
will be please speak slowly slowly okay
slowly okay okay let's start yeah stage
one um had Canan three two one uh I I
trust you I trust
you yeah but well I'm looking it up
still so this is not amazing I'm just
looking at my notes well it's practice
but uh sorry sorry and then after this
we go back to our initial position or
what yes please go back to your initial
position okay
okay so stage
two three 2
one
okay wow wow wow wow okay I'm amazed
that you wait for knowing your own
language of
course so and now we return to our
initial position again yes
okay okay stage
three
one how do you how do you
[Music]
[Applause]
y it will be like this wait is it like
uh you go on until there's a mistake and
then some people if they're too good it
goes on for like 30 rounds or is there a
cut there will be um there will be set
stages and the more you guys right get
it got it right the more uh emeralds you
guys will get yeah okay is there like a
limit though yeah there's about 10
stages I
think but you always say uh each
previous round you you repeat it so I
don't have to remember it really cuz you
say it I guess well there will be 10 of
the commands so yeah okay but it's kind
of like you have
to get yeah at the point of 10 it will
be more difficult because you say so
many things which one goes
first it's not a language game it's a
memory game which
[Music]
I are
I'll try my
best W this next is going to be the
wrong wool stage let's go oh this
is I read I read about this this
sounds what I would hope you read about
no I would hope that you read about your
own events challenges yo I'm here to
accompany you I'm not staff technically
okay you don't need to know everything
yes of course just roughly just
roughly Sor
[Music]
late it's okay you can climb from here
oh okay careful first accident chot chot
no no
no
no don't don't sue
us I'll be explaining in Japanese first
okay
[Music]
okay for for
so explain it in English basically the
team consists of a wool cutter and a
foreman the foreman will be in the Upper
Floor which is
this is the Upper Floor and then there's
supposed to be a lower floor and in the
lower floor there will be a wool
cutter so basically it's like playing
Splatoon kind of the foreman needs to
color all of these uh White wool you got
to replace them with like colored wools
while the wool cutter uh on the lower
floor they have to like cut the floor so
that the other teams foremen fall and
lose or so that they could help their
teammates to color more of the
wol because you see the foreman replaces
the Wool by hand but the wool cutter on
the lower floor they have like the
shears this is all teams at the same
time or there's going to be about four
teams four teams at the same time so or
maybe three I think it's three teams
okay so six people six people okay so
per round there's going to be three
people three pairs going Last Man
Standing which one do you want to be
below or above um I can um wait uh I
don't mind I
can I can be below it's fine I want to
see we could have yeah we could have and
then you guys can
decide
okay understand
[Music]
okay uh do you want to be the W cutter
or do you want to be the
foreman I can
be I can
do okay they're going to
show the example example okay so on like
how to play you want to go down first
everybody's we're going to give an
example is going to be the foreman and
I'll be the wool cutter so you guys know
how it looks like mhm yeah you guys can
from above or you use two colored wool
just in
case okay I'm I'm going up okay F1 why
F1 okay I am
ready uh the foremans will be using F1
later we don't know know oh so we don't
know yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay okay L are you ready I am ready
okay we're starting in five that
means two
[Music]
[Laughter]
one Ollie opens it up for you okay okay
oh but can also punch her own wall ah so
if Olli is like busy um making holes to
uh drop someone down she can make her
own holes during that time yeah but like
so the people on top they have to be
careful so they don't
fall let me see
Bel so I think like the foreman just
makes holes and there's no way the foran
can know who's under or up because
they're using
F1 so the one above has to be
[Music]
careful who who's who's supposed to
press F1 the bottom one or the top one
the bottom the bottom one bottom okay at
the top one if the top one falls down
it's game over for them yes yep and they
don't uh their wols do not get counted
and they're eliminated and the the
bottom one if the top one falls down
that means the whole team is like out
right I can't cut anymore okay so uh my
tip is that it's best to not fall just
so that you can get your wols counted
it's best to not fall try not falling
I'll try
[Music]
the person at the bottom can also make
holes and undo your points
basically but like if you're the upper
person can only
do yeah and if you want to cut the wols
like if the foreman want to cut the wolf
you can cut the white ones but you can't
cut like the other team okay yeah well
the wool cutter they can literally cut
any wool they want okay and we get only
one color right now two
colors was showing how it'll be if
there's going to be like two teams ah
okay okay crunch AIO I don't know would
you guys like to try
yes wait is the crunchy audio still
there you all do at the same time I
don't know so I guess like my Minecraft
is like showing it's making the audio
crackle so I'm going to try to
disconnect first is it still
there is it there now
no okay what about this
one s noral to
[Music]
me testest
back what what exactly is crackling know
somebody says there's like a crackling
sound but I can't hear it
[Music]
either I really can't Trav shoot it
because I personally cannot
[Music]
here sound like a robot to you
not a problems right
now I'm I'm not at
home are you
okay happens
for it is it really bad guys wait hold
on I'm going
Tove is it really bad guys if it's
really bad I'm going to call staff but
if it's not if it's if it if you can
live with it it's so
yeah because if you're going to be the
wool cutter you have to jump to cut them
it's pretty bad uh I'm going to call
staff actually I'll be right
back I think I think upper is easier I
think I think yeah you don't have to
think so much it is
[Music]
I'm going to
I'm gonna I'm going to call staff be
right back
uh I don't know I
don't yeah because this the setting is
very unorthodox in my opinion it's
really hard to troubleshoot when in the
middle of program
so I'm just like I'm not
sure I'm really not sure what to
do hold
on
for is it still
is bad I don't remember this until
tomorrow it's still buzzing I literally
do not hear
it I literally do not hear it I will
never be able to fix it and I think like
even if staff comes in I don't think
they will be able to fix it because I
don't know what's up
[Music]
and it's not even my mic you know if
somebody says
mic see it's not from me guys it's from
when somebody talks but there's there's
nothing I can do about it so I'm just
[Music]
like what should I
do it's just the mod I think it's
just it's just the mod acting up
uh sorry I'm sorry uh thank you for
waiting I'm not fixing it but yeah you
know what it's fine it's fine it's
fine okay yeah guys I'm still going to
I'm still going to stream it if you need
to mute it's okay I can uh instruct you
through chat yeah yeah like um honestly
guys uh there's no way we can fix it you
know if you want to turn down the volume
I don't mind but I'm um it's impossible
to like pause and like try to fix in the
middle because it's literally an issue
we I I can't troubleshoot
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh okay do you want to be the foreman or
do you want to be the W cutter I can try
to be the top for now I can try to be I
don't know uh what do you want to do I I
I'll do top and then later okay I'll do
bottom then hold on okay okay see how it
is I suggest you guys to take about two
uh what's it called shears just in case
one
breaks and if you guys hear uh I would
suggest you guys to like hold the shears
in uh both
hands just so that if it breaks if you
guys hear it breaking you can
[Music]
on both
hands
okay uh woman please press
F1 okay okay we're going to
[Music]
start okay starting in five 4 three 2
one
[Music]
is
you I'm far away from
you can I just
like fill these up yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah fill those
[Music]
up I already ran out
okay I'm close to
you okay my controls are now reversed W
wo wo wo careful y y y someone's getting
rid
my no no no no
[Music]
it was pretty in terms of colors
yeah I fell the colors do not count so
the winner is
Bui Bui
win
wow sorry guys uh I forgot to press F1
but I will make sure to not do that in
Home bun sorry I'm like in the middle of
troubl shooting as well so it's littleit
tough this will be even more chaotic
when there's free teams at the same time
yeah oh also I don't know how to
translate this but basically if there's
a stacked wall uh there will be a staff
that will clearing them out so you guys
don't need to waste your time C you mean
if they're accidentally play like on top
like this yeah okay nice
oh I know yeah guys so if you read the
pin message thank you very much that's
all I have to
say
okay nice what a service yeah so would
you guys like to switch now yeah
[Music]
I'll be bad at it okay I'll bring back
my
orange yeah I wasn't looking at the
names anyways mostly I was basically uh
trying
to get the greens off
because Wawa was nearby anyways so it
wasn't like I was specifically targeting
anybody sorry so give her the woles
please I already put them
back you can take the woles here
[Music]
please take two
STS any color
is I'll take
blue I'll take the is setting to just
turn off the without do F1
okay so for the foreman follow me
upstairs
no
[Music]
foran I can try to troubles shoot but
it's going to take time and we're in the
middle of practice so I really really
can't do it all you have two
Stacks yeah I
do
[Music]
listen do you have two
shears yeah yeah one one
two no one two H please uh what What's
it called um so we don't need to F1
right for the up one up people oh no
upper people don't
need so two shears on guy please like
put uh two shears on both
[Music]
hands
two okay okay like
this I don't have shears well whatever
is working like left left left right
yeah just so that it
so
bre so uh when it breaks you'll hear a
sound right so if it breaks you can just
switch it out with
okay when everybody's like screaming
during the match maybe I won't hear the
sound of
breaking well I think you'll notice if
you
start you you know if it's
[Music]
slower
yeah please press
[Music]
F1 ready
for it's fixed I
didn't it's fixed I didn't do [\h__\h]
didn't do
this okay we'll start in five four 3 2
one t
wait what color are you I'm I'm light
blue light blue okay oh don't
worry hey can I jump is is it allowed to
jump yeah wait I'll go sabotage a little
bit well the colors
look sorry it's okay e e
[Music]
look too similar in this
lightning I don't know if I'm really
getting rid of green or
[Music]
blue I wasn't even doing that
intentionally uh I have one
uh suggestion although I think it
depends on the monitor on on one of my
monitors the colors look pretty much the
same on the others s uh very different
but like maybe we can light up the space
somewhere I don't know or or we should
like the blocks you know like just just
use the red block
and red block maybe we'll use a more
contrasting block yeah I think that
would help yeah like maybe we can avoid
having green and blue together in one
match I don't know but if I look at my
other monitor they look very different
yeah sometimes it's it do be like
that like it's much brighter on my left
monitor on my right monitor this is what
practice is for guys so we can spot
these
stuff
okay we'll we'll prepare it on the next
time okay thank you but so far how is
it do you guys want to do it again or
move
understand I understand too yeah
okay oh no break okay so which one which
one do you prefer to or
bottom W so do you which one do you want
to be bottom or like on
top you want B do one round in the home
B hey in the home is there is there only
one round or
wait let me
[Music]
check know
which and it's like plus then you don't
have to worry about it we could always
discuss later too
yeah honestly way even way is fine for
me though okay so there's going to be
about three rounds okay well there's no
problem we can switch so um but each
pair will play um at the maximum two
rounds go against each other in the
final so like kind of tournament style
uh there's like preliminaries and then
the last round is like finals between
the two winning teams from each
match I wonder if the others are
practicing this game a lot or if they
also just did it one time and then call
it day I also I don't know at the same
time I think there's really not much
point to practicing too much you know
the same thing plus
luck I would I think during home
although this is already strategy talk
but like I'll try to find your color and
then stay close to you but sometimes
maybe I'll go away and sabotage but I
can tell you that right um yeah but then
the other team will find out as well so
well yeah that's
fine well I I I see your name at the
bottom anyways basically if there's a
hole near me I'll feel
it all right feel a hole Misty feel a
hole Misty if there's a hole there's a
way yes if there's a hole there's a way
Miss
real oh okay oh okay okay wait I'm sorry
there has been a misunderstanding it
turns out
understanding so it turns out there will
be three rounds and everybody there will
be six pairs against each other for
those three
rounds what the
H yeah to be a lot more chaotic than we
thought at the same time I feel like
people will fall down immediately
yeah I think it's just like kind of
bed it's pretty luck based there's three
[Music]
rounds only
only somebody falls down first uh versus
somebody who falls down third do the do
the third ones on who fell down third
get more
emeralds
um like it would matter probably right
uh who who fell down first they get
emeralds I wonder yeah you're I
hearing yeah and then I guess so if
somebody Falls they have to immediately
announce like for example pavoni P
out yeah it becomes easier for the
organizer yeah I think with so much
going on I wouldn't if I was at the top
I wouldn't even notice h no if I was at
the bottom I might not even notice when
you fall down immediately and I might
still be digging holes so only the last
one standing gets the
emerald threee rounds and then
okay so only threee pairs out of six
pairs can even get points yeah so it's
always only the last man standing gets
points point so if even if you finish
second you don't get
anything if we lose it's going to be
just luck Bas you know don't can we try
one more round where all of you
including Ollie and Rizo are
participating to like recreate the chaos
a little bit more we
can I think
yeah um earlier sorry Ollie because um I
earlier I said uh just P the colors that
are contrasting to each other but then
if there's going to be three going on at
the same time right cuz it's like is it
six teams or two teams or yeah so we
need six colors that means there's no
way there's going to be there's
definitely going to be weird a the low
contrast colors next to each other which
was K it's okay I just have to look at
my other monitor okay okay then okay I
was I just wanted to clear it up it's
just cuz it's darker down here when I
was at the top it wasn't although we use
different colors at the top but I think
it's darker down here ah so maybe
lighting will help more lighting down
here a little bit honestly yeah I think
uh but it's hard because like you can't
put anything you guys won't be able to
uh yeah you guys won't be able to cut
it's okay I I will look at my other
monitor but we should tell the other
members if they have the same problem
that they should brighten their screens
or something yeah yeah yeah okay
understood thank you well
for yeah
[Music]
okay
okay wait you want to be top or bottom
this time uh I can be top I'll try okay
I'm just I'm I'm kind of bad at putting
the boxes but we'll see okay yeah I need
to practice being at the bottom okay um
I'm going to go with dark blue this time
so it's kind of easier for you to see
maybe take a picture if I just pick dark
blue that will be easier for you to see
I think and I'll put this it's okay I'll
put my game on the other
screen I'm going to be building
[Laughter]
blocks pray for me y other screen switch
doing a switch or
okay yeah uh do you want to be the foran
or the wo cutter I want to be the foran
what digo sounds does somebody have a
digo in their home a digital what a digo
what's up what's
that the uh it's like an instrument
that's really long and it makes a
d oh the it's the the horn thing right
yeah kind it's not really it doesn't
look like a horn it's just a
long yeah wait is that I hear it who is
it yeah
did who's making no sounds no not
[Music]
me is it you ol say something hello sis
hello
hello well well we we'll figure out
later now let's try practicing
again yeah it could be a vibrating sound
okay get position did do you
okay
[Music]
okay down here oh you
guys do you guys have two
stacks
half maybe I have one I think that's ju
yeah very
very very
very we're going to
start oh my God start it wait let me get
the timer ready it's going to be 1
minute uh Indonesia
wa what's your color wa wa dark blue
dark blue dark blue dark blue okay so
starting in 5 4 three 2
one I found
you out out out out out
out what you doing
[Laughter]
[Music]
I
didn't I didn't even
know I think I made I made the hole that
you fell
through yeah I think
B honestly I wouldn't think too much
about this game I mean I would stress
over it so much
[Music]
what what's going
on no I I by to the ground I I
personally think tournament style would
be much better everybody has more fun
playing so like three teams and then
three teams and then final instead of
like the you and instead of like the six
people Point thing I honestly think it
would be more fun uh since I'm ID even
though I'm not staff since I'm not ID
I'm going to like talk to them but I
mean if it's not if they're not able to
change it then it's
fine I never have my phone on because
like six people is just so random and
it's kind of like it just feels more
like a luck base than like and then some
people actually like they don't get to
play the game or
something I think tournament St will be
more fun for everyone because this is
actually fun and then it's just sad if
like somebody wants to play and then oop
you know they fall just because of bad
luck
squirel it was the squirrel all
along wa do you want
to I know I what you mean do you guys
want to do it again yeah I do yeah myars
myars you
more it's okay K's handing me hers okay
I'll take I'll take orange only only you
can go up I'm orange Way Orange I might
people
again
okay OU I'll
be okay
okay create some
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah go go further
away we're starting in five four three
it's hard to tell two
one I don't know where I'm aiming
at who is this this
yes yes yes get it get it get it get it
you you guys have 35
[Music]
seconds orange paint the world Orange
[Applause]
[Music]
no don't talk don't talk okay it's very
orange we like it we like the
[Music]
orange stop stop stop stop stop
stop because you guys are still alive
we're going to count the
shears she walls I think
wow I think orange wins what happened
with purple I ateed
them wait don't don't don't break them
yet she's counting oh you're counting
the orange one tail ah
okay sabotage
all right I think wa hey I think I'm
more
talented yeah you you also prefer
putting down the blocks right yeah cuz
like I realized my strategy now
[Music]
wi like I feel like uh in previous
rounds I was trying to find wherever
waya was but this one I just didn't try
to even find her I just tried to find
any hole and fill up any
hole focusing on
that be
fast easy
if there's going to be six people at the
same
time but I feel like I was pretty good
at dodging the holes that close if it's
like six people that means like three
three
right or is it six six
okay six teams yeah guess wait six team
there going to be six pairs so it's six
pairs oh I six on top six on top and six
on bottom oh my
God yeah got careful yeah double of what
we just had yeah so I mean we just like
um improvise adapt overcome you know
okay or you know a tip would be you got
one of the wool Cutters they could just
cut like the edges and the other ones
can just fill it from the insid or
something fine
manage manage
manage so
funny here okay uh what's the next game
we should go to the next game I think
waya doesn't have too much time
[Music]
since we don't have many time we'll go
to the um last game
first
[Music]
okay five game yeah wait before that I
need you guys to put your items in one
[Music]
of9
pick this is just construction stuff
[Music]
go anything but goh oh but will we all
have the same Gohan because some
different gohans are more strong than
others oh
then I have
bread yeah
I have
Ste a potato
potato
potato potato
potato I love potato
[Music]
oh this is going to be a little bit
tough
yeah we'll be using the group
VCC let
me group voice chat
[Music]
I read the tutorial how to do it okay
but somebody makes a group and I just
join it right
yeah create a group create a group
you want make
it group type normal
or normal or isolated players that are
not in your group can't hear you and you
can't hear
them uh isolated isolated
okay isolated
oh my
God hello
wait okay W I'm gonna make p group and
then you immediately join yeah but the
thing is after after we join a group we
can't hear the people outside that's the
no problem please make the password 1111
okay okay yeah
[Music]
okay good job
hacker I'm here okay
now all right
[Music]
yes
yes I don't know what that
means I wonder
how oh please you me now please leave
[Music]
VC okay this was just practice that we
can
make hi
okay you guys already know how to use
the group only only one question um this
place is really big uh toilet
gim toilet you can you can you can do it
uh behind the bushes here yeah see we
have so many pushes
okay no no no before you do your
business you have to say
[Music]
per
okay because you don't want to make the
the d
[Laughter]
[Music]
mad okay
h
[Music]
so yeah for the English viewers
basically in Ma's fight there's going to
be a fighter and a navigator the
Navigator will sit on the top and guide
the fighter throughout the maze all yeah
so they have to help the fighter defeat
the opposing opponents as well and the
team whose fighter is standing last
advances to the final round okay so it's
just like fighting it's fighting and
then there's a navigator that will help
but Navigator you say they on top on top
oh so we have all of
these okay yeah okay if you go inside
you can go to the top through the stairs
over here miss you here here here here
this is the stairs it's yeah pretty
hard follow maybe we can put up a sign
here's the stairs oh dear yeah okay but
it's hard to see what's like far away oh
no don't worry you can see the
names
uh-huh for like this area that's in
front of me the red area
basically
here H am I one more time please am I
navigating through the whole maze or
just this red area the whole maze you
can just say Oh Renee uh there's a
fighter if you go to the left so go
there or something like that and
Navigators they'll be handed bows and
arrows so that they can help the
fighters when oh we can shoot the
enemies too yeah oh you can even shoot
the other Navigators too oh oh what
scary what the other
Navigators
so I guess over
there let me explain to the other team
okay yeah okay ooh waa what do you think
you'll be better at being down there or
up here I I'm not sure honestly because
even if I'm up there like what's what's
the
goal uh like helping the ones down there
and like killing the other see like for
the ones down there like they have to
navigate I'm just like do they need to
go to the center or what yeah that I
want to know that too yeah yeah no but
she did say that the last one standing
wins so maybe not necessarily going to
the center just surviving but honestly
we can't really um go that far because
then you wouldn't be able to see
anything yeah that's what I was thinking
so maybe we should like sort of stay
yeah well but then they know that
they'll maybe see oh they're always in
their own territory so they just go to
our territory to fight us that's what
I'm thinking you know like if you
there's there's only so much you can see
but it's also hard for them to see yeah
for the others not just for us but I'm
just thinking like at some point the
Navigator wouldn't be able to do
anything
mhm no armor Weapon by what I don't
know m I also I only can tell there's
another place there but this is like
probably I see one there but it's too
far really and I don't know and I think
like uh MAA said no armor weapon buy so
we buy the weapons from the emeralds we
have gathered or
something that's why it's the last game
H but if you didn't do so well then you
not only going to get shitty weapons I
don't know
guys but the one good thing is that the
sniper like for bow and arrow is always
the same like there's no better weapon
like so maybe the if your person down
there doesn't have like such a good
weapon you can rely on the Navigator a
bit
more
pin it's pay to
win it's pay to win oh my
God I'm just I'm just the messenger okay
I have and I guess this is also
everybody at the same time
yeah everybody do you think it's
everybody at the same time I'm sure it's
everybody at the same time considering
how big the maze
is yeah is there a platform there hello
I'm back what's up we were just
discussing thank you I'll I'll stay up
here for now how about
that wa yeah sure oh also don't forget
to touch the bed in case one of you guys
die one of you guys die
M I touched the
bed leave
bed there's a bed over here
too where yeah oh
here okay so only take basically the
emeralds that you guys collect
throughout all of the mini game so you
guys will use it oops uh for this one
mini game game mhm yeah you guys will
use the emeralds to buy weapons hey hey
hey
[Music]
hey please please give me hey
hey if you guys are ready ready yeah I
guess what if in the off chance that you
know Navigator and person down there
does at the same time wouldn't the other
person get kicked out of the
bed huh they if we touch the same bed
and we die at the same time and they're
like very low chance should we have
should we prepare like two beds
instead okay okay it's okay like even if
you guys yeah okay okay okay one B is
enough okay okay okay because you guys
will just respawn
one more question um the goal is to just
survive there's nothing like in the
middle that you have to touch or
something right yeah you just need to
fight
okay okay let's go into
wi what should I do let's go to Bey
groups ah oh
okay VY groups let's
make she's going to be my what do you
call it
I'm bad at fighting though what the
heck hi W hi so okay Gladiator yeah
you're my Gladiator
way
okay can I is it am I allowed to like
stand here I
wonder dangerous ah oh oh
wait oh you have to eat way I I I ate
before I no I can't climb up I'm stuck
or
whatever well it's too late way you
either die or you live down there okay I
will do my
best maybe first
is how I to shoot fighter stand by below
I need Minecraft fighting tips
guys um instead of like mashing mashing
mashing mashing mashing hold right for
crits yeah just load it back up yeah
what weapon did you get wooden sword
there's only wooden swords
okay 5 4 3 two is that s i s by oh
[Music]
God go he where do I
go yo don't I can't see that I can't see
I have to change my
settings we I have to change my settings
uh uh uh
um
uh random
distance render distance awesome yeah
yeah I can't see s s by when she steps
back yeah I know because
um I'm also using a fresh computer with
sticky keys what is
this what is that for how you doing down
there waya have you seen anyone yet
no oh should should we go F1 or what
because I see name tags I'm so sorry I'm
so
sorry like she's not even fighting back
oh no she
is Die My die Senai die Senai I'm lost I
don't
know yo this is uh is that you I wonder
I'm at the are you running towards the
corn ah you on the blue okay four more
minutes i h four more minutes minutes I
don't see
anything go go go go go go go go go go
oh I'm at shoot again shoot again shoot
again she's hiding oh I'm wait that is
that you you're you're still on what
color I'm at dark blue right now okay
and not anymore I'm at the center
I almost got
it who's
that oh oh no I hear I hear something
it's so hard to
hit I'm at purple right
now oh there there's some people
fighting in ping I'm P that's me oh God
I don't know which one is you it's hard
I lit can't tell which one's you
you you die no no no no no don't die I
killed Yi yes let's go I'll die say I
got so many hits on
her oh you did it what win hey yo what
[\h__\h] oh I guess
so I forgot to I don't know what to
navigate like I'm busy like taking down
the
enemies I think that was fine though
like you just you know we got to we got
to be independent oh yeah I guess so you
can have yeah we we we should be
independent both people fight yeah you
just got to look for some enemies to
fight I mean I can kind of tell you like
oh there's someone in pink but that like
do you even know where pink is you know
yeah and I I can see like name tags
that's why I was asking should we be F1
or ah oh I see we can ask that yeah yeah
because um I saw like a name tag back
there but it's like I don't know but
like for real I can't even protect you I
wasn't sure like which one was eoi and
which one was you because you both have
like white hair in game and what if we
miss or
something yeah okay let's back I think
it's better to focus I don't know how to
go back up and you you press V and then
leave group like v v and then two group
I want to go up
oh ask
Ollie come
in
[Music]
for where how do I
and that's how you play hi
[Music]
okay
okay I have one more question
actually um is there
like
[Music]
okay so for the people down
do we die at some point cuz I I didn't
get hit so I don't
know that's why you guys have to touch
the bed for
[Music]
uh
ah fighter dies then lose okay um okay
yes one more
question so I
sawai like Tower over there but besides
that I I can't really tell like is the
the thing on my right side uh the big
house is it also a temple cuz it's kind
of in the way and like merging with the
other
area is that is that also like where a
team would be or how how's is that do
you know what I
mean Ollie Ollie wait sorry uh I'm uh
communicating with the uh the staff oh
what was the question uh like where I
stand if I look to my right there
there's this like big house that like
merging with another enemy area but like
is that where another team would be cuz
it looks different from the tower where
I am and it kind of no definitely not
it's it's uh it's on how do I say it um
there's four Towers just like yours on
each side of the maze four uhhuh yeah so
not everybody will be competing at the
same time
either if it's four Towers yeah there's
it's going to be like uh 3 three I
think I think I I'll have to ask again
also it turns out I I there's another
miscommunication on my part another
misunderstanding it turns out uh once
the Navigator dies then the game is also
over
this is
only and uh this will be this will
actually be like tournament style so 3
three and then 1 one
okay
yeah so there's three rounds one is
three and then one is three and then the
last one are the finalist by one um is
there you say there's four Towers I
guess on each side in the middle like my
view to the right tower from my side is
blocked by the is it the wool game no
it's yeah it's the wool game the wool
game is blocking my view completely from
that side yeah well um every side is
also having some of their sides blocked
so it's it's fine we are block
okay okay it's okay we pray destroy the
building
okay
maybe oh shoot I still wa wa wait I'm
going to put my items back in because I
thought
yeah I thought we were
done moreid that can't shoot that's true
they group V let's go back to group VC
[Music]
okay okay wait okay uh I should I uh try
the bottom uh sure you want to try top
okay um I I kind of suck at bow and
arrow if I got to be honest with you
okay I think I'm pretty decent at it I
got a lot of hits on SOL sire okay so
let's um okay we got our rolls decided
then you stay bottom okay yeah sure for
you okay but just like how in the wool
game I'm also top and you're bottom yeah
sure wow okay but actually I'm I no it's
it's okay I guess still have enough
probably so now this is 3x3 is so scary
because like there's it's there's a
possible scenario that two two teams are
going to gang up on one even though
unintentionally yeah it's all right it
is what it is well I I can only really
reach with my bows the the pink side
from here realistically so I can help
trying to get the Navigator down there
and maybe also the whoever's running in
there I think it's still eoi but the
others L I don't think I can reach them
from here okay so pink uh so ideally
where do you want me to be try to go for
pink first for sure I can try to help
you there okay and then after that maybe
let them come to youi should try to come
to you in red because there I can shoot
them
okay yeah we we we bring them over we
bait them okay I don't know if that's
smart but I think it
is it's so scary though because what if
like I fight and then the other team
third
parties after like I'm super tired
no it's all right it's all right we can
eat too but what if there's a stalemate
at the end and they like there's only
two teams left and they stay on their
side we stay on our
side nobody goes to the other side may
they come up with it well they'll come
up end what the hell there's an end
yeah all right let's see if s Senai will
try
that oh I can't see I can't see can't
see either there she's too far what the
hell why can't I not render that
distance she she's she's better now
she's better now are you in yellow yeah
oh
oh I can't see sh I don't know where the
exit
is a what if I accidentally look at the
Enderman right now oh no oh no
sucks why openong what the hell
man e is still in pink e is getting
closer to you H wa weer is in red we's
in
oh oh
oh d it come on where's the door that
squirrel that squirrel wiu is in the
middle wiu is running in the middle
you're there too I armor yeah take her
down take her down don't duck don't duck
we wearing armor there's no way I
win oh
hi Mo ah they just me in the middle I
think I die don't die yeah I'll es
I wait someone's wearing diamond
yeah it's I was like yeah cheating
cheating yeah I was like I immediately
realized Ru was wearing armor there's no
way I win uh but anyways that's what
happens just I think going to the middle
is very
bad yeah yeah and I just straight up get
third
parted yeah maybe better than but
anyways it's just a simulation it's
whatever
yeah well now it was so much harder to
get sort of simple
but anyways it's fine just just
testing I wish I could see
better the UI didn't make the names
bigger
either uh I like an accessibility like
setting or something no it doesn't make
it bigger you can make the UI bigger but
it doesn't make the names bigger test
it but I should yeah render a bit more
distance but um you see what just
happened if if I go to middle I get
third party uh the the the yellow part
is so open so I'll try my best yeah but
like they're not they could also you
could for like uh go with you know the
other team against someone else too like
it could go both ways yes but uh that's
only after I like I hear somebody
fighting mhm
basically so unless that whatever like
your instincts tell you is I think fine
oh they're still f in they fiding
still yeah wiu was in red area and I was
really trying to hit her that was the a
good opportunity I think she was
probably looking for way yeah maybe oh
my God there's an Ender
oh weu wins so that's like that the
squel the squel takes revenge for the
her stolen um tail stolen tail even that
was the one who sled
it good
job
oh oh did you just hit MAA no what
happened
no she
fell
mysteriously I
see yeah okay I guess we go back
probably yeah I'm just going to get uh
items so I think that's good like
simulation with uh three people oh [\h__\h]
hold on I'm back
uh
all group
all hello
there
hey
hey Nani the
frck pleas give me no I'm poor please
give me money instead
she doesn't even feel like doing it
anymore no no no very much
so you don't you don't feel like talking
to me anymore cuz I'm so poor no no uh
is not with us anymore I am P Senpai P
Senpai please give me
emeralds and
nether uh what what you say uh what you
say
such if such a question arises
[Music]
I think so far
so I
[Music]
have I don't know
[Laughter]
hello but no that would destroy
everything I would
cry yeah
question
would have been
Gooding system system system
[Music]
if I die in the game I die in real
life oh
can you still use to fight the other no
no okay no you can only support mentally
[Music]
[Laughter]
so um okay so if Navigator dies um they
don't
lose but I think we can move on to the
last one does everybody still have
time I told you I told you it was 45
minutes ago earlier no I'm looking at
the time for you because I know this
will take
longer uh what else do we still have Oli
uh just uh the build and guess so
basically you build and then you guess
what the other is
building end
no
okay don't don't J don't J don't yeah
thought if a Ry needs to leave I think
um just just continue and then I'll tag
along for as long as I could don't mind
me
okay then I'll I'll pick you guys up and
then we can do the build on Guess
[Music]
build there's actually one game we have
in practice which is the treasure hunt
but it's not done yet okay okay no
problem
[Music]
yourm Luna had a terrible accident I
don't know how she fell down there but
her leg is broken and and I think help
her she she can she can
recover definitely not me though she's a
strong person strong independent woman
[Music]
oh I might die I might die I might die I
might die
no see see so much for being a securely
built
building well you know I can't sue
myself well
the die
where do I put eat your vegetables eat
your
[Music]
greens see there is the
the somebody PE in the bushes that's why
the spirits are
angry oh my God I wonder who feed
[Music]
can can proper safety precautions be
taken tomorrow that Endermen are not
running around can we can we all gather
where we're supposed to build the thing
yeah let's go let's go I don't know
where it is can you us follow me
okay how do you throw it again
[Music]
ah we could turn on peaceful mode but
this is on the
main I guess it would be
fine
okay okay okay let's go a little bit
over here to a bit more open space to
the open
[Music]
space they do what they want it's okay
it's a
[Music]
natural
obstacle oh so like if you you try to
build and it look if it looks like an
apple like you know you try to make it
Apple
[Music]
this okay so just take any wo any is
okay is this one of us building
yeah color Okay wa you better AR
understand me
you orange okay okay
she'll do it with flying colors AKA
[Music]
yellow where are you I'm here I'm next
to Yi we not am I
notos how about here now she stands
here okay there you good can stand there
okay okay okay okay I'll be uh giving
the theme now in Indonesian since the
the the one buildings our ID okay okay
[Music]
yes how do I I just shout it out how do
I
[Music]
okay no no no
no I don't
know does this one mean anything this
one
[Music]
does this not look like
it
the the letter
really I don't know how I don't know how
to make it even more I don't know how to
make it man I think I think rain is
doing a good job I'm doing a good job
right it's not my fault that she can't
get is doing a really good job is also
doing a good job
what no
[Applause]
[Music]
it's only because I read it from the
chat but
okay so something like
[Music]
that okay I
take uh you please uh mute
and I'm going to leave
[Music]
and Def is
okay okay
hi
[Music]
okay starting in
what what excuse me
you you can spam Okay we okay we'll spam
I'll spam
[Laughter]
[Applause]
if something like that
[Music]
to go to certain words
but like literally
if that's how the game is played I'm
gonna I'm going to do that
[Music]
then maybe let everyone choose color
everybody can choose everybody can
choose the
I'm going to return
this yeah if they want it to be a
rapping game I'm going to make it a
rapping game they asked for it
[Laughter]
[Music]
in the actual game are more difficult to
yeah yeah that's what I'm saying the
point is like not I'm not saying you
shouldn't spam words but the point is is
not to make so the game is
over without people can build you know
there are some keywords you can
avoid I'm but at the end of the day I'm
just a participant so I don't
know I also don't feel like
Chang because it's the ultimately it's
the
[Laughter]
for
firefighter firefighter
firefighter what are you discussing
about
wait why are you Ana now I hate Ana you
know that oh sorry [\h__\h] we shouldn't be
talking at all even
now I am back I was lost for so long God
finally maybe way secretly EnV Ana and
that's how she expresses her en this is
like my you know it's kind of like a
problem to you know
[Music]
oh my
God
cute wait I didn't know your your was so
good
[Music]
okay but if you guys want to practice
again we can give you guys
prompts
[Music]
for okay okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
my God what are some Ana words what what
are some Ana words I can say to make
myself sound more like Ana uh just
Japanese anything Japanese it's just
Japanese any Japanese will be fine but
no no no but like her her Japanese like
everybody when they speak Japanese they
have like an accent like I have to I
have to study
that I think you have to sound very like
like angry I think she's like often
yeah
okay okay okay I'm going to Def okay I'm
going to Def
hi okay
hi
hi you want to say I don't know I don't
know I I I need to check her
clip don't forget being snarky sometimes
be high pitched okay
okay bro
bro bro
oh you
can hi lost okay
hi wait I'll build on the floor it's
allowed so I'll build on the floor
really
okay build on the
floor build on the floor the maze
n ma question mark duck bird what the
[\h__\h] are you building
bro you that doesn't look like a flower
[Music]
I maybe leave it to
you building building on the
floor gu
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
okay banana
sorry sorry I pressed
wrong okay
[Music]
no no no you're better than
me take your time or don't take your
time
orange chicken chicken
[Music]
look at what they're
buing so that's very good
[Music]
good a horse
uh you're doing good too
[Music]
[Applause]
but I see now you're like building it
three dimensionally upwards okay I
thought
you I still thinking better on the floor
or no it's just hard
banana so no we have
to I think we have to discuss
beforehand I on
Flor no even whatever you think like
fits the situation I you can
[Music]
was good as
so I don't have any tall space
maybe can can we bring our own
scaffold oh yeah here uh here's some
scaffold oh oh you have your own yes
okay what are we
doing we'll be doing it again oh again
okay I team building right you're
building again right
rainy yeah wait to
build I mean I mean if you don't want to
do it no it's fine it's fine but by the
way they're not allowed to pick colors
after they know right they know they
pick the colors first right theck colors
first yeah okay okay pick a versatile
color she told her in Indonesian
[Music]
don't spoil it
Chad don't spoil it I look too much
ready ready
this me
e oh she's building on the floor
okay uhhuh very different building style
so
[Music]
far iing
it could
be first one
[Laughter]
[Music]
glass yeah it could be magnifying
glass okay yeah me too good job good job
job oh but the heads up the rules may
change for the
okay maybe we change
[Music]
but
nice thank you so much for you
know thank you for practicing thank you
good luck I know you guys must have so
much on your plate but good luck guys I
support
you
tomorrow see you
tomorrow where's
my can we uh can somebody enter us to
the outside and we kaang there yeah I
can oh okay
[Music]
take a picture
and
practice practice SE and H the picture
using a NE next day thumbnail okay
okay uh where is outside
wait I think I found the
path here maybe
[Music]
where are you which exit is the right
way is
there she's in the wall I'm in the first
game in the I'll get you I'll get you
I'm at the first game the first game oh
Simon Says Simon
says I see it I see it I see okay okay
okay okay how do you know
is let me out let me out let me out let
me
out [\h__\h]
why work
[Music]
this I made it to the
outside H you did but
[Music]
uh I am in the outside where should I go
um other uh climb up again
[Music]
okay over
here looks good
[Music]
okay yeah thank
you what about what about
and come in coming
[Music]
wow
cheese let me let me take a picture of
you guys too
okay nice thank
you thank
you Papi will win number
[Music]
one I I doubt it but I have to say it
anyway no sometimes you got to be your
own hype man you know
yeah you can't do it
thank you guys thank
[Music]
you see you
tomorrow wow okay guys so it is the end
I'm going to go soon too um we did
practice today
we need so many many many you have my
stuff
[Music]
right here wait I'm going to leave the
chat
[Music]
W okay OU cheese never mind
hello okay so we did the practice we did
the everything and I guess we just hope
for the best for the homean where is
Wawa where's
Kiara Kiara is I don't know she is um
she needs some alone time I think or
maybe she is um she is being called by a
secret entity where is she heading
nobody
knows oh my goodness where is she
going is
she oh my
God bye
see you tomorrow
guys I'm so happy and it's good that we
have all the infos for the in for the
stuff tomorrow they're still going to
change a bunch of info so to recap there
is um so to recap there is there are
three I think the first one is Simon
Says Simon Says is basically um yeaha
you separate it in the wall and two
people have to follow follow
instructions properly uh and then the
non-indo will have to remember the
Indonesian phrases you know and then uh
they say it's going to be like Max 10
Rounds or something so it's going to be
getting trickier trickier trickier and
trickier as the rounds go on and then uh
the second one is the wool um I think we
kind of established that you know who's
good at being the foreman and who's
being the one on top uh so it's good
basically it's kind of like
Splatoon uh but also you make other
people fall if other people fall you get
disqualified sorry if you fall you get
disqualified and it's going to be
chaotic and then third one I think is um
The Maze one it's also pretty much uh
the emeralds you gather by winning from
the previous rounds you will use it as a
currency to buy weapons and in this one
it's basically Last Man Standing and
then it's a little bit tournament style
um and then for the last one it's guess
the build basically which you just saw
but there might be other stuff or tiny
portions of rules that will change but
uh we'll see uh obviously this is just
practice and tomorrow will be the real
thing so yeah uh there might be some
things different there and yes please
give it up to the team who the staff
team they um arranged this so well and
we're very very excited for tomorrow me
and wa will be seeing each other again
and I guess I'm going to use the
thumbnail that we took just now yay
see you
tomorrow thank you very much for your
attention thank you very much for
watching salet everybody and byebye bye
bye bye bye bye bye see you
tomorrow SHO
[Music]