[Music]
do
um
who has the heart to move my cat
i don't he's so cute
and soft
[Music]
let's keep her until until the loading
screen has to go you can stay for
one more minute
shadowverse also loves cats
cats control the world oh oh she left
you know what
she doesn't like it when i start
streaming and start talking
[Music]
building a cat deck
is that a thing
[Music]
no
bom bom bom bom bom
[Music]
welcome uh i haven't seen you guys in a
while really
because i took another day off
and here oops oh [\h__\h] i shouldn't do
that
wait yeah i took a day off did you guys
miss me
we changed the window size here oh oh
that was way too big on that side
there we go now i have more space for
that
yes of course hi shadowverse in the chat
yes someone's here to help me
okay welcome everyone welcome welcome
coming coming everyone
what ah what you cannot skip this ad you
you have to watch it it's it's gonna be
two hours
and welcome everyone
it's been such a long time since the
last shadowverse stream which was in
december but um
uh yeah shadow race was so nice to
you know sponsor another stream and
it's actually not only one stream as you
guys maybe know
uh me and kelly will eventually be
battling each other
uh which is also uh gonna be part of
this whole sponsored
adventure i wanna say thank you channel
thanks for doing this
i um back then in december when we first
played shadowverse
nobody jam oh oh wait you don't hear
that oops okay there we go
here there we go yeah back in december
uh when we first played shadowverse
i already had like a lot of fun because
i wanted to play
another card game for a long time but
it's hard to like get into one on your
own especially for
bored uh lazy people like me who
just don't really take the time on their
own but
yeah the thankfully shadow verse
kind of uh well i wouldn't say forced me
but
it's all my choice but it brought me to
playing another card game
for the first time in a long long long
long time
yay it's a busy and fine now guys
is it okay do you hear the beautiful
like middle age fantasy bgm i love the
btm it's all good okay awesome
awesome awesome well let me
let me uh start with some important
points a bit too loud really
what for real i don't think so
it sounds like on my observer it looks
actually too quiet
[Music]
so talking uh uh points
i have some important things to tell to
you
you might know these things if you
watched uh the stream in december
so first of all this stream is free to
play you can i'm i'm personally playing
it on
on pc via steam so you can just download
it on steam and then there you go you
can
like try to play it like i do it um
and as you can see it kind of has like
an anime style uh there's
lots lots lots of different artists uh
who did art for this
so nicara manikama is so so so uh
lots of cute cards but also some darker
darker cards some cool
cool badass cards cards so not only like
cute muy stuff but also you know some
something more on the cooler side for
the people who are not that much into
anime
and yeah there's like uh as
wait let me let me show you a loop
uh no wait where where can you see that
overview is it on decks
oh wait oh there's eight
eight liters oh i don't know why do i
see like an overview of them
not not here probably there's eight
liters
uh that have like a different like kind
of class
like for example like sword craft
a top left top left
yeah huh
oh wait i think
uh yeah this one's here yeah look look
look
so these are this is for example forest
craft uh alisa she's like
um the main character like in the
tutorial and all that
and then there's swordcraft erica and
runecraft isabelle
dragoncraft brought rowan rowan
shadowcraft luna
bloodcraft audios haven craft at ease
and portal craft you want and as far as
i know you can
play for example first craft but have a
different leader
uh i'm not that deep into it yet i don't
think i have
other do i have other leaders no i don't
but there's other leaders and you can
still you know
you know play the for the same class
because depending on the class
um you play the game very very
differently hello
hello well i'm dangerous you got you
calling up for tension did you guys miss
me
it seems so
um i think last time well obviously
because of the
tutorial and all that we played the
forest craft
but i also dabbled a little bit
in like some other classes and
i think i will go for it haven't craft
i think um you know
i'm not sure if i'm allowed to mention
other
card games but there's a specific card
game that i used to play when i was
younger younger younger and i used to
always play
um like white white decks uh
or maybe sometimes mix in a little bit
of a blue
but it was mostly white and it kind of
reminds me of haven craft
yeah so
uh i feel like it kind of fits me also
yesterday practice a little bit to get
back into it
um get back into like get the
get the feeling back and i i played a
little bit with heavencraft and it was
fun
it uses like amulets a lot
from my understanding where um
like you put them on the field and you
kind of like
they have a countdown and yeah it takes
a little while for them to activate
but in the end you will uh
get like really really powerful effects
by activating and waiting for those
amulets
am i not super informed hello
gotta say uh good job kiana i'm talking
i'm talking as if i know what's going on
yeah wait let me see what else um
practice yeah we probably we have like
two hours to gotcha and build a deck
today but i might
just get done earlier because i kind of
like i have to be honest i built a
little deck with what i have yesterday
and i was already pretty happy with it
but we're gonna get some more amazing
cards today um
thank you for clapping for me thank you
thank you thank you thank you vega burp
has done some research
i even watched a few uh shadow verse
videos on youtube
um yeah we will see
uh also there is right now uh
uh a kakuyasama love is war uh
event maybe you guys know the anime
uh wait where do i see that it
showed me in the beginning but now i
don't see it anymore
is it oh there you go see they're doing
a tie up they're doing a lot of tie-ups
last time what was it last time in
december they also had
they always have some tie-ups really
cool and i think this is a really
popular
anime i didn't watch it but it's really
popular it's the one that that was
with chica
[Music]
dmca dance
i hope i hope um uh you guys all know
that she got dance
you of course you do don't job let me
see is there like oh
oh you can buy a a leader from from
kaguya
oh you know what that's cool but
what what other leaders oh
we're just a leader pack to get special
eternal sleeves oh
i just want a different leader to be
honest
oh wait they sound like ah they have
like updated designs here
it looks kind of different from usual or
maybe not
i don't know they do look aries looks
different
yeah they have a prince connection tie
up as well
oh sadden saren would be the havencraft
leader
cool cool cool stuff lots of cool stuff
there's like you get it you open this
game and you see so many familiar
people ah grand blue fantasy
oh god fairy is so freaking cute oh my
god
look at her what i don't know her but
she's gorgeous
and she's the havencraft leader
can i have her 500 crystals
you know i got i got some um
gotcha crystals
can i use some of them for her
what wait i wouldn't does it matter like
does the leader really matter
like isn't that just like a visual thing
shadowcraft in the chat help me out
isn't that just does that actually have
effects on not not really
cards first yeah of course of course
it's just okay so it is just visual okay
okay okay
oh my god i want her she's cute
well she got like all kinds of sparkly
jewels anyway um
we are however doing mostly gacha today
let's i don't know how long it will take
but yeah oh yeah also there's like
temporary
card decks as well like in case you
don't really know what you're doing i
guess like me
you could get like a temporary card deck
also to like test it out
um they are like uh
there's a between march 30th
when was my chest a long time ago
there's a official release of the 21st
card set
darkness over velsar wait i saw that
i saw that i saw that wait
oh see uh
we're not are we buying packs sorry
oh yeah we're buying packs i think
this one is the the new one she looks so
cute
who is she they're like all kinds of
kids in their foxes
friends fubuki senpai's in here so if
you want if you're missing fubuki senpai
you want to get
closer to fubuki senpai this is the deck
for you
um one thing i was wondering though
which i couldn't really find an answer
to
uh depending on these uh
packs they like they they are like
mixed i guess like mixed classes in
there but is there like packs that have
more
of one class than the other like is
there london has more haven craft
is that a thing or is it just like
always completely mixed
does someone know the answer
no wait no no all even
oh it's all mixed they're equal okay
oh well well well
what should we pull from
it's great to always have people who
know who know the game that i
am talk uh playing it's great to have
you guys
thank you thank you um
um let's get your cards for all types no
no
no no i want to focus on havencraft i
mean obviously we'll get all kinds of
cards
eternal awakening
okay okay why not get the newest one
first
okay darkness let's see some new ones
okay okay okay you guys want to see some
new ones let's see my gotcha look
uh this is also currently the only
godzilla game i'm playing
yeah shadow voice doesn't need to answer
anything it's my viewers are already
answering the questions
so smart i'm always surprised that
there's always people who already played
the game
it's fascinating to me
[Music]
but it's also reassuring to have shadow
verse in the chat so please stay please
stay and in case the chat
you know sometimes the chat claims to
know what they're talking about but they
they don't they don't sometimes
okay look i have a lot of lots of lots
of gotcha currency let's go
buy with wait i have
i have 10 tickets oh
oh i have i have 10 tickets wait let's
go
let's use them first oh yeah okay let's
where did i get those from you get a lot
of free stuff in this game you don't
even notice it at some point
bats and darkness
look this looks so fancy i love this
review uh-huh
uh-huh uh-huh see the thing is i don't
know what's special you guys gotta tell
me what's special that look kind of
normal
to me is there something there's lots of
dragons here
whoa look at him crazy
[Music]
okay next one we we got
10 packs so let's see what's inside
oh wow i love this i love this effect it
gives me like a feeling that i really
pulled something amazing what is that
sarah's bright red bird of the night
bride of the night oh you guys are like
oh you guys are like getting really
excited whoa
okay baine what does that mean i don't
know english
last words do one damage from random
enemy follow-up
evolve put a darkest desire into your
hand oh last words steal it free damage
to
random and
cute she got like like with her hair she
made herself cats
cat ears those are fake but i like the
[Music]
effort
okay we got another fancy one only two
costs very cheap i like it
and during your turn when this card is
added to your hand from your deck if you
have at least ten
shadow ah wait this is shadowcraft oh
yeah i don't really what was the other
one was that
something i could use we're focusing on
haven crowd give me something nice for
handcraft
haven craft please herman craft
hermancraft
havencraft please we want some angels
and stuff i guess i don't know
wow it's gold but that's not legendary
right that's one under
under but that's runecraft okay
and gl
yeah he does look kind of edgy yeah
he's like so i would probably listening
to the rasmus
in his free time yep
oh my god i love that they did that okay
let's see
six out of ten packs oh wait that looks
really pretty
it got like special effects i just are
we so we live in a society
but this is room craft that looks pretty
pretty hard wow oh it turns into fire
wow i like animated cards i want all my
cats to be animated
should i turn on some bgm for this
pulling session
wow oh wait no no no i have a set double
then okay
whatever unless you'll say you want some
bgm for this
ah oh that
that's oh wait that's a pretty tree
that's forest craft yeah cause all the
fairies sportscraft uses all the fairies
you want btm guys nobody you need okay
oh
yes yes yes yes yes i know her she's
really good for handcraft i saw some
like
good decks using her wow oh
that's the only one that i know that i
wanted
[\h__\h] yes oh sorry for uh
saying that yeah
i don't know why but she's good i don't
i i just know she's really good
yeah eat that's crap perfect
oh hi hi my okay we're done we're done
we're done here i don't need
[Music]
and that's another thing um the game is
fully voiced guys
they all have voices it's fully voiced
it's so dope
calm you a singer yes talk to me coming
washington
god is dead
forgive me no never forgive never forget
okay so what does she do
um deal two damage to all allies and
enemies
allies too oh evolve this
follower to deal five damage instead
restore free defense to a later okay
that doesn't
like that this is
sound like super crazy to me
but you guys got crazy about it
oh what is that is that so special
i mean she looks pretty pretty combos
combo
sanctuary yeah yeah okay i heard about
yup yup yup
yo yeah part of the strategy um
i guess i mean the the two damage to all
allies doesn't matter if i don't have
anyone else on the field but
hmm interesting well
we are definitely gonna have her in our
deck she looks cute as hell too
but she's bloated look at her wow she
like totally bejeweled her
axe do you guys notice like some people
uh be drew well everything this is
like some kind of old trend like putting
like small
plastic jewels on everything you own
bedazzle
be dazzling she got the trip
yeah she's really cute
okay what is that by the way that's
forest craft okay okay
demonic assault ooh cool
damn did you know that i didn't do such
a thing i would never
what
[Laughter]
oh i got the gotcha logo
so we can put two in our deck
you run two johns at most yeah i think i
saw a deck that had like two
gems yeah so yeah holy [\h__\h] we're done
we're oh we're really done
[Music]
yes thank you
does this happen a lot oh
voice crab haven't grabbed when's he
who's she
she oh my god bubbly reaper
it's like a cute cali she's
uh she doesn't look as dangerous as
kelly
you know i i would still prefer cali
cute voice
i know that was from somewhere
i've never heard that voice before a
young cowing
maybe like her maybe her sister maybe
her younger sister
yeah that could be her younger sister
wow this is so dumb
okay that was [\h__\h] lucky well no we
got here two times what do you mean
okay awesome well i don't know what else
i want from this
but i guess let's roll a little bit
somewhere else huh i guess that's
rolling do you guys want me to roll an
eternal awakening
is this scramble fantasy
there's also you can also sell row and
dose by the way
uh there's like these here altosphere
omen
of 10 grampa yes need one more john yeah
i had i got two is that not enough
ah oh that's that's great the gramble
fantasy oh that the other one too
wow this is this this feels like it has
a
lot of haven crafts but i guess maybe
not maybe it's all really just
balanced out very well needs to max out
jung
you want me to get more done no problem
i probably can do that don
break night edge that looks pretty too
oh
tempest of gods rise of bahamut darkness
evol
plastic carpet okay so wait so john
is only sorry
you're making a rotation deck so i would
stick to the decks on the previous
ah okay okay i i will i will
go buy that advice okay
don't go on old pass if you do rotation
interesting you guys always know what
you're talking about
so is john only in darkness of wells
over
relsar is she only in here let's do
what uh
yeah i want more than one that a pack
but okay yes okay
well then let's go one by one whoa
give me another jump come up i know you
can do it come on come on come on
come on why don't we need free guns
though
let's see who is this who is this
wow okay who is that
who is that runecraft okay okay okay we
don't need that but cool
looking really dope like some kind of
steampunk
stuff is going on here
don't give me those cards around in the
beginning it shocks me
someone an owl cat i love owls and i
love cats maybe i have to switch to
runecraft
owlcats who are you oh oh man
look at me look at that again
it's an owl cat oh and there's casper in
the moon
what is this that is so cute
[Laughter]
oh man okay dragon craft mm-hmm
he's neutral yeah there's also neutral
cards that you can use in any deck
oh parting of the flesh she's cute well
she's forest craft
okay not a hotel no
um
no john but we'll get her ah
let's go let's go four or five let's go
five
uh yeah let's do
i'm sure we can get her one more time i
am pretty confident what crap are you
looking for him craft heyman crap
hey oh oh wow
oh hey there's a there'll be jeweler
again oh and the beautiful
beautiful good oh wow that looks pretty
it's so sparkly arc
demon damn blood crab looks dope
imperial dragon damn that also looks
[\h__\h] dope
look at that dragon it's beautiful
wow wow wait does does the dragon talk
i mean i guess you can call the talking
what about you
i can do that too okay everyone's gonna
be a bit loud
yep i can do that too that's the exact
okay i have to admit i am the voice
actor of the arc demon
yep that's me just kidding that was a
joke
let's see come on come on
no that's okay the cards still look
pretty there's a broom
i want the broom it's the runecraft
though who are you runecraft
when you portalcraft bloodcraft
swordcraft wow
and she's hot look at her
pretty i love her dress those little
little
uh knives on her
leg wait those are those what do you
call those again
what do you call them those are like
some um
what do you call those kunai
kunai oh you guys you guys have your
knowledge too
where's my luck come on come on we can
do it
everyone put your hands together and
pray for me come on come on pray
me now tell about
oh my god okay but we need more hands we
need more hands
this is the fifth who is that she's
pretty
much what the
what is that portal craft it looks like
me after i use my transformation belt
another one of those robot voices i i'll
i'll i'll not do it this time but
who is she fallen necromancer
oh oh she's haven't grabbed you could be
useful maybe storm and ward
wait ward was it protects you so they
can't damage the leader
will a storm again that they can attack
right away
after being put on the field or was that
something else can i
get ah there we go yeah oh my god see i
was korea i know what i'm talking about
oh ho ho ho oh yeah that's pretty useful
storm and ward it's pretty dope
cute
please hire me as the voice actor
[Laughter]
i really want to get some uh voice
acting jobs just you're saying
okay no john what the hell who who put
their hands
uh uh not together who did who was it
let's get more
[Music]
come on come on come on
come on
cute fashion hazard
forest craft well she's so cute oh my
god look at that arndt
i love the art oh my god i love all the
art of the cards ah
it's so pretty oh my god look at her
wow i love her clothes
she's so cute can she become a beacher
wow what the what i like that voice is
like
like a like a like a voice that goes
[Laughter]
like that
she's like crazy oh my god she says this
will looks like
like disgusting to me
would you not get closer to me stay away
from me
oh my god oh my god wow
i like her oh who are you human crab
lunarian paladin
seven two holy cavaliers oh cool if x is
at least five revolve them x equals the
number of allied followers that had ward
when they were destroyed this match what
then if x is at least ten give them
storm he sounds kind of
good he might find the
spot in our deck
oh that's what he summons oh hmm
he's really good oh i'm sorry oh
i got too excited okay okay that's not
bad
that's not bad yeah yeah i can looking
for the content that's right oh i got
another one of them
come to me daddy come back to me
down
oh no oh okay
i'm lucky but i need john okay poor crap
what is that
handicraft whoa pine twisted justice
give all enemy followers the following
effect at the end of the turn
deal one damage to you oh wait that's
[\h__\h] dope
oh that's good oh
enemy followers the following of at the
end of
my turn did one damage to the oh
what that's pretty good like if they
have
five five followers on the on the
on the field deck that it fits into
right now
yeah you could accept anything except
block craft
oh give all other allied followers to
flowing around there
um well i mean generally look at her dog
off
and i love her sword her lance
no wait it has something inside that's
uh that's a syringe
syringe lance well she is cool
i like her
oh oh pretty
come on
um who is he well
where is he wow
i mean we see we've seen him before okey
dokey
interesting yeah it's a what's in
concoction
oh again i really want to use you i
really want
ooh what is that
wait cat summoner
but don't elect you kidding you can't
build a cat bag you can
oh my god look at that cat
so
that's when your cat touches your
electrical socket
and gets heated
that never happened okay it never
happened in my household nope
they don't even touch they don't care
about the sockets thankfully
[Music]
i love that i love that
it's hilarious oh this is already the
fifth out of the five oh my god
oh no
[\h__\h] okay no done
uh i was especially lucky in the
beginning
he transferred a pumpkin into a skeleton
wow that's cool
oh water
he forgot who he is he got some memories
should someone help him out
she's neutral dog that's okay
i mean that's just ame a detective with
a dog that has uh
blonde hair hello moshi moshi ame
amelia watson
ah oh man i love this i love this
okay well well i guess we're going for
more we still have more than enough
uh crystals so what the hell let's go
hi marshall my scotland
[Music]
[Applause]
oh who is that we got a fancy one
runecraft okay it doesn't matter
hurricane golem ooh
he's cool oh he turns into a unicorn
and he always was a unicorn
uh haven't craft oh do you want damage
to your enemy to the enemy later to
restore one
i mean that's good we could we could put
that in our deck
that sounds good to me for like the
beginning
phase um maybe not even the beginning
like the middle face
uh yeah otherwise
um oh hell
okay it's pretty good yeah draw two
cards is pretty good
um oh we got the dragon again
oh man if only i would play dragon craft
i would be [\h__\h] excited about this
oh
he's dope also i like that lion
sacred groundskeeper
[Music]
that's not quite a meow
wow
who is that roy dragon river dammit
dragon craft again
more havencraft i want to use her i want
to use it
[Music]
john please
who is he though swordcraft okay okay
we've seen them before
we got her again though um she's
uh pretty nice she'll probably get in
our deck
let's see at the time this is the fifth
number five no
john why are you not coming to me
anymore did you say two is already
enough it is not
auction this spoils what is this card
yeah hey
i like the squirrel what happens if you
evolve it
that is a language
see they even voice those animals isn't
that wonderful
[Music]
mermaid
five packs let's go bye
[Music]
i don't really need free jam i guess
yeah i guess i can create one
okay this is the last one we pull from
this um
thing okay and then we try another one
dun dun dun dun dun
and this one is fancy animated though i
like it
okay okay come on come on come to me
come to me
three out of five come on come on come
on come on
who is that spark
accelerate someone a flavor
this just fits my lure very much 72
plate hedgehogs
but that's pretty cool isn't it if you
have more evolution points on your
opponent give plus zero plus one and
bane
to all what is that again folks that
have been automatically destroy
any other followers they attack
followers that attack them are ottoman
okay well let's go sink these squeaks
what the [\h__\h] that's so cute
two people in heaven followers
tearing creatures
he's cute there it's like a looking like
a mouse guard and they're praying to him
how cute they're like giving him cheese
look at that
oh no
that is cursed that is
that's cursed no
that's not what we want to see
[Applause]
[Music]
i don't want that in my deck
i don't want that in my deck no
i like i liked it that way i don't like
what comes out of it
no thank you
[Music]
my face hurts oh last
no no no not last one yet ah okay
okay we got a big tree
cool looking cool how does he talk
oh he doesn't really talk okay well
last one guys last one
give me a shot oh nice nutcrack
ah they gotcha pain i had too much luck
in the beginning okay let's try out this
one
let's see if we find some is there
something special for havencraft in here
that i really really want to aim for
does someone know let's open 10 i guess
okay
[Music]
please give luck back yeah who took my
luck who took it
temple temple okay okay
uh then what holy see
the holy sanctuary there's a card called
holy sanctuary
what that i want
give me something nicely this looks like
you know with the wings it looks like
there's something good for having crafts
[Music]
cute okay okay who is she she's cute
she's cute let me look at her
sword crap damn shortcraft really got
all the cute chicks man
dragon craft yeah nothing it looks like
nothing nothing looks like even craft
grandma fantasy card wait which one ah
this one
is it this one that looks like that
looks like gpf
oh
no more guys you're like no trust me
we'll come back to me
oh
oh is that to lessen by
cycle pump tour guide
now kind of different voice but close
enough
different hair color so cute she gets it
she
gets from one ponytail into twin tail
[Music]
[Applause]
no
[Music]
it's a shark standing on two legs i mean
that's that's good out after she takes
her makeup off
i'm so sorry
where is he's got a cute voice
oh wait that's a pretty cool kind
of oh
what else we got
oh he looks cool oh
parliament arts oh
he's out he's so bunny oh this is for
heavencraft i think i already have him
i already had him i think um
cute
that dragon is getting cleaned like car
wash what the hell
this is like dragon blush what cute
cute haven craft whenever you play an
ambulance subtract
one from the cost of this card
i've seen this one used in a deck i
think
so might be useful maybe
oh okay let's see come on we can get
something nice out of this
whoa folia who are you cute cards oh my
god look at all these cute cards
runecraft goddamn it but she's so cute
come
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
they they look so cute
[Music]
i like those shields
or likes i mean it's supposed to be
shields right that's kind of dope
i like those they're like i have a
really weird
wait sacred tiger oh wait sacred tiger
wait he's cool
that that that's hate mancraft i feel
like i already have him though
i feel like i used them yesterday when i
was practicing
could be my imagination but it's a big
kitty
meow
come on give me your sweet more voice
no why not come and see me out meow meow
meow
let's go let's make a freaking kitty cat
a cat a cat
uh the deck
what you don't get cats out of them that
that's that's
that's cool a bird getting eated by
nature oh no let's save the boob
need to save the boob
uh huh i already have the fluffy angel
um it looks dope but we don't have blood
crabs we're using havencraft
oh who is this dude
unicorn all flower dough is for us help
you
no um
something for me please
word if this follower has two defense or
less whatever an allied follower attacks
their two demons to an enemy leader
sounds ok
cute i'm butler it's sword craft okay it
looks
it looks cool
sun priestess is something for us yeah
victoria's got rapple again she looks
really cute
skull runecraft
swordcraft
[Music]
that was it guys no
we weren't really lucky in those temples
but this time this time
it's a not very pretty doggle
shadowcraft okay
ew yeah
doesn't get much better he gets some
jewelry though
oh forest craft okay okay
wait the spin artist what class was that
what there's a ramble fantasy card cute
killed goat deal one damage to an enemy
follower then one damage to enemy leader
restore one defense to your leader
deal two damage results
i mean that's that's pretty
cute is she
she yeah she sounds good for havencraft
yeah should we put her in our deck
oh doesn't sound bad to me oh hello
that's not for human craft though is it
neutral given that anyway followed by
the following effect and this fellow
leaves play battleship instead
transformation doesn't count someone
combustion demon
that involve all uninvolved allied
combustion demons
oh
he's neutral so we could put him in our
death in theory but he doesn't really
suit my style
tempest dragon it looks cool though
wow wow wow
that sounds really dangerous he uses
fire
okay okay okay okay okay
oh what happened here okay we're gonna
dance it runecraft cute but no
dragon crap okay dragon crap so much
dragon grounds
human ground
okay okay okay okay okay
so cute
[Music]
that's a dope card i
think there's some people who envy me
for that card
ah
[Music]
oh
i love her i need to play grandma
fantasy oh no i already have noah
i already have noah in my deck uh noah
works with
uh rally right yeah yep yep yeah yeah
yeah
uh i i guess
does it make sense to put two noahs in
my deck
portal craft um
um three noise you need free
why i don't understand why do you need
free
why but maybe now i have possible three
who knows i don't i'm not sure how many
i had before
hallelujah she's so cute she's from
grandma fantasy tour
i see that i recognize the art style and
the the outfit
design the whole theme she's cute
well that face is kind of crazy let's go
back to that one
as many copies as possible of your best
cards oh
okay
[Music]
oh in my face oh my god swordcraft god
damn
[Music]
nope nothing for us nothing
nothing for us
unfortunately oh that was over the tenth
one
[Music]
yeah we still have 7 100
uh crystals so
let's use it a different cat
different cat different thingy fortune's
hand okay
we can try
okay a lot of you guys seem to want me
to do that one okay
let's go 10 packs from fortune hand
come on come on come on
grabbing my hands together you're here
right
come on give me something nice
oh what is that
[\h__\h] okay
poodle craft she looks cute though
holy [\h__\h]
holy bright i'll taller oh that's where
me and callie will get married
if an allied follower of war is in place
subtract
one from this emma's countdown
that's what someone oh that's actually
good
screw it go run out no no
yeah oh wait that card is pretty good
i feel like i should put that in my deck
wait he's haven't craft two
restore one defense to elite if an
allied follower will
war doesn't play drunk on restore four
defense to arm
he's dope hello hello me no voice there
let's
show them let's show them sing a song
sing a song
oh my god he's like speaking shitty
english
that's shitty english beauty for the
boys
for the boys
oh pretty it sounds
good we could put them in our decks i
like this box too that reminds me of
some game i think
[Music]
wait the feather folk guy was he also
even craft
oh my god look at those pretty cards
what
who are they cats
oh
[Music]
um
i hear it nana there we got another one
of those
okay oh cool
let's see hey she's pretty lovely if
another allied follower before doesn't
play destroyed and follow otherwise game
word
nice
she changed his hair color completely
and her whole hair style oh my god
i like her too okay we're getting some
good stuff for havencraft here
nothing like super legendary yet oh but
i already have her i already have her
but she's dope
i mean uh yeah she's pretty i love her
look at her he's so pretty akari me
[Music]
although the last time i used her i i
used her wrong so
oh forest crab okay
[Music]
let's see storm over variable has the
best cards for your class oh really
wow what's that
let me take a good look at it sword
craft goddamn
swordcraft runecraft pre-built deck
again
there is john i kind of want to build my
own deck
though i don't know i mean it's probably
better
if we build like if we get a little like
already pre-built back what do you guys
think i i do want to build myself but i
feel like
it's probably better if we get one
somewhere okay
oh there we go um
pre-built just take a break pre-built
deck apart
buy a pre-built bit
ghostly made what is that room grab
build build your own hmm
rebuild and make your own yep how that
sounds good i guess
let's do that well we're almost we're
running out of uh
crystal soon so we can get started on
that
soon we got a new pretty card but that's
portal craft again
god damn it optimistic beast master
hmm oh look at the tunnel key so cute
you got glasses
oh [\h__\h] i started opening
who are you cute cute girl hello mossy
music
oh my god oh my god
cute as hell also we got
this dude and this dude
[Music]
she's cute i love twintel girls
[Applause]
can't resist twin tail girls right
is that havencraft i see havencraft
yes i like her i like her
put lorena's holy water in your hand
during your turn when defense is
restored
to the good card right yeah
what about scalpicky put ellerina's holy
water into your hand during your turn
when defense is destroyed
to your leader if it's the second time
this turn
gain the ability to vote for oh
wait i feel like i already had her but
maybe not
[Music]
i'm happy with that okay okay what was
the other one you guys said
uh ah this one this one you guys said
this one i should pull two right
okay let's go let's make it fifteen
oh i can only do ten okay
[Music]
opening it with a van
okay wish me luck guys
oh crap nothing i already have her by
the way the guitar guitarist
um and the sacred uh girl down next next
to the guitarist yep i have her too
oh she's cute cute
she's a room crowd but she's so cute
whoa her style changes a lot
look at her that's a pretty card
oh cute
you know my eyes always go to those cute
cards but
this is cute too oh my god the pumpkin
is like crying
oh that is so adorable
it changes into like a like a like a
magician
where's that dragon choking on a
pumpkin oh look at the
cat in the back wait did you see the cat
in the background
look it's like in that shape when cats
are like scared or whatever
cute okay go
come on come on come on
oh said this uh haven't grabbed yeah
i've seen that one
restored very defensively the bain ward
can't be
targeted by any effect at the end of
your turn
you're strong he's pretty good i can put
him into my
um in my deck too
yo young bingo oh
spiderweb damn look at those cool cards
four out of ten bags and countdown from
the d
that looks very scary
wow
nothing really for havencraft okay
gotcha
got gotcha gotcha next up
is hemograph wait what does he do
transform a card and play into sacred
teachings
to play point havencraft amulet
countdown one
i'm in the holy falcon i've used some
that before yeah
hmm
what is that vengeful sniper ward deal x
damage to an enemy follower and then x
damage to an enemy leader
x equals half the number of allied
aminos destroyed this match
all rounded up so you would want to use
this like pretty much
like in the late game where a lot of
aminos are already gone
you can see oh she's strong yeah
i like to hear that
okay okay this one too possibly we can
put that one in our deck too the goblin
queen
not so much oh the revolver eagle too
hey i have do i have him already
we're fully eagle he's also a pretty
good like card for like the later game
oh [\h__\h] we got another one we got
another one
but it's dragon craft damn it
which is cute what a cute phoenix
from another dimension one of my cousins
yep um
forest uh-huh forest craft
channel craft neutral
i belong in dragon rap it's too late oh
we're going for haven craft
so what i wanna i wanna use hayden craft
i'm okay with that i mean there's
there's really like in every class
i see things that look interesting to me
it's
it's just uh i feel like
i can find happiness in any class
but we're going for haven craft
yep we're gonna we're gonna win with it
don't worry
okay that was that we still have
more uh
we didn't try this one yet but should we
give it a try like one
like five five packs maybe see what's
inside
yes no no
no oops what the [\h__\h] did i do
oops
no i thought you guys said it's like
balance
[Music]
okay then more of this one
let's go and then we can go maybe to the
granville fantasy one again something
or to the first one we want the first
but maybe we don't need it
maybe we don't need it because we can
create it ourselves huh
hello who is that
holy crap okay see i i wanna um do some
battles too
in this stream so let's get this done
soon
and go over to deck building see what we
need and what we have
and then we do a few fights what do you
guys think
we can also continue the story because i
i'm not that far in the story eva
but wait the story forces you to use
certain uh classes right so
hmm we can't really practice with
havencraft there oh
we got another set and now the set
and runecraft oh [\h__\h] oh no no no
i accidentally clicked skip what did it
what did i get
what did i get forest craft
another phoenix anything cool
you you guys see something shadowcraft
[\h__\h] swordcraft
[Music]
so animated set other than that
not really
no i want to try this one
a bit more maybe
[Music]
again let's try everything again
yeah unfortunately no sharks in haven
craft sorry
but we have a shark in halloween don't
worry
uh-huh we got the the young sister of
cali again
okay okay okay come on i feel it i feel
john coming right at me
[Music]
you've changed you changed very much
why do you put on that pumpkin you look
so pretty without it
john please reveal yourself
koi oh who is you
oops who is she portal craft
cute but we don't need her lots of fire
going on here
okay then
let's do a few more of that
that was a kind of fail for me as a
havencraft player
let's see come on oh i already have her
and i like her and we got one more eel
nice
we're gonna we're probably going to put
you in our deck oh i never know no
okay more noise the more the merrier i
guess
okay alisona again
interesting
oh again here but i i want
needles
[\h__\h] unfortunately
oh who is who is razia
dragoncraft god damn it she looks so
cute
come on oh my god
yeah razzie has busted oh she looks very
strong yeah what does she do
game plus one plus zero daily extension
enemy leader x equals this false attack
oh oh um
that was it damn it what should we spend
our last
money on we still got 2 800
more more storm of revenue
tell me what do you think is best i
guess one of those three
storm or fortune spend it on the pretty
later i do want that too
strong fortune storm
ovary okay
let's let's keep some money for a pretty
wait let me buy the lead of this oh wait
uh where was the leader not the cards um
shop supplies
violators i want a cute leader i don't
give a [\h__\h]
i don't give a [\h__\h] we have probably
enough
vials to make any cards that we need
let's get
let's get my cute cute girl
okay yes
i don't play grandpa fantasy but she
speaks to me
i bought her yes
look at her
ah
[Music]
cute it's all about the optics and the
aesthetics guys it's all about that
but
[Music]
okay let's let's spend our last money
oh yeah grab a pre-built oh oh well
we'll be fine we'll
i don't know which deck but
i am not sure which one pre-built so you
got a base oh wait well how much do they
cost joe now i spent
probably too much money now i probably
can't get anything
i just i just like this feeling of gacha
oh carney who are you
that art style looks familiar to me who
drew that
it's oh it's free oh pre-bill is free oh
oh hello there you go all
of my ticket
i guess we will do that then yeah
um
but i also looked at um like winner
decks like the
like in the game you can check like uh
for like tournament winner decks oh
death of the party uh
and i saw like one havencraft deck there
that we could maybe like
recreate phoenix girl
radical gunslinger cute let me look at
this
oh hello she got the horse now and look
at that
glass breaking
dramatic retreat ooh that looks dope too
thunderous roar wow
she's looking fine right really fine oh
so many car car means car mines
um yep that's that was
it goddammit i used all my luck in the
very beginning
okay um
and how much do i have left 13 350 we
could still
get them i didn't buy
buy pre-built dicks
let's see how does this work hysteria
won't grow
sanctuary hey oh
wait if that gives me all the cards for
free
why did i pull all the gotcha
[Music]
this one is only temporary
yeah okay how long
how how long
i guess we're getting done three months
oh
but that's even enough time to take part
in the
tournament okay well
okay i guess that's what we're doing
yeah let's create a
uh rotation
oh it's the cancer deck what do you mean
what's the problem of this deck
uh okay so what's in here eo is in here
nice
lorena is in here nice yep seeing some
familiar faces
my john baby is only in here one time i
have more
john's gonna put in more
i hate this deck this deck is meta
can't why is it cancer
it's not that hard to beat yeah yeah
i'm gonna edit that i guess
um set is in there three times
she kills my things i guess so yeah
unlimited healing wipe it out which is
why people hate it
this is exactly what i need though
oh you guys are just calling it cancer
because you had it as an
opponent
well that's good that's good endless
battles of cali it will never end
so our tournaments will be like five
hours
well that sounds good to me should we
test it out but wait i want to i want to
change some things like
i don't know
what what could we change what could we
tweak
let's see what we have for example holy
sanctuary if you have more evolution
points than your opponent recover two
play points
um if you have zero evolution points
on turns you are unable to evolve during
each of your turns when your leader's
defense is restored
for it the first time
deal free damage to a random enemy
follow the second time
summon the holy flame tiger the third
time give a random island
follower plus two plus two lord and the
following effect wow that's pretty damn
good
wow
ah so this means i don't i i personally
don't own
any of those but the deck gives me three
of them
that's what the plus one plus two and so
on means right
add one to the class of all
non-follow-up cards
in your opponent's hand ooh until the
strategy next door
that makes it more expensive for the
opponent to play cards
[Music]
okay give your leader the following
effect at the end of your turn
deal x damage to enemy leader
x equals your current turn number minus
five sorry that's too much text for me
to comprehend what
give your leader the full event at the
end of my turn
deal so and so damage to the enemy
leader sunso equals your current
turn number ah minus five no
damage is dealt if x is less than zero
this effect is not stackable
uh smile kill priest
restore two defense to you later
give your leader the following effect at
the end of your turn restore run defense
to your leader
spanish banishing i have uh researched
is better than just destroying
a card on on the opposite side normally
because banishing
it it kills them without activating your
effects like if they have an effect
that gets activated when they die or
giving me damage or whatever
dad will not act activate right and and
they can also not be revived from their
deck and all that
yep yep yep so it's always better to
banish them rather than killing them
normally
then verb did researches
deal damage free damage to all enemy
followers ooh
restore freedom defensively later yeah
draw card
at the start of your 10th turn invoke
this card then evolve it
what does an invoking mean
yeah i did some some homework yep
and can you imagine i will do even more
homework
for our battle of kelly i don't
mind spending a whole [\h__\h] day or two
days or one week
[Music]
in vogue means someone directly from
that oh
the start of the 10th turn invoke this
card
wait you mean that even if i don't have
it in my hand at my tenth turn i will
get this card
ah no i if i get it earlier and play it
it will come no wait that was what it
means it just comes out there because i
have it in my deck oh
restaurant five defense to elite ooh if
your leader has 14 defense or less
before defense was destroyed
drop two cards and randomly destroy one
of the enemy phones with the highest
attack and play
wow can't be involved using evolution
that sounds pretty
good restore one defense to you
[Music]
one of the best cards in the deck um
nice i want to test it out and then see
what we can change
before i change anything i guess okay
save that
um i'm staying
forever with callie dick
okay dammit
actually i have a chaotic craft oh okay
oh that's that's still here okay
i want to test it out i want to test it
out let's go let's go let's do practice
practice
[Music]
who uh we fight against
so can we you probably use one of those
which one
is it shallow crabs or blood craft we
want to fight against the one that she
has i guess
wait amazon one second be right back
[Music]
oh sorry sorry for the wait i will uh
play uh three minutes longer
yes sorry sorry sorry sorry uh
yeah yeah yeah yeah i always order [\h__\h]
of the things from amazon
yeah i'm back okay so what do we say
what do we want to fight against
[Music]
baby was milked or got milk
good shadow blood
[\h__\h] oh you guys say both
okay let's let's play against shadow
i feel like i mean cali would probably
choose that because of the skeletons
or blood crown
but wasn't bloodcraft like really
difficult i feel like she would
people will tell her to not do
bloodcraft because it's too difficult
i don't know let's try let's try both of
them
uh i guess let's try experience
let's battle the battle is on
the battle is on guys open the doors let
me in knocking knock knock
first ferra tiara vs experience
little luna
holy [\h__\h] those cards stand in the kitty
[Music]
uh
okay would have liked the card with only
one play point in the beginning but okay
we take what we get and this is the
first time i'm using this deck okay so
wow
[Music]
minus five so we want to use raw as late
as possible right
right voice actually was if you have
more evolution points on your opponent
recover two play points
no the effects use route on on five
play him as soon as soon as possible huh
it got like
[Music]
your current turn number minus five but
like if it's only the third
turn and it's minus five then it does
minus damage
[Music]
effect stays for the rest of the game
that's for the rest of the match current
turn one
so ah ah
he does that each turn
[Music]
oh he does oh he does that at each turn
as long as i keep him alive
so i just need to keep him alive well
that's also difficult though
do you free damage to all enemy
followers restore free defense
okay well i mean we don't have any
enough points for anything but i just
want to read the cards back oh
yeah give me a leader
if you have more evolution points in
your opponent recover to play during
each of your turns
when your latest defense is restored for
it oh my god this is
this is very complicated we'll just play
everything as soon as we can for now
okay okay
even if he dies the effect continues are
you [\h__\h] kidding me
are you kidding me
oh my god okay uh well
i guess i want to plan on something that
has an effect when it dies
but oh well okay
done
kind of wanted to play that later but
okay we're playing everything as soon as
possible
oh necromancer
oh we got a unicorn oh we got lorena
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
uh when defense is circulated if it's
the second time the stream gained the
ability to evolve what's your revolution
points
ah but let's get our unicorn first
[Music]
yeah i think i think we'll wait
with that amp okay
okay yeah your turn your turn
[Music]
well no problem we'll just get all our
defense back
oh [\h__\h] we got a second
but it's not stackable but anyway we're
gonna play him now
[Music]
let's play raw
was that a mistake you should do it as
early as possible right
[Music]
it will go well for sure
can't evolve now
oh [\h__\h] give me keep my defense back
please
defense please i wait that oh that was
holy sanctuary i don't know what i was
saying i thought it was a round
but we do have five uh two rounds
well wait what does that do again
[Music]
ah yes i need that
[Applause]
swipe the whole field
oh yeah ellie
that's that's pretty good we're cleaning
up we're cleaning up
oh [\h__\h]
they all love [\h__\h] last words i hate
it
[Music]
my hand is
overwhelming
okay
[Music]
vanish we should banish this dude
well that's six points
um
but yeah you guys say playing wrong or
are we playing
john
and blind justice
well well we want this effect each round
right okay
[Music]
[Applause]
okay but wait do i want to evolve him
maybe not
[Music]
above okay
okay we gotta keep him alive but we have
another one in case he dies it's all
good
oh yeah that's all i can do
yeah okay she got one damage
let's get her down let's bring her down
undead king oh no
wow
okay no no no no we're getting serious
here okay
this is wait oh i forgot to attack what
the [\h__\h]
um
i guess a vote for right away too i
would say
when she got involved uh ah
she's already evolved oh
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
i go for underlying
we got eight points oh god i got so many
good cards
[Music]
invoke this guy didn't involve it
oh yeah was it oh is this a tenth turn
oh thank you for the membership welcome
restore five defensive oh yes if you
later
had 14 defense or less before defense
was restored draw two cards random
destroyer
[Music]
hello hello hello okay we could also
play
uh i guess him oh yes one more defense
another one let's play drug oh well
let's play him now
keep on healing when are we up to 15
yeah it looked a bit dangerous well at
the moment but we're fine we're fine
with fun should we involve someone
huh we don't really need it
she's [\h__\h] dead
this is great this is awesome we're
going to win this
i'm going to call you all movies
did you kill my world yeah
when there's so many good cards i'm
having a problem to choose but the thing
is like
raj is not stackable anyway why don't we
have rat twice i guess to get him the
chance
to have higher chances to get him okay
let me let me try to understand all
these effects again deal
enhance five deal two diamonds restore
two defense gain plus two plus two
enhance eight wait what what is that
enhancing thing again
how do i know how enhanced i am
i already won yeah i guess i did
it cost eight more ah
oh and normally she costs less and now
now she costs me eight so she does more
damage
and stuff oh my god
well i mean we won actually yeah because
if we do this it's over
you can never win against me kelly
yeah i just need some more practice to
understand all my cars and then it's all
good
holy [\h__\h] oh my god
okay let's let's uh let's try against
bloodcraft let's see what happens there
um solo practice
nice thank you thank you i mean the
the deck did all of the work for me
i don't feel like i did much but
that deck was just too easy
that's really as experienced
um
damn
okay who's first office yes
first oh okay
[Music]
okay okay let's go let's battle
we start with jill brilliant nice
yeah give me that amulets give me which
one am i getting
holy section
i like what i see i like what i said
okay i can't play blind just because he
has nothing on the field
i guess i'm just avoiding them
oh is that the oh is that the only
amulet in my deck
what it doesn't hurt me because i'll
just recover everything anyway
what does she do put a random follower
of crystallized or amla with countdown
from you deck into your hand
oh i also have the unicorn ah true
turtle so i could um
maybe a bit too early to play blind
justice let's play hello
hi cat oh yeah walk in front of the
camera yep okay bye bye
um
ouch
okay we got four player points first of
all um
do i i want to attack the leader yeah
[Music]
and oh we got the unicorn
holy second oh we got two holy factories
what's going on
let's play one
[Music]
um
uh-huh okay she's dead no problem no
problem
okay we can't evolve now um
we got five points we could we could
play another holy sexually
uh and maybe a unicorn
benevolent one ah that one
ah yeah that's good because he has
currently quite a lot of
uh cards out there um
let's play sanctuary afterwards
you
hello hello please move please move your
butt
thank you sorry cat is passing by just
checking out how's it going she's like
oh my god you've got some great cards
yes yes i do okay six points let's play
[Music]
i got so many good cards like what am i
supposed to do with all these amazing
cards
that's so blind justice maybe
wait i healed him with that huh
[\h__\h] what
oh [\h__\h] oh that restores defense to him
oh
oh well okay
oh oh we'll get him down again we'll
bring him down again
oh he hurts himself of the wolf and
again you hurt yourself again i guess
that's what bloodcraft does
is that what they do
[Music]
do this
again um blood craft is
masochistic
yeah play the unicorn and
evolve him
let's go straight for a leader i can't
okay that's no
no problem go for him
[Music]
let's see what he does he's thinking
he's thinking
we'll get too much really doing free
damage
oh [\h__\h] we're down to nine okay i i need
to oh
yeah welcome
welcome eo welcome uh what deal four
damage
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
we don't need to evolve it do we
[Laughter]
this is fun i like winning
okay increase difficulty okay i'll go
[Music]
but you gotta think cali is not not
gonna be an elite difficulty
even if we make this this npc elites
difficulty like the highest one
kelly is not gonna be that good at this
thing
[Music]
maybe set
set
um
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] what did i do i can't attack the
leader anyway
wait what what gave him the four damage
was that me
with uh holy cemetery
oh was that was that right
hello the world
oh yeah it got invoked i was just about
to say i didn't even do anything
um
wait i can't
oh
i mean the only thing i can only do is
play this
okay
yeah because then my field is full
thanks ryan it did the job for me
fun oh my god
oh
[Music]
what's this one what the deck name the
[\h__\h] deck name
let's play against luna again but harder
difficult way let's make it an
expert or expert too maybe
that that sounds a bit dangerous because
i still don't know really how well
like not well to use my i don't know
that well how to use my deck yet
do you think we could do experts too
[Music]
let's try it will be funny if uh
i don't win
let's sing
let's mix mix i'm second okay most of
the time i'll always first interestingly
but okay
you can you can be first i don't mind um
said sorry bye-bye i already got hulu
sanctuary i can kind of kick it out
because i feel like i'll get it soon
enough
anyway should i kick it out
um okay keep it okay
lorena okay that's good too we never
used her yet but she is good
always keep sanctuary okay
okay luna show me what you got on expert
two difficulty
oh hey nice nice nice nice
at least i could play something
countdown starts now
thank you for the super chat thank you
oh johnny
my bae okay
if it if she's only 20 defense and i
restore her five does she go up to 25 or
is that already the maximum
can it can it go higher than that only
try off
okay well then if it's capped out then
then i have no problem of using that
hear that early
what does that do again do you want
damage to the enemy no
no need for that yeah yo
let me play lorena keep her okay
lorena what does she do again put on her
and that's holy water
during your turn when defense is
destroyed to you later if it's the
second time this turn
can you will you do a little frontier
okay yeah
don't play lorena now huh keep lorina
[\h__\h]
okay whatever well we will win this
anyway
maybe
going pvp and get destroyed no
no lorena rest in peace lorena
uh oh
oh there's her holy water
[Applause]
[Music]
now sanctuary mm-hmm
there we go
your turn what can you do
what can you do
ouch no problem i'll heal myself later
there we go we got one here five points
completely you oh we weighed a bit more
i think we weighed a bit more
[Music]
i still have two points left but i'm
good
ah yo
two damage right
wait which one do i want to kill
whatever
[Music]
yeah a little back to full health
and we got a little a little holy flame
tiger welcome
[Music]
where are you parents your parents are
not here stop talking to your parents
they're not going to come and help you
no one's here to help you
okay six six play points let's see
[Music]
hmm
um
play maybe the water
but but ally means to a cart not to the
leader right and
we wouldn't need that right now
because he has full defense anyway and
that is capped out too right
capped out too right i can't give him
more right
i love both him though and
she has uh
oh i can't tackle no wait i got 25
health now oh wait what's that
stat is here too
[Music]
place that
okay let's go
[Music]
oh it gives me maximum defense plus five
damn
i like him i like this deck it's fun
shall we play john no
yeah yeah cause he has he luna has a lot
of
uh enemies on wait that also kills my
allies
oh it hurts me too yeah right that was
the thing about john
at that first
[Music]
and then play here
i mean she's nine health and i have 25
there's
no way that she will win against me
bye-bye
[Music]
okay
oh it's already been two hours i feel
like playing longer
i will probably still you know tweak the
set
a little bit to my personal taste
although it's already pretty [\h__\h]
perfect i don't know but i don't want it
to be like exactly the same deck you
know
um
[Music]
i want something
um
ah yeah give me some new cards
ah what do we got what's what's this
dude for them
we're dragging it out a little bit here
and we're so close to winning but i
don't really have
we could play like
i don't know i'm just playing anything
now really
[Music]
what does that do again i keep on
forgetting we start two defense uh we
really don't need to restore
any defense
[Music]
ah [\h__\h]
um oh it should have evolved her maybe
dammit
holy sanctuary again
your freedom
[Music]
m
well next turn
don't know what his effect would have
done but we don't want him here
what's that little random ambulance yeah
plea play all my cards dude i totally
need to
heal myself
okay well i mean next turn you did
[Music]
let me kill you come on come on
come on little girl
you shouldn't play with phoenix's keep
on playing with your little dolls
you little punk you little punk
oh oh there we go hello it's uh
that time again
[Music]
i want to get expertise
okay well
i kind of want to continue um but yeah
that's it for today's uh shadowverse uh
stream i think we're gonna go
read uh some super chats i think that's
okay right
um i think we did that last time too
should be fine that was fun i can't wait
to battle kelly it's happening
soon oh very soon soon soon
um look forward to that uh
i think we know who will win
[Laughter]
in the in the description uh there's a
link
to download the game if you want to
download it use that link to do it
because it will benefit me thank you
very much
uh please please go ahead and try it out
yourself it's
so much fun if you like card games but
you've been looking for something to
play like me
then this is the game to go and
yeah who knows maybe maybe i can battle
you someday i don't know if that's the
thing
don't get cocky
[Music]
we can do it dad's gonna win shut up
mom's gonna win this fight that is one
too much recently
you know in in in uh the
the other collab that we did i forgot
the name
you know the game you know it you
watched it
now it's my time to shine my time like a
phoenix i will shine and i will rise
and i will not let her take me down that
is for sure
so i will go have a little um
super chat intermission uh
let me check is there anything i forgot
to say i don't think so
just look for it uh on our twitter we
will be
letting you know uh newest um updates on
when the next collab is happening and
when the tournament is happening
and and yeah otherwise you'll just
if you don't follow us on twitter i
guess you can just wait on youtube until
the restoration stream restoration is up
good yeah thank you guys for watching
this stream
[Music]
i will practice the havencraft deck
more until i master it
and uh yeah i'll see you guys soon i
hope i hope you liked it
and i'll see you i'll see you in the
super chat reading actually
in give me like two minutes yeah me
funko
all right for everyone who's leaving
already
i say and in german we say affidavit
for everyone everyone who's staying uh
thank you let's let's
have a little chit chat thank you saddle
face for sponsoring the stream
thank you i had a blast thank you
thank you thank you see ya
[Music]
me
foreign
no
[Music]
hello hello i am so excited about many
many many many many many many many
things guys
many things um
let me drink some water
[Music]
okay
yes i am back yeah i'm excited about
some things um
yeah some things some things many things
many good things uh
i think the one one thing that's not so
good though is that
um i'm moving right
and i'm having um
a little i had a little bamboozle moment
today let's say it like that
uh so a while ago
i booked the the moving date right
and i kind of did it for like
a personal contact let's
just put it like that and i got my
moving date
i told them i'm moving on the 1st of may
and i need to have internet
moved over so they made like the
contract and all that
and set the moving date to the first of
may
and now yesterday i was like looking at
the calendar it was like all that first
of all first of
may is saturday second of all
it's it's a it's a national holiday in
my country
so i was like is that real
is someone coming over to my place to do
that or do i do it without anyone does
that really work out
and then yeah the person from that
internet company was like oh [\h__\h]
yeah i doubt that someone's gonna come
on that day i mean someone will come
in general but uh
on that day yeah let me check up on that
so he got back to me and he offered
to eva eva sent me someone
next monday the 26th
or the 27th
which is i thought first earlier is
better huh but
no because once i do that i i'm at that
point i'm not moving yet
but the internet will be cut off from
the place where i currently am so
earlier is not better and then the thing
is the first is
the first the first is a saturday so
the second also doesn't work so it has
to be the third so yeah we settled for
the third so i don't have internet on my
pc
on the weekend so on the first it's okay
because i'm moving anyway but i kind of
wanted to stream on the second on
on sunday but i guess we're not
streaming the whole weekend
uh the first and second yeah i will not
be streaming
i will get my internet on the third
so on the third in the evening i should
be streaming and then we should go back
to normal
yeah oh well it's just two days but the
thing is i'm also taking
monday off probably so next week i might
have
three days off i'm not sure because on
monday yeah no actually i'm pretty sure
unless i stream early before no time on
monday which is probably not gonna
happen
but on monday me and my friends
are going to paint my apartment
the whole day and then later have some
dinner and all that yeah
so we might only perhaps only have four
days
of uh streaming next week
which kind of stresses me out because i
feel like that's not
enough and uh falling behind
already yeah i mean yeah i might upload
like a small video
like the m2 videos yeah but still it
stresses me out
oh well oh well there's nothing
really i can do about that
but stay with me guys please stay with
me
stay with me and
maybe help help with the algorithm by
commenting
on my streams after the streams are over
comment on the streams and and you know
give them a thumbs up or thumbs down
whatever
that would help because if i stream less
for a little while
then there is a possibility that youtube
says [\h__\h] you
guys
[Music]
i'll try to be as active as possible
anyway but
i'll take i'll take the weekend break
sure
but i'll try to also squeeze something
in on monday
uh before because we start
like painting uh after in the afternoon
so maybe i can stream like for one hour
a quickie like sliver.io or mario kart
uh on on monday also i was thinking
of doing a members only stream next week
but the thing is like if i can only
stream on four days or
perhaps maybe getting in five days then
having a members only stream
takes away a normal stream a public
stream
which i already don't have much of next
week
if you understand what i'm trying to say
don't need one make it public really i
mean we did have uh two member streams
in in a row like in in two weeks
uh recently
um is it okay
i'll definitely do a member stream in
the follow-up week in in may like in the
in the first week of may
um i'm fine with it being public okay
okay okay
but the good good good um
happy news for you guys so the thing
that i'm planning to do as a members
only stream
is
is maybe not so good but
i just want to um chill and sing some
songs for you guys
for members only
is
but i personally don't mind if within
the members
the people who were there would share
like a recording of the stream of the
people who weren't there but only
between members of course
um if there is a way that members can
share with other members
um then i don't mind
if you guys can just you know if you
know someone else who's a member
anyway that's that's a topic for
sometime soon
uh i i know there's members only
archives but if it's an
unarchived kanoke stream that means that
i'm unarchiving it because um
i'm singing songs that are not like
copyright
free you know so i have to delete the
archive
anyway let's read the super chats from
today's
what's wrong hi hot wings
please give this money to the beatles
family yes the people that you and your
wife wrote off
his family needs some money for nectar
they are hungry
ggs thank you what's wrong
why are you sad
[Music]
oh you like you have so many different
kind of moods
like a roller coaster i i don't know if
i can find the beatles family but i feel
very sorry for the beetle too
and mr gaspings again thank you this
money is for you dog
thanks for giving us tons of good cards
and kiara you're the best and never let
anyone
tell you otherwise thank you thank you
thank you thank you it's fun
to give you all this content guys i'm
really glad to have this
job so i'm enjoying doing it and i'm
glad you guys enjoy it too
kiana's pretty damn you mortal kombat
announce the voice finish it
i don't know what that sounds like but
um i'm planning to do a drawing stream
next week
where we can finish that sketch although
i'm not sure if you will
see the original rough state of the
sketch i'm not sure if i'm allowed to
show
that's maybe something for like for like
you know maybe one year anniversary
yourself
that would maybe a moment where i can
show you like the
the first rough states of
of kiaga's design
maybe not maybe now is not the moment
you know
he on our back when
i'll try to one day draw myself
showing my back to you guys so that you
guys know what it looks like
[Music]
chat mwah after an extra day without
tanjo this week we decided to fry one
more chicken today hoping to please
thank y'all
the sacrifice has been accepted the
jokes aside tanjo i'm actually really
glad to see you take another day off
you've been working too hard since day
one thank you
i mean not too hard i would say
oh i mean i've definitely been working
hard but not too hard
that's something you should you should
tell kelly
uh but i've been doing my best and and
yeah thank you
um yesterday i was actually like
most of the time uh
i went i went to my apartment yesterday
twice
like once i showed it to my roommate and
then later on i showed it to my um bff
um and uh my
me and my roommate we went to my
apartment i just wanted to show it to
her
and then when we arrived we saw that
like something
uh like came from amazon and when i was
not there
um and uh my roommate just started like
building the furniture that arrived it
was like two
tables like couch tables and she's just
like oh should we should i should i
build up now
and i'm like it we didn't come to build
anything but
i guess if you i guess if you don't mind
okay
like i love her oh my god so she built
it those two little tables
in like five minutes or so
oh my god what an angel yeah rmt
i explained that to her yesterday why
people say rmt about her i explained it
to her
she's so good like she said that it's
kind of like fur
pherotic that it's actually she doesn't
mind doing that kind of stuff
i'm so grateful to have her
yeah it's like building legal yeah i
guess it's like a puzzle
i mean those tables really weren't that
difficult we didn't have any tools but
do you know those so small small thing
that always comes with
like furniture that you buy just a small
thing that you
like like turn around and around and
around and you know
i don't know what it's called allen key
that's what it's called in english allen
key oh yeah that's probably what it was
yeah so she just did it with that you
have the metal outfit yeah yeah
yeah yeah um
so she built that for me so i now have
one
piece of furniture already
and i i brought because we went there
twice uh yesterday i already brought
some suitcases over there that i already
had packed up uh
previously so a little bit
of work was done even before the actual
moving date which is pretty good yeah
so that's how i used my day yesterday
and also
[Music]
i guess you guys saw that i made that
omelette that everyone was like super
shook about like
guys i want to say something you guys
were
way too surprised about me being able to
cook a decent omelette
first of all omelette is not difficult
to make that's like so easy
second of all
some of you guys
underestimate my
staying alive or living a normal life
abilities
you underestimate me what do you think i
am do you think i cannot stay alive when
i'm like
on my own i've lived on my own
quite a lot of times and i have been
i have left home at an age
so early that even my mom was shocked
i've left home as early as possible as
early as legally possible
and ever since then i've traveled around
the world
on my own lived overseas
continents away from my home
and some of you guys still underestimate
whether or not i can keep myself alive
and care for myself what the [\h__\h]
is wrong with you guys
i can very much take care of myself i
can very much
cook if i wanted to okay it might not be
so tasty always
okay i'm just a little bit lazy
sometimes
it grinds my gears
because because people who underestimate
me in that way
it's not like those are haters it's you
guys some of you guys some of my
supporters
who think i'm some kind of like baby who
can't speak
can't move can't walk
i am shook should i repeat what i just
said
how i've lived my life up until now i've
been very very [\h__\h]
independent okay
i know how to i've i've lived for a
while
on such a low weight because there's
this system
uh in in australia that we call lehrer
which um where you do it like for three
years
you work at a place any any place
for three years while also going to a
school
that has something to do with that job
uh
you go to that school like two months in
one year and the rest of the time you
work and you do that for three years
that's that's the system we have here
called lere
in the first year you earn like
basically nothing
i earned like what was it maybe
500 dollars
maybe uh in the first year and then yeah
it's an
apprenticeship and and uh
in the first year i already lived alone
with that 500 600
i lived alone in an apartment which cost
me
uh 5 450 a euro okay 450 euro
and my income was i don't know 500 or
euro and i survived okay
so stop doubting
my abilities to be an adult
i know very well how to be an adult and
how to
live my life how the hell did you do
that yeah that's a
good question i i had another small side
job
to you know pay for a little bit of food
but i
lived off a very cheap cheap chip cheap
food i've always looked at the cheapest
prices
i bought not much food and tried to eat
as much as possible at work
and all that but yeah i am indeed thank
you sui
i am a strong independent phoenix i know
how to live my life
so yeah just like my mother mother if i
wanted to be
i can be a survivalist um
so if i see yeah if i see one more
person doubting
this i'm gonna be really really mad i'm
really disappointed in hearing that
it's all funny and jokes to doubt uh
what i say
but i feel like
you doubt me a little a little bit too
much
a little bit too much you guys need to
have a little bit more confidence in
your potential
after all i am now the leader
of a worldwide dominating fast food
chain called kfp
stop doubting me i have complete faith
in you thank you i love you
[Music]
okay there's still some idiots who still
think it's funny
to doubt me i'm not going to ignore that
and just feel sorry for you guys
yeah free languages too there's all
kinds of things where i can i can
say as an argument
but yeah some people cannot be
uh i cannot be cannot i cannot change
some people's minds it seems
anyway thank you felix
chris duncan the beetle girls packaging
oh
oh my god is
i think that and your wife cast me into
the void froggy the nectar was to feed
my beetle wife and nine beatles babies
why why did you do this
subs
oh my god why is there so many people
talking about the beetle
did you all emotionally connect to the
beetle that much
looking for the top vacation paul
mccartney
why what's your bloody problem with the
beatles
mate don't go around saying i'm a ghost
rude super chatter looking for a fight
i may be all but still kicking
[Music]
so that my viewers understand what what
it means
speaking of imposters did you guys
there's not the tangents today guys lots
of tangents
i could go on a tangent of a tangent i
have so many tangents prepared too but
i'm gonna keep some
for tomorrow but did you guys see the
the video
that i retweeted on twitter the the
among us
um one see okay that was a imposter
because that that's a real baby
uh that video is like literally me i
always play
with an orange skin and with the egg on
my head
and that was so cute how he was cracking
the eggs and then
a chick came out and another one and
another one
and another one that was so cute
it's like me cracking my eggs when when
the membership
time comes that you guys get out of your
egg
and i'm like hello and you you just you
just um
put it and you you what's what's what's
porza
in in english you roll out of the shell
saying
you stumble yeah you stumble out of
tumble dump your tumble out of
the egg when i crack it open
so cute i just asked oh congratulations
i love that video that felt like it's
literally about me
that's why i retweeted it
[Music]
that was so cute
i love that need attention version of
that vid what do you mean that is
potential version
miss vince darkishan bradley hello ellen
thank you soon
sorry about this unflattering
screenshots i took of you just want to
say any photo of you is always beautiful
and flattering no matter the space you
make you're always cute
yeah that's true thank you
thank you bradley duncan harbaugh line
danke i know i promised previously that
i would never miss your streams with my
kikiri queen
but i'm not being so good right now so i
hope it's okay to take a day off of
course
please take care of yourself and feel
better soon
as leg hair reduction tai chi thank you
for the red super chat
wow may the gacha gods be with you thank
you
they were with me in the beginning but
in the end it didn't really matter
because i
could just get the free deck but hey
now now you guys know that you could
also just get a free deck and just play
with a really epic deck
yeah that's pretty dope
i like that i like that i guess see this
is i guess a good thing about
like um playing card games
not in reality with real cards but like
online
on the pc because like getting like
like free card decks like that instantly
is not a thing you can do
like with real cards right you know what
i mean like this is something
that makes digital card games a bit
superior i guess
although i mean playing with real cards
will always have its charm i mean that's
that's just a charm of of card games
playing on a table
with uh with an opponent right in front
of you
that's just to me that's the charm of
card games forever
but there are some good things about
digital card games
as we can see yeah
nothing beats a cardboard papercut
yeah getting cuts from your clients i
mean i never really got that but i liked
having you know those fancy sleeves and
stuff too
hmm yeah
best thing about in person cartoons is
that i can cheat and live all in fact ah
yeah i guess like that's like in digital
card games you know everything is like
like pretty much automatic and you can't
really lie yeah that's true but in like
real
real battles in person i guess that yeah
that is
wow okay motion i will never play a card
game against you in real life
that's for sure
uh anyway time to thank you for the
support i hope you enjoyed the stream
tai chi
arizona lc lapin thank you soon p.m
dead crying baby donkey stream the
certified question
i really wonder is it that crying baby
a side account from the baby or is it a
fake baby
simon marshall duncan why are you so
kind and lovely it should be illegal to
be as lovely as you
much love from new zealand cool new
zealand
i want to go thank you
sanchez foundation white buddha
and elsie lavender
in
ss20x function thank you
these streams really do cheer me up
thank you i'm glad to hear that that's
my goal
hey wait let me translate the name
[Music]
um
that finger dankeson
that's your thunkushin hello from south
korea i haven't watched you in a long
time hope you will
come sign me down thank you for coming
back you should watch my streams more
often
thank you for the pinky by the way thank
you thank you soon i hope you enjoyed
the stream
and yeah thank you thank you
don't forget about me that's crank baby
thank you soon
dead crying baby
i'll be moving to a new place tomorrow
i'll be staying offline for my own
mental health for a while yeah that's
good every once in a while
i won't be able to catch your stream but
i promise to return with fancy art from
you
for you thank you i'm looking forward to
that good luck with your move
and i hope you feel better soon you're
always welcome to come back
and get shot thank you thank you
what does that mean can we call it song
is uh phoenix in korean
[Music]
the guy with that one face you soon
canvas night thank you soon
my dad always used to say train hard by
easy
practice against the hardest challenges
challenges so
you can so you will improve the way
something catches you by surprise you
aren't tilted by it yeah i'll try to
upload the enemies um difficulty
grade even more so that i am prepared
well yes yes yes yes
thank you
uh oh my god buddha you can speak
korean
wait wait did i stop i just refreshed um
there we go
samwell somewhere else for telly thank
you soon
i have a good question i have a question
about the road back sitting what is it
exactly never heard of it before i have
a good
weekend by the way thank you well
backseating is like when some
when when the audience tries to help the
streamer
um to like show the streamer how a game
is played for example
it can be in a good way i guess but it's
mostly
like a lot of people hate it because
like they want to play it on their own
i generally don't mind it most of the
time
[Music]
oh muda is korean oh no
yeah i mostly don't mind you guys
helping me okay since the baby just sent
two super chats like that i guess it's
uh
the same yeah it's their own
their own uh account i would guess
it was a flying and
yeah anyway i mostly don't mind unless i
i specifically say
uh i'm usually when i really don't want
the back seating i put like a little
a little uh a little note up and say
shut up please
but mostly i i want you guys to help me
because i need you
only thing falling behind is me falling
behind on my super chat please take care
of yourself and don't stress too much
thank you
i'll try at the moment it's going pretty
smooth i'm a bit really from
i'm just worried if we if the painting
will go
well because
i don't know if i wonder if it would get
like really like
spotty i hope i hope it will
turn out to look nice i hope so
but other than that i think the moving
will go smoothly
we'll just um barrel my friend's
car and well my friend my bff actually
just got uh her license so um
now she can help even more so we're
gonna
probably do like 10 trips with the car
uh yeah it will take some trips because
it's not like a big
moving truck but still it will be fine i
don't know really
i don't really have any furniture
besides my chair and and maybe a mirror
a standing member yeah but that's about
it
congrats to bs of young
i have my pc of course but it's not
furniture that's not furniture
the green villain is
don't worry we aren't going anywhere you
can't upload some clips and have like
premier thing or whatever to keep
yourself happy
yeah i guess i'll do yeah another
premiere for like a five second video
we like that don't we that hypes it up
it hypes a little little
little video up so much that at the end
you're like what was that what just
happened
no i didn't buy an yet i want to wait
until
i can go to a furniture uh store
in person rs idle thank you
and until then i just use my old towels
well fireface sand was a great stream
looking forward to the cali battle beat
her attention you can do it thank you
finally someone who believes in me
uh you know if at least my own audience
would believe in me
that would be nice
thank you emperor gold slime thank you
and danny scope thank you black friction
thank you for the pinky
got some extra cash from a birthday
bonus at work have some kiana also don't
fret about the days off
if you really want uh a stream that's
not too internet intensive maybe a
simple that stunk will work yeah but the
thing is in on those two days i only
have my phone internet and
i i don't know how
i don't know if i can like use my phone
internet on my laptop or anything
probably
no it's okay i just won't stream those
two days but
but yeah wait let me read the other one
that i skipped
empire gold slime i think that's a pinky
probably
well since you're doing a kind of
looking could you sing pink's sake from
one piece sorry but i have to say
no because i don't know any one piece
songs and
i don't have the time to learn
uh whole new songs that i
don't really care much about sorry
wait anyway let me read the rest
uh also we do memberships as another way
to support you mama we don't need member
streams but we appreciate it love you
thank you that is a bit
reassuring but but i still don't want to
go too long without a member's only
stream
so i'll do my best to um give you a few
more
to make up for the missing ones this
week and next week
mewtwon
[Music]
my girlfriend recently introduced me to
hong live and now i've fallen down the
whole life well
broken my legs and can't get out but you
get the honor of my first super chat
thank you thank you
i hope you'll get out of there uh
someone help him cyrux function the
great philly means sankishon
shut up you're roasting me with that
superstar yeah i can cook more than the
[\h__\h] omelets
and everyone said my omelette looked
freaking good you guys didn't even
believe
some of you guys were like did you buy
those did you order dog did you roommate
magnet
no i made it myself and it was yummy and
today i'm cooking the carbonara with
asparagus
with asparagus and uh to rolla
thick i was too old
it will be super yummy i'm going to
share it with my roommate
dominique
was raised to be able to survive she can
adult very well and honestly cook better
than i do now if we bring up doing more
than five push-ups shut up
but thank you for the rest of that super
chat because that was nice yeah
black friction function strongest
phoenix live never doubted you for a
second
and black frickin
why remain unseen duncan
as an apology for darling attention
thank you thank you i accept it
james mcphee thank you for the red super
chat
wow respect for our strong independent
potential
danger thank you
hmm
all right just had a random thought in
my head
that i can't say out loud right now
has nothing to do with the super chat
sorry um i'm just
losing uh my focus
thank you thank you thank you james
jameson james and
james one of the good people for
actually
acknowledging and recognizing my
my ability to survive
thank you
good soon from canada if i remember
correct when you traveled here once
which part
it's a big country no i didn't
i never did i wish i did
second monkey donkey
oh wondering which donkey should muda
dankeshan let me try to translate that
[Music]
this super chat doesn't say anything
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
but now muda sounds korean to me indeed
dude i said she wants to marry you when
did she say that
i'm marrying her on the spot let's go oh
sorry i actually have calories sorry i
forgot
but i love gouda
oh he's not korean oh why did you guys
think he's korean
after that
[Music]
i'm surprised there's so many here right
now i'm just reading super chats and
they all say they i i asked them like
okay if they hear now these must be
japanese bros who actually understand
english and they say they don't
they say they don't even understand any
english
but i feel like they do
a little bit at least
[Music]
wait i think something was announced
while i was streaming
um
yeah where is it where is it
where did you guys see that oh there it
is
reach over pack two nivea
[Music]
yeah so uh if you check the groove
coaster
uh twitter the group closer is a
good idea to stream on groove coaster
recently
and now me and callie are in there as
well
yes yes yes how exciting so
that means i will perhaps
do a groove close the stream
i'm not really good with like
rhythm games music rhythm games but
watching
goodall play it like it seems like
somewhat
manageable um
good at any kind of rhythm game without
even practicing it seems it's so i'm
like shook
it will be um very very
very very big fail but we'll listen to
my song in the game so i'm excited about
[Music]
that
yeah i know she makes urban games look
easy in general but grove coaster just
looked
easier than other rhythm games to me
yeah we'll just use the easy mode yeah
thank you for hatching thank you
hmm so let's go
cyrik thank you black friction alberto
duncan
black friction thank you and telescope
thank you alexander the lion
at this kfp fast food chain i would like
one that is very high in management the
position that say could potentially
bankrupt the company you've done wrong
the great feeling means duncan spitfire
zero duncan
oh please watch the archive then so
we're almost done here but yeah
monster hunter tomorrow also exciting
skydiving evans l duncan
using some of my college funds to say i
love this community you'll make me so
happy even though i don't know any of
you
thank you i'm glad to hear that please
enjoy your time here
kind of new dungeon even if you do
japanese only stream camera we will come
and we mean it we love you that much mom
thank you thank you thank you
thank you soon oh i'll think of
something we'll definitely do
one in may
matthew kingsley
[Music]
thank you i'm happy that my song is
included in the game
that's that's exciting
gosh duncan
thank you and i think that's
it i really need to go on an idol
meeting yeah that's
it okay thank you guys that's it for
today i'll see you tomorrow we have two
streams tomorrow
minecraft which will probably i guess
maybe maybe be on the
japanese minecraft store we will see
and uh monster hunter rise
oh celebration is still here thank you
thank you thank you
okay i hope you guys had fun uh once
again
if you enjoyed today's shout-off stream
please
uh check out the link in the description
and maybe get the game for yourself also
you know help the algorithm leave a
comment after the stream
and and and and yeah i had fun
guys thank you i'll see you soon
and enjoy what we say
[Music]
thank you everyone who joined this
stream
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
you