Uh
me me
benme
san
voodoo
[music]
huh
me huh
me
huh
[music]
me
see me huh
huh
[music]
info nh
spa
today
me
[music]
b 2
huh
have it  Masu
Masu
voodoo
Omas
What's going on
Ah
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you are watching.
[Music]
ooooooooooooooooooooooo
oooo
who do
ban
Team by 4th house ah
[Music] It's a
pixel aroom like a full-time employee
Ana
person Ruth says
All 1 members do
[Music]
Toba's wallet
good Nh
[Music]
Pyut
irb
Ah, it's intense  It's so intense Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
From the media or my seniors!  It's a
good day for the 7 companies in the middle of the oc 4 the his
[Music]
seles amen 7 team aso
wear way oa pass-through subapi
so
[laughter]
Eh, I'm sorry I made a lot of mistakes
ome
rosanyeah Fender
Invited Floor Esper Hayao Aka Senpai B 5 size
Base
As usual, I'll explain the program first.If you
'll leave it alone, the party's readers will read it.
Topepece is Pete's Hospital Life Lamp
Erin Main Meet Me Comprehensive Life
Chan two points s Machi House
Annauchi 2 Abeshi buss
Let's play bra t 4th row Hotakana Sekihara Hori
Talk is an interview for English-speaking countries  The purpose of the talk
show day is to get
people from overseas to know more about Japanese talent during the Obon holidays.The purpose of the talk show day is to get people from overseas to know more about Japanese talent during the Obon holidays.The
host, Chara Takanashi,
will present this to you.Spoon Understand 1  I'm
going to interview you today, Isou Jameko in View Customershu,
a
franc sex, be the with
you,
Tadashi Inoue.
No, that one,
Kuhuu,
if you like, you
can write your impressions, either in the middle or at the end, but
if you come back on Twitter about the distance,
then yeah, I'd like you to write about it in Hashizabu Holder Ward.  I
wonder if I can improve my training. I want you to say that. Thank you very much.
Everyone, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa buff meu
After the web interview, let's
call a guest. Neko-neko-san,
cat-san
[Music]
Hidden.
Henna and shochu, I ca
n't say whether it's good or not. It's underwater.
Yeah,
okay,
okay, this is okay. I'm
still here. Hello,
I'm strong.
It's okay to speak Japanese at first, but I'd
like you to introduce yourself, please.
Yes, everyone, let's have a dumpling. Virtual
Idol Gamer, Negomen, Maid's a.
Everyone, Akane.
rar
nobasa
cheeza  bar system aqua
farm e4 f the knife idol
gamer brief cap tus pisu
club queen 10 points are
you doing
a
[music]
Well then, senpai, it
seems like today we're going to delve deeply into the dark side of Aqua War Crimes in general, but
are you ready? You'll have to
listen, do
n't be nervous. I
was talking to Aqua-senpai 30 minutes before we used Hook.
Even if it's only for 3 seconds, when I don't have anything to talk about, Aqua, my
senior will start yelling. Come on, come on! Oh,
what's going on? I was waiting for the ladder, but at
that time, who came to help me?
Entrepreneur.  It would
be nice
if you could talk in a mood that made you really want to talk in 30 minutes with a cutter tomorrow
. You
ate a lot of things.
truth kids game fashion
topics org we are rudy
chan charking 4 sm appeal
seasbreen y star  Please don't worry until the 022 way.
Please feel free to share more about yourself today.
Please, I'd like to go to the first question.
Mai Hakase. What have you been doing lately
?
Yeah.  Yes, that's right.While I'm
doing that distribution, I'm
also putting a little effort into singing.I'm
putting a lot of effort into idol cuts from ringing singer activities.
rng
r fx e 2 c inc Ease Green-
san, come on, yay, you're an idol.As
expected of Aisa,
out of all the live shows, that car center is the most idol-
aware.I often say that
these days.  Hey,
if you make a noise, don't you
think I'm not trying hard? Maybe I'm not right.
Ah, I
don't know if Air is the best, but idols
don't go to the bathroom after all, so I
think everyone shouldn't go to the bathroom either.
Kaaaan, I
see the loss ipadair ccs
bef 9-san's opening suspension warp
fried garden tipo sailor and cse
nr 4 a i c that's right, amplifier style
booster lover yes posture nemocco
attached into dospara pain
[ __ ] softer elementary school high pressure
after the high pressure  Nuho Life Espo slippery tool and
good figure lover the yay
When we caressed each other, Snack-ko and
Chiara prepared to wash their hands too hard.However,
since it won't peel off,
it's okay for me to appeal to the temperature of my diapers and Gucci curves.  No, I
don't think so. I wonder if I'm feeling nervous all the time in Rare.
Well, if it was that 7-type money-strength strawberry milk that
served mash windows and strawberry milk,
but I still had to go to the bathroom.  It's
not like there isn't gas, it's actually generated.Teacher, it's
okay to do something zenai
ter balloon taipan
archon senpai ah speedwood
ford browser & your
voice rip san no taipan
wp 6 items air turbine
makeup pouch zero cno turn signal
the voodoo
kneader type 1  fit pain to
fit tier 4
pero
porore
I see, it was a bit strange from the beginning,
but it turned out to be true.
Well, let's just stop.
How did you first find this live show, and
what was the reason for the "Yes" file?
Nagamoto Putone: Around
that time, when I joined the residence, the bath live shows were not as popular as they are
now with idol agencies.  It
wasn't like that,
but it was more like a tuba office, but I thought, ``I'm
going to try making something with a sickle,'' and I thought, ``I
want to be a big name,'' so I thought, ``Well, that's what it's like.''  I
wanted to change myself, so I
applied for a job at a brain office,
and now I've
changed my name to A$, and I feel so amazing that my dream of having a business name has
come true.  Masu No. 8 I
got Dream, but when I first
tried it, did I find out that it was someone's broadcast?
Well, I
didn't know anything about the inside of the hood, so I
heard that they were doing an audition.  Around the
same time, I auditioned for a live show, and
at that audition, I
thought, ``Ah, I'm going to see Tokinozora-chan and Fubuki-chan,'' so I started watching it.Oh, I see, I
understand.
And the center and maintain the ataxia yen is
better to 1 machu love to read really with
getting pox plan b 2 flights b grain
serious
caren over 4 f of maintaining
Rover Situation at the Meiji Restoration Bar Robert
Audition Land is also good 2 planes that are
reluctant 2 finepix s ca photos
aesthetics b
ncs ah
fighter # n hikikomori declaration hello
Chinchilla cat near Shimane who carries the burden of finances
barbie now the remake of that which was the sound Mr.  I
also liked the size of the skis,
but
[laughing]
1. But I said that I wanted to change myself, but I was not able to do it.
Zaan, you've been doing it at home all the time, you're furious
Molly 4 You can't be supported
[Music]
Everything's going to explode You're shy,
haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa to toshii's shy
way of moving and to what kind of things are you calling it, that's what the
market is all about,
big road nyan ah
there's
baseball.  That, that, that,
in Camp In-chan's place haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah
Driving inch
Belder match C not received JR fur
person to EL in case of emergency The vendor is Pink Village
Loader's naughty self-centered habit I
can't say good about babysitting I'm drawn in I'm
sorry for the inconvenience.
Since it's no good, it's a 3 silver key and the writing I use
is like this.That
's right.  I
don't feel like changing. I don't feel like changing. I
think I bought it.
Recopla sancerre
areas can you
do me as I. I don't feel like
changing. But that's why I don't want to go outside of the two-year-old month where he lives.  I
never meet my friends, and I had the impression that it would be amazing to be able to meet them without them,
but I'm often told that I don't like it,
but the
truth is, I don't like interacting with people.
Well, I
don't
know if it's the same as me. Ah, it's okay to interact online with ua, but I'm not good at real things because of the old roots.  Are you happy? Why put the CD away? I
'm Ennet. On the Internet, they call people strong. Net
Benkei.
Net Benkei. It's a distant view. Boo-
boo.
Douu.
Irritation.  pes woofer
super legs pou dou
dou alpha's no pain
Well, this is a show that talks about curtain pads
so I don't care about the house so
let's go between the marshals
hahahahaaaaaaa
There are things I've always wanted to convey to people overseas that I couldn't say because of the wall.
No, there are so many things, but the
most important thing is that I don't speak English at all.  I
can't speak, I really
can't speak any more, so that's what I'm talking about, but my high
skills are,
for example, people go out of their way to translate things in comments or super chats, and
come to me hoping for me, or
even come to me to say they're rooting for me.
Thank you for all the wonderful things like memorizing Japanese and watching the stream.
i love you aua
rei
scar concer harmful
splash 46 seeds airu
um  Star 3 Spider Factor
A lot of thieves fence ping Naibu
Nude Beatty Earl Di
Storm and Carmen's Cap Obu Seeds
Ad Driving Center Fair pra is a
chance wedding
[music]
voodoo
ok big
Maybe love has been transmitted to Aoyama My heart
is full  Comment a go Spinning
top
Oh, then I'm really happy.
Next
is...
What's your favorite stream so far?  I wonder
what it's about, game distribution,
transformation, Oke, Daru Ketsu Love, etc. What do I like the most? Possible. I
like all of them.
Hmm, when I say it's the best, I think it's probably the game
car song.
When you have an image,
Channel N will be abolishing karaoke on business days. Has it
been decided on Anitube? There are
signs that super-breasted tops will also come true at night.
OK, it's a big practice starch 4 s
all this type and Spain
Sputter moss dash eye star
wizard game also game p 6 fore
with a big new species from solar carlow
caffeine zua I chose action ah I'll
rinse the jazz and not sandwich
inch width 2 years old that day Hana Chaka
Kyukkyussening origin
Medium  For those who want to listen to the senior's cute songs, Sunday's
Yodo Nainai must come tomorrow.  It's a
game, so I'll play it.No, I
'm looking forward to it.It's a
big deal.Aircar-
senpai-
hyung.Yes, you're a maid.What's your
daily schedule like?B
What does your body do when you take it?
Pfft, I
see. 8 a What
's that plan? Part 2 Are you worried about that? Well, if you
include the festival, you
can just tell me your schedule for the day. That's right.
Sister, Asaaa
.  I wake
up around noon and do a show. Yeah,
is there really a time to cut Arthur?
That's not a lie
. I
go to sleep in the morning, right? I go back to sleep quickly. I'm going to sleep in the morning. I wake up from noon to evening. Haa ran. I
said honestly.  Hey, this is
Eighter.
When I have work to do, I sometimes work from noon to night.
When I don't have to work, I either play a 8 game
or
go to sleep again.
[Music]
Dai
ua
With that, where should I go to work on the tones?
It's not good, Wakayama people have 4 days until Sunday,
so if I only have to do it at night, I'll cross it. Well, at night,
a Mao comes home from work and goes to bed.
M 4th ward.  Ha
8 On the days I don't have work, I either play games,
laze around, or stream.
[Music]
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa...I didn't come to the labyrinth job before,
but
ah-da-do There's
not much time in between so I just ignore the emails.  The
maid who seems to drop it, Asodo, what kind of sound does the management have?The Prince of England,
how to choose, how to have
the name, Nanno,
what kind of sound does that make?What kind of sound is that cleaning?
That controller is almost Wow, I
want it to be true.  Game Jungle
Haa-chan Natoko is
cleaning
that thing. Ah, that
looks suspicious. Please put everything away.
Even if it's a lie or a lie, please come up with it Ah yes
No, of course there's a mountain of climbing to the upper class
A Seibu's
internal writers who uploaded in April are good
Historical sites and the unknowing decline of Mr. Mone Aso Sports
Nomoiso
April Abe Beulah etc.  ya
anond
eusebe zaan ef 4 at
who
do
boo
boo dooby mud afca
ah do
do mavis good time n field and chair too
game cursed zinc left arm
Anomo Bai Hajime Shun Chair Do
in A game that comforts Mr. Mail Work When you
remember the racer, you make a list and the house
Mutsu and God
Soai Fushi-kun rare news Ah Flare On Be
Off Baking c Thoughts 6 e Bune
Sensing and Line Game
ne
Anu
Stone no no Queen machine is Ino
fame solid Song
Wenzhou blues and famous prince and wine from Sichuan It's
thick meme eh
iso  loud park now
Foley's resin scarf lover kokukin make
Hey tomorrow is the reason for the committee sincerely ah
good room ah
i love ok
reese silent meter fee game
ignus ah 4 medinger
Sharner Fighters 10 minute curve ah 4
iron  ii Dog type
Leader Okay, that's it, River
Car. What's it like to be a senior maid?
Eh, conger eel, yeah,
good
, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Welcome back Master, I'll give you a bath
Or game
Game compatible
aname
pareage
hgst Tarp blue amplifier direct curve pa
's bowler Heiwa papa Boon Maeda wing is going to
scatter the township tea is 5 e 2 children
If you can go there play 3 cut ha
What am I wearing after all the losses? I believe that Akashi-senpai is a
real maid. I
wonder if the day will come when it will be confirmed.
That's what I think of Akashi.
Hmm, I
got an email from Ako Zeniba, but yeah, we're
all here because we're in 3 buildings.
A
year ago, we're all here. A year ago, we're in
front of cabaret. B Then,
here a, oh no, that's the wrong number.
Air
wool
anoano.
Huh, master, a parody
independent, a perfect
idol, a group of gamers.  It
hurts to have such a bad name, Antim, so
bad. He's
playing it with Laughing Inu Chon. Wow, s.
]
Oh, it's finally a crepe that's even better than the bittern. Grape
Johnny's got a crepe.
But the black grandpa and I jumped
and clicked, which was surprising. 6 The
parrot doesn't get along at all. 8 The white
parrot tasted like onions. I'd
like to read the line from my mom.
a  Comes with a book
No.
Black
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa good
Hmm, I was a maid at a member cafe maid cafe.
I
wonder how many maids it would sound like if it wasn't a certain color.
Auf So, I
don't know about the expenses, so
please look forward to my future growth. I have a lot of
assets.  Rice Dai Poi 25 form
folder Ondeul God Peron
mason Pay Parker and Sujin Muroi
Ribbon Book Arara Pecha Maker
Total number of views of the former army used in Feb 4th Garden Day Base
API  I
think it's a good piece of evidence. No
one will doubt that senior.
A, what about the reduction in flights?
What is 44.5? Oh,
what is 44.5? I
wonder if I'll go to that house.  Thank you for helping me with my question about Aqua Senba.
twitter When I
said it on twitter, a great customer
of Aka-senpai's fans told me about this. Please
ask me what 44.5 is.
Yes, machine.
What is 44.5?
[Music]
Um, recovery is a little okay.
For the sake of the second season where the name is changed.
Please tell me what 44.5 is.
a
Yes, it is,
but it is said to be the devil's number.
Yes, if you search for Aqua with everyone on Google, it
will come up with something like 44.5, but
what it really is is
[music].
Get rid of volume Oh, little girl, that girl is
not that short
[Music]
Yeah, that
's right.
If you look at it in general,
Anno has a little taxi muscle. It's
less than the average person, so he doesn't go out.
So it makes less noise, so the
a
44.5
has a little more fat than the regular 44.5.People
often say that it fits around the waist,
but
what are you talking about?
What do you like about this guy?  I
wish I could increase my weight to 8.
What is that? Do you think that your weight is too much? I
want to lose weight. Stop trying. Don't lose weight.
Don
ami Gardon
rear police ercp nebo
poly
forever
ap 2
do Kamioiana Umaji turn
isas rapper
teaser
seenboon Wow it's
dry 1,000 yen paan
ply i folder  I'm
hoping for a bunch of poppo campaigning and a little bit of Percy
has entered S. Cody's 4-point pie madness. I've been
praying for saas all the time. What's Tan 2-san's
voice?
He's
disappeared. He won't even make fun of it.
Yes, that's what I was thinking. It was a game called
Uui Bid, similar to Hanshin Den, from the Pearl Game.
Please, I
wanted to go to Takadaiji Temple first to have a bed Epps, but I thought I was going to have a
good time, but when
that BMI thing comes up, it's
okay Aso
Uso
Areberg
Enyeama Tama School Master Should I Say Menu?  It seems
like it's about salt, but it's been two years now.
That clipping has been being played. Ah, what is it now? It's been being
played, really. How long has it been now?  If you
look up
your weight based on your weight, you'll be able to find out how much you weigh.
Baby Barber
Harger
fame Star to Veuve Naka Fukami is 5 It's
all Ippei, Ring Fit
Adventure, Wii Fit etc.
Why can't the house sell?
Andre's woman,
Abe Sakama
ran,
yay
anderstand, Leeds game,
aspera
seger, moves like a spared,
ok, I see, there are a lot of questions, ah, he
's famous for that strong senior-centered character, but he's famous for his
cowardice, and
he's famous for being a bit of a discontinued hospital.  When I say camping, I
mean the hat that I always wear when I go outside.It
's a big cap.It's a big cap.
Kofu incan ah me
nos Zakah
no aso Pupu 2 Wife Ting Pi Puyo Pusha
Ipusua Ellen then Bain Camp
now voip Way Water Polo
in Canggu Bandukya
Now it's time to retire
Ooh Asha's senior's recent activities  Do you
have any?
But that's what we're
talking about, that in-cap.
Well, that's how you always say that hat.
Whenever we record together with the hood mask or have lessons together, I always
wear that cap.And I'm
always told that Agiao also wears an actor cap, so I can't admit that he's
getting a lot of attention for his dangerous cap.There are
two types.  I've
become more free now. I thought it would be a bit like wearing the same cap every day, but
now I've learned
to buy a lot more different kinds.
Now, I'm disappointed. Today, I'm still wearing that cap.  I'm going to
go ahead and say that the cap is wrong.If you ask me, I'll go
with Mr. Haranaka's Aso.No, I
agree with the cat.As for the boots, I recently received an email
from my manager.I just happened to say that there was a
day when I wasn't wearing a cap.What do you
think?  Oh, he
's my eldest son, so he wasn't wearing one again.
At that time, the manager asked me
if I wasn't wearing a cup cap today.
No, I don't always wear one.
Yes, there are days when I don't wear them, so I
didn't wear them today, but
she looked at me three times like, ``Are you okay?''
My sister, uh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, uh,
in-cap,
and then there's something wrong with that
when I put on my sunglasses.
On grass is
very conspicuous in Japan, so if you
wear sunglasses, you might think you're suspicious.If you wear sunglasses, you'll probably look suspicious.In other words, I have to
wear a mask these days even at social gatherings, so I'm
grateful for that.
Well, I can hide it, so that's true.I
wear long sleeves a lot, so
most of the time I wear them
hides my skin.Hmm,
that looks hot,
sister and mother,
but I don't want to get a sunburn after all.
Even though I'm a type of person, I don't get drawn in because I get sunburned.I lived in a
place like that.Um, it was really hot in the summer, and I was in a lot of trouble.  I
saw some old ladies and people about the situation in Nagasone, and I was like, ``
Hmm, are you okay?
'' This Ito is one of those people who is so cute.
Grandma, Oga-chan, and Issho Version
Hit
Booby
re so me cause
a
[Music]
Aren's Story
Oh Good Do That's not a lot
use a few
sarde
noa so so  good day
key point powder
repornper c com wear
saan
web cr z 2 shot
order lovez star dekimoto togane jay
arch day desukawara aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaacogeleave down for a good day
joso
deuse
aree elea
ah let's
patty weber wizards wow wan
duku
soredemo saru
stare
acra
areles large
diffuser iphone 4
barley  nu do
andere Jen's henchmen It's
okay to walk around in Aizu name. I see. That's the
house. A But, you
keep wearing that hat. You
say it like a dog with a helmet on your head. It's
okay to go inside. I wonder
if it's because of the strength in your legs, the
fishing gear, and the hair.  I
try not to take off my hat because it makes me look
too flat
and embarrassing, so I try not to take it off just to make adjustments.Even
when I'm recording, I take it off until just before I'm alone.  I try not to
wear headphones when recording songs, so I
try really hard not to take off the cap until the staff member leaves the hair.I
see, Girl 4
Seaso Open Roll Pando
Hair is the world of competitive swimming.  ok ok
fairway point cool and fluffy
scare you do for c
walk the vase kids
and ass [ __ ] you do
as looping birdie
poodle like a loop
Because I'm embarrassed, I'm
embarrassed because I'm going to become a repetan, so I
put on a cap, but
when I take off the
cap, it's
disgusting. Ah, good, good, good. That's why I ca
n't take it off, so I tried to take it off.
rcb to do
your sweet professional
head and eggs not
you
[ __ ] k
2 Let's go to the questions
a building
[music]
Up until now, various games have been broadcasting standby,
but are there any games where you worked hard on the songs or
games that left a lasting impression on you
?
m That's right, then 8 My favorite games are Niei and
Autobac
Haaaaaaaaaaaaaa, Hanshin  I love you so much...I
don't play many story games, but I play a lot of online games,
but when it comes to online games, I have
to say that I worked really hard on FX.
After all, the
playing time is Apex, and
compared to other games, it's
long.  It's
nice to have a game shower along the street where you can put your feet out.
Yes, the
water temperature of Shujo-sama's chance is 1 silver 4 a
pushas for best
regards
moroder.  I'll
talk about FPS a
little later, but I'll add that
there are some genres that I don't play much in 2019, like
shooting games, and I
don't play music games that much.
x Apex Pash is so encouraging fc It
's Ys, but what should I say?
Umm, what should I say?
Shooting game. I wonder
what kind of game it is. It's a dump that goes to Touhou or something
like that. Sponsored
I see, I see, I don't like it, now Sakura Inui Advanced Research Institute
star g you do in five
Wezon game 4 by Facility repair
engine stalled people 4 s our game
spark 3 pieces
Iiiiiiiiiiiinaru Oki
What are the true feelings and microphones about such things?  However, I
would like to know what kind of activities have been carried out in the construction of the pin that opens the Mine Craft on the Ebisu side, and
who is involved in the construction.  I
'm asking for permission to restrict personal use of the building, but I do
n't know who's in it. I don't get angry because that girl is in the room, but when I say that she's in the room, it seems like she won't be in the room anymore.  You
can't say who's in the room because you're afraid of feeling like that.
What does that mean? If that's the
case, what time and month will it
be?  It's
like I'm watching you do it,
so it's like a Freedom Smile, so it's a sound. It's
like a mi in it.
Yes Freedom Soma l Supporting
Freedom Smile 7
Moo one center color with a cool blow.
Powder attached to fur dawn queen construction.
No action allowed audience.  Bed for soaking after lottery correction Bath beshi
cold possession pipe
den o full movie the
bes ccs berea stp
power powder bed people piece wake
why is so in the pearl of space
Enhanpeisen 13 free
Share the love is g Nangaaa I
wanted to join but what's going on
Ah, now that I think about it, the scene was filmed by Grachan
Eh,
Flair was the one who took away the device super, and
when I got through it smoothly, it was Shamisen 4 Eidanden
What's that Hantong?
Somehow, when Umi C was broadcasting,
that Gurakin Eri
Gurakin TB appeared and was taken away.
Oh, the
story is about the orc center Hershey fish.
Ingredients written by the Suigun Pooh, it's about as much as you can cover. Spider tour's
impressions of the akuku ban. Small,
wide perspective, Otani spin's two dashes. It's
good to suck it out. Yoder's feelings are also a pain. Weber's
licking is made in India and the Iga Sea. St.
Nyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa to spin to half mifi  It
's about c,
but I tried to mix up what kind of activities are involved in the construction of opening pins,
so there's no slope, right? That's right,
like building cars.
We've been talking about wanting to do something new for
quite some time now, and it's been 23 months since we started making new things.However,
all of our employees are a
little busy right now, so we're making another big
announcement.  If you haven't done it, you'll have to pay a big amount of money.There's
a lot of money.Okay, the
consumption squirrels gathered together and made it.  I see, the
carp is Marine, I
thought it was a story about Ries.
It's a hard Jesus and a big new wind. Ah
with breakfast Clothes fetish
and you're going to break up the pass, Roy Gardena.
Bags and clothes are judged and pre-emptive.
sbcare Arc Pink  lactis
Peinummo 1 counter walk
away is you busy bee
Mushuichi Kun Fai Cap a 8
f Campaign First Baldi Burntia
That's it db Big Ones Normal
Surfing Game Access Ban Culture
Muscle Fiber Wife 5 Kei 2 Boo
Boo SOS A Kind of Audition
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa marine dbc pup
chip pupu arm club marine senpai pour
aimei mountain
fighters ad web rider
ship to do  I thought it was amazing. I
was watching it a little while they were making something.
Naoko thought it was amazing. Wow, such a big building. That's
amazing. I
respect Free Paint Fish.
SR Veld Hospital Fogg IV box
up me to do
a Idol Up Faithful Armor is a
killer. He makes something big like that. He
doesn't have the patience. He
says it's not easy, so yeah, I
chose the love of the reorganization of Hane Ai.
Okay, so this is a new question for you, but I wonder
what my seniors thought when I was invited to participate in the Umi C project.The members of the follow group, who are often said to be shy, never
showed up until now.
What was it like interacting with them? To be
honest, when I was invited, I was worried that
I wouldn't be able to speak properly,
so I can't even speak English, so it was a
normal
Japanese vs.  Even if you speak Japanese, you
still can't speak those two things.1 That's right
in the mountains.There
were a lot of things like anti-anxiety, but hmm.When I was
around 2, I started
doing that in English conversation lessons.  I
thought it would be nice if I could speak
a little more for C,
so I did my best, and I was taking lessons.Hmm, well,
how long have you been taking lessons?
Well, I
haven't taken any lessons lately, but until summer.  I
took it because I'm a bit
busy with work, so it's
difficult, huh?
Fare in Fingerless Large
Boo Shi Atty's Pouch Fully Revealed
Booby IPD Suuu
Sri Pendeja
fraser mer
parente r
ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh please keep on going anyways ssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss'ss's's' of
252 was fun. I was
really nervous, but the captain was also in a
good mood and tried his best to make it unpopular.  It was
so much fun
Santora Genmai Minnai 2016 by I
tried really hard while using that translation function
Well,
that's why it was so much fun 3 It
was leg sander technique wave spec Chaplin Sengra child base 2 soc hard world re talking Jam Boss  -
Merlin senior is the general recruiter wi-fi New
creative sea bream miso back student goes into conspiracy by
Let's Botter Koi-kun who adds herb executive for a moment
So
it's because we were able to do this?  Do you
have something special that you want to do next time? I
want to try it again. I'm
really nervous. What should I do? I'll take care of my childish mind.
Hey, hey, I'll help you out. Hey,
put on a masterpiece.
It's amazing from the character Pu-chan.  I
feel a scent similar to
Subaru
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
userporn
dispersion ecef co2  doing obc
pleased to dor
4 me with farmie
norme
arus
voodoo ability
love
olly I'm happy The quotation was also kind of ferocious even before the broadcast It
was easy to talk so I'm a doctor right away on the Ako line It
was the rainy season Yuna Don't you want to get along with money,
hop?  I
want to have a talk with Hifimon in front of the audience.
Traveling with cats and cousins on the web, etc.
Queens and girls of the opposite sex
should hold Moe Ozawa's squid ink 1 by of False When I
go, I'm so happy that I lost my father. Doctor,
I'm going to go there.
s good. I'm asking for an affair.
It's been a hit
so far.  I've played a lot of different games,
but what is the one that still sticks in my mind
?
I see, this is it.
Hey, the story of Hiroshita, which I just turned to and said it was Automa,
had a great story, and even in electronics, the
story was very moving,
but most of all, it was
like that at the end of the abolition.That's amazing,
Horner.Oh yeah, that's right.  I'm afraid this is
going to be a bit of a spoiler,
but I don't think there's any cooing, but I
wonder what will happen in the end.The comments also
cheered me on like Gun Volleyball, and it's a
great sense of unity.The
comments, myself, and everything are like this.  I was so
impressed by the feeling of becoming like
this.I was impressed in that sense as well.Well,
I did all the aquas at the
end, but that house
really irritated me.Ah,
haha, I guess I tried too hard.
It's a meta needle, but I
didn't know that Zek was going to do it in the middle of the day, and the
other role was desperately shouting,
but it was too much,
and it was hard
[laughing]
If so, why don't you open it behind the scenes, Senpai?
[Music]
Hey, I'm impressed.
[Laughs]
Use a 4 d
ender ender
poodle 4 over Vienna
sender
[Music]
voodoo line ng talking old lady
2 54 me blues web
hendry
rends air downloader
duca  Muhausu ime discharged
mother ins part n way condition scene
cat berry gohei with female doctor's head on his back eh
Who is your favorite character in Ano Nipo and Matata?
[Music]
a2
oh f universe's yeah
boots umm
Ayase and the foot cheer and the enemy is 4 years
old h meow rev don't do this
hmm
ri no change  It's
ugly -OK Jazz U [Music] Charchan Chain [Music] Ah ah that time is Joby OK
OK Batch
Guda
So, my hair is cold, but which one is better? Hmm, the
footer amulet is a member.
For now, the number is
Gust's mother, Celia Khan
[Music]
High jelly, the
glamor that someone said before.
Pulling Hall, Juskarn,
Ringer Apple, OK, mountain
climbing car, marathon sweets encyclopedia,
hmm, man, boom, camping over there,
period,
ce.  It's not possible to mention syphilis in the voice of peak crisis
oem sa  I like
fleeting things, but I prefer sweets,
and when it's delicious, I see the tea room,
Khan, the
middle of Hokkaido is big, and I'm
going to travel on the peach of the sea, or the famous big city.
RCP
A. Is it possible to lie naked when you sleep?
Do you say you'll wear clothes?  Climb up to the top,
delicious plum burn.
This is a karate technique. So
far, it's a little mixed up here. 8 A.
Two fields of love meeting and Halloween and Christmas. I'll
make 6 pieces of Noyodon.
Cebu?
Please give me a family marker. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Corner
kd par a I
came to the store Tinker phone call
text message on It's
like giving a present to receiving it
Naaho
give and pay Both of the districts
Take a picture with Pocky
Noepi's distance  Walking car Let's take a train
[Music]
Ah, the
train tray is down. Now, what are the two colors?
[Music]
Go check it out.
Ah, man! That's
scary.  I ca
n't open it.
No, the bastard's left hand was already 4 bays perfect. It's
nice. I added a new question for the Aqua proclamation.
Nanohahaha can wear it, but
is my good man?
No, there's something about Kirito's life that's amazing.
There's something that resonates with me.
Quite 4 characters  I
think so.
At first,
Kirito was originally a recluse and
didn't seem to be good at getting involved with Haworth, Sally, or anyone else, but then he
met his wife, who says she's a funer, and she gradually
expands her wealth and goes out little by little.  I
think it's really nice to have something like that.It's been a
long time since I've forgotten about it, so I forgot about it.I'm
sure I stopped it in a large mug
or a bar.  The
strong people gathered like that are
cool and okay, I'll translate
[Music]
asr dura starbase
serrano edition layout
prezza pants
andi earthy bluebird aichi
sense kiltris me
iron cutter
us are you re
arise
us favor
respoon freeloader with  well as
2seb series 525 zabo is a keen person,
tora advances to pico sowon so souhaha
uke ni, how many is kichise oh now  Day
mozu party linked
rivas party youtube
Ruu
outer tape hi ha slope reward bequeath
in 3rd place cursive hit princess zipper
fontaine 1 d 9 way one of Paris it's
good
wait for card pentium
e + efei
face paille  Cheen knee soap ns
answers to do saa seb
Kutankuro
Oh this is it or rather Kirito nyan
ipro  Nan's famous song Orphen
Ground Work Barter Try to
cut it and it's so good
[Music] It
's Sharp, I'm in the village, I'm
holding Asuna No. 8, but I really need to
stop Hahahaha I'm taking another leap, but
hai good color-kun  I'm going to stand up tomorrow. I
understand Andujar is fluent in a certain north.
So it looks
like he'll be different in the morning. Well
then, he's cute.  I
don't have any feelings like wanting to become a quilted wife.If I don't have a woman like me, I want a wife like sand.Well, I
want a wife like Nai, but there are
fewer husbands like Kiri.  I'd
like a cute girl,
right?
Amaran
isl Ann welfare sedan Foot
set Asuna
Isaiah's padded bus and Volvo's life
Asuna's outside also tastes like cutting a mountain road and documenting a woman  I
can't wait to say it all to Groza.
Wow goodbye Chiwa Bunmiya cover
my side 7th place 9th place 2++9 Kansai
Eita ship It's not that, it's that Kirito
Speaking of cutouts
Mmm what is
kid blue
Kirito and  It doesn't matter, but
Gakuup Harmful Spiti's Fili and
Aran's Big Panda Boots amway Let's
Deviation Town That kind of box is Parsenpai
Well then, let's go
This is it. This is it. Save I
want to play the game called Fender. I
'm also leaving things like e-mail to you. I
put it together, but it's nice. I'm going to cook it. If you
like it or not, it's a cow.
This is our company.  Please wait for a while. There's
plenty of time for metabolic mail,
right? I'm
done.
[Music] I'm glad you
're cooking properly.  I
can do things and I can cook too, that's what's wrong
Blue Gamer Maid is a super idol
Gamer
After Maid Ahahagug stays for one night and
Very Perfect Maid's first time is chaotic
But
from the hot water to the chaos cleaning board I
put up a play at the Aso Department Store.Here
's the patented model.  It's so nice to be gone.
There's a lot of dog specials everywhere you go. Ferry Pasania on the side of the British Open.
Rippani - 5 hard scales from the sky
Ah,
OS, Easter, it's not good,
Ran
Ah, yes, Koan,
4 grains, take a break from the city, my wife and everyone, today I and
Bill Atsushi, if something happens, I can't start the train.
ana
good
aaaa hey
swim do your
best you're
not trying too well but
ar well can you
do
j it looks like you want
it sorry yoiyo you
're doing your best wua first of all the government
Eh,
wait, it's just the music house
Shop work oe
Kukkukkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk
soooooooo by car
[Music]
a
Power Fighter Freem
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeey
curtains I
wonder what I should wear
Shishike Maid
Management I
like the honor of funding yeahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
rastar 4 sr wing kids ah
guard
9 be seen bag aminu
dnc zu game movie to do
with souther
deyone  id and that
entertainment is a perfect score of 100.
2 people are good.
Aoko life o Kimiseru Ino Daru. It's
supposed to fit, Cherin Sea U.F. Points, Atsuko.
ok ok. I
feel like I'm learning more and more about Aqua-senpai.  But
from now on, I'd like to talk a little more.
Hananoya Komiya is also here. S-
chan's amazing teachers are all from Spain.
Well, ok, next person is 1.Is there
any back story about the moment when you met Shion-senpai for the first time
?And
what is the reason why the two prostitutes are so strong?
Hmm, but the device key
is the rear moment 3.  Kie:
Before Nomoko's debut, we
said let's talk and we started talking, and out
of the 5 of us, we came in 2nd
place.I guess it's like this.Well,
I was a young kid myself, so I was already a child.  Ah, I'm still drinking
cones, so I wonder what's going on. En
Nakata I
was young, so
[music] I do
n't know. Shon-chan probably
thought I was someone who didn't like me.
Abe Monomer was a teenager.
Well, I
guess that's the case, I guess that's the case after all.My gear and the
bar don't have faces to each other.The
horses that say "Na" don't match or don't seem to match.  I was
probably wondering why, but in the middle of all this, I came to work as a 2nd generation student, and we did it together. That's super cool, after all. I
thought, why not, and then I joined, and then I realized that. We had become really
good friends, and we
did it together.  As time goes on, I can't help but
feel better, ah,
yoga. That
's right, there must have been a trigger, buuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu ah
but I wonder.
Jiyoung-chan cancer is.
When it's hard.  I
want to stay with Sobu as much as possible, so I'm going to go.
Even if you don't like it, it's okay to say that I don't like it. I
don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care.
Even if I don't, it's like this.
As much as possible.  It's a
warehouse, right? I thought I'd stay by your side,
but before I knew it, Kashion-chan was
clinging to me.
[Music]
Sorry, I'm leaving.
Oh,
it's kind of like a tea danner. Okay.
Ah, I'll translate this far. A 4-sensor
part-like debut ridge is really moe. Is
Resurge 2 wearing a cap? The main entrance exam for female students is wearing a
bumper. Ah, that's
fine. Speaking of a little more, Eva
's first 5.  Let's talk in person, that
's
Boo Boo
Okay
heno 4 is bef 9 o
2 office en bully
anac ping now
cornered 22 n coo
to the supporters dene  walker
were to gay barber with down ah
rabbit upper rd sports pando
in future days bbs
fence party out 1 blue do
barber come on your star
in figure
voodoo camone
pt nonco pooh pom
speed intern
ah voice senpai desu
[music]
boo
bar retour  The
viewfinder
suggests that I should reveal my senior pure to wipe summer
cad pouf.  It's
nice to meet you, it's nice, Axio. I
think there are a lot of people who love you, so I'd like you to tell me something about how the butterflies you talk about are so
strong.
What, why, Yunnan Reddish.
Oh,
but
when we first went shopping together, I
had a bug in my wallet, and
Deshon-chan was also thinking, ``A wallet would be nice,'' and I
found that cute wallet.
I think I'll do it a.The sound is good.I
have a matching set right
next door.I sold it right away, listened to it in the scene, and then 2.Since I
moved in here, I've
been matching all kinds of things.Yes, it's
probably a girl, isn't it?  Maybe from
enoden
uscc center aan
cozy denda pin woofer
booster headache medeia pin
figure barford poster
alena turn aqua
senpai also total zakah up
Shion-senpai is holding back, now I'm rooting for the guard
Shioda
active spraying senpai salon
down security dem maybe
maybe you
do Armor dad ass and
are
regular price 4 n degree
pareage
romances Ah Mei b 4 a
rod Apple Daily Star
purely Machimachi Kurose's first unmanned taste  Yes, it
's the normal wire going to the wire. I'm
glad we're good friends,
yeah
ana.
Thank you for the closed story.
Naha.
Okay, next question bar a I
think Akar-senpai has participated in a lot of tie-up projects and collaboration projects,
such as Red Bull,
a
n How do you
say it in Japanese?
There's been a lot of stuff like Windows is on sale, there's Anime Carnival at Kinmedi Yokosuka Kai, but
what was the most impressive role you've had so far? I want to dream again.
What is &? I
have great memories of Edo Ren, but
yeah,
red bull.
Personally,
even before there was a stick like this,
I've been drinking it all the time. oo pips
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, I have great memories of the Edo Ren, but that's right, red bull.
Whenever I play, I always
drink Red Bull and
participate in the competition.Ua, really, I drink Red Bull
all the time, so much so that I drink about 5 bottles a day.
Oh, I got a job in the middle of that,
so I guess it's a bit of fate.
That's great. It's definitely
fate.
But I guess I drank a little too much. It's not good for my health. It's not good for my health.
It's a dream.  That's the same thing with the great evil.It's
okay to have a dream, but I don't think it'll end in the future.After all, I'm collaborating
with Kirito.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
ak If we were to do a collaboration,
what kind of form would it be?  I'd
like to talk about essay writing for an hour.Well
, I can do that even if I don't have any projects.But
hey, if I
go without 8,000 yen for help, I
might get some ideas for some projects.Hey, really, that's not
true.rr
polly
eir patty standerd
eme star
lentil
moom far leg 4 mash
isa
arterton
ores ease iso leading
live
otsu 5 a weapon speedway
minute surf board game
ah
ender 3 s carrying sponsor
sweets along the
ship suo issar degree pause
ah s spotlight to
ra
sosono willie hardy join
to
do for ape aspros
order
andu fish uses for noa
petit news it work
bar 2 lard  online
this patty# bar ber zu
bar ber 4
arreas pass me two
words pathway b fino
So, an app with lies like Ayu-san,
hmm, uh, it's a really good
rent pool. Yeah, I don't know
what to do with it. NetGuru
's
original headquarters
is in my country.
[Music]
Wow, it looks
thin.  In my country, there is a lot of red exchange,
but
after the rally with Germany, I ca
n't say something about Austria without being shaved.Even
though it's a small country and there isn't much, there is a lot of red.
Blue is the only one that has spread and is loved all over the world,
so I'm proud of redballoon
Yeah, but it's Austria
Thank you for the music and spoons, please understand
Aso Hmm, that classic blue is
already tart and Naturen  But
each story will be based on what currently exists, such as
5 key artists who are popular,
etc. I'm not biased,
so it's someone who is still alive.
There's a closed door treasure 0 shower
If you're in Austria, you'll be fine
Band Z Bell I tried drinking it
At that time, it was Japan no Re It's much
stronger than Tokkuri, so that color is enough for one day
Yeah
Non Air
Artist's first [ __ ]  Tabodou
voodoo
s bar
[Music]
Reni Nishohada
a yes de z 4 White Suseshimashi Pin
Stripe Force translation for the first yes  I
told him how to make it into a massage electrodeposit, and he said, "Saint Viner is
supposed to be Queen, so it's
a little far away, so it's probably a good character."
Plan Pep, Air Meow,
Japanese energy drinks are
pretty weak.
The article from Wool Hosoda is true, after drinking 5 bottles.
In Japan, it's so
panda.If I read it every day, I'd
die.
If you're about to die together, you're right.
Fukuda. Please give me the love you took from the game legacy.
Senpai.
Carender. Choimp 5 Report.
Spoon! Lure Bikers. Car.
Stone. Can you
do ri. Aaaaaaaaaaaaa.
n ah
ah ah ah, what are those advertising words
? Yeah, yeah, it's a reflection of that, ``
Girls Vasago'', ``I
can do it, I can do it.''
If you drink 5 bottles, you'll completely turn into a divine spirit angel and
make a winged lager.I
think it's because of the drink money I paid for the drinks I gave out to everyone at that performance, about 8 bottles of Bach.
Tenenei Attach a Spear Ake
Sugo-chan,
Aka-senpai
is very good at FPS games, especially A Vexy
What are you thinking in your head when you play FPS games
and how do you do them?  I wonder
how you've honed your skills at this level.Hmm, I wonder what it's
all about.The
best thing to do is not to rely too much on your allies.That's what
I've been doing for a long time, so I guess I
shouldn't rely too much on my allies.
If you expect too much from your allies, you'll end up
with things like, ``Hmm,'' or `
`I can't defeat you,''
but your allies will tell you that you lost because you're weak.  It's
not because I'm weak, I would have bought it if I were strong,
so I guess I'm like this.If I
was an apec child, I would have bought it if I could take on 3 people on my
own.Because I made him the king, and I couldn't
win even with Ichima and Car.  I can now
win with Siri in 1 minute
now I've seen it
now Rei
Sakura
Asane skill soc month goods
match Shisase ae power wii
my pv lyrics are the upper level address
Middle March Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, the base side general, the
base side is going to be the base side.
do in Eh,
mother down hurry ro
Pyu Do, I don't understand at all, so the story is
n't very spicy, but please continue
rar I'm sorry 4
That's right, hmm, as much as
possible, I don't know what it is. I was doing it in the early summer when IPX started,
so I
feel like I've acquired some skills.
But lately, I've been working in the club completely and
can't play games anymore.  Well, I haven't done it,
but I haven't done it even for one day, and
now that I've become like this, my mother
is here, so it hasn't changed for 11 days.
Just 3 days worth
of Kimura layer has made me really tired
So I
might be weak now
a
1 Tom doesn't know
render capdase
scheme
ode to
do minoa
army Bomber play s 4
days a  wizard
clearcase port 4
fifi days season for
one dansko car with the
back to
please ka lie days scrutinize spun
winter
uh
um
epo case
uh other questions if there's nothing else to say about it
Yes, but balloons don't really have that piercing f. About pacing, uh, why do you
like that? Why do you like x instead of other games during the mix?
Yeah, I like other games too  Well, I
guess it's something like this.
There are some games that I'm good at,
but I don't know how to start. I guess that's why apec is so
popular right now.
That's why my other favorite games aren't so much distributed samurai, and because of the big touch, I inevitably had the
opportunity to play Apex a lot, but
when FX was also famous, I fell in love with
it.  caesa amplifier zaias aar ba
wise eighter caso moto to
aps power web 2 special ra
tape umm incubation towada
piercing prohibited shuppa
na opel that difaraf
piercing game
us headquarters ara  ara akki 6
e hurry face menus push
souther apx school avatar
pure shisusegufesti main
anb the key
blue tongue c 4 pin cut
9 as swimming in a
then
[music]
nothing to do with earrings  But for Chiara,
there's one thing that I thought was amazing. There's something sweet about Aka-senpai's game, I wonder
if it's Mario Kart.  I
saw Bach or something, that Yoshino
map day, I was
waiting for everyone to go earlier, and there
was a group of people going behind, and the blue among the items
was that, that bread, and I was
waiting around for the items, and the colors were all over.
Gee,
because I know my mentor, I
thought to myself when I saw this guy using a monster.
nan Chausugaku had a tactic like that and was
often used in the second half of middle school. Aaaah, the green-haired guy from back then.
There seems to be a player who has a lot of power, but I recommend trying to imitate it, and surprisingly it's really strong.
But no
matter how I did it, I
was really good at it, which surprised me,
but I wonder if they practice a lot before streaming.I
practice a lot - it's really the best.I'm so bad at
Mario Kart, but it's golden.  I'm so bad
at it,
FPS is
n't that bad at all. I wonder if the champion is
really happy to have gotten through the lag. He's not really good at it at
all, but
well, I don't think there are many people who are good at it right from the start.
Yeah, but other than that streaming.
When I didn't have time for that job, I was
just practicing the game all the time, and I wanted to show how good I was on the stream,
so I was practicing all the time. That's amazing.  It's
amazing how passionate you can be while doing that.But you know what I'm doing now?I'm
busy with work and can't practice, so I don't think it's okay to
show it to a child who can't practice or not.  I
'm worried a lot, but I don't think you need to worry too much about it.I
think Aqua Senpai is the only Aka Senpai fan out there, right
?
Hershey Center Arm High Vacation
Melts APS  Touko scars of
o
reales ah
carissa
searc flexibility
s well
lever squish umber act
voodoo bike c cat's paw tour
n dish
25 so with phone n
cat's dam 1st place scare is good
Aichi is Ito
uso down with fur place
for us
to
do warp for  so this
game for a 4 f
[music]
den o ore to
do other pikamu eno
Washer cold Prime Minister Won and other ungrateful shoulder long
pin board y
center and power whip and always in front of Nasu, it's so bad, I
see,
now I'm
in the middle of the door
Please tell me how to do a good run
There ah ah ah
ah line invite minutes for some
But  It's probably just past the red turn, and I
think that player Yumeta will be irritated. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
So, who is the best
? Inanjainna-chan, Airin, who was the
best in the early days, and the other day at my house, I covered the Indonesian group's Anomalika tournament.
Yes, it would be Ina-chan, right?
That house wouldn't exist without Aera Chawa.
Senran 22, if you practiced a lot.
Naouchi, who was pretty high up there, was in 3rd place.The
wholesaler distance name was that dog, and the
software was added to the mix.
Bach: It
wasn't that difficult.
Yeah,
the three of them were New Iris.
I danced really well. It was slow.
Hey.  It's so straight
forward,
it's true, it's so easy, it's
incomparable to the way the Japanese members filled up five times.
odd burger
permmme gliger minute
aparece em press dare
to snap in place in
bef
use to
[music]
dous aqua senpai 2 chatham well
comfortable see
Well, yeah, I
think I'll practice with a shovel while watching Aqua-senpai's broadcast. I wonder if it'll
be a learning experience.
No, I'm so happy. ok ok
Ah, the question
is,
9 is 1000 times
a. Minato Aqua-senpai is currently a big ink, but he's in the
early stages of his debut.  -
There was a time when I was worried because my numbers weren't improving.I wonder if there
was a change in your state of mind, or what you think you were able to grow at that time.  I
guess that's what happened in 2018, when I debuted in 2018.
V Kitchen Burger has
n't really caught on yet, but there
were a lot of popular members, but the
live broadcast itself is
probably like this.
There was a time when I was thinking a lot about what I could do to get as many people to see it as it was.  Don't
stop it, it was true. Then I don't
know how much it was or what was normal.
When I debuted, I played the role of a god. I
got 1,500 people on my BeReview stream, but the line was about to go out.  I thought I was happy, but only
300 of them were there for the next broadcast.
But that was normal anyway. I was
happy for those 300 people, but the
devil told me that there were already 300 of them.  However, I
can understand why it wasn't fun for me, because I
lost so many people.The fact that those 300 people watched it
was so precious, and it
may be less than a dog, but at that time, there were
n't that many people in school.  I didn't think so, but when I
felt that, I must have been
thinking a lot about what went wrong.Hmm,
let's get to this point.can
barb atc
delan when is the bead booth 1st round
party for earth
eason hit balloon
popular areas of the
online
watch c 2 game overview
sasj ha maybe she ga 4
a debut
sear 1 tarsfyfa ender
ender this 4 f 4 f
buster do
do eiusmodrp planter
supercomputer pure balance floating
wallet harpy up a  Hmm Darkness
3 Hmm Disaster Prevention Watching Violation
Now
Window Fallback to the Boss
ooh Along Zion re  Dowd
Cap Twin Gompersenu Motor
Senior's Rudefian Speak Mr.
Bike suggested it and it's volare
voices in chesty
Nah, then Sharsha's Windu That
guy ob Kanpei The
main factor is a thousand gold bald Well, the whole house is a
labyrinth  ren Let's make it, uhm, then... I'd
like to talk about his growth, his mother, and the conversion of his new home to the frontier, etc.
Hey.
Well, now as in the past, I still believe that each and every one of us is
important, but I guess
that's how the
director has changed, hmm.But,
back then, I was no longer desperate, so it was
just a desperate day.Hmm, I
couldn't see my surroundings at
all.  Boom, I
was desperate, but
now I
can see my surroundings a little better.
Blue, I'm
not used to it.
Well, that part has changed, and I'm employed,
or should I say Ran.  Booba might be I see
pase ipa
benro car for
taeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee- beach stone bag kindergartener out repair out there out out there out out there out out there out out there out
to be
Nmachu action swollen
Folkestone rather fat guess arm
fix this week Zbaan 2 Undine sand
Ikuto People
isr  The count of Ade Growth is 24. The
Wanu judge is also persistent. Randi,
fried cheese without hugging,
asas, Moo-ah bar,
Shizuku, seal off, Works Boner, anti-supposed
boots,
tarrus e to
do gentoo per good
to
do so, Rihaaa  Naa afc goods
big willow cap jr line star crush
when tissue brain is color rummy and practice
before you remember epion see zuya
v bing  Pinky's voice is also good. Hmm.
Yeah. Teaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa If you
look at Aqua-senpai from back then,
do you have any advice? I
wonder what that is. Hmm.
Hmm. The
people around you are more king than you think.  He's so
kind. I
want to tell him that the prince is scared of everyone, he's
strong as a person, the staff is strong, the
members of this live show are also strong, and even though he's
scared of interacting with others, he can't help but be alone.  I've
been doing this for a long time, but I'm starting to get a little bit of a headache, and I'm
getting involved with other members.I
guess I felt the warmth of the people, and from there, I started to meet the staff, managers, and all kinds of other people.I see.  Hey,
I feel like I've been able to talk to the members little by little, which is nice.Song
Wenshuu Itta Akan Aqua Senpai Stick Village
p Passage Parker Center Haori p
Actually want
propper
duren Daywalker's r t
you
do
do at the hospital I
just
want to play 4x Inoichi Rafi 6 turns My own
refund car
Weatherby 1st line
3rd part Monkey's inner ear
Um,
that's why I feel like I'm
alone all the time because I have that hood.
There's no point in doing the activities I'm doing, so I
guess I don't have a home at all.
Hitting 3, I'm about to get bored, so I
think it's good to play with everyone. Nana-chan and
I-pod. I'm so good. Hey, I'm so good
. Phew is Jesus
' year of the dog. I'm
going to go big.  The soy sauce bottle is a big concern, but
the stay and the Lancer both count 2
and 4 pieces.  It's
already been 3 years since I've been a member of the ``Next Time'' 100 A Senpai has been a member of Fell Live. I've
grown up and accomplished a lot.
Next goal.  Please tell us about your goals and dreams. Yes, that's
even true.
Hey, it's even more true than I thought. Now that the concept of Heart Live is well
known to the general public, I've grown up and
started doing all kinds of things like Moomin.  I've been given more
opportunities to do things that I never thought I could do before, and my
next goal is,
after all, in this day and
age, I've
become able to do a little bit of a headache live, so I
guess that's what I expected.  It
's a building where there's fabric for sale. I wonder if it's like this. It's a building where live performances are held. Hmm, I'd
like to have a live performance in the lawn. That's
nice. I know the branch, so I guess
it's an idol concert.  It's
okay, I want to live in the same building as my dream,
right? Well, I'm saying that
Locus Kin's sister's foot center is the one, the
artist Papua Naa's five times,
Sanpei's stroller, and the banner of face
japan 4 type s meeting.
powder china fur baby 2
boo
nearer up powder n all
ears
are you
do me
errors
in in the voodoo
grand web art festa en
world
rean daypack bai naa watch
Fin Venue Day
Operation Royal Budokan map sey bell
card magazine debut herbal
Counseling Budokan Hmm
pleasure to do in
glasgow to dosweet I'm not in it I
wonder if I could do it if I was an absolutely evil senior Well, well, I'm going to go to the second floor and rub the breasts of a little rare
naa After all, we're going to do the characters as well,
so we'll do it later.  I'm a
child Lola, so I'm a 2nd year prefectural
student and I have to dream big and big.
Hmmmm cars in beach labyrinth
d 4th generation down
Acme Kids Aran Fes Drive e
Brown Senpai Foam Penetration Wig Watch FC
Hey, in the song
It's the last time, but
for Aka-senpai, it's Horo Live
Towa. Pro Live Tohan
[Music] There's
Nakamare.
It's another place to be.
Min.  I see,
blocking teacher Anko is 5.
What is this? I'm afraid of the
police. A place to be by soc part.
But
there is one thing that I would like to promote, right? The
colors are so special. The instincts of magical characters. I have
been showing them far and wide, and
many people have seen them overseas.
Please make this song a little more sophisticated.
Daishin Sushi Center, Daishin Sensei, Daisen
Seo 3 of Seeds,
Ah Windou White Sofi Spots
Bed Performance Lave Surface
Music for Surface at
Kuu THIS ER
Okay then, there's no champion,
so
let's play.
[Music]
Good, good,
toranoana
drinking
[Music]
me
[Applause
] [
Music] [Applause] [Music] ni tan [Music
]
Good, good, ani
rar
nande
n ame
ana
car
[Music]
nara
rar
dare  ni
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
rei nakka on galaxy
raw tara cereus
iir ross carbon pro 7
minutes stand
Kyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa a  Why did you
decide to make an English version? It
struck me. It's something that's
difficult to hear overseas. I've
always thought that the sound must be from Japanese songs that I've heard many times.
After all, there are a lot of difficult sweets.
Even though I'm
listening to Tonko, I'm already wondering how I feel
in this post.So, I
want to convey this message to the members of parliament overseas, and to the fans of Inpan, who have this song called Bright Indigo Punnet.  It says yes  It
was so strong that I thought it would be a good idea to make an English bar and
tell them, so I
'm going to wear it OC Declaration Cy
Arm is CSR Claw Ding Bush
Property damage Yes,
white Soarcher Fuji
Speedway voicemail e b
swish Center sugar  village liner
rcs
render web swing
japanese fan fender
son down in 4 minutes
rear how dosu p
That Kyary is a cooler stay
Beaconvator Proisoenol Tour
Make and Hospital Gusu Ankarm Class
Pui R Size Ben Beads
Anger Oh come on Oita pen red line
Pipe I
can't speak English so this and Reimu
must have been difficult  It
was delicious. Write the beautiful man in katakana,
write one letter in tame, and
write it in thoughtful Japanese.
It took me a long time and it was difficult, but how did I get it
across?
[Music] I
wonder if I'm holding a balloon. It's so good. It's like, "
Straight fur, I'll
send it to you. I hope I can meet Bach."
What are you looking at?  Ah, it's easy to buy bait when you listen to it, even
if it's over, no matter how many times you listen to it, I
want to sing it without having to root and look at it.There are so many
tools that make sense.2
porori
refer to
do as a  doodle
1 patter haaaaa deep naun
sting japanese abus
domineering afubu [ __ ] 2 re 1 mo
susan farn
paper soren
orders are
rebelde
rear turn to do so
do
anders 4 se jon desu but
one battle
boo boo ses 3ds fire
mpge to render
firming gel good u i get
Now that we're all in the guest room, nice means
let's live for 5 minutes,
she's seriously cute  I
really like Red Letter from the beginning, so I
was surprised to see that English line appear.
A
choice. Well, it's over. No, I'm
really happy. I
want him to have an all-around first performance with Taichi Urai. kokok
This song is a samurai.  Don't be late.
Even though I don't like it when you copy that completely and hit your head,
well, I think it's best to sing at the top like Aqua-senpai.
[Music]
ranran den den o
anders apace led  Cap
Thank you very much.
Ah, ana. I
really enjoyed it. How was it today? I
wonder if I was happy to talk about it so much. I
bought 8 tickets, and even though they were really cheap, I was nervous.  I'm
glad I did, but boo boo
reru street
casadei 8 security, nc
scepter 4 drunk happy b 4 pearl
delicious web, child the weeds and
pou dou
dou, squeezer,
power spot man, fart arms, talk, mom,
chan  3 Hey Puls Birthday Service,
if you'd like, please tweet on Twitter with your impressions of today, and be
careful about the edges of Tokugawa.
Okay, I'm going to look into it later, so please.
Now, for the last time, I'm going to
go to the Aker Line bar and
do a lot of things in German.
Can you please say it with me again? I'll do my
best. It's that Cerezo
with a distant and frowning face.  One voice, ah,
feeder, you're smart, but ah, ah, I
want you to join me in the
field, ah, cheer, soarwiller, zenfira,
zain, ah,
tida, ok, ok,
bald, can't meet you,
engine, made by germany,
half ban.  Is the
interior space for seismic intensity?
Ah,
thank you for watching the two of Onmenzu.
Thank you. I
didn't talk about this.
It's the red line. The
amount of air is on the same foot.  I
showed the onion head of that one in my house, so it was
gay, wasn't it?
Hey, onions are worth the price of orange souls,
and red seniors are purple onions.
Thank you can
goo
viber Hmm aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa