if you know me well you know that my
favorite Japanese food is tonu
especially hu I found this place that
serves unusually fix slices of tonkatsu
called tonkatsu mariti and went with my
manager jenma this is the one that JMA
got which is apparently more premium and
thick but it looks also really fatty to
me uh this is the one I had it's not hiu
but I still enjoyed it a lot we are by
the way not very good at this holding
food into the camera thing yet oops
but here you can see the comparison
between hers and mine mine almost looks
normal to hers but I swear it's
unusually big trust me it oh my God it's
crazy of course you get some hot soup of
misoo and if the massive amount of meat
gets your taste buts board you can add
any of these here to spice it up but I
just like to drown it in tonkatsu sauce
JMA finished it but to be honest I had
to take half of it
home