[Music]
me
this
[Music]
say
do
[Music]
foreign
so
[Music]
uh
so
[Music]
did
foreign
[Music]
do
did
[Music]
oh
hey guys hello hello
how's it hanging can you guys hear us
okay
yes
ready to start the anniversary uh
anniversary festivities
hey can you guys see us
wait where are we huh
it is kind of dark
i just touched my butt
that wasn't me i know we're standing
still
i know it seems i know what it seems
like
i hate
oh god hey listen
enough guys we need to figure out what's
going on where's amelia
is
i hear gremlins i'm building a portal
i'm gonna press the button now
hello everybody
welcome to our anniversary as you guys
know one year ago today i started my
investigation on hollow myth and today i
will conclude that investigation we will
make the case close once and for all uh
but first let's uh meet our prime
suspects
yay there they are
hey
what's up
yeah it's finally time
so i brought you guys here to the small
timeline lobby
as you can see what do you guys think
huh
sometimes i collapse in on myself but
it's kind of fun it feels interesting
this is just side effects
crying
oh there i go
i don't know it wasn't me but i think it
was uh an old ame from a long time ago
who one one day it made yago cry uh i
hear it happens pretty often oh yeah
smiling that's true
maybe he's happy
super proud of us we're here to conclude
the investigation so i hope you guys
introduce yourselves who would like to
go first
oh man um
[Music]
[Laughter]
english
[Applause]
over here
[Music]
there we go oh [\h__\h]
oh yeah
next
hi guys my name is calliope mori i'm the
first
reaper sorry i'm really excited about
this new body i'm just really really i'm
really danced about this guys i've been
waiting a long time to be small and
sometimes i get even smaller but you
have to wait and see i can't force it it
only happens oh there we go now we're
coming in now we're cooking you guys i'm
really excited about uh this and i've
been excited for a while
uh
not to say that i knew we were going to
be scared oh my god that's all right
stop it
no no i was trying to thank you
give her some room
all right good huh
[Music]
you are saying
good as the is the chat master today
instead of the dungeon
all right watch what you say
what do you guys think
no i'm inside
oh my god what's happening what's
happening where am i right here all
right so how about we all take a seat
we'll take a seat this is my chair here
here and sit here okay
all right my little seat is in my hat on
there
all right
cute girl you look cozy you gonna sit on
the floor get out of there and then she
said sit so i said it's nice that's okay
you don't have to sit in the chair
that's fine
ally you look a little you look a little
confused yeah i'm i'm extra cozy right
now
i don't really know what's going on but
you know it's cool it's just fine
that's fine oh then i'll just check okay
all right
so today i'd like to conclude the case
and uh i have a verdict to deliver uh to
you guys um so me and the small amit
council and the big honor council we
came together and we made laughs and we
came by the conclusion
i'm trying i'm trying i can't can we get
a seat belt
i'm trying it won't allow myself
i've come to the verdict that uh you
guys shall remain in surveillance for
the rest of your life under amen
what
we gonna say in this no
i can beat you up
i can beat you up you wanna you wanna
turn this into a cuff all right you guys
want to fight we can fight
all right you me come on i've been
waiting for this let's go put them up
here we go
yeah yeah
[Laughter]
we love you but you can't you can't keep
us in captivity we can't allow that well
if you guys want to have a real fight i
have your weapons but we'll have to
enter each room
as you guys can see here
oh that's true well we have a weapon
as you can see here we have each room
for uh each one of the small myths today
and uh we can go in there and get the
weapons and do some fun stuff but uh
first how about we take a tour around
the lobby what do you guys think yeah
let's go let's go
all right as you can see here we have
the big jago
yeah he i can't really tell what kind of
expression he kind of looks like deep
fried or something i don't know
oh it does look like a potato a nice
golden crispy potato a nice russian no
no he's a yukon gold potato yeah yeah
he's one of the high quality ones
or if he went to the tanning salon too
often
hold on
gotta send him to the skin doctor
and you can see he's crying so this is
our beloved yoga fountain
wow
okay
i'm gonna i'm gonna drink some tears
[Music]
next if you guys come over here
oh yes can are you callie you're good
i'm fine with having some i'm having
some trouble adjusting the
united we small here um oh that's in the
language you guys can't read because
that's the small i'm a code sorry ah
it looks like braille oh yeah it's
similar
no zooming in the hall no zooming that's
right guys be careful
you gotta follow the hey hi
i'm gonna call the police
i have recorded footage of this
up here of you guys um to commemorate uh
the new decree of lifetime surveillance
of me to you because i will forever be
your friend now that we've been together
we've made these unforgettable memories
and i will check up on you whatever
whenever no matter how many years that's
why it's surveillance
[Music]
okay so first i think we should go to
cali's room let's go check out kelly's
time
i'll follow you guys
[Music]
wait there's another cali here what's
this
here we go
it's me wait a minute
no it wasn't i didn't plan for that it's
finally flat
it was a bad situation i thought
that's not a nice thing to call people
okay that's very right
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
don't do anything weird do it please
please i'm gonna touch it or you can't
stop me
please
that's okay i got i i was in a weird
position behind you a moment ago it was
very strange i got excited and it looked
kind of suspicious please please
there's also couches in here and look oh
there's a taco
[Music]
oh we found we found cali's weapon
hey wait no ricky you got to give me
ricky the person who finds it keeps it
right
no i will beat you
[Music]
weird stuff in the back
just touching the cali cut out weird
oh got it okay hold on actually there
you go
i got it i got it i got it i got it i
got it i got the sign oh yeah she like
it yeah
come here
[Music]
oh man watch out guru i'm like i might
come and slice you where's evan
it's your turn now
while you're at the store can you bring
us back some uh props you know
hold up
[Music]
i have a
quest for you could you pick up the cali
microphone and the light sticks i forgot
to bring them
thank you
no
no it's my side
[Music]
yeah i mean for now in small world i do
oh no
that was like mine yeah maybe the pool
there's one i think the cool thing is
floating
down no okay oh because you're on the
stage
oh
thanks guys
[Music]
thank you thanks
yeah
hold on one sec
okay there we go thank you you're
welcome
i appreciate it dory
really yeah
you had the orange microphone okay
all right take some cool pictures you
guys have any poses that you want cali
to do on the stage i mean we can
commemorate them forever yeah nice idea
nice idea let me
oh a light saber fight
ooh that couldn't fall
i have the high ground
okay now we're kicking
um
[Music]
let's get some poses from cali
okay
[Applause]
with me
that's a good one
yeah
i should do some more expressions hold
on let me see uh
okay i got it of course it's me it's
your birthday you're gonna party like
where is
[Music]
oh
there's
oh my hand bonked into something
i'm exhausted
[Music]
we've only been doing this for like 20
minutes oh yeah what's the time all
right are you ready i think callie
prepared something today for us
only a song no fruit style wraps that
would have been uh something that i
would have done except we were in big
trouble and we almost i almost couldn't
join today so let's just be glad that i
can sing a song today for you guys yeah
are you guys cool with that
no freestyle wraps but that's fine
all right um let me set it up i'm happy
just camera
you know
i love you
thanks girl i appreciate it
i love you guys if you don't mind i'm
going to just take one second to reset
my time
and then grab my slide because ricky's
got to be part of the performance
if you guys want you guys just make sure
you don't get in front of the camera but
you can shake your glowsticks here like
around the ceiling um i lost my glow
stick can i go get another one oh sure
yeah we'll wait for you yeah but don't
stand right in front don't you think we
can get started i'll be right back now
we can't wait we can wait we have the
anyone
there
you doing okay kiara
yeah can i grab something or am i gonna
ruin it what you can grab that
kelly don't move okay
don't move
you betcha
[Music]
yay
is that's a good place to hold the like
can't find my mic
where'd it go
it moved out of existence
you might have dropped it into the
oblivion
let me see or are we searching for it oh
no i can't find it oh
good i'm looking and i'm like i was able
to look inside your head but there was
nothing
you were inside me
why was it empty there cause i see it
guys look above
huh huh over yonder
oh i see the microphone
how do we grab it
how'd that happen
that's weird did i just throw it yeah
[Music]
i feel bad
yeah my scythe is my new microphone kind
of i don't know it's like i like it i
will i'll try please
let's do this [\h__\h] all right let's go
out
you know can i get a count down
wait all right
let's count up what oh count up
yeah okay
get your glow sticks ready
ready all right
[Music]
all right
one
two uh-huh get ready
hey hey
party time get ready party time guys
okay here we go
grim reaper live streamer timer yeah
grim reaper live streamer time
deadbeats
kfp employees
teammates taco dacias shrimps are you
ready to go
when i showed that to me ladies
out of control
[Music]
step out to the city but you don't know
me think about it's right whitney but
they don't owe me maybe feel like going
cyclone the streets later instead of
making a treat
[Music]
just laughing just saying
it's agonizing disguising live
[Music]
oh
have a great night
[Music]
hey
i'm smoke cali huh
[Music]
thank you
when real 3d pops off someday huh
i got it i gotta run a little more often
you guys i don't know what i'm saying
move on
sorry thank you girl thank you amelia
thank you
my first
3d performance
nice beautiful all right thanks guys
as small callie what could what else
could it be
oh yeah true facts correct
i'm what crack you crack what does that
mean
i'm not hypothetically
really cracked like you're super good
like you're crazy or while you're
watching whoa i've never heard i've ever
heard that thanks for telling me girl
girl's really hip with the times yeah
she really is
she's riding on time
oh yeah
nice nice nice nice nice
did you like it
thank you i feel really proud of that i
want to do it again someday in my full
body form
[Music]
swirling who's next i want to go to
someone else yeah
let's check out inna's room inaudible
yes let's go
i grabbed my glasses
you could bring baby glow sticks those
are the most important organizations oh
yeah i want glowstones too i gotta grab
one yeah there's more i buy the
auditorium yeah okay grab mine
i brought the pink one they have the
other ones
yeah this one for you
thank you thank you kiara
it's your color yeah
[Music]
behind me
oh behind me hi
hey
[Music]
you're a mythical figure
for me oh okay sit next to me
yeah
oh it's cute
those are adorable
you guys are so cute
so cute they look cute
stop flirting you dummies oh okay let's
go too we're all ready
okay
we're going to
[Music]
turn on some air conditioning so i'm
just going to chill in the book corner
for a minute guys just a moment
yeah you know you painted this
apparently these are some paintings you
made uh in your first pass apart out
stream yeah that was so long ago yeah
yeah coincidentally
when stanley made appearance again like
oh look it's so cute
thank you
yes paint on me like uh that pokemon i
don't know what the english name is
is it sweet
smeargle
sparkle
one that goes like
oh
[Music]
okay i lost my brush
it's fine
[Music]
i should have expected
yeah there it is
i'm here i think my trackers are a
little wonky
are you in a bunk chair
jack-a-bunked
[Music]
thank you
you might choose to be muted
it's cali back speak
speak
your voice is getting lost in the void
let me know i'm back i'm
i'm here for that yeah
ooh i'm looking straight
i don't have a fancy performance but i
haven't broken her okay your art is here
that's good
you're beautiful swapped your ankles
right now
look at your butt don't look don't look
ass
don't worry about it
all right
i'm not okay
why am i like this you're always like
but yeah we're good
you're not you're always okay oh
i love you
feel great
you're lying to me oh don't you lie to
oh no my me is i'm running i'm getting
kind of hungry i think some chicken
would be good for your lunch
chicken chicken chicken
well we of course only have vegan
chicken but we can go to caffeine
[Music]
wait wait wait did you see the big comfy
chair
can you sit there oh i want to sit down
in your comfy room you know my oh it's
so pretty yes
i think something's wrong ah
okay there we go oh
do you need a roommate uh
i would like to move in how much is the
rent
uh three three four oh no lunch
you can cook for you if you want oh
there you go um
[Music]
i think i'm teleporting where am i i
think i'm back
hi
okay
[Music]
yeah we're gonna
party big time party party let's go
[Music]
it was really it was really really hot
in all these rooms so how about we like
cool off with some
in a park how about that oh nice
[Music]
oh
oh it's so bright in here
look at the great outdoors
yeah yeah i'll give you that one
two chicken
[Music]
do you want one is there enough for me
too
yeah well you only only you can only
have it if you can pay for it with a hug
oh
okay
we come over here
oh oh hell yeah
you you
[Music]
they
so wait i don't actually have a
stage so i'll just stand like in front
of the statue yeah oh
let's see here
okay
[Music]
basically the same as uh as a glow stick
right it's the same thing
why do i lose everything it just
disappeared ah it's there
and this one here yeah oh my god how did
it fly
all the way here is this mine
you can just use it whatever sure i feel
like yeah
mistake
okay
wait dang it well i want to jump on the
ground
yeah i'll do it i'll do my best shake
those hips
thanks you too
all right
yeah you have something prepared for us
right
yes
all right wow yes i have my most recent
single that i released on my birthday
james box
and what's got um vibe microphone
version it is
you want to count us down
aye
okay one
two
three
four yeah
yeah
[Music]
yes
just take
[Music]
don't forget what i said
and get out of your head life is
[Music]
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it everybody's gonna
know you they'll say it's like
[Music]
[Applause]
that's right
[Music]
is
ladies
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
but no a phoenix cannot have a heat
stroke i'm just i'm just making the heat
feel better about itself but what do you
think about these beautiful alps in the
background just like you usually see
them in australia right hmm yeah in
australia yes it's free yeah
we're in australia
oh that's cool and they had a cave at
the main branch here and in that house
over there and mozart from australia oh
lived in right that house that blue one
yeah unbelievable right wow historical
there
and then well of course his favorite
place to grab food
was in that kfb over there oh amazing
right
he was here
oh wait where's the door
to kfb
uh
it's closed yeah it's just it's closed
right now it's a holiday apparently um
for some reason that i cannot explain
all the chickens in there are dead
i don't know what happened i did you i
know nothing happened does it have
something to do with something you're
holding on your hand right now
that's not
and that's um
that's what is it then
have you been talking to me oh man i
don't even hear you sorry
i didn't hear you that's okay i fixed it
sorry about that okay
oh
nice performance thank you kiara that
was awesome
so whenever you guys need some food just
walk by kfb and you'll be served
there might be a way in but there might
not be a way out so
oh oh okay i don't know sorry i don't
like i don't like hearing that yeah
take that like the sound of that
oh
you're shoving that thing down can i buy
it
we can slice it in oh
yeah i got it i got it leave it to me
all right well next shall we head to
under the water and really cool down a
little bit yeah
it's so hot
you know all right
i lost your gloves
[Music]
guys don't forget your light sticks
okay
here thank you
where's the crowbar oh it's in the
middle of the of the lobby by the way i
see it
by the chicken
[Music]
can i take a bath in your water
oh
context
it's under me
yeah i'm talking to me yo can i take a
bath here
um
are you clean
no that's why you want to take a bath no
get out there that's what people do in
the ocean they do even worse things than
taking a bath
i know in the ocean did you did you
notice that before
yes i noticed that i can smell it i can
taste it
dude that's yucky
i'm just trying to take a bath that's it
it's one of my many senses as a shark i
can smell it a mile away if any of you
get any funny ideas let me know i'm
looking at you okay
okay okay
okay
yeah let's go google this is so good
it's good is this like underwater this
like the entrance to atlantis or
something it's almost beautiful
do you like it you see this do you like
this guess what this is what is it a
trap
you got after a miracle
[Music]
we did it
i broke the charger i
here too
um no they're currently out of town but
they should be back i don't know some of
the time
you call this a town
more than what you call a town where is
i have nothing to say about that
you also have something prepared for us
right yeah sing you a song if you
haven't yeah
[Music]
let's go
foreign
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
oh
right
[Music]
all right
no one hears you anyway
[Music]
i think so um
oh
[Music]
um
little
[Music]
grandma we had a time baby
thanks guys
[Music]
she's hungry
she's growing sharks she needs to eat it
smells good
oh no
all right
oh yes it's time okay
we have some announcements let's do it
in the lobby
announcement time
announcements yay
[Laughter]
oh a chair
yeah
lady very ladylike lady
all right
i'm so ready
ina is on the ground beautiful i'm on
the ground hi it's so cute
all right we're just going to go into a
little loading screen for one second
all right okay one moment please
i'll give you five moments
[Music]
do
hello
we're back with some announcements for
you guys sorry are you guys looking at
the screen kelly what are you doing yes
i'm just being myself
where are we we all have the script
we're reading it
all right first up uh the first
announcement we have officially decided
on the myth official logo yes
edition logo
it looks freaking sweet look at that
yeah it's like they've incorporated
everything it's really really cool
yeah thank you i think we have another a
close-up here
[Music]
yeah behind the trident yeah oh cool
my sword
wow
it's really cool okay i think this is
very edgy
eyes into our next um announcement
okay
do you guys like this logo do you think
it's super sick and would you totally
wear it in front of your friends like no
big deal and like be super subtle about
it because it's like not readily
apparently myth well too bad because we
have merchandise that has some sick art
on it as well as the logo
the art is mumbai
solani big ups to you thank you for the
beautiful art uh it's really quite
fantastic um so basically what we have
arranged for you guys for merchandise is
a hoodie a shadow play hoodie with all
of us art of all of us together um as
well as the logo all together on a
hoodie and if getting a hoodie isn't
your thing or you want something more uh
if you want to have a nice uh sip of
johnny walker blue label um or i guess
whatever drink you want to drink while
wearing your hoodie um then you can also
get a mug with each of our images on it
as well
oh the mugs look awesome
accent colors of each member's image
color is so cool yeah
yeah
the art is badass i love it we look so
like powerful and strong i mean i know
that you see us right now
don't underestimate us exactly don't
underestimate our power and then just
another look at the hoodie because i
didn't see it
yes
[Music]
i can serve my guests and say here
you're drinking out of my friend never
mind that's the understanding
i will not sing that to them
girl she was oh god
[Music]
oh
we are all like super dorky and and
comedians but the merch is like so edgy
and cool
yeah actually in that club
all right well shall we move on to our
next announcement number four
is it um
i don't know you know oh bye callie
delicious i'm here
[Music]
that smile company has decided that they
will re-release the gargour and android
sales starts at 12 jst so if you'd like
to get your hands on me one more time
good smile servers i apologize for what
may have happened
i got 10. i ordered 10 of them
[Music]
i couldn't get one
oh i'll send you one don't worry you
know i'll send you one you're my hobby
all right
and all right for the next announcement
uh well next one's kind of a chunky one
yeah
information
number four
we call our english is having a
collaboration with pixiv
not only us but you can also draw the
concept members as well and iris
what is big skip i know okay so
you might be aware of some of the uh
contests that pixiv has pixiv is like a
art uploading site gallery site if you
guys didn't know and um
basically everyone can submit uh artwork
and it'll count towards uh battle points
and you get to fight us hall live myth
as the bosses
what uh the game
it's kind of like a game but you gotta
draw you gotta draw a drone
yeah and then uh winners will get
special special prizes and there's even
gonna be uh prizes for each talent
special special special awards so
make sure you draw submit your art
defeat us in yeah
[Music]
for me personally this is the most hyped
one so listen yes everyone yeah uh
no
clear date and all that but holy myth is
very soon
having a new set of things
[Music]
[Applause]
voted for this specific theme we voted
together and then yeah we prepared a
nice outfit for you so please look
forward to them we will try our best to
show it to you in the very near future
definitely within this month so let's go
let's go
yeah
all right can't wait
five spots all right well that's it for
announcements but uh we do still have uh
another
uh
something uh another treat for you guys
so uh
stick around
i want to see your room oh yes ah room i
almost forgot okay
let's check out
the small i'm in the room yeah i'm gonna
go invade your personal space i'm going
invaders personal space i'm going watson
i'm invading personal space
i think she got frozen in time
oh the one that was sitting on your lap
in your stream yeah
oh yeah
you know what this reminds me of huh
it's a drawing reminds me a little bit
of uh near automata oh would you like
them
i did i played a little bit it was
really good i liked it but
uh you do not have to play it anymore
if you want me to kiara if you if you
force me to i'll do it for you oh
my god
[Music]
oh yeah that's true yeah
fault i didn't do this she'll come back
the knee to the desert will get her and
then the nightfall will get him oh my
god
he's fine
oh hey
over yonder
[Music]
i have to say though i hate sand it's
coarse and rough and it gets freaking
everywhere you just had to say it huh
yeah there we go now we're cooking
oh
wants to battle me
what this is a litter box
i'll bury it when i'm done
i don't have anything uh
maybe i could do pududin
okay all right i got it i gotta find it
though so you guys say just give me two
minutes all right i'll wait for you
girl
okay hold on
here we go
i've been waiting a lifetime i've been
waiting five million lifetimes let's go
eye sighs
guys
that's the magic spell it's inflicted
[Music]
oh
we'll pick this up next time where we
left off next time we'll next time
god will not be on your side it will not
be right it will not be yeah
next time
yeah it's until then uh let's chill
together how are you doing girl have any
more of that stuff you had in the bottle
the other day oh my god
the bottle
i don't know i don't know oh i think i
know what you're talking about yeah
yeah
no no but i'll pretend i i uh oh i got
it
so fast
that was quick but uh everybody will
hear me but you guys won't be able to
but you'll be able to hear the music so
okay
[Music]
okay i wish you guys could control the
camera but
what we got
it's okay here
oh okay i'm cheering for you thank you
okay
you need backup answers amelia oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah
dance oh thank you
it's for you my microphone
i waited my whole life for this all
right the music is going to start any
second for you guys
me
[Music]
hey
actually
okay you guys will have to hear me say
yes
i'm excited
you're gonna kill it as
always okay
all right did they hear us
um they can hear you guys yeah
cool
[Music]
oh yeah not yet okay hopefully this
works so we gotta test it
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
remember the words
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
thank you
oh
we're ready uh
i guess we're gonna go to the last
section yeah surprise everybody looks
like there's an echo guys
an echo oh that it should be fixed now
if
did i check the chat
i checked the chat we're a little behind
but it's okay
okay everything is double the hearing
double no we're all good everything's
gonna go
okay yeah i fixed it sorry about that
okay
all right oh i need the camera
concoction
[Music]
[Laughter]
i think there should be extra a little
extra clay
all right i'll be extra careful though
okay
i can see up your skirt when you fly
we have four left perfect
oh nice what are we looking there for no
i just i'm not looking there on purpose
i just see it when you when you fly no
my sticks and microphones yeah
yeah
all right i'll be careful to not lose it
i just want one of mine you guys can
have a yellow one if you want
i think though
is this the red one
we should put our props we should put
our oh we knew this is where's the
turret
uh oh my god
you guys are gonna die
and then i'll show you guys one second
send the cameraman
grab this all right let's go
[Music]
this is cool play
welcome welcome to our stage we can't
wait to get up there and act out like a
shakespeare or something or a little
school have a talent show
a tree
a tree where are you kiara
uh
i i'm on my way to becoming a tree oh
okay well that works something cool
avocado tree and train
wait i want to get my glow sticks what
am i doing
yeah i broke something
oh no i'm back oh there's
on the stage how smart so we know where
the middle is and all that
whoa professional
oh i'll stand here
all right
what are we going to do here chad i
wonder do you guys have any ideas
[Music]
and can we dance and sing
oh yeah yeah no problem oh my god oh
sorry i just destroyed something
oh wait let me take my mic at home
nothing
people say
i don't
like it
shut up
chat yeah you tell them beat them up
with your words how was your face callie
huh
i'm normal
[Music]
yeah
okay i broke something
behind
hold on i think i could fix that
[Music]
broke her leg
i'll fix it i'll fix it
i'll get it
over the mic
[Music]
hello
hey guys
i don't know
we are
we
are
here we go
can we just um give a big ups to emilia
for organizing all of this
[Music]
i couldn't have done this without you
you're amazing
yeah i did
i did it was a you know it's a pretty
short notice project but uh it
definitely worked out we had some uh
things we had to iron out but it was
pretty good and uh a lot of
big ups like cali says to the modeler
sea phone boy actually it's their
birthday today coincidentally so happy
birthday and they made this map for us
they made us so thank you so much for
cooperating
you guys are awesome you're awesome
you guys are great amazing oh i think i
forgot somebody i thought i had a light
stick a smile it's inside you sit back
once
you keep inside yourself
all right you know we could get a
countdown from 15 this time i need a
little bit more time okay
all right
yeah
here we go okay
yes let's do it lately our first
performance together okay wait
are you ready
hi 14.
[Music]
hey
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
is
it's not even a real song i just i just
felt like going crazy there for a second
wow
get down with your back you guys want to
do your your um most crazy moves like
your sickest moves right now
while we're waiting
[Music]
circulation
foreign
[Music]
every day
strange to me
[Music]
exactly
okay
ten eleven
twelve
[Music]
[Applause]
all right
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
hey
[Laughter]
hey hey all right get down okay okay
stop it
all right all right we're good
so
that's pretty much all we have for you
guys so if you guys have any closing
statements um is anyone callie want to
go first you go down the line
okay no problem your boy is cool with
being first that's how we began this
journey that's true that's how we'll
continue this journey basically everyone
a whole life changed my life not only
because i met so many cool deadbeats and
amazing people behind the scenes but
because i met you girls um
i don't want to get unsappy and whatever
but
this has been really fun um
and i want it to continue being fun and
i want to keep having fun moments like
this together um
i guess the main thing that i was
worried about when things weren't really
working out this morning is i'm not
going to be able to have fun with my
friends that was the number one thing
that i thought about but it ended up
being okay i really love you guys um
and i'm just really glad that we met
somehow by some string of fate i don't
really know if we would have met
otherwise and so that's what all the
tough stuff that's happened and tough
stuff that will keep happening um it's
worth it if i can keep hanging out with
you guys
thanks
[Music]
everyone and watson uh thank you so much
for this this is really incredible and
um it's like something so special and i
really appreciate all the work that you
put into making this happen i think we
all do
thanks everyone watching you guys are
you guys are pretty cool no you guys are
sick i love you thank you everyone
watching thank you you guys are great
thank you so much for supporting us
come on else go now someone else go good
up
um i've had a lot of fun today i hope
everybody else has had fun it's been
really fun
buddy like this i never thought i'd get
it to experience something like this
yeah in such a special and unique
environment like this and i don't know
it's just it's uh i'm not gonna cry i
promise i said i wasn't gonna cry i'm
gonna cry i promise i'm not gonna cry um
but yeah i can't believe it's already
been a year already and i am
i didn't have anything really prepared
to say other than i really love each and
every one of you and like callie said i
don't i don't i don't i don't know how
to uh
yeah
[Music]
just don't move your hips when we do
that thank you okay yeah you better
i love you
it's my heartburn
i'm inside your
like they're head they're just wrestling
guys okay calm down
i'm down you sillies you guys are
weirdos
[Music]
very much for putting this all together
because if it weren't for you then we
wouldn't be standing here like we are
right now as well as all the other
people that worked hard including each
and every one of you watching right now
this is a big team effort between all of
us every single person involved in this
every person watching right now every
person on the stage and everybody's hand
who helped create this sketch and
everything inside it's all thanks to you
we are here in the
because of you because of you because of
you
and i just want to say thank you and i
can't wait to see what we do next
and
we'll put it
i'll go um for me this was like this is
my dream you know i love being able to
set this up and having the resources and
the ability to do it and i want to thank
you guys to first for believing in me
because it was just so stressful to set
up kind of so
i'm glad i'm glad we could all have fun
and i'm looking forward to a future
where we can keep doing this stuff for
you guys and yeah it's really all about
you guys uh making uh it possible for us
to be able to do this so thank you thank
you thank you thank you because without
you guys none of this would be possible
and uh thank you again to the en staff
to the vr chat team the official vr chat
team you guys were gaming clutch uh for
the past like week and a half you guys
have been so so helpful thank you so
much for all your support and to our
rigger chanzo to our modeler seafoam boy
and uh yeah thank you guys i really
appreciate it and again thank you to you
guys for putting up with me and uh
letting me help you and
putting up with us right around
exactly
well thank you guys for believing in me
and letting me do this yeah everybody
you're the only one you're the only one
who can do that kind of stuff you're
you're like to me
you're like kind of like somewhat of a
leader
i think we're all a leader in our own
way like we're all we all have our own
qualities that uh you know that shine in
different circumstances
yeah
you know
going later was a bad idea because i'm
almost happy already
but this one say um
thanks everyone who made this happen um
[Music]
no i'm not
it's okay
i'll make me slither over there and give
you
[Music]
oh i know we had our ups and downs over
the year but i'm just glad i can spend
so much time on you guys
i'm just thankful that i cannot be here
today
and get all the stuff who works so hard
behind the scenes as well and making
this happen and
uh
i promise we will someday yeah make it
happen okay
[Music]
thank you for the technical support too
because i wouldn't have any good
i'm things
i'm just happy i can help someone with
the stuff i don't know much but this is
really helpful
you're always so helpful they're always
helpful always helpful yeah thank you
for everything yeah
anyways
[Music]
me
i have a lot of
feelings right now
[Music]
thank you everyone thank you for
um watching us grow
and even though i would have hoped that
at this point of time we could all be
together
but
even even when the odds are against us
we
together with our
power united we can make it work you
know we make if we can't do a pretty
um
debut in person then we just come here
together in a freaking vr room like
we're
unstoppable unstoppable
yeah
all of us together
i want you guys to do one thing
and that is just
whenever you have time in your busy
schedules whenever you feel like you
want some joy and entertainment
then come to us and we are more than
happy to give it to you because that is
our purpose
yeah let's go
until another year and then this one i
will not
i will not
just accept not having proper freedom
you will have it in this [\h__\h] next
year yeah
[Music]
i'm gonna stop being sad then
kind of zoomed out for chat but it's
pretty good
yeah
yeah let's take a picture i'm going
gonna set up the camera properly one
second okay let me i don't know what's
tears and what's sweat anymore
i mean
it's kind of soaked right now i probably
need to give it a wash
the stuff that comes out of your nose is
mixing until uh let's not talk about
that one
not yeah
enough it's not
taco bell oh
[Music]
yes
i think that's it for us of course we'll
be around for now until who knows a long
time we'll be here and thank you guys
again for a wonderful first year
everybody's worked so hard so
thank you and to everybody who helped
make this possible is really really
really really fun i can't move the
camera damn it okay
beach and yeah no we already had our
speeches
yeah okay
reach for our dreams which we still have
a lot of dreams and uh you know we gotta
achieve them our idol dreams yes
dreams all right we have a video a
special message for you guys a special
video um so you guys uh thank you again
for watching and uh yeah that's all i
can say really thank you
thank you thank you everyone i love you
ass shower now
see you guys again soon okay okay
y'all come back now y'all
[Music]
come to the shark side
ah
[Applause]
[Music]
the ancient ones are calling
i am death itself
i am timeless
hey we can both boing boing boing boing
boing i prefer not to do that in front
of the people
[Music]
it's elementary i hate it
i'm undercover so i can't use
my real accent or i'll be
bound down
i've noticed your accent waxing and
waning it has made me question your
claims of being british
i am
nervous
but
i was so cute it's only been six months
what the heck happened
and my papa says i belong
in the bottom left don't worry about
bottom left papa was joking i don't
think it will get attached to your
character oh how reassuring
i felt fine before my debut you know i
was so calm and then like
like right before the debut i was like
oh my goodness i'm gonna be streaming in
front of all these people
[Music]
oh what kind of voice should i do okay
probably should be cute
nice to meet you um
my name is clyde b murray
hey guys two quick questions uh number
one what the [\h__\h] am i looking at number
two
could
can you stop
my favorite senior
uh
[Music]
thank you so much you guys ever since
the beginning you guys have really
showed up for me oh my god
please
i told myself after
the mad father's stream that we weren't
gonna cry anymore
when people are this generous and i
shouldn't be surprised but here i am
anyway
i also heard a rumor that
uh when you go in a pool you need
floaties
i told you that
when we first met she was the very first
one to like you know that that friendly
i'm gonna make fun of you i i i don't
have a song prepared but i have a lot of
horns
i know i'm really proud of you i don't
know like oh good
since the first time that i knew you
met you i was gonna do something
really special
and so you shall be known as tentacled
sometimes they um
be gathered
in a big big project to display their
work
on
the
times squares billboard i really don't
deserve
the kindness that you guys give me
happy birthday dad happy birthday oh my
gosh you are the freaking dad
i'm really happy that we became friends
because when i first met you i wasn't
sure if like
if we could really be friends for
whatever reason but then once we met i
was surprised that we got along so well
i made you a rep okay you want you want
to hear my rap yeah please don't please
don't cry
don't fly around my room
what are you doing
what are you doing stop
come buddies
it's a pdf should i be nervous
dear guru
gargumba gargoyle shark g floaty goomba
roomba gar guru from youtube buddy
oh god
letters written by all of you
the thing is i already did give up on a
dream that i had i was pretty much done
with believing that things ever go
upwards again
but
something totally unexpected came into
my life called holy life
i spent
most of my life caring for somebody and
uh when they weren't here anymore i felt
like i lost my purpose
and so i just played a lot of games
and shared that happiness with other
people
and i hope you guys
also can carve out your own happiness
your own happy place in the world
and find your own slice of happiness you
know we didn't um
we didn't really have anyone to help us
um and i don't say that as like a a
bitter thing or anything like that
nothing could have been done about it
you know
we were the first en generation and um
it was hard
i don't know what to say
[Music]
thank you and i love you all
oh my god
oh picture
catch me when i'm not blinking i mean
you