or like stuff in there yeah wait is this
what we're supposed to say oh
yeah
[Music]
I'm gonna take the right one
yes one more set
one more
[Music]
okay and then a golden apple stack right
yeah
what is super thanks okay
it's fun I'm just uh I'm just going on a
little journey
access work uh if you like the sword is
better if you do like quick uh hips but
the ax does more damage if you do like
shorter hits I guess does that make
sense yeah it's like a clay
it's like it's a heavy Target yeah yeah
Florida's AOE attack the sword is quick
damage right there are all my junk in
these chests
yeah you guys got the food
got cookies
I want cookie
and I wonder if we want to bring like
something like scaffolding you guys
definitely want some um
I'll bring sand all right forget this
guys I gotta look at the um I have a
bucket
okay coordinates the coordinates
nothing to buy puffs up right no
your graphics card I'm just kidding
was it F3
I haven't played this game in so long
so yes
are you lost yeah Kelly yup I'm lost
um we're just the ferris wheel went to
go get nope went to go get some wood so
I could make a chest but everything
around our areas is owned so I had to
kind of go outside of the area the trees
are known I'll give you a tree a tree
I'll leave you a chest chat what are you
guys complaining about the audio
is it really that bad are you guys just
looking for something to complain about
yeah I can't well I I don't know where I
am what is the X Y oh God don't don't
hide
Phantom
what is it
someone tell me where they are
someone please tell me can someone
please tell me where they are what
please give me the coordinates please
of where we are you mean what is the
hour uh X
uh 326. okay why 79 well the Y doesn't
really matter and set minus 481 wait
minus 400.
okay
I like you I didn't hit anything uh
hello cat
yeah they're afraid of cats so they were
attacking us
oh really yeah yeah
that's how I got a lot of the membranes
for the potions
so by the way I brought I'm bringing
sand in case we want to go up to the
towers with sand instead of shooting
them and I'm bringing dirt because we
probably have to build like a bridge
from our Corridor to
uh the actual main island and what did I
say the coordinates wrong 330.
and that is x and z is minus wait sorry
it was not 400 it was what is that no no
minus 480. okay 470 something like that
how did I get this far away
I was just trying to retrace your steps
and I was like what where did you go
I mean I was walking in the darkness
sorry for yet another delay you guys I
had to control being useless at least
once so let's follow the adventures this
is basically like getting ready for the
family trip you know
[Music]
gonna get there
are we there hope you brought a diaper
all right there yeah
it's Jack what the hell are you talking
about I've been telling her the right
coordinates
Chad are you trolling
you I am correct you guys are incorrect
idiots
one of two
yeah thank you Ina thank you enough
there you see it yeah clearly yep
ouch
oh this is this is turning out to be a
bad morning this is a bad morning baby
I'm already enjoying this
yeah where's Cali
I don't know we all don't know where she
is oh wait I thought the last time you
played you were like uh doing the ferris
wheel or no oh I know I I was
um a couple minutes ago uh I went to go
make a chest
um so I went into the darkness and I
went looking for wood and I made sure to
go far away
where you like shoot it up into the air
a flare
yeah yeah the sky do you see some of our
monuments or like the do you see any
subscribers nothing I'm thinking about
just dying guys like at this point
I think the problem is that we're giving
her our base coordinate when she's all
the way in Phoenix town
[Music]
I'm up
oh uh I I just want to die guys I I
honestly I just want to die like reset
Callie
gotta find a dark darkness
oh God what is this sheep
stay away you are Kelly where are you
tell me your coordinates okay
2.99.
2.99.99 77 which doesn't matter
and then this is the one that's effing
me up that I can't see negative 692.
oh not really what
um I think I kind of know where you are
Maybe
I don't know I'll follow you I'm on my
way
I'm coming too actually I don't know
where you guys are so it's Ina if you're
already going then I'll stay yeah I'm
already on my way you're better with
coordinates and you're right sorry
come on
oh sorry let's see are you wanting to
snow or grass right now
I'm on grass
was
she couldn't have gotten far yeah
it's only one place we can go where
there's trees
pressing on this way
is somebody bringing a leash
leash
one of those like those baby ones that
strap around your chest oh yeah there's
three of them some people like to walk
their children yeah children and they're
like all over the place mommy should I
put me on one of those oh what color oh
it was like green
Tartan print plaid
okay what are the coordinates Cali all
right 305 for x and negative 692 for Z
and you have five
negative what six
I'm thinking like Cali like something
okay
like I go to Negative X
wow where did you go I have negative six
nine two I just walked into the darkness
really
just tried to go somewhere away from the
camp turned around couldn't find the
camp anymore
I'm gonna get up on a pillar
but that about figures that checks out
uh you you got lost really quickly that
might be a record that really probably
was a world record
definitely a world record yeah we saw
the difference
honestly it would not be surprised would
not be surprised if I was
okay and full sir
smell Cali it's negative 692 by the way
I'm on a tall pillar
I see it I see
um Kiara and uh because I was about to
say Kiara incusatori Kiara um
what's it kind of hard to miss a giant
stairway
yeah there is a dragon stairway right
above me too you should follow that yeah
I guess I should okay please just let me
signs of civilization
follow the moss covered rock nope I came
all the way here for this freaking wood
I will sit here and I will hit it with
my hand until I get it even though my ax
has now just broken I will hit it with
my hand because I got lost for this wood
determination
hey who was that are you guys all ready
to go I remember this
no literally holy
[Music]
to myself
foreign
useless and ugly pink
it's a stress ball
wasting arrows never hold down
just testing I need to practice
buckets
did I hit you all right I'm on my way
back I thought I hit you I guess I guess
you're back in baseball I had a ton of
buckets
sorry I have a lot of buckets oh
Elsa drinks for everyone
please at Taco Bell
you guys think we can play some of those
those Minecraft mini games have you seen
the like the Minecraft mini gaming
servers oh yeah yeah
we could mod our own I could do it
probably I found the cow it was gonna be
a lot of fun you know
where's Ina
food
[Music]
.com
we deliver everything from humans wait
cool tape Where'd I get this from
yeah
all right Kelly and here is W's
okay um
I can give you one oh it's okay I have
one I made one it's okay I went out of
my way to make one don't worry everyone
come over here to my my lab yes open up
the right chest and take some slow
falling potions
okay you'll need it I got it this time I
got it now I got it thanks for the clap
clap clap chat I appreciate it
it's been a rough morning
uh slow falling potions I think you can
take uh
five one two three four how many can we
take I'm sorry yina uh four or five I
forget oh four five okay inventory
yeah I mean I'll take the leftovers
myself so don't worry yeah okay oh you
can't yeah can I have buckets five each
five years
you can open up uh
there's seven in this chest over here
and there's like four on the outside one
okay thank you yeah
so feel free to take
okay thank you for all the preparation
you guys did this is really helpful you
guys are amazing Sasuke
wow yeah do you have any extra under
pearls on you I have one
yeah if you guys have any extras Could
you
um
because I'll bring some please rolls
just in case you know our eye breaks
before we find
okay
I have like a couple lights
I have three and the pearls
uh as for diamond armor is that in front
of Kiara's Place yeah come to my house
okay
did everyone else already take their
sets of armor that you should like take
probably two but what if we die and burn
and then they all burn but if we die
then we'll just spawn back and spawn and
then we can try to meet back up in the
yeah
wait I forgot
wait Kiara did you take the under chest
Where'd I put Thunder chest I didn't
think the end of a chin I took it from
Michaels wait wait yeah go back okay
yes I see you
it is
two two full sets of armor yes ma'am
okay anybody have any wood
one usual
okay you need more the other one in case
you die I need a shield
okay oh yeah and then on the right side
okay
how do you say shield in Japanese wait
what the hell happened to you
please take one of the diamond axes
[Music]
one of them uh maybe the the second the
first row second one oh yeah okay I'll
see I guess you can also take that 100
that someone put in but that's not you
iron sword okay
and then one of the um
one stack of arrows okay one stack of
arrows golden
no the normal ones the golden ones are
not really not really useful yes did you
take an ax as well the diamond one the
diamond one um
one more one more Bowl because you might
lose one oh okay uh-huh that's all right
which one should I take any of them ah
it doesn't matter oh as long as it
shoots it's strong all right we're blue
all right and one stack of arrows okay
[Music]
seeing some snowballs but I don't have
many uh you know didn't you also get
snowballs are you bringing them too oh
yeah I was gonna make this snowman oh I
gotta go get a shield guys
snowballs for
to shoot the towers uh like there's
Towers then you just gotta shoot the top
and the Snowballs are really good for
that I think oh okay
um
[Music]
wait Kelly did you get the gold uh you
have to think sorry one more thing the
two golden apples from the chest oh yes
ma'am I'll go ahead and do that
nice crossbow
thank you dirt in my house uh one one
helmet damn it
this resources are precious don't waste
them precious weasels oh well
you can get some water Vibes here
okay feeling better now
your arm my arm
I think I should be good all right cause
somebody more responsible want to hold
the scaffolding because I do not trust
you I certainly don't trust myself
[Music]
I believe in you that Believes In Me
should I have a pickaxe you guys
[Music]
I have okay Pokemon I don't have a cape
are you using OptiFine or maybe somebody
was saying it might be your shaders I
don't think Cali is using OptiFine so I
don't know I am
oh you are okay it must be OptiFine then
I should bring some shovels and stuff
too I forgot
it's free to dig
chant
I'm so glowy
glowing did it
everything
[Music]
their membranes come give me your brains
where are you where are they wrong kind
of membranes but
it's membrane that's like when when the
membrane wall of a cyst have you ever
seen cyst removals you have to remove
the membrane wall otherwise the cyst
will grow back oh
oh
did I hit that no I didn't just shots
absolutely yeah beautiful shots
at least put it in the corner I can't
see anything
all right so are we ready
I guess yeah we can start the car
yes everyone got their snacks you got
food snacks
yeah good all right
oh there's another uh
are we sleeping
it's horrifying yeah I guess so let's go
to sleep
[Music]
all right there's another bed over here
I think I'll have to go inside the house
can you stop that please stop please
[Music]
okay okay
sleeping through this night oh
there you go all right good morning
everyone
it's time Cali in front of your house
there's a zombie I will destroy it okay
it's very kind to me yeah there's a lot
of enemies out here oh my oh my God
are you okay oh yes yes I will just run
how much oh Ellie ate some torches
outside your house wait wait wait there
Callie okay I'm not moving where's Kelly
I'm sorry I'll destroy them right
now
oh there's no more no more explosion
waiting for you okay that was horrifying
enough come come with me quickly can you
take the end of pearls out of the chest
I have a full inventory okay not this
chest yeah
ender pearl tosser am I the you're
chosen my pictures that's what they're
called right oh thank you
I have to grab a chip I'm sorry my
stomach hurts so bad with them one chip
just enough to not hurt my stomach
I have a sausage that's supposed to be
spicy but ever since I ate those spicy
noodles nothing has ever been as spicy
oh
thank you for the sausage oh
[Music]
um
I'm guessing we're not doing okay
I'm breaking wood and well so if you if
you need to make more bets then
I have one two three four five six seven
eight beds maybe nine I don't know a lot
of them
too but yeah
normally two depends oh thank God oh the
pain is going away thank you everyone
okay everyone has checklist everyone has
armor yes everyone has weapons yes
everyone has arrows yes everyone has
slow falling potions yeah everyone has
two golden apples yeah yeah everyone has
a food some kind of food yes I have some
leftover in case everyone has uh one
chest at least
[Music]
everyone has maybe one or more but more
than one water buckets they could be I
mean I don't know if you if you were and
if all of us are that skilled I'm
probably not skilled enough but I
brought a couple of water buckets and
because if you fall down then you can
um
I think you can use that too yeah
probably I don't know okay on the floor
then you get into it at the right time I
guess
now
and I have some building material I
don't think we all need a building
material because yeah just one of us
so as long as I don't push each other
off
I'll
just bring them along whatever okay
let's go yeah let's go
[Music]
right and it'll go towards it yes yes
keep your eyes on it though because I
think you can collect it again yeah oh
yeah
how do I toss it no idea
like
what
and
I think it was that uh I mean just just
wait here let me see if it works did you
throw up or at the ground
it kind of threw like
horizontally yeah okay
uh we said chances I went the opposite
way maybe opposite way I went behind oh
there's no oh
yeah
I have 15. everyone go try videos
anymore
okay I'll go see the slit see if it
came really quick I'm just following
Europe
because I will be lost Sparkle
mark
oh you make one of those
was that not supposed to stay Polo uh
you need Blaze words yeah
our eyes as well
um we're supposed to do it I thought you
were supposed to do it in the other
first information and it's in another I
don't know I don't know I that's what I
thought I didn't know I don't know you
can do it anyway
um
okay I don't think we'll find it
doesn't
despawn in like five minutes probably is
there a radius like if we know a block
radius then we can do like a you know a
circular sweep
but
all right Chad maybe it goes the other
blocks so we can calculate from where
you know through it and then we can set
up a point but maybe maybe throw another
one it didn't go that far because it
pinged really quickly
and it has 10 to 15 blocks okay so let's
go back to the original one and then
search 10 to 15 blocks away from the
corner that you know threw it okay so
close yeah that is pretty close
I'm sure we're just missing it it could
have broken apparently
ah yeah that's true they break sometimes
right away I'll say it probably this is
probably broken
okay I'm gonna group up and throw
another one everyone
you can see which way it goes I'm coming
back to uh Cara's roof or why on the
roof roof back Arthur again roof party
ladies
oh how's it off up
oh
I I I look I looked all right
one
what what I didn't see it I lost it
again
it didn't see anything I was in third
person so I was looking and I didn't see
anything
yeah it actually literally just jumped
beer are we all using shaders somebody
says it went down
I wonder if it is a shaders thing what
the hell
no I turned off shaders
uh are we right above it
no and there's no way there's no way
then we then we would have probably like
dug into it yeah with uh Amelia's
underground Subway the cave turns way
further that way like to the left but
maybe we should dig straight down from
where you're throwing it in Kiara's
house
Kiara your house is Olivia
under construction you're forbidden to
use it from now on what the sweats
um
try dig down but
somebody says
it's not a good idea before we waste all
the pearls though should we there's no
ah all right let's dig I have one carpet
wait throw it somewhere else where would
you try throwing it okay let's try maybe
let's go tomorrow let's go into a flat
field like uh is there any place like
that yeah in my cabin
ocean
oh okay
like the flowers we'll go back to the
cabinet yeah like like behind my houses
yeah like we're gonna get a was gonna
make Atlantis but then we went to the
second stop
don't worry guys I definitely know where
my cabin is it's just not optimal don't
let your dreams be memes
and memes boys and girls is it so we
already wasted two of those and uh I
have one I think I'm happy to offer it
wait yeah
so as long as there's pearls that's all
we need
the Pearl will travel towards her house
oh yeah this is not very flat I sure
you're is this what you consider flat
Ina
uh should we go okay
no no you had to do it
surrounded by water
yeah
Maybe
uh still alive oh we're gonna we're
gonna test at her house over there we
can do that that looks flat
okay
[Music]
and you wanna ride
I would like a ride actually I have a
boat weekend
[Music]
okay
pretty flat
this cake
it's getting dark
got a Triton on it it's like I tried it
yeah this is so funny you're welcome
have you seen your cape pretty cool all
right
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait I'm not there yet oh my God
please
[Music]
okay oh who thought this was good
look towards in a shrine I guess one
person
trying to ruin
I'm gonna look around our village
oh you don't want to throw it in the
ground I thought you want to throw it
towards like Shrine like some people are
saying no of course the sky either
throws the ground like what
I am I have beds if we need to sleep
yeah ladies
yeah let's sleep first before right down
the beds slumber party ladies camping
yeah okay
okay
I'll see about your feet
but what did you say what finish
yes
what all right
oh maybe if we go maybe enough you go
really high up like on a on some blocks
like this okay
what's my easy block okay
dirt
would you like a dirt bike I'm too high
though because it will it'll be hard for
this is good I think that's good
all right I'm gonna throw it towards
three two one
oh
did you see it right here it's right
here
look so should we build the bridge then
is it underwater
wait but don't we have to keep throwing
it that way until it goes down yeah
yeah he'll go straight down and again
okay
oh there it goes It's Working
is it there no I got it should we throw
again let's do it from the toy gate it
doesn't stink yeah good idea
[Music]
what if I mess it up
okay
oh wow really far
oh bro no oh God okay maybe the last two
times just broke
that would be pretty unlucky do we have
to I mean we still have like three spare
ones and what should we do here like
should we make a bridge or should we
just go in that direction and then do it
again I feel like rich is just gonna be
wasting yeah as possibly we have other
boats because if we have the other other
boats we could just go in this direction
a little bit and then until we reach
let's go this way until we reach land
yeah who has both I got a boat who needs
a boat I don't have a boat
thank you gura
um
let me check in this chest oh yeah there
should be one more Lobby road all the
way here
um
oh
all right I'm coming
what is that oh it's a trident farm
right now
okay I'm gonna throw it again oh God
oh okay
okay keep calling the sketching gadgets
I think we can go a bit further yeah the
next one because yeah we're wasting them
do you still have enough you think it
has 12 girls 12 plus three pearls and
five plays rosin that makes like a
couple of Colors Let's go until we get
to land and then uh we can do it again
we have like a perimeter to check
this feels so cool you guys
it could be
done I'll be unlucky though I was
walking on water damn
what a Pro Gamer a man okay
I'll go until let's go there on that
Hill
imagine yeah
okay yeah
let's go dolphin
I'm the photographer
I'm taking pictures of us
beautiful
on the way to the Ender Dragon yeah
beat up the Ender Dragon where am I I'm
gonna look up epic Minecraft music
all right copyright RTA let's roll
this Minecraft playlist that I'll put on
like a 10 hour playlist while I play
okay
and everyone gets over here
we'll see hold on
oh
I'm gonna play all the nether tricks
oh yeah a good idea
oh hello sorry
I'm ready can I play that too
oh uh nether mine yeah
epic Minecraft trap no that'll give you
remixes from from other music producers
also look up yeah use the nether ones
Minecraft soundtrack all another tracks
2020. oh yeah
yeah
500 sounds trustworthy
everyone here no
Gora
oh she because she's Googling stuff hold
on I mean a little Google
oh this is scary music
it's pretty epic going in three two one
fight
oh
all right let's go further than put in a
break yeah it didn't break it fell
as
all right okay I'm going in this
direction
I have boats yes
okay good
this music is being anxiety
let's keep going for like a couple
minutes yeah how many blocks maybe like
500 blocks is there like only one or is
there like oh we're back at Water maybe
we should go to where those trees are
over there
um yeah until the tree let's go into the
tree wait I lost you girls me and Kelly
are too far away from you girls I'm not
the only one yeah
that's lost anymore
so close did you go uh oh come on I see
some names I found found you Cal you
follow me let's go to the top of the
hill oh wait where are you guys
oh I see them
uh
um
I I got one yes
all right together how do we go
wait I have someone's
bed oh yeah there you go not mine
yeah
all right let's go drive drift
oh that's it
wasn't at first
then we should go to the top of the
mountain and then
yeah yeah maybe yeah yeah
is there only one or is there multiple
welcome to the Moon
is there multiple yeah that's the one
there we go yay
there's tons okay bubbles okay so I
guess it's just the one we're closest to
uh-huh okay cool
foreign
[Music]
for everybody
can you go a little further
uh sure okay just a little
maybe like on top of the uh yeah oh yeah
I was thinking that to you we're an
unexplored Terrace
would have been good to bring a map
oh true fill in the map
we would have needed a really big map
though if he went real far
yeah that's true I want to make a
macaroon
stuff
yeah I'm gonna throw it start from here
we're on top of the round top of the
tree
what is that did something
how is that naturally possible pumpkins
all right guys
[Music]
and then we break Minecraft's number one
rule don't dig down
[Music]
um
one more time before before it gets dark
young curious
actually helps
okay where are you guys
yeah I can't I'm watching it
honestly well oh yeah oh I found you
guys okay come on pick up the Pearl or I
don't know
[Music]
on top of it
oh it's real dark sleep over time
[Music]
there's a bed over there
thank you okay
hurry the break really it is on the tree
but I thought it still hit the ground
I mean we can check hold on oh I have
your bedina oh it's right there I see it
there it is
so much for hearing it
on my bed ah
[Music]
oh yeah
okay
all right it's okay okay
oh this is nice and open I don't know
how much is loud music me too me too
okay
oh oh
[Music]
um
you do it like at the edge of this Cliff
here yeah
[Music]
mmm watermelons
oh oh
so I guess it's over here
oh there's someone stand here
oh okay and stay they put sit I can stay
[Music]
I'm really good at standing still and
not doing anything
yeah so the one thing I'm great at this
game
[Music]
I think you're on to it yeah someone
stands like somewhere here
[Music]
getting close
yes ma'am
okay it has to be like around here
probably here yeah
can I move I already moved hold on yeah
let's stick where we're amazed okay okay
how far down is it yeah I don't know
until it's pretty far down I think we're
thinking yes wow so nostalgic all right
ladies I can help oh no she's thinking
straight down
around here
you'll know that because the stones will
change it'll look like brick stone I
should probably stay with someone
I don't have a picture
I opened up a cave here there's a cave
down here
oh
I'm gonna build some stairs we can Mosey
our way down yeah good idea
and then you guys can drop yeah
we have 31. I dropped the water uh if
you guys want to jump in my hole
welcome
like uh oh but I guess it'll go through
the wall huh
I have I have no space
though then there's a there's a chance
it's okay they'll find it
okay I'm gonna stay with you because
it's all right I have no clue okay
I'm gonna start digging down again just
to see
all right
[Music]
oh there oh
okay I'll put torches outside of it
ouch oh it's gonna come along
okay
so hold on
head count wait hold on one okay
hi
whoa this is cool
and can you open the door for me yeah
yeah there we go oh there you go
okay
[Music]
it's amazing
oh wow so it's like that huh okay so
excited
this is so cool
there's like stairs
oh yeah
[Music]
is that the summer is that possible
I think so might as well also there's
there's careful there's some there's a
lot of people I don't have any more uh
torches I ran out
okay don't look at him holy yeah
okay oh
yeah
okay okay
oh
there's a library oh oh
[Music]
that's so awesome
treasure music let me put that there
there's uh it can be behind a false wall
as well I know there's like cheeky uh uh
uh joke walls
oh I'm doing Watson uh throwing away
blocks
please
that was scary
this library is so cool
yeah
we can take them yeah I've hit the
spider webs of the sword they go down
really fast
oh cool thanks oh I think I found it
nice it's a ladder to get rid of the
spawner though
oh that was that was actually Espana
that was really exploring yeah I'm gonna
borrow a torch
here I can give you some I didn't look
at you I did not look at you
I just want to say it's really scary uh
oh you did find the other way yeah
there's no eyes
wait you know what I have exactly enough
I found it
want me to go get the one I have I have
one more no I have exactly 15. oh dear
God oh my gosh okay everyone everyone
[Music]
oh my gosh okay it's almost on the
coordinates for this oh yeah
good idea
okay got it I got the screenshot it's
good let me make sure I'm absolutely
prepared chest should we put on the
chest guys just in case oh yeah ladies
yeah bed and chest
stupid door uh okay right here ouch ouch
what the hell oh
my God what the
yeah
what do we do with the bench
there's a thing you gotta kill it
they come out of the the walls and stuff
what are we starting in the chest
uh
like your second set of armor and uh
maybe some eggs
some some of the potions we only need
probably one for now
oh that was not me I did not do that oh
my goodness I did not do that get rid of
them
chaos
what the hell the bed is about to burn
underneath the portal
well if there's no lab on the portal
really break it for some reason though I
can't leave
can we break the spawner
pour water in the lava
yes okay we don't we don't need the lava
wait
so let me put my something it's dark in
here
it's so cute though I don't know they
don't look edible
how about the uh the potions you guys
the slow falling potion yeah yeah maybe
bring in one one only for now I think
yeah because it's pretty dark yeah
keep it to me leave it to me
okay I'm gonna start putting the eyes in
all right
I'm putting
tests but those are those those are um
okay
yeah okay
oh yeah I will bring it that's okay
[Music]
everyone ready
can we take a group picture can everyone
get on the stairs okay I want to take a
picture nice idea
[Music]
okay well I have a really cool Cape too
yeah no yeah everyone look to the front
and yeah
I want one too
[Music]
okay I got it thank you
me too yay
damn it when you put the under chest
here
uh thank you
what if the front people use the under
chest does that mean
they have their own storage
I opened yours earlier and I didn't see
anything in it oh that means you guys
can use it too
oh well
okay well I'll put
it
looks like
oh okay okay
let's take a punch
what do we do
just jump in
maybe not all at once because I don't
know how big the platform is when we
land and I push each other from where we
stand I want to go first I'm nervous
Watson all right how is it is it like I
can't see wait you guys I don't
know wait okay it's a small platform
um you guys could oh God there's a house
do we have buildings right here it's
already here
make it bigger
okay
I'm working yeah everyone ready
yeah should I be holding something
specific you guys are holding blocks
yeah to build but yeah to build yeah
I'll help
uh do we use the you know do you think
we should use the following potion right
away I think when we when we go in we
can use it when we start the trip let me
start fighting okay also uh Kelly don't
yeah there is a lot of Endermans down
there like a ton oh when you go up
to the dragon try to look down because
there's really an army of Ender Dragons
don't look at them they will kill you
once you look at one should I make walls
I don't want to do a staring contest
with them no no if you do if you do and
wear them or water and get in it because
they can't yeah
but Cali remember we're not fighting the
Ender man because that's the fight we
cannot win we try to fight the Ender
Dragon anymore okay and we can look at
that one right I have to make a bread
you guys can drop me everything
I'm ready now
ready
I'm loading look just wait it's just
loading okay yeah
climatic
oh my God I'm coming in
it broke
oh trees
whoa
oh no
I think we should probably make a bridge
over to the bigger plot for me for me
that was too much the portal is too
powerful
what is this place
is it cool here is back in here
dirt
I also have a lot
okay now wait which way should I build
because there's one close to our left or
should we just build upwards because we
could build stairs here on I got one
yeah we'll put it I think we should go
to the main main uh platform over there
where the dragon is
okay
I am in the end
just let Ahmed do her her thing okay
Uncle push her what the hell well you
won't get anything back
is that normal
what does the sky look like noise to you
as well guys
yeah it looks itchy
it doesn't look like that in uh
[Music]
we need to put walls up
yeah okay okay
you question do you know when you go
into The Nether and that thing that goes
can you and you can like hit him hit the
the Fireballs back at it can you do that
with the Ender Dragon I don't what is
this what is this smoke can I walk into
it no that's that's fire on the ground
that's the Ender Dragon oh okay okay
we'll have to wait then we can't build
above it
oh God
oh
that's our platform oh wow I'm in bad
shape right now oh okay this is bad
this is bad you need to build fast
is all the stuff still there because
I'll just spawn you yeah yeah
stop it how do we make the fire stop
oh God yeah
I think it yeah that's a good idea
turning off shaders my vehicle I'm gonna
collect more materials
please collect my item
oh nice dragon when the dragon shoots
does it break walls also
I don't know nice Mr Dragon
if it doesn't break
all right we'll have to build walls
there
get your stinky breath out of here are
you big scaly thing how long does it
happen there by chance you guys
your stuff is all still here you just
gotta get here okay I'm coming well
actually maybe I'll tell you there's a
fire guy stuff is there yeah Fire's done
you can come in okay that's fine I'm not
gonna start over
I want my things
all right I got a bunch of stuff oh God
the diamond armor is already so low we
really should have brought all of it
yeah
[Music]
um
walked towards the the platform
what does that mean hello Mr Dwayne whoa
thank you wait what's in this what is
that noise
oh
huh oh it's a enemy
my game doesn't work anymore without
shaders
[Music]
I'm in danger
all right hello
we need to build stairs you really want
me to step out there Chad
I chose
1.171.1 the most recent release
yeah this isn't great guys oh
sure my bow and arrows are gone
um so I'm thinking maybe I leave my
stuff here for you guys
here
Serpentine
thank you Watson you don't have to
okay
you sure there's more outside I'll just
uh okay do you go outside can I catch
the fire
turn off the shaders like uh manually
maybe I'll be your eyes in the Sky
What's home
watch out behind you with fire fire fire
fire fire fire fire fire fire fire
okay it's gone it's gone it's funny
are you are you guys already fighting
the dragon oh no no
he's coming back
okay
uh-oh where where is the setting again
okay oh hello
oh he can't fit in here so okay got it
can we kill him
we try to kill one
I mean the others can't see it I mean
this one's already angry does anyone
have a pickaxe so I can dig I can't you
can't use uh arrows or arrange to attack
for Enderman yeah
Tony anybody have a big name may I ask I
do
who picked up my stuff uh there's a nice
dragon and stuff in here so I don't know
I think some stuff might have fallen out
we got stairs ladies and gentlemen
yeah that works too
uh
I died exactly what Cali died so whoever
picked up Kelly stuff might have my
stuff
right now
should I turn off shaders did you guys
turn them off or did it myself
you have to like reload the game if you
turn them off
I'm worried about myself yes oh my god
oh that's bad okay
because here is a bit safer to give me
my stuff thank you the Thunder stairs
one side of armor and like some dirt
blocks some eyebrows
um I only have I only have one set
and what you're wearing one here
I'm only wearing the one that I have hey
where are you guys by the way this is
definitely yours we have TRX here you go
um
everything that you have is messed up
that's okay
okay here here I have my dirt block do
you have an air screw you have no dirt
yeah wait can somebody kill me so I can
go back and then collect all the stuff
okay you know what the summer I wear
held um
wait I don't want all your stuff though
no it's fine it's fine there's more
stuff uh here she asked me to Pure
stream heart Challenger the ax yeah
can you bring me one uh yeah we need one
full set of armor because we're sharing
right now yeah there's two full sets
here so I'll bring I don't have one
either and then um oh do you have uh oh
damn it the golden apples uh I have two
here I gotcha chat
I just need one one okay
yeah no I don't have any it's fine okay
it's cool I'll just try not to die oh do
you guys have bows how many bows do we
have yeah
one bowl uh
uh a few more times please
armor right now me me and Kelly yeah I'm
missing pants and boots okay
I have the bottom Parts okay okay
there's enough uh there's only one ball
I'll probably because the ice cream it
has extra last time you get ice cream
dreams
[Music]
please the Homie house
I think I can make some but they won't
be enchanted
and I'll be right back uh can you bring
some building blocks yeah
how do we leave do we just leave
um all right can I leave these things
here and then come back you guys
yeah would you be able to hold my things
real quick yeah my my Thanksgiving oh
yeah I guess technically they are yeah
oh wow that's loud
all right I'm going to go
play some Sudoku I'll be right back
okay good luck on my glass bottles
oh I'm holding a shield
God I'm such an idiot all right well I
got regular bows wait Kelly wait what
what I should have brought mine potions
up the top the timer
God damn it look
s
to kill you that way he's gone we have
three armor tops here three pants three
helmets one full one all right
one full set nothing much
don't make anything else for me please
just keep it you guys I'll
survived everyone so there should be uh
one more set for you and one more set
for me it is missing but no I have
everything sorry I have it right now I
was gonna go back with it hold on I'm
gonna be right back
we have a because we could store
everything I mean I guess maybe we can't
store stuff now
can I shoot this thing or is it gonna
come after us
depends on what the thing is
yeah
I mean it's gonna heal itself because we
still have the crystals
oh okay
yeah you have pants already I have shoes
and pants
okay
thank you mint ice cream anyone destroy
the crystals all right chat
and then they're at the top of the tower
right the crystal ball I've only ever
watched speed running of this so I won't
I I barely know what happens plus I
always bead Runners always have like the
uh the like the pilgrim outlines turned
on and stuff
yeah and shoot it
[Music]
okay
I gotta get good guys I gotta get into
this ice cream first though crystals are
the things making the beams they heal it
yeah
okay
I can't get into my ice cream
nice look nice weather here today
how's the weather up there you know no
it's a little bit cloudy with the chance
of dragon fireballs
what material is this this is like so I
take the potion now I think it's Ender
Stoners whatever yeah
Anderson
oh I got it
last time what do I do with this glass
bottle to capture something
is it okay to eat the apple now oh yeah
yeah
all right wait where's Cali because Cali
said she um
oh yeah I can't read into the game now
but it says the server is outdated yeah
that's because he turned up
um
no use use the option that it says
OptiFine the normal one that used up
until now then once the screen is open
uh you click into options and turn it
off manually
um into the Minecraft server okay uh you
know where you can choose the Minecraft
servers before you click that you go on
options and then turn off uh Graphics
settings you go to uh shaders and then
turn off the Shader manual okay
thank you
no I'm done
[Music]
don't don't touch myself
you heard her don't touch it I'm not
touching it
all right she's back in the Yukata for
Revenge
Brighton's breath
oh
I'm scared
don't move for myself
so I can dig
wait wait wait wait
oh
that was sensory overload Captain hold
on I need a what's up it's nice pick
pink step
you okay video settings and then
let's see shaders
graphic settings yes Graphics Graphics
settings oh my God damn CA sorry keep
keep focusing on the game sorry uh I
need food I need food I need food yeah
the chickens
hey I I think you can pick it up again I
didn't oh my God how do we do this
okay
is pig step part of the game or is this
a remix hello do you have food please
that sounds I don't know copyrighted
foreign
[Music]
we can start trying to destroy the
tallies
we have destroyed them
can I even shoot that far
it takes only one hit what the hell one
hit
as always right into the bullet time oh
yeah did someone look at me don't attack
me guys don't attack me
oh my God in the bullseye not Bullseye
bullet's eye I don't know
boom boom okay let's go
wow
first try
okay I got a problem I got one
let's get Enderman
[Music]
hi fellas
all right
generating Health
species
why is that water so tiny okay hold on
are you guys oh yeah we gotta do the
towers first okay water all right
ours first oh okay
what am I shooting at I need I need more
arrows no
uh at the top of the towers you're gonna
there's a
um can I put a bed up here can I climb
up there I'm feeling dangerous
it's only those with the cages right
who wants to watch me die
oh no
I think the potion how do you drink a
potion you eat it like it's food yeah
the third one
[Music]
yummy
up that way okay oh wait there's one
here how do you blow these beds up
okay
[Music]
go right click Roger
okay
I have no more arrows unfortunately
thanks Jeff oh so fun I appreciate you
guys I'm good it's gonna be okay
I'll find you guys don't worry
I'll never mind
um I can't does anyone have arrows I
have some uh okay uh I have Infinity so
I can spare 14 for you I think oh wait
um
I think it's free or something I'm I'm
in front of you in front of me I'm sorry
sorry I'm in front of Inna I see you
guys
oh yeah
Inside the Cage now thank you yep got it
I don't have a pickaxe I can't help
anyone
these
okay that'll be a good idea
[Music]
oh I'm happy to just so much
I think someone echoed the Enderman it's
the water
oh yeah
oh oh no yeah someone hey did we get all
this crystals they seem pretty angry
yeah
okay
buddy
well we'll see I guess
I'm missing
oh were you trying to oh yeah it's
taking damage see if it regenerates
oh
G from any of the talents anymore
does this means
oh nice oh nice
I hit I hit him yay how many is the bed
going down
I can't see I think my arrows are doing
anything
sword
I think we're supposed to tackle the
sword right now
for beds beds where are the beds good at
how's your chance
I have one more chicken
Nancy and my arrows aren't doing
anything I'm just wasting it
for a little bit but it was good
you're not flying again
maybe it actually is good all right I
see how to do it now I remember never
he'll go
I remember
the fire oh that's a fireball
[Music]
I have water
it's really actually
excuse me
I'm still gonna win Enderman get lost
yeah bye nerd
there's no stop where's my stuff where's
my stuff
it's raining
okay you know what
I can't get to it
taking back some of my water
did he regenerate or not
you're gonna put fire on top of the
water
Where's My Water
all right
until oh wait there's water
can somebody hit the bed
[Music]
oh my God
you're really excited to see us
stay in the water seen the water
hear me oh
wait what the hell uh where are you
where are you buddy
this is not good
we can do it
Red Power
now I'm gonna kill them here but before
we kill the chick right oh wait I have a
swords I can't do anything
yeah sorry I would agree
I need to blow this list
my life Journey please
[Music]
and you can get a sword
oh yeah guys
like me
do it
hey oh you need to take my stuff
no way he did I don't think
I don't think so
here we got it excuse me hang out with
me
yeah
I have a sword I'll borrow it
oh
now but don't don't don't
hey oh oh what's the fire okay
I love my life
huh
oh
never mind
foreign
I threw I threw my things out there if
someone wants to take them
Slender Man
or no sword there's that camera on the
floor yeah okay I think we're okay are
we
um did you pick up my stuff when you
said you were taking my sword nope
was that a yes or no no Enderman
there's a creeper okay just kidding time
to go back to you guys
nope
the water killed me
whoa that is a powerful portal
are we all still here prepared when I
died
okay
is there a way we can put out this fire
they didn't like no I don't think we
just haven't thought that you know Ricky
R died
the sword use a bottle I know I got a
bottle
where's the fire
[Music]
what did you find my stuff okay I'm nice
I am useful again okay let's go
um as long as I have oh shoot I should
be fine
my things
my my helmet and my chest plate I wonder
if my bow is here
are we still doing the the band strategy
I have yet to get it to work okay it
might be a pipe dream
[Music]
s
yeah I get him it's an experience
I've only got a shovel but uh
all right all right
[Music]
foreign
definitely not helping but it's well
it's nice to feel like
[Music]
oh the portal
yeah what is this oh
are you guys seeing credits
oh she went through the portal already
oh
we have we have to go yeah okay okay PC
[Applause]
Minecraft it's the end of Minecraft it's
over bye-bye is it over
there
it was fun building yeah
[Music]
you mean
yes take care it has reached a higher
level now
oh there's like meta gang
it's talking to us whoa
part of the game
wow I like this layer it played well it
did not give up it is
I think we're at different parts
I think we left something important
many things when it is deep in the dream
of a game it was confusing we go back
baby
can we re-enter the court oh yeah
because
there are treasures and gallium
I'm gonna build a rail to the Ender
Portal
yeah please
but yeah uh my my mission is to get an
elytra as soon as possible because of an
elytra you can fly uh yeah as long as
you have fireworks yes
[Music]
it took us so long but we finally did it
you guys did so much amazing prep work
yeah
[Music]
I'm just privileged to have been able to
come along to watch The Journey
you guys prepared so hard I hope you
arrows
[Music]
yeah
flushing down the toilet Restless
[Music]
zero dance club hello can anybody else
say the same that is pretty dope I will
say yeah but it's kind of awesome pretty
good with the bed I did a lot of damage
yeah that was so cool I did one I think
I did one that was like something out of
like a crazy action movie
you're the bad girl do the bed
[Music]
first try shots were quite quite a lot
of them I would definitely give PR the
Sharpshooter award yeah
[Music]
can I scroll up I want to get a
screenshot of delgoura player of games
that's gonna be my gamer title now
I'm changing my manager Ethan I'm here
do I want to skip in
well we ain't nobody's like Yay how long
are they yeah how long is it
[Music]
okay
oh the Enderman are still here
oh this is their home huh
wait where does it
[Music]
says
spawned back
there's the portal thing
a woman inhaled on me
[Music]
what inhale dummy a woman gathered the
items and she inhaled the player in her
body we got bored
[Music]
millions and millions of miles oh wow so
you might not find it right away but you
gotta travel from like Islands there's
like all kinds of separated
and to get to another Island are
there more dragons maybe we can go on a
treasure only one Dragon oh
is that the egg you know yes but
what does it do Genie
I can let it land on a torch you can
respawn the dragon with the egg oh just
leave it for now I guess okay the dragon
egg yeah I won't touch it it won't go
anywhere
become Daenerys
sometimes
[Music]
we're being spoken to encode you guys
zeros and ones it's the mark of a true
gamer
wow
Universe said they love you by the way
you know
that was very kind also the universe is
inside you
that makes me feel violent
[Music]
I gotta know more the universe
says you're not alone
[Music]
where's the egg
am I
you can't get up
you're awesome
wake up I know I know
from that horrible dream what the hell
is that
now wake up
wow did this take us less than two hours
you guys yeah
here
[Music]
anybody have a pickaxe
okay
hello hi hello uh just uh read the title
if you want to use it that's important
yay
oh a streamer Challenger and Sparks
that's right that's right nice should I
do it Fame Sparks collecting materials
bye that was that was a lot of fun
that's a blast you guys thank you so
much
are you building a what are you building
me
oh oh don't worry is that a creeper yes
oh no
sorry
oh no are you okay
you moved in my line of fire
down Mr President
I can't wait for the railway railroad
railroad I want me a werewolf I want
some books
now what do we do real party did I say
this letter
oh nice
too because I lost so many items did you
guys see this dress
there's books in it there's not much oh
oh
I have so many books okay that's all I
wanted to take just a little bit this
place is so cute
um I have something to confess
um
I
I went I I might have been the first one
to open the chest and I might have been
the one who took something out of the
chance oh what was in the chest yeah
two two two books that were in Enchanted
nothing super special oh yeah well I'm
level 68.
when uh
I was level 30 earlier
hey how do we get an elytra can we get
that now
the what I thought no I had to look for
Treasures in the end the world yeah oh
wanna do that
I mean I thought it was gonna take
longer to be honest
even though they lose them all of the
time
don't do
anything there is no limit it will take
a while
yeah it might take a while to explore
because you have to find the place where
they have it and then you gotta like
clear out
stuff gotta kill stuff oh
we wanted to take a picture yeah
should we not take that like in the end
that would wouldn't that be cool
again
in in the end and then we'll just take a
picture and quickly go outside again
sure what do you want to do that I don't
know wait where is it where is it can I
go back into the middle and let me go
down the stage what the hell is it
is there yes okay
yes
all right I'm going in did we get the
egg
I think you have to keep leave it there
leave it there until we know how to take
it safely
yeah let's let's get to the egg and take
a picture in front of it yeah let's do
it
off my
um silk touch pickaxe
I have cutting Corners oh yeah that's
mine
oh no what is that thing I don't like me
they don't like me I'm here to read and
I chew here you go uh
thank you for keeping it
[Music]
uh where do we take the picture
make sure you don't stare at the
Enderman
one thing
about that of this of the perch
if I switch views will it make me look
at them
just don't touch it
um not necessarily
app
okay oh I'm ready whenever
everywhere
you guys gonna get it with this little
touch
this is like Opera nicely
you guys you can't mine it
don't exactly don't touch it no touchy
check once then break the block under it
with a torch
now the block under if somebody says you
need a piston yeah so don't touch it
right now okay later
yeah the egg is part of the journey
[Music]
gets close like maybe in front here oh
we could build like our own pillars
right behind the egg and it look really
cool a pillar yeah
some building material and I fill in the
portal yeah
I'm from the
oh I'll take him Kelly here you go
oh yeah
I know I got it okay
um then okay this one touch one heart
will it oh don't touch it just a little
touch oh no
oh
sorry I I panicked I left okay guys
destructive
disable Health achieve Victory clean out
yeah
wow they're real quick they like to move
with the blocks
oh yeah they're real men
yeah I'm watching and I'm a sword
I'll sit here for a million years I'll
just stand up I'll just run
out
Mommy
crunchy stuff is there a way that I can
help you no it's okay
oh
they're angry this is gonna be tough
I love it
in their home
can I have another uh
okay I'll be back where is he okay I'll
be back
okay okay
I'll be back thumbs up
this place is a lot less scary without
the uh
Dragons
I'm excited about the shaders but yeah I
was at the dragon as well
yeah the sky is prettier without the
shirt but it's not yet it's much easier
to see without it yeah pitch black but I
mean yeah it wasn't much better when it
was noise
you can get his head
you mount it to the wall that's no use
any tool or even your bare hands hit the
Ender Dragon egg Until It Breaks oh yeah
remember remember Mikko Senpai and
suicide Senpai uh wearing those ender
dragon heads yeah
this is good
or should we do okay
I guess for every picture we can look
into a different direction okay
yeah I think this angle works for me
okay oh yeah this one works for me too
oh wait this is confusing everybody look
up and to the right
right look I I'll just look where I try
to stand I guess that means
am I looking in the right side yeah yeah
yeah I am too okay I'm just gonna leave
this to you a little up
yeah I can't see oh
hey buddy
sure
huh
get out of here all right well I'm
jumping back in the portal we got one
right
I think so oh wait
I didn't can everyone
where I stand
to the to
um to the front yeah
okay and three two one
cheese cheese
anyone else that wants a picture
um I'm let's see oh yeah sure
then I should be looking in the right
direction yeah all right everyone look
up this way ready
I got it I got it I got it I got it okay
all right I'm jumping in the portal
all right let's go all right here we go
yay
[Music]
does anyone want to like go back home or
like is everyone ending now or because I
feel like it's a lost
I'm gonna uh I wanna go treasure hunting
later
okay oh yeah what you know we're not
doing the egg though how do we do that
whoa look at it and he torches somebody
else yeah
uh no I have one
can I have one
I'm I'm playing Minecraft later today
guys
just don't take all the treasures yes
there's infinite Treasures oh cool
I'll be leaving
yeah me too thanks so much everyone for
the fun time
won't forget it
it's quite an experience thank you for
everything you guys need to prepare yeah
it was yes thank you it would not have
been easy mode without all of your
preparations
thank you so much guys it's always
cooperating whenever you needed help
thanks for the fun times
[Music]
thank you
foreign