[Music]
uh
don't chicken out
[Music]
okay
um hello
no oh dear the music is so loud
when i tap out of it it suddenly stops
okay uh hello it's so loud to me
wait a second
i'm not scared i'm not scared
i'm trying to find the right uh way to
set up my
my my my whole setup volume is low which
volume my
volume i turned it down on purpose
because i'm gonna be screaming probably
uh i turned it on on purpose
it turned it down on purpose
anyway
so how about this balance actually
it's probably slow
turn that down don't don't want anything
[Music]
okay today
i shall be playing my first ever
horror game um
it's halloween tonight it's almost
midnight in japan
i i i was hoping i could uh
run away from horror games until someone
forces me to play it as a as a
as a punishment game
but the game on there
but apparently this one is a short one
and apparently it's uh a game that
is not even that scary apparently i i
read some reviews it's not even that
scary apparently
people say but i have a very uh
easily scared person very
still a mic to look well you will you
will hate me once i start screaming but
okay i can turn it up
there a little bit a little bit but you
will hate me once i start screaming
okay i'm not saying i'm a chicken
because i'm not a chicken but i guess
let's go
oh nightmare mode
a more challenging game would you
explore a mania main
manor with a mechanically powered
flashlight and the horse ribbon are more
deadly
okay
[Music]
what do you guys think did anyone ever
try the nightmare mode before
did anyone ever try where is it is it
bad
regular that's my first one i can't give
me a break
okay give me a break please here we go
i'm not scared you're scared i'm not
scared i'm not scared
you're scared i'm not a chicken i'm a
phoenix okay hello this is not even that
scary this
game is not even scary apparently so
it's all good it's
not it's not a proper horror game it's
just a puddle game it's just a
solving riddles which i'm also not very
good at but
okay uh okay uh to move the mouse what
press e or the left mouse button to
extend mind certain items when the
magnifying glass appears okay
like this heavy bronze ornament
oh thank you uh what
with the lettuce km does it's
does that mean kill me or crave it i
guess it's craving
manure okay uh
anything else notes of william crevin
cabin initially i landed what
i told you you'll hate me once i start
screaming
however wednesday i turned my back to
the stage here i thought what
this is way too quick oh my god you
don't even want me to read that do you
what okay anyway
to throw an object you're holding okay
okay cool okay
i don't wanna i don't wanna play this i
don't wanna
it's okay this is
oh
huh
[Music]
nothing's scary about that
what am i even supposed to do am i just
walking around is this how you play
horror games you just walk around and
see what you find and just
you could just stay where you are but
you purposefully like go through
the whole thing to try to scare yourself
like why would anyone even do this it
makes absolutely no sense
am i supposed to go in here i don't want
to go any
oh it's okay okay okay okay wait i heard
you can
i i read in the control all that you can
run
but i don't i forgot how also there's a
i think what was a journal my search for
ansys has to start sometime
i just wish i had picked a better night
oh yeah it shouldn't be halloween
it should not be halloween shift
that shiny thing scares me
also there was one more button what was
it where was it
one more button bt i don't know
oh flashlight flashlight f for
flashlight okay
i don't know i don't know what am i
doing i don't want to do anything
we're not gonna do this in one or
apparently you can do this in 45 minutes
but
i'm not gonna do this in 45 minutes
everything is locked where i can't even
go anywhere
[Music]
oh there's a oh this is this thing is
leading me
ah oh dear
hello
no no
no
hello the heat does not reach far into
this cold room and
that's done comforting this house is
supposed to be abandoned yet something
started to fire
well it's because i'm a phoenix and not
a chicken
for whoever do not in the truth what
bursting of phantasms brag that they can
do miracles
be destinated to the torments of eternal
fire
phoenix lore phoenix lore phoenix lore
exactly oh god
hello
rejecting the music of spheres as the
moment movement of astronomical bodies
are incapable of what are you even
talking about
hello hello
press e or left mouse button to lift
drop or manipulate certain objects when
the hand icon
okay
like that what is that wine cellar model
what i found a scale model of a wine
cellar
it matches the mama i saw in the
entryway uh-huh
did i see anything in the entryway
okay it's just an old old old house
okay i don't know why this these things
are falling down but
wait what do i do with this i have red
was this like this before i don't know
i i read that you're like supposed to do
something with these objects
and scale them or whatever kind of uh
reminds me of the idea of
uh what was this other game that emily i
was playing uh
oh my god
what turn on the flashlight
what happened what happened
oh [\h__\h]
what click and drag to move the room
rotate through
room while dragging what am i doing
what am i doing bring other scale
remodels you find to the table and
further explore the menu okay
maynard whatever how do you say that i
don't know
oh as i regain my footing the glass
around the scale level was shattered by
whom or by what i'm not sure
that i want to find out yeah i really
don't want to know as i brought the
scale model
close to the model on the table it flew
from my hands and positioned itself on
the table as if it was meant to be there
then i heard sounds of of stone against
stone if i remember correctly
a model of a library was attached
earlier and now it is missing
oh okay
where do we go next shiny light tell me
where do i go next johnny light
don't wanna tell me
is there an open door
language i didn't say anything what did
i say
where do i go next do i go back in there
the statue
hello
it's probably somewhere else now
probably hiding somewhere to jump scare
me
please don't kill me he's gay
i can't go anywhere
i don't wanna paint it
is that my is that supposed to be my own
breath or is that supposed to be
somewhere
[Music]
else
do i do
do i go back into the room i can't
wait how do i even which one was that i
don't think i can go there anymore what
the hell
go to the table to the to prog which tip
this table
again oh the key the key
how do i take the key
i want to take the key
can i take the key
huh rotate room while dragging
oh wait does that uh influence how if i
can get in there
ah attach the room to the entry ah
but i can't move the entryway model
how was it first god damn it
is this how it's supposed to be
there's a slot at the upper part what
door connects so yeah right door connect
door connect
but why can't i take the key
is it like this
wait it keeps on returning it yeah
it keeps on going back
attach the room's at the door and it
will unlock a room
sorry am i being stupid oh
okay okay well that wasn't really my
fault
hello
saving
hello oh my god
eww what i notice to all craven
metalworks employees
thieves and layabouts shall be
disciplined by lord craven and shall
receive no way just
sounds like kfp
i don't wanna play
okay cool
cool
is that cali lp murray's wine bottle why
did you leave it there that's scary
do i really have to go there hold up
[Music]
what is that i see something oh god no
no no no
no no okay thank you for watching
today's stream
uh i will read super chat now uh
thank you for coming sorry it was kind
of a short stream
um uh happy halloween yeah it was a nice
halloween
um
wait what yeah what's that seriously
okay it's there yeah you already see it
you don't have to be scared it's not
that one's gonna
probably wait oh god oh god
nothing's gonna happen it's probably not
even gonna move no no no no nothing's
gonna happen
get out okay yeah i would love to i
would love to
i don't even want to be here
can i put it in there can we put it back
ocd
i don't wanna be here okay i'm gonna get
outside
huh wait
what
is it
[Music]
okay wait so am i i'm supposed to run
away from it why
i'm supposed to run away from it right
okay there's nothing scary about it i
already saw what's happening so this is
not scary anymore
it's not scared it's not scary it's not
scary
blueprints kfp blueprints the blueprint
design is
attributed to william craven the
architecture reflects both scruples
detailed extremely stained strange
structural components
okay
that's it okay bye-bye
why did we not see this place before
wait wait
we skipped it did we skip it
i already saw this before
[Music]
hello
what what what that's different uh okay
no no no okay
okay it's gonna happen now now they tell
me to run away from what direction
in what direction in what direction in
what direction but i don't understand
what what what what
what
and what's my what's with my flashlight
where do i go
[Music]
oh i don't see anything
okay
[Music]
i saw something working in the shadows
hiding from the light i'm not sure what
it was but i hope
to not see it again i stumbled upon
another scale room while this one
appears to be a bedroom
wonderful i love it let's bring it back
and get this over with quickly
i understand that this is not even
really scary for you guys but
i don't like it i don't like it i'm
sweating i'm sweating
okay i can do that
maybe here okay wonderful
i'm not a chicken though let me just
tell you i'm not a chicken
like which door opened
up there oh
i think it's up above it's up there yeah
yeah yeah okay
okay i'm coming
saving oh god the store
oh hello it's me takana
i'm stupid that's why i'm following you
i don't i don't understand the logic of
horror games why do you do
you this to yourself i don't understand
the logic really it
makes no sense makes absolutely no sense
inside this book there are many diagrams
and sketches of human teeth
was he a dentist
okay we want to go into this of course
we want to go into this door where we
saw that stupid puppet
nice bed
um oh okay i see the blood
i see the blood i see it i understand
we have to follow the blood crime scene
photographs labeled
george craven for blah blah this black
and white photo depicts a male body on
its knees leaning over with its head
submerged in a vat of molten bronze what
what
this is just a game
oh
those figures
i don't wanna play in the snow
oh there's definitely a puppet in there
like a half dead body or something
oh no okay
oh
this is this is just game channel it's
just a [\h__\h] game
there's nothing this is not real piano
this is not real yeah that is not real
yeah
this is not [\h__\h] real yeah that's not
real
it's not real it's not real it's not
real it's not real it's not real
okay wrong run no no just run away just
i probably just have to run away
probably just have to run away
gotta chill chill the [\h__\h] out gotta
chill
your neighbors will call the [\h__\h]
police
can i chill chill
[Music]
this is fun this is fun i love this
place still the phone do i have to read
those things again
hi wonderful thank you for those
photographs
looking sweet i just have to change my
my mindset you know
i just have to change my mindset just
have to change my mindset
and see those in a positive light hello
leg
nice leg shave legs what do you shave
your legs with why am i so slow
um the question is just where the where
do i run to
uh hello so i think i'm not supposed to
look at you um so good it's so good i'm
not trying to look
i'm just
[Music]
no
i have to look at it no no no that
doesn't make sense
but before i ran away and it worked
i have to really
really
okay okay
[Music]
what blurry photos of six nude
you like light you like that
look into the light they tell me to look
at yourself where where are you
huh where are you where are you where
where where where okay hey
is this what i'm supposed to do how you
doing my friend
now you're not even that scary anymore
what's happening
what's happening what do i do now just
do this wait
oh uh what
i what back a wasteland okay
okay okay back off my friend
back off back off or ah i have to walk
backwards while looking at it or
i can only move when i look away but how
do i make it stop then look at the
picture
no no no i can't look away now the
picture frame how do i look at this
thing and also at the picture frame
it won't move
what
okay what now
am i like supposed to do something i
can't
run okay bye bye bye bye
don't run get touched nah nah i don't
think so
no no no no no no
i don't understand
what what what what what
interact with the picture okay
okay okay okay
um i interacted but i don't think it
liked my interaction
nothing happens
what do we do now
it's so close don't look away from me
i'm trying to
first eat nothing happens with me
i don't understand i'm doing it wrong
focus
click the picture i did try
sexy pose though press
e on the oh oh eh
you collapse the floor and slip into
darkness ah
huh i pressed e on the painting
you told me to press e on the painting
i don't understand this game i
i i don't care look at the picture at
the same time and
didn't we do that
how is it so difficult by the way this
game is free
it's free made by students
that are obviously smarter than me
open the goddamn trunk
yeah i need directions i need
explanation
[Music]
okay but again what did we do
nothing happens
leave them away and then interact hi
come here baby
looking at you looking at you don't move
don't move don't move don't move
nothing happens with the painting for
god's sake we need someone who
understands this
this game
emulates
you're not supposed to die so often
throw up some object at her
first there's no heal well every time
i'm getting uh
used to it now
number one
oh oh
no i'm not scared anymore keep trying
you're improving oh really what am i
what exactly am i improving
okay let's dance again i guess yeah
we're just dancing we're just dancing
hello hello throw something out here so
[Music]
there's no reason to be scared kiana
painting and then rope what
check the super jet
there's a cord on the right of the
picture frame on the corner of the room
on the right of the picture frame on the
corner of the room on the right of the
picture frame on the corner of the rim
like uh by the way that picture is not
even here now
is it
is that a different room
isn't that the room where we were there
the whole time and now it looks
different
okay there's a cord on the right side of
the picture right okay okay i'll go
go go okay
no it's the same room wait i didn't even
see that drop down
do i have to see it
i see there was a door here there was a
door here before
this room is different now
wait where's that cord oh
it's not there it's not there i don't
see it and i
i did the court thing okay oh
oh
thank you super jet
thank you the nature of
limbo has revealed itself to me it is a
receptive
receptacle in a state of existence where
in their spirit can become like limbo
isn't that another word for
limbo a carefully detailed illustration
of a human arm being
dipped in bronze nice
okay hello oh we got a model we got a
model
[Music]
see now it's back to normal i told you
okay we're playing architect here i'm
playing architect
ah limbo is limbo
okay i got another room that i really
don't want to go into but
what choice do i have how do i like that
no like that
no how do you want me to connect that
huh
puzzle puzzle puzzle here no
usually it shows me when it where it
wants to be connected
well maybe i did
it's on top oh wait uh is are there
supposed to be floors
oh wait oh hey i just realized i can see
that
i can see like uh how it was how it used
to be
but wait it doesn't fit anywhere
it doesn't fit anywhere
bottom left wow it doesn't go bottom
left
joke's on you try to remove
[Music]
oh that works oh
i see it didn't know that that would
work
hello new room wow
at first there was no need to assure
that thoughtful consciousness
of what indeed for the likes of the
first 19 their minds were no great loss
okay are you saying that they were
useless to begin with
doesn't matter if you killed them
i mean that's suspicious i wonder what's
underneath there
oh i wonder i can't i can't
get rid of it oh later i'm sure that
will be
gone later on
very funny very funny
very funny very funny my friend
oh so funny what did that do
oh nice um yeah i totally want to go up
there
no i don't want to go up the nose
okay
guess we're going straight for that
chest no
okay okay jump scare incoming probably
probably behind that thing very
suspicious i must say
oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god oh
god what am i doing up here what am i
doing up here what am i
birth certificate the person chocolate
okay don't care don't care where or when
you were born
[Music]
what is that even for that option does
it even do anything when i throw
something
wait i have to sh i have to have to turn
the light to it okay okay what what is
the riddle what is the riddle what is
the riddle
what is the rail what could i do what
could i do what could i do what could i
do what could i do what could i do what
could i do what could i do
oh my god i don't know what to do i
don't know what to do i don't know what
to do
i don't know what to do what is
i don't think that's it where is it
i bunked it funk that's not very scary
though
that just bugged around i think okay is
that look it's so cool it's behind that
plastic thing we're safe we're safe i
think
i think
bye bye bye bye
i'll just go back wait a second wait a
second wait a second
wait a second wait a second wait a
second isn't it supposed to be there
logical thinking i don't know let's go
down
probably wants me to go down again right
and then it's there
no let's close it again please thank you
let's just leave it up that what there
supposed to do
probably not
okay no problems oh wait
is that the same ledge
this is different ledge
why are you counting my screams
there's something on the sofa upstairs
oh wait
containing a philosophic description on
the application of the
choice zest chemicals remedies drum from
the light
of nature and grace okay oh god
i think i have to copic and i probably
missed something
right right
or is there anything here you need to
throw items into the hanging barrel
upstairs
okay
we'll do my friend
let's go back up there yay
let's face the horror again
[Music]
up throw objects into the barrel throw
objects into the barrel for objects into
the barrel
throw up just into the barrel
hello objects oh god it's still there
it's still there wait which barrel
up there
what i'm do that barrel
boy basketball but that's fun
that's fun i'm really bad at games with
falls though
ah is this really what i'm supposed to
say
sometimes the character jumps weirdly
oh uh almost almost almost almost almost
wait
wait is this really what i'm supposed to
do
get closer aim high ah
how many do you want me to phone
oh no it's lifting that thing no no no
no no no no but it's gone
oh yay
oh yeah this makes so much sense i can't
even oh is that like
high enough already for me to go for no
this one
okay nice bro
okay friends here we go
protect yourself for something close
your ears
oh god
hello um i'm following you for whatever
reason what the [\h__\h] is that
what is it where is it where is it where
is it where is it
it's gone it's gone the finger just
dropped it's gone
ew you okay it must be over there
don't be scared chiara don't be scared
it's nothing scary
oh more things are exploding
oh god i heard something move i still
hear it move
oh oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh oh
oh why are we doing this
why are we doing this why is it
where is the puppet or is the puppet
[Music]
i went the whole round
is this the same place where i came from
everything just moved around
am i supposed to go down again
no probably right now i can
go down
look up no i don't want to look up why
what did i miss
what did i miss oh
i dodged that one so well dude
oh never mind never [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
no [\h__\h] mine never [\h__\h] mine never
[\h__\h] mind oh my god
okay where's my model where's my model i
dropped my model
hello just gonna take the thank you
where's the door where's it i can't move
i really can't move right now
i could you either kill me or
let me go
okay yep okay thank you i still
can't really move i still can't
exactly move right now can you end this
quickly
i would prefer it if you would end it
please um i know i'm going to die okay
uh jump there's no jump
smack his body
i'm just gonna wait it's probably i have
to change my sitting position
it's probably um gonna eventually kill
me no
you don't want to do anything come on
oh okay okay uh oh there we go i still
can't move
um
what's with your neck should i look away
okay yeah i gave you that for free
because um
you kind of cornered me there
um this is what you called cabadon in
japanese
kabedon thank you
very romantic indeed
[Laughter]
and we have to do the whole thing again
the whole room wait my
my my game crashed
[Laughter]
my game crashed it
this is again wait it did save though in
between so
i'll be right back oops oopsie
everyone stay where you are stay where
you are
[Music]
please let me continue
let's see why we continue
james is crashed while i was loading man
10 minutes until november oh
holy [\h__\h] when you think about it that
way after halloween is over it's
november
what kind of wanted to do this in one
hour but it seems like i'm especially
slow
okay let's just oh oh we already did
that part okay let's save that part okay
good
okay my friends um i
i forgot uh oh god
no no no no no no no no keep on moving
keep on moving keep on moving wait what
oh there it is there it is there it is
there it is and now here comes the doll
the eye is it downstairs yep yep okay
wait what do we do once we're downstairs
what do we do
i don't know okay
um hello don't mind me can i go out here
please please
oh wait can we trap it
can we trap it
wait i can't touch it anymore
what did
am i cornered go what sofa
[Music]
throw the model no no no don't give it
to him
can i go around him okay okay okay
bye
[Music]
where is the door which door is the one
i came in from
this is a bit confusing
oh i made it i made it i made it i made
it don't kill me now
bye bye we [\h__\h] made it
okay okay we did it
we did it okay which one is the new one
this one right now it huh wines ooh
i took bedroom library i think
find someone which one is the new one
or did i just lose my did i lose it
library is a new one okay
library library okay
okay i just keep on does it even matter
where i connected to wait there's a
another one that can connect there
interesting oh wait uh maybe i
eventually have to do it so that it
connects with the okay wait so let's say
we connect that there
and then we connect that there and then
we can connect that
if we want that i don't think we want
that but let's just say we're gonna do
that
uh but wait it tells me to connect
these
what about this one though
oh okay look at this puzzle game
okay okay now i think where do we go
do we go upstairs again where
exactly did i place that library
is that upstairs
huh or just on the right side no
i think upstairs get key
can i get it they didn't give it to me
before
and i realized that breathing is
supposed to be my own breathing oh
okay daiso
do i use it
it's missing a lever
the gear system appears to be missing an
important piece okay okay
okay okay okay okay no problem you can
do it
i'm not sure about that uh there's many
factors that are uh
here uh giving me a hard time
wait
wait the new one is
which one is that didn't it why don't do
both of the
uh okay so that said uh attack model for
a second
but okay so the right side
library okay probably upstairs because i
can't go there
puzzle on this curious part
let's try to get in here should be in
your room yep
it looks like no wait i was here before
oh
but something's happening what exactly
happened
can i go up there no
oh wait is it because i connected it
wrong or
find a way up there i will find my way
oh god i was here before though i have a
really bad headache right now oh my god
but i feel more calm right now
what maybe can i use that to get up
no yeah why not i want to use that
oh damn that headache though damn
no i don't think there's a way to get up
there
come very calm yes i'm very calm
oh what can't do anything like that
very suspicious though ah
huh is this like uh
i wonder what that is
i'm supposed to probably put something
in there paradise lost an epic poem
concerns the biblical fable of the fall
of men
interesting of one man
yeah think it's probably connected wrong
let's try to reconnect it how do people
play this in 45
why am i walking so slow in 45
minutes drink water
eventually okay but
okay so this light is telling me those
have to be connected
but maybe maybe this is
no this also tells me to go there no
ah but they tell that doesn't really
matter it seems like it can go anywhere
okay so what if i i can't connect those
i can connect those
but why would i want to go there again
attic model doesn't really make sense to
put the attic down here though does it
wait am i supposed to see this here
rotate the library it doesn't change the
name here
that should be the library
[Music]
thank you for the super jets
now nothing wants to connect anymore
maybe if we connect this yeah the
library wants to go here
or here oh
doesn't that change how we enter it yeah
it does
let's just connect that as well just for
fun
okay that should change the way we enter
it am i going in there from here yep yep
okay
hello books a false book
what the hell was that another first
book
oh
[Music]
very big brain no it's november
oh i told you guys before in the stream
november is a very hello
exciting stream for me exciting month
okay i saw you there don't think i
didn't see you
okay the music is a bit scary and the
cold door closed
oh god what's with the music
[Music]
take this oh my god oh my god oh my god
what
where's the next book i probably have to
push another book where is it
[Music]
it's so fast
there's nothing to be scared about where
is that stupid piece of [\h__\h]
where is it where is it where is it
where do i go
where do i go am i done
am i done
no i'm not done what do i do next
the horror lives lives in the recesses
of darkness
a place between curiosity and madness i
can feel it it seeks to destroy me i
found a
library model the one that was on the
entryway table when i first
arrived the library model appears to
have two entrances
one goes to the top floor i see okay now
please tell me what am i
keep on looking for false books
okay
really is that when i need to do
i didn't activate the last one okay
where was that one
hello hello hello
nice job
am i done with the game please tell me
i'm done with the game
oh like that did we play the game
oh my god if we did play the game it
feels like i cleared the game
oh wait we connected it to another room
eh but wait yeah
and if but that no no yeah
do we want to go that direction or the
one where we came probably the one where
we came from there's no reason to go and
actually is that going to be useful now
wait a second can we go back where we
came from
can we go for here is it open oh thank
god
hello i have another
souvenir oh wait oh wait
what the [\h__\h] is that
isn't it that is that not for the
elevator i think this is for the
elevator no
wait what the [\h__\h]
what what what is this moving noise
do you want my the thing that i just
picked up whatever that
is oh god what is this
hey can i go oh
oh was that the ghost of mr craven
oh god is this the last level like the
boss level
is that a chess game
no what is that um that's scary sound
are you gonna follow me no you're going
up
okay but what about that room
no okay an old photograph dated 1877
shows a massive mania on the run
no face and the back
what
i found another model run piece with
white and glass walls within did we
incredibly this piece floated onto the
table on its own and sealed itself
ah that was that fingers just flew away
okay uh tied on
to this table surface i feel whatever is
leading me there but i am desperate and
out of options
i mean we could just leave this goddamn
manor but okay i must somehow get to
this white room i can manipulate the
other rooms on the table to create a
path but the pieces only seem to fit in
the various pieces okay no problem
okay no problem
is it gonna be showing up a doll again
no okay good
okay please no chance
what's your problem with chess
chess is a beautiful game appreciate it
i hope we're ending this sooner i hope
we're ending this soon
okay so this is the new one but we have
to attach it
probably we have to go through all no
maybe not because this one only has
one one entry point
this one has two so maybe
oh wait um wait a second this one cannot
be moved okay
interesting no no no
can we start from there or do we have to
start from down
below oh i can't move that piece
so i have to reach okay wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait first this
yes then
[Music]
it doesn't have does it have to resemble
wait there's no other
entry there actually this might be
useless the attic is maybe useless
i think the attic is useless is there
such a thing as a useless
follow the dark stuff oh
oh wait did that just make a sound like
as if it was
the right way to do it
wait a second what
ah that don't look wait
does this look like it it does
oh and this and one
attic is useless yep
that just goes anywhere stay there
okay
i think we collected the connected and
collected
the pieces correctly uh which door is it
though
what where which door is that
which door is that it's from the top
sorry by my logic it would have to be
there wait is this behind the picture
uh under the stairs there's a room under
the stairs
on the other side
that one
oh makes sense okay
i know okay door is closed wonderful
hello hello
um i came here because i'm looking to
rent this house
um could i please rent it
right now i recently just moved but oh
my god why is it so loud why is it so
loud
what do i have to put in there i
recently just moved
but i'm not really happy with
where i live right now because there's
ghosts oh god i see it
they all look the same
please hug me
i have found a locked door a globe some
globe frames and a series of nearly
identical porches of a woman
each with an odd inscription on them i
feel a word mind is testing me
the mind of yago is testing me
what liar i didn't lie the [\h__\h]
i'm the most honest person in this world
okay let me change my sitting position
again
okay what's in this book
wait i can't
this is so heavy
blood stained book the portraits of
jacqueline kraven each have a different
inscription
only one of the inscriptions has it
jacqueline and green the globe belongs
to the right ah to the right most frame
the jacqueline ring blue is honest okay
what does jacqueline and blue say the
jaclyn ring
green is a liar so it's not the right
most frame
the globe belongs in the third frame
from the left
so blue and what did you say again
jacqueline blair and blue is honest
green is a liar
glove belongs in the frame on the
leftmost side
purple is telling the truth but is that
green doll no it's that yeah that's
yellow
left most side so here
oh oh wait no these ah is that left from
like from where are we talking are we
talking from this
perspective
or from you yeah i guess from their
oh [\h__\h] hell no please no
what's happening what's happening what's
happening what's happening what's
happening
i write the center of trembling bleeding
hands the trap was sprung as i placed
the glove in the frame
i must have done something wrong you
know that was right
no the other left oh
i must have done something wrong i am
sure this globe is linked to the door
but it would be reckless to randomly try
again
as i bound my wounds i noticed a book
near the portrait
but i should not try it again
sec was second left what what did you
say
frame on the left most side purple is
telling the truth
you want me to look at the book again no
no i think it does want me to move it
again
and so do you mean that left oh god
okay okay okay okay a nice
bleep sound what now oh the door's open
okay oh [\h__\h]
hello good morning
it's november um i think it's time to
stop hanging around
like a lazy fox maybe we should start uh
uh putting up our december christmas
decorations
what do you think i don't think these
are good decorations these are
a bit uh depressing i must say
but okay if you if you think this looks
good
i don't want to go in here it's going to
close right
oh god my heartbeat
is this asmr do i have to read that i
probably have to read that children's
book
wow the book is open to an illustration
of the scared child about
to look under his bed and the devil
waiting for him underneath
what is that do you see that
what is this music
[Music]
are we gonna watch a movie together
the nature oh i already read that
i guess we turned it on oh movie time do
i really want to watch that right now oh
okay i see those are your
secret projects oh what's happening
what the [\h__\h] are you doing oh wait is
that
it's that ball
movie time
want me to do something with that or
just ignore it
i would like to ignore it my early
successes were brief but invigorating
after the ritual mellif
physical what the large herbs held the
spirits for seconds
at a time and glowed visibly
i can't interact with it
a carefully detailed illustration of a
human arm being dipped in bronze with a
set of pincers delaying appears
instructional as if it were torn out of
a manual
okay i don't think i can do
anything here
grab i can't grab it
no no no no
maybe i'll go out again have a dance
with these
beautiful people
okay yep they're gone nice
um and i hear whispering
awesome uh i guess we're going to that
door now
probably open yup wonderful um
it's the bedroom again one of my
favorite rooms
lots of things you can do in the bedroom
sleep for example
i like sleeping if i'm not streaming any
nightmares
that is
i'm not even that scared anymore though
actually like it was way worse in the
beginning i'm from like
not even kidding but um
wait a second where does it continue
wait huh
oh oh let's let's let's let's let's was
this here always
okay okay
okay another secret room
almost like the one in in minecraft that
my papa built
hello take that wine bottle
no okay you can't take it telling me to
not drink
alcohol i agree with that alcohol is not
very good
my children i do not recommend it
[Music]
what is happening i didn't do anything i
didn't move anything
no please
[Music]
no problem this is just a game it's just
a game just a [\h__\h] game just a
[\h__\h] game
where did i come from where did i come
from
i have lost my
sense of direction torn painting
dozens of finn fine spreads i don't like
these noises oh
oh what is going on is that some harry
potter magical what
hello i don't wanna go
there it's probably more afraid of
thank you for the super chat am i
supposed to go in there
why would i do that no no no no
cool cool magic trick very impressive
is that what you prepared for our date
honestly i have to say i don't really
like magic tricks um
you could i would be happy if you would
prepare something more
i don't know funny this is not
funny oh what the [\h__\h] is that
what
saving when do you need to save
i don't want to move this
[Music]
what me what
the order of the four tones seems
significant i may be able to recreate
the glass sound somehow
[Music]
ah
wait put it down ah
who's coughing done i think this is the
first
nah maybe not
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait can you do that again
dun dun dun
why is it turning green oh it's gonna
kill me
oh my god wait what what what what
no wait wait wait wait which one is that
check please tell me oh my god [\h__\h]
tell me please
[\h__\h] tell me
then this one this one maybe this one
[Music]
one three two four okay
wait did it work what what what what
[Music]
one three
two one
oh thank god go away poison go wayne
go wait do i jump in there too no okay
i'll just move on probably
okay okay thank you chad
thank you thank you i'm also scared
since it's like after midnight if i
scare any louder than this my neighbors
might call the police so i'm just trying
to get this over quickly now
a barely legible note including the
words leather bottles
and well in the rough musical scale
several combinations of
aha
what is this like am i supposed to read
this before
what i just did
this dude looks really familiar to me
though
close the door i should leave it open
he looks really doesn't he look like
someone
that i needed
i've met that dude before
uh bookmark is a settle is set to a
photo of a young man dipping a glass
ornament into a va okay cool your hobby
i see
oh is that the the thing that's stuck in
amelia's tie
the syringe that she has in her ties
did she leave them there
hello i think this is the top level
is it please say yes oh god the light is
changing
oh door closed nice and locked awesome
yep i love that
guys i'm scared i'm scared is there
someone in the chat who can help me
what saving
what are we saving for am i going to die
now finally the time has come actually
i'm a phoenix it doesn't really matter
if you kill me so
i don't care i don't
care is that an elevator
nah what is that oh god that what is
this
what is this room i don't like this room
i don't want to get in there
okay we have no choice this is how
horror games work
nice um hello
i finally reached the white room why
can't i read that if
what is happening is that game crap did
they can crash no
oh there we go finally reached the white
room filled with glass walls it feels
cold and dry within
and smells of blood and metal unlike the
rest of the manor there is no more
mistaking this place for home its
purpose is clear people died here
wonderful yep i knew that from the
beginning but okay
this is um oh okay this is a
like a labyrinth a maze
oh god make it end
a large shade of glass of it seems to
have burst from within the broken glass
right that's the one from the video
maybe
oh god oh wow that is very um
couldn't you have done that a little bit
more
yes
gently gently is there are there no
materials that are more gentle than that
syringe tranquilizer beneath and small
attacks
appear the words lysergic acid
just a simple simple puzzle okay
no problem the doors keep on opening
wait where did that come from oh i had
to go around there okay
[Music]
it's it's giving me a tour like a
private tour pretty cool
thank you dear ghost for taking your
time to lead me around your beautiful
home
i can't take it so too bad appears to be
dull from extensive heels wow
okay we're almost there
i think please stay with me my friends
for a little more moment
wait i can't go there
did i miss something oh no okay okay
okay okay i'll keep on moving kiana
[Music]
what disrupt what dropped
human brain calling blame
[Music]
i have to go back
what is this where am i what the [\h__\h]
okay we're running i think we're writing
my friends yep uh i don't have time to
read a [\h__\h] journal
i asked
[Laughter]
okay uh no problem we can do that again
i missed i missed the ad but inside
where am i supposed to go
here we go again i think we're gonna do
this a bunch of times my friends
i can't move i can't move i can't move
why can't i move
did i disable the movement buttons
i can't click anything
oh there we go okay weird
okay here we go again where where here
yep probably
follow the flood when you're being
checked okay
okay okay follow the blood flow that the
blood flow of the blood follow the blood
break the journal it's lit what it's
okay you even have time to write
anything at all in that moment
what the hell follow the blood follow up
no
wait a second oops
wait what was i supposed to do there
wait wait wait wait wait the music is so
intense it's so scary
are you winning i'm not winning nothing
about this is winning
journalists on the journal oh am i even
allowed to read the whole thing
yeah it felt a little bit like that
okay okay okay okay here we go again
hello there's no no reason to be scared
this is cool this is
okay this is okay but the the
the tip with the blood was a very good
tip thank you very much thank you
uh wait wait what where here okay let's
run
running running rates journal i have
little time to write the master summa
returned and attacked me with something
something that stole my breath and
chilled my blood the spirit flew at me
when i shown my flashlight in the
monster direction
wait what what is it telling me to do
is he telling me to turn this flashlight
at it
yeah okay
dodged a bullet my friends friends i
dodged it
so wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait a second
what do i do what do i do what do i do
keep running but wait there was no other
way to run unless i i go a different way
go for the door with the sparks don't
look at it
the door with the sparks
hide behind the globe
gonna grow what grandpa what try around
as fast as you can if i don't think
you're supposed okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
open the [\h__\h] door
open it right
thank you run run run run run run run
run
run why does it sometimes get slower
where does it slow down
high behind the globe hide behind the
glove this is what i'm supposed to do
oh it's coming though holy [\h__\h] hello
oh i didn't write the monster spirit
struck a glass orb
and seemed to awaken it somehow my path
opened but i'm still being
awesome
what's next okay what what
what what what holy [\h__\h] what
okay i think we're running out of the
manor now um
we're just running now probably trying
to get out of
there's here [\h__\h] earthquake or
something oh god oh god
oh god oh ha ha ha ha where did i come
from where is that
get out i'm trying to get out give me a
break
huh where is it opening here okay
okay okay you got it open all of these
things
open it open it
was there specific um yep
okay yep okay specific order okay no
problem no problem no problem we got it
my friends
just saving in between oh my god
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] oh okay
we're having a boss fight or something
what's going on what the [\h__\h] is going
on
oh there's a door did i come from the
door didn't i come from that door i
think i came from that
no wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait this is what we do this is what we
do right do we do the same thing again
yes
why we're here only to suffer
okay cool uh yeah looks easy thank you
i'm a ballerina
in the previous life i was a ballerina
so this is no problem for me
what the hell what the
[Applause]
on books yeah yeah it seems realistic
holy [\h__\h]
wait wait wait wait wait where do i go
where do i go
where do i go i'm gonna die here now am
i i'm probably gonna die now
oh my god eh no sorry the monster is
following all the way back to the
entryway i do not know how this will end
up but i must see through
can we just accept our death i'm okay i
want to meet callie
i'm okay with that wait i don't know i
really don't know what i'm wait wait
wait wait
what about this do i have to do
something here
no okay uh do i go upstairs
so sometimes it just doesn't move the
way i want it should i keep on looking
at it
where's my guy going
[Music]
oh god oh god
where am i going where am i going wait
there's nothing here
do i go into a room nope
find the globe there's a globe right
there
where's the girl
[Music]
oh my god open the door
what's cool it's floating around them in
oh how did i get it does it come over
here
i'll guess i'm supposed to hold it there
and then like have it as a shield or
something
where are we where are we where is this
where are we starting okay here okay
perfect
okay i see the globe now i see it i see
it we run out there
and get it from one side and then we
hold it i guess
and then i don't know what exactly what
we're gonna dodge it
thank you looking for the top thank you
take it take it how do i take it
what so that it should
that shoes at me in the moment where
where where the globe is in front of me
i tried to do that it wasn't wasn't that
what we were doing
to reflect okay okay i thought i was
doing that but i guess the timing was
not exactly right
okay no problem no problem no forever i
figured it out
you think you can fool me or something
i know what game you're playing this is
actually not a puzzle game nor a horror
game this is actually
a rhythm game this is actually a rhythm
game
i figured it out always has been
a rebound game okay now come on [\h__\h]
no ah not now now
no no no no no no no no no
no shoot me god damn it
shoot me wait wait the timing is off
shook me now [\h__\h]
nope okay how about now
i think that's done
wasn't that it oh god we're almost dead
guys
how what now don't kill me
try the other side okay
[Applause]
[Music]
right why do you not run faster
oh god how about you shoot that thing
actually maybe it should
should you should we maybe open that can
we do that
oh god hello
almost almost
almost oh no please
didn't that work now how about now
it looks like it's working but then
again not
it i gotta jump
but there's no jump button in this game
[Music]
jump as in walk off the ledge okay
but then i did that before i just fell
down
okay height
that wasn't it that wasn't it
when you move to the side it throws the
aim off
i'll pop the thumbs on i know
wait i don't understand has to be
directed to the to
the to the okay okay okay that is a bit
weird but okay you should
ouchy hey
no
this is a bit difficult to
20 minutes
close okay am i doing this
right i
no really that wasn't it
okay stay still
before
[Music]
oh it's not over there it's over there
now okay no problem no problem no
problem one thing i mean
okay i understand i understand what i'm
doing i know what i'm doing
uh oh god
[Music]
protect me
yeah okay i think oh
not timing it's quite right no no no oh
okay okay
this feels like in junior high school
with all the ball games nobody wanna be
in their [\h__\h] team
but i was the best at dodging
so i was always even though nobody
wanted me in their team i was always the
last one to stand on the field
and then everyone would throw the ball
at me yay
come on buy your food
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
actually i don't have to be the sad face
anymore now
i'm feeling much better about this
hey is the game done
korea korea easyclap
oh
hello are we still not done here are you
[\h__\h] kidding me
you're telling me we're still not done
part two what oh
i turned in um
that's another whole level of creepy the
end
eh
what did we take from that what happened
that is that a bad ending
or is there only one ending is it a
happy ending is it a bad ending
it's a bad ending
there's a bad ending are you for real
or is that just how horror games end the
the ending is that i always have been
thank you for the super chats i always
have been um
uh a golden sexy doll
mannequin that you can play around with
always ask
i wonder if there's really different
endings or if you guys are just like
trolling me um
gold this is the golden goggle
this is the golden juggle now
amelia keeps giving up
wait now it don't make
sense emilia has been
giving away golden yackles
in a bunch of our collaborations
and we have seen seen syringes
in this craven manor
maybe emilia watson's real name
is emilia craven
what
amelia
amelia says conspiracy
theory the pluck duck
the blood thickens
well my friends i hope you all had a
happy halloween
this was my first horror game i must say
um
according to the reviews
it wasn't as scary as i thought it would
be
but i like that it's a combined like
uh puzzles with it that was pretty cool
happy halloween everyone
and i cannot promise you
that there will be many more horror
games in the future actually i mean
actually tomorrow we're playing a horror
game and next week it seems like i'm
also playing two horror games
i don't know why this is happening
we are actually um playing fasmophobia
next week
which i think i'm guessing will be
scarier
than this game but i guess it was like a
good
like warm-up into um
scarier hurricanes but let me tell you
after i'm done with these collaborations
where i have to play horror games
i will not play them again until you
guys force me into it to do it
and tomorrow we're also playing a horror
game with all five hello en members
[Music]
we're streaming on all channels at the
same time at 1pm japanese standard time
and i will not tell you yet which game
it is although you probably will
see it soon because i'm probably gonna
reserve the stream um
and then prob as i said next week i'm
going to play fasmophobia with a few
certain members and
and probably going to play a horror game
with maddin if i'm not already
sick of horror games by that time
yep
it's been amelia's mainer very much fun
on this the scariness skill i must say i
was just generally expecting
it to be more scary that that was
probably why i was so
chickening out in the beginning
but it wasn't even that bad actually i
wanted i wish it would have been a bit
scarier than that maybe even
but at the same time i hate horror games
so much
so much yeah it's uh i think it's
kali gura and me i thought idon was
joining too i think ina is joining to
to be honest for the phasmophobia collab
i saw kelly's schedule and she uh maybe
forgot anna but i think inna is
participating
yeah because it's a maximum four players
game i think
so yeah i think we did it so that um
this time i can join so amelia is
actually sitting this one out i think so
inna is actually supposed to join as
well i think kelly just forgot to wrote
that in her schedule
it's very scary looking forward to it
but at least
uh vessel phobia will be at the time of
day for me where it's not
night it will be in the middle of the
day so that's me that makes it a little
bit less scary and
cali will be with me not in person but
she'll be there so that will make me
feel much much better
also thanks for the red super chat again
a few minutes ago
thank you for your support today i will
read the
the super chats of this stream um
should i read them now or should i read
them another time it's probably
wait a second probably not that much
we could probably do it quickly you want
me to read the super chat now
we can do that trick or treat ah
actually no i ran out of treats uh
since i did one spontaneous one
yesterday the
the crane game one was a spontaneous one
where i already showed my last
three not my last week my last street
was today in the
in the stream before this one so
actually uh
i don't have any treats for you
i ran out of treats i can show you a
different treat
if you're up for it should i do you want
to see
a special treat yeah
okay
i have a few tweets one is this
look at it look at those hips
mmm that's better than any treat in the
world
right oh yeah and then that treat oh
yeah but there's one treat
that is better than every other treat
one second
the best treat for halloween
yap buddy
this one happy halloween
trick or treat
it has been a while since i've uh pulled
out my chicken legs
that's been a while since i showed you
my chicken legs
my chicken wings
i got wings these are my wings you want
to touch them
you can't they're mine get my dinner for
tonight because i haven't eaten anything
besides breakfast today
happy halloween now we shall move over
two not that one no no no no
to this one
hey are you ready for some super chat
reading let me play some bdm
i'm actually quite relieved it was much
less
scarier than i expected i'm really
relieved
anxious
trick or treat thank you
let me cut out those super jets
one second please
hope you enjoyed the stream my first
horror game stream
hope it was not uh too frustrating
because i just don't understand these
kind of games
i think like many many horror games work
like this
i've seen uh like wasn't there
a certain um
a 3d vr horror game that
for example piccolo senpai also played i
think where there's also like this
this weird doll following you in the
exact same way
and you have to i don't know if it was
like you have to look at it or you don't
have to look at it
i i think you had to look at it
there was a game like that
ah emily wants to play yeah so
that seemed kind of familiar to me maybe
that's uh how many of these horror games
just
work by any chance is that is that the
case
um so yeah since that was my first one i
just had to understand it first
play it please is that a vr only
is that a vr only i don't have a vr but
i guess maybe at the studio they have it
but if i ever have those glasses those
vr
glasses on them you can't really see my
face like it won't move
most horror games rely on stealth yeah
it seems so
seems so can you speak in a british
accent
of course lavalay
no please no okay let me read the silver
chats from today's
stream and everyone who wants to leave
thank you for watching today i hope you
enjoyed it
thank you for chatting um british
chicken
are you reading super chato oh yes
oh yes
the ending that the boss fight thing
reminded me of a netflix series
what was it called again uh the one
where they all have some
powers where there's recently a second
season came out
and the ending of the first season
reminded me so much
of what just happened
umbrella academy yeah yeah yeah yeah
exactly oh thank you for the super chat
did y'all watch at umbrella academy i
thought that ending of the first season
was uh a bit ridiculous
it just went way too crazy
but uh actually what happened in the
second season at the end i thought i
feel like
on the ending of the second season also
like went absolutely like crazy
yeah but
the endings of both seasons i didn't
really enjoy that much but
the whole series in itself i did enjoy
you should watch it if you haven't yet
it's on netflix
umbrella academy for the ones who saw it
don't you
feel like the ending of the first season
looked like
the ending of this horror game just now
like that the one with the violin the
ending with the violin
you know not trying to spoil it but yeah
right
it was so dramatic everything exploding
and burning and that power like
woof
for it pretends to know it nots
anyway uh i love refrigerators thank
take a shot every time kiana screams did
anyone do that
drinking game take a shot every time
kiara screams
you must have already gotten pretty
drunk in the beginning and later on it
was more like laughing
they're dead well i'm sorry i told you
don't drink alcohol
thank you thank you so much for your
support
and b gamer free 11
think of it this week yeah this is
finally a chance to prove once and for
all that you are not a chicken you don't
want to pass this opportunity up
i think i've proven that i'm not a
chicken
many times before but especially today
right i didn't really
i was very brave no
no but the [\h__\h] alone
that i chose on my own to play a horror
game for you guys on halloween without
anyone forcing me
that fact alone proves that i am brave
i think that makes sense jake it's
monkey dank assurance like other than
sanji not a good user named ventus wolf
crest thank you
so much
i like how people started to super chat
a shout counter but you probably
had to stop at some point in between
because
yeah you probably didn't go through with
it until the end
because otherwise i must have made a
million today
you lost count
not enough money for that to keep it up
so gundam paperbacks
ice cream counter not possible to keep
up that was early
you only went up to two wait there's
like a really tiny red spider like right
in front of me what do these red tiny
super tiny i want to kill you oh i did
something with the chat window
i full full windowed full screen still
chat window hi
how did i get out of there and how do i
make it normal again
how do i fix the chat window
oh god f11 i don't think i pressed f11
okay actually that did the trick thank
you
just tried to kill a spider and this
happens
this is what happens
ah i don't think i killed it
i missed the i missed my aim
paperbacks thank you i'll be the
dunkishan foggle bjorn but thank you
gum late night thank you and trick or
treat
i was just wondering if you saw my tweet
which would which tweet
i pretty much i feel like i pretty much
check every single reply that i get
even if i wake up and i wake up to 500
replies i pretty much read all of them
probably saw it but if you don't if you
don't tell me what it is about then it's
hard to
hard to guess
that sounds inhuman a little bit yes
you are the jump scare thank you
side quest
a minecraft screenshot uh was it the one
teaching me how to
throw the eggs i think i saved that one
anyway but i don't know if i'm gonna do
that i want to throw the x by myself
i don't want everything to be automatic
a lot of chicken i don't think i saw
that
ah oh no i did see that i stay i did see
some weird chicken
and juice me too me too
you
[Music]
meaning of my name poor buddha i hear
from
oh thank you
mario alvarez zelos wilder wilder thank
you
julian jule thank you
your screams scare me more than the game
i like it happy halloween
thank you you're welcome
thank you for always going the extra
mile for us and trying new things i hope
to catch more of your streams thank you
you're welcome
i mean horror games yeah but i think one
game
and one one genre that i will never try
because i just have
zero interest is fps games
horror games i mean it's kind of funny i
i understand
like the charm of it a little bit
and it's funny for like times like
halloween or like a
like a punishment game but
fps no never
sorry
i understand that's not mine that's not
my type of genre
i would be horrible and i don't think i
would enjoy it
um he talks
she doesn't need me she doesn't need me
to play
fps games
i also absolutely don't enjoy the first
person in minecraft
i wish i could just play in first person
forever
anyway
ah thank you for that thank you for the
tip thank you for the advice by the way
i don't know what i have what i would
have done without you
dan kishin viva la chiara danke shin
dante ldh dankeshan oh by the way i did
make the
spa base division oh i can't wait i
can't wait
i can't wait to go to the spa with cali
i reserved a really really expensive
massage
and i could have i could have asked it
to be in the same room
but i i specifically asked for two
different rooms okay
ahoy
i i asked for two different rooms okay
yeah cause you're probably gonna be
pretty naked
i'm respectful in that way yeah yeah
it's more it's more about me not wanting
me not wanting her to see me naked i
don't mind seeing her naked
but i don't want her to see me naked
[Music]
also thank you for joining the
membership hydration check thank you
okay i barely drank any water thank you
oh
this time ice water with some nice
strawberry strawberries mixed with
veggies checking because you're sounding
kind of raised
don't know what you're talking about
obama would you guys notice any
any difference at all in um
the i don't know the
way my voice sounds like like in like
microphone wise
audio wise
probably not right it's true probably
too little of a difference
really like compared to like yesterday's
stream or something
because i did change something
[Music]
really um small i guess
like i'm using the sure sm7b
and on the back side of it there's like
something i don't know how you call it
but you can like change something there
i don't understand it but apparently it
changes the way
i don't know i i can't explain it at all
no it's not a noise bubble turn no no no
no i don't know how
hard what no it's also not the gain
control
pickup pattern probably something like
that
face roll up i think something like that
something like that i i switched
something
um high pass filter
could be so i wonder if it change if it
sounds
i tried to record myself and compare it
and i think i heard a slight difference
but probably not that big of a
difference
i'm still not 100 happy with what i'm
hearing you know i wanna
i wanna sound like amelia i want to
sound as clear and beautiful as amelia
i wonder i wonder how she can sound so
nice
you can definitely hear it really but to
why when are you comparing it
to what stream to like one month ago
or recently see i don't know
i think amy told me before which mic
she's using but i don't remember
my current microphone is like really
expensive
and i even bought the cloud lifter so
my equipment is expensive i would expect
it to be
good now but i don't know
i don't even know what sounds good
anymore i only know that amelia
sounds amazing
it sounds like her mic is just better
than mine
i don't know what it is i don't know
what it is
my audio is nice okay well thank god
i feel your pain when it comes to
dodgeball when you're the best at
dodging even your own teammates want to
throw them at you
no no that's a bit different
that's a bit different from what i was
trying to say
i hope you're okay thank you
you did well despite it being your first
horror game so proud of you thank you
i feel like i did so bad i feel like
really i didn't do a good job
hey where was i hope you have a happy
halloween can i try not to get any
spooked any oh actually it's halloween i
should be eating chocolate what the hell
halloween
everyone get your snacks
i'm gonna eat my german chocolate
that i bought for
dollars because it's imported and
expensive but it's the best
it's worth it
oh
hmm
seven zero seven zero
dollars
[Music]
bueno
um
happy halloween
no no no i bought like a like a lot a
lot of chocolate
but still it's a bit more expensive than
telling my japanese bros to go get the
same chocolate as i
bought
best chocolate
russian name i cannot read let me
actually try to get this one for once uh
on google translate
google translate
here we have a russian name
russian rosia
why is my ghouler japanese anyway ah
andre or andre andre
or seroff
thank you jkh monkey danke shane
congrats i'm beating the game kiara
thanks for facing your fears and trying
out the horror game for halloween
thank you honestly i was really really
not looking forward to this
but it had to be done and it wasn't it
really wasn't that bad i was just
much more scared of what could happen
then of what actually happened
[Music]
okay
yeah everyone keep on spamming the
dunkishans
monkeytank
mr maniac nice profile picture by the
way
exposed by tantrum herself
i feel like it made a lot of sense
[Music]
60 times which was less than my hundred
bet oh
good job on playing a horror game even
when you were so afraid to do so from
the side
thank you you guys are so sweet
you guys are so adorable you look at
congratulations on beating the game
here's your hug for completing the game
good job attention on your first horror
game you did great happy halloween thank
you
zero five six zero then kfp inventory
report screen counter 61 screams are
unofficial and subject to observer
official report available later
thank you thank you to elemental 98
james mcphee
how much more scarier is phasmophobia
than
this game
like if this game on a scale of 1 200
was only like 30
a lot oh [\h__\h]
i'm gonna be screaming a lot
but like it's a if you play it with four
people are we like a team
and you try to solve something together
so i can just
be behind my friends and let them solve
everything
okay thank god it's a team game okay
awesome
i just stay behind cali and and then
i'll just
have her protect me
all right it sounds good to me
cyrex
steam powered twist thank you jacqueline
duncan bikini
no duncan thank you
your streams are a highlight of waking
up these days can't wait for all these
spooky streams so we can see our
i can i can't i can't wait for it but
thank you i hope you're gonna enjoy them
at least one of us has to be be enjoying
them
thank you very cute stream thanks for
hanging in there it was fun thank you
for watching this ridiculously horrible
stream
thank you
[Music]
to bring up a depressing topic
my mom passed away a week ago oh [\h__\h]
i'm sorry about that just wanted to say
that watching your streams have helped
me put a smile on my face in these sad
times oh my i don't know i don't know
how
how that is even possible
um if it's only been a week
but i i hope i can take uh your mind off
of it
every now and then um
i could not imagine how you must feel
but i hope
i hope
you can find some some happiness for my
streams
so i will continue streaming so that you
have something
to check out every day on youtube to
cheer up every now and then
thank you with that i shall refresh my
super chats and that should be the end
of it
one second to the caution she
uh so must we are also don't worry about
bringing it up i'm i'm glad i can help
thanks for
letting me in on on your feelings and
emotions
register as dankeshen wilson 97 dance
congratulations on completing your first
hurricane and happy halloween brave
phoenix thank you so much
i i feel like i've accomplished
something you guys
took my first time
yeah you took my horror game virginity
just like you took my minecraft
virginity
you now have taken my horror game
and i don't understand why you guys get
so crazy about the phrasing in this one
especially when i tweeted that about
minecraft
weeks ago i don't understand
literally every reply was a
freezing chiada and i'm just like
it's just how it is
i was a minecraft virgin now i'm not
anymore
i was a horror game virgin now i'm not
it's just how it is
[Music]
thank you for your support and thank you
for your generous donation
maximus solar potato
[Music]
i can't read your name but i may be just
soon
thank you
what does that say again the first one
is wool and the last one is knee
and the middle
is it whiny probably not right
ah close enough we'll
see who are me
you like me say
what what's going on beetle anyway
potato thank you
mtk
crispy
thank you for watching my stream i see
the real phoenix today
yes i am a real phoenix
rock m zero zero one thank you and judas
thank you
patrick chen danke shin wrangle station
dan kashan happy halloween
oh here's a language i cannot understand
so i shall not read it but
it's something like gracias por el
stream
me diverti mucha
but i don't want to read anything maybe
it's my instincts are right
seems like doesn't say anything bad
latino americanos
i understand i understand
gracias muchas gracias
e i think i understand
riddle thank you thanks for this fun
stream and extra treat after what you're
welcome
my english is not good but i like you
very much your life is very warm thank
you for hard work
thank you thank you
mrs worldwide that's right that's me
i actually can't taste the difference of
different chocolate brands
please don't hate my taste buds please
don't hate me my taste buds are just
defective
it seems so because every chocolate
tastes so different
also especially like depending on
which which country the taste
of chocolate will be so different
i don't understand how it can taste all
the same to you but okay
[Music]
okay last time refreshing
let's see what we got in the last
refreshing there we go
patrick
noob ptfo dan kashin
actually wasn't there never mind
me and my sisters enjoy your streams
also how's the fairytale series oh
any fairy tales in mind yeah i will read
all of the
all of the grimm's fairy tales you know
the really scary
german ones and i will read them in
german and will not it will not be a
stream because
i will read them in german and then i
will subtitle them
in english
so i have to do it as a video
it will be a pain in the ass because
those fairy tales are pretty long
and subtitling that will be a bit
annoying but
i'm working on it and somebody uh
actually i was gonna commission someone
that's why i did a shout out
on on twitter i was just looking for
artists but then
um some people just started drawing
without even like me giving them money
and uh a certain someone is trying
something really nice right now
so i feel a bit bad for like just just
taking it for free but
uh okay
i'm looking forward to that so once we
have a background
i want like a um
yeah i was going to pay for people what
i was going no i was going to pay people
for out
no it's not yoona this time i'm looking
for like a specific
room and yoona is already doing some
other stuff for me
she's too busy
freezing yeah um
but there will definitely be crack of
course credits
i was i was ready to pay though
but i'm also um for the talk show
for the talk show i've been
commissioning a lot of stuff i've been
commissioning a logo which is basically
done i just have to choose one
because i have a a lot of
choice right now for those
logos and i asked my i asked the other
members
and everyone says something different i
don't know what you want to go for
i wish i could let you guys choose but i
don't want you to see it until it's
decided
but it's a really fancy really fancy
logo
and then i also commissioned a whole
like 3d rendered room
that looks like you know like a typical
late night
tv show but
uh made for me
just made for me uh with like a
comfy couch and my hosting table and all
that
it's gonna look amazing and i also
commissioned two two
tracks and that's basically the last
thing i'm waiting for right now for the
tracks for the music tracks
yes i'm excited
so the first talk show should be
happening
probably in the third week of
november i think probably
yeah i think so and
still deciding on the first guest
as well and uh and which day and what
time oh
i'm probably gonna put put out the uh
a poll or something on my community tab
or on twitter i'm not sure
probably better to do it on the youtube
community tab and to ask you guys what
time frame would be the best
and also considering that probably
since it's mainly gonna be a japanese
interview that i'll be
translating to english um
probably there will also be a lot of
japanese people watching so it's
probably
also always going to be uh
in my usually time slot like in the
evening time
no i'm only i i'm gonna clear this up
right now i'm only doing whole lifetimes
because i want you guys
to get a deeper understanding of the
japanese especially
japanese hollow life talents that you
are that up until now
most of you uh we're not able to
understand hundred percent
except for those of you who speak
japanese
but it's i'm basically doing this for
the
fan base that speaks english mainly
or any other language but japanese so
the ones that are we're only able to
understand
uh the japanese talents on like a
superficial
basis you know on a superficial level
so i want to like get some deep deep
knowledge other than some cheap stories
you know
and i'm gonna translate them for you but
also since it's a japanese
uh side of whole life there's probably
gonna be a lot of japanese viewers as
well so
probably gonna be in a japanese prime
time slot
and probably two times a month or maybe
eventually sometimes i might skip it's
one
one time to do a different collab every
now and then it's hawk show fun
thank you thank you thank you thank you
i'm only getting
the bestest of the best
to make my logo my music and everything
thank you thank you i'm really looking
forward to it i hope i hope it will go
well i will try my best to plan it
really well also amelia is helping me to
work on some kind of intro video as well
so that's really cool too
cause emilia is really good with that
stuff i really like the the video that
she did in that taxi
if you guys remember that i really like
that one
so i asked her i asked her if she could
do something similar for me
yeah i i did mention doing whole stars
as well
i i am still like open to that but first
to me the priority
is the whole life japan girls
and then later on eventually if i like
run out of them
then i can move on to hollow stars but
then by then probably there will be new
generations of holo life japan so
i'm gonna mix it up at that point and
but mostly to me i'm just a huge fan of
whole life japan for the most part
but i will mix it up it will not only be
whole life japan
not only but first of all i'm aiming for
for the um talents that have been around
for a long
time yes yes yes anyway i'm pretty much
done with the super chat reading um
looking for the top thank you
didn't you say you were leaving in a
different super chat
thank you for coming back
ptfo kishon and mudadan kashin
and i am not creative thank you shane
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
it will be a very well made investment
i hope you're gonna watch the first talk
show
toki no solar interview oh yes
definitely one day if she
would allow me to have her on my show
but
i'm a bit too shy to ask her to be the
first guest
i'm probably gonna ask someone who i
already had like contact with
up until now um
and i think that's it
did i read all of them
i think i did
uh polka no no no no i won one of the
older generations first
because they have more to tell you know
the the most recent generation
will be very very very late i want them
with
uh i want those with more experience
thank you yaga for your confirmation
yes subaru would probably be a good idea
probably but we have to chill in that
collaboration i know when when the whole
birds come together
we go absolutely batshit crazy
but in the interview we have to be
serious
fun is loud but we have to be mostly
i know she would probably not turn it
down but for the very first
uh talk show that i'm doing i i think i
i don't want to mess it up
so i i want to go with someone who i
already talked to before
yeah try so loud first don't be shy no
no no it's the first one i'm like scared
of messing up
so i gotta go for someone who
yeah who i feel more who i feel more
comfortable with and who also the guests
would feel more comfortable with me you
know what i mean
um
anyway that's it for today and we're in
november now holy [\h__\h]
thank you guys for supporting me and
how long has it been now
almost wait is it like two months now
almost almost two months
no i mean like generally about two
months right
almost almost oh
wow wow thank you for supporting me
thank you for coming to today's stream
don't miss uh the whole live in full
members collab
at one o'clock and i think i'm probably
gonna take monday off because it's been
a bit of an exhausting week for me
um i know monday usually everyone else
takes off and
i try to fill up monday because everyone
else is sleeping on monday for some
reason so i tried to stream
but i think i gotta take monday off
yeah yep
i think this this time monday will not
be chiara day
unless i decide to do a crazy gorilla
thank you everyone and in german we say
in german we say
[Music]
bye
subscribing
[Music]
do
down
so