[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
already switched oh you did
this now oh you're kidding me
no you don't have to say okay
who is that who's this okay
who are you is it Baba Kiara again
popular
[Laughter]
I didn't know we were playing Among Us
I think we are done because it's kind of
it feels it feels like I'm intruding on
a knee Gene girls collab maybe did
someone get sick and I have to come in
no no
you know what you know what no I I have
a bone to pick with all of you I sent
you all a tick tock this morning in our
group chat oh yeah nobody said haha Nina
This Is Us
and yeah I didn't even watch sorry Nina
looks easy I don't want you either to be
honest but I'll get to it okay my
parents did the same thing they sent me
like tick tocks and it takes me like
five days to lie to them I don't even
have tick tock
wow Nina's out zoomering everybody I've
never like been on Tick Tock it's only
when people send me like Tick Tock links
never been yeah yeah
thank you girls
I I feel amazing anyway Sports how how
is everybody else doing huh welcome to
this collaboration we organized Nina put
it together yeah
yeah
it's not streaming
you honestly just want to hang out with
the girlies
oh should we introduce ourselves yeah
yeah well where do we start from
first
[Laughter]
I was the first to admit it and made it
easier for the others to admit it true I
know I'm not afraid to disappoint Nina
ever wait we're gonna do a voice voice
like uh volume check as well while doing
this and my view is already telling me
Nina is low so I'm raising her don't
worry I've never had anyone tell me that
before
I guess from Whole Life English uh I am
intruding today on this lovely cute
collab with these girls I'm so happy I
put a lot of cuteness into the thumbnail
I think it kind of looks like a purikura
thumbnail yeah
yes I look like yeah every time I take
pretty cool
we took
[Laughter]
yeah
yes one time I asked roseme and rainbow
to take a break with me and they said
later and we never know
um
everyone under the bus today everyone
will pay it's just airing all this dirty
lunch
it's just so we said we'll come back and
then we forgot or something I have one
question girls
are you playing uh Uno with controller
now or with keyboard and mouse you can
play with controller I don't know you
can play controller either yeah that's
how I think I used to play and now I
don't know how to jump so hard but the
jump in button is for keyboard I think
it's w maybe but yeah it's gonna say it
on the screen it's gonna be like press
yeah W or e or something yeah do you win
a lot playing with controller
uh tilt controls
maybe try changing the Boston keyboard
no that cannot possibly be the reason no
no no anyway I'm gonna throw the the
button of itself introduction over to
Rosemary
yeah okay uh
okay wait I'm nervous
um
hi everyone I'm resmi
Rosemary The Rock to me I
back if if there were an actor who would
play me in real life it would be the
rock I believe that 100
me too me too
um
I mean I have don't you remember
I just wanted to see you again
[Music]
I missed out on a precious moment sounds
worse than it is yeah I can hear how shy
you are in your voice I can hear you
like being beat red I was just taking
the back I was like
[Laughter]
you know I told that um story actually
on my stream before yes
I feel like that's all you'll ever think
about now maybe I should
she's never gonna show you her underwear
again
you better have ingrained it in your
memory
[Laughter]
every little ruffle every little ribbon
yes yes
memories
[Laughter]
it was really cute it was really cute
can we go to the next intro
how is the volume for everybody so far
you guys yeah
don't tell us it was quiet who's loud
yeah
for the streamers we will say William
good it was me a little low okay
I love you I had you a little down
actually so
audio good nice
nice
oh nice
probably did no yeah I gave her the yeah
I give it to you Puma okay
I'm Polo
need to send it and first wave
if an actor were to play me it would be
Jack Black
I like how we made that a thing
you are not Polo what because
that is as uh blonde right now I thought
I was meeting uh oh yeah silver-haired
girl today what the hell oh I am I'm I'm
you know I'm a silver fox you know uh
more foxy than the other Fox the actual
fox that's here yeah that looks more
like a cat as long as that makes you
happy
well I'm a silver fox I'm looking at the
screen and I think we're all a bunch of
little gray people
is it the actual silver fox
I'm Gray
yeah you don't have a profile picture
I was not on board I did not understand
okay
we're catching my jokes when they flop
thanks by the way for buying me Uno oh
yeah
welcome did you see my message with it
no
oh my God even though I had it on my
Xbox
you have Uno everybody
we were scammed both me and Nina we had
to buy it a second time
I have to say this really quietly
like every few months I buy Uno again
and again on both my Steam account and I
genuinely feel like I've bought Uno 6 or
seven times already yeah I don't
understand where my Uno game is going
why am I pretty foreign
[Laughter]
and like I don't understand where my Uno
games are going
agreed okay Grandma sounds like you're
losing your Uno every time
oh I think Mr bigger note is on to me I
think he's doing it on purpose he's
trying to rob me of my money Mr John Uno
you the game is called Uno you can't
just buy it once you know
hey
get it yeah get it because Uno is one
yeah yeah do you understand what wow
well next by dos
I'm so sorry everyone
uh okay is it my turn yeah yes it is hi
honey
don't change
a little tone change hi honey I am Nina
kosaka of niji Sanji Ian's third wave
etherea and I must be in luck today
hello everybody it's a pleasure to be
here with you
um I am excited I organize this collab
because I want to hang out with the cute
girls I already opened up some wine I'm
having a nice glass and I'm ready for
all the embarrassing batsuits and all
the fun times yeah
who is she
it's too powerful you know I try not to
eat this
yeah the whole atmosphere changed
it's fine it's fine I guess I can stay a
little cute but I will have a list of
batsu games on the batso wheel I'm not
showing it on screen but there is
um the famous good old baby voice the
grandma police the robot voice like I am
robot let's talk like this could you
demonstrate the other two voices the
first two oh yeah
in the park
boys yes and British accent and okay
singing while talking and then yeah
after every sentence
let's go
oh that's it yeah okay yeah I like it
there's some laughter screams after
stream ones too right we have to get a
couple off the stream ones that we can
do oh yeah I really want you to lose now
Kiara I'm sorry no she's Flawless and
everything she does except this game
clearly she just told us how much
because someone calls Uno uh we will see
who has the most cards left after at the
at that point when the game is over
where's the um
we'll have to do about the game okay
okay fine
yes no matter how long you I want you
girls to be committed okay oh yeah okay
it's about drive it's about power
yeah
I'm very nervous what is seven zero what
is that uh you when you have a seven you
switch cards with the person of your
choice zero it goes oh it's the whole
board yeah oh okay okay
maybe we waited in the lobby for too
long
what do you do I just quit yeah okay
okay
I think maybe like I said the lobby was
off for too long I have game audio
either
oh
you can't argue with the people
[Laughter]
I'm not afraid
I'm Not Afraid hit me hit
oh my gosh
she really loves that bottle my wheel is
spinning it's gonna be oh wonderful a
British accent
my British accent is Pang in it what
absolutely pink oh my gosh the British
slang she knows no way boy
you know
what's a Peng it's like hot like if you
see a hot lady walking by you can say
ooh Peng or that's a pain
sounds like you're saying pain
I'm trying to join your game let me
reinvite you no I think it should it's
loading oh white bird oh wait I got it
Nina I'm already in your lobby
I'm going to reinvite you again
and now it's stuck on my screen
talking when we get into the game
so I don't know if you really like being
British be British all the time don't
let don't let Society tell you whether
you should be British or not
I want to hear British Nina
I love British
one with me
I think I'm learning it
play come on I want to play I wanna play
I wanna play
loading and it's still loading it's so
slow
now oh wait I think I'm in I think nice
don't crash don't crash anyone's game
oh we all in
um
my hair was so good last time oh my God
wait my hand is so nothing hello yeah
I couldn't even hear you on Discord is
it your Internet
no I don't think so I have oh I have
really good internet
Lobby okay
why do I want now talking in a British
accent oh my God I had the best hand too
I was ready to go out are we quitting oh
yes please join me did the bot just plus
two of me
okay I'll quit
wait Nina are you making the room again
please one of you make the room okay
because I got another invite from you
okay classic Uno it's not you
so we're doing the jump in the 7-0
and that's it
yeah I think that sounds good enough
right okay now we couldn't change Royals
later too okay okay I know there's like
a Teemo we can do like two V2s oh yeah
yeah
okay I invite you guys invite friend
uh we're not friends we're just
co-workers promo wait I can see you guys
oh invite the game invite the game but
since we are not co-workers are we
friends absolutely yeah absolutely
I'm friends with everyone except promo
that's true
can you
a friend of Pomo because everybody is
pomu
got you there Nina
um
I know I timed you out because you told
me you went into the chat and said
everybody spam
I said you are omitting the details
why did you do that would you like to
object yes objection
I said pomu is very cute today please
spam so it covers my text and she
doesn't see it
so yes I said please
[Laughter]
why would you compliment her if you
didn't want her to see it
Nina are you gonna join the game yeah
wait it's it's not it's like black
screening me I'm so sorry
Owen collab is betraying you
the worst part too is the only reason I
didn't check Uno is because I played Uno
like two or three months ago and
everything was fine yeah
attacked yeah Ubisoft is like
like you Nino yeah I will I will [\h__\h]
everything up for you now thanks Ubisoft
you'll get it
you'll just in case can you guys buy the
game on switch yeah okay
I have a feeling we might have to do the
switch Uno oh my God I don't even I
don't have my switch like set up to my
PC no that would take like two minutes
but um or yeah we can also play a Barbie
party no
listen I am a big fan of Mario party so
yeah
just because the the downloading okay
but yeah should be fun but let's let's
try this come on Ubisoft PC version
let's go come on come on it's it should
be loading now check this board real
quick
[Music]
um
I'm just buying Uno on the switch right
now
I don't even know if mine is set up
either
nice
should I go set it up like oh she's
playing Uno Nina
what I don't understand is previously it
opened Uno and now it's not even opening
yeah actually maybe Monopoly would work
right instead we would have to do one
player though yeah I mean
um
I love Monopoly wait what I only played
it a lot I played it for the first time
like a few weeks ago
I will play Monopoly with you but I only
have it on the switch
I just bought Uno on the switch
wait do you need to buy it
do you need to buy like Monopoly if one
person is well it might be different on
the switch it might work the only reason
we do one person on on PC is because
everybody else crashes every time
hold on I since y'all three are
streaming give me two minutes I don't
know why I'm just gonna reset my PC
sometimes that works you know sometimes
when things don't work so I will be
right back have you tried resetting your
PC generally I wasn't good I was gonna
suggest that but you know okay right
back
simultaneously I'm also setting up my
switch as we speak oh you know what I
should do that too she's a multitasking
girl not really but
these uh desperate times call for
desperate measures
Monopoly
Monopoly um wait oh yeah okay I already
have Uno on switch interestingly and I
have Monopoly on switch so I'm ready for
whatever let's bring it on baby
what is this let's see
Ian cursed yeah does the encourse apply
to ninja Sandy too it does
I think it is a widespread virus
I think I think I know what the cause is
though oh can I just say it yeah
that
all of us little shits do not test the
games before could that be could that be
cool so many times
it's not really uh
you know but then again the Ian curse
also happens so often that should be a
lesson to us to also test everything
then because if the encourse keeps on
reappearing and we should also test
things I'm also a culprint though oh she
was fast back
action that I organize huh
you know if anybody has any concerns
complaints or anything direct them to me
okay I should have checked the game and
I didn't so please no no no
where from now on I will triple check
every game even the ones that I played
like the day before
I promise Nina Nina Nina yeah yeah yeah
how long have you been in niji Sanji in
uh too long
sometimes I don't install a game until
15 minutes before stream
stop doing that I did that maybe
sometimes in my early days but I stopped
doing that I I installed at least a day
before you know the difference between
you and I is that you are what the
people call a professional
yeah no
yeah all right
okay I'm inviting you
is no longer we've broken the curse
Maybe
[Music]
yeah look at her she's like it stalled
the game early what's what's next wake
up before the scream starts
okay
looking promising
it's gonna switch my
eyes
oh
wait are we in
I'm in um
no way really I think she's messing
you're still there you're still there
though yeah oh no okay never mind she's
not there she's a robot
how about this how about this I can just
react to the robot and pretend it's me
playing
[Music]
the boxes of the robot loses
I just keep delaying the streets I have
Uno on switch ready to go yeah I can
download it right now if you want
I I seriously yeah where I just like
pretend to be the robot and if the robot
loses I do the batsu we could do that
while we wait for the game to download
on the switch yeah let's do that we can
like play something else or play it on
the switch it's up to you guys
whatever you guys wanted I just don't
want to make people wait you know I have
two Unos open right now
[Laughter]
let's go
I'm excited I'm playing with the robot I
got it I know I I know you made me skip
my turn
oh sorry
what are they gonna change it to no you
fool it's my turn it is I the AI green
[Laughter]
s
does everybody have to
more Uno and then download it or is it
just uh I think I have I'm downloading
it right now so yeah okay my switch is
all set up why not
oh Chihuahua left
oh in activity because
I'm not much of uh
it's just a normal one right it's like a
Ultimate Edition
code oh [\h__\h] okay
and okay well I'll hide this for a
moment my seconds
how is the bot winning what is going on
hey you just get my turn
Nina bot is too strong I know all right
I was like you know what the box because
then I'd win finally friends again
I could finally have a victory
I'm downloading Uno oh this is
The Click your Pearl pepper thank you
okay it's been a long time since I added
new Switch friends I don't I forgot it's
exciting
it's a new time yeah oh I'll add you
guys
I think uh only one of us has to add you
right because uh
so it's easier for you okay
now wait Nina am I friends with you or
yeah we are yeah
why is my Uno download so slow on the
switch why what is happening
yeah mine's gonna take a while guys I
don't know really mine's not even Well
mine's a little over half nine minutes
nine minutes
for all the Kiara fans this is something
new right piara
[Laughter]
here you see the behind the scenes now
we we're so we all got together so early
too we were ready yeah what happened
everything was set up yeah
oh I had to put in the wrong oh oh oh
sorry I'm putting in the friend code for
Nina yeah people on my chat are asking
if you verified your game files did you
try that I'm already friends with you oh
you did
Ian curses alive and well so true
it's just I'm telling y'all I have
bought Uno so many times every time you
have Uno that's why we shouldn't play
UNO anymore we should move on to
something even better which is Monopoly
Monopoly I say we play Monopoly because
okay if y'all want to I don't mind I
have eight minutes left on my Uno on
this list
what you can't say no it's three versus
one oh I'm fine with whatever I'm gaming
sorry and I'm eating my bread
to win her to be fair but I don't know
what's happening
you're
[Music]
yeah
this is the only Uno now this is the oh
or Monopoly Monopoly Monopoly
thank you by yourself
roseme's here too how dare you insult
her like that no no I'm Alex how can you
be playing all by yourself
no no no that was a real bad that was a
real
Monopoly on
switch right
yeah
um yeah okay okay wait so do I have to
buy it too yeah oh we're gonna have to
download it might still take some time
that's faster
okay wait I just need to confirm quick
Monopoly for Nintendo switch
49.99 Yeah
all right
on the PC and have one person like
control it like we did when someone I
played recently
wouldn't that be the easiest no I don't
no no I don't mind buying it I just
wanted to complain about the price
you know
two girls here downloading Uno at this
very moment yeah
yeah okay I just want everybody to
understand I will complain but I'll
still do it just you know
okay so in this Uno downloading waiting
time
we shall we shall talk yeah waiting room
maybe you guys should make your own
robot room so you can play your own who
knows robots listen Paul I'll help you
out I'm gonna make it so that you win
okay oh really
yeah
that's good that's good that's good
that's good no
[Laughter]
it's a boy so heated so excited I'm not
even playing I'm alone
okay
I don't know
laughs that's the only guy I was gonna
ask you a question Kiara since you're
here um how are you enjoying Metroid
hello oh my God I recommended yesterday
and I love Metroid Prime I am so happy
I'm so happy what jumping are you
playing
um I I recommend it but it was like um I
had a lot of fun with it in the middle
and up until the end when at the end the
met the the fishing metroids were
absolutely tilting me and and the last
two boss fights were also absolutely
tilting me but besides that it was a lot
of fun understandable
did you play the whole thing I played
Metroid Prime like over a decade ago
I didn't play the remastered I didn't
play yet oh well yeah I also just
remember like playing the game when I
was a child but I didn't really play it
I was just like on the screen running
around in the very place where you spawn
when you start the game because it was
too scary I wouldn't go anywhere
yeah I played I thought it was awesome I
was like oh my God this is like it was a
bit scary I do agree but I was like this
is so cool
I think your impression now would be
very different though you should play
old games that you played a million
years ago you should play them now and
see how they changed for you oh yeah I
used to be like that as a kid if like if
the game was too scary at the beginning
I just couldn't play it oh yeah yeah me
too
as many games that I like oh one camera
I thought was really scary when I was
young was um Final Fantasy VII I don't
like this game but the the overarching
like theme of the game was so scary to
me you know I know stuffy red was scary
but he was cool okay I saw something so
cursed today about Final Fantasy VII
that I can't believe is real
wasn't there recently a remake of Final
Fantasy VII yeah
um yeah yeah
yeah I saw a clip where the main
character what is his name Cloud
he gets seduced by her hand massage
person
I'm like this cannot be from the actual
game right because he's moaning he's
moaning and is this the kind of game
final fantasy is
it feels like I thought this was fan
made like yeah
so what
what
I I don't know processing I actually
don't even remember I remembered I think
that District that area
it is real it's like you get the choice
apparently between free massages one
where he's like you know I don't know
suffering having a bad experience but
anyway one of them is being like kind of
seduced from a pretty young lady you
know and a kimono and yeah when you log
into the thingy he's moaning sorry I
like interrupting you off oh my God
what is happening uh switchy oh 15
seconds I have one minute left on the
download
crashes
wait you have Uno on the switch
but yeah oh my God that's so I'm so
sorry for interrupting that that is such
a oh I feel like
imagine oh I don't know Final Fantasy is
a little funny oh Frozen me no I'm
actually playing by myself
homo we lost to the AI it was Kiara
would have had her win
okay now they're just bullying me I'm
good I'm leaving my my download's almost
done
when life imitates art wait what
the Hello Kitty oh my God
was downloading Rainbow Six Siege while
I was playing Uno
your download has not been complete I'm
like what download
into the Ubisoft account as well in this
switch version just one second
oh I have bad news you're gonna have to
re-log in to your YouTube yeah yeah oh
okay I remember it it's okay
I'll show you I'll show you guys
I guess
okay now none of us are playing with
Nelson keyboards so yeah
scaling isn't that exciting it's
controlling gaming we were on the same
level with the keyboard right
now we're on the same level of a
controller
I I'm using Joy cons I'm on tail
controls
I'll connect because when I play Mario
Kart with the wheel I always have to
move my body to move the wheel
into Ubisoft yeah maybe we got aim
assist now with them with controller
oh my God it's not touch what okay yeah
it takes ages to put it put it in man uh
wait what was that oh wait I don't
remember my email
welcome back Kiana home alive let's go
yeah okay wait do you oh Ubisoft connect
so you have to connect with that right
or do you have to or you have to I think
okay
doit.com
let me
oh wait why am I already logged okay
this is weird but I'm already in what
really do you have anything else on
switch maybe maybe I previously logged
on to like another Ubisoft game wow okay
invalid email or oh no thank you
I'm I'm Zelda oh
here I have a profile picture yes yes
hmm okay so let me set up my uh catch a
card then give me a second yum yum yum
yum
girls yes baby talk to me yeah it's like
early in the day for you girls I suppose
why did you eat so far oh I had chili
I think I have to make a new account
[Laughter]
can you not log into the same one
Froot Loops yum I had an
man
yeah I have a grocery store that has
anpan close to me
grocery store
actually it's like uh 9 p.m here but I
only had breakfast today no
no hey cook afterwards I'm a big cook
eat so you can grow big strong and Tall
baby so you can reinternate hungry right
now it's okay
as long as you're taking care of
yourself okay yeah
that's good
thank you for that question yeah
tomorrow is April the 1st so I'm making
the following pizza from Little Caesars
the the advertisements yes
why is it fake right I thought it was
real until people told me it was fake
so I decided because it's fake I decided
I'll just make it myself fine I'll block
myself oh my God yeah one time homo made
a durian Pizza by the way yeah I know
like what are you are you crazy I had
doriendo when I was recently in
Indonesia oh and I I expected it to be
really really yeah bye but they prepared
Frozen durian for me oh so that's what I
still kind of Frozen State and it was
like it was acceptable because of that I
heard it tastes really good I'm having
problems oh what's your problem baby it
won't let me make a new account because
the email is already in use but it won't
let me log in with that email
it's the same email right that you
logged into the Ubisoft on PC with right
maybe I'm joining through your thing oh
wait no no it's telling me to connect to
Ubisoft try it with me try it with the
Uplay account that you connected with or
do a password recess
what I did is I actually just retyped
like whenever you can type your email I
just type the same email that I had on
my yeah computer yeah that's what I'm
doing but it says yeah I promise not I'm
never gonna have another Uno collab
you know I remember one yeah we're just
chilling when my Jen first debuted we
had an UNO club and then one person kept
crashing and then we had another Uno
collab and a completely different person
kept crashing
these are moving on why oh no
okay so can I ask um because every time
I tell people who are in N A about corn
on Pizza they're like yeah that's so
weird I heard it's like a North uh
European thing like that happens a lot
in North Europe right corn corn
in all of Europe and and Japan but yeah
tuna when I say tuna and pizza as well I
get the same reaction from n a I've
never tried two they're like what two
numbers I guess it's more the tuna thing
actually listen Kiara people in an a
freak out over pineapple on Pizza I know
like they're not ready for the for the
tune on it's actually even that's not
even that like crazy because even in
Italy where the pizza comes from yeah
yeah
please try
okay it depends I feel like that they
make it really well it can be really
good otherwise it might be a bit like
weird but if they make it really well
then it's like not that yeah I have this
like um I have this like mental uh I
don't know what to call it like a mental
block so I used to work at a breakfast
restaurant you know that serves like two
eggs and bacon omelettes and I remember
one time somebody ordered a fish
omelette it was like an omelette with
salmon the restaurant smelled like fish
the whole day like I remember bringing
the plate to the old man and it just
stank like freaking guy about the first
time I ever hear about a fish omelette
yeah yeah it was a fish omelet
interesting yup I mean salmon is great
and all but
yeah I don't think I've ever had like a
fish on my before either I thought it
was an old guy right it was an old man
taste
yeah you get Peculiar tastes with age
Maybe
oh my god oh
he's still someone acceptable I think
okay
oh is she dying yeah just a little
tell us we can help you yeah yeah
okay for our collab Kiara set like
everything up did I yeah you're like
okay Nina do this click this for today
you're like okay
this this I'm like oh girl okay
that's the only things that I learned
from AMA anyway word not online Rosie
homo can you invite her it uh it won't
let me there's no invite for me
but I see you on my friends list Nina
and like
I'm so sorry
rosie no it's not what it looks like
Rosary stop AI Luna
how do we get out of this game remember
you are honorary wait Sanji we're gonna
adopt you there's no way for me to leave
the game how do I yeah
cogwheel at the top you either play or
die
how do I reach the Cog wheel
okay
what is happening
what she tried turning it off and on
again
oh yeah it is a Luna
oh my gosh that was so stressful Nina
how could you do this to us
when I invite somebody the invite button
and the unlock and spirit Lobby is the
same button it's in the same face so I
just like fat fingers oh have you do you
not know how to play on a switch Nina
come on now okay I'm back in the group
Nina I I like yeah my fingers
I'm not getting an invite are you sure
okay okay let me let me see
umu and
a meal so we should this is six minutes
until the stream starts girl so we
should really like it let's go yeah
you're right you're right
we move the stream back an hour yeah in
one hour can you checked the friends
list on Uno
like how do you check the friends list
on Uno on the switch you don't need to
check your friends list don't know
because it's just the switchfront list
[Music]
yeah but I like either I make the lobby
or I get invited right so how do I
because Nina said join off of me but I
don't have any invite
uh can you it just pops up on the top
left yeah
and they don't have it I'm not getting
an invite really click the little house
and then go to the top left to the
friends and then like find me up there
ultimately I lost I'm out again the
little house yeah at the bottom or you
know what Rosie you start the game
yeah yeah
[Music]
oh my God you know what I'll invite you
Nina and then you can invite everyone
else maybe yeah that sounds good
oh I'm so glad we're making it on time
in four minutes we start the stream
isn't that exciting yeah
I mean if I'm minutes but we still have
like loading screen time like maybe five
minutes yeah true true and then we need
to do the introductions
yeah sound sound checks
still got time don't worry don't worry
it's okay yeah and then you know things
often don't work right away and Ian
collab so then we have the Ian curse
extra time oh yeah maybe 30 minutes so
it'll be fine it's fine we could just
talk during that time I think people
will enjoy us just hanging out you know
down the street chit chatting yeah
yeah my chat looks so excited for the
stream they're just like wow I'm so
excited yeah
okay okay wait wait I'm inviting
okay okay
I got the invite I'm joining okay I'm
inviting
I'm here
but is Nina as as not the the roommaker
able to invite me Rose you're on Uno
yeah you let me join off of you
okay I don't see a way to invite anybody
yeah wasn't me give me a friend called
please oh okay
oh my God
unlike my friend's list I see Rose yeah
that's the same thing I see you on my
list but I don't see on Uno
um
all right yeah I see I think you're the
one who has to do it okay yeah
okay wait I don't have Kiara's friend
code
um
you're gonna confuse me
apparently
[Music]
cheat skills a skill issue
okay all right
um this will be it this will be the
solution for all our problems yep okay I
won't let you guys down maybe yeah you
got this oh yeah believe in yourself
okay all right I sent the friend request
now I'm going back to Uno this is so
crazy
no we were never meant to play this game
apparently I promise I will never for as
long as I live make another collab why
is it searching oh wait get me out of
here
I think I've been someone
oh I think it's searching for someone's
game
get out of there okay okay hold on I'm
just gonna force close there we go
the real friends is the troubles we got
into along the way huh I don't want the
troubles as friends
I am awaiting my invite with open wide
arms okay you'll get a really big fat
juicy invite it's gonna be coming in
okay like crazy big inside okay
you can't miss it once it happens yep
do you see it coming yeah you'll know
you'll you'll hear it smell it feel it
everyone smell it yeah
by the way there's a big question going
around who gave kiwawa the kiss on her
cheek on the thumbnail oh
she had the small little lips what about
my
life
my little lips on her cheek I was
sleeping I don't remember who did it you
know
it may have been Palma and it looks like
it's like call it like a what is it
called like um lip gloss
[Music]
um I'll take the the DNA from it and
I'll test it
yeah so on your thumbnail I'm on the
other side of you so it's not me it has
to be Rosie or poke who do you think oh
my God it's me okay well the only way I
can find out maybe is they if everybody
gives me a kiss and we'll compare the
the stamps
all right who's going first okay
Rosie you go first
that is it that is the kiss but will you
go first
um I don't see roseme or Nina
guys I don't think this is meant to be
like you don't see them here I'll show
you I'll be invited you promo there's no
way what no I I promise you
look at this look I just see
what there's no way to scroll down oh my
God it made me delete the other friends
yeah maybe there's a smell of friends
they could just get rid of them I don't
need them if I reopen the game would
that help oh let's try that okay
prepare your forehead
what yes Are You Gonna Kiss Me Kiss
you know what when your mom like licks
saliva off of your your face
[Music]
not enough time that was nice
yeah it's gotta be a little slobbery you
know
[Laughter]
you want a chew toilet that kind of Kiss
it's all right I'm sorry I didn't hear
yeah
okay wait so I'll I'll does Nina have
the game open I'm about to reopen it to
girls checking again I'm back on the
game let me know if you can see me okay
I'm gonna I'm gonna close I'm gonna
close the lobby and reach her eye
okay all right it's so weird
God please Uno just let us in let us
play your game
I love how it says classic Uno because
this is just classic Uno
I think it's my most recent friends that
I've added and it won't let me scroll
down so I'm going to unfriend um yeah
yeah yeah
okay I'm going to go delete you guys and
then re-add you guys
okay oh I was gonna say don't delete
Nina and we'll see me delete all the
others that are in there oh I mean that
works too the new friend by Nina kosaka
okay friend deleted friendship ended up
roller coaster such a roller coaster
emotional damage
friend deleted Rosemary if she and you
wait what
okay I think I see your code Nina um
roseme can you put yours in Two on Two
you just have a physical copy of Uno at
home like right now
role play like we're there with each
other like okay guys I'm playing
I draw
I have a lobby but I can't I can't see
Rosemary in the lobby no no wait I'm not
on the game right I'm like giving my
friend clothes yeah yeah okay thank you
okay now I'm searching roseme since I
have everyone like recently added at the
top I'll try and remake it again okay
let me know if you can see
I did
uh
okay okay
actually okay if anybody asks
we can just say this was pre-april fools
throw the game April Fools
do you think it's realistic that we're
logging into the game no it was all
meant to be yes rosami I sent you a
friend request okay
this will continue until midnight in
every country so that's really April 1st
and that's when we say we're never gonna
play the game can't you spend nine hours
with you girls so let's go okay yeah
okay okay until 5am okay
oh
was that a yet wait was that a happy or
was that a bad it's a bad
yeah um now I'm not on it right now I
don't think that has anything to do with
it it's just showing my friends for some
reason then then the last person to try
will be me with the superior European
you Uno and switch I agree save us Kiara
I'm gonna remove you and re-addle you I
already did that I removed you in
reality deal okay okay pull my check
again right now maybe
maybe no
should I restart Uno oh yeah let me try
restarting it oh [\h__\h] okay don't look at
it I forgot to accept your friends list
oh you did
I don't understand
I didn't realize you all so unfriended
me that's how it works
it's a mutual unfriending
Genie Mutual friendly
it's all just warm up
my head is still confused right now I
have no clue what is going on
I'm sending you a friend request right
now okay I am sending you a friend
request too wait you unfriended me too
yeah okay okay
[Laughter]
I'm making a Lobby
I'm making the lobby
this is true Grandma action
okay I'm entering the lobby
I am
oh gosh okay Moment of Truth okay okay
I'm entering the game the game is being
entered right now
okay let me know if you can see me oh
God
oh man I can't see you guys it's the
same list as before
okay okay let me let me see oh my God
[Laughter]
[Music]
maybe I should update you know what but
no because Kiara still shows up oh I got
the invite such a good initiation for
Kiara because we are insane
I love this so much I'm enjoying
everything
okay I feel like I've said this before
but in Japan when we're going to meet
with Kiara right we were four girls and
Cato was alone and rosami's like I don't
know I'm just I'm nervous to meet God
I'm like why are you nervous it's a
little meeting us we're four we said
yeah
[Applause]
you know my whole thing is freaking I
was freaking it yeah do you guys know
that episode room now yeah can you see
me no no you don't see me you're in
she's Nina Cena
okay okay Nina I did not see you okay
wait I'm gonna try to join off of piadas
okay because everyone else is here like
everyone else is in the lobby let's just
play
why am I going off of your profile
listen I'm friends with everybody right
now right yeah
let me make the room okay see how if it
works with imagine
no okay how do you do this uh I think
you should do this at least once a year
where we just get together and don't
play a game
game you know like that episode of
Fairly OddParents when he's he's on the
escalator and he's like when do we get
to the ride and he's like and there's
parents are like this is the ride
this is the Stream
[Music]
[Laughter]
one second one second
wake me up I can't wait God
take two all right all right
don't worry we haven't even tried yet
Nina also boosted our server
long overdue anyway for you girls best
40 I ever spent yeah
40. we can we can hear each other go
into despair in higher quality that's
true
[Music]
ask how high is the highest you can see
how high the highest is
oh I've done some like Vocaloid covers
where they go really high yeah
so pretty high but I don't know a key
why I was just wondering because there's
this like rock song called dream on oh
send it to me I'll sing it in my next
non-archived
it's the classic rock fans are gonna be
so happy
I think it's a fun song it is yeah oh is
it Aerosmith yeah no no uh yeah it is
Aerosmith oh
heard of Aerosmith before like a
different song though I think and I
don't know what was it
forever to touch no what the hell is
Aerosmith oh isn't that Aries I've
already seen that one yeah yeah I
thought that was one question okay girls
one set one second when you girls
created the lobby how did you do it okay
oh you hit the planet and then you click
um you know where you're at
but they just keep it as free for all at
the top yeah yeah free for all classic
Uno what that immediately sent me into
uh oh no
I think I was in a different thing then
okay
you do the three first guys you're right
okay score limit
I can't stop thinking about when you
were singing in Russian oh my God okay
so I've known roseme for over a year now
right and yeah okay I was singing a
Russian song called
[Music]
drunk and then I look at Rosemary and
the song in Russian and I'm like you
know we forgot well you don't know but
like when you're kind of drunk and I was
just you speak Russian and you've never
told me but it's because she was reading
the Japanese
aggression
[Laughter]
[Music]
like I felt so betrayed oh my gosh
that's so funny and that's simple you
just accepted it I just kept on singing
like you and you were like okay
like a big smile on her face she kept
going
[Music]
Mommy
all right
we're here
I'm gonna print screen for you the only
friend that I can invite is Pomeranian
yep the others are all whole life
members why are you doing this I'm sorry
it's just like randoms like who's on
your list and then you can't divide this
is sucks because I don't know what do we
do but I I am Googling right now
showing up what if we do
fine and then we have a passcode
okay yeah test it
I'm trying it right away yeah oh wait no
no it's putting me in a random match
guys this has been one of the most
collabs of all time someone in my chat
said is it because your online status is
hidden
oh my God tech support who said that
where are you m e j
well no because some people other people
can invite me oh that's true yeah the
thing is like a few of us can invite a
few of us but not all of us right
um that's true
how to fix Nintendo switch can't join
friend Lobby
is there a way to make it so anybody can
invite some people why is it like this
okay okay here's a new idea what if we
just all join online at the same time
surely that can't be that many people
playing right I will I will now delete
all my uh friends one second except for
you no no
[Music]
eventually
give me just a moment please it is a
good idea but like I feel like that
would work I'll do it out of solidarity
okay who am I deleting I'll delete any
niji Sanji friends I'm deleting
one by one oh my God the stream right
now and she's gonna be fine oh
as well why not for the other
I'll go delete them
that's a little dramatic yeah okay okay
but because I see in my friend list
y'all are online
um and and if I delete everybody else I
mean come on come on then the game has
no other options it has to show everyone
right yeah the issues that the list is
too small to like show everyone yeah
there's no way to scroll down yeah
scroller but yeah we went a little bit
oh
everybody except roseme still
and he deleted everyone everyone except
for you so that's like it's weird right
he knows then rosami join let's get out
our laundry do you have a problem with
me do you want to talk about do you want
to talk about it what's up Rosemary it's
because this is Nina you you saying that
Russian song and I really wanted to sing
it I really wanted to sing it that's why
I was singing it with you but yeah drama
wait why did you send it really cute in
my jacket Rosie and I'm glad that you're
wearing it and it's your jacket
yeah what does it mean to unlock the
lobby and have them join what does that
mean they have to chat now if anyone
here for real knows what's up how to fix
this let me know I'm looking at a job
okay unlock the lobby but then what if
it's like a random player that isn't off
I'm gonna die from you again should I
accept it I'm in the middle of deleting
all my friends
[Laughter]
I think we should try the technique with
like only a few friends on the list and
if that doesn't work then maybe we
should try something else yeah I think
so too we are already all friends from
Ubisoft connect right
okay yeah yeah ladies I wait I have you
on nobody self connect right Nina
yes yeah okay yeah we do so yeah we're
all all friends on both yeah connect
hmm
okay okay
oh God I got so many friends over the
course of like three years man around
it's all popular over
you're fired and you're fired
oh my God
and you're fired the lead friends we're
witnessing we're witnessing like a mass
deletion like oh my gosh on on air this
is
Larry please double think of this they
still love you
yeah I want to start from scratch
because I feel like maybe some things
went wrong here and there you know
I want to restart also it's kind of nice
restarting from scratch because they
will give you all these like butterfly
feelings that you had in the beginning
a fresh friendship is something nice but
also an old friendship is also something
nice oh wow someone said kfp layoffs
no
[Laughter]
I'm playing a game of deleting
people this is the game today kfp we've
called you into this meeting to tell you
and then I'm almost done I have uh one
two four left okay oh my God
okay I'm waiting Soul Mina is it dead
where's Nina oh she's deafened
oh what maybe she went maybe she
couldn't stand us anymore
she's finally done with us she's just
like I organize this collab I can take
it out
he's finally done kill her motivation
for organizing collabs because she told
me I really want to organize more
collapse now even when I'm not the one
yeah
yeah okay guys it's done okay okay oh my
God oh my gosh
I'll restart the game though
okay this is promising don't get your
hopes up I know I have many homes for
this this is gonna work believe I'm
crossing my fingers coming
[Music]
warning right before playing you will
not be able to play it with your friends
because we will not show them in your
friends here in the oh
what happened
hi welcome back I have deleted all my
friends I'm not now gonna try my best to
all your past friends don't count we are
your new friends we are like a cult we
are grabbing you away I'm kidding uh
welcome back you will now enjoy a
greater experience when playing Uno as a
member of the Ubisoft connect oh
yeah
this is sounding a bit culty now they
don't let you play unless you connect
yeah it's the only experience get that
message too though
yeah I mean I don't think so yeah I got
the message because no I didn't I didn't
because I was already locked into
Ubisoft somehow maybe I just didn't read
I can't read
I can't read I'm homo I'm nine
centimeters tall and I never learn how
to read
I'm sorry for laughing
no did it get worse
and now I'm on Alicia's phone because
all uh all the others are ghosts
wow I'm sorry for laughing interesting
okay guys maybe we should play something
else or just fat I don't know
no no actually
Monopoly we can play Monopoly here like
only problem is since we counted at each
other on switch if we play Monopoly on
switch wouldn't that also give us the
same exact problem no no no no no
that's what I'm thinking right we would
have to like have a single person play
it or we can play something like you
like Pummel party Monopoly is different
give me a second no it's also by Ubisoft
it's the same thing it's the same thing
you try to see if you can invite all of
us yeah I'm opening it right now let me
see if it even tells me to log into
Ubisoft yeah yeah if you can well how
would it we don't I don't have it
installed so you know yeah I don't have
it either if she invited us we would
have to
be so good it's a good thing that we um
you know delayed the stream by two hours
yeah
okay
I'm losing at you guys
[Laughter]
what
that your actions have consequences
it doesn't count me too long Ubisoft
that's a good thing already
oh
yeah
I think you only need to log into like
Ubisoft once on the switch and then it
like transfers over it because I think I
was logged in from like Just Dance and
it like went over to Uno but then again
I don't think I could even see you girls
to invite you if you don't have the game
download but I'll I'll check okay maybe
maybe
[Music]
um
only work yeah I looked at the trailer
it looks way better than the Monopoly on
the PC
there's no in I can't invite I guess
because I have no friends who have
Monopoly okay so I'm gonna go buy
Monopoly
is gonna work though oh my God even if
it doesn't work now one day I believe we
will play Monopoly together
or Uno yeah which one what I've never
organized
this is it this is the final Uno and we
never got to play I need to ask Grandma
what happened because she didn't have
Uno working and then it worked
so am I buying Monopoly or what oh wait
it might take me a long time to download
on the switch though I feel like it
would be bigger than Uno but last time I
played Monopoly was it on PC or was it
on switch guys do you know I think the
switch one looks super cute yeah I think
it was on the PC one does not work it's
it's real it crashes every time
I'm pretty sure it's the same server
though
okay
you confirm your token first I don't
know if we're gonna get one guy but
confirm your token to see if that I can
add AI oh
what's my name
What's My Name Say My Name Say My Name
otherwise I know we can play garlic foam
oh yeah
yeah wait I am are we doing Monopoly or
no I don't know because if you all buy
it and download it and it doesn't work
then we spend a number of hours this is
true
[Music]
that's a stream of the hopes of some
time playing games
uh again I just want to apologize I did
not check the game because I played Uno
and everything worked this time you know
um
wait do you can we play scribbleo do you
guys know that is
yeah
sounds wait I'm gonna do a poll I'm
gonna do a poll okay you guys want us to
uh try Monopoly or we'll play garlic
phone now
[Music]
this phone is fine for your girls is it
like in terms of you know I think so I'm
checking let me check
uh it's even free guys it's free yeah
oh wait no sure let me take a look
really quickly at my games list
I had issues with Monopoly when I played
it was a collab
never I didn't have issues inviting
girls I didn't have issues with
connection either I think I mean maybe
at the very end somebody disconnected oh
yeah yeah Monopoly is a bit famous for
having
um silver issues at least on the PC I
don't know on the switch
and I feel like it's this well it's the
same Series so maybe
okay oh well garlic phone seems fun yeah
I think like
fall maybe like Pummel party stuff like
that
yeah I put it I I put the I put what uh
some stuff in there in the chat
they're saying play garlic film now
30 are saying try Monopoly and 70 are
saying play garlic phone that's pretty
garlic
um
I also love garlic baguettes
um okay so we what do you mean it's
called garlic bone what do you mean it's
not it's the garden styling foam uh
there is a game can you double check on
your end there's this game called
unrailed it's super cute
and on switch it's super fun it's super
easy to play we just build a train
together like train tracks together
I don't think I'll build a train
well I would have to basically like is
that the weird big game like no no no no
it's a tiny it's like a tiger yeah it
should be like maybe under a gig okay
it's a super like if anything
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay I wrote you the reason yeah no
worries have you um
uh have you uh played Terraria okay oh
oh my God Terraria stop suggesting new
things I think we should just go with
what we have let's just do it yeah yeah
okay okay garlic yeah yeah
okay I'll start the garlic foam Lobby
because uh that way you girls won't
accidentally show it on your screen
okay oh oh okay okay oh yeah it's been a
while that's been a while I love garlic
foam garlic phone
is it what's the website we'll have to
change to a beautiful thumbnail later
but I'll just change the logo yeah
the invite uh there we go I'm having a
lot of fun I I know I know sometimes
folks are like stuff didn't work but
this this is fun for me yeah this is the
best like huge delay I've ever had
I know I know realistically if you're
really looking forward to Uno and you
don't get Uno yeah it's disappointing
but this is an adventure this is a ride
we're all you know
take this oh
my god oh yeah the German ads
did you guys hear the German ad no no no
but I kind of want to now
Deutsch Deutschland no
[Laughter]
speed
a what besides English
uh oh gosh oh yeah Russian French what
about you speak something
English and Japanese Japanese right yeah
just a little
sure what about what's up
she speaks the language of the earth
look at me speaks a lot of languages but
a little bit like she understands
Spanish really really well the Russian
right I mean we know that yeah
um yeah Japanese I took a bit of Italian
took some I took some Latin
Natalia I just saw your room Nina okay
hold on one second
okay I um
because I don't have a phoenix yeah yeah
yeah okay chicken
you can change it
we are getting together how is it
possible that a free game is letting us
play together versus a 50 Euro or do we
actually kill this game
it was so easy is there any music on
this site I don't hear anything I don't
think so okay
okay oh yeah yeah let's put in your own
music yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you for reciting my music
I don't feel like I need my stupid music
my ad blocker doesn't work
your what doesn't work my ad blocker
doesn't work but it's okay I'm just
cutting off the sides
oh yeah yeah I always I always like uh
on on websites sometimes um when I'm
streaming like the the wheel website
that's spins the wheel I have to like
cut out all the sides or Gazo because it
just sounds like 15 different ads I'm
like I'm sorry I'm not trying to
advertise anything
okay
[Music]
garlic phone are we gonna like do some
uh that we're just gonna do normal first
I suppose whatever y'all prefer I
haven't played in a while
okay my pen my pen I have a pen I have a
tablet okay
oh my God ads
it's more scarf
[Music]
like I I somebody was giving me a prompt
of Yago tea bagging and then what what I
wrote Because I didn't know what tea
bagging is is
the supermarket at the counter putting
stuff into a bag a tea you put a tea
into a bag no that's genius what are you
talking about
oh my God I keep getting ads on on
garlic food is this normal
a video in the beginning of the middle
okay is it really in the beginning yeah
but just I don't have an ad maybe my ad
blocker is superior
okay I'm in I'm in
she just gave me like a whole video oh
my gosh it's got like two hours to me
all right ready I'm ready oh my gosh
oh do we need to do introductions first
since we just started the stream
oh my God okay let's go
like a small PGM
yeah
what are you stuck
[Music]
hmm
I'm
uh I can start yeah let's start it all
right what are you doing this game again
write a sentence
[Music]
I don't think you can hear it yet oh
write a sentence um
um
already
okay yeah I'm good you're good
I'm so sorry
it's okay I wasn't including myself
[Music]
oh
my God
oh it's been a while since I drew
something me too wait I know me too how
much did you change any time settings
so badly okay uh
um how to draw I don't remember how to
draw
it's it's cute it's very cute
I love them I'm having the time oh my
God okay whatever
thick man I'm a stickman I'll show you
my mom's yeah
oh this is perfect perfect
oh yeah okay
okay
well why am I oh my God
upset at me
I don't I don't think they know we'll
know what this even is let me decorate
it maybe we have so much time we have
too much time you have to make a faster
round later yeah trust me it's gonna go
no no I'm not gonna have another one
it's gonna go quick at the end oh my God
does it look more like what it should be
no oh no it's happening oh my God this
I'm already stressed out and we just
started how does it look like I don't
think oh my God I don't even know what
it looks like
how's that everybody
[Music]
sure
I eat a safari what are you eating I
want to eat the fairy yes it is
and stuff oh my God bony
how do you know because she's nine
centimeters I got a meaty thighs
sure
okay Nina let's see your thighs first
and then we can compare
and losing weights
try to gain how is this everybody
second do you like it do you like my art
I like it oh I like it you do oh my God
why am I lagging what are you lagging
the game lagging or you are lagging like
[\h__\h] is this like is it better now
the game was lagging I don't know what
is up that is uh that is Nina
[Laughter]
[Music]
I think that's a close game just in case
this is so good okay what is this
whoever Drew okay I'm gonna move
What's Happening Here there you guys go
this is so good whoever Drew this what
is this
um
[Laughter]
I think I know which one you got what
oh
okay okay how do I draw a skull oh my
God
decrepit
okay that's whenever I put my mouse on
the guard take phone it like gets really
laggy for some reason and don't put your
mouth there yeah don't just don't do not
draw with your imagination draw with
your head
don't you have a tablet
I guess I wouldn't change it
so thanks for the references you guys
don't worry it's [\h__\h] anyway
no it's not it's beautiful
listen I think
okay guys I apologize for my drawings
but I am drawing out like two frames
right now is your computer laggy
it's only like the garden phone like
window I don't know why
this is the John Ubisoft curse for being
like
she'll be playing with them
oh yeah I have to draw me too sorry not
sorry oh my God that yeah that is so
accurate here let me help them out a
little bit otherwise it's too difficult
um okay I did my best I think this is my
masterpiece
oh hold on I'm looking forward to seeing
it
oh my God I can't I can't okay
it's gonna be so obvious that somebody
is using a mouse and keyboard I mean
yeah a mouth I'm just saying I think
this is good you guys
oh yeah thighs you're right
there we go here here that's oh my God
is happening
okay
[Laughter]
I think I'll rejoined
oh my God oh God we're conditioned at
this point the guard take lobby after
this are we doing now yes right oh yeah
voiceovers please please
four people ends really quickly huh
that means we get more rounds are you
girls ready yeah
wait are you actually Rosemary because I
know you're having issues I don't know
if you can like show it and then after
I'll join oh okay okay
everybody else got to draw though did
you
um
drawings good
all right let's go
uh Kiara describing
[Laughter]
beautiful undergarments
what slices you
know
really old Doritos these girls playing
you know you know you know
[Music]
[Laughter]
we're gonna skip to the next one okay I
don't know no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no
um
the next one yet I want to say I want to
point out in the one that promo drew the
shape of the faces looks like uh like a
bird where the nose would be the butt
the mouth would be the wing
wow
all right oh my God I mean this one is
so funny though no stop I love that one
big card or is it like one big Uno table
like I have so many questions listen I
am not cheating like Kiara is doing by
using a tablet call out oh my God yeah
scale issue
tablet issue um
why are we always giving the same
prompts almost
it's pretty
where is Rose
okay I couldn't put in my entire prompt
it was gonna be
two okay yeah you guys okay we'll see
we're not allowed to brag while you're
using AIDS it's like you know when you
ride a bike and you have the little bike
wheels that help you ride the bike
about riding the boys the tricycle
we're unicycling here take it back wow I
can't ride a bike well see it was going
to be with their with their babies Kiara
and and I didn't have space
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm 174. he's nine Nina's shopping for
her pamoo for dinner
oh wait he's trying to eat me or like
oh my God what happened to you
oh you Scarface
oh my God she's been shopping for a
really long time
she did not age or fine like her wine
maybe we can play a a mode that we have
never played before
let me rejoin that let me rejoin
what's interesting
completely start writing and keep
drawing until the end
okay complete the sketch start with
basic lines and see the other player's
interpretation that could be cute
okay yeah we can try I'm open for
everything one sentence to ask questions
and have fun with the others drawings
wait which which one is that one
Icebreaker compliment sandwich
oh compliment is if you start to
complete the sketch start with some
basic lines oh that's kind of fun don't
feel comfortable clementing
this room
[Music]
start writing and keep drawing until the
end I'm fine with any of them
animation is fun too but with four
people We're not gonna get a really good
anime yeah I'm thinking that too unless
they give us yeah we're four people
I swear this game's doing it on purpose
[Music]
speed run
I'm ready
I'm ready girl okay all right you're
going down
oh
um
I know me too okay it always I know it
has to happen but I never think about it
like I know it right oh gosh um um chat
give me a prompt
I don't know
isn't that a realistic
[Music]
oh okay Speed Run Speed Run Okay
um
what is this prompt I'm the same way
okay
um
okay oh sorry I'm supposed to be green
why is it still like this
that's my garlic foam like this
[Music]
oh I'm so excited for this oh my mouth
is watering I'm getting hungrier by the
minute this oh yummy oh Brown
wow
I mean this just turns me on this is
kind of my Kink here Arctic clock scared
beautiful it's seducing me oh thank you
I was gonna say you're making me hungry
because I thought you were genuinely
hungry oh my God I'm also genuinely
hungry oh
yes okay I even got done earlier
yes oh my God I had no time speedrun who
oh
you know what her Kink is now
[Music]
this one's very easy
okay
thank you let them guess
we'll let them guess she's a bone she's
literally bones what the hell
look I have to draw quickly
end
um what does this mean what what is this
okay
what undo okay you know what I have an
idea I have an idea I'm very confused
too I feel like some people here are not
taking the game seriously
yeah
it's bad at Art
he's good
[Music]
I think she has like a she has boobs too
gliser or something
[Music]
oh my God what is happening I forgot
about that about what I forgot about the
boobs thanks for telling me reminding me
yeah of course of course
got other ears
[Laughter]
that's it oh so fast all right all right
Kiara cooking corn Pizza
foreign
[Music]
I heard I don't know what I think I
heard service I was like what kind of
service
it's not my cake
[Music]
well look making the corn cob Pizza
frozen meat got it wrong batsu game
it's never a real you can't just put
rules on the flashlight
I vote we spin the wheel for Rosemary to
do a batsu no I vote too okay
drawing two Nina
are you joining us
it's gonna be majority and roseme will
have to do the botsu of your spinning
choice I think I accidentally closed it
but we can just choose one for her
randomly okay
um just point your finger she just left
um
what
I'm gonna get bad girl she deserves
punishment yeah yeah it wasn't me this
is your this Rosemary oh she's back oh
she's back welcome back I will not stand
for the Slender and this bullying here
for your daily punishment honey
[Music]
although I mean now that you told me it
was Samus and not me holding like a
veggie wrap or something I thought
rap
God this is clearly salmon what do you
mean well now yeah but why did you
censor my eyes because she has a visor
yeah I'm pretty sure
[Laughter]
that's her gun in her head
it should be a little more gun like
maybe
there should have been some people
coming yeah yeah yeah it looks like a
like a gun like a cannon
it's giving me more Mario tube than like
you know hand Cannon
I feel yeah oh yeah yeah
and it's okay it's good it's beautiful
though but it's not my king
but it could be if you think about it
long enough
like okay Kiara tell me this like tell
me you you see Samus and you're like
okay she's not cute I mean I have to say
I got so fan art of me as Samus and that
was like mind-blowing yeah you see now
you're starting to yell where I'm coming
all right let's go next
um
[Music]
oh what the hell
it's supposed to be collecting
[Laughter]
ears
it reminds me of something something
that looks like a hat that looks exactly
like that some characters looks like you
have a small alien on your head or
something my main character anime
characters
who has a hat like that but different
color
[Music]
Green Line the butt crack
oh is that this of my butt crack on the
bottom I think that's my mouth and then
the eyes are my question marks right
have you guys ever watched
yeah but I don't I haven't watched all
of it but like I watched a little bit of
it he's my favorite anime
okay recommend it to me so somebody
who's not watched back in monogatari how
would you recommend it to me how would
you sell it to me if you want
um a long really intricate story and a
lot of cute girls
yeah the characters are really cute
I know the story is just absolutely
mind-blowing but uh this is just like
overload you have to focus when you
watch it but it's so yeah
I have Kiara's chat open is that the one
with the tooth brushing scene yes
there's some funny fan servers in in the
anime but there's also a lot of like
really serious plots as well I love that
one it's really good it's there's a lot
of reading
titles are of
oh kinda yeah wait what there's a lot of
text yeah yeah
it has big recommend okay let's look at
it
I'm just thinking uh
sorry I ran out of time we found time
I ran out of time
hi brother
is this one you said some people don't
take this seriously
no no
I'm not serious but
like Kiana I didn't have the time
I'm too busy laughing so I don't have
time like the extra person there's a
ghost
who's the extra person there's two
faceless people oh my God you're being
haunted
[Music]
yeah maybe I commanded the I don't how
do you even say that face dancing Nina
oh my God
Nina shaking the desk
more more
no why are you always a skeleton what is
happening
oh
you want to talk about it homo
I mean do you want to talk about it have
you guys seen her she's she's literally
wasting away she's so decrepit she's
she's old I'm only 800 and something can
you not you know what is happening there
yes what is this I'm not that old
older YouTubers than 800. yeah right
yeah but like it doesn't reflect in her
beauty anyway like she looks very young
I am here I am cool Nina I'm just it's
it's a artistic representation of your
soul okay it's true you cannot critique
you cannot critique stuff like this
there's Beauty in everything you know
yeah I am yeah
I like the shape of the left boob I know
right
cuddles are those herd potatoes or is
that another butt on my chest the Tata
there's so many questions she's bending
It Forward last one and that has the
boobies and in the first one she didn't
have because she only had ass so yeah
maybe like her old butt went up and then
she grew a new one oh
do we have like a recovering skill on
your trade on your book Bud
atmosphere
that we have created in this
collaboration thank you yes
I have to plan to play Uno
no but yeah you will not I will I will
have this I love Pomer but I have to say
Nina is beautiful she doesn't look like
this
[Music]
your body still looks good it's just
your face maybe like you know what I'll
give you some sunscreen Nina you'll
still hang this on the fridge right
you'll mom you'll still put this on the
fridge right
no
no no
[Laughter]
Nina Nina pay back pay back next time
you draw something we give promo about
this game now because she has gone bad
ger game will be uh
well because related you have to learn
how it is to be a real grandma you will
talk in a grandma voice oh
they're being
[Music]
close people learn what it means to be
old now
listen I can't Implement you know I said
I think my face is saggy
no but the rest looks good
[Laughter]
[Music]
screen
you need to change I mean sorry you need
to change that sunscreen right now
no it's only a matter of time
anyone want a toffee I have some candies
in my bucket
[Music]
why do you sound legit like why do you
know I'm a method actor right just from
this oh no collab I just want to very
quickly like say this because I know
there might be a lot of new fans
watching uh we like please don't think
for a second that you know they're
bullying me or I'm bullying them we
we're that close like it's please do you
have a gun to your head right now
Nina
this is the description
if they say I'm old and saggy and and
stupid I old and saggy and stupid end
[Music]
I mean smelly
I am contractually obligated to say that
we are the bestest friends
yeah please Pierce me I know because I
feel like we we have we banter really
really hard yeah we do and I just want
to make sure that you know folks that
are tuning in don't feel like oh are
they actually like being mean to each
other are they like I would not be
inviting people that I think are mean to
me to a collaboration with me you know
who invited the people yeah I hear that
Rose to me
oh you hear this okay
I am very timid if I'm like saying stuff
like that well it's not like I like you
guys ready I don't like you guys
I'm very I can say lots of stuff like
um
uh like what like what I like green tea
I like green tea can you say I love you
to these two girls
um these three girls
you love her before she dies yeah
okay
um well it's it's been I guess like a
yeah my breath
it's my final hour like a pretty cool
collab I guess you know you know wow
I feel like if ever really grows old
Rosemary will be not will not be
visiting her in her I know I mean
no nobody's gonna visit pomu
wow that's a joke
[Laughter]
you know what there will be no need for
visitation because all YouTubers end up
in the same old people home
that sounds like hell
we'll talk about you know the good old
days when we're really old yeah you've
already done that
okay Rosie you have two more people to
love say it
no I like maybe I'm having I mean like I
mean maybe not but like I'm maybe maybe
having a good I mean a good time with
you know what collab guys
you guys okay
I love I love green tea I love Crepes
um what else what who is that they're
not here green tea and Crips are not
here I'm drinking tea right now it's
it's here it's right here kiwawa why can
you say it to things that are not even
alive but you don't say it to us where
it really matters
I said it was good and cute
[Music]
yeah
I can show you my underwear though but
there isn't much I'm okay I'm okay well
I mean I will take that offer yeah yeah
yeah
I'm I'm actually blushing oh
you know freedom for the you know I'm
wearing
[Music]
but there's Pom-Pom oh my God pink pump
have you seen those underwear with like
where the butt crack is it's a heart
oh yeah yeah
you mean an open heart
oh wait what what wait you have that
what
what no I'm like okay I not right now
but I used to have underwear like that
and then it had a little like heart
charm I think it was
sorry sorry can you just tell me is the
heart the Open Heart above the butt
crack or it's on the butt crack
it's like the top of the butt crack
okay okay okay
like a draft and then you'd feel cold I
don't know
I'm sorry I'm gonna get a nosebleed off
they weren't backwards boxers were they
let's play another game please
oh no everything's gonna be about
underwears oh my God
[Music]
try really hard not to make it about
underwear okay challenge impossible
level
hmm
what but but but but but but but but
like one tea right
I don't know
wait
no
[Music]
problems this is a table everybody
oh yeah that makes sense that makes
sense okay that's cute though I can
someone like draw it for real this like
a good artist I feel like niji Sanji uh
you girls you have like really great
artists in your fan Community if you are
such good art can they draw this too
it's an e you guys gosh
[Music]
there you go
this is now a Canon this is real this is
the the way it's meant to be
okay I want this to be real in the
future I want to see what it is what
it's you it's me
uh what color should it be
I kind of feel like drawing Poma with a
hat now instead of the headband you know
am I gonna get that if I do this I don't
want to like get us banned if I like
why is the table oh try it
I also feel like I'm gonna give you some
things about my character that people
don't know okay that's a good tablecloth
you guys gosh I muted from them yeah
[Laughter]
what
did you is there is there waiting yeah
like where
will we find out no that is
if your manager has a problem with this
I promise you I will apologize I will
write like a written apology for this
I just don't know how to like write this
otherwise
wait what
don't worry about it
wait is it is it uh uh an ash goodbye we
call it a joke uh
is it on top of your burnt
on top of your butt
um
okay I feel like we're just drawing a
normal
what is
what
are you okay are you okay what am I
into the eyes of the joke yeah use your
use your use your fun jokey
um
it what is this
[Music]
okay I'm just gonna drop this literally
because I'm so confused by everything
yeah me too I'm just gonna draw this
literally
[Music]
all right well I'm getting serious now
yeah I'm drawing oh wait I have to there
we go there we go oh yeah guys oh yeah
on the lines
hey I'm having wine
I said lines maybe you've had too much
brilliant
oh
oh [\h__\h] no space no face oh I'm naked
how to draw this
oh okay ribbon
It's My Life the booty needs to be you
know more like this
[Music]
but who is this yeah bye yeah bye-bye I
guess it's me I guess it's me
oh
there's a lot of
a lot going on here yeah this is not a
crazy crazy
it's a very sensual round that's for
sure
[Music]
is it not strange feelings and emotions
okay
I'm sorry
it's not good everybody chat says it's
fine
I swear if I had a tablet
next time like I feel like you're meant
to draw this with your mouse right
that's like hey that's
guided why
oh my God
who wrote this okay I'm sorry who
who wrote this prompt
well if you're saying it like that I
feel like I have an idea
if that means this right that's like you
know another way of saying that
I'm learning so much English today
like so worth it my vocabulary is
expanding can you give us an example of
what you've learned
um
yeah
so first I thought Twin Peaks maybe a
mountain
but I think that probably means
yes it's a mountain it is it is
like two mountains and I know so much
about climbing now because I just
watched a video about climbing oh really
one of the twins
smaller than the other you know you want
to go flying yeah yeah we should go
hiking together one day karaoke
and it's I need some safety do you say
do you wait safety somewhere at the top
is someone at the top to save you yeah
Jesus Christ
yeah I don't know it probably is Jesus
up there yeah I don't see anybody else
who's gonna be at the top to save you
here here's some nice armpits for you
guys to enjoy nice
I'm gonna love some armpits I don't know
why people love armpits so much I'm
gonna I love it people love armpits yeah
so happy it's cool to love armpits again
armpits it's never gone out of style
just like the shoulders okay I'm not old
armpits are sexy and so are ankles
ankles are sexy oh yeah ankles can be
cute
did you guys notice um this like the
YouTuber or I don't know if he's really
a YouTuber but she made like videos you
know in Victorian only fans where you
get like ankle pictures but it was a
joke yeah
and a lot of people signed up for it
actually
what really oh wait but for real yeah
yeah y'all not think armpits are kind of
sexy I'm a Touhou fan
we have a lot of armpits there
yeah there's a lot of character designs
with yeah
this is my prompt yeah wait why did I
get my own I got my own prompt too me
too because there's like not enough
people
or maybe or we compare did everybody
draw everything maybe maybe I think
maybe maybe that's what Icebreaker means
oh yeah
[Music]
wait I can't now do it myself I already
did this wait what I cannot do it better
than what I did before yeah
I'm so sorry I can't forget it I know my
grandma today yeah you are gonna need to
do another grammar round this was really
cool
oh laughing Grandma okay
I'm trying such a lovely young lady
right now
I said young lady
she's so beautiful
I don't know what my prompt even was
like I don't know what I was trying to
accomplish with that I'm so sorry
[Music]
wait two I started trying to like be
cute and I'm like oh this is not cute
um um yes
yes
she is Conquering the world
[Music]
okay
so much
foreign
[Music]
how is this everybody
pretty good I'd say
[Music]
all I heard was
hello
yeah hello I'm really busy Ricky I'm so
sorry
we need to come up with the prompts man
I know we do
these props I just I just want to say I
I am ready to write like my apology if I
need
oh yeah everybody draws it
wow
there's a Dorito under the table
[Laughter]
wait I just need to see koalas again
yeah it's so good I'm downloading this
one yeah
it's so deep oh my God shut up I'm just
gonna put that on our fridge
I'll send you a better one promo
oh my god
of course I thought it was like a bot
prompt because I didn't understand what
it meant at all but when you guys got it
like so good except the tree went like
why did you not like
you all you've never been told that the
joke is under there
under the tree under there under the
tree it's it's the joke is under there
you want me to ask underwear yeah
stupid I don't know what's going on
listen I'm never okay for anybody who
doesn't know this is like old trivia
roseme is the first one to have fallen
for that joke really no is she really no
no no no I fell for a dog I underwear I
knew that you guys were talking about
underwear but up dog
our dog is My Kryptonite
I ever fell for up dog but like
yesterday I got I think I fell for these
not stroke twice
twice isn't fell for even uh
[Music]
not my fault they're also childish
Chad what are you doing bullying huh
okay
anything you want to tell us
Megan came from my chat I'm sorry I
don't know I don't want to make
something interesting and that always
the same [\h__\h] it looks like she's like
sleeping yeah
no time oh my God
awesome
the old lady I'm still smoking hot
why do you have bigger boobs as an old
lady
[Music]
sagging his house
because they're sagging exactly
Cuomo decided that now it's enough she
doesn't want to get called Flat anymore
so she got you know oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
like like is that one you put like
Silicon yeah yeah oh you're a great
candidate for that too no I'm not good
Nina's attacking everybody today oh my
God
you old woman
no
so uh Kiara we have this one co-worker
who's pretty flat and she always says
medium is premium and it's like a honey
you're not medium
true you know
medium is like such a cope I think she's
gotten a buff though right like I mean
mine's foam
[Laughter]
Wellness
the squish when we hug yeah
I failed I felt squished but I don't
think it came from me
for me right for me
no I don't know
I remember squished from Nina
that was a good squeeze from Nina
that reminds me uh Kiara ages ago me and
Rosie were in a hotel room in the mirror
and I you know I I don't care a bra
because it hurts so I just like talking
you know I only have a few like you know
firm years left I want to live them
a lot of firmy years left you know
genuine question when do the firm years
end yeah
soon
for you 800 years old
really oh no that's stressful
honestly like I'd say any time after
like 26 27 Oh The Firm years are about
to end wow really that soon
yeah can you do something about it you
can break out I think working out helps
yeah yeah
but you know the bigger you are the more
inevitable the no are you just bragging
at this point
it's just so hard exactly that's what
she
didangas just keep bouncing and flopping
me in the face
[Music]
my big breasts called the sauce that I
dropped
wow she would she'd be like how could
you say that
look at it
it's like an anime it is
well we're at the hotel I think I was
wearing just like a tank top and I I
forgot what we were doing but I think I
was doing my makeup and I was like I
shook and something and Rosie's like she
turned to the side and she looked and
she went oh my God
so flat
realization is
did you girls ever go to an Onsen
together I want to go I believe I want
to go
it frozen would you feel comfortable
going to a nonsense with us
I mean like
maybe yeah
but like
like just don't look okay don't work
it's all granny's in there it's fine
[Music]
in Japan and it took me so much courage
to like get in there with her thankfully
we went to like we went to a resort that
had like several different onsens there
and there was one that was supposedly
like not so popular because Cali scouted
them all out for me because she doesn't
really mind at all and instead we could
go to this one this one's always pretty
empty so we went there and the moment we
entered you know there were like two old
Japanese ladies there they probably
feared the Gaijin so they left the
moment they saw us thankfully so that I
felt a bit more comfortable about that
and then well you know even even justice
of Cali I felt really nervous and I
didn't want her to think that I was
gonna look like looking at her but you
know oh my God it's oh it's rough it's
rough it's rough but I'm glad I got over
it and went with her but I also one one
time one time I went alone to a big big
big public one which was a big mistake
because that one was so crowded oh and I
felt like everybody was looking at me
because I was the only guy in the only
Foreigner
and I I and I was like I didn't know
where to look because at every corner
since it was so crowded that I recorded
it was a naked lady I didn't want them
to think I was looking at them I didn't
know what to look it was so awkward
the whole thing is you're not supposed
to stare like you're supposed to be
respectful I'm not there at any of the
Japanese grandmothers they sure as heck
did not get them
Eric and I'm like oh my God
normally but just because you were just
overwhelmingly you know pretty oh yeah
they're like she's a model
I'm telling you if you need someone to
go with you I'll go with you I can scan
before before I'm good if I need to get
into a fist guide I'll get into office
like private ones yeah
it gets worse though it gets like I mean
worse in terms of a comfortableness what
so I've been told that in Korea they
have an also like something like an
Onsen but there the old ladies will
start to wash you
until then
say wash your back and stuff rub my back
would they give me a massage no I don't
make a massage but they want to look
apparently apparently I'm like really
scared that's like next level Onsen
honestly just random grannies just
started washing you apparently maybe not
randomly but like it's it's pretty
common apparently you just have a granny
washu are they naked too
so you maybe that's like a volunteer
service you know how like when old
people don't have a job anymore they're
bored maybe they sign up to be like a
volunteer bathroom okay that's just
that's just uh exaggerated it's a
service but you know okay yeah
okay random grannies where they would
just come up to you and just by like
scrubbing your back yeah I mean they are
strangers
there's a lot of cultures where it's
like you know like a lot of cultures are
very communal
right and you're all by yourself I feel
like the grandmas would be like hey like
you know we can wash we can help
that I think it's a community thing
they're not it turns out they're not
naked okay so that's good that's good
anymore
being naked would make it fairer to me
like would make me feel more comfortable
I'm the only one naked yeah right maybe
they should be naked
make it equal make it fair I'm not gonna
push for this but I will say when we if
we are in Japan at the same time ever we
should go to an Onsen I won't push for
this I won't like but if anything
give me the sign and I find like 12
private and you're in leave reviews oh
[Laughter]
oh I love waterpikes there's a water
park
um no it's not a water park it's an
amusement park and hot springs together
that have been doing
I thought there's a ferris wheel in
Japan where you can sing karaoke in the
ferris wheel oh you can do like the
Inuyasha ending
you know that one okay I don't know it
but I want to do that yeah
what kind of specific that is
I'm excited one day one day we'll make
it a reality but not the onset no thank
you you can go with the ninja girls I
won't I won't go I will not go
she can't just imagine me being there
can we stop looking at whatever this is
on the screen
cut out oh yeah who did that
what is this
what they are now oh it wasn't me so say
so wait what do you mean
whatever
wait see Paul
hey what is wrong with you guys see you
guys are like Rosemary so stay so but
this is what it was meant to be
I've been betrayed I thought I was
getting the joke for once
no what no no yours is perfect thank you
I don't care I tweeted it everyone's
timeline needs to be cursed
I can't stop
Nina looks like you're Looks Like a
Torpedo like don't worry about it
people like rocks that are like crazy
knows that erupt me yeah yeah yeah
and the new information that we have now
where your markings are you are the
markings
oh
yes
illegal information
[Music]
also like like kiaras
yes
what
do you mean what do you mean that's what
the body looks like
it's really realistic actually I'm quite
proud of this one it's actually really
good
yours is a good Kiara I meant Nina's oh
I'm in the fridge I'm gonna print this
[Music]
might need to go to a doctor yeah I have
no idea what is happening you know she
already told us this is what happens
later on apparently rest sag when you
have big ones okay
something you girls don't know
[Music]
flat is justice
all right all right girls let's move on
okay let's see Rosa means
this was sweet very sweet
oh my God
I'm sorry I cannot stop
why did she have like a beret on her
head I finished the blanket
mission
alive that's beautiful
wow
I like Grandma Puma very much I told you
I want to pull with my grandma oh
have you gotta have you heard like any
of your stories about Palmer's grandma
no she has a grandma I do
[Laughter]
what stories are there why do you girls
know her grandma Stars she tells her
Grandma's stories my grandma is a little
crazy
um you know some okay so I'll tell the
story that people quote the most
probably so one time I was at my mom's
house and we were eating dinner and we
were just having a nice time and it got
quiet my grandma just says something
unprompted no no reason Roanoke Rhyme or
Reason why she said this but she just
says you know if you come up behind me
you better fight me or [\h__\h] me
and and we were like Grandma
wow that is the feisty Grandma yeah
every she's gotten into fights at the
old people's home her roommate had to
move out
he's my old sheep yeah she were more
like her my great grandma would like
flirt with every like guy and she would
see she'd be like she's like unable to
move and she'd be like flirting with all
the guys and they'd be like 20 years
younger than her and she was so popular
with the grandpa that's crazy a lion
what is that called
[Music]
every year that we get older it's one
year that we are closer to being cougars
girls
what's that again it's when an older
woman likes a younger
but what if you just don't want the
younger guys
what if you just like women yeah
I think it's still a cougar
oh
oh is it yeah I don't know though
um I just wonder like if I'm really
really old what could be my pickup line
like hey boy I'll add you to my will
have that one ready yes
you were too eager to say that
oh my God
have you I know really hot girls come to
a funeral you want to come to my funeral
what
oh my gosh
that is really confusing
yes well I'm I'm sorry in advance it's
okay
and I don't think I could even I don't I
don't know any any pickup lines
[Music]
I lost my phone number can I have yours
oh yeah
well somebody wrote what a borrow my tea
when the bar might what my teeth
oh ew
that is so gross
you don't know any pickup lines try them
try them
pick up plans on us all grandmas have
candy
okay I have this famous one that I came
up with oh that I never brought it back
because it's so bad oh
hey hey girl are you a pizza cause your
mods are really cute
you're what never mind
I've never said
he said what because your monster really
cute MOX matzah mozzarella yeah but
Mozzarelli mozzarella really cute you
wish maybe change it not Mozzarelli
mozzarella cute
right oh just mozzarella what's a mean
wait what
oh I think the whole thing is you're
saying because you're really cute yeah
just adding the mozzarella in it yeah
because no because it's a pizza are you
a pizza like are you a cheese pizza yeah
I
don't love it but I'm also old and
cranky and stinky and stinky yeah
uh
[Music]
baby are you a side quest because I want
to grind you real man
sorry oh God that's worse no no no go
back to real bad for experience makes no
home for experiences I just got done
from the chat I don't know about the
grinding part
if you have the crown experience it
really sucks man you have to grind so
hard for some games can't get to you
know a certain point go to this one area
and kill 30 lions and then have to go
here and kill 50 salons
lead me through the game properly
I wanted to be done properly all right
anyway my God oh my God my child is
coming up with some crazy ones are you
what's that guy's name Jason Krueger
who's that who
the what what's the mouse guy's name
Jason Krueger
Michael Krueger
who's the mask guy Michael Krueger who
is that what's the matter the guy with
white mouth
because I want you to wear me like a
hockey mask
no I want to wear you like a hockey I
don't know
well I'm crying
where did that come from
a huge Jason corgis because I want him
[Laughter]
I don't play the scary games at all I am
so bad with the scary games
yeah me too I cannot play scary games
you and I can lie against the plague
right there The Scorch yeah but again
like you know before we had you know
similarities in terms of uh free sizes
and now we have similarities in terms of
interest uh when it comes to games
scary games and not so scary games
must be mine I just named the three that
Marilyn Monroe has and I'm like those
three same as Marilyn Monroe
by the way
um you wouldn't understand it's for
people who have hips and breasts
so I have no body I just have I'm
literally a stick figure I don't even
have a yeah you're right me yeah this
one for you was me okay are you are you
Samus because I want to glump you like a
Metroid
oh
what is the glomping mean exactly
that's what it felt like to me I don't
know it's just like that's literally a
glove Oh I thought that was like an
action
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah right
apparently it is a Run and Jump hog but
for me it felt more like you know like
Bloom glomp you know long I would rather
be um running hugs than die
super ring my whole body in that Metroid
you know imma be a metric for you girl
you're the only Metro that you will not
shoot down then
oh my God everybody what are some good
pickup lines hold on someone just sent
me this one
are you a fossil sample because I'm an
impatient paleontologist and I want to
date you badly
oh my gosh really good
because you're old it has eight S and
you want to find out what that where
when that that fossil
yeah
that's good
I'm getting Indiana Jones Vibes I like
it
and oh that maybe that is a reference
what is NSP
[Music]
that's paleontology joke has layers is
that a is that a joke because because
layers you know you have to like there's
layers too fast so she's cooking she's
cooking
in the kitchen the kitchen's on fire
it's on fire oh she's burning it down oh
God blow it out Kiara
extinguisher I have to ask you I was
told to ask you from the chat oh what is
your type and why is it me
ow
I mean I just genuinely want to know
this is not supposed to be a pickup line
oh also uh I want to add really quickly
when we met up in Japan uh promo wasn't
there and Kiara kept asking about Pomo
and she kept being like hey what about
pomu do you know this about no no no
my phone
[Music]
I mean
actually
so my my next month's members only
wallpaper
I will reveal something now I'm sorry
it's not related to the other girls but
I'm gonna hoverboard with purple I'm
remembering tomorrow I
I send you
you are this to draw me my name is
there's a little reference to you in
there
I can't wait oh my God oh my
[Music]
gosh I can't wait to see it
I have to use the restroom oh okay okay
too much excitement and too much wine
we know can we get to think of a
actually you can chat tell me yeah for
the next round good one okay
come on chat
[Music]
thank you
oh oh
I like
um
maybe nothing that's related to oh
that's interesting
that's an interesting one I will choose
this one thank you for the gifted
members of 15
minutes that will come out as an
interesting piece of art you have to
think about what will give you the best
result and the best confusion to the
next person who sees it
[Music]
oh
I don't know oh I like that one actually
okay hold on I'm gonna write that one
down
or cannot get advice from chat
can you can explain me something I've
been seeing a lot of the like
what is that where it come from
[Music]
no no it's like because
why is it just recently that it's become
so popular
know I don't know I guess more people
here Australian saying oh no no
because I I saw it I think where I
started seeing it is do you guys know
new jeans
oh yeah yeah yeah I knew like one song
yeah that like popped up the popular one
yeah all the members are fluent in
English and one of them is from
Australia and she always says Nara and
and then they make a joke about it don't
worry so I'm the one from oh that's not
everywhere else too
yeah we have a couple Australians in
England so they say Noir I think that's
yeah that's why I got popular yeah this
is because we have like so many
Australians
I wanna learn a proper British or or
something else action
[Laughter]
[Music]
when I was in Japan the other day I I
was walking by like a store which the
name I took a photo actually it was
literally nor
it's the hair and makeup I will upload
the picture hair and makeup
right now actually no no no no no
[Music]
yeah yeah
tweet write s
is what smelly why did I tweet what
the Discord oh that's when I was typing
up your script
and I just didn't delete it I was lazy
okay well if you if you want to go to
the nor hair and makeup place I posted a
picture now you will find it easily
Twitter oh on Twitter it's real it's for
real
Naruto
[Music]
oh my gosh you're right
it looks really good it looks so trendy
too I think it looks a little I mean
that sign is pretty beat up
I guess so kind of cheap they have to
re-renovate it
oh no maybe now with all the new
customers incoming they will have the
shirts there's your popularity yes get
your horror and your makeup done yeah we
should go we should do one more like
normal around or so because yeah good
proms now okay okay
I need a second one too
share some with me okay I like this one
take the one that's already written
place the word with our names
yeah
that is uh thank you Maple Leaf why
I made it even better I'm ready Freddy
my name's not even Freddie
[Music]
what's happening
what does that mean you'll see
[Music]
oh my goodbye
I'll figure it out and and that to me
and that to me you don't let me down now
don't let me down how do I
oh I'll do this I'll do this okay yeah
okay perfect perfect now uh Hey Google
here is the head all right all right I
mean I'm just being realistic here
because I don't think I could really do
it
okay okay this is words
[Music]
I sign up some questions like what is
this
perfect
ask questions just create good
good yeah right when you're the one
saying that so I'm expecting big things
now
give her a little t-shirt
touchy holes oh wow he's always naked
let's make them wear some clothes yeah
give them some clothes
otherwise this is gonna get age
restricted we don't yeah
Nina Drew her full-on breasts on stream
I think we're just
I don't know what you're talking about
the Twin Peaks she did yeah oh no oh my
god oh no
oh shoot
Bob and I need a little patch
Tick Tock time is running
yeah okay I think that's good
Cara what are you gonna cook after
stream
um
you
oh
oh my God what is the name of that Trend
um
[Music]
wait is this not as cute as I thought it
was is this maybe
laughs
I think so Rosie
[Music]
's like so pretty cute oh
okay
[Music]
why is this so detailed
I got this i got this I'll do my best
I'll do my best I'll do my best you
gotta hurry up you gotta hurry up I
don't have a lot of time
no it's so fine
there we go yeah we got plenty of time I
just started
[Music]
[Applause]
oh God
oh my God
okay you guys
saying
okay okay
hold the whole dream job I'm getting to
the point where it gets funny oh
what do you mean what is it
I am so sorry for it whoever sees this
this know that I tried
you guys get it right chat
do they really I think though
[Music]
oh my God this is good
okay maybe it's a nog maybe it's not
good
veiny so done with their [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
no you love us
honestly really honest all the time
that's my European genes that I can't
hold back so I wish I wish I could maybe
maybe I should be tsundere maybe oh
it's submit it I think that's good right
giving my homework early
filter no filter at all
sometimes good though speak your mind
say it loud and proud
for the people in the back
I will always speak the truth whenever I
can all right are you ladies ready no
yes
yeah
show me
babysitting Rosemary oh this is so cute
oh yeah
[Music]
you're happy really you're working at
night
this is just too stressful I'm gonna
like yeah
[Music]
don't worry do not worry about this if
you don't know don't worry about it yeah
there we go
anticipated confusion
great Finance been erased
we are doing the worm on the Dance Floor
[Laughter]
[Music]
Yeah by herself for a big strong sexy
unrealistic
[Music]
[Applause]
is so cool
I like how your breasts are touching the
floor before your feet
there is no floor yeah
I thought she was like Superman flying
through the air
Victorious why did you send this
[Music]
[Laughter]
in case you don't know every time I'm
sick that's what Nina calls me okay I
have to tell you ages ago Rosalie and I
went on a trip
and uh she was like on another
co-worker's couch right Millie uh I
almost said Millie parfait Millie
parfait's couch and she was just like
and she really looked like that like
Victoria child she was like oh I'm just
[Music]
and Billy was on the floor
both of his arm and like caressing
roseme's arm well Rosemary was on
Millie's couch like dying
dramatic
that shows you who the real ones are man
who are there when you're dying right
and you're dying Victorian child
I was laughing I'll be honest
I noticed I was like not feeling those
like oh my God I feel so bad and you
know it's like haha you look like a
dying Victoria
okay
I said I did ask like do you want some
tea some water some Advil
you were taken care of and you were
still kind of like oh I I did you know I
didn't the air conditioner was on she
was listening to her favorite music
you'll see you as being really really
caring like that too yeah I think
you can be caring and still make fun of
your friends
until random songs
oh
[Music]
yeah until we're doing anything in like
a karaoke and roseme is feeling like a
little sick you're gonna love it it's so
cute
he really does look like a dying
Victorian child
wow
Rosemary twist
I hope that will not happen I hope
everyone will be Genki and at their
bestest yeah yeah okay can you tell me
like when we go to karaoke until five in
the morning which we will
what are some of the songs you plan to
sing oh hello projects
I mean realistically I'll probably sing
some you know Idol J-pop songs like
like what tell us
and that you do you know hello projects
[Laughter]
and and oh I guess I might you know when
it comes to uh like English songs I
might sing some um
[Applause]
oh
Fergalicious I don't know
um
and maybe uh I'll sing
um Leaving on a Jet Plane by rabbits
giving her on a Jet Plane I don't know I
don't know what I don't know that one it
is a very meaningful thought like we was
a crying now they're book bursting out
in tears oh
it's it's a song that you know it has a
lot of history because when I left Japan
after like a one year stay which is when
I joined Polo uh at the end we did like
an uh a karaoke me and Kelly did one
that was like a farewell cuddocket and
one of the songs I sang where I started
crying while singing it was a song
Leaving on a Jet Plane I don't know when
I'll be back again yeah and something
that is kind of like a PTSD song Oh no
they've been crying in Japan singing
that song yeah but you'll be back in
Japan it's like you know exactly Circle
[Music]
what would you guys sing
yes
song to impress people to impress people
I am known for my Yokai Tai so deity
because I do the dance
[Music]
oh
dance
[Music]
I know a little bit of I never learned
like all of it entirely oh you can teach
me oh you know
you know you know it's really good
Rosemary's really good at singing one of
marine song songs
no I actually don't know it yeah you did
it so well that was amazing the talking
parts and that was it
[Music]
I know that Nina keeps on talking about
you know trying to improve her singing
skills
in karaoke I typically will sing a lot
of like English like Dad Rock like
Nickelback you know stuff like that uh
but my favorite Japanese singers when I
was growing up was gagged Miyavi and I
really love me
stuff like that so I think like kind of
like I guess the dad rock version
wow that is awesome though yeah
but only old women love gack
[Music]
do you have any young cool cute friends
that love gact be honest
I don't know old women love visual K and
gact and all that stuff come on
I think visual K is still popular in
some circles yeah
oh God
I really don't have many Zoomers either
right yeah I think that's the issue yeah
usually my go-to is like old anime
openings like you're talking like old
um
Inuyasha openings and endings
we're talking like old Gintama opening
has like one of my favorite uh openings
uh endings from holic like I'll usually
do anime openings
oh oh I want to sing one song for your
girls remind me if I wanna I like when
we get there okay there's a
Mariah holic
um opening where there's a lot of
moaning
[Music]
what about you what about you
um
[Music]
why do you why are you always asking me
about temples
I'm hungry
I sing I sing like a bunch of like chica
Idol songs that I can't sing normally
because there there's no karaokes of
them that exist
[Music]
ing
machines sometimes sometimes like the
more popular groups are
um will you do the dads too maybe
and I like to sing Macross songs
[Music]
French Discord for not thinking that up
yeah okay micro song is always goat yes
goat yes
girls I want to feel this yes
should we do like one last round and
then end it because there's hungry
people okay yeah let's do one more or we
can just zatsu for the other round what
do you prefer
[Music]
I feel I feel as we keep drawing I don't
think I'm gonna draw any better because
I've had a little bit of wine drop
better
it's not the point of the Guard tech
phone
I I I'd be okay to talk if everyone else
is cool with talk people want the zatsu
in my chat okay
probably because we stopped talking when
we draw yeah that's true
draw mode or something that you could
just like uh
I have an answer let's let's imagine a
different timeline where kiwawa gets
into a ninja Sanji Ian generation not to
replace someone just as an additional
member which generation would Chihuahua
be in Plaza light
because you were early on and off
right in terms of time but where would
you like fit in and see you like getting
along well in etherea also yeah I
thought I was gonna say ethereum oh yeah
because we have a lot of uh yeah we have
a lot of singers
and honestly I could use another
extrovert
everyone in like etherea they're just
like so like extroverted like even like
and not like I don't know
I wonder
of course I would wanna be in lazulite
though because you probably
come come come
I just feel like early on yeah I feel
like it would because uh the uh myth
debuted I think before lazulite right
yeah yeah yeah my instant reaction was
like well you'd be in the first gen I'm
your Senpai I know
do you girls have like a like a quite
the Senpai cool high like I don't know
thing going on or not at all
not that much I feel I feel like some
people call us Senpai but we don't
really think of it for example Ike calls
me Nina Senpai but I'm two months a
senpai to him and for example I have
zero respect for Pomo as my son
for example me and Rosie have two months
between debuts and obviously I don't
trust her and like I'll ask her for
advice on stuff but in a lot of times
like I might have really unique things
happen in my stream that Rosemary might
not be able to give me advice on because
she hasn't dealt with that as a senpai I
think in like uh for hololive you guys
have a much more
obvious like Senpai kohai culture
yeah yeah also because there's so much
time in between yeah that's what I was
thinking well I think a lot of us we all
kind of grew together because we were
all
so short in between debuts
[Music]
and who's the most reliable
me what genuinely uh since debut KOMU
like you you you did my freak I told
Pomo I didn't I couldn't find anybody
for my outro and she made me my outro
despite having just debuted and being
busy
Anita Pomo has been one of my most
reliable senpais since the start
genuinely
that's so sweet
what's your statement to that
um
well you know I just
oh oh my stomach is growling I love her
a lot I always will like give me her
advice give me her stuff no no no
um
good good sample you wear the Senpai
title very well
oh
and she'll always I feel like everyone's
so busy and everyone kind of like for
example I don't I never joined any scary
game collabs I will not force myself to
do a scary game but I feel like homo as
Senpai will always go out of her way to
try and like make sure she's interacting
with everybody she's joining everyone's
collabs she's there for everybody oh I
feel really really goes out of our way
to do that kind of stuff
okay I'm lying she's
nor
yeah she's a norm what what but doesn't
that just mean no yeah no I I feel like
for my senpai's personally a lot of them
are pretty introverted and like kind of
you know in their own little bubble and
I feel poem has been consistently the
Senpai that's tried our hardest to get
out of the bubble and to try and help us
and to like even if she's like kind of
shy and not feeling it she's always like
trying
I don't think it means it means Senpai I
think any like who's the only one yeah
the most reliable in Ian and generous
reliable I'm not really the type of
person to like reach out first like if I
have like a problem I'll try to like
usually like fix it myself I feel like
one person who's very like Tech oriented
would be like that's what I was gonna
say yeah yeah but I don't know I guess
there's like a few people who are like
if you have an issue with this here's
this thing yeah yeah yeah yeah there's a
few members I think who um don't use
Discord very often so like they just it
does not they just don't like answer as
often but there's a couple people that
are very active on the Discord so if we
have a problem they're really quick to
answer yeah yeah
and one of my so one of our one of our
co-workers Kiara his name is Shu he like
until I went on a trip to Japan with
like him and other people I didn't
really get to interact with him a lot
but he has always helped me with
different stuff that went wrong like he
he wouldn't be streaming and he's like
oh I see that Nina and Scarlet have a
problem and he'll jump in to help us fix
oh yeah wow I always told him like a
deal as a co-worker he's wonderful you
know because sometimes the closer you
are to people the more you kind of help
each other out but having a co-worker
that you're not really close with you
don't share jokes with you don't you
know but they still help you when they
know they can help
they'll just be like here's the fix for
this if you ever have this one oh yeah
yeah
[Music]
oh what about you yeah what about you
I think like the the answer would be
probably amen I mean nowadays
I'm not really receiving much help just
because I'm a pro
oh yeah yeah but definitely in the early
days that would always get help from
Ahmed I think
um
I'm trying to also be reliable and help
out like plan some projects and also
tell people like give them advice like I
think I give I give someone like
thumbnail advice like I give crony from
now why advice can you give me
thumbnails
well I mean I wouldn't say my thumb is a
really really special but you know
was motivated
motivation so I wonder oh yeah okay the
Advent calendar yeah yeah I hope people
can see me as someone reliable
um it's nice to be relied on right
feels nice so I will be more reliable
I want to be reliable yeah we'll be that
Senpai because I have to be I'm from
Virginia
you know you you don't you shouldn't
pressure yourself that much yes you're
the first gen but I think every other
person that comes into the company you
know we're all professionals and you can
do your best to help everybody but at
the same time like don't don't put that
pressure on you
I don't know it's not a pressure it's
it's a pleasure not a pressure
[Laughter]
that was very old
laughs
kind of words
trying to get better at English for my
whole life now
I think another thing too is like
sometimes you want to be a really good
Senpai but a lot of people can be pretty
independent and that's okay yeah
I think in our uh Ian there's like most
people are always very moving very
independently that's what it appeared to
me
ask for help
yeah
we have been here I know so often I'll
be like I want to ask about something in
my chat will be like you should ask so
and so and I'm like I don't want to
bother them but uh
[Music]
I'm sure they wouldn't my day would be
happy probably get a message from you no
we definitely I feel like everyone's
always so independent the only times I
ever asked for help is usually for like
music I'll ask for help we have a lot of
people who know music and Ian too
you have so many like talented like
Petra oh my God yeah do so much stuff on
her own yeah like a production company
yeah I know she's cracked
I wish I had so many skills I wish you
could do though you just have different
skills yeah yeah
I guess so
[Music]
happy I'm so sad oh my God girls wow
where do we go for dinner if we go for
dinner
where do you want to go wait we're going
for dinner yeah we're here
to go for dinner I need to fix my hair
um yeah where do you want to go oh yeah
are you good at grilling can you yeah
I'm afraid of the grill
places they Grill it for you anyway but
I think the grilling yourself is more
fun I think so too yeah so difficult
I don't mind helping to grill but I'm
always really happy when somebody else
grows
I know I used to always be the one who
lets others grow but like with like
non-holo friends in the past but
whatever every time I went grilling with
whole life en members I'm I end up being
the griller a lot of the time
look at me in the eyes do you want to
grill or not I think that do you want to
grill over I would probably over Grill
things sometimes oh I like because I
like that I like it a little bit I don't
mind it I don't yeah I don't mind it
like over-grounded
I've been to yakanika so many times that
I I have like some knowledge for example
after like a little bit of grilling you
should always ask the canyons and the
the staff to change your grill because
it will change the taste yeah yeah I
feel like every time I went they've
always done it like they know when to do
it right oh yeah sometimes they do it
for you but sometimes they don't notice
so you're gonna be like somebody Mustang
Ohio
[Music]
good morning oh it's already very light
in the evening but I guess good morning
yeah if you want I will grill for you
give stop secret money to grill for you
we should all be grilling there
shouldn't only be one person
inaugural I cannot Grill okay I'm happy
if you guys can Grill I bought a little
Grill recently I'll practice oh
something on top of the grill and then
you take it off after a few seconds oh
but I'm so bad at knowing when to take
it off and all and then I feel like I'm
almost like fumbling I'm like I'm gonna
drop I'm gonna drop the meat everywhere
you will see but free a lot of y'all can
eat for places though the staff can cook
for you and especially if you tell them
that we're beginners I can pull the Baka
guys it's about doing it yourself but I
cannot access how happy even other
people can do it
yeah
actually uh but when staff do it I feel
like kind of embarrassed when they they
Grill it you know how they think is best
and then oftentimes it like is still way
too red for my personal preference wait
yeah
I'm I've been trying
I think like you said like one of the
meats was like
right uh maybe
um
your steak Kiana oh no now medium rare
is fine oh that's amazing yeah that's
good but maybe I maybe a few more
seconds
[Laughter]
what's the order what's the order it's
rare medium rare no no it's blue oh blue
blue is a thing yeah I've never seen a
Blue Cow before
it's blue
what that's just like really really raw
I guess that's wrong real the size of
the steak
I've never heard does it come from a
blue cow or
called Pomo rain puff ninji sanjian's
first wave lazulite I'm green
color blind does that even cooked is it
like cooked or where medium rare medium
medium well okay I would probably prefer
a medium don't say the medium well don't
say it don't say it
I mean medium is fine just but I will
only go for medium when like out of
group pressure because I don't want
people to judge me
over the years I've been I've started to
enjoy a medium very much and Yeah medium
is premium as we've heard
in your defense yeah again this is I'm
just gonna say this very broadly I have
heard from people who own Korean
barbecues that you should be well
cooking a lot of your Korean barbecue
Meats oh really because typically like
it's better to just well cook them just
to be on the safer side
um
a lot of you know since you're not
getting a steak at a steakhouse it's
like thinner it's really thinner yeah I
think that's okay
as long as it's not bleeding I think I'm
good
yes I'm
the same way I don't like if it looks if
my plate turns red I'm like but even
like like medium rare medium rare has
like
Ken has a lot of blood right that's the
ketchup okay but I have had raw like
really good quality of course raw beef
before
and the Capers and the mustard
it's really good it can't be really good
but I would prefer to just Grill it
that's fair that's fair
yeah oh girls have any like vegetarians
or vegans
well when you like rounds I don't know
that I know I don't think if we do I
don't know if they've ever told us yeah
I have met like I think I'm one of the
people who's met one of the most members
and I don't think anyone's been veggie
some some people don't like fish
um
oh my chat says Ren is pescatery what's
a pescatarian oh it only eats fish no at
one time he got an Uber Eats and it was
just a chicken finger with tartar sauce
that's it
all right
okay she's vegetarian and to give it
more I always forget I always offer her
meat and she's like you know I'm
vegetarian
I've met Mika like three times and we
always have this problem I feel so bad
oh I wonder then if you remember my
preferences for drinks you don't drink
alcohol
[Applause]
drinking at our meeting I think Petra
wasn't drinking oh I think the tree poor
Lira I kept ordering drinks for both me
and Olivia oh my God I would never want
to go at your pace in a little bit but
she wasn't drinking as much as YouTube
yeah
and you and you you guys are going off
we have the most and Kiara and I were
not drinking the most sober karaoke
that's what we'll do
well you know kind of stay sober too not
accidentally say something and then get
bonked by my company
yummy
I just remember the place where we were
at they had a limited amount of pizzas
[Music]
like okay wait do you still have the
pizza they're like yes and we were so
happy we're like oh my God yes but it
wasn't even that great I feel like
everything else was better than the
pizza okay okay
it was just like we were so surprised
because it was late in the evening
really late and if it's so limited they
said what like five ten days
and like we were like no way they still
have the pizza but they did what's wrong
with them why nobody ordered the beef oh
no I love the pizza yeah yeah yeah this
is so unpopular what you learned the
reason why
I didn't I honestly like did not think
it was below average I thought it was
good it was all right I was enjoying the
other food a lot like the pizza was all
right
sorry you weren't even there and we'll
keep on talking about this day it's okay
let's let's include her when we go to
Japan the four of us it's planned it's
already happening I want to go to zawa
to Thrift Store please
you know it's kind of rough on old
people you know okay yeah it's a hill
Nina you'll have to like we go on a
Monday we go on a Monday afternoon
there's not a lot of people we go to La
foreign
oh
um I'm the one I'm the one walking slow
when you get out of there it's better
and the other streams yeah
every time I walk for Turkish when it's
crowded yeah oh I I think about the
things I would do to these people
oh my God please don't beat me up one
day
I'm just gonna come in with boxing
gloves
um don't worry it wasn't me I'm never
gonna beat you up
she'll beat you up and desert you
no
and then she's gonna be there
with my crib I'll be like oh no because
I'll just just walk you in some more
I'll lock you inside it's a banana
because she had never gone before it
wasn't so bad actually how was it it was
mildly crowded but not so bad but
there's always so many aggressive people
around there that like yeah they like
try to offer you or try to get you to go
places or offer flies yeah the story
people yeah I think that's way stronger
in other places like uh Shinjuku oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
not that bad and or these kind of things
yeah I did get awkward every once in a
while someone comes but then they say
hey would you like to join this model
agency oh my God yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I'm glad so my Senpai told me at
the airport she's like people will
approach you Nina and they're gonna try
to interview you you have to say no you
cannot and thank God she did because I
would have been like yeah of course I
want an interview yeah because I
realized that like you know my voice my
oh I did once
um like many many years ago when I was
in in somebody else you want to join
this company oh I did once go ahead and
like went for like the interview oh and
then and then I think they took some
pictures to possible
I don't think it was Polaroids but yeah
I went ahead and I mean it wasn't too
bad like they had a nice decent nice
like office in a good location and it
wasn't too bad but generally I wouldn't
really recommend because you never know
what you're doing
yeah and it was fun yeah it wasn't two
sauce
I don't know I think it was fine but I
went like to a lot of
um like self-initiated uh interviews and
stuff as well like to you know do stuff
wanted to get a job wow like in that
industry but yeah the self uh uh what
did I say self-initiated ones are
definitely
on the less satisfied yeah yeah you can
at least like look into the company and
yeah not someone on the street
this is scary yeah
I'll be your bodyguard
no no no it was really fun it was okay
you had a good time yeah but if you need
me just tell me I can bark at people
like a like a little dog
Chihuahua
[Laughter]
feel like you are you wouldn't be that
intimidating what was it mean
yeah you'd be surprised just the barking
that's the intimidating thing they don't
call me Bros me for nothing Kiara
I know you've met her and she seems so
shy but when she has like something to
defend she gets like fired up her arms
expand three times yeah I'm like yeah
I'm like Popeye yeah
[Laughter]
who are you gonna call
Busters
can I ask um Kiara when you're in Japan
do you have a favorite neighborhood or a
favorite and like please don't say like
your favorite favorite spot because I
don't want people to you know but do you
have like a favorite
stuff that you like to do
and like a favorite place I used to have
a favorite like area but not So Much
Anymore these days they're like
um I feel like
I like a lot of places I wouldn't say I
have a favorite one but things to do I
just I mean I just always like going to
karaoke and yeah
shopping also stresses me out at the
same time
yeah too much shopping yeah but I do
want to do like a bit more sightseeing
because I when I lived in Japan I didn't
do much sightseeing it just kind of like
I mean certain I know a lot of places in
Tokyo and Osaka but
I want to see like different corners of
Japan that would be nice but there's one
place that I used to always go to that I
always like when I'm in Japan with
someone who's there for the first time I
always bring them there it's called
enoshima oh my God I'm gonna be going
there for the first time next week
yeah it's one of my dream places to go
to I just never had a chance
no right what
wait what yeah I'm going to Japan next
week
[Music]
you kind of is that something you're
allowed to say yeah yeah I've already
talked about it
if it makes you feel any better I too
was surprised she said it I too was like
wait what she said it yeah I've already
talked about it on stream before
okay let me if you already plan to go to
enoshima let me tell you so so there's
this I mean energy man this is like a
bigger place but the one thing that you
really need to cook right no no no it's
an island like a little island
when you walk over to it over a bridge
ah you probably saw it in an anime
didn't you no
probably look me at the eyes and tell me
you'd never take a trip based off
something you saw in an anime okay I I
used to play this game called love plus
and then you get to take your girlfriend
to enoshima and and I just really wanted
to always go with it and I wanted to
bring her along together
with my anime girlfriend is
are you bringing your anime girlfriend
are you bringing her
maybe
an anime because apparently I've been
recently it wasn't in an anime again it
shows up quite a bit
oh bunny girl Senpai I think
apparently also in bocce it was a multi
recently
be prepared you have to like walk up and
down so many stairs oh there are
escalators
a lot of walking guys you're really
exhausted make sure to like walk around
the whole island you can easily do it
and even like pop wonderful day what do
you like what do you like in on the
island tell us like everything what's
what's the tea uh there's a secret spot
that I showed um you know people before
as well
um but when I went there the other time
when it was bad weather it wasn't even
it was really underwhelming
[Music]
but there's like once you go up the like
beginning path where all the shops are
you will know it when you get there then
if you go to the right and then for like
I have like a secret path
yeah
[Music]
there's a secret plan that leads it to
like a little store
um yeah and in summer there's a lot of
people there but during like colder days
not so much but it's like a really
serene
seen for me like oh you sit there and
then you look at the water and just just
I don't know it's just flavoring I know
I've just been wanting to go to the
beach recently
I just really want to go at the beach
yeah I'm gonna go to the beach too but
it's not like warm warm enough for the
beach yet right not really uh
Japanese people will probably agree with
me but kanaka beaches are definitely not
the pretty beaches in Japan
is in I mean there's a lot of surfers
there but it's not really like
especially in the cinema you don't go I
mean some people still go there to swim
but it's not though no I don't want to
swim I just want to watch the beach I
just want to see the ocean I don't want
to swim
yeah washing is fine or or surfing if
you suddenly take up a surfing hobby
I've surfed before
later on in my life maybe one day I want
to move to Portugal have a lemon tree
and sir
wow
oh surfing fairy well not like well okay
so not I couldn't do like big waves but
there's like a really thin board you can
get and like you ride on like the the
really thin part of the water with it I
don't remember what it's called
um
the skimboarding was like yeah yeah yeah
that was look that looks more like what
I
would do
[Music]
oh
yo can you do a flip
yeah yeah
yeah I'll do just you know Kiana you're
showing your screen just in case
[Laughter]
I completely forgot
oh God that's fine you know what's the
worst part I saw us talking on your
channel and I felt like I should have
been like hey we should make you should
make yourself like big screen to talk to
us
big camera to talk to us like you know
the big like
talking camera
anyway yeah
[Music]
anyway where were we hunger what yeah I
am still hungry yeah I think food time I
think it's full time all right wait guys
what what restaurant are we going to
what where are we meeting
okay we caught on such a tangent after
talking about how to grill the meat I
just want to say thank you so much for
joining me I had so much fun I'm so
sorry the game didn't work if you want
to do more collabs I will make a better
point to research the game anything that
is not Uno anything that is not Uno I am
down yeah I will look for co-op games
for us okay
okay I love you girls yeah
you know it wasn't there it wasn't
didn't pull me like say that she's
planning something big and I don't
really think you are you really planning
something big no it's big even I heard
about that
collab a big one did you just like say
that a long time ago I think we were
talking about maybe doing something but
we just got busy yeah it never it never
happened
you should have a crap game a crab game
crap wait a game I never played that
before I'm afraid we'll be too toxic oh
my God
friendships are broken if we ever played
craft game
like you would never want to be oh yeah
I go feral I go first that's so bad
and but you know what uh I I wanna I
wanna play yeah we should continue on an
idea I want something bigger you know
what do you want to play
I'm not many ideas we can talk about it
yeah
but yeah I want to see if we can get
some I mean I would love to like always
have you girls to myself but I want to
see some other girls
yeah yeah it's been nice though thank
you for accepting me like decent and
opening up to me and you taking me in
like you know I'm I belong here it is
really nice to be so welcomed with open
arms thank you I told my audience after
Alaska lab we like we started talking an
hour before the collab and then we
collabed and then we kept talking and
the only reason we stopped because we
were both yeah so we're like we gotta
eat but it's like right now honestly I
know the thing that stuff is once again
the food the hunger no always food that
prevents the further it really is I only
have breakfast and now it's almost
midnight so I I mean oh my God
please what are you making tonight by
the way did you say no I'm not sure I
have two two recipes left with
ingredients from you know the hello
people yeah
[Music]
I literally just take a salmon I put
like a foil around it I put lemon tomato
garlic garlic garlic garlic and then you
just put the foil in you put it in the
oven
salmon is so easy
okay hungry sounds very intense right
now
thank you girls for having me bye-bye
thanks for having me too thank you for
having me thank you for having me
sorry for the foreign
yeah this is a normal day I have worse
things happening
Uno honestly the whole like one and a
half hours of figuring out how to play
Uno were really precious to me
[Music]
yeah I just have to say I love that what
we got to the
um switch part of Uno it didn't work for
different people so it wasn't just me
the problem
we are all the problems we know who the
real problem is
he saw jian's first wave
I went to the servers and I deleted your
names
now I have to send all those friend
invites again tomorrow I feel so bad for
that all right fine that's fine one by
one step by step yeah thanks for
watching guys
[Music]
are you guys gonna talk to your chat or
are you gonna no no no okay let's just
talk a little bit I don't know okay if
you guys are here after one I don't know
okay
oh
[Music]
I'm fine
muted
[Music]
hold on I'm still on okay bye
thank you
[Music]
foreign