[Music]
oh honey
do you feel the music baby
[Music]
me
foreign
so emotionless
[Applause]
[Music]
something to keep
don't look me now it's just the two of
us
[Music]
baby underneath
give me
[Music]
me uh
who's watching us
[Music]
[Laughter]
i still had that
ah
in the
in obs huh
oopsie
sorry that was
uh i'm i've already i already like
lowered the volume last time so at least
it wasn't like
super loud right
[Music]
okay
come here come here little chat no you
can't run away
or you can run but you can't hide
let me put these things here meow
i should tweet something i didn't
tweet anything
uh because it's just a super chat rating
so i felt like oh whatever
um
streaming now
okay let's lure them in
learning alluring them in uh oh that's
the wrong link what the [\h__\h] oopsie
okay
a simple tweet must suffice
super chat reading i have
some pineapple fanta here with me um
it's pretty good
let's see
um
[Music]
you know what i was thinking
once the birthday concert is over i have
new pictures to put over here
and higher quality ones hopefully
because these these are all like shitty
quality screenshotted off of the
live concert
yes elsa yeah i am you don't know why
i'm wearing this today
you wanna know
because i saw a certain chicken in the
stream chat in the beginning asking if
you guys rolled out the orange carpet
for the empress so i was like okay
that's the key word
i will be impressed today
here i am
i felt inspired
i saw that
i saw it
okay now we need some music
doshi yo
doshi okana
this room
ah this room is so hot
again
i [\h__\h] want air conditioning
why do apartments
in austria does not come with air
conditioning it's getting hotter the
earth is getting hotter have you noticed
ding dong austria have you realized have
you noticed something that you're
feeling [\h__\h] hot in your home
yeah that's right how about you start
building air conditioning
oh my god so [\h__\h] hot oh oh my god
the moment i sit down
[Music]
you can't buy a unit yourself um well
the thing is like you know i've i've
looked at like you know
how would you call them
like some kind of like before like years
ago i looked at some
like
air cooler thingies not not proper air
conditioners
but like smaller versions of it i guess
and i i remember testing them out and i
remember they were [\h__\h]
they didn't really
work well
so
if anything you would have to buy the
proper thing and then do construction to
like
you know
make a hole in your wall i guess
and i don't know
like usually depending on
you know what apartment you have they
might not allow it
uh
too hot what the [\h__\h] portable units
yeah they're just [\h__\h]
they're not good they're never good
um
but i i think i'll have to look into it
because i don't want to suffer all
summer what the [\h__\h]
otherwise how about
just for the summer
i moved to
what's a cold country england
no not england
they're not in the eu anymore
[Music]
stupid england making it harder for me
to go there you little [\h__\h]
how about norway then
or finland i don't know
[Laughter]
you little [\h__\h]
alright i still didn't find any music
how about some um
what are what are these
hello
all these [\h__\h] audio settings
keep on changing every time i restart
the [\h__\h] pc
only the english are allowed to insult
england well that's good then because i
am very much english aren't i
look at me being so dapper don't i look
very dapper today
cheerios
oh man i feel sorry for that for
the english people who get
made fun
uh like this uh off like this
by obviously not only me
uh
sure thank you for the red super chat
holy macaroni what's up
[Music]
um he's not on the screen right now he's
like more over to that side
outside of the screen because he's kind
of shy but he's playing for us right now
live live music from the one and only
mozart my buddy
my man
hey hey hey we should move to the
ballroom
but then i have to like bring everything
over there
[Music]
wow it's getting really dark
don't talk to me anymore i'm busy okay
i'm back
[Music]
so we're going to be reading super chat
though
because i i got some catching up to do
oh
you know what arrives today besides
uh bale's super snack box
you couldn't really call it a super
snack box this is [\h__\h] huge
didn't look inside yet though yeah it
took me stuff it already arrived a while
ago apparently but my neighbor had it
and um what the [\h__\h] guys
it's two insanely big boxes
and then some longer things that i don't
know what that is
the document presents
i didn't open that one either yet but
it's in
this it's huge
[Music]
so
i said before
we should do a
like a review
another review but like an opening
unboxing
presents unboxing members only probably
uh because i feel like well i need to do
a premise on this room anyway so i'm
thinking maybe tomorrow we do
uh
members only chit chat and a hand cam
unboxing
yeah sorry i turned mozart down a bit
yeah told him to go further away
uh
plus
uh we could
we could also
additionally
finally
re-watch
the dokomi concert
uh yeah
[Music]
if we wanna
ah yeah yeah i'll just do wind waker
weekend on sunday
cause um i feel like you guys need um
members only stream
yeah yeah yeah
okay and then next week i'll be doing uh
the australian snack box review
originally i wanted to like even do it
as a collab
um by me sending her an austrian snack
box review
snack box to review um but then it
didn't line up
and she's not even home right now so
i'll send it to her
um later on
so it's not much of a collaboration
anymore not quite but yeah
[Music]
they go straight no no no not real
i don't know is that a mosquito bite
that i feel on my leg what the [\h__\h]
which [\h__\h]
bastard did that
so my legs i think have been like
swollen
[Music]
after the flight and also i think before
the flight too
yeah my feet are so [\h__\h]
i need to take a hot
hot bath
[Music]
i'm on the road all day and don't have
time for your stream
that's okay you can watch it afterwards
[Music]
yeah
you should afterwards yeah i kind of
wanted to do it yesterday but then i
fell asleep so early i fell asleep
at like 11 p.m
and then i woke up around like 8 30 or
something
but then i took a nap before the stream
and now i'm kind of like drowsy
drowsy
[Music]
whose stream do you think you're
watching
ah waiting on the train station oh it's
hot
you managed to have a nice lunch no i
only had
i only had like a
breakfast um
pastry
that was filled with
raspberry
cream and raspberry and yogurt cream
[Music]
you must put your leg on ice
yeah i don't
know
it's not that bad anymore i think i
think
i
i didn't get a key what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
i forgot
[Music]
oh there we go
no it was on purpose because there were
not enough people in the beginning
to hear my
call
mmm
no this is cute yes now i am kiana
[Music]
so we're gonna get some [\h__\h] done
and then there will be
this
music video coming out you already um
saw the teaser
not really there's not much to see
because blurry but i think you can make
out the lyrics
in the teaser actually pretty easily
even though it's blurry right
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah did you look at it did you try to
make it out
[Music]
gonna listen in today because it worked
but i love you wawa
cute
love you too
i guess
you guys are cute
hey can i have some new new mods mozart
i have a few more tracks but i want a
longer one i mean i have this one
but they're like no
more i want new
new moods on it
mozart put on a new track is that all
you can do
[Music]
there we go
well you got audio stuck
got something long maybe
oh this is k310
[Music]
wow
audio stock
they got rid of that
probably only if you are listening while
you're logged in i guess
that's nice
okay and this is six minutes long so
it's pretty pretty good
okay and then how about
[Music]
what is this
not that's too short help um
these are short short they're also short
what about this one
you like jazz
[Music]
it turned mozart into jazz
don't know what i think about that
no
that's not mozart that's not my man
oh
seven minutes okay free free free
[Music]
oh it's like spring
i see jumping bunnies on grass
[Music]
so sophisticated
amazing
well i am so i'm getting i'm becoming so
sophisticated by listening to this
aren't i
okay let's get this
okay so this is
310.
and then we got
mozart
333 apparently okay nice
let's show
oh sure okay
well then we shall start uh begin to
read
those naughty naughty little super chats
holizer where are you
let's see
what you guys have been trying to tell
me for so long that i've been ignoring
for so long
literally when i go and holize literally
everything okay it's not even as bad
as it was a few days ago i guess
it's really everything is hollow cure
[Music]
so unoriginal girls play something else
i'm dissing them [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
no i understand you would want to play
that because oh
we are in the game so cool
oh my god vampire survivors whatever
wow
amazing
[Laughter]
i can't stop watching them
yeah you better be watching me right now
okay where do i start reading um
[Music]
you guys know
is that maybe stanley
thanks stanley
[Music]
working the friar that's all right you
got you gotta be working
[Music]
okay stanley oh muhammad
i mean
does viva happy yeah viva happy has like
oh no those are just membership messages
okay
stanley parable ultra deluxe
let me put up the thumbnail
here we go
and
mario here we go oh [\h__\h] what did i move
oh you stay there
this is what we're reading i know
there's a lot of going on on this on the
screen right now oh this is what we're
reading
okay
[Music]
thank you for the pinky cat food bad
fonts thank you
[Music]
oh yeah just yesterday i bought new cat
food yeah yeah yeah
this movie is like
i feel like she is demanding not only
wet food in the morning time these days
but she also demands
wet food like later on in the day
and i'm like no
no lady young lady no
i mean
i guess i could give it to him
but i don't know
we've established a tradition in this
household
of having wet food in the morning and
now she's like bitching about it
stand firm don't give in
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
no yeah i'm i'm thinking like maybe
maybe it's good to have like some
variety you know
um
defense movie
yeah when my
my bff was taking care of my cats a
while ago
um
she was like repeatedly
she was like are you sure are you sure i
shouldn't give her more she's like
really annoying about it and i'm like
don't give in
she's probably even more annoying to you
about it because you
you don't you know normally take care of
her
so she thinks she can get something out
of you
no no no no gotta stay
strong stay strong
[Music]
yes if i if i cave then she wants it
every [\h__\h] day and that's annoying
and
whatever
so
they will continue to eat like cables
although i've been trying to give them
different cables too
um like i don't always give them the
same kibbles i try to bring in some
variety
so they they don't always eat the same
[\h__\h]
[Music]
why are you yawning at 4pm
my
[Music]
huh
okay
[Music]
so yes here comes google
why do we yawn
when we are not
tired
causes of yawning even if you're not
tired another reason you may on is
because the body wants to wait okay no
this is what we're not talking about
[Music]
why do you yawn when you're not sleeping
here there you go
[Music]
where's the [\h__\h] answer
yawning is a response to boredom
see well maybe i'm just [\h__\h] bored of
you
no okay uh
boredom isn't the only young factor if
someone you're conversing with yawns
chances are you will too but maybe
someone in the chat yawned first in an
ions okay
[Music]
and
maybe i'm just [\h__\h] tired
so what let me be tired if i am tired
i just woke up okay
ah there's more a new theory suggests
that yawning cools the brain and the
sinuses may play a key role and see i've
been saying i'm hot so probably my my
brain wants to cool me uh-huh
the brain ex the brain is exquisitely
sensitive to temperature changes and
therefore must be protected from
overheating yo that actually fits with
what i'm experiencing
[Music]
i'm really feeling hot
okay
i think there was another one um
is a form of social communication
[Music]
okay so
so no more complaints now
i yawn when i [\h__\h] yawn okay
you cannot stop me
and you will have to deal with it now i
feel like me yawning should be your your
littlest concern
unknown
one time i don't turn on
hyper chat and it's like
falling apart
[Music]
come on
chat
okay i'm closing it
let me let me go get the hyper chat
eh wait what say it again
[Music]
wait okay wait
apparently i didn't skip it i was gonna
go there anyway
it's all according to cake
wait a minute my youtube is [\h__\h]
dying
[Music]
oh my god
just open up
open the [\h__\h] up youtuber
i know what i can do i can go twitter
and click click the link
[Music]
it's so hot
oh [\h__\h] hell youtube
so slow no it doesn't work either
okay i'll be looking at the obs
comments for a while
they're tiny but
i gotta deal with it
okay i'll get back to the other super
chats in a moment
uh did i'm not back but i'll get to the
super chats that you guys are
mentioning in a moment when i'm done
with this okay e-type fan one dungeon
scratch cut me off thank you and skye
thank you for the resume
money for your cats and medicine thank
you oh this was when i was sick right
uh
not good times
oh there it is there it is there it is
youtuber
[Music]
and now we have hyper chat
thank you
[Music]
okay
thank you skye
thank you
i survived i [\h__\h] survived let's go
[Music]
ah that was um really bad
yeah
bad timing terrible timing
i'm just glad it seems like i got none
of the girls sick
oh
bail says there's a little birthday gift
for me
in the snack box and yo what
hey yo what
[Music]
i'm curious
all right she said she might be able to
call in uh to the snack box stream
depending on the time i guess
um okay i'll go
thank you
that was when i came back after being
sick or so but i was still sick i think
um
took me a while like even to be honest
even during the recording
i i had um i was like healthy but i
still had like
some low-key headaches
from i guess i think probably like still
after effects from being sick
didn't you say sniper stream would be
members only
no not the australian one no no no no
i don't think so
no i don't think i said that i think uh
i said the review that um
unboxing of
the
dokomi presents will be members only
yeah
yeah so that was another small
handicap
while i was
dancing so many handicaps man
but you can't stop me no no don't stop
don't stop just go your own way hmm
yeah
so thank you thai tea
out here thanks for the pinky i got made
into a bucket today finally freedom
freedom not much freedom there is there
you've squeezed into a bucket but if you
say it like that then that's good
you're welcome to see it like that so
positive what a positive chicken you are
thank you for one year of membership
support that cushion
thank you so much
yeah i hope you're still enjoying my
content
and like on the first day or maybe even
more thank you very much membership
stream tomorrow
tomorrow so i hope to see you there
thank you
jacob 47 out thank you swag for
thanksgiving not applicable
thank you
brandon duncan jade the wise thank you
soon
oh you got sick too on you i'm sorry
[Music]
popping off
the satisfied ancient shadow pencils and
logical paradoxes
[Music]
glad to have you back just sell my
membership status and the official
officially a bucket all you seem to have
joined on the same day
maybe as the other person
thank you greatly for creating this
community and love how much you how much
joy you bring i'll continue supporting
you however possible
okay
how do you pronounce the c in spanish
surida or kuida na
chu chui
chu
chu or soup
[Music]
thank you
thank you also for one full year of
support
yay a bucket bucket bucket your bucket
and we all know how much i love buckets
[Music]
thank you for your love and support i
appreciate it
[Music]
all my exams and and essays are done
this week i can stay attention freely
from now and i'm so happy for that oh
thank you
does that mean that for all
all koreans
uh the semester or like the exams
and essays
are over
so
most koreans should like who are in
school should have more time now is that
what you're saying
is that what you're saying
yes
there they are my korean friends
[Music]
okay you guys are done studying
then i shall
now that i'm back
and
my time is a little bit more or less
more open than before then i shall get
back into
studying um
yeah
okay
i will do my best
let's learn korean again although yeah i
wanted to do the colabo i need to check
with
nabi mama
not be mama
let's ask before i forget again now be
my mom i'll be my mom
and there she
is know she first tried to communicate
in english with me but her japanese is
better so at some point she was like
sorry can we communicate in japanese
so we actually communicate in learning
hong kong
and not be mama
[Music]
foreign
i don't think she'll be able to collab
until sometime next year well
miyaku
you're out of the loop then
because
she told me
that she'll collab with me
yeah
she will she told me she will
yes
yes she might be busy but she told me
she'll do it with me
she promised me
and as long as it's like before a
certain time
yeah
that's why i'm coming to korea too to
hang out with her
i get special treatment yes the hell
yeah i do
of course i do
[Music]
are you
okay
[Music]
no she did say when she did tell me she
didn't tell me until one
until when like she has time before you
know
mm-hmm
[Music]
anyway it's daijoubu all okay
yeah i'm gonna meet ami's mommy
[Music]
okay
thank you oh wait this one [\h__\h]
moment
i skipped the pinkies ellie smith thanks
to the pinky
congrats on going undefeated at midnight
ah the wrestling thing that's already so
long ago holy [\h__\h]
thank you very strong chihuahua i mean
i couldn't
couldn't quite
re-um create that strength during the
arm wrestling match but the one time i
used my prominent
left hand
i actually did win so let's just assume
that if i would have used my prominent
left hand for the whole arm wrestling
match that i would have won every single
time even against kelly even against
ahmed
it's just
i mean i had an obvious handicap yo
yes
wow
wow incredible
unbelievable
you guys everybody who's pressing x you
know i'm coming for you i'm gonna arm
wrestling with my left hand yeah
yeah
i'll be aware of that
[Music]
hmm yes i right with my left hand i mean
there's also a lot of things that i do
with my right hand but i wouldn't say i
am
bi dexterous
oh anyway so crazy thanks for the pinky
hi ken i'm glad you're almost back to
full health uh here are some funds for
cat food and medicine thank you may i
request an employee number in the drop
down oh also twitter meeting great
picture with twit with twitter circle
but that would reach you
what the [\h__\h] is twitter circle is that
like some kind of app
where you can tweet
okay i can barely lift like okay well um
you are gonna go into the usual room
it won't let me
i think cause i'm in a hyper jet
where'd you go
[Music]
where did that little [\h__\h] go here here
you are okay time out stand in the
corner and reflect on your words
get him
i got him
[Music]
wait
okay um well
i see two people saying i'm a tyrant
i'll show you tyrant
here
i'm out
[Music]
you little shits
get out of here
no [\h__\h] respect for me
you too
ah you think i didn't see that one
golden umi
okay
okay okay
i took care of a couple people using the
room very busy now
she can't get of course i can get you
all
[Music]
motion you're getting into the usual
so now you got time that even though you
didn't say
the supposedly
truth
dancing you're reaching dangerous
territory
no we're not just throwing everyone in
there referring everyone in there who's
being a rude little [\h__\h] to me
[Music]
i hope she is no tyrant exactly
kfb union forever
[Music]
i'll i'll i'll let this one go over
your little [\h__\h] i'm gonna cry
you guys are you guys are not on my side
[Music]
you guys are so mean
oh yes
no tyrant only empress yes yes
detention so merciful i really am
no
thank you for understanding
[Music]
okay
sorry sorry that i yawned
maybe i need to mute myself in the
future when i yawn that's gonna be a lot
of muting going on
lucia boing boing you a little [\h__\h]
i'm too lazy to ban all of you guys so
whatever let's continue
so crayons almost forgot you want to get
a job and an employee number well your
employee number will be um
five
five zero
and
your title
will be
ah
children's
play
set
because your crayons and the children
who come to kfp
are gonna need something to play with
so
is that
worded
well enough children's playset
i think that works
korean is tired
[Music]
you stay don't go don't sleep
what kind of logic is that
do you have a
problem with my logic
[Music]
do you have a problem with my logic
do you have a problem with my logic i
don't think you do no no no no
no problems here
only happiness
and agreement
[Music]
perfect thank you oh thank you very much
adikata thanks
elbowing
[Music]
i'm scared
is that some
copyrighted
it seems like there's an original yeah
what is this
[Music]
mute
super chat is advertising something they
made
stream
one is watching
how do you get to a stream
i just try google kiata oh and we look
at this orange
tell me please what do you see
just a boring old chicken huh maybe to
you but not to me
flying bird wow flying along and kicking
at me i don't get all that meme
because you're not watching kiana
streams wow
look at my cats wow
it was my cats to express myself that
sounds really cringe [\h__\h] you i used my
cats to express myself
when you're wearing a german stream
don't you find an exciting night
take another look
and see a frog i can see a red hair
dressed as a dog i can see a shark i can
see a snake i can see a monkey who
doesn't have a dick
no no no using your money to have a good
time i might work are you even gonna
tell him whoa dear friend you might need
to slow down
oh it slowed down
this is so good
ah
i had to not be so bottom left go and
collect some tweets and clips and post
them into your favorite reddit
oh
um who's that a whole life member
glad game of the enslave you listen to
the rules failing into your doom listen
to the voices in the usual room come on
chat let's start cooking
oh my god
so good
ah it's a recording of me
let me post it in the chat
brainwashing
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] it gets really scary
oh my god
i like it
now let's all agree to never anger kiana
again
oh
nice one
thanks for showing me
oh you guys need to listen to it too
when you got some time
[Music]
unity chat thanks for the thank you oh
wait bgm come back
mozart mozart you can continue
hi dojo hi dozer it's just like that
you need to chat says uh so i lowkey
disregarded you ordered to wear mask
cluster so we don't catch a cold because
obviously you can't get infected for a
screen but here i am now with an
inflamed nose and in need of tissues and
someone oh
wait you need to chat how did that turn
out did you did you have to see thing
how'd that turn out you how are you
feeling
how are you feeling
where are you
you're detained
[Music]
are you okay
oh my god please don't tell me
you're in the chat
where are you
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
you're doing me a concern
you're doing me a hacking
concern come back i'll see you again
soon hopefully
you need to chat
be healthy next time you better wear
that [\h__\h] mask
[Music]
told you to wear it it's not my fault
oh no
see you again sometime
so i'm on twitter okay
ah
alright thank you thank you soon
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
oh no
no right something no we can't do that
because you can only control quality by
knowing quality well
and
young lingus can't do that so i say you
you stay
you stay in your current position right
so for rise after you're saying that
he's too old for his job wants to become
a super chicken no no no no no don't
worry
maybe you're not old but you're normal
and they're just too young those zoomers
yeah don't make them
don't make
them feel you what don't make them
don't
don't let them
make you feel there we go
too old
took me a while
okay
i'm using my words
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay i'm gonna mix up my fanta
english very musukashi
[Music]
friction
black friction you change your name
and
end your profile picture what the [\h__\h]
it's probably back to normal now isn't
it
wwe world champion of myth night and now
the settings world champ oh
kiwa what will you do next oh i wonder
yeah what champion title will i be
getting next oh how about dancing
champion after this
yeah
baby
champion of life
thank you thank you thank you bucket
friction
it sounds
sounds so similar doesn't it
ultra hair extension i miss your
popsicle sortencho
[Music]
i guess i haven't had it uh
out for a long time huh oh but it is it
is on here surprise you guys want to see
the full image so actually
you know this and some others
were supposed to be used for
3d debut countdown
so but they were made a long time ago
um
and then yeah genma said you know
we can use them for anything now
they might make new ones
when we actually do get a 3d w
so i was told i can use them
yeah yeah let me see where did i put
them you want to see the full version
because they're actually full body
and they were like refined and all that
so they look really nice
[Music]
i can show you this one
if i find it
and there it is
[Music]
okay this looks really cool
oh [\h__\h] it's so big
[Music]
there we go
i chose the pose
look at that cool stance
[Music]
i say that's me yeah tilt it
where is the butt crack now huh
man that flat ass
[Music]
nice backside shot thank you yeah i
wanted something
like from the back
some cool
fighting pose but holy [\h__\h] that that
sword is so [\h__\h] short
oh one thing um
this was still
i think
like kind of outdated uh you may have
noticed in the
stream
um
in the arm wrestling stream
uh
i actually got
my skirt length and so on a little bit
fixed
uh so
yeah it should actually have been
shorter than uh during link you wish or
or
[Music]
no no not no i think it was a bit
different i think i got them too
because you can't barely make it any
shorter than this i think i got them to
lower the
the socks a little bit so that it
doesn't overlap like that
and because it shouldn't it shouldn't
normally and uh
i got them to like
like um
the skirt how you know it's supposed to
be like skin tight
but it would sometimes like stand off a
little bit like here as well so
i got them to like fix that too
so that's why it might have looked a
little bit different
[Music]
the spots
i'm not
[Music]
they sure have made it shorter
i joking i think i jokingly said
make my
spots shorter but i don't know if they
actually did it
i didn't think they would do it
maybe they did do it looked shorter to
you
maybe they did do it
um
a put this like on like a figurine
podesta thingy and then have it like oh
this looks like it could be a super
smash brothers figurine
and then we have it like standing
somewhere
in the back although i have no [\h__\h]
space or maybe up here but it's kind of
we need to turn it around turn it a
little bit tilt it a little bit
oh my tummy is saying blah blah i'm
hungry
kiana for smash
yeah i'm talking about the trophies not
amiibo i'm not talking about amiibo
oh hungry can i eat my banana
i will i'm gonna eat my banana
so hungry i might throw up
[Music]
okay
they'll make me one apparently
[Music]
yeah i always i always feel sick when
i'm too hungry
[Music]
yum
um
i went to the supermarket today and i
bought
a bunch of pears because
ever since i've been at amma's place
i've been craving pears because the
pears that she had tasted so good
[Music]
no i didn't buy a pair i bought like
five or so
i hope they're as good as the ones at
amma's place
try korean pear
is it special
[Music]
i
korean pear is a lot better i got better
than what
you have you compared them to the pears
that you get in austria
well i'll give it a try though we'll
give it a try i'll give it a try but you
can't say that i haven't tried austrian
pears
[Music]
i mean i believe you they taste
different surely but you can't
you can say they're better
[Music]
i wonder if they're like
the pears in japan because i've had
pears in japan before i think um
yeah i have to defend my country man
defend its honor
[Music]
i can't compare
okay that's funny
i didn't even notice
that did you know that su sound is very
cute
when i say tsu
[Music]
are you trying to make me say to
okay when i say foo too
[Music]
you mean fu
gosh okay
i am
on my last bite
[Music]
i like when she says the number three
what
i'm saying perfectly fine
nice fun and fresh
[Music]
[Laughter]
i would like one hour with the bucket
please hey
you go get your own bucket
go get your own bucket silly the [\h__\h]
it's my bucket my bucket is my bucket go
get your own bucket
no no no you can't just use my bucket
it's not an option ew
my bucket
we were also jealous of a bucket why
would you be jealous
you shouldn't be jealous you're on your
way to being a bucket
and so many of you are buckets
there's no need to be jealous
my bucket also i already kind of forgot
about the bucket don't worry
[Music]
i've been seeing your name pop up a lot
more these days what's going on did you
miss me
are you missing me
as expected
nobody can go on for too long without
kiwawa um
yeah
i've been seeing you interact on on
twitter a lot welcome back
now don't leave
don't leave mundo thank you
thank you for the red super chat
thank you attention
ah that was probably
like what the ending song or what
ah
i don't know what melody you're trying
to
imitate
but thank you captain
thank you
[Music]
no not stalking no no i mean he replied
to me more often
i made the song what what song
can't live without you plus oh cute
cute
[Music]
that in the background that's that's
cherry blossom petals
[Music]
nothing else don't worry
no i don't no i don't stalk anyone no no
no no no no no no no
[Music]
thank you for the right super chat
you could have told us why the ribbon is
on the right side tension we would have
accepted it you know which chimpkins are
always on your side bucket chun is such
a cutie with those stickers we
understand
mr attention happier feeling better
thank you
already separated with the bucket we're
not lovers anymore
some things have transpired
while i was gone
um i've been notified of the
bucket being unfaithful to me
yeah so when i came back i threw him
into a melting machine
you know like the one where you put
throw in the companion cubes and then
there was no more and now all i have is
you
and i'm happy with that i have i've got
you buckets
[Music]
[Laughter]
at first you were jealous and now you're
like
oh come on come on isn't this what you
wanted
isn't this what you wanted all along
i wouldn't do that to you guys no
because you're made out of paper
your buckets are made out of paper i
wouldn't have to throw you into the
melting machine
i just have to like set you on fire and
then i'm good
but that's a different story
[Music]
um
so thank you for
watching
for the pinky in the game
[Music]
what
no you already wear a bucket before that
baby
i am the lord everybody knows my name
thank you
bucket friends
[Music]
no no yeah i was going to sleep when i
get sleepy while watching youtube but
it's time to go to work in an hour
oh my god
korean fans are next level
they stay up all night
to watch my stream even though they know
they have to go work
so they just go to work after pulling an
all-nighter
oh my god
thank you i'm enjoying the piano in the
background yeah it's nice isn't it
[Music]
you
don't do that too often okay
you need some sleep
but thank you thank you for doing your
best to watch my streams
uh phoenix2612 thanks for the pinky i
think you're glad you're feeling better
love the new outfit oh
the
dandel thank you glad you like it it do
be very cute yes yes
thank you very much joe knight thank you
also for the pinky and will you be my
bucket no if anything you should be my
bucket what the hell
i don't become a bucket that's your job
animal is at 4 am so no sleeping for a
while oh don't worry i mean i won't this
this won't go on for too long you can
get some sleep in between if you really
want to watch it live
aliba thank you for the
is this a bucket
no that's a chicken that's a chicken a
cute chicken so fat mmm cute
thank you for the red super chat
looking fabulous
no
no i'm sure i mean it's been an hour
i'm sure i'll be done like in the next
two hours
[Music]
hi even if i'm not
sorry that was me yawning and screeching
[Music]
bits thank you for the pinkie
kiwawa thank you for the dokomi weekend
i had the best time meeting kfb dining
out
singing karaoke carrying dominic
adventuring around town and cheering for
your concert i would do it all again in
a heartbeat until next meeting love kfp
and kiara
ah
so sweet
no
thank you
it's already been quite some time
that has passed since dokomi
but yeah
i'm very happy you enjoyed it so much
it's a nice memory i'm glad i'm glad you
guys had a good time because i was so
worried
whether or not you guys would you know
come out of it thinking it was worth it
[Music]
but it seems like you guys
even the ones who came from so far away
felt like it was worth it so
[Music]
that's really really nice to hear
yeah
thank you
thankful to the cafe who shared their
experience
maybe you can be part of it next time
[Music]
definitely worth it yay
um
[Music]
you did good up there boss thank you
maybe we can rewatch it tomorrow
[Music]
night
yeah we can combine the two things since
it's connected anyway by being dokomi
related um
[Music]
falcon boom thank you for your pinky
tension thank you for inspiring me with
smoothie and chocolates to finally adopt
the cat myself
hey yo what
can you wish my new kitty onion
that's a cute name
does it also have
layers a happy healthier since he was
adopted it would mean the world to him
cute eh why the [\h__\h] are you not showing
me pictures of your cat
i know it's not possible in the super
chat but now you gotta send me uh
a tweet a tweet
are you here falcon boom
i need you to send me pictures
onion
it does kind of sound like that
i don't think you're here
but i demand the pictures
you can't just tell me about a cute cat
that you adopted and then not send me
pictures
if someone knows this person
let them know that i want the pictures
okay
[Music]
come on in come here onion
oh i today oh speaking of cats
today i used um a very special brush on
my cats again that
when i used when i first got it i i
realized oh [\h__\h] this is
this brush is
um
it kind of like it goes so deep into the
undercoat and then kind of like
pulls really high
on the cat there so i noticed my cats
really don't like it so i didn't use it
but then today
i randomly used it again
and it worked really well
because i got a lot of the undercoat
from smoovie
who's been losing so much hair she's
been shedding like crazy and i got the
undercoat out really well um it wasn't
so bad like um
yeah just have to have to like be
careful when using the brush no it's not
wired it's like out of metal
and it has like this this hook
looking
um
the shape of it is like it's like many
tiny hooks
[Music]
that people can currently get in japan
where i am
part of the special
lineup
i got like a
like a sparkly card
i wonder if i can show you a picture um
some people have been posting it
i'm cute oh
my art hashtag is looking cute
i wonder because my birthday is soon if
you're gonna get some cute
birthday
art
then i should get some pictures
[Music]
this one i just found randomly on
twitter but it looks like this
sparkly and i got this cute outfit
ah
this cute pose
[Music]
online
ah so cute i really like the outfit it
feels like
like a
sailor it's like a sailor outfit because
of the little hat
and the colors
it's so cute
like a
i don't know like i'm a sailor
it's so cute
it flattened you
ah yeah maybe a little bit oh
didn't realize
it
makes you look younger
huh you're saying i look old
couldn't fit in the outfit on the shadow
she could she should be my oh she should
she should already be roshi
i want the card i wonder if they'll send
it to me
um
like i have them send me all merchandise
off me
just because you know
it's nice to have it but then like when
i get it i usually i don't know what to
do with it like all the omocat merch
that i got
um
some of it i use for like pajamas but
then i also don't want to use it too
often because i don't want it to wash
out too much
so yeah and all the hats almost had hats
and acrylic charms or acrylic or
whatever like everything that i got from
omoket i'm not using it
and all the other merchandise
i'm not using any of it because i don't
know what to use it for i can't i can't
just put everything on my bag or
whatever
you at least use the hoodie no first of
all it's too [\h__\h] hot now second of
all it stands out so much
i can't use my hoodie maybe in
wintertime when it's cold
i'll wear it at home
maybe but i also i don't wanna as i said
i don't wanna use the clothes too much
because i don't want them to be like
washed out and like 10 years later
when when
like i tell someone oh i have all this
merchandise of myself because you know i
used to be famous
and they don't believe it i want some i
want to be able to you know show it off
and
have some proof
[Music]
yeah
so that's basically you know just for
the sake of collecting everything i've
put out so far
i have them send me the merchandise
but there is no use for it
besides that
[Music]
yeah
now that ain't you oh no no that's
obviously me
uh where was i here space waterfall
thank you and girl boston question angel
thank you for the rest of the chat
random super chat i just felt like it
i'm having fun
hell yeah why not
you go you go have fun thank you so much
for participating in my stream and
supporting me thank you angel
such an angel
angel
los angeles
connection
dun dun
[Music]
i am done finally with this stream that
was one of the
relatively big ones why am i just
getting slower
when i read these
okay so we have super chats now from a
super chat reading stream
[Music]
i hope it's not too much
oh it's
it's not so much most of these are
membership
messages
okay okay
[Music]
okay
i was too stunned to think of anything
to say during the outfit reveal still
not sure what to write the little very
cute kiawah cute now that's out of my
system could i ask you to say in a
commanding tone
oh
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
go
do it
why the hell are you not streaming it
while watching my stream on the side huh
go
stream fever night
or you'll go to the usual room
got
it okay
gave me some extra
[Music]
no don't turn off the stream you gotta
do both but you know it doesn't seems
like youtube doesn't count it as a view
if you're not fully tabbed in maybe so
make sure to be tabbed in fever night
yeah okay
i'm on mobile okay but after the stream
you gotta stream it okay
ransom chad
here's a small comment on your german
channel breathtaking spicy dinner and
totally official marriage
again you rattle over and sink your
talons into my heart yet sadly yours is
already taken cute i'm sure you'll make
your cats very happy because your whole
out animation is so cool oh thank you
that's also something that happened a
while ago
indeed very cool thank you so much at
german channel
i need to
start putting out some content there
eventually sometime soon
ah thank you gervadin thank you
that's listening to feminists what if i
help you as well of course it does yes
please do
[Music]
hmm
german debut yeah i should do that
[Music]
although i did it before but yeah oh
yeah i said i wanted to if i do it i
want to get some new
assets and i didn't yet oh i need to
commission it um
[Music]
ah
let me write that to genma so i don't
forget
no to self commission
news
assets for
german
channel debut there we go
yeah
check my channels tab exactly
um
[Music]
thank you
i have completed my year-long mission to
get buff to impress you what are you
saying you were not buffed before that
because
i already saw you being buffed like a a
long time ago
that might not have been a year ago but
still long long enough ago that it would
make me think that you were already fit
before that
did you get even buffer
please take a look and let me know what
you think don't worry just say so you
can show it on stream if you want to
where am i supposed to look
i hope you see this project as a sign of
my gratitude for how much you care about
your friends it means more to us than
you know i also want to thank kfp
because everyone's kind words have been
a great source of motivation for me it's
twitter
wait but the profile thanks for that one
is like
pretty old by now no
okay so
[Music]
oh
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
so that's a
before and after
[Music]
oh wow
wait
your heads your head's changed too
your head
you're different fish now is this really
the same person i doubt it
i mean obviously the head is a different
person
[Music]
damn
what is that three hours of running over
what is this
the running
you ran a marathon wait what the [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
wow
that's really um impressive holy [\h__\h]
after a year
[Music]
but
would have been better to have a
picture from
the back to compare the back too wait no
is that
oh what that is that is uh
that is supposed to let me compare it
like this oh
whoa you got so tan too
yo you were such a white ass fish and
now you're grilled
[Music]
what
and now yeah okay okay
grilled fish let's go
big respect for
going through with that as we know i
have not been going through with my
workouts
but i danced okay i've been dancing a
lot recently so
i got a pass i think
congratulations
thank you for your support
yeah
yeah i've been dancing non-stop thank
you thank you indeed yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
since you're done dancing you're gonna
go back to the gym oh
well think about it
i know thanks a little pinky your new
outfit looks absolutely amazing i really
love everything about it so much you're
always absolute cutest and most
beautiful ever love forever love forever
thank you
glad you like it i'm not wearing it
today
i'm wearing the other outfit that you
guys love so much but thank you unknown
i appreciate it i'm glad you like it
much much love for you thank you
drowsy cat thank you
sprout fruit hurts by now thank you
thanks for the pinky i don't know where
to look your new outfit is hello cute
apron hairstyle dress cotton is and
oh all three of my attention too well i
see what you mean you succeed on making
me fall in love with you again i feel
like since dokomi i keep loving you more
and more
i got you under my spell
i see hold on
maybe you've
been like loving me more because you
finally got out of the usual room huh
[Music]
maybe finally
finally that gave you some freedom in
your feelings
[Music]
no no that was only a timeout that was
only momentarily today
no he's not back
no no
hmm
how's it going
yeah
[Music]
um
and with that we finished the super
chats from the super chat reading
and now we go to
zelda
wind waker
part
oh no i turned them off oh yeah cruise
down kitchen that's it
okay good good good good
now we go to pop-tart stream oh
pop-tart stream
[Music]
pop-tarts
offline meeting super chatos
[Music]
that one was fun
star creator thank you so much thank you
soon daisy duncan atlantean guard bjorn
duncan miss fist duncan
calm down relax and prepare pop guys for
watching this stream work where we can
purchase it oh
are there pop-tarts in
available for purchase in korea
maybe not in normal stores but maybe
there's like stores that sell american
food
maybe
because like i remember at least when i
lived in japan they had some stores that
sold
some like european chocolate and so on
but i don't remember seeing pop-tarts
there either
i feel like
hmm probably don't need to
bring that overseas
yeah probably in amazon you could
probably get it
on
[Music]
we have places where we can buy stuff
from america ah
[Music]
everyone must experience the froze
frosted cardboard
oh ammo did mention it
oh i wasn't sure if i should mention
yeah um
you know because of uh
uh
ax
um some managers came to america
um
so
yeah janma
was there
the j chad
was also there
[Music]
and one more manager who you guys don't
know because that manager has no
like fan name
yeah yeah yeah
hammy said genma left over the couch to
hug her ha
i guess she did but she loves me the
most
no hannah wasn't there no no no no but
jenna has been like
at every [\h__\h] convention that's why
you know i was really worried about her
like um before dokomi she was at like
some
american
conventions i already forgot which ones
then she went back to japan then she
went to dokome and she went back to
japan then now she's at ax and all that
oh so much [\h__\h] traveling poor jenna
and she doesn't even get like anything
better than economy seats
i i suffer for her because she already
doesn't get any [\h__\h] sleep
and then she gets put into economy
i am i
here and now i am
trying to get better seats for genma
but maybe at least [\h__\h] premium
economy come on
please she's traveling so [\h__\h] much
oh my god
um
[Music]
you know they're doing it because of you
know the boobs i think
[Music]
oh you know
before she came
she was like oh do the girls you know
because she met like
most of the girls besides me and kelly
for the first time yeah
so
um she was like oh
can you ask them kiwawa if they want
something from japan and um yeah good
that was like snacks snacks snacks that
was pretty much the only thing they said
yeah so um i didn't even ask for snacks
but then gemma ended up bringing these
huge bags of snacks for every member
yeah for every single one of them
um and i was like genma
see i didn't even need snacks i tried my
best to fill them
make them fit into my suitcase a lot of
snacks like baby birds feed me
yeah
yeah she brought so many oh my god i
thought she would only bring it to like
gouda maybe or the other girls but not
me because i actually only asked for
like
a small size face masks
uh not not face masks like the you know
the masks normal masks but small size
because we only have like big sizes here
um
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
gemma sounds so generous
yeah wait i feel like she she um paid
for all the snacks herself but she
bought so many must have been quite
quite expensive
yeah she brought an entire caravan
pretty much
surgical no not surgical but you know
yeah
face masks not the ones where you know
you you moisturize your face
actually did you know that in japan
probably also maybe in korea and so on
in asian countries who focus more on
like wearing masks
um
there's masks
that like give off moisture when you
wear it
so they recommend you to wear them the
masks while you're like uh on an
overnight
um bus traveling for example
because it's really good like for your
nose and your throat if you breathe that
in
yeah i used that before and it's really
it really gives off a lot of moisture
[Music]
it's just a normal mask but it gives off
moisture
[Music]
it's like especially like even not even
when you're traveling if you live in an
apartment that's really dry
then you wear the mask overnight
[Music]
hmm
it makes your throat and all that feel
very hydrated
and your skin too i guess i don't know
[Music]
yeah very helpful for dry fruit
they have so many all kinds of masks yo
it's amazing because they have this
whole mask culture way before the sea
thing
so they have this
wide variety and choices of masks
yeah so i asked genma to bring me masks
from japan when she when she comes to
see me and this is why you know because
she because i knew that i would see her
in america
the farewell at dokomi was really
not
a big deal
um
[Music]
hmm
yeah i wasn't that wasn't clear about it
but yeah yeah yeah
okay see
[Music]
you said that you will be seeing her
soon yes
and who knows maybe i'll see her again
within this year
maybe maybe
maybe
my beloved
genma
so where was i um
where was i
why was i
where the frick was i i right in the
beginning mystic has been established in
daisy dangerous and atlanta
[Music]
the only surprise here is that you
didn't give us half a day's notice on
the stream frame
congrats i'm finally getting this off
collab and i can't wait for tangents
about this
no no no that wasn't the only surprise
it was so funny looking at the chat when
i opened up the stream everybody for
like the next two hours everybody in the
chat they kept on coming in and coming
in and they don't stop coming and they
don't stop coming and they were all like
what the [\h__\h] what what question mark
exclamation mark question mark
exclamation mark
like i checked an hour later and they
were still like what the [\h__\h] what what
what the [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh it was so funny
that was really funny
[Music]
yeah sorry i didn't tell you guys
earlier like it was really spontaneous
it was literally the day when we got
together and i didn't want you know to
spoil the fact that i was
you know meeting up with them
that the fact that ina would be there
was also like you know big surprise
yeah it was all a surprise and it was
spontaneous the pop-tart thing was
spontaneous we didn't even know if we
would stream on that day beforehand
you know because that was
just a day where we first met
[Music]
people thought they were visiting me in
austria
i guess
you see anything else crazy in walmart
that you didn't buy but sticks in your
mind
the lines were [\h__\h] insane
maybe it was just the timing of the day
the time of the day when we were there
but the lines
were like
at least at least 20 meters
insane
[Music]
but that's about it i didn't look like
too closely um we were like
zooming through the walmart trying to
find what we were looking for
[Music]
but when i was at target i was really
excited to see like american
flag
swimsuits and i was like should i buy
one because i'm going to the beach
should i buy an american
flag swimsuit
and i was like but that's so [\h__\h]
tacky no one wears that right but then i
saw people actually wearing bikinis like
that
yeah oh yeah that was a thing that i
kind of already knew but saw in person
for the first time
americans really love their flag huh
so many have their flag outside of their
home like outside of their house
sticking
on the stick
at the window or whatever
yeah
[Music]
we don't do that in austria
if anything i've seen recently i've seen
flags like for other countries
but
not not for austria no one has an
austrian flag outside their home
it's really not a thing
almost july 4th oh yeah yeah ah because
of that like i've heard like fireworks
popping up i guess they were testing
every now and then i've heard fireworks
going off yeah
um
i mean yeah i appreciate austria but i
won't put a flag outside my home like
why i know i'm in austria why do i need
to put a flag there
i know where i am and the people who
walk around my home know that they are
in austria
it's not like i have to like remind
people that they're in austria
sometimes yeah maybe you guys forget
it's funny though
yeah it's funny
i do think it's quite the american thing
yeah i don't know do other countries do
that like like quite as much as america
[Music]
yeah never seen it in japan before
either people putting
japanese flags up
but i mean that's also partially because
like
they just don't really
[Music]
i don't know how to explain this but
like also inside apartments people won't
really put much on the walls like they
won't
like make holes into walls and all that
usually
because it's not allowed in most
apartments um
i've seen mexican and puerto rico flags
up i see mexico does it oh
[Music]
oh my god
not even to hang pictures yeah they find
like different ways of decorating
uh instead of instead of putting up like
um nails hmm
[Music]
yeah but it seems like you know besides
besides america and mexico
it's not really common huh
[Music]
um a basic an australian flag into the
snack box
well i don't know what to do with that
then
maybe i'll wrap myself around it if i
ever visit australia
yeah try to fit in
i'm one of you i'm one of you i'm from
austria i'm one of you
it's just missing a few letters but it's
basically the same
hanging outside to confuse people
yeah i could do that
because we like to joke about that like
austrian souvenir shops always have like
mugs and t-shirts
and bags that say
uh
not australia or no kangaroos
and have like a sign with a kangaroo
crossed out and all that
yeah
i like to joke around with that
but the other way around you guys don't
do that do you where are my australian
friends mates
you guys don't have souvenirs that say
not austria right it's kind of [\h__\h]
sad it's because we're not significant
enough nobody confuses australia for
austria it's just the other way around
it's so [\h__\h]
sad oh man
[\h__\h] you
[Music]
why can't we be more significant
you guys don't know how it is
you guys you australians don't know how
it is how that feels
to keep on being mistaken for another
country
[Music]
it's really [\h__\h]
frustrating and sad
makes me feel
sad so
insignificant
um you're irrelevant
[Music]
never heard of austria before until i
what the [\h__\h] where are you from
[Music]
oh it's so sad
that's so sad
but you're not the only one though
can't can relate you can
okay
say dad to new zealand uh why
[Music]
didn't know about austria eva until i
watched sound music what the [\h__\h]
you just have to win eurovision we did
win eurovision fairly recently
with a phoenix person
[Music]
heard of austria like once before you
what the actual [\h__\h]
yeah people think my country is called
holland instead of the netherlands and
that's probably german speaking people
know
because
[Music]
uh
you're a thought of seeing seen rise
like a phoenix
oh maybe then unarchived
[Music]
netherlands thing is a little bit
confusing also in japanese
the netherlands are in japanese called
orlando right which sounds like holland
too
[Music]
i'm kind of misleading yeah
kind of misleading
[Music]
i barely even remember all the states in
america so it's nothing personal
i guess
anyway let's continue um
oh yeah
we went so off topic again what the [\h__\h]
mapped and ape thanks to the pinky uh
jeff star thanks for the pinky you're
amazing thank you so sweet thanks for
the super sticker i appreciate it thank
you soon
[Music]
no i didn't go to the golden gate bridge
wasn't that
in san francisco
isn't that a san francisco thing
um
i went to l.a
san francisco is nice though like i was
there once i know i say i don't want to
count it because i barely saw anything
but the atmosphere was nice what i when
i did see was nice
um
so i mean there's so i know there's so
many sides to america so i would like to
visit again sometime
[Music]
but i don't know i'm traveling again in
august
uh
and then who knows where i'll be going
after that
i've been traveling a lot the past
like this this summer i guess or even
since like the whole year i guess i'm
traveling a lot so
maybe not so much traveling for the
later part of the year even though i
would like to i would like to travel the
whole year but
[Music]
then i'm away from my cats and
creating content is not so easy
and all that
[Music]
so
i guess i should
tone it down a little bit
yeah
yeah i should i want
to be able to get to japan by the end of
the year um definitely
so yeah that might be
one more trip besides korea
[Music]
thank you good night
non-tour group tours yes please
the fact that you can only enter as a
tour
part of a tour is so stupid it feels
like
a certain other country
anyway
thanks for uh writing chad um what an
epic surprise just who could have geesed
your first off collab with them was
going to be our bad pop-tarts really
[Music]
well i wonder if canada will have a
different opinion
opinion
of them after this will she fall for him
like suga
foreign of events what
what
[Music]
i don't get all of these references it's
a part of ah i did hear of it before i
was wondering what it was and what's
what's bit bitter bittern supposed to be
return
bittern
b-i-t-t-e-r-n b-turn is a bird what
return
whoa
funny bird
what what a neck
[Music]
wow what a funny neck no
wait sometimes it has a neck and
sometimes it doesn't
it looks funny
little bit turned on a walk
how cute
oh they look funny
look it up just like you no i always
have an egg
they're quite rare
funny
[Music]
they look so funny
it looks so funny
what the [\h__\h] it looks like a [\h__\h]
giraffe
you're the eurasian bittering
looks like a [\h__\h] giraffe
giraffe bird
thank you travisti for that knowledge
for the pinky
a letter
[Music]
i send it i don't know when i'll get it
but just do it
cruz duncan skye duncan shadow pencil
thank you
the game of korean spicy chicken taco
taco
who changed your name right i like out
of reflex i read spicy chicken taco
spicy chicken
what happened to the taco
the fact that this only happened because
of the birthday recording
it would have taken even long even
longer probably until we would have been
in japan for a 3d debut
to actually get us all together if it
wasn't for the 3d birthday recording
imagine
like it's not like we weren't like able
to travel i mean it might have been a
little bit difficult last year for c
reasons
but
[Laughter]
oh man
yeah i think most mostly all of us were
waiting for the japan trip and just kept
on getting delayed and delayed and
delayed and yeah
yeah and now things just came together
nicely
especially also because of um
yeah
ax i guess
which i didn't go to but still
yeah isn't it like
right now here it's the first of july
but i guess in america right now it's
still night time but it starts on the
first of july right so first second
third f
is ax
as far as i know
hmm
made it in the cave now i wouldn't call
it a cave although
maybe partially it felt like a cave
it's morning here oh yeah good morning
good morning
are you guys going to anax
anime expo
[Music]
i'm at x right now
oh are you like standing in line or what
[Music]
show me some pictures on twitter must be
really crowded right
i'm an ax too oh
i heard
that the tickets are [\h__\h] expensive
one day what like seventy dollars what
the [\h__\h]
in germany and so on that's like at the
most what you will spend for a whole
like three day ticket and people already
complain about that
about the price being so expensive for
free days
american coins are expensive what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
it used to be much cheaper
um
i paid 60 for one day for megacon to see
your panel last year oh dear
oh dear
huh
for san diego comic con super expensive
140 for the four days
[Music]
damn it's so expensive i have my cafe
ring shirt to represent oh
nice yeah oh
you guys will be wearing kfp merch if
you go there hopefully
i think you wish two days 200
in person right i would say that's
worth it though
[Music]
that was a huge concert hmm
i would say that's more or less worth it
[Music]
i'm wrapping kfb2 thank you
ringer restock when yeah i know
[Music]
i'm wrapping kfb thank you
thank you
[Music]
oh no i just scratched myself with
something under the chair
[Music]
that's the best part of merch
of the merchant and never restocked well
i wouldn't give up yet but yeah i guess
that one is just difficult to
restock because of i don't know either
some materials used or
that's probably that
[Music]
ah
background music is mozart yes
yes yes
my my friend from austria
my best friend
uh cruz duncan
wait wait where was i i always read that
i think
i think skydiving shadow pencil thank
you
duncan
the game of criticism spice chicken
pablo i am already already i lose track
because i go on an attention
video
satisfied duncan
felix sal thank you for the rights of a
chat this caught me completely by
surprise but an absolutely welcome
surprise it's like waking up missing a
wing but then you realize tantra is
cooking it on the stove before dinner
with venus
i see
i guess
i guess a lot of the people in the chat
can relate to that
thank you
for
the sweet super chat
you got you are you're so dedicated
felix i love that
yeah it was
a big surprise for all of you guys i
think and uh
yeah
nice surprise
[Music]
it sounds like an alarm
yeah thank you felix here's a kiss for
you
[Music]
is that a rainbow that i see oh my god
thank you viva la chiara thank you for
the beautiful
rainbow
you didn't even make use of the
of the
um text limit
thank you though
thank you for the beautiful rainbow
i think it is a rainbow yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
giggle queen that
wooden is
the gamer crate dunkeshen dressy cat
thank you for the red super chat today i
celebrate your resurrection and i really
enjoyed guda's birthday life but what
else is this you rocked me how long have
you waited for miff together mm-hmm
and wait there's something in
korean
maybe it's the same as the
english
[Music]
sugar
oh and then it says
i need to raise money for the birthday
goods but oof i couldn't stand it
oh
yeah birthday merchandise is coming soon
you need to be prepared you have like
one month to buy them because they're
usually only available for one month
well you better be ready
yeah
are you ready are you ready
i like i like my birthday merch
i've seen it
and
i've seen it not in person but i've seen
pictures of it
being used
uh like
they showed me like you know some some
real life photo
shots i have yet to request
yago
to
you know
present it maybe i should ask for that
um
can we
get a photo
of
yango with my merch
[Music]
michelle
got a new job just in time nicer
[Music]
let's
go don't see him
i don't see him i scrolled up but i
didn't see him
hi there who what
i read you super chat when you were
saying like you got sick how how was it
did you get better did you have to see
thing
or was it just a normal cold
ah he's super jealous oh there you are
recovered quickly with something else
i'm not a hotel
i i'm just uh wondering
if anybody got like the c thing from
going to dokomi
[Music]
holocure virus
which is basically just being addicted
to the game and needing some time off to
play the game
i got it
oh dear
laughing i did not i was healthy haven't
heard of anyone
no saving for me wow
wow most of you dodged it
nice
hear yourself by watching chihuahua
exactly that's the best thing to do the
best homemade remedy
[Music]
have i even worn a mask oh
that's really unfortunate man i guess
you know masks are more like to protect
others
rather than protecting yourself so
someone around you
probably didn't wear it but have the
vibe had the virus and then gave it to
you
yeah
but good to hear that most of you were
healthy
okay
yawning emote is being
used a lot
today so drown the cat thank you
birthday soon get ready draw the cat
thank you
tell us
[Music]
encountering chickens
thanks for thinking
happy to find happy to you finally got
your wish to see other myth girls
besides kelly rl how was it i bet you
gave each other a big cuddle gotta check
the vlog of gooda's birthday celebration
love the screenshots of you hope you
enjoy your time with them thank you
yeah i mean kelly you know with cal it
was a reunion and not it hasn't even
been that long because we met in
austria not long before that but yeah
meeting ame and gouda and ina for the
first time was very exciting i was
really
nervous about you know what they would
think of me
and um
yeah i was i was i was nervous
um
i already like talked about most of the
things that happened
um i feel like as i said
i bonded the most i think with ame and
and probably also with inna
[Music]
yeah
and it was it was very it's very special
time
yeah
i'm really glad
that i got to meet all of them finally
it took us too long
[Music]
who had you most nervous or probably
good because like she was the first one
i met
and like i came from the airport to our
accommodation
and then you know
i don't know that that just made me the
most nervous
um i was jumping around the
apartment
yeah
i was nervous about taking off my mask
um
yeah and she she seemed like pretty
chill
about it
yeah then i felt kind of awkward for
being so nervous because she was mostly
like calm like
she was she didn't even seem like it was
the first time she met me
no
[Music]
took us a thousand years yeah pretty
pretty much
[Music]
yeah she was
um
i think i think she was mostly
preoccupied with like
some things about her stream
because
i think i came
i when i arrived like uh
she was like preparing for the stream
um
and i think that made her nervous but
like
it didn't quite show so much
to the outside like she contains it well
[Music]
yeah and i was sitting next to her when
she was streaming she must have been
very nervous
or like not nervous but like intimidated
but as i said before i didn't even look
at her because i knew it would make her
feel more awkward so i just stared at
the screen the whole time
and then midway through i was thinking
maybe i should go somewhere else but it
would make some noises and
it didn't i didn't want to um
be like a distraction
and have the people in the stream react
to some noises
so i was kind of stuck for the whole
hour
i wanted to move but i couldn't
at some point i felt like i needed to
sneeze
and then thankfully i didn't sneeze
[Music]
idle meetings nah no i didn't need to
even during yeah doing this
it's so weird like um during the when
she was like playing that um concert
thing
uh
you know i saw an obs we both saw it
that like out the microphone was muted
but for some reason she was like
still like
um she's i think she was really scared
of like having a hot mic moment so she
wouldn't talk and then i would like say
something and whisper and she would
whisper back at me but she was really
trying hard not to talk
and i'm like isn't the microphone muted
anyway and she's like yeah but i don't
know
so
we were just like quietly looking at it
and she was listening i guess but i had
no audio so i was just
really quietly staring at the screen
trying not to
bother her
or make a sound
it has happened before yeah but like we
double checked or we actually like 10
times checked
if the microphone was
muted or not
[Music]
and she's very careful yeah
very careful doesn't it
[Music]
but i also tried to help a little bit
like for example i was monitoring the
chat because i think she
it was so fast that i think she didn't
really like she wasn't able to
like really read the chat properly but i
had nothing to really pay attention to
so i was reading the chat very carefully
and i would like um like try to signal
to her
i would like stop the chat and scroll up
and then show her certain comments about
the audio
and trying to signal her like
louder or more quiet and so on when i
said when i saw someone in the chat
saying oh too loud or too quiet then i
like pointed at it
with my finger
i tried to help a little bit
yeah tend to assist yeah
no i didn't ban anyone
no
i wouldn't go that far
[Music]
yeah i know the microphone like i didn't
hear it because i didn't have earphones
in or anything but i just judged by the
chat
so i told her to lower
the microphone
volume
[Music]
but i think it was still kind of scuffed
yeah
[Music]
will you be playing hollow here
i don't know i guess maybe next week
maybe maybe if i feel like it
except for the ten of us what are you
talking about that never happened
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
no not tomorrow tomorrow members only
did you ain't gonna have any deep talks
well you know
only only really on the pizza night
when when it was um only us two left
that was
pretty much
the only time where i guess we had some
kind of like deep talk
kind of
hmm
[Music]
yeah
hecking love pizza hell yeah pizza
pizza
it was not soggy no not at all because i
put it into the oven it was really
crunchy
did you want to bond more
maybe yeah
[Music]
no it was not
dipped into the bathtub
you got a neck massage from any of the
girls now
i mean i was in a lot of pain but i i
don't want to like you know there's some
types of people who
like to give people massages and do it
like automatically
and those people i love very much
but uh i i didn't ask anyone for a
massage specifically
i should have won the arm wrestling
match
[Music]
nina yeah lana would do it actually i'm
really surprising
[Music]
auntie watson oh she was happy she
seemed happy
you were never going to win shut up
i i won i won one
[Music]
it wasn't a shut up
okay um
[Music]
you deserve
uh
a time out cause you're a [\h__\h] horny
as hell
[Music]
all right okay uh where were we
shadow mistakes and santa maria's
dancing
i already read them
jd pakistan thank you again for the
pinky so this one i did read i'm pretty
sure
[Music]
no way you can fool me suika
sekka wrote in japanese
that they're a first time viewer
i know very well that you're lying to me
you cannot fool me no no no no
especially not if you just sent a red
super rainbow super chat right before
that
no no no
[Music]
you're trying to tease me huh
first time you were i don't think so
thank you dosaica
[Music]
i'm too smart yes
i have a good memory when it comes to
your chickens like i genuinely have a
bad memory but then i do remember
the super chatters if they're new or not
that's
one thing i can remember well well
mr vic thank you
lorenz smell of the lost shrimps thank
you soju
thank you
i'm so happy this is finally happening i
hope you have tons of fun with your chat
mates and today's my birthday so this is
extra special for me ooh can i request
an employee number and a raise i love
you thank you
no raise but happy birthday
you're
it's kind of late sorry but your um
employee number shall be
two
oh
six
because i think that was the day
the day
of your birthday i think
i think
[Music]
maybe ah depending on your time zone it
might have been
two one six
are you here kotaku
[Music]
you can choose
if it was two or seven no two one six
then you can do two one six if it was
two or six you can do two ah it was 21
okay that is two one six for you
your birthday easy to remember what's a
raise you know when
when
um the birds and the bees oh no the
flowers and the beasts i don't know when
they like each other very much just
kidding
[Music]
no that is something that um
that's um
it means um
it means
um
loving your boss
endlessly until the end of time
and therefore
that is something i cannot give to you
that's something you have to give to me
[Music]
so give me a raise come
on yeah yeah sounds legit
so happy belated birthday kotaku
everybody wish kotaku happy birthday
i hope you don't feel too old
my birthday is coming and i'm also
feeling like i'm getting old it's scary
but at least i'm a phoenix i guess
so
not too much of a problem i guess
yeah erase
thank you
[Music]
thank you for the pinky watch my oshi's
try my most hated snack not sure how to
feel about this
i'm not your oshido you don't mean me
right because uh your name seems seems
very new to me
it does seem very new to me i could be
wrong but
hmm
but you sent it to me
might be a lurker maybe
maybe a worker he's a new fan
how do you know
i didn't buy a new fan
i don't even have an old fan
[Music]
maybe a name change could be could be
could be
maybe who knows
thank you for the support though
in any case
[Music]
thank you for the pink super chat i take
a day off to watch gordo's birthday
stream but i didn't expect this
wonderful another collab stream oh yeah
makes me very emotional how lucky i am
thank you
oh yeah i guess that day was really
packed because i guess gura did
two
streams
kind of for my birthday and then it was
the pop-tart stream yeah
a lot of
feelings on that day a lot of
other feelings happening
exciting things happening
although the collins were like 24 hours
before right
[Music]
happy day was good today thank you well
i mean i didn't do much today
yet
besides picking up some
things
i need to clean my apartment
urgently
[Music]
sorry i just got a message from
something
regarding my
birthday concert
[Music]
[Laughter]
how much cat hair did you find
that's that's a weird question because
there's always a lot of cat hair
everywhere
but
um
i need to really clean my apartment
[Music]
dan kashin
our ronin duncan thank you
justin reinhardt
[Music]
it's not cookies but it's enough to
satisfy the tacos
tacos are [\h__\h] horny today
have you guys seen
i checked out the art tag of inya
and
what the [\h__\h]
what the hell is going on
[Music]
just because of that one moment when she
showed her back in the arm wrestling
stream
oh my god it's probably partially also
because
the takodachi's miss inna so much
because they haven't seen her for a long
time but
but
she's coming back isn't she in a few
hours she's doing her revival stream
[Music]
i think i left my window open
it's movie
[Music]
it's moving
i was gonna go somewhere but this movie
was right behind me
maybe
[Music]
baby
um
[Music]
yeah she doesn't want to leave me
anymore
i didn't even notice she was behind me
probably the whole time
oh
just like lying down
lying down on the floor late night while
i'm streaming
she's cute and so fluffylicious
[Music]
have you traumatized her by leaving her
too much
ah yeah 10 days was
probably too much she missed me and i
think like i had like three people
taking care of my cats while i was gone
like in shifts
um
but i think
they didn't give them enough love enough
pets
and that's why they're so needy right
now
[Music]
she's uh watching a fly fly around right
now
i have i kept my my windows open
all night so like a million flies
entered my apartment
it's [\h__\h] obnoxious
[Music]
you're just irreplaceable that might be
true yeah yeah yeah yeah i definitely
missed the mommy cuddles because even if
they pet my cats i just do it
differently
i know i know the right spots i know
how to pet them correctly
yeah sometimes they may act as if
they're annoyed by me petting them too
much but then when i'm gone they miss it
they do like it
yeah
i'm getting so hungry again
but i feel like i'm reaching the end
soon um
mvp thank you for the pinky can't wait
for more collabs i mean more collabs
thank you yeah there were a bunch more a
bunch more collaborations even with some
you know
um
like
one-on-one
uh
combinations like me and ahmed
hmm
i think we got some good streams out of
that
had a collaboration
oh yeah i guess that yeah that came out
a little bit ago
the
um what was it called
in english i forgot but
yeah i'll be in there for free episodes
so
look forward to it that's where that's
what i was talking about when i said um
i recommended elena as a new joining
member so they actually put her in
so yeah
wait
[\h__\h] i spoiled that
wait that wasn't information that was
out yet
okay i think for once i actually spoiled
something
people say i spoil so much but i
actually don't okay i spoiled something
because
was already out oh well um
you don't know which episode it's going
to be so
[Music]
you heard nothing
you heard nothing you heard nothing
ah don't worry my reputation is already
ruined even though i didn't ever really
spoil anything of importance or
something that i wasn't allowed to say
people still already say that i spoil
everything which i didn't i didn't
but anyway
what's spoilers
it's daijoubu it's probably daijoubu
[Music]
yeah let's move on we're moving on where
was i here
thank you bishop thank you
[Music]
around the same level of taste and
except for certain ones i would never
toast them
thanks for the surprise of collab it was
a lot of fun
thank you i mean
i've heard that you know
doing something with them besides eating
them raw
is just generally better
oh my god that was loud in my ears um
yeah maybe maybe some of them shouldn't
have been toasted i don't know
they're wrong the only way to enjoy his
toast see it's a it's a it's a matter of
taste
a matter of toast
um but yeah you still chose to run
they're on the wrong flavors shut up
that's what was in the walmart that's
just what they had lined up
i just took like whatever was there
and johnny was so funny
[Music]
unfrosted yeah that sounds like a wrong
flavor
but i guess it's like a do-it-yourself
thing put whatever the hell you want on
the on on the pop-tart thing
but
i i i did give the pop tarts
surprisingly good um ratings didn't i i
gave them better ratings
than the girls who were familiar with
them
therefore
should be used to them
i gave them better ratings
yeah what the hell
yeah i have higher standards normally oh
no maybe i was just in a good mood i
wonder why i gave them such good ratings
[Music]
i guess maybe the other two rated them
more strictly like as food
but if i had to yeah rate them as
food then of course they would be minus
one million points
yeah
i wouldn't eat that
over my dead body
[Music]
i prefer to eat good food and not suffer
while eating
thank you
for pinky thank you so much for the
spontaneous and awesome of collab girls
you are welcome
thank you for watching it
and yeah i'm sorry for the people who
had to watch it as a board
i know a lot of people were like
mad about it
but yeah as i said it was um
it was a surprise and the other ones i
always tried like i reminded the girls
like
even though it wasn't on my channel i
would remind them yo you probably should
make a thumbnail and put up the
reservation
are you making a thumbnail are you gonna
make it
are you putting up the reservation you
probably should
because everyone was like always like
chilling
so i pushed a little bit to get it done
[Music]
oh amis oh you know the arm wrestling
thumbnail
um the fumbling was made right after i
did some more recording
we did some extra recording um
because yeah i used i used the the suit
that ami brought over
even though that one wasn't the good
stuff
but i had to record some things so
actually all of the poses
looks like a holographic yeah it was so
good right all of the poses
uh were made by me because i was still
in the suit
and uh
yeah
i think it was gouda's idea to like
recreate something
some image
[Music]
mm-hmm yeah and then i i got into
everybody's bodies
and i i did some poses and was like uh
good how would you how would you like
pose if you were in the back there like
cheering for less
yeah and then for for callie i didn't
even ask because like
i immediately took a pose
that she was like hell yeah that's
that's that's perfect
and then for inna too like that that
thinking pose
i took it without really like
you know i just i just went into
character immediately and everybody was
like oh that's perfect that is so inna
yeah
yeah so i i did each pose one by one and
i'm gonna put together the thumbnail she
did a great job it looked so good
it looked so good
[Music]
just for fun their purposes i really
want to get the suit as soon as possible
for myself but it's taking so much time
yeah i probably won't get it
so soon
yeah
well it will still take some time but
once i have it you can trust me
i'll be
making a lot of thumbnails with that
[Music]
but you know i was originally thinking
that i could do like a lot of like
dancing streams and all that with that
suit but once i tested it out
it's so inaccurate and it's so buggy
it's well it has like
a lot of problems depending on
where you use it
so
it might not be very good depending on
the environment
it's not not the same thing that we used
for
for most of the concert it's like a
cheaper version a lot cheaper
um
but yeah incorrect representation of
twerking for example yeah
so i don't know i mean i might do
dancing stream
but it will be scuffed
and
not much i can do about it yeah
yeah i will use it but
don't get your hopes up too high cause
it's not that good
but i did for example i saw like ame
playing that um vr game uh uh where she
was like it was like kind of like a like
a puzzle game
like that would be fun to do that looked
fun
[Music]
yeah you know when she yeah the temple
puzzle yeah yeah that looked fun
oh yeah one of those like i don't know
music
vr game but that's we are i guess i
don't need to put on the suit for that
[Music]
i don't know we'll see we'll see what i
do with it we'll experiment experiment a
little bit around
[Music]
a beat saber
go away [\h__\h] fly [\h__\h] off
[Music]
stay away from me
a simple conduction brandon superstar
shout out to
[Music]
let's see if there's some super chats
for the casper video oh there are some
thank you guys
done with this
[Music]
i don't
video was good wasn't it it was so good
i love these videos i wonder which one
we'll make next i wonder
i wonder what's it gonna be
casper was a big sip of nostalgia yeah
it was
kyle carrot did so much research for it
and and concard said they wanna like
upload a longer version of it
i don't think
i don't think they did it yet
let me see
yeah they didn't do it yet
but there will be i think a longer
version of it
because there was apparently a lot of
footage
that didn't make the cut because it
would have been too long
extended cut yeah
yes yes look forward to that
mr casper extension jackets monkey
dungeon unknown
[Music]
thanks for the pinky thank you this
casper telling me to give kiana a pink
super chat hang in there on the birthday
prep box we know you're working hard
proud of you thank you
yeah totally casper telling you thank
you casper good job casper
hey cruz donkey shoes back in hand thank
you also for the pinky how could i not
give a pinky to someone so beautiful and
so talented casper you are my only she
excuse me
well too bad for you because casper
basically graduated
how sad for you how unfortunate
[Music]
too bad
oh by the way wait a second
if i do countdown videos
i have to start on sunday right
because i have three countdown videos
and the birthday concert is on wednesday
so i have to start on sunday right
[Music]
that's so soon
okay good i hope i don't forget remind
me if i forget that's the wind waker day
let's not say things like that kia what
he's gone
this movie is thinking
i love you so much smoothie
she's just sitting right behind me
it moves me emotionally you don't even
understand
and you probably really don't understand
like the fact that she's right behind me
even though i've been noisy for hours
almost three hours now
she really wants to be so close to me
it's so cute
you get it really you understand
yeah
so
cute
ah we gotta give her some love i gotta
give her a snack i think i'll give her
the
the the leaky snack
soon skydankeshun uh
[Music]
i didn't have photoshop on my traveling
laptop so i was making really scuffed
thumbnails with uh
comic sans
because like i was using this program
that gooda uses what was it called like
uh not firefox that's browser something
like that though
um
it's a free program
that she i was so shocked when she told
me she uses that all the time
she doesn't use photoshop
fire alpaca yeah
i was
i i still can't [\h__\h] believe it i
still can't [\h__\h] believe it
yeah before that she used [\h__\h]
i can't
i [\h__\h] can't
she was this [\h__\h] [\h__\h] and fire
elbow the most subscribed
youtuber on youtube
uses [\h__\h] and fire outfit
i thought i can't
i mean i would have never fought
that by looking at her from this because
they look fine
but i'm just so shocked she has mastered
the free programs because they actually
look fine
and then i had her like teach me a
little bit about how to use fire alpaca
because i was like oh [\h__\h] i gotta do
this from there for the pop-tart stream
but i don't have photoshop on my laptop
and then she taught me a little bit
about how to use fire alpaca and file
packer alpaca is missing a couple of
very important tools that photoshop has
like the font outline and so on so she
showed me her tricks like how she does
it which is like so much more
inconvenient
than just using photoshop and like
taking one box to have an outline around
the fund
and she does it so much more complicated
and i'm like girl
girl you do fun things like this
i can't
ah
yeah no no she basically she copies the
layer of the font and then like makes it
bigger or something no no no no it's
more complicated than that
oh no now she did something with a
selection tool
and then adding a few
um
centimeters to that a few pixels to that
to have the selection be wider than the
font and then she fills out
that selection puts the layer behind the
font
it's
really unnecessarily good complicated
[Music]
but it's so funny to me
but the thing is with that program um
that you can't
really like see
a preview of the fonts like properly
like it's really difficult to find the
font if you don't know by heart
how
each font looks like so
i just went with comic sense
even though i don't like it
you something like this oh my god girl
what
so funny maybe maybe maybe we need a
sponsorship from photoshop
but yeah maybe she wouldn't even want to
use it anyway because she's used to to
fire alpaca and it works for her so good
for her
use my world's number one v2 but yeah
she could use that use that or they
could use that
what's so bad about comic sans and every
time
every time i see it being used
by like
companies like for their storefront
thingies
logos and all that
makes me cringe
and i'm partially
um probably
influenced by my arts
teacher like not odds teacher but
typography teacher i used to go to art
school and then we had a class that was
like about fonts basically and like he
made fun of comic sense and he said
never ever in my class will you use
comic sans because that's a sin
and it is a sin
i believe him
with every vein in my body
i use comic sense to inflict pain yeah
you can use it like
in in like a meme
um context
yeah
which i did in this case for the
thumbnail
i was laughing at myself when choosing
comic sense yeah
[Music]
it just screams i'm unprofessional
exactly
so when i up whenever i see a store
using that font
i'm pretty sure it's
made by someone who is very very
unfamiliar with graphic design and
computers and just technical things in
general
anything probably a really
like like a boomer
yeah a really old boomer
someone who has no idea what they're
doing probably someone who just has this
store
and just doesn't really know anything
about graphic design and they didn't
think about asking anyone else so they
just used you know comic sense
[Music]
anyway
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
tell us how you really feel plus i told
you
i told you just down
the gm fits really
okay so we're reading super chats from
this stream above me
cruise dancing skye duncan my face is
full of cat hair
ah my nose
pyrohichin conduction the gamercraft
dundeeshin pepsi duncan
oh and thanks for the pinky as well i
wanted to say that my month long holiday
for europe it was a full month
wow it didn't feel that long
because i didn't follow so closely was
honestly an adventure of a lifetime i
met so many amazing people and saw so
many spectacular sights most important
of all i got to see you perform live on
stage and talk with you
one whole
[Music]
yeah amazing i'm glad you enjoyed it
yeah nice
yeah it must have been nice to get
away from
home for a while to see the world
oh
i'm stopped do i have the thing on
that's minimum two weeks old
ah
like recently i look
because when i uh
i'll turn it off because when i um when
i
um make new streams sometimes i take
like previous streams as like the
the
template and
there must have been one stream where i
used it
and it just keeps on getting copy pasted
and normally i turn it off
i feel like i turned it off
it hasn't been on for all of my streams
recently because then it's not working
when i turn it off
i'm pretty sure i've been turning it off
manually
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] i've been turning it off
every single [\h__\h] time
i swear
it just turns itself back on that little
[\h__\h]
i turned it off now
huh
[Music]
it was not intentional
not at all
every time i make a template i use a
template i turn it off
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
okay turn it off now
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] oh i can chat now hi i'm
so sorry
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
hello
everybody new subscribers
hello patsy
oh my god you guys thought i did it on
purpose huh it didn't
[Music]
oh my god
that must have left a bad impression to
newcomers
[\h__\h]
wait was it on for the pop-tart stream
finally i can unsub you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
i see
i'm so sorry
oh my god
i noticed so late i thought that
i'm i'm i'm shocked okay continue
ah thank you patsy so mapped in eight
thanks for the red super chat with a
nostalgic stream time how are you
enjoying any time zones i hope you're
not too worn out from the past two days
can't wait to see the end result thank
you for streaming tango it's beyond
appreciated yeah i can't wait to see it
either i just saw some snippets
and the snippets i saw look pretty good
so i have high hopes now
but i'm still really nervous about the
outcome
but it should be good i trust
kanauru to put my
captured dances
uh together into something that looks
good
but yeah you know the the one um my
appearance
in goodness concert i told you guys that
wasn't me but i promise you and i would
not lie to you
i promise you and i'm proud to say
that all of that
is me
in my birthday concert and i worked so
hard for it
i worked my butt off
and i'm [\h__\h] proud of it
so i want to
make that very clear
that is me
yeah
thank you thank you
thank you
thank you thank you just don't want you
to misunderstand that because kanawha is
editing it
that it's not me or something like that
because that's not the case
yeah yeah yeah
i just you know i didn't know who else
to ask and i thought you know because
like he made these music videos that he
might have the skill to make it into a
concert
and he does
yeah
i'm so excited
so excited
[Music]
thank you guys thank you very much
thank you
continuing marching for uh you get a
kiss
[Music]
thank you thank you kaito crosstalkation
mr
vegas some local chocolate oh i didn't
um i didn't eat any chocolate at all
i think
yeah i only
what did i eat so i ate like a few um
ubereats like uh
i ate some some curry i ate some
yakisoba it's um and then i ate some
stuff at the izakaya uh
i ate the taiyaki i ate the ice cream i
had baskin robbins i ate
esquitos
i ate
in and out
and
i ate some waffles with nutella
and callie made sure to get me nutella
by the way
thank you so much kelly kelly honestly
like she the
the place that we stayed in
she
let us stay in there together which was
like really really um bendy uh
convenient to have us all together
she got us a really nice place
to stay in that was really comfy besides
being [\h__\h] cold
but yeah she took care of like ordering
uh
getting us food and drinks yeah she took
care of us and then you know after she
ordered groceries like later on i was
like oh i wish i had this sauce for this
food and then she would like make
another order to get me that sauce in
particular
[Music]
so sweet she was taking care of all
these things and yeah that was really
sweet of her
she did not get me orange soda no maybe
she understood that i don't it's not
like i i mean i'm drinking fanta right
now but that's really a rare occasion
i don't ever drink orange soda
she got something in her head there that
was not really a thing
[Music]
yeah but
um yeah
had a good time was a comfy comfy place
to stay and really chill
and
yeah it was like good to have us all in
the same place
for like streams
late night streams and all that
she said i always drank it if anything i
drank it once
[Music]
it's not my favorite my favorite is iced
tea for [\h__\h] sake
[Music]
oh my god so uh where was i um
oh yeah
thank
so happy to see you are with your
friends good question is it okay if kfc
made a map of cool places to go and sew
for you
yes feel free to say no if you don't
need it or anyways enjoy your time over
there no please do please please please
please please please please please pong
please please please please please
please tell me
please tell me what i where i should go
what i should do
and yeah
preferably um
because i don't know if nabi can be with
me
um every day
probably not i wouldn't want to like
force her to be with me every day would
be nice to have some places that are
easy to go to uh alone as a foreigner
who doesn't speak
korean
not too far from the city center
i guess shopping i'll definitely go
shopping so tell me the best shopping
places
i want to buy many clothes and makeup
but besides that you know going shopping
is easy
you're welcome to tell me about some
touristy things to do um
i wish i knew do i know anyone else in
in korea
do i know anybody else
don't think i know anyone else
[Music]
not fans
cultist recruiters well that's fun
because um
i feel
like i'm something like
i'm i'm
a little bit of a cultist recruiter
myself
we know if you know anybody i don't know
do you know
i don't know if you know if i know
anybody in korea
do i know anybody in korea
[Music]
gangnam for the high street heist height
height what high
high street friends what high street
well do you i don't know
i feel like i don't
maybe i should quickly make some friends
before
[Music]
maybe i should quickly make some friends
before going but like who are there like
some
maybe some
some youtubers
[Music]
who live in korea
in seoul
doesn't need to have a need to be a veto
but
[Music]
yeah meeting up with nabi mama but like
i'm not gonna um like i don't know i
don't want to
occupy her for
too long
[Music]
i'm kind of shy isn't it kind of weird
to like suddenly be like hey i'm going
to korea so i want to make friends be my
friend now
um
interesting
i didn't really
i don't have like any connection with
her though besides you know
that's just a business connection
never like interacted with her really
tax refunds
i don't know about that
[Music]
oh
korean tinder days
[Music]
i mean i guess i did that
in japan to find female friends and it
was very effective
[Music]
but
i don't know i don't know about doing
that in
korea
maybe maybe maybe i can contact twice
[Music]
we're for shots
maybe
[Music]
maybe someone
maybe they want to hang with me
[Music]
how about side no
nah girls cute girls please
i i guess i'll i'll hit up um
at
jyp entertainment
i'll be like hi
what's up so me yeah i love she she put
out a new song now she's doing so much
promotion
um
uh
some me
please be friends with me
[Music]
i don't think that's gonna work
like how how would i how would i go
about that
[Music]
let's do it not with that attitude hey
i'll have to look around a little bit
maybe i'll try to
contact someone i don't
that is
nothing's gonna come out of that
oh man i wonder if i could go to like
some kind of concert but i guess like i
don't know i don't know how to do that
also i don't know those korean fan
chants and i would feel very out of
place if i would be there and not know
the chance but it would be kind of cool
to experience it like maybe one of those
like tv show recordings how do you get
into that maybe i could ask some
contacts
you know those tv shows where they
showcase the new songs i don't know when
they happen and how you get into that
but
i want to be in the audience would be so
cool
[Music]
i know they have videos yeah yeah no no
gentle currently drinking and worry
they're usually on the lottery and that
sounds like it would be kind of
difficult yeah yeah i'm sure there's
like a million people like signing up
for that
maybe
[Music]
i might have some connections
let me write this down
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] did i just do with my hand
could
[Music]
okay
written down
i know a few people that might be able
to oh ooh
interesting
thing yeah yeah i'm in the dms of
mamamoo right now yeah yeah dm'ing
mamamoo as we speak
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah if we had whole life korea that
would be really useful right now
i would just hang with all of them
if only
see you on sonar's channel
collaborate
you don't waste any second yeah gotta
gotta grab those opportunities
gotta make it happen
just do it don't let your [\h__\h] dreams
be dreams right
yeah
all right
all right all right all right all right
maybe
korea probably also has some kind of
onsen too right probably i could imagine
like hot springs
maybe i should go to
one a traditional
korean
hot spring do you guys have that
[Music]
ah but going alone is intimidating you
guys know i can't get naked in onsen
and when i'm alone i don't know why
intimidating
[Music]
korean saunas 10 things you need to know
about korean saunas
a korean bath house like no other if
you're visiting visiting the k-pop
capital
experiencing one of these unique spots
is a must jim jingle bangs are part of
korean culture and they're pretty
awesome but you have to get naked first
well [\h__\h]
jin jinbang is a traditional korean bath
house where people come to enjoy hot and
cold pools relaxing saunas massage areas
and communal sleeping rooms
uh-huh it's a cultural institution
enjoyed by uncle and being a family
exclusion on date night for couples on
pampering sessions for friends who are a
social outing for older people
jingle bangs are a place to meditate
relax and unwind
[Music]
ginger banks are an important part of
most koreans weekly beauty rituals
weekly
[Music]
ginger banks are gender separated okay
good okay but still
don't be afraid to get naked but i am
afraid when you enter the wet areas
everyone is completely naked yup you
need to strip down to your birthday suit
[Music]
i will do that anyway on the 6th of july
initially this was bizarre to me because
teenagers adults and grandparents of all
shapes and sizes walking around they may
be self-conscious and feel completely
exposed at first but remember this is
completely normal yeah but they would
definitely be like hey yo what is this
orange-haired
like white ass
phoenix girl
doing here naked i'm pretty sure they
would like look at me
i think i would stand out
um
oh yeah you maybe
everyone gets naked nobody cares i'm not
sure about that i tried unsuccessfully
to cover up with my tiny towel but soon
realize that if you look shy and nervous
you'll stand out from the crowd oh i'm
so [\h__\h] then
this is this is what will result in
stairs not the nakedness god damn it put
towel on your hair yeah i've seen that
before in japan too
[Music]
scrub like you've never scrapped before
with hundreds of people hopping in and
out of the hot bath surely they must get
dirty right nope and that's because you
have to scrub everything yeah this is
like an japanese onsen
you'll notice many koreans scrubbing
each other this is also common practice
but they know each other right this is
not strangers scrubbing each other right
don't be surprised if someone comes and
starts scrubbing your back unexpectedly
excuse me what
they do it with strangers
[Music]
what
um korean friends
can you
tell me if this is real
that is in the old days
hopefully
or maybe like in a like
countryside
um jin jilbang
where people know each other maybe
[Music]
that sounds awesome no
friendlier than americans
eh i can ask for someone to scrap my bag
okay korean cafe are denying it
oh thank god
thank god
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] that would be so weird
okay spy case
case my case
that worries me
you're worried about being alone weird
strange orange hair girl and naked wrap
your towel above over your head so no oh
you mean cover my whole hair in a towel
oh i don't think that's the only thing
that stands out with me though
i think i have this whole um foreign
aura about myself
anyway
uh
what the [\h__\h] for a true jim jill bang
experience is this a [\h__\h] posting
article
i highly recommend getting a scrub from
one of the ajumas older korean
woman um no thank you
i will not be getting
a back scrub from an older korean woman
this crap oh wait this is actually
professional and costs money okay this
scrub also known as seishin takes about
30 minutes and costs between 15 000
korean one to twenty five thousand
twelve to twenty dollars don't expect a
soft gentle massage the ladies will
scrub you properly and it's intense oh
and they're also naked
[Music]
so
i'm paying someone who's also naked
to scrub my back
[Music]
intensely that sounds
funny
your body gets red from the scrub
oh what the [\h__\h]
please not so intensely my poor skin
[Music]
at first this was something i wasn't
keen for but after my fair share of
visits to jinjin banks in korea i
decided to give it a go and you should
too
um
[Music]
you have to do this
i guess it would be an interesting story
to talk about on stream so do it for the
streams do it for the content
this person has a clear bias
yeah
uh
it's a great place to spend the night
okay
maths to sleep on on a soft plastic
block which is used as a pillow so it's
not an actual like bed okay
super cheap activity korean bath houses
are extremely affordable for what you
get okay
jim jill bangs are not a tourist trap if
you visit a gymnasium bang in korea
there's a high chance that you will be
one of the very few foreigners in the
bath house
yeah uh-huh i can imagine to really get
the most out of your visit it's best to
go after strenuous activities like
hiking book hansan mountain in seoul oh
hiking huh
it was one of the most unique things i
did in korea and if you want to learn
more about korean culture in an
authentic way make sure you make some
time to fully immerse yourself in a
gingival family
they're really pushing jim jilbang onto
me
etiquette
you need to be prepared and know what to
do before you arrive some signing noise
boards are in english but the staff may
be able to point you in the right
direction but don't expect to be
handheld throughout the process yeah
that was also like when i
when i first went to a japanese onsen
that was the reason why i stayed away
from it for so long because i didn't
want to do anything wrong
and when i first went even though i
understood japanese like i still felt
kind of like lost
and probably did do something wrong
don't be those tourists whilst many
koreans visit these bath houses with
their friends or family it's still a
place of trans tranquility where they
come to disconnect when the other
silence is golden okay be quiet okay
make sure you pay pack the right things
oh
shampoo body wash
don't rush
[Music]
oh that's a step-by-step guide
and how to do it
get naked step three get naked remember
that
[Music]
the towels are tiny and equivalent to
worse than hand towels
okay how how am i gonna hide those
badonkadonks
with tiny towels huh
[Music]
how will i even wrap it around my head
if they're so tiny that's impossible
[Music]
i know you don't i know
and the wet area and scrub
naked you'll walk to the hot and cold
pools of the jimjilbang the entrance to
this wet area is for a separate door
little blah blah blah as you make your
way inside you'll notice the hot baths
and showers that line the room before
you do anything take a shower and scrub
yourself clean you dirty [\h__\h] spend
time making sure every inch of your body
is clean as a string gel bang etiquette
to do so
if you wash your hair be sure to tie it
back up again sorry that was improvised
just your face is okay really
it doesn't sound like that's okay
no then our children say that
sauna i've been i've been enjoying
saunas recently but preferably i want to
be alone in the sauna
oh what is this
[Music]
what is this sand
there's like a picture
of a fermentation room
is is that sand
i hate sand
it looks like i guess it's like a hot
sand room
[Music]
i guess at least if you're not wearing
shoes then at least the sand can't get
into your shoes and never leave you
anymore
oh there's recommendations on which ones
to go to
[Music]
oh dear
oh dear okay anyway sorry for that
little um trip
uh that was an interesting article
very biased
eh not send hardened clay
looks like sand to me in the picture
[Music]
i'll think about it
i
i don't i can't say yes if i'll go out i
don't know if i can
um get the courage to go
especially alone and i wouldn't want to
go with nabi either because that's
actually pretty damn embarrassing
that you know getting naked with nabi um
it's just a little bit too much i don't
know
oh
i don't think we're you know at that
level of trust yet
um it's not not really my culture so
i need a lot of trust for that
uh
[Music]
it will be a burning i don't know
no
no no if anything maybe i would go alone
i guess i don't know
[Music]
even trust anyone that much well i went
with callie
at least with cali it's like you know
like we're i wouldn't be the only
foreigner
and i think there's more to look at
um
at cali so if any if they would look at
anything they would probably look at
cali not at me
[Laughter]
um so that's maybe kind of a relief
and she had more experience with onsen
that me than me because she goes to them
more often more frequently so
um
you wanted to use cali as a decoy no
that wasn't really i wasn't doing it
consciously that was not my my
my reason or my my fault when going with
her um but it was definitely um
[Laughter]
helpful maybe
um
yeah but no i we did we did when we went
we did um go um to like because there
was like a quite a choice of
different
baths to enter and we went to one
where
we knew that there wouldn't really be
many people in there so
yeah when we went there was like two
older ladies there and they left
immediately when we entered for
whatever reason
and then until we were done
no one joined us so that was perfect
that was perfect
[Music]
yeah
take cali yeah she would probably enjoy
the jim jill bun
i'll feed the butt
[Music]
how do you feel about people getting kfp
chimken tattoos as well as tattoos in
general i hope you're having a great
time i don't have any tattoos and i'm
not planning on getting any
in the future but i don't mind people
with tattoos i think you know it can be
pretty cool
there are definitely some tattoos that i
feel like are kind of cringe
um
but
yeah i don't know if you want to get
something like that tattooed i would
like something like kfp or so okay
related i would want you to think about
it very very very hard
because
as much as you guys may love me now and
i appreciate that a tattoo is
forever
unless you get it removed
but even then it doesn't look good so
um
i would not recommend you getting a
kiwawa related tattoo
just because i don't want you to regret
it later on
um
but i guess it depends like if you're
for example if you already have like i
don't know 50 tattoos on your body
then it won't even stand out that much
and then
your your whole tolerance about
tattoos is
higher anyway
[Music]
now so
you know and then it might be fine but
yeah think about it as long as you're
really really really really sure about
it
that you also won't regret it even when
kfp is no more one day
then then okay
if you think if you think it's a
good idea hmm
[Music]
okay if he is forever
okay
okay can't be forever
always in your heart
[Music]
taylor's saying thank you for the rest
of the chat ooh is that from australia
hey mate
hi i'm going to be traveling to phoenix
land austria later this year for work
really do you have any recommendations
on places to go to see or things to eat
not a hotel uh i've i've given
recommendations before
and
i mean obviously the capital
has a lot to show
um and it's pretty easy to check out
everything by foot actually
like especially there's so much in the
city center
that just by walking a little bit you
get from one spot to the next spot
and
so yeah just check out everything in the
capital i guess and then besides that i
i'm gonna be honest i haven't been
around much in my own country
there's
so much i haven't seen i've seen
less i've seen like maybe 10
of my if not less of my own country
um
but
i
from the things that i have seen i guess
i can recommend you um
salzburg
and now i haven't been there but a
classic place to go
would be
which is relatively close to salzburg so
you could go like from south brook to
houston to
vienna
for example
hmm
but the thing is of houston is that
it has been
dominated by tourists
for the past centuries
during the cold
times
it's been better but
i don't know how it has been recently
it might be getting more packed by the
end of the year
[Music]
but as you said uh
later this year i don't know how long
you stay
saying but if you're there during the
winter time then definitely check out
the christmas markets
yeah
there are a lot of things to see i think
because we have really pretty
architecture
yeah typical european architecture
and uh yeah food wise
um
austria shares a lot of the foods from
a lot of the cuisine from
um the countries that surround us
so i don't think there's anything wrong
with like eating italian food and
hungarian food like um like goulash
and german food and all that
because you'll get a lot of it
any cake anyway when you're there
um
so don't i think that's totally fine
because that's just what we eat
ourselves a lot too
but if you want to eat austrian food i
would say the viennese typical schnitzel
with the lingonberry jam don't forget
the lingerberry jam that is a must you
have to eat the meat with the
lingonberry jam
and then there's also like a lot of
austrian desserts like
apple strudel you gotta eat the original
and sacha toite which is a cake
and uh if you're in salzburg it's not
particularly yummy but there's a dessert
that's called salzburg
which is just a really fluffy
nothingness it doesn't taste like much
but it's really fluffy and wobbly and
funny
salzburger
[Music]
n-o-c-k-e-r
that's it
casey spatzler hell yeah go get some
cases spatzler
um especially if you plan to go up on a
mountain which i really recommend
actually because on the mountains we
have a lot of
um what would you call them maybe like a
tavern or so
and up there they serve really really
great food like if you go skiing
but you don't even have to like if it's
if there's no snow
then still
they they still um
work up there
and have really really really yummy food
but it's the best if you go there like
while you're skiing you just stop by
at one of those
tavern thingy restaurants the rest the
the traditional ones
and they have really great yummy
traditional austrian food
yeah
up on the mountain it tastes so much
yummier
[Music]
yeah
and so on um table spits for example
table spits is another
thing you could eat
[Music]
yeah okay continuing
thank you taylor
have a good time in austria
thank you so let's keep playing for the
red super chat it's been close to two
years since you started you flew into
our lives i always think what would have
been had i not found you or who alive
this has easily been the most
life-changing event for me in the now 28
years i've been around this earth
you're still so young
wow
well thanks to you thank you
wow what made you
write such a
emotional
deep
sweet super chats was it your birthday
because you didn't say it clearly but it
kind of sounds like
a little bit like a birthday super [\h__\h]
[Music]
that's just me
it wasn't your birthday
[Music]
or were you just feeling emotional
it's near the end what do you mean near
the end of what
[Music]
oh there's a boy
oh there's a rainbow
ah
okay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay oh there it is i'm
putting myself out there so much more
i'm making new connections and real
relationships with internet strangers
that i've only met maybe once or twice
and turning them into lasting
friendships something that i wouldn't
have thought possible and then there is
you who continues to constantly
enlighten my life up every single day
whether it's an entertaining stream or
silly twitter interactions with her
fluffy chimpkins while she does her best
to be an excellent idol i can't wait for
your birthday on the 6th only a crazy
dedicated bird like yourself
would go across the ocean like this and
my respect roof for you seeing your
heart and soul poured into this
yeah i went really far for this
the feelings i have now the love for kfp
and you and the excitement i feel now is
the best birthday present for me the
second time as a cafe member oh thanks
for being new for my birthday is on the
27th aha you sent it early probably
knowing i won't read it until later
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday so let's keep waiting
happy birthday to you
[Applause]
thank you for the rainbow patty patty
button
and i'm very happy for you
that you're having such a great time
sounds like your life just got better
after
uh joining kfp huh
congratulations
[Music]
i hope you had a great birthday it's
already over but you hopefully celebrate
it properly
[Music]
hope you had a good time stay happy and
happy and wish you all the best
and please continue
being part
it's great having you here
[Music]
m
um
[Music]
nine five two seven thank you for the
red super chat duncan thank you very
much no message with it what why
why
but thank you for the support mwah
castle thank you so much
are great but as long as you girls are
having fun with each other in person
after being apart for so long it doesn't
matter how much of that form fun happens
in the form of streams or not thank you
for understanding but i definitely did
try to
um you know stream as much as
possible in the time that we had
so that we would have something to look
back on and also be able to share it
with you guys because after all we are
streamers
so
i mean it's nice having some off time to
get to know each other offline
but in the end we're streamers so i feel
like we need to
share
our experiences like that
ping on next is duncan
wow thank you for being so generous
pray for kiwawa take care of your health
thank you
i am
now much better now that i'm home i feel
healthy it's just my legs maybe that are
a bit still
sad
about being used so much
kind of damaged but besides that i'm
very good now
thank you very much for your worries
yeah i wish you all the best to please
take care of your own health as well
okay
thank you soon
[Music]
thank you for the pinky i'm so proud of
you kelly you're always working so hard
for us thank you yes i do i do be
working hard and i know that it kept me
kind of busy for a whole month and i'm
sorry about that but
it's it's it's gonna be back to normal
now
yeah
so don't worry and if i go to korea i'm
also gonna try to stream a lot
like maybe at the end of my day
after i did some sightseeing i will try
to stream
maybe
almost
every
day or every second day
[Music]
korea has good internet really
i actually you know when i streamed from
the hotel during that stream that one
that we're reading super chats of
i know i i couldn't move right but i
actually forgot i had a
um a solution for that before and i
forgot about it but next time i'll
remember
or if you guys
see me being cardboard again
tell me that i have a solution for that
and i might have just forgotten it again
but there's a like a round around around
the solution
that i forgot last time
because it's been a long time but i know
i know how to fix it like not really fix
it but
there is a way to
get around it solution joe
i i work around yes yes yes that's it
that's it
[Music]
for the rest of the chat
love our determined persevering phoenix
that word is so hard to say but thank
you
[Music]
you worked so hard and it's finally
coming to fruition
fruit fruit
fruit fruit yes fruit shouldn't fruit
fruition
[Music]
uh
fruit fruits
very excited to see your concert also
very glad it all worked out for you to
hang out with the move in person
uh hope you're having an amazing time
thank you
thank you very much
yeah had a good time have a good time
with them thank you
pudding challenge
[Music]
virtuous liberty thank you i haven't
been able to watch you live in over a
year
hey what are you doing this is the first
time i can finally and i don't even
complain just watch vods people thank
you
because of the time zone or because you
were i don't know doing some
i don't know exchange year or what
[Music]
even if you live in an american time
zone
not being able to watch me live for a
whole year sounds crazy you must have
been occupied with something else
[Music]
it seems like you know because it's a
a us dollar super chat i would think
they're in america
and not to yeah i mean on the weekends
maybe
on the weekend in the early
noon
time
i feel like it's not too impossible but
i guess you had some other things to do
but nice nice thank you for watching the
vods though thank you very much
martin ate duncan
[Music]
the great billy mays thank you for the
red super chat you never know secret kfb
customs and border protection agents
uh are we talking about the
the passport control story
[Music]
i don't think so but it was a weird
situation yeah some things were kind of
weird
but yeah
i think we're
we're good that was not someone who
[Music]
would be a subscriber of me i think
if anything they maybe
knew
what youtubers were and were acting as
if they didn't know if anything but i
wouldn't that would be too much of a
coincidence that the one
passport control person i walk up to
is
coincidence
coincidentally um
a kfb member i think that's just too
unlikely
so
i tell them to subscribe it's a joke but
they he said no
he said no
rude
i hope he at least left a
thumbs up
and there we go
so a great really amazing thank you
here's a kiss for you
[Music]
murph laser dangerous atlantean guard
bjorn duncan friendly
[Music]
just making
sure yes i bought it
thank you for always super chatting
thank you so much
what
yellow fruited martin
that eats cats
what
is that the thing in your profile
picture
yellow fruit
martin
that is that's so cute
but it eats cats
holy [\h__\h] it's so cute
it has such a nice color wow so fancy
how come it has that color
oh look it up guys yellow
fro ted
martin m-a-r-t-e-n
it's so pretty
[Music]
that thing eats cats
really
that is terrifying how does that thing
looks really small how does it eat cats
it looks too cute to do such a thing
but
that's in your profile picture you must
really like it
cute thank you thank you for the rest of
the chat wow thank you for your love
always thank you so much my loyal
loyalty
can always rely on you thank you
go to kat did nothing wrong danke soon
leave me soon
sky thank you sushiro dancing
[Music]
i just
i had to look up
um
the name just to make sure i didn't like
to say something political right now but
it seems to be a star trek character
okay
[Music]
the all navy train is
done
oh you mean you went to the military and
you're done
[Music]
and i'm glad you're good i'm watching it
well in korea too
huh
and there's some korean texts
[Music]
yes manager it's been a while i'm
watching it after the navy training camp
[Music]
are there more coming back to me now
it didn't feel like it's been that long
i thought you guys were going for a year
or like two yeah because isn't it
two-year
[Music]
he's just becoming private what
are you going there again
[Music]
basic training
i hope you can stay
johnny depp
[Music]
thank you for coming back to me thank
you for not forgetting about me
that's my biggest worry when people
leave for such a long time and you guys
are probably not even like able to watch
my content
while you're gone
so
that worries me that you forget about me
[Music]
if you volunteer you can go out fast
what
really that's interesting
after training you about go back to
having internet
we get phones after a month oh
nice
at least something
don't forget about me
[Music]
oh ellie
i think these chickens can forget you
well i don't know like if you have like
if you don't have time for a whole year
or two years
then i feel like
now you might move on it's normal it's
okay but it's sad
[Music]
shadow pencil thank you looking for the
top finishing the game create transition
and cut contact
i'm done with this
holy [\h__\h] it's been four hours
ah
[Music]
the one from yesterday
i want to stop
yeah i think i want to stop i'm bored of
it
i'm part of it
i'm sick of it
four hours of super chat rating are just
enough
[Music]
enough now i want food
and oh
this
i want this
i'm really curious what you guys think
of the english version of the
translation
[Music]
so i'll give you guys some time now to
chill
uh
ah cat hair in my mouth or maybe take a
nap if you want
is the translation spicy
i think it's about as spicy as the
original song yeah
it didn't change the meaning
[Music]
two times two hours from now two
two hours from now it will be uh finally
released uh originally kind of wanted to
release it last month but then things
happened kind of busy
translation took some time uh but it's
finally ready
yeah yeah yeah
i'm excited the art is so cute isn't it
they're so cute
so
it's nice to check you're welcome i
would have done it earlier if i knew it
so sorry
yeah
sorry i took that away from you
[Laughter]
okay
so i'll see you um tomorrow in the
members only stream and on sunday for
all the non-members i'll see you again
for the wind waker stream the last one
the finale
yeah do you plan the celebration club
during the next week yeah we can do that
i'm not sure what what to do though
um
if you guys have some suggestions
let me know please don't say vr because
vr is [\h__\h] exhausting
let's collab for next week bundleman
i wrote to her
[Music]
animal head crossing
yeah let me know maybe on twitter
let me know on twitter because now if
you write it to me on chat it's just too
much in my brain
i switched sports ah i've seen some
girls playing that as collab
game you don't have to be there together
in person huh
you can do it online that's interesting
i'm not sure if i want to do that with
um dana doll but definitely an idea for
a future collabo
[Music]
no i do tomorrow members and then sunday
it's still weekend so i'll do um
wind waker on sunday
[Music]
wouldn't there be lag i don't know it
seemed fine when gouda and shion played
it
[Music]
yeah
what time is the membership um i didn't
decide yet maybe around the same time as
today
are we getting him yes it's not finished
yet i'm so sorry actually
some problems came up like um the
original artist that i
had in mind
and already
like requested
for july
kind of like last minute said sorry
can't do it so
i had to quickly find a new artist and
um the new audience is working on it as
fast and as hard as possible
it should be done by the end of the week
[Music]
by time by the time i use um
the new art for the new schedule for
next week
yeah
yeah yeah
yeah okay thank you for your
understanding and in german we say
alvina zayn i need to go to an idol
meeting so
bye bye thank you for watching love you
guys thank you for
listening to me and chilling and hanging
with me
[Music]
guys have a nice evening see you guys
soon oh bye bye
[Music]
bye bye it was fun thank you
thanks mozart
thanks thanks dude yeah you can stop now
[Music]
you