Maybe the color is too thin, Pee Noi Sod
[Song]
Cool Sai Kerd Jer Toey, thinking about walking.
I'll say that if you don't peel off the sun, you'll go to university and report it. Possessed
by eating, so you
can
meet
[song] See Ban Pai
Tee No No No,
but come today and you won't be able to see the color. How can you tell?
Pee Dam is gone. Mother is love.  Jiao
[song] No matter
how little you can get if you have reason and your mind to do it,
Snee Bakari Marie
Chao Nai Sod,
don't want to come on Friday, maybe it's from Yod
Lawyer
[song] The
person who lives in a famous place.  Operator comes to
take care of you,
but the house still has a bed.
This should be possible. When I grow up, it probably won't be.
Come as you wish,
come and provide services that
Mother is watching.   The one
who really came to Panka's house to take care of her in
January.