la
[Music]
n o
do
n
[Music]
booo
oo P Bo
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm a
ghost at
kfp haunting
[Music]
you
oo I am to be very
feared you must fear me I'm a
[Music]
ghost hands belong to a ghost too
sometimes I I am what
remains for
tonight for takanashi KI your
boss because she has perished once again
for the
256th time
oh
no or should I say oh
[Music]
no but fear not little one brain cell
chickens as you
remember she's a phix
boo so she'll be back by
tomorrow KY Boo by the way
[Music]
she she has had a little accident oh
well it's me I I I I don't know why I'm
talking in third person Boo I'm coming
up with this at the
Spoto she's not gone forever remember
she's a phoenix it doesn't take her long
to
revive so on this night we must
celebrate her death which leads to her
Revival
boo hopefully my motion capture will go
well
[Music]
today ah now do you want to see my
beautiful booty
please say yes I want to be desired even
when I'm a
ghost thank you I'm making a heart for
you yeah you want to see
me
o oh well since you are such good
chickens who are taking care of the
restaurant while your boss your boo is
dead I shall reward
[Music]
you if I find the right OBS thing what
the hell ah oh it's the wrong thing I
see oh here it is ah I'm
[Music]
flying oh oh
interesting what
[Music]
happened
woo and G
[Music]
woo face tracking only works when my
face is facing the camera
[Music]
wo what do you mean I'm in a bed sheet
I'm
not would you like to see a
twirl say
yes well let me take off my imaginary
headphones all right please look at my
[Music]
twirl
yippe that was fun wow being a ghost is
fun
seems like I keep on getting
closer well well well it is
Halloween happy
Halloween let me make the microphone
higher
um what a coincidence that I have died
on
Halloween let me sing for you a song Oh
ignore ignore these things by the way
for now why did I already show them I I
will have some people calling
in so that's for
them
okay uh
uh maybe a little bit less of
that uh uh might a little little little
bit
more okay are you ready
[Music]
more more not
for
[Music]
fore
foree
for
[Music]
Fore
for spee
[Music]
boo Bo
[Applause]
yay
but I think something is wrong with my
script I was singing what that's you
vampire I am vampire and
yet I am a Ghost something's not right
something's not
matching can we match can I perhaps
match it up so that my audience will
enjoy this
[Music]
more H oh what a
coincidence I have prepared for
this um which
button a [\h__\h]
[Music]
wait
uh that
was that was
fast
yay okay okay okay this is a really like
last minute um
Halloween
costume and if you cute if you recall uh
from long sorry from long time ago this
is my for streat vampire
w y let me do a twirl now
too yeah B grew up I I am adult
now
Yahoo my my hands are a little bit yahoi
hands I just
realized or is it in that case yudy
hands I don't know man oo SP but look I
got some beautiful legs I still got to
have my sporty shoes right but besides
that it's like my default outfit shooty
R&B what's up my default outfit but like
kind of recolored and a little bit
revamped ha because I'm a vampire now
yay super cute thank
you I finally became adult I finally
grew grew up it to it took me so long so
now we can stop the whole I'm a ghost
thing well actually no no I'm still a
ghost I'm still dead I'm still dead oh
maybe I just revived I should rewrite my
script maybe I just revived okay I
revived
yay hi what's up kikiki uh what have you
been doing while I was gone H have you
been taken care of the store I guess I
should probably play a bgm
again
H what was I playing this one there it
[Music]
is be gone Undead sh
sho are you guys dressing up have you
guys been getting trick trick or- treat
kids M I haven't I don't think I've ever
been trick-or-treated in my whole life
so today is the day I will be trick or
treated I'll have some Callins from a
few members who have kindly signed up to
call into my stream uh as you can see
depending on there's two wheels they can
choose depending on what they choose we
will get different kinds of results over
on this side we have a trick wheel
on the trick wheel we have interesting
things for example EMS paint me now it
doesn't have to be EMS paint but they're
supposed to draw me like really quickly
and send it to me within like 5 minutes
then plan a collab for us is like um
well they have to think about a collab
that we could do and then it can't just
stay in our imagination it has to be
real it has to be made into reality in a
relatively realistically soon time yeah
hopefully
kind of uh working
towards I mean I guess I'm still kind of
forcing the collab but in a way they're
inviting me to a collab
right and then there's you owe me candy
basically that one won't happen right
away whenever I meet this person in the
future again or for the first time they
will give me candy hopefully lots of it
hopefully good ones and then there's
sing my for treat yeah just like the
chorus and just a capella I just want to
hear them sing uh the song because I'm
wearing the
outfit yeah and on the treat side this
is supposed to be a little bit
more wait no it's the other way
around I just
realized
yeah the trick side the trick side is
supposed to be a bit more
um making me put getting me into trouble
I don't know making me do things that
are hassle uh there is uh what is there
five
push-ups kill me
please uh and tongue twister T yeah
we'll we'll find it we'll find the
tongue twister this is Mirad left hand
oh yeah it's Mirad we'll find the tongue
twister and uh then we both have to say
it and we'll see hopefully like only one
try uh we'll see who is better at it and
the winner will get
nothing except the glory of today and
then there is the furnace dance what is
that H uh does that sound familiar to
you
guys
uh copyrights and stuff but um it's
supposed to be some popular currently
popular dance uh song dance thing but I
will try to recreate one or two or three
moves of it and then there's flirt tool
if we get that on the wheel and I shall
flirt with the collar or I shall attempt
to do so uh as best as I can perhaps
using my body even
yeah my microphone I'm kind of I feel
like I need to stay close to
it yeah so uh there will not be like an
endless amount of callers uh but a
couple we got a couple and I will sing
afterwards some more sing and dance some
more and that will be our little tiny
kind of improvised Halloween party
because this wasn't yet in my plans
three days
ago yay so so so so so are we ready for
the first caller oh I have DMS too on
no
oh oh never mind I think first caller
actually needs
a a few more minutes that's okay
maybe maybe oh no problem actually I'm
wondering I I should probably I didn't
really look much at this model yet I
might have
some the DMS are kind of funny um might
have some interesting stuff here what do
we
have oh I got freckles and stuff again
[Music]
oopsie
sorry a yeah nothing too crazy
but
[Music]
ah
what why I thought this would just be
like making my eyebrows visible in front
of my hair oh I got fangs
it says eyebrows eyebrows on eyebrows
off I didn't think it would be eyebrows
like that but
yeah I'm a vampire let me suck the blood
out of your
neck oh yeah uh I think the caller uh
likes
vampire also there's the freckles are
back cute a freckle vampire have you
ever seen a vampire with freckles before
[Music]
it is
me that's like six members yeah eight
member wow so many
fans
nice okay okay okay let's see where are
we I'll turn down the pajama a little
bit
uh oh hello a ky K KY K Kyo KY boo happy
Halloween happy Halloween to
you how are
you oh I'm a sizzling and bubbling you
know how it is sizzling and bubbling are
you cooking right now what are you
cooking I'm not I'm not cooking oh that
did sound like you were cooking I know
maybe you should be cooking
it's it's okay it's okay it's okay well
happy Halloween yay happy Halloween to
you what are you dressing up as
huh ah an elf an elf
gadriel oh scary gadriel or nice gadriel
just normal just I didn't have time to
get like a proper yeah I didn't have
time to get a proper Halloween costume
so I'm just using something in my closet
oh right you actually like kind of like
dressing
up yeah oh cute can you send me a
picture l
I have the Privileges give me
pictures if if I have if I get if I get
into it properly and it looks cute I'll
send you a picture I'm sure you look
cute oh but then if you if you get
trick-or-treated as gadriel when you
open the door you have to be spooky
gadriel what what does spooky gadriel
say again in the movie I'm thinking of
does everybody know what I'm thinking of
when I say spooky
gadriel yes yeah right when like she's
like
it's very spooky yeah what does does she
have a famous phrase in that moment I
will be a dark queen is that what what
she says yeah I'll I'll be a dark and
beautiful queen oh yeah something like
that like this I will de dark
queen yes terrible and
beautiful I love it it's time to watch
Lord of the Rings again man I know it's
that time of year all right me lady
give me a trick a trick no I'm not a
trick don't you love me I do love you
but I want a trick I've never gotten a
trick for Halloween oh man everybody's
just too nice nowadays in this world huh
I'm only giving treats okay I will roll
the wheel for I will spin the wheel for
you
spin the wheel oh it doesn't look like
it's spinning on my on on on the screen
but you got tongue twister test
I swear I swear it's real it's real it's
true I'm not trying to fake this I'm
very honest I wanted five pushups are
you kidding me if you continue watching
we might get it still I know I I'll be
I'll be here no worries okay now do you
have a wait no I shouldn't ask you cuz
you're probably going to choose one that
you that you can do well a
tongue uh do you have any tongue fers
that you can do well that I can disqual
unique New York York yellow Leed New
York wa what I can't even say that
unique New York unique New York oh my
God I never heard that one before but no
we're not going to go for that then cuz
you seem to know that too well yellow
leather red leather okay we're not going
for that one Ean how about
uh what is
that what is wait let me Google that
first what that what that word
means okay ah okay what h h
I learned something new you know what a
tobogan tobogan is
toog no you're making up oh you're
creating a fake word no no Google says
it's a like a
sled what wait I'll send you yeah
toan how is it pronounced uh uh it up I
don't know yeah that might be important
to know how it's pronounce yeah why did
I
ch toog toog
again okay so I sent you the tongue
twister uh let's read it out slowly once
to begin to tobogan First buy a tobogan
but don't buy too big a tobogan too big
a tobogan is too big to to Big A tobogan
to buy to begin to
tobogan okay to begin to tobogan First
buy a tobogan but don't buy too big a
tobogan too big a tobogan is too big
aogan to buy to begin
okay that was just you like doing one
practice right okay yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay and we will let the chat decide who
was the winner of
this
okay okay H you want to go first uh
what's our goal here just saying it
without flubbing or saying it really
fast saying it better than the other but
yeah fast
though and uh maybe one more maybe twice
in a row
are you muting yourself and practicing
Qui no no no I'm I'm not muted I'm just
I'm reading through it in my head and
I'm trying not to say it with my lips
but I I can't help but like kind of like
melt it okay okay okay I'll go
first
okay begin to tobogan First buy a
tobogan but don't buy too big a tobogan
to Big A tobogan is to Big A tobogan to
buy to begin to tobogan to begin to
tobogan
to I can do it twice we to to First buy
of tobogan but don't buy too big of
toban too big of Togan is too big of
Togan to buy to begin to
Togan
buget buget oh that so
good I feel like I can already give up
okay I'll try to no do it you got go
three two one to begin to
put wa wa we try we try yeah yeah start
over I know who
won okay three two 1 to begin
to to begin to to begin to to begin to
toan First buy tobogan but don't buy
toig to toan to Big A to is to Big A to
to buy to begin to the oh to begin to
the first to but don't buy to Big A to
Big A to to to Big the p
p yeah you win I don't think we have to
ask CH y it so good though you too thank
you you are you are my angel thank you
thank you I love you I love you
too yippee thank you for coming
by yes thank you for having me I hope
you have a happy Halloween you too my Yi
hands wish you happy Halloween
[Music]
too have fun bye
bye well yeah I mean English her first
language but she was really good there I
was better the first time I read it for
some
reason should have been
me wait uh okay the next caller there
was one plan who wanted to go early
let's see if she will come um should we
tag her shy do you want to tag
her I I have a really hard time typing
with my yellowy hands like genuinely
there's like so much stuff a lot of tape
also on my yahi hands because um these
$6,000 gloves keep falling apart and I
have to fix it with
tape
yay yeah not too bad though it's working
pretty nicely today okay she is like my
my sexy assistant now she tagged the
next person if she doesn't come in like
one or two minutes then we'll have maybe
my sister come
by okay let's zoom out a little bit more
again to see my glory my beautiful girl
at the end we should go back to ghost
again cuz I really like being a ghost
too catch these yellowy
hands ghost are super cute right
you know um okay come on I can do this
uh if you want you can join me under the
sheets and we can look cute together
that's the purpose just uh looking cute
together in a in a ghost costume if you
can't you know you
know also we didn't talk about me being
a vampire like doesn't that turn you on
come on
[Music]
I broke her yay if only she would have
taken the flirt thingy wherever that is
that that's here there if only she would
have let me flirt with her
[Music]
I'm waiting for my Caller you know what
she already come
in
[Applause]
come I chose you a there she is
she y hands y hands do you want to be
touched by
them uh in an appropriate manner of
course I would only there yoy hands
actually you know what I don't think
it's possible to touch someone
appropriately with yoi
hands well you can like just tip them or
head Pat them I think okay I'll try that
when I see you next time if I still have
my yoi
hands dang you guys are going to know
she hits me
then okay she will she will we you've
been watching so you kind of already
know what's going on here I assume
yes I am to hit treat or trick yeah what
are you interested in I am interested in
tricks of course oh no wait nobody wants
to treat
me I should force everybody to do both
to dinner some other time oh okay uh I
should really Force everybody to do both
though okay yeah you should P the others
if we get the same thing uh as we just
got then we're going to spin again okay
yeah it's fine please don't be push-ups
please don't be
push-ups okay I'm going to I'm going to
spin it won't be visible on the screen
for some reason but I'll be honest I
swear I swear to God okay spin I'll
imagine spe spe oh no oh no oh no oh no
oh
no right now you see it you see it now
oh no no never mind that's just spinning
on its own H it was so close being five
push-ups but then it moved over to
tongue twister so let me go again oh
speed so it should be five push-ups then
h no no no just spinning again
oh oh it went on five
push-ups see I'm on it I'm I'm
honest can you do five
push-ups you want me to what if I just
make grunting noises and pretend I did
five push-ups but for you you can show
that you did five push-ups you actually
have
the ability to show that you did it yeah
but I mean more like in theory would you
be like able to do them oh yes in theory
modified of course modified yeah you
mean with the legs up yeah yeah got to
do it all like I don't think I can not
do it like that but I I don't even know
how this is going to track
honestly we'll see oh well you can
always do wall push-ups that's like the
easier one what wall
push-ups yeah yeah it's just like
push-ups against the wall it's also
better probably for tracking okay not
sure how that works well let's see first
uh okay oh I'm floating oh but yeah okay
the body kind of oh yeah there you go
all right she's showing her full
strength look at that can you
count I I okay I will count
one
two
three four
[Music]
times five more
times [\h__\h] [\h__\h] those were screams of
the
Damned I so difficult oh oh no you did
great you did great than you that you're
going to get abs in no time I wonder how
it did it look like like was it w
capping properly yeah I think so I think
so was it also visible that my first
push-up was still like the lowest and
then it got like less lower less lower
each time I to be honest I was focus on
the scream so I wasn't too sure which
one is the lowest understandable you
need to focus on the screen so you know
when to call the emergency services to
save me from dying again oh yes yes
definitely not making it my ringtone
right now
absolutely sh did you do you like
hearing me suffer
oh well I don't claim to to like
anything I'm just acknowledging that you
have very good
screams h i see maybe I should a
Halloween a Halloween Scream Of course
oh interesting maybe I should become
like a screamo
singer oh yeah like a death metal band
baby yeah yeah but I kind of tried doing
that before for some Koke and like
practicing it oh that hurts it it just I
don't know how i i l I looked up a
tutorial and it was kind of
understandable comprehensible and then I
tried it myself and then it just didn't
work anymore how to like scream prop for
uh for death metal music what if you
just get those giant Rubber Chickens and
each time you have to scream to squeeze
those are you saying my screams sound
like giant rubber chicken screams no
it's just like you can have like a
another singer with you and you won't
have to break your vocal C course oh I
mean that's a good life hack yeah that
will save me from suffering indeed okay
if I ever make a heavy metal song I will
buy that rubber I will buy all the
rubber chickens in the world I I look
forward to it I have like maybe a two
foot chicken right
here you
do well I don't know how big it is it's
it it's like the length of my arm maybe
like not a foot actually is it is it one
of those that we're talking
about yeah yeah yeah yeah it screams for
maybe I think if I counted it it was 39
seconds can you make it go yeah sure let
me seconds really
low I I use it all the time it's going
to scream for a while I just reward you
ready yeah okay I'll do it a distance
away
it's going to be a
while that was totally me oh my God yeah
it's it's going to it's going to be a
while give it give it a few more seconds
this is not the oh that wasn't that long
it was longish that's something you
could use it for a death metal band
that's not a healthy sound for a chicken
to make what are you doing to that
chicken uh um it's been it's seen things
it's seen
things maybe the chicken police should
come up come to pick up your
chicken if they want to scream like that
too they
can okay Shi you are the perfect guest
to give me some spooky Vibes here in
this stream thank you so much for coming
by yeah happy Halloween enjoy your
Halloween you to
byebye she was really prf
she's so nice she's so cute she's so
sweet she will be I get nervous I I got
nervous around her
sorry for no particular
reason okay it seems like the other
guests are in the startler
here so come on well I go to them I'll
go to
them K
ke k y
yay happy
[Applause]
Halloween it's what I wanted to say it
in German but in German it's not really
like we should say happy
Halloween Halloween Halloween
Halloween happy
Halloween
Halloween Halloween
[Music]
y so so
Cecilia what are you dressing up as
today yeah I have I have an outfit
prepared but it's SP so I can't say yet
uh it's it's it's green oh green it's
green and it has dots dott snake M no
kind of snake have that would be that
would be kind of cool actually yeah
snake will be
cool we will find out in the Justice VR
stream right yeah yeah
excited good luck with that are you
nervous we are scar we are scary yeah I
haven't I haven't used VR in a long time
it's like yeah it'll just be shaky cam
the entire time maybe like showing like
the wall I know how VR you know the
makes everything better it makes it
Charming I hope it's the spice of life I
hope so I hope so oh I think I know what
you're doing but I know what your your
what what your costume will be you can
guess I will act uh and lie if it's
right so don't worry I'm just taking it
from the chat because they're genius but
okay now I believe that you will be a
cucumber because if you're a cucumber
you will scare out but the dots on a
cucumber normally cucumbers don't have
dots honestly from my experience unless
you cut it in the middle then you have
like the little seat Pockets you know
that's kind of like dots I'm a cut up
cucumber I'm a sliced
cucumber I mean I've seen I've seen some
cucumbers that are a little bit more
weird looking than others and those you
could say maybe they have dots but
pickles maybe yeah in Cas small
cucumbers yeah we'll we'll we'll we'll
you know keep it for our
future uh enjoyment we'll see we'll see
not think about it anymore okay
Cecilia imma gr forever gr um we have
two wheels one on each side you're going
to trick or treat me but you have to
choose are you going to trick or treat
me okay I want um what did the others
both do treat they both tricked me okay
what I expected okay okay I'll do treat
then I'll do treat here's a little treat
for you a little treat treat coming up a
little open wide yay I'm excited I want
to know what this one will
be okay uh I I kind of mess it up it's
like not showing it when it's spinning
on the screen uh but I will spin it and
don't worry I've been honest so far so
here we go can't believe you I
[Applause]
trust oh oh I like this one I like this
one it became Ms paint me
now
yay Ms paint you okay okay yes you can
either do it like uh off call or on call
however you feel like more confident
okay I'll I'll I'll speed you
onall what's your favorite um what
outfit do you want me to draw you on
maybe this one this one okay okay I'm
aamp she's a
vampire okay okay okay um please pose
for me draw me like one of your French
girls Cecilia
oh
oh oh wa wa buet
buet oh okay okay I'm just gonna I'm
going to try being I can't draw by the
way just see you know please you can yes
you can put down your expectations oh
I'll put my expectations up up oh no
okay the higher the
better in a when you're in a gen with ra
you can't say I can't throw because
she'll be like of course you can you
have to believe in yourself you have to
believe in
yourself we were actually we together do
let your dreams be dreams we had to like
do draw something for our logo right
when we in the Far East and then
everyone was in before me and they all
they all really good at drawing right
like
Gigi and can all draw and then staff was
like wow all of Justice can draw and
then I went to the table and I started
drawing and it was like oh never mind no
no no no no I'm sure what you draw is
cute too I think I've already seen
scribbles of you anyway scribbl okay
okay I wonder what's I I didn't look at
what's under my skirt ah I see okay
sorry just I didn't use I didn't check
the model yet until now you going to up
UPSR us I already did but thank God you
were looking at your painting as you
should I'm struggling I'm struggling K
I'm struggling oh my God come on you can
do it I'll be more uh waa le le is that
that's the leou is like French right oh
Le buff oh the the the guy yeah yeah sh
Leff don't let your scrible dreams be
dreams just do it if it's in in your
head then it's in your hands
just do it came up with that one myself
that if it's in your head then it's in
your hands pretty good very that's
inspiring H you can sing the you know
the cannibal song cannibal song You Know
accident accidental cannibal shy All
Above he's luring in the woods it's shy
above I've never heard that before what
what that you know that song no it's a
song chat back me up yeah it's a song he
like it's it's like it's like I I don't
know who made it it's like this people
made it as like um you know as a joke
but it was got so popular that that
child above even got involved in the
video where he at the end he like stands
up and claps and everything yeah you'll
have to send that to me cuz I don't
understand do you still need me to pose
uh no I took it no I took a you can give
us other poses for the enjoinment of
your chat other POS oh um
cute and um um
um
oo yay that good oh thank you yeah um
um I don't know man I'm uninspired now
okay I'll give you one do like a
um can you try jumping up you know like
the idle woo oh okay okay do you have
any ulterior motives of that one arm in
the no me never with one arm in the sky
okay I'll jump with one arm in the sky
okay three two
one
cute okay yeah I'm a I'm a professional
jumper you know really good so how's the
drawing going almost done almost done
I'm almost done okay um um it doesn't
it's not it's uh you look really pretty
however in my drawing you look a bit
um what do I look
like maybe I should have made you draw
me in my first costume in the ghost
costume maybe maybe that would have been
easier of course that would have been
easier but now no you have to make your
dreams you have to set them high and
then look up to them and then grasp them
and then just do it you know just do it
okay I'm doing it um I can't believe you
you chose to draw this on screen cuz I I
would be too like distracted to draw it
on screen um it's it's okay I have no
abilities so it's nothing will get lost
okay okay do okay when you see it don't
laugh and act act as if it's like really
good okay okay I'm not by the way I'm
not being like false humble this is
actually
not okay okay let me just okay I'm
sending your screen
oh what will it look like I wonder you
have a body by the way did you draw me
like one of your French girls I reallyu
like yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah Cecilia imag I tried okay I told
you I
can't it's cute though it's cute though
it's cute but the I mean I is this like
a a reference to
aongus no it's suppos to be your hair
it's your
hair no it's not among us it's your hair
is this baby version of me cuz it looks
like I'm like wrapped like a baby you
know in like a blanket so cute oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah she's
she's a baby it's her baby outfit and
you even look French cuz it kind of
looks like a French I did like one of my
French girls oh yeah oh yeah thank you
so
much yeah you did it honestly like I
couldn't have done it better in five
minutes so y Phoenix
burito thank you happy Halloween
hallowen hallowen
[Music]
that's a cute
baby a cute
baby that's a cute baby I want a little
like bit maybe like a really tiny like
keychain baby waa
plushy can I be your
baby okay okay okay okay I know uh
yesterday two days ago I said like oh my
God I only have two people signed up
turns out in the end I got four so
here's the fourth person yippee
[Applause]
[Music]
hello you sounded kind of wrong there
for a
moment are you sick no I just woke up
okay did you just wake up did you not
see my yoi hands
yet I I'm watching I'm looking at your
hands also I have vampire teeth do you
like vampires can you zoom in so we can
get a really good look at it I I do like
vampires
look oh my God so
cute oh my
God W oh wait you have a
tongue you know you you know what that
tongue do what the what it do what that
tongue
do well well well happy Halloween gig
happy
Halloween I'm so happy to hear you I'm
happy to see you
[Music]
you're so
cute I can't I'm looking at you I was
when you were flashing everyone
earlier oh when you were posing I was
trying to sneak a
peek stop okay look how cute she is no
look how cute you
are I can't take
it look at this are are you excited for
your big VR
thing I I'm
excited I don't know I feel like when I
get a VR I get motion sick do you get
motion siek h it depends I got to be
careful it happens sometimes but I like
immediately when I notice like oh oh
that was weird then I just like try to
like stay in one spot still yeah it's
easy to happen but you can do it
gigy any spoiler what what your cosplay
could be uh your CR your costume ooh
spoilers it's going to be
spooky can we get a color a color orange
orange y okay yay well I would think
that you girls are trying to at least um
go for costumes that haven't been done
by myth in their like famous like Myer
treat music video so so I would say your
orange cannot be a pumpkin cannot be a
pum
unless no no it's not a pumpkin
unless keeps on coming back with the
unless oh no no her orange perms were
reinstated really like quickly within
the collab so she's allowed to be orange
yeah cuz I I double crossed um the blue
ones you
know I do is your costume Tak from Life
English myth oh my God what I wish
should I ask them that actually be like
such a cute little like thing it would
be so cute if all of you like cosplay
like other
Senai yeah that be kind of
cute want to see
it okay although I think like maybe
maybe you would look better in someone
else's clothes mine no I want to be in
your clothes really are you know
I love your mini skirt a skirt it's a
belt at that
point it's beautiful I get to see all of
your leg I don't know I I don't have the
thick thighs like you though e they're
not that fake they're kind of everyone
stream
Mirage you are such a supporter G which
is why surely you will choose the treat
wheel
no I
pick you know what cuz you're the last
one I'll make you choose both both oh
I'll pick both yeah I want both what a
deal yay okay y cuz I I prepared so many
things here that's obviously not enough
for just four people so yeah it's time
for Trick and Treat hell yeah let's get
the most out of it which one do you want
to start with I want to start I think
you need to start with a treat and then
you end with a trick okay sounds good
and it won't look look like it's
spinning but it's spinning on my side
don't worry and I'll be honest three two
one ah okay I'll spin again cuz it went
on Ms Paint Me Now although I would love
a doodle from you cuz your Doodles are
so cute but I'll spin again oh I while
CeCe was doodling you you can have the
one that I did while she was doodling
you too he also
doodled yeah what I didn't even ask you
to and you still doodled me you sweetie
patootie I was watching the stream okay
but the actual thing that came out uh is
quite a delightful
one oh cute wait cute let me show the
the
doodle wait yeah Windows uh the
D where is it are you still there gigy
I'm still here I'm
here image it saved as image.png here we
go that's so
accurate you are posing so
cute no stop we going
[Music]
to okay so the real thing that came out
of it thank you for the D by the way is
plan a collab for us and then it will
have to like actually happen I know
we've been kind talking about a lot of
colls so you'd have to come up with
something new something new okay I'll
think of something I'll invite you to my
home it's going to be awesome we can Yap
together we can play games you okay I'm
thinking I'll plan something okay okay
yeah it doesn't have to be right away uh
um I would like an answer
within this
week okay
okay and it has to be something that is
like doable in the near future so don't
do an off
collab unless you're going to come over
you think that's possible in the near
future I mean only if you come over to
Austria packing my
bag I wish I want to come over I want to
see the kitty cat yeah you should okay
next we have the trick and there's
actually two things on the trick wheel
that I haven't done yet
so we're kind of aiming for that okay
okay I'm hoping I hope you have to do
five push-ups no I already did that oh
I'm spinning what
again uh it landed on five push-ups but
I'm not doing that again no no no one
more time sp sp flirt flirt flirt FL H
it landed on the tank to my stone which
I also already did FL maybe I should
just do
everything you should do all four no
well yeah oh nice it's five push-ups
again come on come on I should just get
rid of 10 push-ups h no you're not don't
add on to it that's not the rules I make
the rules
oh
gy oh what's going on
it
it it landed
it yeah
it it landed on flirt yeah
yeah I'm blushing are you looking at the
screen I'm I'm
looking cabon you
shyly looking away I'm too too shy to
look at your
eyes you your your orange is an orange
I've never seen
before it's so
beautiful I want to share our oranges we
should
kiss and we should mix our oranges
together
[Music]
but um
wait um don't be shy come here my
beautiful princess I want to my orange
and your orange and we combine them into
one orange and then ooh let's just mix
our orange colors yes yes wait wait Ki
po uh it should be like
this cuz you're so small
oh okay let me kiss
you I'm I'm reaching up on my Ticky toes
you want up do you want uppies up up up
please yay
[Music]
up that was not as romantic as I thought
it would
be I kind of was more confident like
before the stream when I was thinking
about flirting with someone I was I felt
like oh
easy I will seduce got so sexy though
really you're so beautiful I am
seduced you're easy to seduce it's not a
challenge to seduce you is
it I just you're basically I say no to a
beautiful lady you're the husband of
like every whole lifean girl basically
already no yes no we are just I there
just so many beautiful
ladies well it's nice that like someone
takes
responsibility don't worry princesses I
will um be I work for us you have to
stay home you don't have to lift a
single
finger my fingers will not be lifted
except when I give you appies yeah my
hands look like this so your hands can
look like that wait am I supposed to
imagine something um um let me see if I
can find a a photo a meme photo my my
hands yeah it it was on Twitter a while
ago and it was just this like [\h__\h] post
of someone with really you know muscular
dirty hands and um like my hands look
like this overworked and then your hands
look like like this oh I found one oh
there's not even such a strong contrast
between those
two you're eating chicken nuggets I am
working okay what if I find like you
should be feeding me the chicken nuggets
no why am I lifting a finger still
ohing that is ridiculous it's okay okay
to describe the image the one that is
like working hard so to say is U taking
apart like a man Manda Tangerine Mand
Tangerine yeah yeah in German it's
Mandarin I think it's both say both yeah
I've SE I heard it both and the other
one is what the [\h__\h] are those
stickers is it oh the the nail um glue
lines I don't know nail stickers wait no
wait those are not stickers those are
those wait those are the stickers from
the from the
T those are on the
nails it looks like nails it's yeah it's
just random stickers from the fruit
that's funny okay good one good one you
have entertained me even though you
didn't have
to yay thank you gy uh we actually have
a collab this week we're finally playing
an mm RPG an anime mm RPG of our
dreams yippe yeah have you played that
one before I forgot I played it before
super long time ago did you get really
far or um I got to max level when I
played it releas which was like 50 or 60
at the time I didn't play much
afterwards hey let's go I didn't know
you get you got so far we're going to
grind
together I'm excited I used to know life
so many games I had no Hobbies except
ging yeah same same it was my everything
and then the gaming industry took it
away from me because they decided they
don't want to do any more free toplay
animeo
anime gaming industry is like let's not
make MMOs anymore let's make phone games
yeah [\h__\h] that why there was totally no
one who enjoyed that genre besides that
stupid Phoenix and that stupid orange
sister M no bring the MOs back bring
them back we'll revive it together
together we will our Palace shall be
United yes do you want to do a here bro
fist oh okay I'm fisting my screen right
now I'm I'm touching my scre your fists
are so dangerous you have to be more
careful with your fists oh sorry I I
take off my glove my power glove and I
fist you gently with my normal fist get
out of here get out of here
okay byebye I love you
byebye I love
you sorry sorry sorry I got like a
little bit too excited sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry I need to calm
down I don't know what's wrong with me
what's wrong with me she's just such a
cute cool high
okay what was I doing uh why is it doing
that
ah okay that was all my Callins but I'm
still going to do a few
more K songs dances singing blah blah
blah so thank you for all the callers
for joining I still I'm okay here is the
the furnace dance I practiced it a
little bit though
um a little bit more here
smaller okay it was something like uh
okay you know it go like furnace furnace
furnace furnace furnace furnace
furnace uh furnace furnace furnace
furnace furnace furnace furnace furnace
furnace and
then what was it then I forgot but
that's like the most
important something like that right
totally furnace it's furnace p h o e r n
i c
e I wish I could do like the full dce
for YouTube
shirt and then there was like something
like this I don't know and then there
was like the Gangam Style refence but
she dances kind of
differently there you
go there you
go can you do a green screen you know
what uh I can maybe can
I
um can
ah
H I don't know right now maybe
not uh unless I don't know if I can find
a green screen
background cuz I don't know how to set
it here in the
app ah let me Google green
[Applause]
screen wait yeah why
not
uh that would be
funny let put up a green screen in my
office really
quickly let's make it
bigger that works that looks
realistic okay uh wait I'm kind
of there okay what was it here furnace
furnace furnace furnace furnace furnace
furnace furnace f furnace furnace
furnace
furnace let me look up that other move
that came right after I
forgot you guys can put it
together
dance I can't type with these
gloves Mama
Mia okay uh wait
it's so
silly okay uhuh ah that one
right
perfect and
then and then what was what was the end
of that some
kicks
uh wait what how is she doing that H
H I don't know feel free to combine
that
yay and this one one more
time how did the Gangam sty move is so
difficult there you
go yeah okay get on it now we shall have
some more
fun with
performances
okay let me drink some water though
haven't drunken water since before the
stream
oh let me put away the the green screen
Z wonderful well that was fun and now
I'm going to sing um three more songs
for you just small small little bit of a
uh CL Orest just a small one cuz there's
not that many that I can archive
[Music]
anyway
okay
okay so in the beginning of the stream
in case you missed it I did
uh what did I do
vampire and now we're going to
do this
one I
think
okay one
second okay
okay here we
go myth a
[Music]
treat yeah she's waiting in the closet
tonight no way to stop she's dead said
I'm giving you a BRI trick or treat but
now we're all out of candy feeling just
a little stick this chaina all to come
and Andy I got a f chat possessed so
let's experiment about a little
dissection is best Drop It Low babies
hiding behind your screens it ain't a
spooky Halloween we about some mythical
beans chat is
blessing look at those red
jeeks how
cute I'll fix that up drain all your
that's what you
see or treat oh what a curs ified stream
there's no bones about it you'll scream
only show you on Halloween our spook
terrifi scarier s oh the got
toite Mythic witches with an Spight C
Escape or idoles might no Cy inside so
your souls will
suffice bust a funky dance tonight what
a spooky scary side hungry dinosaur just
one tiny bite please spook of viewers
with a song if you break and sing along
not your wife I am a pumpkin ding dong
in the graveyard we will be if you're
looking for a scream singing songs that
make you P RC y give your Shivers make
you sh just like that now my out spooky
ladies B what we are
[Music]
about y yay that was me for
treat I don't remember any of the cor
besides that
part
y such a banger right even after all
these years it's still such a
banger M
or yeah it's so nostalgic too has a
corer well not like completely not the
whole song but a little bit Yeah will
always be
special that was wasn't that our first
group song so funny that that was our
first group song but I think it like
then motivated us to do more because you
guys received it so well cuz like it was
just like a little quick fun joke
project thingy but then it became so
high quality and you guys liked it so
much
so you know then we were like ah maybe
we should do more songs with
my yeah after Country Road oh yeah I
think yeah that also felt like we were
like oh country Ro and maybe we should
do something like
better yeah I remember we were all like
yeah let's do something
something good stuff good stuff but even
now now when I like not even now but
when I think back now I can even think
fondly
of that part I don't I don't dislike the
song okay just clarifying again some
people are like
misunderstanding um but
yeah oh Reverb so oopsie well I still
need it anyway and let's do the next
song I don't think I did I sing this
before did I sing this before in K I'm
not sure but is it really cute song from
my Japanese SAS it's a whole life song
as well which was Halloween
themed so let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
fore fore
[Music]
night
for
night crazy night
[Music]
for
hallowe for
[Music]
crazy
[Applause]
[Music]
night yay y did you know it before I
guess it's in Holo here so a lot of
people know it
right thank you thank
you yeah I I I don't really know the
Coro if even if I don't even know if it
has a Coro but I
just came up with something on my own
such a banger
right oh yeah I had one did an English
version they did but I know the Japanese
version better so I Sanga Japanese
version
suori should we do DOA here for for your
picture usage uh uses Sing My lyrics
next okay maybe not right now maybe next
year for Halloween okay
promise okay here's a
DOA oh I'm floating should we bring out
the green screen
again
I okay
I think you kind of like go really down
right I don't
know
the yeah there there's the thing is the
map um mine is like I explained this
before but mine's like kind of Wi-Fi
based so when I do stuff like that it
will like not know where the floor is
and where I
am yeah the stuff that am has is like
not the same that one's like you know R
real cameras I don't have cameras around
me she has cameras around her so in her
case it would know and it would like
like she wouldn't be floating around
that's the difference between our
Moab yeah okay I
have one more
song I was thinking like man there's
like a couple of songs that I want to do
but like I can't find like instrumentals
that we are allowed to use like for
example killing vampire girl from idle
master and stuff like that
so didn't find anything else that was
really Halloweeny and could be archived
but
well here we go
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n I'm alive still breathing Stu to hide
done grieving realized that to survive
someone's got to stand and fight and
I've tried to believe in only time stop
the bleeding I'm not waiting anymore I
know what I came here
for cuz feelings
Temple but broken hearts keep the SK for
Life the darkness no longer scares me
I'm chasing and hunting and this time
I'm coming for
blood be the last one to laugh when you
run out of catching
up I'm a FR and a half baby you don't
even know me at
all I'm alive still kicking Break The
Rules rewrite the system and my story
wasn't done sharp a KN and cut the guns
cut the cord burn the witch and you'll
regret what you're missing and I'll take
it to the Grave that's the price that
you pay it cuz feelings are
temporary but broken hearts keep the
for the darkness no longer scares me I'm
chasing and hunting and it's time I'm
coming
[Music]
for be the last one to laugh when you
run out of catching
up I'm a fresh and a half baby you don't
even know me at
[Music]
all n
oh
[Music]
yeah feelings are
temporary but broken he keep the
for the darkness no longer scares me I'm
chasing and hunting and this time I'm
coming
for be the last one to laugh when you
run out of bre catching
up I'm a FR and a half baby you don't
even know me
[Music]
at you don't even know me at
all n
n n n n n
[Music]
finally we hurt it
again
oops
Yi finally for
blood I love this song so much it's so
fun your favorite cover mine too I think
maybe but mean cover it's my original
song right is it not but you know what I
forgot I I mean maybe it wouldn't have
been so suitable for this song or like
any of them although it would have been
funny
but where is
it I I didn't switch back into ghost
anymore no
I'm a happy
ghost
oopsie my glove receiver stay
put I'm
go W you must be so scared of me did I
shock
you sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm so sorry turn on the ey
oh oh maybe the eyebrows are supposed
[Music]
to that's what they're
for now I understand
a that's so
[Music]
funny that's so
adorable
oops sorry I was a bit
loud was
it maybe
not
boo I will be in your nightmares
[Laughter]
[Music]
you it was you you killed
me you are the reason that I am like
this so I will haunt
youo
[Music]
wo in your dreams I will Haunt You by
twerking as a ghost
[Music]
almost broke my
neck it's difficult to twerk as a
ghost no don't suck me in no not the V
no there's only one ghost out there who
deserves to be vacuumed
[Laughter]
made
okay I love you guys
[Music]
there we
go
[Music]
C okay okay okay I'm I'm really sweaty
spaghetti and this was really just
supposed to be a little funny small
spontaneous
stream and thank you for tuning in I
hope you enjoyed it thank you for
celebrating
Valentine's Halloween with
me and thank you seon for really like
last minute uh fulfilling my ideas
my very selfish ideas and throwing a
blanket on me and giving me all this
[Music]
power I love this
form maybe I'll just stream like this
every
day I love this waa boo
I shall be known
henceforth as
B Invader of your
nightmares yay okay so yeah I'm sweaty
I'm going to go take a shower and take
this sheet off it's so hot this is a
winter
blanket I'll see you tomorrow for I
think Diablo 4
all
right I'm kind of exhausted I've been
planning to stream all day I'm going to
take a break now
aome and in German we say a
Bo I'll
[Music]
be
boo boo
oh my merchandise sales are ending in a
couple of days link is in the
description also keep on stream
streaming Mirage we're so close to a
million go stream Mirage otherwise I
will haunt you even
more maybe I'll upload a short today I
feel like one of is
ready let's see one no two how long did
I stream 1 hour and okay the the gloves
were powered on for perhaps an hour 40
or 50 oh and they used up half the
battery this time nice not too bad
could be better should be better but oh
well