[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] Sorry to have kept you
waiting, you can hear me. Kaoisho,
wait a minute. Let me
show you a glimpse of BGMBGM in action. I'm out over there
today.  It's a collaboration.
Today, we're going to study German,
so a
first-time
German teacher will be on Channel 7. He's
cute. He's so cute even when he doesn't make noises. He's
moving in a cute way, but it's a little weird.  Let me have you
come right away. Please wait a moment. Please
wait a moment. Change the background music to this.
Okay, then please come out.
Please introduce yourself. Takanashi, I'm
Kiyohara-sensei. Lie. I'm your teacher today. Hololive
English 1.  This
is an unnecessary Takanashi character from the class, but
even though he speaks English, his native language is
German and he lives in Austria.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you very much. I would
like to learn German from you.
Even though my native language is Japanese,
Thank you for saying it all the time.However,
the truth is that I have fewer and fewer opportunities to speak Japanese, and since I
have been to other parts of Japan as well,
since I returned to Austria, I haven't had many chances to speak Japanese, and I
feel like I haven't spoken for a while.  That's what I mean, and I tend to
forget the words, but
thank you very much. It
seems like Chiara's volume is a little loud. There
are some comments in English.
Thank you.
OverseasDiary th
How do you like it?
[Music]
When I'm streaming, I'm basically
overseas.  I have quite a few diaries, and the number of people I visit
overseas has increased.I
sometimes speak a little English, and I was
also learning Spanish, so if I
spoke just a little bit of Spanish, people
would come to visit me and go to Spain.  I want to hear you speak English
a little bit from time to time
Please introduce yourself If you
come suddenly I can understand your
English even though it's bad English Yes
Hello Konkagura Good day
Yes firstMyselfto
English
I'M7
IcametoasFROMTHE
PLANETChiliPepper
youwalk
I's Illustrator Artist
for
dese Naki Ni Ayame Hololive  When I
listen to the English self-introductions of other Japanese people, it
seems like they've memorized about three lines, but the teachers
seem to be able to dodge things, and I feel like I
can kind of understand what they're saying.
So why can I do it? Well, I went to university to study English, the
English department, and the
foreign language department.But I've
never spoken German before, so I
got excited today.
[Laughs] I'm
not as good as the English members,
but Hololive.  It's much better than the Japanese members of the group.It's
amazing.It's seriously amazing.Whenever a foreigner speaks a little bit of Japanese to a Japanese person, they always say, ``I'm good at Japanese,'' which has become a meme.
Teru: You're so good at Japanese, you
're so good at communicating with other people,
but that teacher says you're
really good at English, no, it's true, but Kiara
-chan, you're so good at Japanese, you look like you're so good at it.  I'm
really
happy that I can speak German well.I'm going to
study a little bit today so that I can speak German well.It's
difficult for just one hour, but I've taken screenshots of what I'm going to teach you today and
look back at it several times.  I wonder if I'll be
able to memorize it. I'll
keep an archive of my efforts. Let's look back at it,
study, and do our
best. Thank you very much. Thank you very much. What are you going to
study German for today
? Well, that's not this, it's this.
Thank you first.  Can you explain it in Japanese?
I'll be there next week or whatever in 2023. That's
great. It's going to be a three-day event, so I'll be there for about two and a half days. Wait, wait, wait, maybe for three days.
Yes, it's probably going to be three days from this year.  Yeah, it's been 3 days, it's
always been 2 days, 6 people
is
FREEDtoday
ISS is a
really big event and popular. It's really popular,
but it actually started.
I always, always, always, always, always
say I want it to be at least 3 days.
However, I always
thought that 2 days was too short, but this year, I
was able to get my wish, but it won't be this year.Next
time,
the information that I didn't know
will actually come out all the way here,
Stellacia!  The name of the circle is
Comic
Market 101. I'm
thinking of bringing the full-color 60-page illustrated book that was released at Comiket last winter, as well as some new Kagura goods.So, to be
honest, I'll be honest about this: Kaigan Diary.  I
'm in the chat, but most of the people probably
can't speak German. I
'd like to explain this to you in English, too.
Please.
Heisactorygoingto
japany
andto
your
andre.
Actually, I've
seen Tiara for the second year in a row. Where did you see it?  Well,
since I was on the show,
all of my fans were thinking, ``Well, I guess I'll
be there again this year.'' Thanks to that, there are quite a few people who say, ``Of course we'll go this year as well.''
So even though I'm not there,
there's a good chance that some of my fans will come too.But,
I haven't had the chance to meet them overseas either,
so I
think I'd be happy if I could meet them this time.  I
'm also a mother, so
this machine
returns the ghost, so I can meet the person in question.As an
illustrator,
I also want to meet the person in Japan.When I
come to Japan,
let's meet in Japan someday.
[Music]
By all means OK, well, I changed this to German,
but I think it's
okay to change the German language in a tweet before saying "Where is Germany?" Yes,
please send it after the pack. OK, okay, I made a mistake.
Well, first of all,
rather than words, I
think it would be better to give you a little bit of information. I
know that Düsseldorf
is the city with the most Japanese people in Europe,
right?
No, this is seriously
interesting.  Well, that digital tofu
is one of the biggest in Germany,
and among them there are 5,000 Japanese people.According
to Wikipedia,
there are about 5,000 Japanese people, and I do
n't know if the number is increasing.  This has a lot of history, and
it's like a history class, and it
should be true, but there was a
company from Japan that
had already set up a company in Germany, so
Japanese
people were sent to work in Germany.  Well,
even though it's been a while, those people
seem to have really liked the dresses from Germany,
so
what do you mean by going abroad for work?
Even after the business trip is over, there's
still some lingering feeling.  There were a lot of people there,
so I decided to stay and start a family there.
As a result, there are about 5,000 people now. They're
cute.
[Laughs] They're
probably happy because they're wearing uniforms. They're students.
So I guess I want to leave Japan and live there.  It's a
really nice city, isn't it?
Seriously, if you feel like living in Germany or even Europe, I'd say it's
better to say that because you can experience overseas, but I don't want to eat Japanese food or
talk to Japanese people. I
feel a little lonely.  If you
go to a Japanese restaurant with tofu or something, you can
meet Japanese people and eat Japanese food.I
wonder if there is something like Eo Sushi.I think there is also sushi, but somehow this
leads to the next thing.  But it's set right now,
and it's a
place where everyone gathers after this poisonous event,
and for some reason, there
's a mountain of Japanese restaurants lined up along a straight road.
[Music]
Ramen, tonkatsu,
sushi, yakiniku, everything,
Izakaya, Japanese
Izakaya, I wonder if they have sake?
Yes, yes, yes, it's amazing, so I guess
it's a bit crowded even when I'm not looking at that place.  It's
really crowded at that time, and
everyone goes there.There are a lot of
Japanese people working there.I'd
like to go there, but the people who go there are
cosplayers who have been to the event or something.  It's a
Japanese-themed event, so
everyone goes there thinking, ``Let's eat some Japanese food.'' I
see, I heard good things about it.
But it's my
first time abroad, so it's the
other way around.  It's better to go there. I want to
eat something like German Shock. I want to eat it. It's
really crowded and I have to wait in line for a long time. I do
n't
like standing in line at any store, so I decided not to do it. Well, I'd
better take a look.  I
think it would be amazing to just walk around, so it's
nice to see it, but when it comes
to where to eat, I think I'd rather go to a
regular restaurant in Germany.
[Music]
But
European
sushi is better than Japan.
I heard that it's different from the sushi in Japan, but I don't eat it.It
's fresher in Japan.
[Music] I
like that it's fresh.Well,
uh, if you
have time to go sightseeing, you'll
have a little bit of time.So,
uh, garbage.  I
'll ask the staff if they can accompany me. Maybe they can show me around here. I heard that the
media's
Halfnixley is
famous. I've already decided to go there,
so we
talked about whether we should see Cologne or something.
Yeah, I'm going to go shopping, yeah, I'm going to go buy a dress, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's close by train, but I'm going to see Dusseldorf, I'm going to Cologne, and some other places are more beautiful.I think I'll probably go to a lot of things.It's definitely close. [Music]  ] I've
never been there, but
everyone knows that it's beautiful. I
heard that climbing the cathedral is very difficult. It's really high. It's so
high, so high, so big. I'm looking forward to it.
Maybe the museum has already been decided.  I
probably won't go there, but
there's a museum about that ship.I
think I probably have some free time, so if it's
nearby, I'd like to go there.I
see, ok, this is just a little bit of
information, uh, I'm not a teacher today, but my
teacher's
Nana.  Chanara-chan, this
is a question I asked you earlier, but
before the broadcast, uh,
you
have to be careful with your bags and stuff. Well, well, well, well,
well, well, my
experience is that you have to
be very careful in Berlin, the capital of Germany.
I've never had anything like that before in Thrufu,
so I didn't pay much attention to it, but
Seldorfer says it's pretty safe.I
think it's pretty safe, but tourists should just
watch Nana-chan.  I know you're a tourist,
so you
might be treated a little differently. Is
there anyone who approaches this person thinking they can easily steal it?
Hey, it's
better to hold your bag tightly. Well,
as long as you're careful.  I do
n't think anything bad will happen to me.It
's my first time in Germany, but it's also my
first time going abroad, so I
was a little scared.Well, I guess I'll be the
only one flying.
No, I
have a friend who is an illustrator, so I
'm a little relieved.
[Music]
By the way,
Premium Economy or
Economy or Economy is
poor.
[Music]
Well, if you cry once, I
guess it's still good. Actually, Premium Economy.  I was thinking of doing it,
but it turned out that I probably wouldn't be able to get a seat next to
three of my illustrator friends, so they'd be
spread out all over the place, so I felt like I was going to go economy.  I
think I've
been back and forth to Japan probably about 40 times,
but I've
flown over the same distance over and over again,
but I'm seriously dying.My
butt and legs make me want to have a butt.  It's
really hard. It's
about 12 hours, right? Well, it's like when you get that chocolate. I
was expecting that, right? Now,
take the cushion. I'll
check it with my hands, but I have no choice but to sleep. I have no choice
but to sleep. I'm the only one who sleeps. Maybe I'm the only one who sleeps.  My
body hurts and it's hard to sleep,
and I can't put my feet anywhere because it's so small.I'm
not good at sleeping while sitting, but
Japanese people are probably good at sleeping in small spaces.I see, so
is Marshmallow.  I've received a few of them,
but there was one that was a bit related, so if you have any
customs that Japanese people should be careful about when they go to Germany,
please let me know.  I
think there are certain things that you shouldn't do, such as poses and behavior, but I think there's nothing
that you should
n't do that you think the Japanese would do.They're too
polite, and on the contrary, Germans came to Japan.  I
think there are some things you
shouldn't do if Japanese people come to Germany,
but when I
talked to a friend who had been to Germany in the past, I
thought there were things I shouldn't do.
I often
kindly point my finger at people,
but on the other hand, I heard that we shouldn't do this in Japan as well,
so
[Music] I do
n't really need to worry about that,
but yeah, you shouldn't do it.  I
don't think so, but they
tip in Germany too, although not as much as in America.I didn't
think about tipping at all because they don't do it in Japan.I don't think it's possible to tip, but I don't think you have to think about it too much.For
example, when you eat at a restaurant,
you...
So, let's say 18 euros costs about 2,000 yen.If it were me, I
would probably pay 20 euros by adding that amount to the nearest 0.If that's the case, then I would add that amount to the nearest 0 and pay 20 euros.  If you
think it's okay to get something close to
that amount, then you
don't have to give it
to the cashier when you make a purchase.Where do you go?When you shop at a supermarket or something, you
don't need to tip the cashier.  Well, you do
n't need to tip at those supermarkets or clothing stores, but
at restaurants, you
should give a little more, but to be honest,
there are a lot of people who don't open their doors, so I do
n't particularly care about tourists.  I don't think so.If I
don't give it, I can't decide.It's
not as good as in America.People don't rely
on tips that much.If you get one, you're lucky.Oh,
and
if you go to a fancy restaurant, it's more luxurious
than a restaurant that's a little bit cheaper.  It's
better to tip at restaurants,
but it's a
cheap illustration so don't worry about it.Ah, if you
use a towel in a comment section hotel, you have to
leave it on the ground or they
won't replace it.That's
right, there are quite a few hotels like that, so
why?  Actually, I feel like it's
a bit of a waste to have those towels taken away even though I'm still going to use them,
because it
costs a lot of money.Also, they
're not as kind to that world as they are to other people, so
that kind of thing happens quite a lot.It happens a lot at hotels.
I didn't know that. I
usually have cards with explanations like that displayed in my room,
but they're not in German. No, they're
English. They should have changed both German and English. I'm
glad I read them properly. I'm
alone in the room, so I'm a little
me.  Once upon a time, I worked at a hotel,
and
whenever Japanese guests came over, I was
quite
surprisedand
sad.The
Japanese people were
surprised that the rooms
had no bathtubs, only showers.  There are so many
rooms and there are very few rooms with bathtubs, so
7-chan's room may not have a bathtub in a little while,
so it's okay. I see. Is bathing a part of Japanese culture? Come to
think of it, I guess it's okay.
There was a bust area.  That's
better. You're asking too much. I'm sure I'll be there. The bathtub. Seriously, okay.
When you check in, if you
ask if there's a room with a bathtub, they
might be able to adjust it for you.  I
understand that there is a possibility that it won't happen, so I'm going to be
prepared. I haven't taught you any words yet because you're too talkative,
but I think I should start teaching you now. Well, for now,
I've increased this a little bit from here. It's our
first time together.
It's better to teach this first.  As
for pronunciation, just
like in English, we use the Roman alphabet,
but in German, there are
some extra special characters that
look like emoticons and are cute.Even if you change the phonetic characters, it
doesn't really get the message across.  You should listen to this and memorize
it.
Remember it with your ears. The dots on the first ah are
not eh, they're
nice nice nice nice nice nice.
Well, I guess it's
a little closer to the picture of the English word.
[Music]
What's the point?
By the way, sometimes Um is
written like this.
Because of the keyboard, I can't write this character, so if I can't write it, I'll write ``Is it me?'' That's how I get the message across,
but
next time I'll write ``Uh'' instead of ``U''.
This is difficult,
it's difficult, but the reason why it's so important is that
Austria, the country where I live next door, always starts with these letters.So,
instead of [music] nice nice nice and then
[music]
[applause]
[  [Music] I'm
still close to the sea. My
mouth is quite narrow,
so I make this sound in the shape of a woo.
I hold my mouth
in the shape of a whistle and try to say hmmm. It's
difficult, isn't it? It's that
good-bye in German.  This is used as a greeting,
so the
next one looks like a B, but it's the
letter vision, and
it's pronounced with a strong S.
It's normally SS, so for example,
what
kind of words does it say?  This is
nonsense. Now it's the swastika. It
often appears in the names of towns. It
seems like I said it earlier.
But
when I don't use the keyboard, I can use WS at all.
[Music]
Well, I think this one is
also easy to use.
German.  If you were to talk to that person,
you
'd say, ``How about you,'' and you'd say, ``
C, how about you,'' and C would sound like
you're extremely polite, like ``you.'' That's how you say it.
But, uh, I'm basically.  Generally speaking, I use C to refer to people I don't know,
but for example, people who are younger than me or who look younger than me.It
also depends on the atmosphere, but for example,
at an event, when someone comes to Nana-chan's booth, I use C to respond
to those people.  Honestly, I
think it's okay to say do.Hmm, I see.Yes,
but it's not that much.And
if it's hard to memorize and separate them, you
can use C for all of them.You're
CE.In
Japanese, you say san after your name.
Make sure you put it on properly
Part 3
is the room in German. It's
like that female and Mr.  I
don't think tourists, in particular, need to worry too much about it, but just in case there's this, it's
in front of the name.I
only put it on the first name,
Takanashi, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm
talking about hair, I'm
talking about hair, it's okay, it's okay, it's not at
all.  I'm not talking about mold.
[Laughs]
She's sensitive.
For example,
there's a chance that Nana-chan might be called Maybe-Maybe-Ka-Gura. Hmmm
OK.
This was just basic information, but here's where I get
serious.
Can I use it? I've
seen it before.  I'm sure you already know the words. I
'll start from the top. Well, I've heard it before, so I
think it's that simple. Hello.
[Music]
Gutentag Gutendark
Good morning,
Hagen. Punctuation Morgen. No, nice. Good evening,
Gutenament.
Perfect. Good night,
Gutenaftonat.  That's not it, Naft.
Like a cat.
Cat.
Please get angry.
[Laughs] I
can't hear you. I'm listening to
Discord on Discord, but I
can't hear it. I
can't hear it. I wonder if it's
working.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you very much.
Danke Shuin Dance.
That letter appears here as well.
[Music]
If you want to say just a short thank you, you
can say danke, but that's fine. It's
better to be short.
[Music]
I'm sorry.
This is also difficult, so my suggestion is that it
makes perfect sense, so it's normal.  Sorry
Siri,
anyone can understand it
in English, but it's German now.If you
have any trouble, you can use English at all.Please tell me if you can understand or
have any problem.
So it's
a little different from Japan, hmm, that's true.
[Music] Well,
finally 99.
[Music] The
pronunciation of J in German is
like wine.
[Music]
That's right. If you
read this 9 like in Japanese, it would
be ``none.''  I don't know what to say,
but
in reality, it doesn't exist, but
if I pretend to read it, it
probably doesn't exist, so I want to read it.When you
say ``main'', ``that's okay,'' and ``love'' together in German, it
becomes ``yes, yes, yes, love.''  Yo,
if you hadn't told me that, I would have definitely called you Main
.
[Music]
Plus eye is also
good when you see it the other way around.
Pluseye,
plus good. This is an English pronunciation, but when you put 2 and A
together, it's normal.  I do
n't know if it's a word I'm teaching, but I don't know if it's going to be used somewhere, but I hope you see this,
and the one above.  When I saw it, I knew it. It
definitely appears in beer.
Beer is
not BEER. No,
no.
BL in English is
We, and beer in German is
ie, but I'll never know how to pronounce it
.
[Music]
German is BR.
That's right.
Juice
More  It's also difficult, but this is
also the greeting at the end of Chiara's broadcast, so
I decided to make it chess because I thought it would be difficult.  It
feels more like
goodbye, that's amazing.If I were to be polite, I'd say Anphirasen.It's
a bit of a white joke,
but
yeah, I think you can feel free to say it to anyone.So, let's
see what happens next.
When you say goodbye to someone who came to an event, I
guess you should give them some juice.
[Music]
If you want to make them cute, I
recommend
lighting them on fire.
[Music]
Teacher
Don't cry,
cute.  I'm so happy that there are so many useful words.Oh,
that's right, I just wrote it in the chat,
but this is me, uh, the word I'm writing here is a
word that Nana-chan asked me to use,
but I'm sure there's one word that isn't here.  The
words ``Issei'' (Issei) are
used together in German.
Please. Issei is
living in the same house.
For example,
[Music]
Accounting please.
Well, I don't think I can remember this one.  But
[Music] I'd
like to pay the bill, please. That's
what I say when I'm buying something.
In
Japan, you often go to the counter and pay before you make a mistake. In
Germany, it's
straight forward.  There were a lot of people at the table
holding the press conference, but
Mr. Waits didn't come very often.I
thought he wasn't coming, but I
waited for Mr. Hotta and his eyes to turn green, and then he
raised his hand a little,
and I said, 3 people came.  Yes, I'll give it to you.But,
umm, if you're an
employee and you're a little
embarrassed and can't say it, just look me in the eye
and
raise your hand.  I
'm sorry, it's the same cooking army. I
think I'll draw this one too.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
Japanese. I'm sorry, Japanese keyboard. I'm sorry. Oh yeah, yeah.
Well,
there are so many people who admire Japan so much, and
everyone really admires it, so
Naa-chan
is truly a divine presence for those people.He is truly a god, and he
will do anything to make Germany become Germany.
Everything is forgiven,
and if you speak only in Japanese, you'll be treated that way.I want you to
bring me something spicy.I'm not sure if you'll suddenly bring me food, but it's
fun.It
's Kagura-gami, it's God, right?  I
'm a god painter, so I
think people will relate to it more. What do I
say, God? In German, I say God
as it is. Hmm, it's similar to English,
but it's stronger in WT, so
I say God good.  I am, I am, I
'm here. There's also a
Poi here, so let's move on.
This is my name that can be used for anything. What the hell
is that? Hmm. Kirara-
chan, now that I think about it, it's just like this
marshmallow.
[Music] I
was just here saying that I can use the words in the same way as in English.
What do you think?
This marshmallow
knows about the future. It's amazing. I just happened to
find it and thought it was amazing. It was
like, ``Well, um, uh, um.''  MyNavi SMyname
is
similar, isn't it? Either one
is fine. If you want to introduce your name, either one is fine.
But for example, if you say, "I am God," then
[Music] If you want to
remember it,
use it.
Hey.  Or, I'll
erase English and
start teaching you some simple words.
Delicious
means "rekker", but the meanings are the exact opposite, so it's quite
common.
In German, it's the same with Rekker,
but there is an ER at the end of the word.
At times, I
think people who pronounce things very clearly are able to pronounce them properly, but
when they're talking normally, they tend to
deteriorate,
and when they bite, it's like a tow truck.But
people who speak normally do that.  It seems
like everyone's pronunciation is a little different depending on where in Germany they're from, and that's also Marshmallow.You know, there
was a question, ``Does Germany have dialects?''
Especially.  My
impression is that the
people in Berlin have strong dialects, and the people in
Düsseldorf are pretty standard, and the people
in Düsseldorf are pretty normal, and even
though they're not the most correct German in soccer, they're the
most correct German.  I feel like there are no people who speak this in the first place.I
don't know which one is correct everywhere.If that's the case, then I'm
strong.There's probably a dialect.Eh,
strong, strong, too strong, but it's not the same thing.I can
hear it.Do you
understand?I'm listening too.  There's
a bit of a difference between people in Düsseldorf and Cologne.You know, some
people are too strong and their dialects are too strong, but there are also people who are
kind and speak a little more normally,
so I
guess I'm lucky.
[Music] I'm
not alone.  It's okay,
okay. I'm sure someone who speaks German
will come with you. But, I don't know if there's someone who can speak German,
but they're not there when it's an event. Maybe there's someone there when it's
a wedding. On the other hand, it's probably something like that.
When it's an event, there
's a little bit of someone.  But it doesn't seem like they'll be there all the time.
Maybe they'll just give me a
ride to the venue of the event.
I was like that too, so they're often
not there during the event, so I'm like, ``
Something's wrong, please
help me.''  When that time comes, I
think I'll be able to ask that staff member, ``Well, I
like this, I don't like this.'' It
feels a bit stiff to say that in both German and Japanese,
but...  "I like this"
means "I
like cats," but
if you want to say, "I like Germany instead of this," you can
put the word "Germany" here.
[Music] I
see. For
example, I
like cats.  It's a
good time. That
cat is
a little strange to say that one person is so active. I
should just say that I like cats.
[Music]
So do I. I
like dogs, but I like cats a lot more.  I'll
put it out for now.If you
put in your favorite words instead of that one, you can say anything.It
seems like it can be used for self-introductions, so it's just two words: I like this and I think it's good, and I don't like that.
There's a way to do that, but yeah, it's like that
stone mark dance from earlier,
so it's like, ``I
don't like this,'' so it's probably the
easiest way to tell Makitas, because they
use the same words, or, ``
This is a little
scary.'' Hmm, that's a
harsh way of saying it, but I'm from the A8th generation.  Yes, yes, yes,
it's chopsticks.
This is also a very emotional way of saying something that sounds
like something you
hate. That's right, that's right. It's used when you don't like it.
Which is better and cheaper? But
Magbus has
more in common, so that one is
easier to remember.  OK, OK, and now, just now, he
said it in a really Japanese way, but
let's not put any luck on this word. So, let's
say it's not a word, it's a voiceless sound that ends in S.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.  I
see, when Japanese people speak English, German, and other languages,
no one can understand them. This is the reason why only Japanese people can understand.
Well, they
say it in furigana. Maybe everyone is like that.
Why is it like this?  I
understand, but that's why I can speak Japanese.
That's why I can understand Japanese people's English.
But people who can't speak Japanese can't understand Japanese people's English. The
Japanese that I can't understand is a
set of vowels, so oh yeah, yeah, that's
it.  That
's true, for example, McDonald's,
Disneyland, and that
[music] is
a bit difficult to understand, but it's
not the same for people who can't speak Japanese.  If that's the case, try
erasing the "uh" sound. I heard good things.
Everyone, I see.
Ok, let's
move on. Please help me.
[Music]
Just need that helper, Teacher. It's
easy, isn't it?
[Music]
I want to make it beautiful.  Then I'll add the bitte that I memorized earlier, and I'll
eat
it. Please,
help me. Hilfie is cute. I
memorized it.
Um, to be honest, this line is long, so I don't
think it's okay to say it in English, but I'll teach you
Japanese.  Can you speak this?
Not everyone, but
J in German is
like Y in
English. I'm
sure it's H in
Spanish as well. It's different in Spanish.
If J in English is J, then
this is English, German, and
Why in German and English.  The pronunciation is
like J1 H in Spanish. It's
getting confusing and confusing. Can you
speak English?
Englishsplay
English It's
long, I'm sure.
If you're having trouble,
EnglishEnglish
please
Japanese.
Put a mark after the word and
say Japanese or English.  Okay, remember this too.
That's
great. It's great.
Enjoy. Now, for example, if
someone comes to your booth and
buys goods, you can say, ``This is Nana-chan's greeting.''
BTS,
or at the end.  It's okay to call it an anniversary tag. It's an
easy-to-remember anniversary tag.
[Music] I've
kept it short.
To make it easy to remember, my daily routine is basically
when I greet people, when I say bye-bye, I say "-" and then
leave.  I
think I can use this.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Here, let's
move on. I'm
happy.
Wow, I can say "I'm happy" in short in Japanese,
but I've been having
trouble with how to
say "I'm happy" in German.  For example,
when I receive a gift or
receive a compliment, I have the
nuance of being happy.
I
can't think of many words to describe it, so I don't think I can think of many words.
So, the
lines I wrote are:  It feels a bit
stiff,
but there
's some FR.
[Music] It's
hard when it's connected Hey hey it's coming Hey
hey hey hey hey hey
this is
difficult
When it's connected it's basically like
this I do
n't care which way you say it but
this is  You know, I'm
happy. This makes me
happy. It's a different color. Which
one is better? Hmm,
which one? For example, when I looked at it, some
fans came to see me,
or I received something from them.  Sometimes,
when I want to tell someone I'm happy, which one is better?
[Music]
Natural
[Music] If I had to
choose, I'd say the second one.Dance
White Mesh.However, in
such cases, I usually just say thank you.I
see.  I
want to say it in a way that makes it seem like I'm happy, but I
say it in a happy way.I say OK, I'm nervous.Well, that's
right, let's
put more emphasis on the second half of the word, which is similar to
English.  I
feel like they're putting a lot of effort into it. They're
making accessories. It's
amazing. I
pay in cash.
[Music]
Haraba
or
[Music]
Shorten it and add the word you already know.
This is
pronounced R.
If you say it firmly, you should pronounce it, but this.
If you want to go with the flow, don't pronounce it too much.
[Music]
OK, it's
cute, right? Once
Switzerland.
But
this is an
event where you can experience that Japanese culture, so
everyone knows how cute it is.
[Music]
Even if you don't know Japanese, you're
sure to know the words.  There are a few, but there
's one that says "goodbye." It's
cute. It's amazing. The word "cute" is so worldwide. It's
cute everywhere.
[Laughs]
Pronunciation is important here.
[Music] I
see. That strange letter has appeared again. Hey, it's here.  The
same goes for the next one. It's beautiful. It's beautiful. It's difficult to pronounce, isn't it? It's beautiful. This can be used both for people and scenery. Do is for you. Dance this. Um, if you can buy it, I'll do it.
Dance
[Music]
But  Well, the difference is that I don't
think I'll be able to remember it on the spot, so I think it's
ok to just use seasonal.I don't
think it's okay to say it without a subject.I think it's okay to use the
word Amazing.In
that case, I can remember it.Yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
it's fun.  Yeah, I
really do
n't want to say this like this either. This is also
hard,
hard.
This means I'm enjoying it.
The other thing is, this is
fun. Yeah, this is the difference here. There will
be a WS that looks like Smash SSS B.
Yes, but I
don't really say it like this.
How should I say it when I say it's fun?
Don't you think it's fun?
[Music]
[Music] I don't want to
say it in words, but for example, I
went here today. It was fun.  When you tweet something like, `
`Yes, if you say it
like that, then I wonder what you did properly.'' Well,
if you say it like that, I think it's okay to write this,
but if you say, ``It's already fun in one word.''  I
don't say it often, but on the contrary, it's not
fun. If it
were me, I do
n't mean it's just fun. That's
cool. I
want you to tell me words with various meanings.
[Music]
This word is actually
used in slightly different ways depending on the region.  I think
[Music]
That's right, there's something like ``Yay!'' ``I
want to hear it!'' or ``Yay'' is that
UFO,
not Yahoo Yahoo. I
think it can be used when playing games,
when I bought it, etc. But it's me again.
When I feel like that, I
think that instead of forcing myself to memorize simple, short words, it would be better to use English that I can understand.What is fun in English?
Wonderful Fan Fan
Fan
Fan That's how you are.  I do
n't know what it is, but in order to make German more natural, I think it's a different word than a proper selfie like this. [Music] The words that convey the feeling of fun [Music] If I were you, I'd say it.
[Music]
In German, it
can mean wonderful,
but
it
also has a
slightly
naughty meaning.  I
feel like it's mainly used in Austria.That
's what it means.Hmm, I
guess the meaning of this word is different in Germany and the North.  No
[Music] There is
something like English in English or that kind of feeling. I
say that I say that I don't say it. When writing, it's just like when I write in a sentence, so I don't really laugh.  I
think something like that happened to my older brother, but
people who love games sometimes say it
out loud.I
thought it was something they would pronounce.There
's a word for bursting out laughing in German.
Similarly, I write LOL in sentences.
But if I were to put it into words, it would be
like, ``Oh, Rocky [Music] That's interesting. Let's add this as well.
[Music]
That's interesting.
Please don't take pictures.'' It's
like all the reports from another world.  If someone
took out a camera and tried to take it away, it would be
a different world or there would be no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no.
Niko is
OK, is
n't it? Japanese. I'm sure this doesn't get across to you.
Well, when you say OK, you
can make an OK like this with one hand, but it
doesn't get across when it's over your head. Well,
with both hands.  Maybe they did.
[Music]
Even in letters,
Japanese people would probably use X with that circle.
They would use that extra, but they
would use check marks instead of this.
But,
overseas,
punishment is OK.  When you
play foreign games, the maltobutt may be
reversed.
Well, for example, let
's say there's a quiz,
and there's a check box
next to the answer, and the
answer is a dot.  When choosing whether it's correct,
there are both people who mark it as a check mark and those who mark it as a cross.This is just a
mood.It doesn't matter which one.It
does
n't matter.There are
people who cross out all the answers and only mark the answer that is correct.  There
are many different answers, and there are different shades, but if
there's only one cross in one answer,
then that means it's correct.For
Japan, which is completely different from Japan, a check
mark means a cross, so it's
interesting.Well, it
's confusing.
Checkmark
means the same thing as the Japanese word ``Ok
'' Don't worry, it's from another world
Photos or no no no no no no
no no That's right,
where is the toilet?
[Music]
Nedabonyu means W in English, but in
German it says
[Music]
That's the pronunciation, so where's
the
toilet? There are other words, too. Let's go. But it's easier to pronounce. Um, the word ``bettei'' seems prettier. What, Crow feels a little dirty. The difference between a toilet and a toilet.  It
's like, Oh
yeah, I see. Or English. In English, it's the word for toilet.
So this one
might be easy to remember too. You can learn the German word for toilet, and
say the word toilet with a voice.
That's right. The difficult part here is German.
Dear Adidas.  I know it's there, I don't know. It's
difficult. Before the words, uh,
there's "Dare Dee Dusty," but
that word
[music]
has a gender thing. It's like the Spanish word
"ra" and "none,"
but it's complicated and complicated.  This seems to be the
most troublesome part of learning German.
[Music]
No, I'm sorry. Well, it's
better to memorize it. Let's make it
easy. Voice Star. It just so happens that you're
going through the same trouble. I
understand that
sometimes it's the cat war.  Sometimes it's just a few
words, and
I'll say it, but you're in D.
Why, why, why, it's different,
etc. Actually, it's not really decided,
but
it's mostly decided.  Yeah,
say yes, voice
Yes, that's right, monster specs
Yeah, yeah, what do you
mean, all the words you asked me to say
Yes, I was taught, so I'll do this again in the end
Challenge Nana-chan at the end
[Music]
Stellar Cia Incircle High Shish Stella  Lucia I'll
stay for a long time
[Laughter]
[Music]
4th year 8th year
Equipment
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I
won't push myself too hard,
but I feel like I'm a friend of Germany, and
going overseas
is like
Hololive or
vtuber.  It's a word created by a Japanese vtuber, and
people who don't watch vtubers
won't understand it.I
think it's better to say it in the park, not because it's popular overseas.Yes, I have a
lot of friends who are from Germany.That's
all for now.  Desu-
sensei, it was really
easy to understand Hey, I want to say GOODLUCK. Good luck
Nana-chan. It
may be scary, but it's not scary at all. Please
enjoy.
Please
try some German food. I'd
like to post lots of photos and Vlogs.  I'm thinking of bringing my camera and I'll also
take some videos.If you
need some recommendations for German cuisine, you can
tell me how to fix it, but I think
if the staff comes with you for that meal, maybe they'll
be able to tell you.  But, I'd
like to hear your recommendations, I'd like you to eat this,
etc. I'll
tell you later on Discord.
Thank you. It took a long time, 1 hour and 40 minutes, but I wanted to teach you properly. Thank you. Please
look back and
say hello.  I'll repeat it and memorize it so I can use it in various ways. Please
do your best. Thank you. Dance  It's
okay to watch everything and be in the season.
Similarly, it's a
villa. That
's a really good word.
BTS I
might be wrong, but the truth
is actually disguised. I often write together, but
the truth is the bed and the
difference between losing and losing.
Thank you for your hard work. The last
part of today's broadcast is also a bit  What's that in German?
Bye-bye.
Well, thank you for watching today, Chara.
Thank you, teacher, for your long lesson today. It's
ok. If you have something else to do outside of class, let's
play. I definitely watched it. I was
able to flirt with Hololive's mom again. Yay.  - We're going to start
making out. If it's
Japanese, let's have some fun. Alright
then, everyone.
Juicy
[Music]
Bye-bye
Now that
microphone.
Wait a
minute. Wait a minute. The
mouse is lying.
There it is. There's a
charging cord. Wait a minute. Come back and
spin it.
Prime Minister:
Okay, ok, OK, let's move.
[Music]
When I wake up, you're there and it's new again.
The actions you gave me
were so kind, but I felt like crying. I was so
sad, I
was screaming. I wanted to meet someone.  Again, I
don't know your name, but I
can hear that voice.It's not just that I
started running.Thank you
[Music]It
may be a nuisance, but no one
closes it
to myself.It's
just a place where I can take that cry.I'll
pick up the feelings that have fallen here and
deliver them to
you.  Tell me
[Music] It
burns like this
[Music]