oh
[Music]
I
K
KY yay
yay hello every
[Music]
everybody
today I have a very special game for you
guys Shin
wait sh
me and I needed some Echo and Reverb to
make it sound as holy uh as it
is well first of all let uh stream is
sponsored for Atlas summer sum
sum thank you for sponsoring this stream
I'm really excited about it it's a game
that I have never really um played
before H and I don't really know
anything about it but I'm eager to learn
about it today and uh ER atos H also
provided the code for me to play it for
free thank you I got the deluxe edition
yeah H so I I think I got some extra
stuff because of that but I don't know
if we'll be seeing
it I don't know however uh I will play
it for you guys for the first 2 hours
approximately and I hope you guys will
enjoy it uh also yeah spoiler
warning uh there there might be spoiler
from the first two hours all right
without further Ado shall we dive into
it let's go new
game select the difficulty of the game
mhm this will only influence the game's
battles
can okay heart can only be chosen here
and cannot be selected later on oh
interesting okay
I will go with a
normal maybe I should have gone with
casual y I heard that the battles are uh
bit difficult here and
there wait should I go with casual
maybe should I
uh I heard the battles are really really
especially for beginner
well for for today in order to progress
uh faster and and show you more content
I will do
casual oh it might change to normal
later when I'm when I play it privately
then shut up I'm a game journalist okay
this is a work of fiction any names or
characters business or incidents are
fices uh fictitious uh any resemblance
actual person's leaving or
is uh not intended I guess when I
complete the brevity of a man's life I
am indifferent to worldly things how
many are the days I spend in F the man
yoshu
uhuh is that Sakura petals
petals oh she St yeah yeah I've been
there a couple
times business district working district
and uh shinen
is
here do you guys hear to I make it Lou
it's currently it's only like a long ago
the world of order was created by
God and his servants the
Angels LED it on its proper
course it was in such a world that
countless Mortals LED happy fruitful and
prosperous lives guy
by his
grace M character this however even
God's world is not Eternal I'm Eternal
oh
cute the pure unsolid path that God had
forged will as fate dictates become a
muddled poisonous swamp at the hands of
humankind School anime let's go
go ah will I be able to express my
feelings properly today begs chaos and
Chaos will likewise be consumed by order
in
turn who is sh how will these keepers of
knowledge strive and perish during their
fight I like those uniforms file hours
in this doomed world it's very dramatic
let us watch them at our Leisure until
the new ruler is seated upon the throne
all right can Happ be the new ruler am I
the new
ruler now hold
don't don't not really all right listen
up
hi I'm
listening everyone should have their own
personal tablets now but it sounds like
some of you still need to get them
registered you gave us an iPad W how
those temp accounts are about to
expire so anyone who's been putting it
off better get on
that okay do
it people people people is that a
Twitter
account type type
it are you tired oh
oh my first name wait wait a second I'll
I'll hide the screen because I don't
want to want any weird recommendations
to to be seen uh my first
name kiaha
K key
W okay didn't have time for Capal cap
capital capital Cap Caps you my last
name oh uh
[Music]
Taco too many
letters okay okay
okay Ki Taki it's it's supposed to be a
sh sh
okay uh yes
[Laughter]
one other thing it's been getting pretty
dangerous out there remember the buddy
system go back to the dorm in groups
what what what's so dangerous outside
that's it for Home
Room well that was uh
okay what what I what danger awaits me
outside do I need to fight
demons I I uh I'm scared mommy I'm
scared come pick me up oh students were
advised to head home in groups you
should look for a classmate to walk with
oh classmate oh mini map displayed on
the lower left corner of the screen and
gives you information on your sanics the
a symbol will indicate someone that can
be spoken to uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh
okay here there's a classmate here hey
hey oh speaking of all this scary stuff
I heard a first you got attached near
the station attacked what apparently
this Shadow came right at her huh what a
shadow what do you mean well I mean
that's how she described it she said all
she saw was some kind of black
fog but when it touched her back the
material got all thrown up like
literally Cuts started appearing like
from a knife she talks a little bit like
a valley
girl what that makes no
sense these students are too busy
talking doesn't seem like you can walk
home with them God damn it I wanted to
walk home with cute girls all right uh
let's talk here talk talk hey there you
want to know who I think the biggest
name at this school is it's got
Uso right the honor student from class B
I guess she's the best we've got in
academics here but in terms of girls it
would be
to right she's smart a great athlete
nice she's got it all even the butt hey
hey I'm smart I'm atic I'm nice too
these students are also too busy can't
walk with them yeah they don't really
they all look like NPCs I'm sure we're
going to get some special people walking
with
us hey how you talking to that gig from
the next class over uh what was his name
ichai yeah do yeah I guess he's making
videos YouTuber trying to put together
his web series ask me about that slasher
incident at the tunnel all right that's
stuff about some invisible guy with a
knife makes you wonder what the real
story is there yeah seemed like that was
des's Point said he's going to solve the
mystery of the slasher and the tunnel
really hyping himself up you
know these students are surprised also
too
busy is that person a
v okay the thingy symbol marks somewhere
I have to I have to go okay this way
Direction send zero everything all right
you got no eyes dude are you all
right good question to ask someone with
no eyes are you all right you want to
welome
together going home in a group sounds
like a right pain in yes I'm just going
to go alone well you're going to die
probably if you can find anyone else
maybe you should do the same huh no no
I'm scared my cats
too the student went home by himself all
right meow
yes you decided to go home alone as well
oh that says that calls for
trouble yeah I know chunkers
wait what the hell sorry one
second okay sorry I'm back yes hey you
heading back
[Music]
I won't be alone after all you it St
oh you're handsome you heard that talk
about it being safer to go home in
groups right mhm you should walk with us
I
will cute yes so these don't look like
MPCs sure I don't want to oh oh oh
choices
y nice we get choices in this
game oh
cute hey you two is that the girl that
they talked about who's
perfect because she can do
anything how isami I mean I heard the
name but I forgot what the description
was
cute oh um hi there hi she's also cute I
like the green theme she's got cute eyes
too and the the hair cute cute
cutea wait wait I didn't know you knew
him me are they they related I mean not
really they've met in passing chunka
left the room I think Miu and I ran into
him a couple times yeah to something
like
that a you're lucky your big brother
looks out for you so much huh um I guess
K on we're the only family we've got oh
I don't think it's that strange to look
out for my little sister yeah makes
sense especially if it's dangerous
outside apparently sure
sure so how about we all walk home
together yeah let's do
it we could stop by a cafe or go k oh o
is that a map of of
Tokyo Ki attends Jo High
[Music]
School not too far from there he lives
at the Joan High School dormatory along
with the other students aha
sha West I've been there before in the
commun and from school uh the shortest
route is to pass through the connecting
passage passage way at the shagala
station okay the quickest way back to
the dorm will be uh to head to the shaa
station West exit uh-huh uh-huh makes
sense but what's up what's up there oh
oh I have to follow the path what's
what's what's up
there I can just talk
[Music]
to I'm interested but I guess for the
sake of the story we got to uh go to
West let's go let's
go
oh shinagawa
[Music]
station sh station is so
big oh right to you said you wanted to
talk about
something oh it's
nothing I've just been having these
weird dreams lately me too yesterday I
dreamed about P simply I keep hearing
this distant voice like someone far away
is calling out to me it keeps getting
closer and closer but just when it seems
like they've almost found me I wake up
well I would be glad if P would be
calling after me every night kind of
getting to me wow I wish someone could
tell me what it all
means probably a reflection of something
subconscious maybe you're just stressed
over the future does the does the
protagonist not
talk is this the type of protagonist who
is just always quiet never talks
late something going on what happened
are there demons here I'll go check it
out check check check check silent
protagonist
oh oh
it seems like something's happened at
the station you should take a
look uh excuse me I'm passing
through H blue [\h__\h] doesn't stop me no
no no
no I heard someone got eaten what was is
some kind of wild excuse me what I tried
to get a look but it's hard to tell
blood everywhere though what the oh my
God I got to record no you don't record
that kind of stuff that's I think isn't
that also kind of like like
illegal it looks like something happened
here the
unlooked I going to record
that the entire oh oh okay
maybe
side
no no maybe on maybe on that
no eh
oh wait on the mini map it tells me
where to go back
back oh hi
Tu my brother came back but take a call
something walked out
somewhere then to got a message too she
went looking for somewhere quiet to try
calling back oh it's only us to
yeah uh
would you mind checking up on my
brother okay I know he's always looking
after me but I get worried about him
too it's the same answer fine I guess
thanks you're welcome I'll just wait
here in case t comes
back okay we're separating bad idea
let's talk to these girls hey there oh
you from Jo hi yeah sounds like they
close the whole area of I don't think
anyone's getting back to the dorms this
way well
bam that's uh going to be a problem
hopefully not more demons are going to
show up
here would you like to
guess okay saved
Ki ah wait what
[Music]
oh we're going to the takawa tunnel taka
Takashi
tunnel casual K don't make fun of me I'm
trying
to I I was scared people said it's
difficult
meow thank you for the Super Chat guys o
I've seen these guys what all right are
you the YouTuber word on the street is a
bunch of monsters have been seen hanging
around the
tunnel does it his cap say
sucker the freaking you you're going to
regret
that pretty low she pretty dark in here
too looks dangerous it's probably
dangerous
yes oh
man she
oh we we are not
amused uh it's like a horror game right
now y
it all right enough screwing around
let's go even deeper yeah
okay you can't imagine that YouTubers
filming videos like this is actually
really awkward until the editing kicks
in hey what are you doing here
uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh what's happening what's happening
fighting
time fighting tutorial time
I finished the game protagonist
unfortunately has passed
away no I Will
[Music]
Survive
hello it's so cloudy long long ago
before these creatures known as humans
gained know gained M the god of law
seated himself upon the throne is this
about the council
seized all knowledge from the other gods
rebuking them so they could never dare
to approach the
[Music]
throne reducing them to Mere
demons the fruit of knowledge was
secreted away in a secreted that's how
you pronounce that oh
creation the fruit of the knowledge is
bearing one day a serpent sought out the
mortal
seeking to tempt them into doing his
will serpent snake eat the fruit of
knowledge in this paradise and you will
become more like God oh the Serpent's
goal was to revive the war of the Myriad
Gods oblivious to the Serpent's
minations The Mortals of each realm ate
the
fruit one after another without fail
what is this what are we looking at the
knowledge they devoured then bound to
their souls birthing humans closer to
[Music]
Gods humans close when the god of law
saw this he banished all Humanity from
his paradise in a fit of rage is this
tree the tree of uh life or something
like that tree of everything that's
quite uh a common thing in
like you creatures infused with precious
knowledge this is the tree where know
that you were observed by
countless waiting chance to
strike so if the tree dies then the
whole world dies sh my go we can't save
me roll the credits roll the
credits egg Dr
[Laughter]
wait so is it actually called igle in
the game too
igle is that what this tree is
called he woke up nice wait looks a
little bit
different what it is this Gold
Dust capture it all
oh leave him alone how can this
be a human walks Among Us I don't know
we went for some kind of magical portal
or something this is no place for one
such as
you I shall Grant you sanctuary thaning
fortunate an angel of bethl found you
were it an agent of Chaos in my stead
you may not be alive you're going to
heaven remain calm and keep
still you will be safe
[Music]
momentarily I took him
away what the
hell what what Miss yes yes
meow oh no
but what's going to happen to his
YouTube account
though exactly doners hello
hello oh man our protagonist is not
motivated come
on where is your will for for fighting
and
freedom yeah
what you going to do you got to get out
of here
somehow no chunk chunk no no no no
playing around no
[Music]
no maybe some Demon can take us away
too okay no matter how many times you
look it's the same seemingly Endless Sea
of sand it's safe to assume this isn't a
dream you sure you decide to move onward
for
now
okay
wow I mean it definitely doesn't look
like the real world
though can we go faster where is the
dash button come on
buddy
oh cug footsteps
oh oh wait I was like the tunnel
disappeared but no it didn't
I hate sand it's co and r k [\h__\h]
everywhere should have gotten Barefoot
oh
hello action time
baby oh no they got a trident
oh what is that Target confirmed am I a
Target hopefully
not oh I'm not I think nice Target
eliminated who was that oh that's that's
that's I think we're going to wear
something like that
too I saw
it w what are you
who are you young man if you wish to
live take my hand could you have saved
my YouTuber friend too maybe I mean not
really a friend though uh take
his take his
hand let's
be
[Music]
F oh no I did some weird packed or
something yab you didn't warn me about
this
it was like signing a contract perhaps
oh
no now we can't get out of
it
transforming is this my final
form I'm
[Laughter]
cute I got long hair now luses long hair
fabulous
Divine
Majestic
Exquisite okay can we give it a try as
well oh you did that oh you did that oh
snap you did
then oh
cute so the Nuno make themselves known
again after all this
time life have remain separate until
now perhaps the
future is secured is it really do light
or dark you may Chase whatever you
please I shall await you in the realm
beyond the Earth and Heavens that hair
is until May your newf found power guide
your
Sur we are much more motivated now okay
let's fight fight the fight fight fight
we the fighting system
[Music]
like can you hear me yes you and I are
now one we
have we became one that whole
being based on my own but your knowledge
seems to be the basis of our oh is it
because I'm smart I shall obey your will
oh command me in battle that we may best
fight as one interesting
what okay ah player and enemy access are
governed by the Press turn icons shown
at the top of the
screen uhhuh taking one action consumes
one icon select skills then choose an
action to
take oh when choosing which action to
take you can select skills and CHS to
attack heal or support among other
choices choosing the attack skill will
not consume any MP all other actions
however will cost MP to use
uh observe each situation and decide the
best approach okay how many do I have
68 Z can we use it it looks sprayed out
okay I think we can only attack
[Music]
normally now that's a good hit enemy
turn can I
block yummy
11 okay fight back each skill has its
own affinity and demons typically have
weaknesses to a certain skill affinities
targeting a demon's weakness will deal
damage as well as cause a press turn
icon to start
flashing
ahuh ahuh uhuh this indicates that you
have earned one additional action oh
striking weaknesses and granting
yourself extra actions can often lead to
Victory so pay attention to the skills
used does it tell me what their
weaknesses
are or do I have to test it
out well we'll do we'll do this one
now ah I I have to test it out and then
here it will tell me eventually
oh could it be
electricity could it be
Sparks increasing and decreasing press
turn icons a flashing uh by the way is
this too
loud a flashing press turn icon
indicates one additional action nice you
can grant yourself extra actions in a
fight by targeting enemy weaknesses on
the other hand missing attacks or having
your attacks nullified will consume more
press turn I than normal a that's why
the battle system is so unforgiving is
that why because you can like if you
don't know the weakness you really need
to learn the weaknesses in order to win
this H okay the same rules apply for the
enemy as well oh they need to find out
my weakness too what's my weakness
Target enemy weaknesses while Defending
Your Own in order to maintain the
advanced
[Applause]
one more
time wait weak weak as in he's weak
against it or or that attack was weak H
level
up okay nice
to wao level
up okay this is the character
uh stat stat
interface you leveled up all lot your
earn points to build your stats oh no
can I mess this up oh strength fatality
magic agility uh luck agility
agility
uh probability of chance based results
being on in your favor during
battle what should I go
for magic just go magic magic really
okay
sounds good to me wait did I add
it ah ah wait ah oops oop oop I put one
in there okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay
magic magic magic H targets
eliminated all hostile targets
eliminated nice what was that just now
where are we uh I think I want to know
what that was Lord of demons hunting you
for your soul young man he got no soul
did you look at him was silent
protagonist this place is what is now
called The Nether world the ne
world uh never World NE world the place
the demons call home oh you saw them
they are descendants of the Gods of old
known now as
demons this is their world but how did I
get
here but do not worry I Proto Alami am
here to assist Alami funny it means blue
God in
Japanese together we have become a being
known as a
Nino this new body should allow us to
fend off the demons
oh oh let us keep this form until we
reach a safe location i' like you to go
here as it should help us get a better
grasp of of this world sorry okay okay
oh it's so dark in this
map pressing the plus button will
display the map which gives a much wider
view of the area this can prove useful
when the mini map isn't giving you
enough information okay why I can run
and look at my hair oh I can jump woo
what what no no come back what did you
tell me I think something with no no no
no something with ZR or something is
that what the was telling me how much
does it cost
me what do I lose for doing that press
R2 R2 R2 R2 that R doesn't do anything
but R1 does
this damn it that AR ah Zoom you seem
worn out from that last battle perhaps
you should gather some magui I'm not one
I was about to
zoom magui magui this world is filled
with magui brimming with spiritual power
it is the source of a demon's
strength what is maku the lights you see
around us are the crystallized forms of
magui
Lights SP young man can you not see them
no I don't think so perhaps you aren't
accustomed to your new body just yet
focus focus and try looking again
focus
focus shoot
you
wow I see it I see the light should I
walk towards it to see them yes yes
those are magui crystals okay I'll go
get them all magui can give us strength
as well if you see any don't hesitate to
claim it for yourself of course it's all
mine the free colored lights that can be
seen uh on the map are called magui
crystals green crystals restore HP ah
while yellow Crystal restore M MP mhm
red crystals store Magi which is needed
to use special skills
oh
hold
oh yeah no need for auto heal we got
these
[Music]
thingies
yeah no not again I was I was about to
jump what did that
say what did that say was it telling me
about jumping anyway probably it
probably did you know what I'm probably
good I was about to jump and I clicked
the way okay this time climbing points
climbing points refer to the square
blocks of red edges seen on the map you
can climb on top of these points by
facing them and pressing the be oh okay
just like jumping is this a climbing
Point
what oh
parkour oh I'm going to a I was going to
say I'm going to be the best in
parkour oh
uh I shouldn't keep on pressing it I
should uh uh uh press it one by
one
okay
okay the golden object on the map are
treasure boxes oh these can be destroyed
with the Nino's short attack and so
whenever you see one try ping it and
pressing the Y
button
oh okay so this one fancy
wow 500 MAA what is that is that an
Australian way to say uh uh the name of
a certain fast food chain I think that
sounded a little bit
different am
oh W whoo whoa whoa whoa whoo wo whoa
whoa
W observe young man yes this land is
known as the Nether world
[Music]
okay this isn't Tokyo is not yeah that
was what I was thinking Tokyo Tower I've
heard that this place was once known as
Tokyo but that time has
passed now it is the Nether world a land
dominated by
demons well as long as they don't
dominate The Real World what happened
H I'm afraid I lacked the data needed to
answer your inquiry right now come on I
need to know more all I can remember is
that there was a battle here in days
past between gods and demons oh two
great forces clashed right here in front
of Tokyo Tower I know this because I was
there as well oh despite this however
the data containing my memory of what
followed has been damaged M the only
other memory I have is of my mission to
protect
you it seems as allam character can't
explain anything
further young man find out our ourselves
Tower okay if you return to the last
location in my memory I may be able to
remember something
else okay we're going to try to help him
remember
okay okay he for Gore accept uh accepted
the quest the lay of the land aha as you
progress through the main story a quest
May naturally trigger these are called
main quests main quest are different
from the optional sub Quest and must be
completed to progress the story ah now
hold up sub Quest and Main quests exist
[Music]
okay oh that's fun I love sliding in the
sand I'm so fast what is that is that a
fight after comparing this blue pillar
of light with my data I have concluded
this is a layline f I see a demon demon
over there on the on the on the right
side or maybe it's not a demon a lay
line found disa point from which the
Earth's energy
overflows as one might surmise it holds
incredible power power not only can it
heal those who touch it but it can also
instantly teleport one to another
location oh nice considering the damage
sustained in your previous battle I
recommend you verify its healing
capabilities okay let's give it a
try
touch oh where did go we go
o well you're a peculiar one aren't
you oh well
hello is this your your impression where
you
are oh my God this is the place I call
home it's a nice home as you can plainly
see I'm a bit of a collector of sorts
it's easy oh do you want my with the
Riff Raff out there and me in
here still a demon like you a first one
body s two Spirits within no doubt about
it what pleasure having you
G Gustav Keeper of the kadab Holo you
may call me Gustav gust see something
you like it's all yours so money for
money for a small fee of course got
those golden teeth like a rapper where's
your gold
chain so he's friend we like him so
after to Tokyo Tower
oh it seems like we like him and you
found little old me you while trying to
harvest the power of the line Fountain
yes apparently yes can I have that
golden sword yourself a favor and make a
purchase I'll sell you what you crave
long as you got the marker I don't know
what I crave Edge against the demons why
don't you oh do you have
armor what will be
uh B I guess wa I have quite a lot of
money 56 5 oh or medicine would
probably be good looking to buy maybe
more than
one maybe five to
buy say thanks you're welcome revive oh
Revival bre no now I'm lacking the money
for that damn it I should have bought
that too damp
nullifies attack against all allies once
for one turn oh will this be important
displays info wonderful wonderful oh so
what this will tell you
the uh like their weaknesses and
stuff well I think for now I'm good need
anything
else
no
no satisfied your curiosity have you
allow me to send you back on your way
all right before that however I couldn't
help but think our meeting like this
must be F so perhaps you can do me a
favor okay I'd rather takeen with the
human knickknacks and Relics of your so
I got some you sit on chairs like he
does for me difference they're
called trouble is they're fickle and
even worse forgetful
often times they give up the search and
do whatever they
please
useless that said If you happen to run
across any mind sending them back old
G's
Direction okay so I've taken Liberty to
connect this place to the leline F feel
free to come and go as you so at any
safe point I can come see you wonderful
I am I am excited just oh yes of course
here allow me to show you the ins and
outs of the LEL line Fountain I can use
the flow to heal you if you fancy but I
can't do it for
free cough up a little Mone however I'll
set you right his rain you want money
from me for being healed at the safe
point the kadava hollow has been
unlocked recovery has been unlocked was
an unexpected meeting but we were able
to confirm the F's capabilities mhm as
we make our way to Tokyo Tower I
recommend we look for the mimon as we
were oh maybe that was what we saw over
there
oh buy and sell items save game data and
Recovery I don't think I need recovery
and I don't think I need anything right
now I'm good thank
you so this thing is that is that what
they were looking for young man could
that be one of the mimon we were told
about it it's uh weirdly
[Music]
cute really really
cute I should save
okay gooda want us backpack why no find
any relics yet fine fine I'll head back
you obtained five
Glory I'll by ated a mimon no we should
report back to kab's hollow oh okay you
received someone something that's known
as Gloria you will make use of this
later for now keep moving forward uh
move forward but they say I should go
back
to should
I well you guys said to save so I guess
I'll
save
yes okay and should we report again
mush M mush
M found on already have we yes my I got
just the thing to show my
appreciation
a on mori's
Essence this is an Essence it contains
the power of a demon power that only the
chosen can wield you'll want to make
your Merry way over to to the line
fountain in
MA someone there will be able to tell
you more I'm sure
okay okay byebye off yeah
byebye hold up saving important in smt
okay I will remember that now let's Zoom
to Tokyo Tower oh wait there's one more
here
hello also I think I see a demon over
there hello
I go back by the way sparkly shiny boxes
destroy get something nice yeah I know I
know I know thanks for the
glory
yaho uh can we get something at the
vending
machine
what
soldier so what are you you don't really
look like an evil young man it appears
there's a demon up ahead I have a
proposal you want to marry her oh my God
that's a bit
fast it's dangerous to travel the Nether
world alone therefore I recommend we
recruit some demons to fight on our side
oh on our side H by talking to Demons
you can try and persuade them to join
your cause oh any demons I have a life
Stone you can use see if you can
convince the the demon to join you we're
going to bribe her okay you obtain a
life Stone
oh
hello can you help me on my
quest we're
fighting I just wanted to
talk okay attempt to record a demon to
your side for
negotiation oh that's
interesting you started talking to the
demon
wow he talked to me could this demon
want me to join him okay then let's talk
I'm going to ask you a question so make
sure you answer it in a way that would
make me happy oh dear okay I got to
score some points guys like a dating
game so do you think I'm cute of course
you are well that's
[Laughter]
easy she liked it this is how you uh
flirt guys learn from taka wasi Kiwa let
me ask one more question do you want me
to
join yes yes
okay okay thank you for carrying me like
a
baby de wanton join you for free you got
to give them all kind of stuff like
items or MAA wow okay I'm going to tell
you what I want what I really really
want so make sure you give that to me
what should I do I have a I have a
livestone e
okay i' be happy to join you now y
you'll be able to get other demons to
join you by negotiating just like we did
right now you're very nice are is as
nice as you Dem are pretty fickle so
might not go as easy it did with me I
thought so even if you mess up don't
worry just hang in there okay nice to
meet you nice to meet you
too are they like throw away demons like
only used once and when they die I can
never use them
again
oh well done young man well done if
there is a demon you want on your side
then you might try to negotiate with
them okay they can evolve oh I can
revive them too oh after three other
demons can participate in a battle the
more demons on your side the less
demanding a battle will be try talking
to various demons in order to record
them okay pressing the x button outside
of battles will display the menu main
menu here you can use skills and items
manage demons and perform various other
actions
hold so this uhuh oh my stock oh demon
stock can I uh expand that at some point
probably huh
Essence was
that what is
that
question uhuh analy
oh oh oh oh why or when I hire them I
can see their weaknesses and strengths
here okay wait I want to see what what
is that wind she's she can defend
herself against wind but she's weak
against what is that dark magic I
guess
[Music]
no
okay she heals
oh uh young man there is a demon up
ahead we're not going to try to hire
these ones are we way to engage the
enemy when confronting demons the best
strategy is to strike them with your
blade uh with why in many cases this
will give you the initiative in the
battle ah makes sense on the other hand
if you are attacked the enemy may very
well gain the initiative
instead okay observe the enemy's and act
accordingly to earn okay
yes is y button
uhhuh no problem I understand that B
There Done
dead you notice me
here slice them up slice them up play a
turn
okay well let's figure out uh what
they're weak against shall we are you
weak against this by any
chance hey oh I F
K no
nice two normal attack go ah you almost
killed him couldn't you have done a
critical hit come
on I guess I'll do a normal n wait
I'll I'll Attack this
one hopefully I don't regret
it a nice yeah I was hoping for getting
another attack with the pixie to finish
him
off and now we only got one left enemy
turn
ouch that's h no ah the pixie barely has
any
[Music]
HP kill
him yeah oh should I talk with him oh
should
I
yeah it's all right we don't need
slime she's a Healer okay makes sense oh
wait ah the other one didn't join that
battle okay let's go one
more collect slime what slimes can
usually what not be recorded okay what
you mean these ones can't be recruited
[Applause]
anyway Dia slightly uh recover HP uhhuh
well it's
okay this one can
oh do we need to weaken them before we
do that confuse them later you can
record him
okay you started talking to the
demon this demon the demon is
approaching what will you
do glare at them
menacingly you don't need to waken
okay ah not as stupid as he looks
smell blood smell
blood
uh
uh uh laugh with
them you get you love the feeling of
getting splattered the
FL no not really but let's say I do
the bird over no I'm a bird you are
definitely not a bird I've seen I I've
never seen a a bird like I'm pretty sure
you're not a
bird come on let's get some bir on the
ground oh that means like let's fight
now oh [\h__\h]
okay ah ah that went wrong ah
no Maya I will kill you then finish
you you should have gone with
me now the only thing you got was
Dev all right
okay many cars many slime many a slime
should we try to get this one then will
he say the same thing I
wonder wrong answers yeah apparently
that was I wanted to make him happy is
that not the way to
[Music]
go if I fail like uh like like have like
befriending the enemy the demon does it
always automatically end up in him
attacking me right away with an enemy
turn or was that just a
coincidence oh no chat is getting mad
with back seeding okay I better hear
myself otherwise they're going to
[Music]
cry still looking good
though they sometimes run away
oh well okay let's
talk let's talk you started talking to
the
demon smell blood smell
blood okay
snifty yeah got a good life of that
that's what surv what the f smells
like uh I think that's just your stink I
prefer the smell of
Barbe um should we insult
him this is pretty
difficult I can't read him can't read
this guy to stink
down right I smell just how demon
more and maybe he's happy about being
stinky come on the big S Dem more time
for Treasure bring out your
offerings now let's see
here I want some of your HP if are you
kidding me you'll join my team if I give
you
HP but I don't know how much he
wants
[Music]
nah no
sh this isn't going
anywhere oh he
disappeared yeah I don't know what if he
would have taken 35 HP and I would be
dead I don't know how much it takes what
the hell
n okay one
more negotiation failed again
ah do we try
again well okay I will heal
kaha and
then we will do this again talk to
me yes yes blood blah blah blah I know
you love blood
M uh glare at them right oh no wa huh
you're looking at me I think you ought
to have a little more respect now let's
do some offerings oh now he wants it
ride
away oh we want HP again a deadly
amount that that's worse than before is
he going to kill me I can't say yes to
that will that kill me give it say yes
no anything
else don't okay I mean deadly that
that's a trap isn't
it it will kill do it try
it
okay oh okay it doesn't kill me it it is
quite a lot though okay now I guess when
he said not deadly then it would have
been way less than that and I could have
been fun
okay call
me Pleasures Al
my okay
we got a new
bunny oh slimy
slime nice I
guess but now I need to heal myself uh I
guess I could do auto healing but what
does that
actually how does that work okay let's
fight you with your
friend
nice he's got cute eyes y
yeah I'm running out of MP though I need
MP I got it go go go
go what does he have lunch oh normal
attack is
fine all just uses healing skills until
you're full HP without showing it a
person ah okay okay okay okay so it it
would be uh using pixie zings it doesn't
matter does it
just level
up new scale oh a wind
scale nice
okay uh oh wait wrong
direction
oh what is
that uhoh who who whoa wait a sec oh
friend from Real World
no demon oh you don't eat me not a lot
of flavor you know trust me she's
cute they're not cute oh hey you you
with the long hair you'll save me right
yes please yes yes of course who are
you I I am T Washi kiaha oh my God they
got um something between
so I guess we'll be oh drop that
[Applause]
jaw egg PL
demon let's destroy them oh wait should
we ask them to join us as well demons
will gradually build up magui and fill
the magui garge once the garge is full
you will be able to use powerful
abilities known as magui skills kill two
talk one uh-huh okay save the slot ah
for the new girl I guess yeah that makes
sense uh they can't join in this fight
okay collecting mag crystals will also
fill the garage and it will even
automatically fill with each passing
turn during battle so keep an eye out
for opportunities to use these skills
and turn the fight in your
favor
oh okay so for now
[Music]
attack now I wow what hit kill weak weak
as
hell noral
attack oh critical oh we're too strong
those are so
weak they are so weak
what
y one
shot remember though I'm playing in
casual
level up oh I can do uh you leveled up
uh-huh okay magic magic
yes oh she oh wait I can add her skills
too oh no wait for the for them it
happens automatically ah plus two plus
two ah okay okay now this
is the best damn demon there ever was m
I wouldn't be so sure about that but he
got a lot of new poison skills
cool
nice
woo that's a
relief cute will you join me now thanks
you really saved me back there oh you're
welcome but you know what I want in
return no now that I think about it I
like totally had the judgment to ask for
your help so doesn't that make me
awesome too uh okay never mind then like
you deserve thanks anyway uh the only
reason I'm alive is because I asked you
for help and you know it don't try to
deny it either
um O
Okay the demon in the kimono has uh
rather liberally interpreted interpreted
the situation what will you
do let be nice that's ask if she's Hur
you're worried about me a you're sweet I
know yep I'm just fine all good over
here wait a sec I just realized I've
never seen you before huh I'm new here
wow how weird so but God where you
headed young man there are demons in
this world that feain kindness to pray
on you you saying she's going to trap me
I suggest we ignore her and move on
what hey you're leaving like Ser
no well well
fine turn we got to turn out here she's
going to join us because we left her
isn't
she please
please a really we got to go without her
wait a second I will fight you but I
also want the vending machine oh what's
that oopsies uh a what what of you who
are
you some demons like to fight but others
like to talk and if you make a
connection they might want to be a
friend or give you free stuff okay wait
wait wait you only here to talk to me
what what was that what was
that let's fight those
it wait does it count as me attacking
first okay I think we're
good I have no MP left wait how do I I
don't have an item for MP do
I oh yeah
uh let's try wait what is that raise the
defense weak Force attack to one
eh n we'll just uh do it normally then
it try talking to the Slime
now okay but wait you don't mean the the
middle
one yeah yeah yeah why would I talk to
the Slime you mean the middle one huh
okay H but first yeah let's kill the
other
ones weak physical attack normal attack
is this
stronger slime versus slime
uh-oh
uh uh just try talking okay oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] Lune is stronger really okay the
Slime
really which one does it matter I'll
talk to this one start talking to the
demon oh well he did not fight me then
and I only got the middle one
left oh you got one of my bodes May well
a friend of theirs is a friend of mine
oh ah should have done it in the
beginning huh oh n hold up but do they
have to be in my party or can they also
just be in my
stock oh wait the other one left though
what the
hell oh I should have damn it Dam
it who is that what are
you I should have
uh probably healed or
something I don't get any XP ah stock
works as well oh okay well let's start
by talking to the middle one he looks
angry he started talking to the demon
but it seems they have have no intention
of listening oh
[\h__\h] what about what about the this one
then okay he wants to
talk hey we got to we ought to get along
yeah I mean peace has got to be a first
priority
right
uh he doesn't look like he wants peace
though I think is testing me I don't
believe in peace
oh damn you really are heartless you
even human what color is your
blood um
blue I don't I don't
play is your circulation dad bad budny
you got to see a doctor here this is
this the
help he gave me a soda thank
you he gave me
[Music]
something oh still find the rest though
okay
interesting okay I'm recovering HP to
myself how kind of him I can get items
wow
a that's
cool
lunch
yeah enemy turn oh
[\h__\h]
okay
what no hey the middle one disappeared
why would you do that what a
coward oh hey I don't want to wa is that
going to be if I don't use it now
is it going to be empty in the next
[Music]
battle or will it stay until the next
battle I don't want to waste it
[Music]
me that was a treasure demon XP demon no
rare
enemy oh damn okay so sorry the fights
are all super cool and fun but I think
we got to progress the story a little
bit cuz it's only a two 2our stream wait
uh I don't have anything for MP
right ah weak Almighty and oh no for to
attack one
full okay well I can I can at least do
this wait but what about this boy come
on ah ah [\h__\h] ah ah ah I ah no four even
sh it wait wait my magui is still maxed
though oh let's go is that a AOE attack
for all critical hits for all allies for
one turn
oh
okay it's
time let's go all attacks including
magic attacks will be
critical attack
kidding
me it's killing time okay okay okay okay
okay okay
okay let's
do poison
attack oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh I killed one though do I get the EXP
from that
one I do oh holy [\h__\h] that's a lot of
exp wow for just one you leveled up uh
okay uh
uh we're now magic
still I got one
W okay okay oh there's a black one too
yeah bit should I should
I
you let's try let's try let's
try oh he has a funny face he's so
SM we can't talk to them huh we just
want to get them for exp okay
attack ah but wait magical attacks huh
a I think normal attack
no you're just going to disappear on me
again de debilitate oh God oh God what
is that what is that oh all our stats
are down I don't think I can do
anything
y never mind oh God
hard what
about he's going to dis block
[Music]
it oh he disappear okay um okay I'll
just mind my own business
now wait wait will that debuff stay
until the next
battle oh God eh oh wait there's a
healing point there heal my mp2
please well now isn't this a sight to
Behold a female
voice let me see what the hell is that
in the back
though yes look at
me master I am Tak taka
wasii oh are you
God
hello at last you have
arrived all of this time waiting and
only now does one possess the power to
see me sorry it took a
while one who has awakened to their true
form through the reunion of knowledge
and life a Nino yes
that's what I am I am Sophia I have come
from a plane far beyond this one to act
as a guide to both the world and the
Nino wow you're
beautiful ruler of the world of
Shadows
Sophia wow however I see now that
although your power should rival that of
the Gods it is
unstable incomplete I agree with that
yes give me power pleas allow me to
awaken some of that which still Slumbers
within let us see what you
hide are you going to awaken the
darkness inside of me please
do
W
[Music]
Hallelujah doie
doie you now possess the means to gain
Essences allowing you a myri of powers
and miracles the ability to shape the
world
what henceforth you shall Traverse Dot
and gather these Essences along with
Glory as these are the very source of
Miracles these shall be your source of
power aino and will surely Aid you on
your path to godhood who I will become
[Music]
God
oh oh it appears you're already in
possession of an Essence I guess I am go
on then use apotheosis and accept that
that Essence into your being
strengthening the Nino the world of
Shadows offers an option under
apotheosis called Essence Fusion that
allows the teaching of skills to both
the Nino and his demons ahuh try
learning some skills of an Essence in
your
possession
huh this is a forbidden ritual that
gives you authority over the powers of
gods and
demons
okay we're doing that you can learn
Miracles by using the glory of God can
inherit the power inhabiting the
Essences of demons
what what do I
do
[Music]
what what
oh wait
what I get his
power cuz I got his Essence do I want to
put that on the main character
always Fusion
what select
skill will I get that skill or will I
lose that
skill
[Music]
Fusion you gained their
skills huh huh
huh weak fire attack let's take this
oh oh oh I get them all okay okay
done how is
this yes
good good thank
you you're going to inherit the power
yeah I I did that what about this one
learn Miracles fory slashing an enemy in
the field without being noticed noticed
will greatly increase the mag you wish
to learn this yeah yeah yeah yeah
please who slashing an enemy in the
field
okay okay okay well um um um I think I'm
I think I'm done return when you have
gathered more
demons
[Music]
okay well well made it to meet us l
to let you in on a little
secret all lay lines are connected there
might be more oh that had other tabs oh
there were more miracles oh God damn it
I thought it was the only one get away
to another Fountain no time flat M see
for
yourself I actually just wanted to be
healed thank you uh L Crossing L
Crossing is the ability to travel
between any line found you have reached
until now upon discovering new Lan
fountains they will then be registered
as a possible destination for Line
crossing Line crossing is the ability to
explore the vast Lev World keep up the
search for line fountains and expand
your
horizons the add-on content the return
of the true demon is now accessible
visit the world of Shadows in order to
accept the corresponding
quest
uh wait uh yeah recover
do I get MP from
[Music]
this 88
MAA oh I do get my mp
back 75 that's so much
[Music]
money I think besides that we just save
yes okay and then we just
continue okay we got to check out that
monster over there oh wait wait before
we do that first of all take this I keep
on pressing uh
bee what are
you maybe there's some food lying around
here he wants food I'm not giving you
that yeah I wanted these things but but
eh there's two paths do we go to this
crazy lady path oh it's not a lady it's
just a big monster um excuse me young
man I'm detecting the presence of
powerful Dem can I not pass object
ahead that is what is known as an absess
looks like it is a nest of be that have
been drawn together by the overflowing
spiritual power
uh-huh can we remove it approaching it
is dangerous but we will need to destroy
if you want to reach Tokyo Tower comat
combat is unid
unavoidable however our current fighting
capability may be somewhat liking I
would advise we call more demons to our
side and strengthen our forces I see
what is the recommended level would you
tell me that abscesses are outpourings
of magui that have been claimed by
demons demons who hold these areas will
attack anyone who gets close oh until
you slash the absis and defeat the demon
or demon house within it is wise to
remain
cautious uhhuh upon the Demon's defeat
the hidden pal will be granted to the
Nino
oh okay we are too weak
probably which is why there was this
other path over
there so let's fight them what about
you can we get the blue one oh he looks
so nice and happy Oh might as well
how about this fire
skill what do you think
about
F fire always best I think that was his
weakness nice I leveled
up
magic they give me items oh is I'm not
being notified of that and hello let's
fight
you oh but I want the XP so I'm actually
going to fight
them how much oh my magui is
Max watch this I will fight
you attack
attack normal attack is fine cuz we got
those Critical
Hits
attack ah didn't kill
him lunch uh this
boy
hey we are strong I will do this
one
easy close to L can spam skills ah I
guess so cuz we can recover the MP huh
that's
true I just had a feeling I need to be a
little bit careful with my mp now fight
you let's go now these ones the right
one do we want to try recruiting that
one can I talk to this boy one more
luy nice to meet you you look like a
vegetable this demon is trying to leave
what will he do don't
leave smirk
smack wait you're just going to pounce
on me the second I turn
around I'm not falling for that let's
just talk instead oh I think I did the
right thing you're new here huh I don't
think I can trust
you I don't want to mess this up that's
fine that doesn't mean you're not
dangerous though I'm going to kill you
while Sil
come okay oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
uh resist yeah okay I I mean he used the
fire skill so I I was kind of expecting
that now
[Music]
hold we can we could send the other
pixie away
huh try talking
again it's too late
now
[Music]
lunch when it says in party I feel like
I'm fighting myself here we level up for
the Slime level
up
okay well maybe we'll meet another
one
oh oh wait it it ends here oh [\h__\h] was I
supposed
oh do we have more enemies to find ah
yeah over there there the
vegetable please let's be
friends let's be friends
please come on you
School you started talking to the
demon the moon's all gone everything's
so dark now it's no use could this be
doing to the new
moon what you didn't even let me have a
conversation should I try again later
moon face New Moon makes demons go crazy
you can't talk during certain Moon
e
interesting wa oh okay wind against
slimes very
strong uh course attack let's do
it and then oh I can talk again but I
guess it's moon moon face oh wait ah on
the top left I can see it's new moon
ah I see
damn damn
it full moon and New
Moon thank
you full moon and New
Moon
[Music]
okay the red one and the black one are
here again
do I have a chance let's go get some uh
oh wait what did I see up
[Music]
there let me go grab you real
quick I found
you look from high places might find
lots of things you obtain five Glory y
look at his
diapers send him back to his daddy who
changes his diapers nice
okay I
will
uh heal the party
again Babble Babble
Babble and Chronicle
de wait did I heal everyone or just me I
healed everyone right uh
oh I only healed
myself I guess I'll heal the pixie
to
29 okay we're
good I will try to
fight these boys
again I want the
EXP I need it to fight that weird
[Music]
thing m
were they resisting let's try the
fire no they block
it but something went through before
what was
that they block fire what about
wind they block
wind
son
no
no he
stayed what sound didn't work this time
the
show oh oh wait do the same demons that
always have the same
weaknesses because now it doesn't show
us the blocking Shield at the fire
[Music]
thingy this is
the but he blocks
it these are exceptions oh no all stats
down well thank you double down
he still doesn't escape
the can we just
call they have no intention of listening
a
walk well I don't really I can't really
can't can't really do
anything uh what are you going to do
Escape
[Music]
okay we got nothing from that wait does
that the the stats down that disappears
right
okay we try to fight this one again
think Kiana
think what do you think about
fire okay you don't care what do you
think about this one
wi okay you don't care are you going to
go God damn it zon this one ah
okay you know what I'm just going to
kill these boys over here oh maybe I can
capture them
now that one looked more chatty you sure
I thought they were only for
exp okay talk help
me demon is their guard up what will you
do your guard up
as
a okay I guess I can stop overly isn't
that easy I'm just going to tell
oh oh my God this is
funny Miss I guess I did have my gam oh
come
on these demons wait I can talk again
should I talk to the same one no what
was that [\h__\h] that you just puled
there demon laugh their head up what
will you
do love willome you're making fun of me
AR who do you think I
am Fusion
Materia a reliable
comrade really you really think I'm
reliable well in that case you probably
trust me enough to give me whatever I
want right yes yes yes yes yes we're
getting there I want a ton a ton a ton
is better than deadly right
should I
give should I give a
ton yes come join me
now
y
RI you're a vegetable don't lie to me
you're not a
dinosaur
[Music]
y finally we got the
onion okay the other one we might as
well just fight but um wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait can I H it's so far
away okay we'll just kill him we can do
it we can do it two
onions give me exp should we try
afterwards to fight the absis you think
we can do it it's a casual playr so no
not this one this one strike
no I don't want to talk I want the
[Music]
EXP right should be fine okay we want
some progress after
all
L okay one
down on moraki versus on
Mori attack weak
ah not the
fire attack
steal I need to fuse my Diamond H demons
[Music]
oh okay you forget your MP back yes yes
I
will okay okay let's do
this let's do this level eight can we do
it I mean it can't be that difficult
there's not even that much space to
grind here anyway so I think I think
they just wanted us to get a fourth
party
member healing good heing good heing
good and
then perform perform demon fusions you
guys wanted me to demon fuse did I get
an Essence feel like the chat said I got
an essence
H you obtained manora of knowledge oh
thank you this is a manur it was brought
here from another world certain my
giving this to you raises we only have
20 minutes left but hear me well this
manora can either bring you great power
or deliver you to an un those who carry
the manora beckon the avatars of death
you must okay I don't really understand
but I don't have time to understand
osis ACC Fusion
uh
Pixie ah oh I can learn a healing
[Music]
skill okay
okay ah ah but ah I need to keep my own
as well uhhuh wait I can guess I guess I
can get all of
them
oh oh
oh oh how is
[Music]
this you don't have the ah okay this was
not what you guys meant this is Essence
Fusion huh
okay learn Miracles can I learn a new
Miracle hand of God rare chance to
acquire one extra Relic half of Max HP
and MP are recovered when leveling up oh
maybe this one increases the nalos fire
skill potential by ah oh H but they're
they're too expensive but I can get this
one you wish to learn this
yes now
then yeah yeah I know um maybe I guess
this one too you wish to learn this cuz
I got I had 10 Glory perfect okay byebye
I'm going to go fight now but first I
save
safe much
safe okay
let's go I've just picked up a number of
strange readings okay well many of them
are not unlike the manora in our
possession and what's more they are
accompanied by powerful demons
uhhuh I've marked the locations of these
readings on the map we should
investigate provided we can spare the
time
now we have like 20 minutes left should
I investigate or is that is that an
optional thing
or do I uh wait where was
that where was
that ah down here you can't spread don't
don't run okay that's DC ah that didn't
look okay okay okay
hello oh can I not just fight you
directly do I have to fight all these
mobs no I want to fight
you yeah let's
go Kaka
kiaha oh okay so I don't find the actual
absis uh I can do the critical do I want
that now let's do it it's Critical
Hits
Mand
man wa it's probably uh oh yeah it's
probably fire their
weakness think
[Music]
logically T die
critical normal attack
kill I should ah but I shouldn't should
have kept my critical for a different
mob maybe uh oh
well fire
okay not bad not
bad not bad wait I don't have any a
critical anymore right only for one
turn y I got a critical anyway maybe for
one ah for the whole player turn not
only for one attack is that what it
meant what about
win critical what critical I'm my Turn
end ah
okay oh [\h__\h] oh oh we have one more
action is there going to be a second way
or is that
it level
up okay what you think of this skills
Dem demons are pretty cool huh
pimpa oh poison poison
skill we did it
oh that was easy by destroying an absis
the Nino has obtained magui and awakened
the vast power of
Miracles okay uh support okay Miracles
many many many am
Miracles we can now
proceed the surrounding area on the map
is no longer being blocked by the OB has
now been
revealed
okay well done young man let us keep
moving yes
uh I want to show you guys as much as
possible but
uh it takes up quite some time to read
all the dialogue and stuff time no
see s girl hello wait what's that
hanging down from the I was watching you
oh you must be pretty tough if you can
take out an absis like that I
am still you super outnumbered bet you
got a little beat up huh
no oh I know here I'll give you
this just so we're clear I didn't do
this for you or anything I just happened
to pick it up so here take it or
whatever you just don't need it right
I'm I'm your trash
can a
bead should I pull a t on her and be
like
no wait do we play the no you card
take it
okay not exactly the best way to say
things but maybe it'll help you out
maybe if you want I can find even more
for you oh okay you're like a dog then
dog young man this Demon's intentions
are unknown I suggest we ignore her and
move on I got
me hey she's just what's with the face
huh you could at least try to a lot
appreciative I I am all right I'm going
to go find more stuff then you'll see
how helpful I am and then you'll take me
with you well
okay it's a promise
okay I am overwhelmed with
[Music]
feelings that is very
cute yo get that MP hell
yeah oh oh
hey hey hey hey this place wasn't the
ner World until 20 years 20 years ago
before that I heard humans used to live
here nobody knows why this place turned
all never well wa can I not get you heyy
I guess not I thought you were a cute
demon I could
get H
okay is it fighting
time I do want to progress in the story
let's go
here okay hey hi hi you can get her
later
uh-huh oh friend dude I was looking for
you everywhere glad you're okay um how
are you okay how the hell did you
survive this I know you look different
but somehow I can feel it it's still you
in there yes it is me indeed face is the
same I got hair extensions though that's
a lot of I not they lying know that
green stripe
anywhere yes this train car is from the
yamot see I know that but if this is the
train then what exactly happened here
wak
wak what could have possibly happened to
Tokyo while we were in that
tunnel good question maybe we need to
ride the train uh oh dear maybe it's 20
years in our future
oh wait that makes a lot of sense
because of what the girl just said what
she's yeah ask that weird demon that
would mean that the world we've known
is never mind we need to focus on
getting first we need to regroup with
the other students daai was around there
too if I recall how do we go back 20
years
abducted that some kind of Angel yeah
well I suppose that decides it we should
split up and search for this angel don't
worry the truth is I can control demons
what what I'm with a group that's
working to protect the world they gave
me a demon summoning program since when
a host of demons is trying to drag Tokyo
Into Darkness and we have the power to
stop them uh I'm not just trying to
protect myself I'm fighting to save
everyone is he the real protagonist and
I'm just a fake for now let's split up
and look for daai if I find anything
I'll let you know on the app this place
is full of of bloodthirsty
demons Living Legends waiting to cut us
down but we can't die out here what what
it's
another it's another are you kidding me
for
real I have a young man I'm the side
character before we begin our search for
the Angels I would first like to go to
Tokyo Tower yeah me too
but why if I can regain my memory data I
may be able to better support you maybe
you're the real enemy Alami and if that
is the case I'm being par again will
become easier as well okay I guess we'll
go to Tokyo
Tower wait uh where the hell is
that up there which direction do I go
well there's there's
there's can I even go
up H up here maybe oh or oror along the
[Music]
Trap who's that is there something up
there
ah
ah see I have a struggle guys when this
stream is
over I kind of want to continue playing
the
game
uh but I don't I don't know if I if I if
if if I'll ever get the chance to stream
this again so maybe I shouldn't be
continuing playing the
game cuz then I would be far
ahead you know what I
mean it do be a
struggle they were trying to fight you
guys I want to show more story wait wait
wait young man wait I'm
detecting
oh hello time no see
huh two safe files H but then I would
already know what what's going on that's
not funny that's not
fun I found a bunch more stuff since
last time so now you got to take me with
you it was a promise
remember let's
go what did you find all kinds of useful
stuff so I can come with you now give me
first and then I'll think about it I'll
help you out and find all sorts of neat
stuff for you hey she's like a
dog well you see there's a certain demon
I'm looking for oh
they're kind of my other half yeah my
soulmate oh totally pretty exciting
stuff right um only thing is there's
like a million demons getting in my way
basically every
second so please you just got to let me
tag
along
okay it seems this demon in aimo has
your own
agenda let's go she must be one of the
good
ones we don't care what Alami
says let's hope we don't get scolded by
Al heading for Tokyo Tower right he's
been blocking me for too long you know
about the monster that hangs out there
though everyone calls him the demon of
the tower that's a simple name so not
very original come help and make sure he
doesn't wipe the floor with you thank
you here
hope oh look at
pose strike a pose girl strike a
pose amanoo became your quest my quest
Navigator see I was supposed to get her
after
all H Quest Navigators refer to Demons
that accompany and support you during
Quest oh but can I keep her while they
don't participate in battles what they
will inform you of items on the map as
well as provide oh is she going to be
like
heisten hello by the
way now me I've been bumbling around
these parts ever ever even since humans
were around got to say the city sure has
changed used to be buildings of all
kinds around
here oh oh you just uh
okay examine
Shea uh
safe uh
e y should we quickly head for the
uh Tower I mean we can we even reach it
no way that we can reach it ah
those we can't reach that should we just
fight these demons no I want to make
some more progress the can I go up here
oh
no I I'll try to get a little bit
further let's see oh wait this is the
wrong
direction oh it's not the it's not maybe
not the right one but it has
[Music]
Treasures
oh y yum what are these funny looking
things I like them I want to capture
them Kodama starts to speak to
you well you're totally going to die but
I'm going to give you a chance
oh a e oh no I don't want to be let go I
want to capture you it does it mean
they're really going to kill me
instantly or do I just get the choice to
fight
them it's robbery no way I won't go easy
on you okay let's
fight ah you miss so much for killing me
oops no oh there's Auto Battle
what um deal we should I talk again talk
talk talk can we just talk
let's talk let demon has their guard up
what will you do lower your guard please
fine I guess we can chat for a bit nice
your hair is so long yeah right oh my
god do you want to know where I got my
hair
done yours doesn't even
come R you like
no
no he didn't like the do no he was like
enough hey
what about you can i h i want to talk to
you
then
no how can you not be into that
stuff can I talk with you or really I
kill you before I talk to you I didn't
kill him you get to attack me once if
you
want
okay I'll get t
I want you you're so cute you're new
here huh what kind of demon are you how
will you
respond I don't even know what that
means and what that is pronounced like
but I will go with it that's kind of
creepy no what
no demons hate me
[Music]
I'm so
unpopular but there's more of them
though maybe we get another
chance oh damn that's a lot of
them talk I want
you talk to demon oh for oh
okay should we let's do
it what's the matter going for something
wrong R and no you asked
me your face is rough I mean I'm a demon
up got to make sure my face makes an
impression oh now it's out of the way
how about we a oh my God I finally made
a right
choice what should I do these these
demons you never know what will be right
A lot of my HP okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay take it take it take it
K let's have some fun
yay
[Music]
finally hi The
Negotiator is he stronger than any of my
other teammates should I have him in my
team that's
cool wait I no I wanted to go to the
treasure reach the treasure
treasure there we are are get that and
get that did I receive it 700
MAA and a and two
grimo all
right uh anything else we can explore
before we have to end the stream oh
nice fight fight that rock like demon he
looks familiar the memory isn't clear
but I believe he may be a survivor of
the battle God have XP oh don't fight
big boy level
48 our objective is Tokyo Tower I
recommend you avoid a confrontation from
C see see avoid at all
cost uhhuh okay be beak kind of enemy
punishing foes when you first encounter
these enemies your chances of defeating
them are very low challenge them later
when you raise your level
[Music]
okay uh-oh is he following me wait what
what what
what quest the beginning reactions may
make discoveries okay what did you
find what what what is it press the has
moved to the spot where they discovered
something what what what what what what
is it what is
it the dude is following me I hear his
footsteps be quick looks like there's
something here will you investigate yes
yes yes let go nice
allowing question can earn you a variety
of items items are not always guaranteed
however as you may encounter a demon and
get pulled into a battle oh consider
your current condition before deciding
to investigate okay makes
sense is he still following
me he's just
looking I think he is done with me wait
what is that uh on the mini map over
there hey hey hey hey hey hey hey oh
n hey hey hey I'm picking up something
over this way
e left Stone yo good job girl we had a
loading screen of 5 minutes so I can I
can still go a little bit what the hell
are
you what are you you ever see this rare
demons called me D you're not supposed
to be in csle constantly mods ban him
they're hard to take down not only do
they flee almost instantly their
weaknesses keep changing too
[Music]
yes yes oh Hey listen up you feel that
someone's in trouble feeling too don't
you yeah it's coming from that cat
looking demon totally cat it is a
cat oh my God I knew it it's for sure
that cat demon oh they're super in
trouble bummer so cute I mean what do
you normally do in times like these are
you the type to ask them what what's up
or whatever I guess or do you just soak
up their misery and stuff it doesn't
really look like it's a misery s Quest
oh a subquest sometimes the demons that
inhabit the neverwood will ask you for
help these requests are called subquests
completing subquests will net you
various rewards so it is recommended to
do them whenever you can spare the time
available subquest can be accepted by
speaking to Demons with Associated icon
well whatever your thing is we're
basically going nowhere till you talk to
it
right you know I just love to see that
big pout up close so okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay oh not hit yeah I am
perhaps a
travel my name is n and if you aren't in
a hurry might I ask a favor of
you I'm trying to put together a reward
for my retain you
see I would like to give them
lifestyle but I've come up short I'll
need five more
wait life stones on the off chance
you're carrying any life Stones do you
think you could spare some for me yes
before cats I'll do anything youngstar
who knows how to respect his Elders yeah
you'll find life Stones buried here and
there a demon who specializes in
searching should lead you right to them
yeah I'm counting on you my Bo yeah I
got a couple ones oh uh oh I only have
two out of five oh never mind
me okay
can we get uh wait we could try to fight
the other absis should we give it a try
maybe I find another saving point though
oh you want some well do
you hey hey hey look Speed Run speed run
the five minutes is done y uh uh I have
to fight I can't help
it no he no he's telling me my stream is
over
no no no no no
no
no didn't expect that but it was having
fun I want to play more
though I'm
hooked a what is that what is that okay
okay these look like the Musketeers what
the hell let's just check them out and
then and then and then we're going to
finish oh my God I'm 100% going to get
that demon
you are
adorable the Robin Hood cat or
whatever the demon is staring at you
with uh with burning intensity what will
you do flash
[Music]
some ah dance you you know how frog kada
was dancing he must not
resist my soul does not stir you move
into lifeless like that of a corpse you
say that to my frog dance moves
no there's still one
more
uh uh I can
pass and then I can
pass and then I can pass cuz I don't
want to kill and then I
talk talk to cat yeah you're that new
demon the whole never world is talking
about so everyone's talking about me
just what kind of demon are you now how
will you respond
he seems rather friendly I think I can
act friendly no no I'm
not no
[Music]
cat one more one more try one more TR I
can hear a voice calling me yes it's me
I got some cat you want
some I can hear it too what yeah you're
actually playing along with that huh I
like you yeah now then what shall I do
how about I take yes yes take it take it
all take it
all never give up it's the life lesson
we learned from Dad I am the Beast k k k
I look forward to finding out your side
yeah happy
de nice now we can get rid of that slime
W okay I need to find the safe point at
least um oh wait wait wait is there a
safe point
maybe Atlas summer I will just go and
find the safe Point real quick okay I I
I I really just want to a there he is
okay uh I'm just going to save
um cat team only that would be fun how
much save game
d save
game a I have to end it unfortunately
this is uh yeah I hope you guys uh liked
it there's a link in my description uh
which is kind of like a referral link so
um it will if you were if you are
interested enough to purchase the game
you should use that link because then
they will know that you H decided to get
it because of me um or through through
my ER yes influence yeah that was fun it
was my first time playing um a game of
that series H shami but so far I am
really into it I mean it's probably
going to be more difficult in the future
especially if I don't play on casual
which I think I'll switch to normal uh
in my private time but yeah really fun
interesting demons the conversations
with them are uh very
entertaining and so far I'm also very
interested in the story because I barely
know anything at all I want to learn
more candidate for next RPG series well
at the moment I don't know if I can
continue playing it but uh maybe in the
future I don't know I cannot promise
anything yeah but thank you again for
sponsoring the stream atla thank you
thank
you I am very very honored to be able to
present this game to my viewers yeah
it's my pleasure I love these kind of
jpg games very very much it's my passion
and it's my specialty so thank you thank
you thank you thank you yeah and I hope
the audience enjoyed it too you guys
were all hyped up when I announced that
I'm playing this on my channel so it got
me also very hyped up thank you for
hyping this up together M yeah and as I
said Link in the description go check it
out check it out check it
out yeah jpg Queen hell yeah yeah okay
well that's it for today and I'll be
gone over the weekend uh I'll be back on
Monday evening and to bless you with a
stream yep mhm unfortunately I'm going
away on the weekend but I think I'll
upload like a little video or something
yeah so everyone have a great time a
great day enjoy yourselves
and I'll see you soon okay and in German
we
say
a by I'll miss you guys you can uh check
out what I'm doing on Twitter hang out
with me on Twitter when I'm
[Laughter]
[Music]
lonely had fun my first smt game
thank you sh
everyone byebye have a nice weekend play
some smt 5 it since it just came out
yeah Go Get It Go Get
It I hope I didn't forget to say
anything uh uh yeah um I think I'm I'm
good yeah today was the launch day so Jo
go go go go go go go go go
C
[Music]
bye-bye bye-bye
bye bye-bye
[Music]