I need more the Healer wait do you need
healing wait can you heal Revelation did
it heal you you're the Healer I'm the
Healer actually you just full healed me
you healed four Hearts yes that's
actually
awesome and if I sink what will come of
it I shall save you by then because I am
a hero we're both walking s I'm
sinking uhoh I feel
what did you do to her he my heels I
won't die again I promise I I'll heal
you next time it wasn't your fault it
was the healer's fault don't take any
blame wait wa wait one job has one job
couldn't do their job yeah honestly name
well maybe maybe maybe I shouldn't heal
at all then maybe I'll
just he where would we be