[Music]
This program is brought to you by our sponsors.
[Laughter]
[Music]
As usual, I would like to explain this program a little bit.  This
is an interview talk show aimed at English-speaking countries.The purpose is to let people overseas learn more about Japanese talent while also talking about herbal medicine.The
host, Takanashi,
is brought to you by Chara.  It
's the 28th time! Yay, bye-bye. And
all the requests. Today's guest is
Tokoyami.
[Music] Welcome. Can you
hear me? Everyone, I heard you can hear Toa-senpai's voice. I'm
glad.
First, please introduce yourself as if you were a winner.
[Music]
This is actually our second collaboration.  Yeah,
that's right, so I'm not a little nervous,
but really, it was our first collaboration before, and it
was an off-collaboration, so I was
already excited, so we were there that day.  I'm
not nervous. He's kind. What is Tokoyami and apiter andre after? Since you're a senior, we're going to explore a lot of things today, so I'd be happy if you could tell me more about it. No, no, I don't want to. I'm
sure you'll tell me a lot of things today.
Yes.
Ok, so what kind of
activities have you been doing lately?
Lately, I've been singing as usual,
and I've been playing
FPS games. Well, I
was streaming a little while ago, right? I'm so
upset that I'm making you a streamer.
Posture: None  Are you
ready for tomorrow morning with the game?
No, not at all. There's an APEX event tomorrow.
Does it have a name?
[Music]
Yeah, I'm going to do it.
Streaming OK, everyone.
Please come and support me. Thank you for being so kind. I'm
sure you're nervous.
How many times are you going to do this, and at what pace? It
depends on the event, but it
depends on the event.  It's
something that UUM is planning, and
it's probably once every six months, or maybe once every six months.Kanako,
especially this
festival, so yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I see,
I'm
growing a team. You told me
something before the broadcast.  I'm so excited to randomly join a team.
Good luck. Good luck in English. It
hurts. Do you
have any good phrases in Japanese? Good
luck. Good luck. Good luck. Good luck.  It's
like I'm looking forward to a good result.
[Laughs]
That's definitely OK. So let's move on to the next question.
Okay, where is this?
How did Towa-senpai find Hololive in the first place,
and what was the reason for Gray again?
No.  But the door is Hololive.In the
end, at that time, I was from Sono or Reconciliation.However,
when I was in the human world, that
thing called vtubers was becoming popular,
so I guess that's why I was in the human world.  I
don't have any friends,
so I thought I'd like to have friends,
and I also like dancing, so
when I got used to 3D,
Hololive was really beautiful.At
that time, everyone's technology has
improved and it's everywhere.  It's beautiful, but
the 3D of Hololive at that time
was very attractive,
and I wanted to dance in that 3D.I
wanted to make friends, so I went to Hololive and
accepted it.Ok
Google, let's
dance, right?
[Music]
So let's do it
What, what, what, what, let
's do it I
'm waiting I wonder when that day will come I
wonder when it will come My heart is
pounding So let's move on to the next question
[Music]
Now  Until now, I couldn't say it because of the language barrier,
but have you ever been able to say it when you're overseas?
Even though
there's a language barrier, I mean, there's Passion English, so
there's Place English, so I've
already been saying I LOVE YOU.
[Music]
Thank you for finding me, hmm.
OK, I'll tell you. Thank you for finding it.
Thank you
for finding
assing.
[Music]
So, do your
best to express your feelings in personal English.
Please um
[music]
don't
speak japanese speak japanese
what you say is different from you can know
yes yay yay yea yuh
under stand torran cage
senkyu
ah this just in case  I'd
like to add an additional note: I
don't know Japanese at the door,
but I'm just trying to understand Japanese, and it seems like I'm
getting the message that you're OK.I've
decided to enroll in English.That's
amazing.Thank you very much,
Senpai.
In addition to Japanese and English, I'm also learning a bit of Korean. I
don't really study Korean that much,
but it's a
light game. I do a lot of things with Korean people,
like reporting on simple places.  can only do  I
see, but I've heard that
Towa-senpai has
picked up little words from various countries by doing things like APEX.That's right.Even though he
can't have a conversation, it's
like he's just communicating a little.It's true that if you look into it a little bit, he'll
say something all the time.
Right in front of me Right in front of me
Yeah, that's right. [Music] Things like "like" are broad, things like "
but this is what I'm trying to pick
up"
aren't really words that can be used in real life.  That's
true, is
n't it? I don't really use it that much.
Among the words used in APEX,
are there any words that can be used outside? There are
only words that can be used outside, even
if it's not Korean anymore.
Maybe the only words in English are FPS words.
This won't help.I'Mthe
I'MDeadTOURThe only thing I need is the end.I
hope I don't have to say that.What
about directions?Are you sure you can do it?
No, but I don't know.  If you
're outside Japan and a foreigner
asks you how to get to Shibuya, you can say,
well, if it's close enough, there
's no light at all.  This
is Google Maps, which gives you Google Maps on your Prius smartphone.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Yes
Is this Toa-senpai's favorite broadcast? Games, karaoke, chats, collaborations,
etc.
But I
guess it's the collaboration front.  They
joined because they wanted to make friends,
so it's fun to chat with people about game collaborations
like this,
and it's
really fun to see them all
having fun when they're planning large-scale collaborations.  I
love
it.
I love the Yuruhoro series, so much so that I can definitely say
that. That's great. Please invite me.
Yes, it's lame, but it's
okay to be lame. That's why this loose follow
is
OK.
Well, there was a follow kart conversation from 2 years ago,
but
even though I tried really hard, I
got my name.When I
said ``I got Mario Kart'', it was easy to say that
Mario Kart is unfair, so I
encountered something unfair.
It's like that,
even if everything goes well, when all of a sudden
four people throw at you different things at the same time, it
feels like you're acting like a joke.It's
times like this that you need to come up with a loose plan.  What's
interesting is that it's loose
and easy. I don't always have the ability to
collaborate. I always try to work with people I don't often collaborate with. I think it would be
fun if we formed a team. I don't
need it because I plan things like that.
[Music]  ]
[Music]
I'm really looking forward to the next night, but there
's a cutout here, it's not related,
but it's not related to cutouts in Mario Kart or anything like that, but it's so
written that there are only the same faces.
[Music]
Cute Cute
Even though you were so cute when you were a child, you said you wanted something.What did you
say you wanted? Glugaga's
panda BlueGO is the one from earlier, right? I'm
teary-eyed.  What do I want?
The lantern of the soul. I
guess I'll just say I want it.
[Music] A
family on a journey. It's
hard to move it, right?
Hey,
what is it?
[Music]
What is it? You'll
be surprised. Let's go, let's go.  Come take
a walk, take a walk,
move 2,500, and from today onwards you
'll listen to what I say.Sometimes my friends died in battle
[Music] It's too
late
[Music]
Stay here,
trial shop
[Music]
This is fine.  Isn't it
okay to use the one with the snot on it? It's
really not like this.
There's a difference. It's
cute, isn't it? I
want the lantern of the soul.
Thank you very much, see you
soon [Music] When I tried to carry him, there
was nothing there. It was
this crying baby. It
took a long time to get to the nearest place.
[Music] I
like it
[Music]  ]
Seriously
cute
Okay,
nice delivery How many times have I
felt pity for pandas being treated in so many different ways, and this is
true.
That's what I'm showering with love. It's
okay. It's only love. Did
you get that? Oh, it's here. You
gave me a present. Oh, that's nice. It's dead.
[Music] It's an
exchange.
I was really happy, and recently I've been like that too.  So I
went to get it. You
can find it pretty much everywhere. I'm not saying it's everywhere,
but what do you say
in Japanese?
Camping. Terrible people's camping. What does
mnpc mean in Japanese?
Probably
Yeah, I have a feeling. Well, if you go to her place, you'll
find that detective everywhere right now.
[Applause]
Japan's server, Japan's Colasaba, etc.
Everyone is exchanging various things. I wonder if
I need something too. Let's
go back.
Okay, here.
Okay, let's get back to the normal question.
This clipping tells me that Towa-senpai's delivery
goes something like this.
I think I got it across. It's
not good.  It
's difficult. You're kind to animals.
Even after the panda died that first time, you
did your best to get a new one. I
think it's
amazing that you didn't give up and kept going again.
OK, next up is about FPS.
How did you become interested in FPS games
?I
started playing a lot of Nintendo games like 3DS and DNS3DS.  I can
use the internet and play games,
but I didn't have a computer.I
saved money from that part-
time job.Pubg was popular at that time,
so I saved up money from that part-time job when my
friend
asked me to play the internet with him.  I
bought it there and played FPS for the first time.
[Music] I was
like, ``I won! If I win,
I'll be the champion or something. I'll be number one.'' It
felt so good, and that's why I
felt so good when I bought it.  My
seniors got pretty good at things pretty quickly
and I bought them, but I was
n't that good at all, and it was my
first time making friends, so yeah, I'm already a beginner.We
try our best and don't really have face-to-face battles, but I'm
really happy to see someone who seems like they've won.
Ah, I guess I bought it because someone else was good at it.
[Music]
Well, it's like the people around me died on their own. Was it
kind? I was lucky.
Ok, I'll translate this for now.
and
gameshaveaGOODY
becausesavings
[Music]
andred
Winning
That's how I got into it, right? I got really
good at Senkyu, but
how long does it take?
Well, it depends on the person, but I've played Door quite a lot,
but there's still a lot to do.  I'm not very good at it. I'd
really like to
go to APEX Chinament and
win. There
are other factors involved, like
reporting.
Covers, how to cover, etc. It's
you who has the results, so I think you should admit it. I
have one more question about winnings fpson,
but
yeah,
just tomorrow. I
have Ternament, so this is it.
How do you prepare when you go to an APEX match
?
[Music]
But tomorrow is a fairly casual
tournament.It's more like an event
than a tournament, so yeah, I won't be doing anything special tomorrow,
but yeah, that's it.
When there's a practice period and it's a competition like the actual competition, I'll
go for a massage before the competition, or
take a bath and make sure I'm
clean.If I really
want to relax, I'll relax my
body once.I'll be nervous,
so I'll just relax.I see.
But more than that, what I
wanted to ask was, "How long
do you practice? I
still have to practice.
[Music]
What is practice? It's like that tournament.
When it's a tournament, but definitely on that first day.  3 hours is
There's something like that Scream, that practice tournament, so it
's not like three to six hours,
it's like a month or whatever, but
it's like a week.
OkOkGoogle
[Music]
[Music] That's
amazing. I
started sneezing.
[Music] This
may have been the first time I put Bless You inside my house. It was
nice because I was always told that.
You know, when I lived in Japan, I
sneezed, but in Japan it's a bit...  I do
n't know what it is, they ignore me, they
leave me alone, I thought it was a bit lonely.So, I
can count on my hands the number of Japanese people who would say "Brassy" to me, so I decided to become
this kind vtuber who feels like she would say "A-chan" to me.  I
learned about it from
overseas, so I felt
like I learned about it thanks to the listeners overseas.
It's a word that can be used in real life.
That's true. But wait a minute, but it's true overseas, for example.  I
say something to the stranger next to me at a store.
[Music]
Well, I think kind people would say that.
Hmm.
Basically, I'll say it.
[Music]
Goodone.
That's
what happened inside me at that time.  I guess I
don't say it when I'm absent-minded thinking about other things and don't notice it.
But, well, well, it depends on the moment.
But by the way, in German, you say "
Wait a minute, it's difficult. It's
suddenly difficult."
[Music]
This actually means good, so it's
good for your health.That's right, but you'll
probably lose weight.If you
remember it soon, I'll be happy.Yes, please take care
of it, but it's true that
in the world of Japanese sales houses, you might not be told anything.  I don't know, but
in the broadcast, people
say that sneezing helps.
No, it's only the internet,
so
yeah, but it does help. I'm
happy. I'm not happy. I'm not happy.
[Laughs] I do
n't have a runny nose. It's okay. It's okay. It
's OK.  The
question I received from the viewers was that quite a few people
were interested in FPS,
so that's true.We
occasionally collaborate with e-sports streamers.What do
you like about e-sports?
Well, if you
practice a lot, you'll get better at it.
[Music]
But I think that Mario Kart is also an E-sports. It's
true that it's not just FPS.
E-sports is certainly
something like Street Fighter, and
E-sports is, after all, E-sports.  It's
like a game tournament,
so it's not a sport, it's an E-sport. What does E-sport stand for? I
think a good sport is, erm, a sport. I'm an engineer. I
write this out of love, but I think the reason why it became so good is probably
Well, I
guess that's not true. Electronic sports, electronic games, etc. Games played on a computer or something like a computer or other PS4 are fine, but anyway, I like those games, the Internet, and electronic sports. I don't know what I like about them.
Well, I like normal sports, too.Maybe I just
like fighting.Is it more fun when
there's a rival whiskey in a game where you have to fight and do your best?
But the more I love
cooperation, the more I love cooperation.
Cooperation is so true sisters
your birthday
[Music]
ICEjustthe
By the way,
if Towa-senpai
wasn't a vtuber,
Hololive would be. If it wasn't Hololive, she would be a sports professional.  I do
n't
think it would have
turned out that way.I don't think it would have been like that, either because I didn't want to do it or because I wouldn't have gone
in that direction.
But if it doesn't
go well, I won't be able to make a living, so I
guess I don't do it because I'm scared.
[Music]
liketohave
isportery
But now it seems like I'm connecting two things,
so it's fun.
Hololive I see.
Hey, what about Hololive's Mario Kart Cup?  It was
thanks to Toa-senpai that it
was held so many times, but how do you put it together?Are there any other
projects
like this that you would like to do?  I'm
sure you think it's something you have to do, but
what's so important about it?
But Mario Kart is already a normal thing
to assemble.It's
easy to assemble.Usually, the first thing you do is
ask what day it is and the time to make sure it doesn't overlap with the anniversary.
Well, Mario Kart
doesn't have a lot of lag, but it's
not like I can't do it because of the lag. When I
try to do things in Japan or overseas, when I try to use my home ID, it
's a bit of a problem.
Since ID can do that, I definitely
want to do it with all the kids in that house and ID.There's
no need for words, Mario
Kart
is an individual skill, that's why it
's a game played by one person, that's why Mario
Kart tournaments are.  All of them already
First, we asked the management about a possible date and time when all of JPenid could do it,
and then about a month or two or a month in
advance, we started
recruiting people to tell them what day they would like to do it, and
then we started thinking about it.
Once a block is decided, it's
expensive to make blocks that look good.I
can smell the illustrations, so I'm
thinking that I'll be happy if something gets excited about it, so I try it.Every
time I think it's going to be exciting, I get excited.  I'm already
helping E-chan and the management, right
now I
'm asking them to order illustrations and things like that,
but
basically the
door is the one that communicates with everyone about the script and the flow.  is doing all the work. Ah, I
see. The script is OK.
Google
[Music] Do you want to
plan a game?
[Music] I'm
going somewhere else. I saw
God Field
a little bit the other day, but what kind of game is it?  It's
really a
game like rock, paper, scissors. Rock, paper, scissors is like
water. It's said that water is strong against fire cards. Water is strong against fire. It's the same thing. When a card is played, you block it with water. I
guess it's a trading game.  It
looked just like I thought it would.It
must have been a very easy game.I
wanted to create an Anpanman project that anyone could play.
''He said, ``An
orange cat.''  It
's Godfield.
Garfilt, the
cat who likes orange lasagna. He's a famous cat. Let's look it up. But it's not Garzelda,
it's Garfield."
Hey,
who bought it? Yesterday, my
senior and,
of course, Pai also
participated.  It was
just
that, if I
asked someone to do something like that, it would be easier if I didn't participate when making a machine or something.Well, I
could have participated, but the
number of people would
be a little half-hearted.
No, I'm looking at it and I'm sure it's
your
and I see.
Ok, ok, then let
's move on to the next question.
[Music] This
is Rakuten.
What made you interested in herbs that reduce volume?
And I'll show you a photo.
This is feminine power.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
[Music]
Cute It's an
experience that I often have when I go out once, so I
have some time, so I thought I'd give it a try.Once I did it, I found it
interesting.  I
thought I'd try it at home.
Wait, this is it. I
think you taught me about it the last time we collaborated. I
heard about this, but, but, here, it would
be nice if you could tell me all about it in terms of holds. I see.  That's a dangerous experience. That's great.
When do you make it for a present or something? No, it's
when you have free time. I
thought I'd make it now, but now I
have all the ingredients. But maybe there's no oil left, so I'll join in too.
Oh, this is oil, oil, oil.  It's
all that watery
thing.
What kind of oil is that?
Preserve the flower.
But it's a real flower. Yes, it's a real flower. I
thought it was a fake, but it's a different, real dried flower. I
see,
andresqueense
[music]
and
todayspresents
[music] I see,
that cute feminine power
ISS
[Laughs] I'm
sure we talked last time about how Ame-chan Shigure
has similar hobbies. That's
great. I hope Ame-chan will come to Japan again someday.  When you
come here, how about a collaboration like that between the two of us
?
Well, I'd like to do it. I'd like to ask Ame to tell me about
that Terrarism. He showed me a photo of it,
but it
was so beautiful. Well, ice cream. It was
just the Andred who
showed me the photo.  If I remember correctly, it was
during Yakiniku
Yakiniku
indeeduction
OK, cute, cute, I want to make it too
Please tell me, teacher, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, let's
do it.
ready
[Music]
So, I like the weather, hot or cold. Eh, I like the
stapler, which one
is the main one.
New Jersey might be rare, but I
feel like everyone sells it for dinner. It's a
Loderst feeling.
Eh, I
like both, but I often eat it.
Is
it Twitter?  Instagram
Which do you like Twitter OK
Apple or orange juice
Climbing a mountain or running a marathon Climb a
Mountain Are you strong?
[Music]
Computer or game console?
Ah, I like both of them, but how long will the PC
last? Putting pineapple on pizza.
[Music] Should I choose
tea or coffee?
[Music]
But I was worried. Drinking coins.
Lately, I've been liking it a little. Especially
coffee, or rather cafes.
[Music]
Latte I
see, is it popular on beaches by the sea?
Is it common in famous big cities?
Beaches
Yes, are you naked when you sleep? Do you
wear clothes? No, you
wear clothes, you take a bath. There were a
lot of them. Okay, I'll go. I'll go to my
favorite event.
[Music]
Seven FamilyMart Lawson Which do you prefer?
[Music] I
like desserts at Lawson. Or the
phone call? Which one do you like best?
Phone call I see. I see.
Should I
give a present or
receive one? It's OK to receive one. It's true that we're only one station
away. Walking or taking the train.  Are you going to ride the
train?
What's your blood type? It's a
secret. So, the color of your pants is [music] Pink. Paint. Isn't that a secret?
Why
is your blood type a secret, but the color of your pants is a color?
By the way, the color of the pants is a
lie. I'm saying it was a lie. I was lied to,
so I guess that's what happened. The
light pink is a
lie pink. It's a
lie pink.
So, everyone, let's calm down for a moment. I
'll go take a look. I've
moved.
[Music]  ] It's
a little long, but please enjoy this
nostalgic
thing.
This time I'm going to imitate something else again.
Is it okay? I
feel like this is the only one. Right
? But this one has
n't been released anyway.  It's
not like this, it's definitely going to come out.
[Laughter]
[Music]
What are you playing?
[Laughter] It's
already talking. No, I
broke it.
It's broken. It
's okay. Move again. I'm crying.
[Laughter]
[  [Laughs]
[Music] I'm
getting all sorts of information.
Maybe it's coming from my heart, but
[Music]
I'll let you know by saying yes. No, I tried my best. I really tried my best.  So,
if you didn't understand this and that, it would have been a mistake on
your part.
Since it was discussion time, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I
thought it was an air purifier. I
thought it was amazing that you said glitter.
[Music]
Broken expressions.  I thought it was true.
[Laughs]
There's a possibility that I'll take this one off.
[Music] I don't want it to
sparkle, but let's put it
on. Let's go ahead and make it sparkle.
[Music]
Air purifier
Now.
What do you think, Dad?
[Music]
Yeah, what kind of Gion was that at the end? I thought it would be a
good idea to show some kind of difference, so I
thought I'd take the dirty stuff out of mathematics and bring out the clean stuff.
So...  I thought something was wrong, but then
something happened and I
fell asleep. That's
amazing.
That senior was so good at it, but it's
amazing how great seniors can do it
too. Subaru-chan did his best.  It was
really amazing that Tomio-chan was able to understand it.Even though it's extremely difficult, I can't do that.I
guess I don't know what kind of sound I should make properly.If you
ask me to basically look at the sounds of small things, I think
it's a little too difficult to just use audio.  What
were the other words? It was
two years ago, so I do
n't remember.
[Music]
[Applause]
How is that difficult? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
but it's an amazing imitation of Towa Senpai.  Do you
have any imitations that Toa-senpai is good at?
Satoshi is good at it, but he's
not good at it.He's not good at it.He's writing random things.He's
saying some of them.Everyone is
doing this.Everyone is doing this.Also, Shinji-kun's this.Arashi.This is a
suspicious comment.This is dead.It
moves.  Mr. I wonder
which one of those dead boxers is? Goku Goku Goku looks like he's
in pain and doesn't look like him at all. He
doesn't look like him at all.  You do
n't have to dig too deeply into impersonation.Okay, let's go next.When
did you get back?
Okay, then we'll
go back to the normal questions in the second half.The
song is loved by many people, but
where did you learn the song?  Well, first of all, I want to hear that.I
haven't really learned how to sing.I've never taken singing lessons before.The
other day, I
went for the first time.What's
going on?  You're
good at it.  It
's beautiful,
but I was told that it was too much of an effort, so I
should stop doing it. I see
. Well, that happened once or so. It would
be interesting to hear the opinions of the teachers. I see, I guess that kind of thing happens.  That's
right.
Well, I've had quite a
few people ask me
what kind of music they like to listen to in their private lives.
[Music] The
music that they often listen to in their private lives
is Disney songs. That's a
lie.  One of my
seniors asked me if I listen to rock or metal. I
listen to rock, but I really like Disney.
So for example, I always listen to songs from The Little Mermaid or
Disney songs from movies.
I heard that Daniel from New Jeans, who is currently popular in K-Pop, sang the Korean version.  It's
been played a lot. It's
cute and I like
it. I think I said something like, "
Movie
and I see, OK,
OK. I
wonder if everyone was satisfied with this. Unfortunately, it's more
like Disney than rock metal.
Sorry, I'm sorry, but it's restarted. It's
Disney.
Okay, now on to the next one.
[Music] It
seems like every time we meet our seniors, all of our seniors fall in love with them. What do you
think is the
reason for this? Tell me, why are you so popular?  I do
n't know, I don't know, I'm not that popular. I'm
not being talked about and I'm not that popular.
[Music] I'm
jealous of how
popular I am.
When the kids from overseas come to Japan and have fun, I
do something like hospitality.  Well,
for example, what kind of
thing is that?It's a little bit like that, but it's cash, but I'll
really pay for everything.I
thought it cheered you up.I
want to go see a movie, so I'll reserve a seat.
Like,
that's helpful.
Something like that. I'll buy you something to drink if you're
thirsty. I'll buy you anything.
That's the kind of feeling. That's the kind
of thing we don't do for Japanese members only when members come over.
Hospitality Japanese members treat them to food.
There are times when
I'm treated to something like, ``Okay, I'll bring something out this time, then I'll bring it out next time.''
But there are
times when people buy things like that, like Subaru-chan, etc.  She
was kind, and we were
talking about face washes, face washes, creams, etc., and she said that she had something to recommend, and said that
this store's one was recommended, and then
went over to the store and said that she
would give me a present.  Subaru-chan
seemed really kind to me, buying me things on the spot, even though it wasn't my birthday or anything.It was really kind
of me to buy something on the spot, like the door and other souvenirs.  When I
go somewhere, I buy
something, or when I buy a lot of things, or I
hear that I'm going to eat this, etc. I see, that's true. I think that
leather senpai probably conveys the image of being kind to everyone,
but he's kind.  From my point of view on the piano, I think the
reason why Towa-senpai is so popular is because he's incredibly
easy to get along with.
Even though we've never talked, I
thought he was like that.
Ah, I see.
Yes, yes, and then there's the
problem of falling in love with her just because she's cute.
Thank you.
Who is she?
[Music]
Also, she's really friendly, so I
was really happy when she made my hands all squishy.
Tiara's hands
aren't really smooth,
but she doesn't do her nails, so I
don't think they're that beautiful. They're
beautiful, so I touched them.
That's right, so that's
what Toa-senpai is saying.
Now that there's "Please," I
wonder what words are popular overseas.
Japanese
[Music]
It's a strange word, but the meaning is
Charismatic Yes, Charis Ok.
I'M
[Music]
translatestandby
say
Japanese HospitalityWhatis
Japanesehouse
the
likedraining
[Music]
[Music] There
are many reasons why seniors are loved. I'm
sorry.
Thank you for the translation.
There are many reasons for that, so I
have to do a lot of translations.Oh
yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm
sorry for keeping you waiting, but
thank you very much.I
mean, I'm loved, so I
'm a CMT, so what do you think about being called?
IhatethisHeat You
're a real angel
[Music] I
really
mean it, but I've been getting called TNT
lately, and I've been having a hard time reacting to it.Yes, yes,
once and for all, it's not TMT.  It's
getting tiresome to say that, and I'm getting asked too much about it, so it's like Akita. That's why
[music] I'm
in it because I don't care anymore
. How many years has it been
? It's been about 3 years. I'm getting tired of that, is
n't it?  -I don't think so.Maybe
people who watch Toa Senpai often
understand this, but
people who don't watch it that much may only know that,
so
please forgive me.That's
right.
[Music]
[Music] I wonder
if TNT
was a success.Also,
Chanmari also appeared, and maybe Towa-senpai too.I do
n't like being called cute.No
, I
don't really dislike being called cute, but I'm
bothered by the backlash.I'm embarrassed.
That
might be the case. I see. Ok
Google. So,
keep saying cute.
Well, that's okay.
Google
[Music] Did
you have any difficulties after joining Hololive
? Even so, you were able to
continue your activities.
Is there a reason?
Ah, Kudo. I guess it's because of the
stereotypes and ideas around me that I couldn't do
what I wanted to do.
When I joined Hololive, I realized that it was Hololive after all, and
what Hololive doesn't have right now.  I really wanted to play FPS,
but
at the time I was asked the question, at the time I was auditioning, and
at that time, I really
liked
FPS, so there weren't any people playing FPS, and no
one was entering the competition.
There was a practice period and there wasn't anything like a real competition,
so I decided to do
something like that, and I said, ``I want to be able to see people who like FPS,'' and
just go and audition.
But
when I was auditioning for that door, I
didn't say I was an idol, but somewhere
along the way I became an idol, and
now I
'm an idol.  Or rather, I would say talent.
Yes, that's true.There
are a lot of people who say that idols are
not allowed to interact with men anymore,
and it was quite painful that I couldn't easily achieve my
goal of participating in a competition.  I
guess that's true,
but I was afraid of what other people would think of me if I decided to get involved with a man.Maybe it was
tough because I was in an environment where I was afraid to try new things.
]
[Music]
But
still, in the end, I'm doing it now, so
how did you get that strength?
Ah, but in the end, I
want to participate in the tournament that my friend played.
Well, I entered.  In the
first place, I was told that this is a company where I can prepare for whatever I want to do.''So I started
thinking about it.He
said he would
support me, so I thought I had to give him that push, so I
convinced my manager, and then...
I thought I shouldn't compromise on what I wanted to do, I had to do what I wanted to do, and in the end, it was all about the effort that I put in. I
showed my efforts and won the tournament,
and the fans followed me, and I did it
properly.  I think the fact that we still have fans who support
us is the reason why we're able to continue our activities. We
also achieved results.
Thanks to that, we like doing
theWINGS
and
this
[Music]
COMETRUE
and
This
like
and  the
[Music] That's
good, that's good, I'm
glad that I ended up going the way I like.That's right, that's
good, and I guess the company is
going in that direction now.I'm
glad that I kept going.I'm
glad that they changed.  Well, I
guess I'm happy that that environment has been set up for me as well.Recently, I've been
working on the space Spring and the time now,
and the
path created by Yay who helped me with Pro SS.
Spy Wayne That's right, then Hawaii-senpai. Yes, it's
a little early, but let's
move on to sports and end with nexpressionthis
OK
[Music]
For seniors, Hololive means
Hololive,
friends,
family, and
something important.
[Music]
Amazing.  I think it's good. I
think it's
good. Thank you. I think it's good.
Thank you very much for your
support. Please also
promote it. Oh, it's an advertisement. Sorry about all that. You know, I'll
do my best with singing, and I'll do my best with games.  I
'm working hard, but I'm also working hard on my singing, and I've
released an original song called Private, which is my most recent original song,
so I
hope you'll give it a listen.Thank you.Please
listen to it as much as possible.
[Music]
Listen anywhere.  Kure
Unfortunately this is the end, but
open
Youkai ga Senpai Ii season
singing
It's posted at the bottom of this video
So I hope everyone has
learned
a little bit about Senpai
[Music]
You're a bit shy, I
guess. I'm not very good at being
embarrassed. I'm sorry. We
talked so much that it was embarrassing. It's okay, it's okay. [Music] Thank you for watching today.
Finally, we
say hello together.
OK, please let me know. Well, this one also
has German in it, and it
's called weathering.
[Music]
[Applause]
Please let me know what you think of today
on Twitter using the hashtag Holtalk. I'll
go see it, so thank you.
Seeyounexttimebye
[Music]
byOtsu