[Music]
ba another day in the
B it's beautiful this
is oh
[Music]
she's a little
bit she can't break right
now I'm a little hungry I had a lot of
food though I heard that
I I remember I
remember I was doing something great I
was in middle of great things so let's
continue that what are these though I
feel like my body is so slow right now
maybe it's just cuz I'm used to my
[Music]
horse yeah I want to do great things
today get
strong that's all right over
here oh wait okay I always have a I am
going to do the
thing oh those are all mine I thought I
took
them
huh oh what happened
okay I will still I will
still
yes I guess I forgot
them am I sure they're
mine well I was doing that wait what was
I doing that there maybe they not
mine it's why now can I put them back I
don't know if I can put them back I
thought I had more raw iron though maybe
I didn't I have 14 of the so
oh oh I can't go
away why was it like that
huh oh and I was making voice oh maybe
that wasn't mine have to maybe that was
not mine so I want to
get can I just I can't go like
that what I could do so is I'll put some
here and I'll cook maybe some leave this
there this is for whoever I took the
meat from and then this is my meat and
my
cool maybe that's
fair
[Music]
maybe oh I have more stick
here yeah oh it's
back I guess my w Crystal back we back
to
me by
and I have all food my wooden pickaxe is
almost going I have a stone pickaxe so
maybe it's okay the meat's going to take
a little while here
huh here we're
done
okay
Cobblestone let's see it's
okay what am I looking out there is
[Music]
I
don't I thought my eyes are conf
confusing me okay I have lots of iron
now let's make an iron can I make an
iron
[Music]
pickaxe how do I make an iron pickaxe
stone I have the stone one I want to
make an IR oh
God a question I need a side quest okay
M I'm I'm not too far away yes outside a
court run
yeah to
anything there we go
okay is this the library oh B there's so
many of them now what they talk to me
about my legs are always a little tired
nowadays
uh construction I have I have very much
supported of my did this one I did this
one
right are you sure about that that's the
one okay I'll do
it okay I have five let's go on
back yeah the W muscle is just a little
bit tired do do you have maybe I need
like office which is good because I'm
making mistakes so I'll just keep on
eating
those okay you this is your office did
he take
them take it looks like AIG speak to
him ah you can craft iron sh
oh okay this is your start out we're
going to do this I have sticks I have
sticks it's in my back lot in let me
just get them okay
I'll
go yes iron
pickaxe 100 coins I have
that I can do it yeah okay can I sell
can I sell these I don't need that or
maybe I still need that I don't need
this
though I don't need
this maybe I'll just use it
up now we mine everything okay I'm going
to need help to mine everything then
everything's done there almost all done
here oh was that may the sucess
was this is the one I'm going to leave
then I'll leave
[Music]
these okay I'm happy you think that yeah
I don't need the cooking pot right now
so maybe I'll put it into my
backpack good let's put the thing I
don't need in the
[Music]
backpack oh because it's in my hands
it's not why it's not good
hello there we go I feel
[Music]
threatened
back can't put it in my BT pot why
no I can't put that in there
only I can put that
there I can't put that
there I wanted to though that can go
there this can go here what else can
go I can open it I guess that's
it I guess that's it we'll eat these up
then I'll have a little bit more room
okay we're all
done I think it's time for us to go on
adventure now why are you still why are
you still fiery huh it's be look at the
need to go out M this one's done
hopefully that person finds
it I'm sure they'll be confused maybe
and then they'll check everything
around okay Adventure Time y I want to
make a strong sword and a strong Shield
and for that I think I need this the
iron pickaxe I should
probably we're going to go on
out where can I find the
Diamonds the
planes oh did I see them somewhere in
particular oh the underwater
dungeon okay for that I could use this
right this is a cage maybe not when I'm
on my
horse quickly quickly before I get
attacked I hear something behind me I
hear something behind
[Music]
me I can't figure it out
yet the coast oh no no
no oh no no
this is the way right I am going the
right way
right here just in
time okay is
it where is it
now is it around here that in the
co I still have to probably go a little
bit further
maybe melon SP into the water
maybe is that where I need to
go maybe it's just up in
here oh
[Music]
gosh okay can I stand back up that was
frightening am I am I
I'm okay
okay I don't know where any of this is
it's exciting what's this what are
you it's not
working is it working oh what is this
gold
oh I want to stand
up I feel
funny wait okay I'll just do it like
this then I'll just do it like this then
I'm very close oh but does it make me
Speedy don't Bo why am I so funny while
I'm swimming
[Music]
today I feel funny while
swimming should I make other food okay
here we
go okay why can't I get lots of this
how much of this do I need I
wonder is the blacksmith going to be
happy with
me only
two does it respawn pretty fast I
wonder there always been stairs up here
let's see if there's more oh it did it
did respawn really
fast oh oh oh oh they sinking
okay this is a pretty good area for the
[Music]
nor is this
IR should I get more gold can I sell the
gold can I make the gold into
coins this is okay for
now something like 30 okay now we just
going to take it easy here there's only
two of them here so we find someone that
has more of them
maybe why did it make a special sound
huh I'm happy about it
but okay oh I leveled up
a h up H
up yeah
[Music]
okay so I should get some gold then too
huh why why was there that sound just
now did you hear that
too what is
happening what is
happening oh my gosh it doesn't really
have any books
though it didn't work
okay why could I forget about that for a
moment why is he in the water why are
you
[Music]
there why is everybody like
this help
you he has to go
what's with
that here we
go
no it's it's a problem you have a
problem you keep on doing this to me and
it's hard to attack you have a good
sleep
I want to swim
down down down down there we
go that was a
pain just let me be in
peace I don't think he's supposed to be
underwater
back to
mining we at the gold
too it takes a while though
huh oh you
again you again live up here where'd you
go where'd you go where'd you
go just die
coming down here huh they're not
supposed to be down
here oh because it's night time
perhaps or maybe they just kind of smell
me down
here like there's a fluffy
smell I don't see anybody
so what
dog I'm not a wet dog just you know
fluffy underwater smell
[Music]
what's this how much Diamond do I have
now I
wonder 16 that's like
halfway a and my iron pick it's still
very
[Music]
healthy in the meantime I'll get the
gold
I don't know but I know I don't I'm
almost leveled up again
too
wow
yeah this a very convenient world
really but I'm underwater doing this
right now that's not very
convenient uh-oh I heard a sound again
oh I don't see any danger though
okay I better get a lot of diamonds here
is the queen planning to propos
[Music]
to my levels go up so
fast Diamond's
[Music]
amazing night
okay I want to make strong everything so
that I can be a really strong
here I don't really know how to become
that strong but if I can get good
weapons maybe a good
Shield the
criminal I'll do my
best oh
how much almost
there
a I wonder what I can do with the red
one should I get more
[Music]
iron Coss the steel chair steel I can
make an iron chair Maybe
[Music]
iron easy to get
now there's that sound
again I should look
around I hear bubbles but I don't see
anything so I guess I'm
okay H do we have enough now we have
enough now okay let's get a little bit
more gold here the gold takes a while
though
[Music]
huh Jonathan could use some company I
was feeling like I could use some
company
too that's a
coincidence oh get some extra just to be
sure okay extra
diamond oh it takes longer to mine
underwater
oh I feel like it hasn't been that long
though the G takes a little while though
it's a bit
stubborn thank
you
okay that's fine get a little bit of
this this here
who is a queen it does take a little
while
huh it does
huh oh everybody's asleep good
morning good morning good morning oh
there's so many of you
huh and now we turn
around oh no
[Music]
there we are oh hi
there there's still two of you
huh
okay now let's see if we can find any
more iron around
here if not
maybe I'll just go back to the
planes I can work over there let's work
to the PLS to the PLS the PLS PLS is
this the right place not
quite what's in here oh oh I don't think
they know this it's okay oh it's okay
I'll take a stick sticks are always good
I'll take a meat I have other meat
right Redstone Dust I have some of that
I'll take who is sheing to
marry might as well take it
[Music]
right please lick feet please
lick it's
not feet feet feet
please oh that's so fast you areer
kidding
[Music]
this
is do I need this I don't
know the feet don't work a very
inconvenient
[Music]
times oh I can't go this
way
then it's time to get out of
here I don't know
okay please go please go please
go there we
go wait if I my
potato and what can I buy to make more
money so
fast wow
so fast of course there's
more go go please still owes me my
money there we go I hear
[Music]
somebody my to
the once I get a little bit more I feel
like the iron is very helpful so I
should probably get iron lots of
different Iron things
is it over
[Music]
here I don't need to you fall
down
yeah how much iron is there oh that's
quite a bit that's quite a bit let's get
a little bit more there we
go
really okay
just a little bit more I'm not
greedy don't need lot since I have a
diamond I still feel like you know the
iron has been very good to
me oh this is all gold
here now I'm getting a little bit too
excited
maybe gold gold gold wow it's so much
faster R you right
building what's this one is this
cool I love my
[Music]
pickaxe okay this isn't where I wanted
to
go okay
there we
[Music]
are let's see how this looks
done
seen is
this what why is we're all losing hope
so hopeless I maybe I have to go turn in
the quest is that what I have to do
now now now is back from a little nap
there oh maybe this isn't
it let's
see I don't know if this looks
[Music]
like I've never seen her are you she
Queen I can make those I made those well
I'm glad for you I talked to
you I helped them
right you're welcome I finished my quest
did I
not I'm trying to okay yeah
but we need to prepare for it
no oh okay I finished this Quest
right should I disappear before or maybe
I can just do this
one perfect
okay let's
go we can do this one easy
now okay there's many people yourself
okay let's make
it this got the wi is
de
ba let's see while I'm making this I
guess I could probably over here I use
all my
coal like
this and then like this and
then is this how we do that someone who
kissed me
okay well we can do this
right why did she die hopefully this
works diamonds don't need that okay
a okay in the meantime let's go to my
bag and we'll go like that and then like
[Music]
that there a little bit of
let's go I'll just kind of boil I'll
boil their pool and I'll give them some
more meat
Al that's why is good but what
happened she died from a
misunderstanding that's
it I got it I got all five is Tam Gander
alive
still okay I can now make gold
tools okay but I don't need that yet I
like my iron ones I guess I'm done I'm
done that
Quest
okay ah not this one okay up back we go
back we
go there we
go the one that P
uh uh I can take this for
[Music]
now okay and I can make the diamond
tools but this
time oh just like that oh yeah
ba oh I ate something
okay Throne the throne okay do I have
the stain bones I don't think I
do but how do I make a shield what is
this I guess I could do the other side
quest and I'll find
out it's
unbreakable I want the blue soy I need
to make some money so maybe I should try
cooking some
soup how do we get the stained Bones the
stained bones were from the really hard
stains I
think I have four he needs how many
[Music]
okay St it's okay we'll get that a no
sign do I not have any of my chest
that's right I haven't checked my chest
let's go see my chest take a look at
it it's pretty peaceful in theal today
huh
wow how about you
hello hello
hello oh my goodness so many customers
so many customers to be
rich I don't have much money so you're
not getting anything for
me
that
wow wow oh that's dangerous she has she
stabbed you in your h no she's G oh
[Music]
must this is amazing the queen queen
ouren beloved Gander Tam
Gander I taking a gander at Tam Gand
Gander you are gandering upon
Gander I think you could use some
flowers at the Queen's feet though know
oh yes she should she deserves flowers I
will get flowers her FL
flow it's beautiful will get a few
flowers wow I'm going to go check my
chest oh oh we have oh chickens oh I
want in I want in oh I got some eggs oh
is that okay for me to take the
eggs
ah how do I get in can I just jump up I
like if I go in can I get out let's
hope yeah
what's in here oh lots of eggs maybe I
should put them in here that would be
the kind
thing I got out okay that's
good
this there we go oh gosh oh
no what the heck and
then right here
where w
yes this is mine no I love
freebies no this is not mine is it mine
is it mine which one's mine this one's
mine this one's mine why is all funny
huh why is it all funny huh oh there it
is no this is not mine but wa are
mine no no no this isn't mine this
wasn't mine and I had Violet and start
again again what is this a good business
so far for you get the
bones okay I'll take the
bones is this a so far mine was under
the sound block yeah I thought though
that maybe that's good it was supposed
to be here you have meat too let's see
meat and Beres I'm hungry that's
wrong I need to cook
it okay it's still there okay I will eat
it's still there okay good good good
good good good I should probably
remember to take some of my food next
time supp well let's take some potatoes
and some carrots and I can get rid of
this
later do I need anything else to make
some
soup thank you yeah I don't have any
bones but I I B I borrowed some bones so
that's good right I'll just put them in
my backpack for now bye and they go
anything else to go in goodbye I can put
that in for
now extra steak is good and all
but
okay let's go take a look how things are
going what ouch ouch ouch that's a
that's
W okay
wow everything's wow wow this is
beautiful
here
hello oh gosh ouch that's not so
beautiful can I go on
in oh what's in here what's in
here wow more bones do I do I need how
many bones do I
need I have 10 I have more than enough
[Music]
wow a sign
again
wow what's beautiful in here there's a
an O
head I'm
[Music]
drowning
danger wow I love it
here but all my own is kind of
lonely okay ouch ouch ouch
okay let's go back to the
[Music]
smiy here we
are yes yes potato
salad no it's all done of course no in
here
yeah I'm glad I have a bunch of
coal that's a lot of iron and then this
isn't mine and there's nothing
there okay so for the sword I do have
now enough bones I have enough diamonds
I don't have enough money so let's go
get this we'll take the potatoes the
potatoes too potato salad let's try some
cooking not that
[Music]
one moving
house ah
Lai I don't know what that
is say some
stains that could be easy that could be
good
money let's go do this
a blue Jem that would be good for
later
okay okay everybody gather
around yeah where's a bunch of
[Music]
them there's not many around right now
are
there maybe pie is coming to this land
more and more
everything I don't see many of them
maybe I'll just get them one by one oh
here you
are off the
horse oh gosh why did it not
work
revoltion okay good good good
good there we go oh almost done
Pig are you fighting the
pig somebody's
there oh
gosh
no
what are they fighting each
other did I do it already I caught them
all was that
can jump and hold I get so nervous
though I just swim
wildly okay check can I check
I
ah I don't know did I do it check my
book and my to
no no
okay to is it the to I want to
ATT
hey let's go away let's go away let's go
away let's go away let's go
away yes a three
more I can't get maybe he'll still be
there oh he is indeed still there I
should eat some
first
[Music]
okay I need some food I let's eat this
first okay let's try
not
oh holding it down is much better
huh okay do I have
enough wow okay there we did it
[Music]
trying to get better at
killing
wow I'm strong
now
w wow
I just destroy
everything nothing scary except a
bit wow he just
disappears come back
here you're making me look silly
now there we go there wasn't
many
yeah oh my
gosh there we go okay maybe it's time
for me to leave though see it's all
good yeah
[Music]
okay I should put some stuff back away
my back door this into
there this
this into there I don't know what to do
with the HIDs
[Music]
yet what this this meain
though what else did I need I only need
a little bit more
coins
okay
hopefully I can get just the light
amount of money I'm good oh did wait
wait wait wait I finished did I get any
[Music]
money
a
accepted
done I
did why who do we turn it into
though I'm the quest Master okay let's
go
my bag is too full yeah I have I think I
have a bunch of items in the to right
now so we'll check that in a moment is
this where I wanted to go
no this where is the entrance again
where is the entrance again
entrance okay not
quite there we
go you no
[Music]
huh my quest it's the quest
Master he was right beside
me what's
this oh it looks
different why did you tell me H H where
the
master there we are
y 100 coins I need two more
coins okay I'll stop
there
Mo
B Mo could I have two coins two coins
two coins
[Music]
can I have I don't know I feel like I
could depend on you for two coins right
I can give you some pork
chops I like how do I
TR just two coins just two coins you
want that not 76 three coins would be a
76 I'll take 76 too I don't have much
money I want them I don't know how to
keep them oh I could cook them for you
and then bring them
back okay if you can bring me
back give you that wow
okay are you sure you want this I do one
moment please one moment
please uh uh why is it like this that's
garbage one moment one moment please
don't go away you need
space I'm
panicking okay garbage this garbage my
inventory
is I'm the problem Oh what
really okay I'm not a problem anymore oh
pray with me
please what it says I can only have one
ofe any
time oh
that's
disappointing you have a trade request I
don't where is the trade request show
up accept except oh there we go
okay
Exel
oh thank
you I will I will okay bye by
a okay I can do that right
now she wants pork Toops not
sticks so I can do that there and then
there there we
go and then over here I can do more of
this and then no now I have enough light
I just need my bones out
grab the bones
out I should probably put a too many
things that's enough that's
[Music]
enough yeah I got my diamond
sword I don't think I need any other
Diamond things why I just need a good
Shield
[Music]
B look at
me b
now my hat is also very silly it was a
present from Jonathan which I very much
appreciate but maybe I could
get a cuter H but I think I need money
for that huh well I'll take the co back
too
please actually well maybe I don't need
to make
copper let's open up this door there we
go yeah
did I finish the quest for the diamonds
I did
right
shopkeeper can I sell stuff to the
shopkeeper
a this is what you have here
huh surprise I don't
we I
can I don't want this can you take
this he willon take it drag stuff I
don't think either I'm not doing it
right or he's really
stubborn I don't think
so oh maybe stuffy has in Stu let's see
then carrots oh
[Music]
uhh I don't think you'll take any of
them
cuz it won't take the gold
[Music]
either so anybody else inside potato
salad will you buy my stuff good enough
for b no you're just going to talk to me
Chef
sh oh I feel like like take a recipe
book that's very important also take a
this egg and be
my eggs look a potato salad where's the
recipe recipe book like why to
use why I can make baked
potatoes wait oh D makes a potato egg
carrot I have no egg I don't have beet
yet oh now this will make
sense Seafood Diamond
wow there so much I can make oh
butter wow I just don't know where a lot
of those ingredients are by
T is there anybody that will take my
items oh W that's expensive I just want
to get rid of these ones what you buy
what you
buy what you buy should I plant the
potatoes
B I don't care about those sick bead
what's in this I don't
know door should be open
oh I could do Quests for money yeah I
was just thinking you know instead of I
guess I should just put all my old
weapons in the garbage
but I want to
keep it's kind of lonely you
know they worked hard for
me I don't have a better ax so I going
to keep that I don't need this one
i s them
to a to pun you
[Music]
mean maybe I
can I'll go ask
you I could put them in sit for
safekeeping that's
why there a behind
you
by I heard theion that you will buy my
items that I don't need
anymore you this this is a some game of
telephone that went wrong I I'm not
Shing that one oh you w well if I ask
nicely will you cuz I have a very very
uh wonderful wooden axe and a wooden
pickaxe has been well loved that could
use a new home and your home looks like
a good home for them
right sure
you sure I'll take what's that what was
that just now maybe I should make more
potato wood wooden tools yeah at this
day and age I don't have much money so I
I would expect some money for my well-
loved items oh I'm so sorry but there is
a recycling fee it is one point per
item never mind
that never mind that doesn't sound good
can I interest you in the juiciest of
berries or the highest quality of meats
meat free
berries yes this sounds
scary it's not what's in
it what's in it berries and meats what
kind of her foods are very delicious and
I have had my tummy full of it you the
berries I have a lot of things though a
Mo's always looking for food maybe she'd
be
interested she already took some oh
really is it free trust me it is
completely free nothing weird is going
to happen absolutely nothing weird is
going to happen I'm not going to she's
just a good heart believe her I'm I'm
not going to feel sleepy right no you
will not I don't know something's funny
about your voice there is nothing funny
about my
voice I'll give him my I don't know I'm
getting a weird feeling deep down would
you like to know the secret the reason
why is free okay why the reason is
because we are in competition with the
fart the fart prices are just simply not
fair so we have lower prices to
encourage people to come to this
establishment they have ruined the
economy in our lands and she is merely
trying to fix them again I'm here to
balance everything out and the juice is
free the berries and the meat you can
make it into juice I could do it for you
oh I'll I'll accept the juice the juice
wait do you want the meat to become
juice or the berries to I like berry
juice berry juice okay I'm I'm going
to I'm going to support yeah all righty
I chewed them and made it into juice
would you like some okay I'm not too
sure of how hygienic that is but I'm
very clean I accepted the wrong Quest
okay here I'll throw in an extra oh I
don't
room really really
really that's okay I can hold on to them
or you know
what I will take one of your wooden
tools oh really to encourage you to come
back and see me again okay to take more
berries or perhaps get a taste of the
juiciest of meat this you can take you
can take this just one just
one just one
[Music]
okay pleasure doing business
a thank you oh you're behind there now
too oh it doesn't look so scary in the
daytime yes aren't you both wearing the
same hats aren't you both working for
the same guil you should be able to
trust her no I I received this H from
Jonathan you know it it's only
kind yeah it's only kind to wear present
that you get right M Donathan will be
happy I don't think it look that cute
though is is a proof of someone's uh
realness realness I changed the
conversation topic too early oh God I'm
so
embar what what's wrong before you go
can I interest you in a lottery ticket
it is completely free first 20 people
who take the
tickets win is that it's free it is
completely
free it where you are in the queue but
first 20 people take ticket
win don't worry about it this Lottery
there's no scam involved there's no why
do you say it like that that's very
scary no it is true I have bought a
ticket as well and received it safely no
I've seen what kind of things that M has
been up to oh you're not spending any
money money there that you thank you for
the juice
b i they kind of scary B no I'm noral I
was just making what was I doing again
oh gosh what why would you put that
there huh what does the sign say jump
over it oh gosh it didn't work what does
the sign say gosh open why can't read
that okay what was was I doing again I
was getting eggs was that what I was
doing are you oh egg where's the eggs
where's the eggs have they not been
laying
eggs what are you doing being all
silly I want to slash them but I'm not
I'm
not I'll just take some my
[Music]
the chickens are making me
Snee the grave was never completed maybe
that's a good thing maybe I heard
stuff
ba the potato salad I got egg I have
potato I have a little bit of pizza
sometimes my ears are strong
let more
beats
don't bone and fried stain a bit of a
muffle a a bucket C was looking for the
buckets I don't know what to do with the
bucket cuz I stole
it sugaring oh that's right if I find
more Coco I should give her the pork
tops right I
okay a for
recipe potato egg carrot PE it's all in
my
bag carrot
potato I need some more be be that's be
right this is be be only makes one okay
I can store the tools that's what I was
doing thank
you okay and you
go I need this still I think there I
don't have another one of those you can
go in there that's right I got the
gift
okay I'm kind of suspicious of this so
I'm just going to put that
[Music]
there and I still have a couple bones
but I don't I don't think I need them
right no maybe I need them I want to
make a
[Music]
shield put this right here and then this
way here oh I can't do that right now
can I not move this there we go this can
go back here and
then this can go back
here and then this can go here and that
go there and then this there and then
yeah
okay sweet B maybe we're good
now I don't want to go that way I went
the wrong
wayf to I don't know I put the iron in
the gold that's true I'm not using it
right now when I go back I'll do that
okay Help
Wanted did I do it
properly I want to talk to
you help want the
tower what was I doing
[Music]
again I wanted to make the potato
salad that's
right right I wanted to go to the
garden thank
you I should probably look at my mou I
don't remember where this
is I feel like
maybe it was over here oh it's so
beautiful where was it I definitely need
to look at the
[Music]
map let's see I don't need this right
now oh I thought I poed the
to
oh no is a burn to death is watch
[Music]
okay is this the garden I didn't need
the map in the end oh my
goodness okay maybe I
can be how make butter where's the end
oh gosh oh gosh this is dangerous this
is dangerous I need to eat some
[Music]
food those are for more oh I can't
those
okay no dangerous bushes and here we
are maybe I shouldn't be using my
Revelation like
that is this more than enough H let's
get lots maybe we should get more
potatoes
too and let's make sure to plant it
back there we are oh my gosh that's too
many seeds
try to
make there
go 20 be Roots my carrots I had a lot of
carrots I just need some more potatoes
where are the potatoes
[Music]
at
potatoes potato
[Music]
oh
more that's right I have I have
something for you where'd you
go
[Music]
huh Maybe just
disappeared that was be know I'm really
sure that was W just
now where's the potatoes this looks like
wheat
[Music]
ba well maybe I'm good enough with what
I
have I wonder why moreo pooped away from
me
let's
see I wanted to make I
have then
I H let's
see I have enough I have enough we'll
try to make some right
now I need to use the cooking pot
there you are
M why did you pove away like that before
huh I would like to give you your pork
chops now okay give me a moment I'm
making slime
jum I'm waiting give me a
moment do you know how to make bread
I've never made bread but we can make
bread
together I guess you need wheat do you
have wheat I have I think I have some
wheat
I don't have it with me right now though
I'm waiting
okay
up there we
are three three one I have
steaks do you want
steaks whatever you have a I give you
more money you can give you can give me
more money yeah okay well I'll give you
those
do you won't I only have a little bit of
wheat right now if you show me how to
make bread too I'll give you my wheat
make
bread okay are you going to give me some
money I don't have much
money
yeah now I have 9999 money not 9999
money I have 999 money yeah thank you e
that was like four times the money I
had
wow now I have some more food I haven't
made potato salad before can you show me
how to make potato salad you
[Music]
need I have the maybe I should go get
the quest
though do I have the quest I don't think
I have the quest construction house
stains oh D visited
[Music]
I'll oh there's a bunch of we're
visiting the dungeons deliver potato
salad to the quest Master let's accept
that can I make that right now just with
my cooking pot is that how it works I
don't
know how I used the cooking pot before
and
car H what else did I need
[Music]
potato I
need
potato okay I have
care there there
there
there is it doing
it it heal a lot and
it is it doing it did it do
it does it get help you
again mining just make a bunch and then
keep on giving it to
him Quest
Master Quest Master Quest
Master
accept accept the
quest
accept
yeah do I need to talk to him again
hello hello
no wow I just get a bunch of money that
way
[Music]
accept accept it but I finished
it do I need to talk to him again
um I have the iron right oh okay 1 2 3
oh
gosh
hello hello oh I don't have anymore
I I get
[Music]
it oh I need to put them all back in
there I guess that makes sense where did
they all go where's the
quest huh
[Music]
did I run
out where they you go Oh in my book
[Music]
a
byby I have a bunch of things in
here mutton
M
[Music]
Chien is it
okay
potato
egg and carrot make make make I can make
one more after this and then I can just
do the the cycle over and over and over
again right
make
okay Ah that's why it gets angry at
me that makes
sense I can just sit here and do this
over and over okay yeah got
[Music]
money is this
okay I can I'm making so much money but
I have to pay money for it is this the
potato salad
[Music]
gem this is how everyone's so rich
ah I just I'm not that rich oh no more
potato salad no more potato salad
okay we go to the to we receed the items
oh only a little bit
left
[Music]
okay oh
B did you want to get a strong weapon I
have a strong sword do you I do how I
got diamonds see
look and I have gold too
[Music]
uh I can't I can give you some
diamonds actually though maybe we can
figure out how to make a
shield and then I can go with you and
help you find some
diamonds I can make my sword even
stronger is there one for a shield
lais La
yeah I need to get that as
[Music]
well
in what
shovel oh I have a wood shovel no I have
a wood shovel
no
except I have a wood shovel no oh I have
a stone
shovel
[Music]
silly my St pickaxe oh I have a stone
pickaxe no
yeah oh I put it
away I put it
away I don't have it with me
okay I have so many quests right now
iron
axe there's a bunch of things I could
do does anyone want me to make a shield
I want to make a
shield how do I make a shield though I
don't know how to make a shield I don't
count see had a shield
right make room in my
[Music]
inventory ba ba
oh ba Jonathan ba haveed hello fluffy
good to see it's good to see you a
pleasure to see you
[Music]
today we have just revived Miss Nissa
Raven cross I make a
shield a shield seems you may need some
iron and and some uh I will make one for
you guys oh really problem let me see if
I have any I have iron I have iron too
you have some iron I do but at the
Smithy he doesn't make she F welcome my
cat gathan you are quite the kind KN
Jonathan it's
Jonathan Jonathan with a jeans is
Jonathan I will go get it I will go get
it what
leg run
leg my w muscle is too weak for
this gu behind
[Music]
you we are quite worried about her
okay here you go I will trade
you really Shield
oh thank you should I give you
some oh thank you yeah it's not much
kindness everything I can't accept it
one moment I have garbage I have garbage
I will I will trade you of a shield okay
thank you okay garbage this
garbage for you garbage
garbage I
okay okay to make extra Shi there we go
this is the only Shield I feel like I
might break it I will do my best
as thank
you
your
wow it is looking for the
princess we are party call still let me
call hello
it's not the cutest but it's good to be
safe this means we
we have you done one of the party boxes
before no do you want to do it together
you just want me to spend my money a no
I have some money now so I wanted to try
it okay okay let's go
see okay it goes in your off oh like
this like that
I guess that makes
sense chop keeper CH keeper I don't have
for I have I have
space I'm going to get two two of
them I don't know if I like how it
looks I bought
one okay you bought one yeah let's open
it together then
okay three two
one oh click to choose click to
choose okay which one are you going to
choose
M let's ose the same one the middle the
middle
one okay three two one oh what oh oh oh
from here
ohu is this really good there's so many
hats every
[Music]
hat what should I
pick this is the one that bees you
had I want this hot too but I really
like this hot too this hot looks very
beautiful too isn't this good I can
choose whatever I want
no
ah I got which H should I grab can I
take them all but no it it shows you
what what you have it shows me what I
have
I got a construction box did
I did
I I can I take them all is this what I
get all of
them it's in my
inventory huh I still confused do I get
to get them all oh this is the hat that
I got
a I thought I got them
all that was a surprise but I got them
blue okay I'm happy I like the blue hat
too wait what is what is I
got has achieved a new Global high score
of 100 what what what
Isen May the L
Dar what is going
on I'm going to do the other
one that just this one
oh that wasn't
it oh construction supplies
[Music]
box oh choose the ones to
receive I don't know what this
is
yes that was
fun I look pretty cute no I suppli you
didn't get any
hot I'm going to do one
more um which one should I
[Music]
choose I'll choose this
one oh I was
close
Okay where it go I don't know about that
I just use a lot of
money did I not receive it this
[Music]
time I check the
tone what should I get this
time white blue thy sounds good
[Music]
okay my
yeah I like the blue hat but it s I
[Music]
know I need
diamonds H I'm going to go do you want
to go together
m h let's use the
warp wait wait wait wait
wait okay we will warp to the
coast PLS the
coast is it just one that says Coast PL
the coast points the coast okay let's
[Music]
go
yeah now we just have to find before
before before I was mining underwater
but it took a lot of
time so let's try and find somewhere
good but I have I have something make
mining faster oh really yeah
oh I think we went backwards let's go
back
what is this the
cost I'm lost
again I think it was underwater here it
just takes a little time are you there
there you
are we can find a better spot I think I
need some more
W what you're a little far
away I don't think this is a good area
no it's not the
best
[Music]
yeah let's go to the coast
yeah one the co
the
coost over here
M huh right
here
this oh you're already
here let's see let's see if there's
Diamond around
here underwater is not the best
let
see your entrance
[Music]
yeah it's lonely
here here here yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah where are you I'm going down into
the dungeon area I don't remember where
that was but I'm hearing scary
sounds was over this
way there's lots of stuff here it's
taking up M where are you I'm at the
dungeon entrance where was that
again how'd you get there so fast huh
[Music]
swim is this what it
was
maybe I might have found it
this
way there you
are you're right
here right here right
here I bless you do you see it yeah I
got
one
yeah I'll find more here's some more
over
[Music]
here here's more
are you allergic to
Diamond is D yeah oh there's a bunch in
the walls over
here too yeah yeah that's what you
are can't
[Music]
see there we
go oh my goodness too much dust there's
gold here too oh what's this blue
one is
this no no what is it Lai I'm looking
for that
M yeah I want
that I made a good sound I don't know
why probably you leveled up oh maybe I
was surprised too at first I want more
lapis Lai the diamond's good but
diamond oh you can take that you can
take that this is a good place for you
I'm going to find more of the
lapes there it is is there any more
spots with more of I
wonder is pretty good though and it
comes back so
fast yeah come
on and there we
go try going up up can I go up
there I already have so much Mo what
wrong
[Music]
where are
you go
up
up look
there
diamond
[Music]
diamond should I
make maybe I should make
[Music]
one
more and
then where's the
potato okay I can make
one yeah okay and at least then I got
rid of the egg I guess it took up space
though how much Diamond do I
need
a okay this goes into the backpack I
don't need that this goes into the
backpack
um I can put more in C it in and then
this goes
in that can go
in okay and let's see what's in my
to my blue
Dy
okay let's
see how do I get up there
[Music]
I don't know if I can reach up
there maybe I'll just stick to on the
ground wait how do I get I don't need
anym be nice to have lots of it it's so
blue pretty the diamond's pretty but the
lapis L is even nicer your lapis look
really
maybe you can just bring it back for me
cuz I don't have enough space Oh wait I
do have space you don't have a backpack
M backp you have a backpack
backpack I don't know if she has a
backpack
wow there's so much of it even more than
the diamond
[Music]
are you talking to
someone no sometimes you know I just
kind of hear a little bit of Whispers
here and
there don't have a
back go like this where are you I'll
show you my
backpack I'll show you my backpack of
course okay
you're just standing there Sim look my
backpack oh I can't take it off my back
you don't have a backpack then
huh maybe we can make one together what
do I need for it ah it wasn't that hard
what did I need for it I can't remember
anymore but if you have one then it
makes everything easier
let's
see
okay I got to get a little bit more
Diamond
here is there
area oh what was that did you hear
that there was like
a this is the area that has the most
oppos there's
where is more
Diamond maybe I
should you should get quite a bit of
diamond okay I have 64 oh you have more
than enough
then okay so we head back then I'll get
more
[Music]
gold should the gold is so shiny
here did you get gold no you should get
some gold too oh you don't have
space well there's a
[Music]
lot okay so we get going done
okay okay let's use our warp all right
okay and back to
the H theal castle theal castle
yes
okay do I need a quest a quest oh
there's a bunch of
quests what quest was I doing I guess I
could do the lais no
be
accept obtain 10 I obtained 10 do I need
to talk to you or do I need to talk to
the
[Music]
smiy I guess is that
it is that
it I didn't read it maybe I should have
read it
ah bring some over enchant some weapons
blacksmith Apprentice
okay okay got it got it got
[Music]
it yeah that's a lot of money
did he take all of it from me though
what are these other he took some H I
have a lot
though technically I could just go back
and forth right and then I could get
more of the
boxes I don't want to get rid of all my
laisi
though
laisi oh we have been SE researching the
properties of Enchanted
tools oh
but without out those specimens to study
could you
[Music]
bring a gold shovel enchanted with
efficiency
three I don't know how to do that are
the enchanting tables by The Apprentice
oh I don't need to do
that I don't have a gold I guess I can
make a gold
shovel well let's try it out
I could enchant my sword I would like to
do that let's try this right here
right you have five Ste with you
oh I do I
do okay one moment I'm right in the
[Music]
Smithy I put this
here should I do this
[Music]
okay
one this is the best one
no sharpness
too why not this
one sharpness four or five do I need to
put more in I can't put any more
in should I not do it with this one
yet look at this one
[Music]
wow it's even more
blue
okay what were we doing what were you
asking I want the the stain H oh the
stain hind
okay what do you need them for Quest
what
quest I haven't done that Quest before
can we have five you can have five but
[Music]
oh the backpack maybe I did do that one
then you need
five there you
are you have money I could
have thank
you okay is the there's nothing in this
one
right
nothing I wonder
I I did them if I'll be back St height
can I wait wait did you not give me
stain Heights I gave you stain
[Music]
Heights it's probably in the box and you
didn't open it huh ah it doesn't
work bless
you yeah I need to sell the potato salad
that's
right
uh what did you want me to do again oh
can I have another
uh one moment more COC I'm
thinking
uh
H what did I need to make
again gold shovel gold
shovel gold shovel gold shovel shov for
anything uh there's a
quest okay and then please I need a
backpack I didn't I give you enough
what happened to the last
[Music]
backpack can I get more
money that's a lot of stain HIDs
Mo can I get a 300 no 100 is good I want
to buy more of the boxes
oh is that you problem or me problem
[Music]
one
second just wait a
moment there we go and then here we are
how much
more what do you
want level requirement 30 did my levels
drop okay I thought I was level 30 what
happened can I have Ste now too much
please okay one
moment oh I use
levels is this what he wanted what did
he want level
three level
four I'm
[Music]
waiting
efficien efficiency two efficiency
Two Three or above okay
okay where are you
okay One Moment One Moment One
Moment
Um this can go there and
then okay you wanted the heights right
[Music]
yeah can I have more money
please you want five yeah yeah can I get
a bit more money it's okay for
now
okay I am more
levels how can I level up
faster I can go sell I can go sell this
can I put wait can you not put the storm
gate key and stuff like that in the
back maybe
not I need to take the quest on
[Music]
okay took it away
good what else should I
do I need to go level maybe I should go
I get more of the will use it for my
backpack if it needs
it what was that
M no I just don't know
let's go this
way if I go and get some more of the
diamond I can level up fast
right time to test the
sword there's no enemies here though I
want to swim
faster that are killing the stains I
think the diamonds is the fastest way
right oh I'm sinking
I do have steam
just what's going
on where am
I should I explore here maybe this is a
wrong
place that was
scary where am I
[Music]
don't get stuck down there that's
probably a good
idea come on swim swim
swim let's
see is it
over over
[Music]
here am I going backwards I am going
back oh
[Music]
I hope I can level up soon I guess I
need to to m a lot
then takes a while to get there
[Music]
H down down down
oh there's so much here the lapis was
really but the diamond is fastest to
level
l so let's do the
oh okay my iron pickaxe is getting a
little tired
huh it's helped me out a lot
so only makes sense I
maybe that wasn't
okay I just curious I didn't mean to
break
[Music]
anything I don't know I thought maybe it
was
special turns out it's
not diamond
diamond diamond
okay is around
here Diamond
diam does the red stuff
help let's see oh it does too this
is let's just level
up almost at level 30
so then if I'm a higher level then I can
do even more special
stuff this is a good spot good good
good let's
see okay level
30 my diamond how much gold do I need I
see the levels of the currency for
enchantment
[Music]
a
okay right fish is faster that I can
mine it all
right but I think my iron pickaxe is
going
to we're going to part way
soon that's okay we'll do this until the
very
[Music]
end and then maybe I should make a
diamond
pickaxe should I do that is there a
point to do
that there's lot of on the ceiling but I
can't
get
byebye then it's unbreakable
okay
okay it's even
quicker I feel like my iron pickaxe has
done a lot for me you know
is there an area in
h let's use it to the very
end oh I can enchant the pickaxes
too oh oh oh b b there's gold oh there's
Gold on the Ceiling there's gold
everywhere oh there's other areas that
have gold
too you can reach it
yeah
gold there was another area that had a
bunch of gold I can't remember where
that was
[Music]
oh is my inventory getting very full I
had imagine so
but Snee when she comes into here right
oh it
does let's see I'll take a look
oh I can ignore that best to ignore
those kind of
things I think the pickaxe isn't going
to make it very much
longer the last moment can it make it to
33 oh goodbye thank
you oh I got crystals
where
oh that's kind of cool I need
yeah
okay
okay let's
go I'm here for lottery ticket and
nobody is
here I guess I could just work back now
huh let's go oh there's a one for Coast
just directly
po the best Castle there we
[Music]
go
okay there we
go now I was going to do this and finish
the
quest it was this one lottery ticket to
finish the quest
[Music]
yeah okay I need to
call did it
work do I need to talk to you oh that's
my I am here for tickets in person and
you take a magic
feather okay should I go turn it in
Magic
FEA in the guild construction area yes
I I can fly in my land is that okay
though chicken chicken game okay let's
[Music]
see I did
something oh this is the wrong one just
one not going to congratulate
me can I
buy is there anyone that I've I've
accepted this one wood shovel to the
quest Master did I have one in my
backpack oh okay get free can I have
wooden shovel wooden shovel no wooden
shovel do I have any wood on
me no what
I'll I want to finish the quest cuz it's
kind of annoying let's just go to the
planes well
[Music]
maybe the forest a forest has wood well
do I have an ax that's a question don't
allow me to buy tickets anymore so I do
wait what am I making
a I can never
remember where did the axe go there it
is
what a wooden shovel
okay I feel like somebody's
behind oh nobody's
there okay to make a wooden shovel how
much wood did I need
again inventory is quite full right
thank
you okay let's just get a little bit
more
here I came here for nothing
this tree is quite
amazing did I get my
wood is it in my to is 18 enough it's
not in my
Tob is this why I'm not receiving
it let's put away the blue
tie put this here and then this can go
here let's go back that's why
huh Maybe should get some more stain
HIDs
huh my wooden ax is doing its best and
everything
too there we
[Music]
go well let's use it until it's G then
help
on there we go
[Music]
see why cutting the wood it doesn't
really do much for my level
[Music]
huh there we go back to the city for
us to the best
castle and we were making a wooden
shovel was that it I keep on forgetting
thank goodness you're here
Wen
shovel Oak planks H that's right how do
I make that
again planks no that's not
it o planks planks Oak
planks
[Music]
cute Spruce
planks Spruce and or quite different
will he still accept it if it's made of
[Music]
spuce any wood okay
okay I don't remember how much you need
it how I did this before right and I did
something oh it's not doing anything
right
[Music]
now okay
well I probably have enough
right
okay
[Music]
up I fail to purchase acquire materials
huh does it have to be Oak
planks
planks it has to be o
should I just garbage it
then maybe I can put it in my
backpack I'll keep
those I don't
need it's
trash trash oh I forgot to trash
it
trash yeah he get the right okay let's
go over here and find the oak trees
[Music]
okay I don't have an
axe stories
I can punch it should I just do that
then okay let's just go there ples ples
ples ples
PL are these going to be the trees that
I
[Music]
need will this work will be better to
punch it are you the right tree please
be the right tree you not the right tree
him back to
L and then out we
go okay let's hope this tree is the
right
[Music]
tree I the red
tree H up you look like the red tree I
want you to be the right
Tre Oak
okay that's
okay hey hey okay you guide me the
tree okay we can be friends then this is
oh gosh not
friends
really is this the right tree
it's not it's not it's not the right
me
[Music]
you wait can I enchant it multiple
times okay are you the right
tree you're the right tree
okay look at stay there sleeping so
[Music]
peacefully just takes a little
while the merant sells it but money is
precious hey hey
[Music]
hey there we go
wow
[Music]
okay maybe we're almost ready to go
back is my level going up
[Music]
what
is well let's go back
now yeah back to
the
okay let's see
now we go here
[Music]
hopefully that's right that's right I
need to go over there I'm
stuck okay and now we go like this
planks planks planks planks that's
probably enough planks right I don't
want
you wooden shovel
chicken yes now it's in my tomb
huh let's open up the garbage garbage
garbage and
garbage oh that's why I have a little
bit of
gold maybe I should just kind of make it
here oh that's the wrong
one why can't I use it huh
I don't
know where we go will be announced in
minutes that's
faster and it's in my tomb that's
right like the receive there's my
shovel and I'll take the extra meat
maybe uh the height can go all
together and
then uh
these can go all together
too that's not working
huh
okay now let's see it's done oh and I
don't have room for the cool okay that's
okay and this will be next so that can
be next
to okay time to enchant it
huh that's what we needed to do right
was that what we needed to
do no what did I need to do with it I'll
go back did I just need to present him
with
it hey
no just show
[Music]
it wasn't very
excited I'm
here let's go take a look at the board
I'm here for the lottery to
win thank you uh of a quest Master Quest
Master Quest
Master
okay I did
it okay supplies wanted
tools which Quest was
okay wood shovel I did that one this one
the stone pickaxe to the quest Master to
receive my reward do I have the stone
pickaxe I do not think I have the stone
pickaxe is it in my
bag stone pickaxe yeah is this all the
players one in three
chance
okay y out of the room out of the deal
help one wanted at the
T which one was
this hope wanted at to let how do I get
rid of that for them to be here then
huh hope wanted at the tower what did
they want me to do with the
tower what did you want me to do here
s can combine a a I did
that what by tender
[Music]
no I can make the diamond pickaxe I
definitely need a pickaxe but they
wanted help
right what kind of help did they want
help
wanted what help did you
want I couldn't I couldn't
sister hi help
does the Tom see with the quests I asked
let's take a look my sister isabe uh oh
take cly active Okay elizabe is more
potato oh okay we can make some more
potato salad that would be a good idea
huh let's go check how the food's going
and then let's make a pickaxe
too yeah you can go on
there and
then I'll just make some food maybe M
will like
it I'm being looked
for
n Go
[Music]
here it takes a little while huh maybe
I'll take some of the coal here and then
go over
[Music]
here and C these ones
I could just to let's take a little bit
here H let's deal with
this is there anything else I could cook
that's right m is making a bunch of the
backpacks right if I make the backpacks
and return them the iron
stair I have a bunch
of I don't know if I want to spend that
money
[Music]
though if I if I return this to him do I
get more than 200 coins
back maybe I should make another
backpack we'll make another backpack
okay we're going to make the diamond
pickaxe 500 coins three diamonds stain
bones oh yeah okay should I enchant the
diamond pickaxe
[Music]
I
cannot I can't I can't why not why
[Music]
not that's
why I that become a ghost should I do
it at the bottom
line
okay yeah
okay now they're going to be my friends
forever okay can I enchant the backpack
this to win right
no I wonder what else I can
in a couple sticks that I made they help
me a
lot and here oh those aren't my oh no
these aren't my
steaks a morea like them I guess I'll
take the coal now too
I'm sure whoever put them there I can
give these these ones to them those will
be them these are mine buba lots of
recipes and I've never made this before
and now I can't take it away
uhoh maybe we can do it like that then I
can put it in my backpack cuz I don't
need it right
now and
then I can take the cool back
H okay let's see that stay
there
okay
yeah uh let's see the
pickaxe
[Music]
oh
wow
okay that's I have my second backpack
maybe I should organize them this can
be my cooking backpack maybe oh I don't
okay I'll have to figure this out
later let's have some
food should I make some really amazing
food let's Che my recipe
book I can make more potato salad if I
get more potatoes and eggs
right uh I want to m is making the Slime
Jem oh I have I don't have sugar where
do we get
sugar I should put some stuff in my
chest
[Music]
y breakfast toast bread and slime jum
what's the healthiest boom fried steain
egg bread stain meat stain bone I have
stained meat ah I've been cooking it
steaks the stain
bones SU okay I don't know where that is
I can buy the
sugar okay well let's buy some
sugar that sounds a little
faster uh where's the
sugar I feel like I'm going to get
distracted melon SE pumpkin he cool he
doesn't have any sugar sugar cane I see
I don't have space for this right now
huh uh
of you won
back
warp
let's there's a lot of me there's a lot
of
me stain HDs can maybe go into here for
now maybe the lapis Lai too stone sword
is kind of garbage now
huh let's put this
here Stone SW
wood Stone
shovel Stone soil
garbage Cobblestone
garbage okay St SW it's garbage
Cobblestone
garbage
that's I can Trash the copper too okay I
at least made it
that's in the
backpack that's more important thing
anything
[Music]
okay now what was I doing
again I was making potato salad that's
right okay let's go to the
Garden I think the
[Music]
garden garden
around here was it maybe it was over
here I keep on forgetting where it was
you have to ask
question I buy
potions I love to use
those where's the garden I am B from oh
what's that there will
you there's a party here look everybody
has one it was not a scam oh one what
everybody won this is a
family does anybody want to share their
wealthy there's so much going on I don't
know what's going on perh would like to
share oh thank you
I could to fight the garden
now wow it's kind of everyone's so happy
there that's good but
wow 2,900 coins for jackpot is not very
much of a jackpot
potatoes potatoes those are not potatoes
not potatoes if there was a sign saying
what the world that would be
helpful still always wins in the end
I you know I'm trying to be
self-sufficient not depend on anybody I
except for Elizabeth she's my bad lady I
still don't know how to make oh gosh oh
gosh oh gosh oh gosh I walked into the
worst part
oh Elizabeth she makes the
breath where's the where is the
in
h i want in
[Music]
maybe there we
go no I need potatoes
potatoes potatoes potatoes potatoes
potatoes kind of need potatoes for the
good luck with your
pregnany
ba okay
now oh I need to plant the potatoes
that's right
that's the wrong one wow what am I
doing what am I
doing okay I'm really little into the
ground there I want
[Music]
potatoes what's this I don't know what
that
is okay still lots of
potatoes put the potatoes there and next
I'll
swich where is be I don't have enough of
those
I how many beets did I have I'll put
these potatoes there
okay maybe I should get more
potatoes it's like a
[Music]
okay back into the ground you
go I get to level5 maybe I should grab
some more from the other side huh my
level's away from
[Music]
me
okay that's definitely more than enough
now
I missed a couple spots
H
okay is there
any why am I not
moving there dou we mus have just
tired okay doesn't really do
much maybe I should take some wheat with
me just in
case I will throw something
out I don't need
these yeah and then back into the
backpack I'll
Place couple potatoes I picked up all of
those I need more carrots let's grab
some meat
too if I can make some bread that would
be really
nice oh gosh I took more
potatoes okay the
seeds
[Music]
there in the ground you
go
okay I think I should grab some more
wheat if I can though
I don't see any coal though okay that's
probably more than enough now
huh I just I like to be able to make
special Foods you
know I do have a lot of meat though
right now so maybe I should give more
some of that I think she might eat it
oh I have helped her
byebye H I'm so thank you for your
kindness fluffy oh my kindness oh no
know I'm just taking some stuff I'm
making of
a see oh it was Nissa thank you narissa
ravening to the
[Music]
Gard but how can okay so she's been
destroying the crops what if it's just a
simple prank why would you kill her for
that what what's going on that does not
sound like a good prank to me somebody's
been destroy therey in your heart fluffy
seems that the princess is corrupt
princess what you I me the princess the
princess is my daughter and I've never
seen her acting that weird this morning
acting weird I I don't know there was
something extremely wrong with her today
and I couldn't stop her even her mother
says so that's a good point yeah I've
also noticed her being very strange but
I feel like murder is very ex extreme
can we maybe have a trial we have a
trial
[Music]
I could I could have get my carrots oh
my gosh what is going on
there I don't want to be involved in
that in any
way where's the carrots where's the
carrots I just want to get my carrots
and go it's kind of scary here
now horse will help there's no carrots
in here hor you said no where the
carrots are huh
First's find the carrots why are we not
finding the
carrots here are the carrot search for
orange that's red orange good
horse now I have a good sword
right of gosh maybe that's more than
enough oh my goodness that's a
lot okay back into the
ground I can
make there we go oh maybe that's not
enough actually in the
end okay I pick them all up oh
ah
ah okay into the bag you go into the B
you
go and it disappeared of
course
okay
good
okay now I have more than enough carrots
I
think I can fight okay I am strong more
than enough now we just need lots of
eggs lots of
[Music]
eggs I can put this in there
too
egg let's
go true I've seen
it the princess I mean the eggs were
over
here eggs were over here
egg I got one egg where could I get more
eggs H what do you like to eat what do
you like to eat do you like to eat
wheat can I give you
wheat well you like
that
oh oh uh things aren't going
well I guess he doesn't like wheat they
like wheat seeds oh I don't have any of
those I threw them out
[Music]
time to go back I
guess there we
go um okay never mind well not there we
go do I have space for wheat seeds I
feel like something can come up behind
not at the
moment if I give them wheat seeds then
they'll give me more eggs right
okay this is going to be a little bit of
a pain to me plan that's okay though
that's that's my
[Music]
job okay that's
okay oh it's so dark now I need
this
this my time
ping okay there's a lot of monsters
no there a I should go store the stuff
in the chest
yeah I can go and do that next time it's
very close right
so did I get all the
[Music]
areas okay course redand if it turns
green you are pregnant if it stays red
you are
not over we are and we go okay chickens
do you have any eggs yet no
oh oh I can't take it
[Music]
though
this
okay carpet egg
yes can you make more eggs please
am I getting strong
[Music]
yet SE
here I could have just checked
H hopefully they make more eggs soon I
need eggs I only have two
eggs that's not enough at all where else
is there eggs
need to find more
[Music]
eggs buy eggs but eggs cost
money oh that's my
backpack I thought I had a bunch of eggs
in
there
okay let's put can put some other Saks
in
there can't put that away I can put that
away that's right I have multiple
backpacks I was going to organize them
both okay let's put the stuffs to build
stuffs in
here anything not
helpful this is all pretty
helpful gold isn't that helpful anymore
[Music]
okay you're building You're
Building what else should I put in
here throw the iron in the gold
[Music]
okay I'm going to make my other bag a
Food Bag
I probably need those for something I
know I just took those in and put them
[Music]
out this backpack is the food
backpack there's not that much room for
food
though okay lais wasal
[Music]
body okay no not there okay and then you
go into this PP
there you go there you go there you
go maybe Diamond can go into here
too
here get them back to the food
backpack I don't think I need that much
stained slime do
I I can store the magic feather too okay
maybe maybe I'll keep it here though for
now
[Music]
I don't need that much huh let's take it
out I know you can cook with it a little
bit huh said I don't think I need that
much I'll get rid of
it
garbage garbage
[Music]
garbage is it taking damage oh I could
have sted it in here
huh
hey what I need the bucket for water
right I think we're good on water right
now berries can go in here too rest of
the stick can go in there
[Music]
too should I bring a new one with me
more of the special food
there this should here I can go in there
for now same with
this I have enough is this good now
maybe I guess the coal can go into this
backpack too
huh I'll
eat I the fishing one maybe that's the
food
backpack I should get more sticks
huh can I make the sticks right
here
that's this one what kind of sticks are
these stick okay
[Music]
what's going
on I would like to make more of the
sticks there we
go okay that's enough
okay and then back into the bag
I think that's
good a hold shift all to make all oh
it's daytime now maybe the chickens have
some
eggs if not I will give them more food
and hopefully they will give me food I
don't want to spend money on eggs oh go
eggs okay
good job you get more
[Music]
food okay food oh gosh wrong
one more eggs please
okay oh why you sh what what what is he
magical what is he
doing why
is he
magical do
everything
what why why why it makes it grow
faster oh I'm almost out of the
[Music]
seats please eggs
please I'm going to have too many
chickens at the end of this
huh I means gr I see it I prefer to
think it's
magical this oh I
out please grow big so you can light
eggs
okay is it
happening oh they're
gone that fast
[Music]
they all really like me
huh give them time to
grow how much time I am I thring
out eggs eggs eggs
no
what
hi they're so pleased
I would be just dis pleased if you la a
bunch of
[Music]
eggs I'm going to
turn
oh don't miss me it'll be okay
okay I'm just going to take the seeds
with me and now I have six eggs okay if
I go and make some potato salad and come
back they should have even more eggs for
me right
okay the chickens are
obious I don't have any Co in here I
don't have any at the C you wanted
potato
Sal potato salad that I have my cooking
P okay I just got to get off the
horse and here we are here we
and I need to take out out of my cooking
bag
you
[Music]
you potatoes there there you
go I guess I can stand
closer hello FL one
oh I'm making potato salad potato salad
do you know how to make milkshake P I
don't know how to make that oh okay well
good luck on making potato salad thank
you ba oh I have a question yeah how's
your how is your what's your Allegiance
what was that I like with the what is
your Allegiance are you allied with the
queen I did
SL sorry I
didel oh J okay Al with the queen Que
Queen yeah the queen queen Tam
Gander yes uh I don't know much about
Tam Gander I have only met her maybe
once once once very
briefly oh sorry one second uh I will
call you back in a moment um Scarlet one
member I am in a conversation sorry I'm
a new tunnel
sorry
sorry no no um so you've you've not met
her
no no what about uh Queen Mario do you
Mario support her Mario I've never met a
queen
Mar oh if you if you would would you
call yourself an ally to the Scarlet
wand I'm J so not particularly not
particularly huh I'm friends with
everyone I think though unless not it's
nice okay okay well thank you for your
for the information I wish you good Lu
the potato salads for now okay good luck
on your mie quest
[Music]
baa Al with the Queen the king stay I
don't
understand I'm just the farmer I'm just
trying to to do my best for the best
of okay I'm a little
forgetful okay let's make a bunch of
this one two three and we go one two
three no more eggs OU that's the end of
that but you know the chickens are my
friends I believe on
them
okay
no I finished it a
Tavern who do I have to speak
to I thought yeah
why yes I have pool do the Tav Chef not
have confidence that I can make potato
salad I've made so
much
okay gave me a lot of coins so I can't
complain more than will gives me some
sometimes out off the hor
a here's the
milkshake I of want to make a milkshake
too oh I can't make any more of the
potato
salad was it where was
it there it
[Music]
is okay why did the shf want it
then I guess raw beef is pretty
good how many do I have not that many
[Music]
more oh I still have a couple
more Flip Flip Flip Flip okay there we
go
yes and
then like this once we're done get okay
time to get more eggs Ste okay steak
steak is good cuz I
had here we
go steak I can make some diamond tools
now what was keeping me from making them
again was it the EG what was it
hello I see lots of eggs I see lots of
eggs
yeah thank you chickens I knew I could
count on you four four is pretty good
you want
[Music]
see there we
go oh
gosh are we all happy now will you make
more eggs for
meop I think they're all happy I'm going
to use all the wheed seats St on them
Reg
there's so many of them now I want to
feel this overflowing with chicken
ready please grow big and
[Music]
fast
[Laughter]
okay okay only fours that's okay I
didn't give them too much time did
I what's the popping sound
it's that feet oh my gosh I don't know
if I like
that let me do I can't get
through there we are there we are there
we
are I bring some more potato the Ping s
is are you
sure who is
that I need
is that really
[Music]
eggs no
eggs of a lava block
[Music]
a I wish that was the sound of eggs eggs
hitting the
ground it's not this the are you hungry
again no it's been
too okay let me thr let me thr let me
do
uhoh
uhoh let's Okay I made it
[Music]
out it's kind of scary over
there red
let's
see what was I doing
again I'm very forgetful making a potato
salad I got that but after that what was
my
next my next
[Music]
goal potato salad let's make the potato
salad car
uh
potato make make
make and one
more Str goes up
tooy some more bread no not the horse
there we
go potato Sal
and two more potato
salad more I
other
okay oh
God okay well wait but I'll buy them to
go
faster where the last I go oh maybe it's
in the
T okay yeah oh it's not this is
good that's okay it's kind of annoying
in here I'm going to go like this and
this and then
this oh I can't put it back
huh I guess I'll take the stuffs out and
then let's figure this
[Music]
out I think it's a lot of
garbage let's find the garbage can there
I should be rning right
and then this is garbage this can be
garbage I can cook that at the very
least this can be garbage leather is
leather that help
helpful GB
okay and then I'll go cook the other
food is is goodno
[Music]
oh is it in here do you want some food
no no oh I have two extra eggs are
here that's I can give you some more
meat if you want it if I can have steak
oh um I have how much steak do I have I
have a lot of steak I could give you
some steak but I don't want your small
little room meates though what
[Music]
yeah this is the s for
everybody do I know how cool is in my
for everybody what h no no no it's not
for everybody I took
steak I took I made a mistake and I took
the steaks it's not for anybody not for
you oh I have extra steak you can't put
extra steak over there yeah it's the
commity no
steti and the
chicken it's done it's cooked and then
this one the RO all
b
h let's
see it's
done what else is there to
cook perhaps that's it
let put this here put that there
actually if I just eat these little ones
then that'll make some space and it
won't be
wasted is it good okay no not the
horse there we go what should I do
then okay a do you have eggs I could
have no are you sure you can buy them
yeah but you kind of pause them yeah no
I just don't have eggs
okay she kind of ped huh
B what should I
do I felt like there was something I
needed to
do this let's
try
yeah let's try maybe getting some sugar
[Music]
I'm curious about it pumpkin seeds
Bellon seeds I could buy bread I kind of
like to make bread oh obsidan I've never
made that before portable lter good oh
but I have I have
my wait where is
[Music]
it I thought I had a
torch did I accidentally get rid of it
no
torch maybe I should buy that should I
buy this
H is it in my no it's not in my
hands maybe I should buy
this five eggs for 10 gold is cheap
that's
true that is
true it's
expensive yeah maybe I stoed it maybe I
TOS it somewhere good I would like to
buy this instead of
this I'm going to buy one
okay but let's go
maybe
maybe I got to do it right
now which one is
it
no it's not it okay it's in my
to I'll receive
it and
then what do I want what what's
helpful what's
helpful what's nice I don't
[Music]
know I can save it I'll save
it and you
go
okay okay we'll go make some more
[Music]
where are the
potatoes we have lots of eggs now right
so we can just make a lot of the potato
salad okay I need the cooking pot there
we
are uh we'll just get rid of that egg
there and there and potatoes
[Music]
yeah oh my
gosh a little
scary what can I do with the sugar
[Music]
can if I click away will I still save
this will they just go to my Tob okay
they went to my Tob that's
good okay
[Music]
did I pass it I
passed there we
go
and there we
go oh oh there we
go oh it Stacks up to 64 can I just
click it
like am I doing it the most efficient
no I'm
drowning what is what is stock
it shift quick so
like go away
I like
this I
shck oh I I
so
like I think I
understand no more potatoes what happen
here but it's in my to receive receive
receive receive receive
okay let's try this done and you go and
I'm not clicking up
pois and then shift click
[Music]
I
see okay okay we're done did it all go
back
[Music]
easy okay but now I just have to do this
over and over again it didn't give
any that's a bit EAS though I thought I
could shift click the
[Music]
quest and then I'll have lots of money
to be able to buy that my hat that I
want what other items should I get
that'll make me nice and strong I would
like to make more H complicated Foods
maybe like the
milkshake that seems
exciting Which hat do I one I would like
the the cute hat the stain dead stain on
my head and I also like the Jade sword
hat
[Music]
too let's
see how many more do I
have oh I passed
it there it
is a two left oh we're almost
done oh did I make a mistake there we go
all the hats are cute on my
head Diamond that's
[Music]
it go past the GU of find empty L where
hers can go fre it sounds like a
good good time to you stop by and have a
talk with me
Mason should I try that
[Music]
what should I try make the
milkshake okay I'm wrestling okay I'm
going to try that let's see how strong I
am
okay byebye Brutus where is Brutus
Brutus
okay you must have come after seeing
P but look at you your arms they are no
not sticks what why did you say come
back what I have strong
arms am Marcus this is mine a little
secret speak
to a bucket of milk well I have a bucket
where was my
bucket my buckets maybe back back with
the chickens
do I get the milk the milk from the cows
there's cows in the plains can I just
walk up to them and take their milk is
that how it
works I can do that
okay CH I'm back
over I'm
back XG I just fell
eggs eggs
eggs not many eggs
huh that's okay you're doing your best
okay let's get even more chickens in
here until it's overflowing with
chickens oh my gosh almost out of the
seats
yeah it's like they laugh
me I need one okay no
more wow I've used up a lot of the seeds
huh so there'll be a whole Army
right
wow I really hope I can fill it
overflowing with
chickens ouch what the heck
[Music]
okay and my bucket
okay uh do I need anything
else no no we're
good okay that
is let's go oh we can warp let's War
what does that do to the planes
maybe uh maybe this is the wrong
place
am perfect
bu where's a cow you're not you don't
have the count I want ouch
can't find them when you need them
H lot of sheep why can't I
move
sheep
there yeah
okay let's go back to the V Castle
[Music]
byebye maybe this is how I can make a
milkshake then huh yeah
okay it's a good thing I stole the
bucket
huh I'm holding milk
[Music]
yeah okay okay and it's a recipe for
special stams too
[Music]
that's it I didn't actually I'm wrestle
I'm a little
disappointed it's still not done okay
let's take a look at this recipe then
special stain
still golden carrot beetro soup robit St
butter wow that sounds cool though I can
make butter with just a mil I'm going to
need all
that let's see let's see let's take a
look at my cooking pot see what I can do
with it okay this time for sure right if
I put this in
here if I press it what happens okay
nothing sleeping Edge three how do I
make sugar then
[Music]
H let's see
okay I want to make this the Slime gem
cuz I want to make the
toast crafting table it's Shin is there
one in here is there one in
here doesn't look like
[Music]
it I
want is this a crafting
table okay oh in my inventory
green let's see
oh and I can just
[Music]
press okay then if I go like
this and then
this what am I going to get
butter okay I
guess I guess it have anything to do
with the butter
though I guess we just have to go get
some more
huh that's okay I'm not going to
[Music]
cry watch out behind you
thank you for helping no
problem where is the cow did you kill
the cow I killed the
cow okay there's a cow on the Hills here
why do you want a cow I'm going to get
milk there we go now
box back we going can I hit you I set up
a p for the cow okay put them in with
the
chickens I don't
know let's try this
again let's take a look at the re ofe
book I want to to make what again bread
slime what was
it sweet B let's try this okay okay okay
okay um X can go in here carrots can go
in here actually keep them
here we have enough cool
yet and let's take this and then take
this and then we can make this
right
okay and you go and you go and you
go slime jum let's make
couple of
them I haven't made bread but making
bread seems Troublesome
so
okay let's buy some bread maybe do I
have enough room for bread I do not
let's
put this back here this back
here and bread is easy how do I make
bread
then with a CR in table or can I just do
it
here I have the
we do I just go like this doesn't do
[Music]
anything the crafting table
okay three we in a row
okay let me down let me
down okay
[Music]
three we in a row I didn't listen did
I go away go away go away go
away
go that's not it's not
the I see okay
ah I don't get this oh there we
go okay let's make a little bit
more
okay it'sing
my I want to do
this one second one second
okay lots of bread now I can't breing up
bread
lady I don't know I don't know if
Bread's that easy to make but now I can
make the Slime
bread
right breakfast
toast that's
[Music]
cool
okay I want to make more cool Foods okay
potato salad made I don't want to make
the nourishing soup kind of sounds
[Laughter]
boring I have raw C I have raw salmon
potato and butter I have that let's make
this okay we'll put the butter in
actually let's go back here there was ah
that was back over there okay let's go
back can only make
one but it SS good
right
ah down here how do I fly take on the
chickens again I don't need
jum okay byby
by I'm flying where did the chickens go
oh what happened the chicken
where they chickens here
chickens my
chickens why they go there's not a
single chicken left are they in here are
they
hiding
no my chickens did you have a lot of
chickens I had an overflowing pet of
chickens overflow then h
no my chickens they love me so much and
I love them too you should put a
miss you didn't do anything to the right
there Chicken in here my chicken you
should put a missing a missing sign
up I don't know what to
do I need this I need this I need
this why won't it let me have
it ouch wait wait wait wait wait I
couldn't destroy I need to destroy oh I
picked it
up I get it that's why I couldn't pick
it
[Music]
up okay did I drop the
carrots I dropped the carrots that's
okay my chickens
[Music]
oh I don't even know how to get come
back
why what should I
do what should I
[Music]
do why will everybody see this L
here I don't even
know is it just me
can I throw the eggs in here I have some
eggs did I have eggs I have two
[Music]
eggs that's one
egg no tickets
where did they
go I don't have anymore either
here are you raising my chicken I was I
was Raising all the chickens
Co they were my best
[Music]
friends I did but I don't know if people
are going to see it
[Music]
can call I love them so much
M if you see any
chickens please let me
know I have like 50
chickens another one every last one of
them I can you look for
them can you look for
[Music]
them I know
they what I know where they are you know
where they
are
where I don't see
them I don't see them definitely took
your
chickens
H wait if I take them more
here where are you I'm
here
there I don't see
[Music]
them they have a big chest here are they
tick you don't know how they make the
tickets
[Music]
but have to make the tickets out of
something how do you the water
ticket feathers oh I had one
feather need chickens to make feathers
and
Feathers put this to
Jonathan let's
see this isn't slander I'm just saying I
got to find Jonathan
[Music]
okay put your
Jonathan
Jonathan run
Jonathan do you hear
me Jonathan you answered
me why don't I hear
you my
chickens what happened to my chickens my
chickens have disappeared
my one of them
please tell
me Jonathan's
asleep I don't
know oh do you hear me I don't hear
you
now
hello do you know what happened to my
chickens what happened to your chicken
they're G the G every last one where you
got your
chicken h
where you gone like where you
Jonathan I can't hear Jonathan no can
you hear Jonathan yeah you can I can
hear you I can't hear Jonathan that's so
strange
Jonathan are chickens can I hear
Jonathan
[Music]
now I still can't hear Jonathan I can
hear jonath
what is going on dad
Jonathan my chicks come here come here
come here no no yes
yes right over here where were they
where they were right here
[Music]
mhm and every last chicken is
gone your chickens were here they were
here I love them but there was so many
of them and now they are gone they're
all gone every last one
was it the curse of the land you it
quite near close to what I don't to the
to the corruption no they were very
happy they were so they loved me I love
maybe you should like put something here
on the on the wood so they don't leave
anymore maybe they just left I don't
think they flew away they were very
happy I left this sign
but I don't think tickets can fly I
think oh yes chickens cannot
fly you didn't eat them did you my
goodness yeah big cat you didn't eat
them right okay what why would you H
them on me
it's I love them how could you do
that my
goodness she atat your
chickens I'm not think she would eat
your chicken she is
living on bread for the past few days
living on bread are you
sure
yes know your chickens though nobody
else love me like
they I love
them I can give you more eggs come with
me can you
yeah oh my potato salad was made with
them some
H come here I give you all my eggs all
your eggs are you sure can you accept my
train H let's see I got to move
something around here one
moment and you know what we should do we
should make a better kid so they not
leave a better kid
yeah
okay oh that's a one of
eggs thank you
I to for the chicken I didn't need it
okay maybe maybe you're innocent yeah
you want to put more put more fences
around and you're going to be fine okay
I don't think they F away though they
did I
promise I don't know if you can jump
over it they can jump I can't jump over
it though I can look come with me that's
just because you're a big cat no oh I
should eat something
huh there we
go now that's probably thinking oh it's
so
slow I thought I was doing something
wrongp over here look yeah but the not
the chickens the chickens are that's
[Music]
I don't think
so there there I got a
chen found it
okay come
back okay magic
receive I know to okay let's
see we need a friend we need a friend
there we go friend okay oh go I need to
find more friends for you uh let's see I
don't think they're going to escape
though I just need to feed them you
me I trust
you I don't think they flew away though
really
really did I don't think
so look I don't know how to play this
yet they're not big enough now and they
grow up to just
are you
sure oh maybe this fence is kind of
small you got to put like another fence
between those two trees oh but I can't
jum feel it between these ones I can
stay downstairs I don't know I didn't
make this pen
originally but because I didn't make it
I think it's good no wait wait ah there
they
are let's see I'll come back shortly and
we'll see if they're all gone okay
thank you promise they were there for a
long time thank you for the
eggs you're
welcome okay now that's innocent she
didn't eat
them I just hope that they're going to
be okay if I leave
them are you going to be okay are you
going to be
okay it's not too hot in here right
[Music]
yeah I'm going to keep some replacement
EG just in case okay we're going to make
fish and chips right uh let's check the
recipe again actually green 150 Co I
won there okay okay okay okay potato
potato okay I need the raw
salmon and the raw C and we need a
[Music]
bread what else did I
need potato is that
everything
bu wow that's
cool okay I can put that into my food
back and it
Stacks color
col what can we make next
huh made the breakfast
toast pu fish help where do we get that
from the ocean
maybe
in
[Music]
St okay here we go maybe
let's
see I guess I need more stain me in the
stain bones right chocolate cake M
that's right I wanted to make this this
okay I'm got to make this robit sou
golden carrot how do I make the golden
carrot is there something else I need to
make first to make the golden
carrot yellow here gold etiquette oh so
it's easy
then okay we'll go into this backpack
we'll take some gold and I have okay
grab the backpack with the carrots and
then there they go there yellow
still
gold I'm just going to use one
and one C
okay no it didn't work how many gold H
eight gold okay
let's it didn't work and the crafting
table I think there's a crafting table
there
this 200 that's not
it that's not it let's
[Music]
see can I not use it cuz it's not my
own ow let's go back see my
[Music]
birds look at them
this will help
me is there any egg
yet is there any egg yet oh yeah maybe I
should put the seeds back in here just
in
case can't I get
there there we go see it's back in I
could put the eggs back in too maybe
I'll put
some two
[Music]
leave them a water bucket I don't know
how to make the buckets and I only have
one still if I could make more buckets
that would be
cool okay we're going to do
[Music]
this it didn't
work do I need iron for it
too oh bucket needs iron okay well we
can make that then
[Music]
do we need to do this thing
again is that a
bucket 3
coin what is this cauldron that's not
what I want bucket is a v three
F
like
mine like
that that's a
you there's
nothing only three how do you make like
a like a a
[Music]
this a TR k this is a one shape
now three oh three
two there's a there what I did that
before I'm winning okay H what's this
shears I'm going to get a couple good
buckets out of
this five buckets sounds good
what
the if I leave this here I'll keep it l
okay R where
go did it did it disappear delete
it I could have made more bucket to is
it in a to I don't know usually it says
it's in the Tom right
yeah red we can do it we can do it I
need El toy space yeah I'm just not
maybe being as efficient as I can
be I need that for the carrots okay
we're making the golden carrots
M oh maybe I should make some inventory
space too light okay I'm going to put
the yummy food in
here don't me that I'll put this over
here I cannot put that over
[Music]
there okay put one gold in the crafting
menu and this one one
gold just one gold please 500 if I win I
get 5,000 right one gold and a
carrot oh gosh oh gosh
collect the gold oh these ones the gold
nuggets and then do I collect
this this time for
sure it's so close for
red in a crafting table
now
God
okay 10 9
around 2
[Music]
a that's
cool okay I'm going to have to toss that
one that's
[Music]
okay let's put the eggs over here for
now with a golden car let's make more of
those red r r let's for
red red is still safe yes yes yes yes
red that's good and now over here we
go red red okay this could be it
[Music]
red there we
go am I doing it right it's close
though one last one okay I'm not M more
careful
okay
okay I think this is
it gold
carrot put this
away we can put this away too
[Music]
let's
see let's take a look at the recipe once
more I want to really make you a lot of
that okay well they be Ro
soup I never made that one robits do
I've never made that one butter I can
make butter let's go get some
rabbits yeah it will be good it will be
good ah robits do
second we can go get the robits and we
can go get more
milk 6 5
4 two one where was it okay where was it
time actually I want to go take a look
at the the
birds they're looking so
happy let's get them
fly this time
[Music]
they still little huh they're still
little get
big okay that's
now don't use the seeds yet I Ed them
okay let's go then yes yes yes
yes there
[Music]
ououou
red okay I feel like something might
have just happened deep down see see
it's good hey see it was the last time I
guess I need some meat and some balls
see I told
you is good
[Music]
yeah you too it's no
problem yeah I'm so tired after all that
milk milk milk milk milk that's a lot of
milk now wait
huh where did she
[Music]
go they don't Stu
why doesn't that stack
huh I only have two milks
[Music]
now no I have to go get more
iron if I get more iron then I can make
more of the ironing on and then
[Music]
cuz I got rid of the iron angle light
that was a
mistake where's the
[Music]
iron why isn't it going in here anymore
H you're going to make me mad huh you're
going to make me mad huh
yeah you too
[Music]
huh yeah he tried to
run okay I need to get up higher up here
oh there's a whole bunch of
iron cuz I need to get more of the ORS
and make a lot more of the Ingot so that
I can make a lot more buckets
right it's said to go in
okay let's put the milk in here it
doesn't stock though I thought I thought
it was yours I'm going to stack
it uh this can go here that can go
there this is garbage I won't delete it
yet
though okay and then I can put this here
quickly eat this
to do I hear somebody behind me no okay
is there any more iron maybe this is the
best okay I'm
[Music]
stuck
goodbye
water holy water not
water
[Music]
yes princess eel
huh be I guess I have to get more stamy
I have to get the rabbits
too I need the bones
though I should get a
lot okay
I
[Music]
want here we go fashion I never taken in
fashion what's
the oh oh a phone call a hello
Jonathan Jonathan
Donan I can't hear
[Music]
you I might be in
trouble ah I'm in trouble I'm in really
[Music]
trouble I'm in trouble I thought if I
looked up I could see my hat Jonathan I
can't I can't speak to you right now I'm
being
[Music]
chased not even a
goodbye there we
go hey do you have
eggs head I leveled up because of you
are you dancing I guess I need to find
some rabbits
right do I have enough iron Ah that's
probably enough
right I can put this here
though oh hello Dad oh I'm in danger why
oh I'm in danger how does this happen
huh
why let's run away
[Music]
okay I need to find some
rabbits wow there's so many of
them of course they're still
[Music]
alive wow
where's the robits they're near the
mountain usually
[Music]
right I'm so high
up where's the
robits it's so dark did they go back
home
rabbit D get off I feel a b but
so many of them but I can't catch
them where's the other rabbit G where
are you where are you there you are take
my
eyes do I have enough robbit meat yet
I've never made rabbits too so I don't
[Music]
know not strong enough
hi yeah behind me
again
princess oh
[Music]
gosh
okay I got to Rob at me oh there's
more
okay he sees me oh there's another one
of
you oh it's all going into my
maybe let's go
back
yes
okay let's
[Music]
see let's take a
there and then I got the bucket
[Music]
bucket let's see
okay there's some garbage let's get rid
of the garbage
garbage slime
ball into the garbage is that it oh I
didn't empty
it empty the tomb has a bunch of stuff
though I
think ah rabbit's foot rabbit
hide I'll just stack this for
now and then oh I can't get rid of it
okay let's go make the iron inot
[Music]
okay is the rabbit's foot are those
garbage
too does that make the
soup
H
okay H where is the
co I put the co into my backpack that's
right okay and we
go and we go oh that's
right here we
go now I can make what I need why did I
need it for the buckets okay swiming
here I got it is it always a here
okay what up here and then okay well
right now I can make milk right H with
the milk I can make the
butter milk
and
look
good stack that do not stack the buckets
thought I had something on my head
[Music]
okay
okay well while I'm waiting for that
let's go check on my chickens
flow oh gosh
what what the heck just happened why did
I get
hurt
H
flow more flowers what was
that what was Jonathan fored me about
earlier maybe I should find
[Music]
her huh
what oh there's
egg I got EG but and a
torch B
[Music]
Bo
maybe did they just fly
away not right
now die like this this was eggs wasn't
them more eggs
my
ticket my
backpack IUN oh there's more eggs but I
thought you meant that my chickens would
be in my
backpack
not m is that
you m f my chickens did you see them far
away I never saw your chickens it's
always been empty hasn't been empty it's
no don't give me eggs and they came back
I don't know why you keep on saying that
you have chicken cuz I've never seen
chicken I have chicken are you sure
you're actually growing chcken here
Melissa what what are you giving me 16
of
those what what
for I don't want
that I'll make flowers I don't want that
escape why don't you talk to
[Music]
me come Lu with your chickens I'm trying
to get hats I can't manage to get hats I
don't want these construction boxes I
want hats
too I have I have two extra hats oh what
hats do you have my hat and the
ambercoin hat I don't want those hats
but my
[Music]
CH down do I
down should I try
again thank
you how do I make fence I don't even
know how to make
[Music]
fence is there fence in
this there's a
roof there F in this I don't need
that it doesn't have fence then what's
the
point find
Jonathan I'll ask
Jonathan why why won't it work maybe
should I phone Jonathan
again
Jonathan Jonathan can you hear me can I
hear you
Jonathan you weren't speaking are you
sure you're
speaking Jonathan where are
you I can't hear you I'm near F right
now
though I'm in trouble my chickens are
gone again this is
good the Jonathan back on
[Music]
again is it my
volume I don't
hear I can hear Jonathan near me when
Jonathan's near me
[Music]
but that's it be a pretty Place h s
please
help pap
[Music]
I wonder why it's being so
silly this is how you make it right is
Jonathan going to
[Music]
come what if the queen get made here
hon H
[Music]
right I can't even remember what I was
doing
Jonathan's having some issues
okay Jonathan can you hear me I can hear
you can hear me I can't I can't what is
wrong my my chickens are gone again your
chickens are gone they're gone
yeah what happened to them no I said the
the fence wasn't big enough I don't
think so cuz I kept on checking on them
and they're all good they were always so
happy they they had many eggs in front
of them were you given a hat by any one
per chance I was only given a half by
you very far ago oh well will you
promise me
dearest will you promise me yes my
dearest fluffy one please please do not
accept any hat from anyone else okay I W
I won't yes you promise you swear to me
I swear you not accept a hat yes I'll
get my hats on my own yes I have to
you're you're not safe I think I know
what is happening to your
chickens what is you mean they're not
just flying
away I do not think they're flying I
think someone is getting rid of them I
think it's corruption how could I keep
them safe supposed to look like they
wind I do not know if you'll be able to
keep them safe mayhaps you should set up
a trap a trap should L
yes I'm not that kind of person I don't
know how to make
[Music]
traps it
seems maybe tomorrow tomorrow I will
help you create a trap and
we can see wein any trusted allies but
you must promise you will not accept any
hats from any no hats no hats no hats no
hats I promise and I had to tell you
something too okay the
one the one that people say that you
look very similar to Moo is it yes I
know that you have you are a little you
are close with one another Mo we've
gotten closer today too we got Diamond
we' got closer yes what you cannot trust
her I fear as if she may be corrupt she
may be corrupt
yes why I don't know I don't know if I
can believe you
Donathan well you may not believe me but
I hope you think of my words when
something if you feel in danger remember
my words if you ever feel like you are
in danger remember what I've told you
okay will yes be careful than
princess and Nissa ravencraft be careful
around them okay okay I will norissa was
just asking me about
hats oh do not accept a hat from her do
not okay I won't I won't she didn't have
the hats I wanted
anyways yes yes I see I
see be careful I just I believe someone
is doing something to your to your
dearest chickens okay uh let's pick you
up the trap for now I guess I just not
have any chickens I will help you with
your trap tomorrow okay I promise I
promise yes we will find who's doing
this farewell farewell farewell bow bow
it bow bow
it I can't
believe I don't even want to think about
it I don't know I do trust Jonathan
Jonathan are nothing but wonderful to me
but
to be I can't get out of
here
okay let's forget that let's forget that
and just think about the joys of
cooking we're going to make the special
stain to right we need the stain B I
have the butter I have the stain meat I
need the rabbit to and the beetro soup
so to do that okay I was making that
[Music]
I need this the iron
an I don't know what to
believe I'm just going to ride away from
her cannot ask me about hat
to no
horse there we
go okay now we can make buckets crafting
table
right okay before we make buckets
I'm going to make some space cuz that
makes
s well it's pretty full here
uh we could eat
this oh I could put this away actually I
could put
the maybe I need
that St the Hat that's right okay I just
put it in the food maybe not in the food
backpack I'm going to put it in the
other backpack
this one has lots of space
so I don't need the shovel right now
I'll put it in there I haven't used it
for a long time same with the fishing L
[Music]
uh and this can go in there for now too
this cannot move okay it sounds good so
far and then now we have a lot of room
now this is good right right
right that's enough room
maybe can I put this in my
paw let's
see yes and now we have a little bit
more extra
room
okay let's
see okay we're going to make the bucket
bucket
H can't remember how to make the
bucket was it like
this uh
no
small okay a small V
right there we go okay that's another
bucket that's another
bucket lots of buckets we just making
buckets
right
okay I think I will probably need some
water no
right oh
no
and
one a little bit of
water I think we need that to make soup
right so then if I go like this like
this will it
make oh I can stack the empty ones are
you sure
okay I have bucket
traa ah I soup I need crafting table and
wood bows wood
bows it
tall oops okay crafting table
no okay I have the wood in
here uh
planks let's make some
[Music]
make the B oh I'm
right okay this is how you make the
right that's quite a bit of
[Music]
BS okay do I go
like water that make it
yeah if I press click will no no water
just like that the raw rabbit and the
bow makes the rabbit still it's really
complicated it's not
[Music]
good do I just go
like no that's no water but
carrots too and the crafting
table okay let's try this over here
then okay carrots too and the ra rabbit
and the
ball check the recipe book this
[Music]
one maybe it's not this one is this
I don't think it's that
Tre I don't
know the other recipe book I don't it
didn't have it in
[Music]
there
see fine depending on
you than you
it only has stuffff I made before I
don't know some of them I haven't made
before
[Music]
though oh I need baked potatoes and
mushrooms too mushrooms too okay I know
that I haven't seen where mushrooms are
but I know that they have mushrooms over
here no I don't have any
[Music]
I don't know Jonathan was saying a lot
of things
right
right close the
doors the doors won't
[Music]
close how do I make
torches I hope she eyes up and go
soon how do I make
torches I get the mushrooms Bak potatoes
I have potatoes can I bake them
[Music]
now I
have and I have Co can I bake the
potatoes on
here oh is not going to make it
[Music]
she looking this way where the stick oh
there they
[Music]
are it looks like I used a
oh I made 50 of them
okay one
moment I'll be right back
okay
by to make here
[Music]
I'm back I fixed the spell it looks
like
maybe it was a good
timing now
safe you w
oh I baked
potatoes I don't need this many potatoes
being baked though of Co I can leave
here right and it won't disappear
right right right I hope so yeah okay
let's go get some
mushrooms
God she's not around anymore oh oh I
need room for mushrooms let's figure
this out
mushrooms we'll put one water bucket
here that way we can get
mushrooms okay uh red mushroom Brown
mushroom I think brown brown mushrooms
brown mushrooms work right I it's okay
these ones are good
okay let's go back
okay now we have our baked potatoes we
have our brown
mushrooms okay and I
forgot we're making the sou but do we
need the crafting table where's the
crafting table right balls the
rbit H baked potato the mushrooms and
carrot was
it was that it for the rabbit
still do I need to cook the rabbit
that would make sense
maybe
okay we can do that right
here there we
go I need more rabbit
though the first R should be potato
rabbit bow and second row carrot
mushroom okay vegetables in the second
row go it
[Music]
vegetables in the second
row okay vegetables in the second row
this and this and a ball and rabbit and
big up big
potatoes
okay what was in the first oh that was
the robbit okay
like I wanted to make more of these but
I can't because I don't have enough
robbit can I make what other I think I
need to make another
[Music]
Su the be Ro
soup it be Ro soup be Ro
soup okay
do any mushrooms
too what the
potato six beat Ro spread out just be
[Music]
one okay
oh they don't
stunk they don't
stunk
oh
oh I'm going to lose it all
huh
ah my
be and that
soup at least I have some bowls
still I need to organize like you're
saying H
[Music]
is let's put another bucket
there goodbye piz you should look cool
at night yeah right but I have this I
just need bones do not have bones do
I let's go back to my oh why
okay scary
now
[Music]
okay come on let me do the
pain there we
go oh I'm here below oh I can't go to my
spot anymore your spot
I need to break this no no no no no
there's an entrance on the other side I
don't know I didn't build the wall did I
need to break this no no no no you don't
need to break it how do I get in this
way this way this
way second one second we have to go
around this is a pain now I'm just going
to break it no don't break it there's
already a broken
[Music]
part over this way there we go no what
are you doing I just pushed some leaves
out of the
way okay see
here what am I going to put oh hi here
oh but that's a pain how do I I can't do
this how do you do that I don't want to
do that that's a
pain what is
this
wow that's a pink it's just some
gardening
okay what am I going to put in here what
am I going to put in here I need to
organize okay I haven't needed a bunch
of these things recently
so we're going to just kind of swap
things in and out
iair don't in our
[Music]
house why are you hitting
her I just got to
[Music]
wait
wait fla come back I need to get out of
herea come back I need to get out back
come back it me see under the
flowers I just going to ride
away can I hide can I hide can I hide
can I hide can I
hide nobody following okay I ran into
something oh my gosh
I I'm going to go findun
[Music]
to come back it's safe it's safe in
the is it okay yeah it's
safe ouch ouch he he I'm dying come back
to the
flowers
no I just I just
TR come back to the
flowers I'm coming back I'm coming back
please me go go come
on come back come back come back here
here here here come back it's
here quick
okay okay to the
flowers here here here
[Music]
where
what it's small but see are you
[Music]
sure are you
sure oh my chest is here I can still do
the business I have do
it's nice okay it's bright thank you I
should have trusted you
[Music]
yeah
J Jade s yeah but your hat doesn't
really fit but it's blue so it's
okay your neck looks like it hurt my
neck better I can't
see I can't see oh ouch ouch it's a
little bit tight in
here I'm just gonna figure this out I
almost have my soup all done here let's
see I'm making a great
soup what soup uh the special soup the
great greatest soup the greatest
soup I just need to swap things out a
little bit here believe someone wearing
a
hat and then a lot of things in here can
go into here and then I haven't needed
any of this for a little while should be
safe now same with this that makes the
cold and carrots I don't need this
that's for
sure not that and not this either okay
all of those
[Music]
what oh
okay can I just shift oh shift shift
okay good good good then this goes away
then that goes away this goes away that
goes away this goes away H what else
what else this goes away this goes away
and then I want
open what what what what I'm
open I putting everything away properly
right there's no problems right water
bucket my
buckets ah what
else that's everything I need right
anything else I don't need I have the
rabbits too I have to be I just need
bones I need room for bones put this
away that potatoes can go away maybe I
can keep those actually those are
[Music]
handy okay
what's in my back pocket ah more golden
carot I can go
here and my
bread or maybe I can just keep this in
here same with the
potatoes my special food can go away I
don't need to carry that with me
[Music]
right special food can go
away you go and you go you go
what else why do I have this in my
inventory I want to open exit oh really
I'm not ready to go yet okay then you
get ready here yeah my back this can go
here that can go
here I can a little bit more of those
what
else I'm trying to get really nice and
organized keep on telling me to get
organized
light um
this that can go into the building
right right into
here now this should be good
right
okay oh it was for balls I see okay well
I still have it on me right this is all
the stuff
uh I don't need on me
necessarily
maybe I don't really need these right
now right maybe I should take these for
more buckets I have a lot of buckets
though it should be
[Music]
good oh okay but the eggs is kind of
hard to find oh is there an egg
I'll make one once
again actually maybe I can just make my
special soup right
here let's take a look at the recipe one
last time though no I need bones do you
have stain
[Music]
bones I need
those stain B I have I need more than
that I think let me check let me
check stain bone wait wait
stor maybe just one
okay do I have room to accept I
do thank you okay is that it let's see
now let's see if I can make my special
soup
now
okay here I go oh I need to open the
trade
box okay
and it
goes
okay okay we have the beetroot soup we
have the golden carrot we have the
rabbit St what else did I need a a stain
born oh I forgot the stain meat oh I
have I I think I have stain meat too M
just one moment there we do there we go
there we do um okay let's try this again
stain me robit
still be with golden
[Music]
card
St what else did I need theultimate sou
is this
everything
butter I think this makes it
[Music]
okay I can press it
okay you made your soup the special
stain
[Music]
soup now I'm missing the
bone what else am I missing I like to
make at least three
more is so good I don't know it seems
pretty powerful though it has absorption
2 minutes and strength two 2 minutes I'm
not too sure what that means but make
one for me maybe oh I need to get back
down oh here it
is what do you
need I'm going to put the stuffs away
for now balls can go there actually
this these can be tossed I haven't used
those maybe I can toss those too
let's organize it more these are all
special Foods this is not
special special
food
yeah and
then keep the still in my backpack I'll
put it in there in a bit I'll put all
the special food in there in a bit when
I need
it for now I'll put these cooking good
yeah is there any fire I can
cook oh I don't have any coal though oh
I guess I could
[Music]
cook I'm cooking stff I wanted to cook
one
[Music]
thing can I cook one thing you can have
this
[Music]
oh there the steain
sticks
oh I might have accident took
some do you want them it's okay I'm just
looking okay you can take that
[Music]
then what's in my back
this can go in there and let's get the
trash
sorted don't need the villon I don't
need the
pumpkin right right gold nugget I think
I took your chicken that's okay you can
keep the chicken
I'll why do you have cooked chicken but
no chicken
cuz I got a a a wild
one
that's that very
sure okay let's
go yeah I'm just
confused this can go in there these can
go in there
out okay
[Music]
chick are you sure that you're supposed
to have chickens I am but well there's a
reason for
now
what okay H I felt like I have one thing
I wanted to
do but I can't remember it seems like
everything's still kind of
you
feel it's no sort of maybe huh where's
the safest place to
go is this now my safest place did you
want
meat I have extra meat why do I have to
go she has potato
salad I don't know how to get him
[Music]
over
here over here all the way over
here maybe I went too
far I am
forgetting my
coal I do need to go back over
here I'll think the safe
okay did you want a potato
salad where are
you I'm at the SMY oh not the
horse can I I potato salad for the soup
oh no potato salad is
easy look in your recipe book m
you can cook for yourself too look
potato salad is the first one
right and then there's the special
stting stew
right that's what I just made special
stting Su wait I don't see
it that's because it's really special
how do you get it I can't
remember
yeah I like to try to make the Bor in F
stain I made that oh you made that I
want to make more of that I I I
don't but bread and Ste wrestling I did
the UN wrestling I well you need milk
for that do you have a bucket no do you
have the iron inot yes you can make the
bucket then ah okay just go visit the
crafting
table and then make a bucket shape with
the iron angle
[Music]
what we can go get milk together if you
want a small bucket
[Music]
maybe is that a
bucket I don't know I don't know
what should I make next
just I don't want to make the noodles a
fish and chips I made and that was yummy
made the breakfast toast the seafood
diam seems
interesting but the
B you got it so we go and find the cows
okay let's go to the
planes did you want potato salad I don't
need one I don't need this one though
okay well it sounds like nobody needs it
take it take it I don't want it I don't
want it much potato salad I don't want
it you can go sell
it I'm going to go to the the
[Music]
PLS there's the
C okay this time I'm not going to be
[Music]
white what am I fighting
how
much oh that's that's what you're doing
they don't stock just be
aware then I only have one milk you only
have one milk
maybe
milk another
milk okay I got my
milk I don't know if I want water though
maybe I can pour it out
hey what should I go the water no no no
milk milk not not Dam itk milk milkk
milk milk can I just milk
milk ouch
milk the cow is now
upset I don't want them I don't want the
water anymore
I need to eat
something I need to eat something I need
to do that
[Music]
quick okay here we
fight okay I don't have as much milk as
I hoped maybe that's
okay okay I'm going back wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait
wait oh gosh what's happening I'm
[Music]
going I need to empty my bucket on my
own
M ouch that's right that's right the
milkshake
I'm kind of curious about making the
milk
[Music]
shake let's
see I've never made the
milkshake I have
sugar the arm wrestling do I have a
recipe for now I do not it
[Music]
what you have you made a oh gosh
goodby the
CPS looking
for oh
secret okay okay okay
here
okay I don't need the water I can get
rid of the water here right oh
no there we
go okay everything's
fresh
okay what was I
doing I was trying to make the
milkshake my to doesn't look so magical
anymore
okay speak to the BART
temp
okay let's do it
[Music]
for the horse will go fast enough
special
St golden
carrot I don't know what to think
anymore or
can where do I get a golden carrot start
with the ingredients obtain the
ingredients for the milkshake okay OB te
with milk yeah I got the milk an apple
apple
melon Sweet Berry I got the sweet okay
that's easy enough where's the apples
apples melon
slice did I keep the melon slice I
didn't keep the melon
slice
apple apple
where am
I
[Music]
Apple I'm lost a
little do you have
apples the oak trees no
apples okay should be
good let's go
get the melon the melon should be easy
R it's
me I just want
this
melon okay let's Warp
apples come from which trees again maybe
the
[Music]
forest
elevation oak trees oak trees oak trees
in the
forest maybe that was white
hugget how do I get not have my axe with
me
huh well I guess it's the soider then
you o tree oak
tree and then the carrot okay I think I
remember where the oak trees
were okay okay should be good enough
just from the leaves it has to be oak
trees though
right that was a spruce just now are you
an oak tree
[Music]
really
levation now everybody's quiet
huh come on are you an oak
tree
[Music]
Oak okay we'll just kind of stay here
for a little but
that okay I have garbage I can throw
away right I can do just that okay I
don't need the oak loocks oh like this I
don't need the Spruce Wood no I don't
need the stained slime malls and I don't
really need that but I could keep it I
could keep it I could throw it
away I don't
that okay that
it should be safe now
right right let's get some food just in
case is it apples apples apples apples
apples give me apples give me apples
please I would like some
apples have eight apples yet
oh I don't see any apples are you sure
about
this
[Music]
course I wish you could just show me
this is so tricky
well I know where I get the Apple where
are
you I don't know how much else I can I
feel like 20 no apples
yet do I have space for it I do
still i s a little bit
longer why it has the melon in the B I
have I have the melon now I have the
berries
too I just need the
[Music]
Apple I give up on this tree maybe this
tree is just no
good feel like this tree is even higher
up it's even
taller only have
one
sapling what else
[Music]
I should eat something
huh
really oh you're alive
still why are you
alive oh cuz I'm not hitting you with my
sword
oh I was like wow it's so strong
I got an
app back we go the best Castle why can't
I
move okay let's build some garbage first
though cuz I do know I have
garbage this is garbage this can be
garbage too a lot of not
garbage I didn't do it
right and you go any you go and you go
and you go that
[Music]
is okay let's
go
okay wonderful boy tender I have
everything go really slow
no it's time for me to make it there it
is how much wood do I need
let's check the book once
more
oh oh he told me bucket of milk Apple
melon Sweet
Berry yes I have
this okay I does he want me to cook it
myself
done bucket of milk melon Apple oh the
sweet Berry that's why he's not
[Music]
happy there we do the cting supp yeah
let me mix that up oh quite tasty but
not quite when I remember the milk shap
I have a sticker and a
richer t one slime jum I made the Slime
jum before it was
berries I think I can make that right
now right yeah
okay
yes
okay let's go like
this and sweet B
[Music]
Su
up F balls in here I know have
enough okay sweet berries sugar slime
ball cook there we go and
back back you go back you go back you
go good where did it go
no okay mix it in it's getting closer
but the m you more
expensive a golden apple do I still have
my previous Apple I do okay okay okay I
have the gold no on
me okay we're going to have to go get it
then I thought that this would be easy
making a a milkshake but apparently it's
not this is the wrong way I don't live
at the C
[Music]
okay I'm going to do it I'm going to
make it and then everybody will be like
wow F you made the best milkshake ever I
like yes I'm fua I make the best
milkshakes oh there we
go okay oh it's still flooded here wow I
caused a bit of
a am I going to be able to make it still
here because it's
a okay don't
tell
okay here we
[Music]
go at least you know it's relaxing the
sound of water there
ah I need to make it
with can I just do it like here right
was it like this
yeah that's enough this goes back here
that goes
away
goodbye okay we're going to put some
we're going to make some milk that's
what we're going to
do here we go water here we go and the b
and a and then we're going to stock the
buckets and then we're going to stock
the milk
yes
okay now we can go eat and then this way
I can get
theug and I can take this
SP oh I still more butter here I can put
more butter there but not too many I can
put the I might as well put the B into
this and now I press this and then I
take h no it's a crafting table
right let's see I will show you that I
could do this all on my
own I put the Apple here and then around
around around around around
[Music]
around was this not it
boys okay that's okay I still have them
though so it's okay in the end but it's
a little disappointing I guess I'll put
you there I was so so ready to be
[Music]
correct there there there there there
there there there
[Music]
haha okay we just needed the golden
apple
[Music]
right this is not the
right I made a bit of a a problem there
bit of a
[Music]
m oh I can make the nuget back into them
okay that's okay for now it's just
taking up more room huh did I need
anything else this is just the golden
apple Maybe
I don't know if I'm going to be able to
make
this okay let's see almost
there
okay goodness I can't think you enough
this is right oh
ba I did it I did it do I still have it
I still have it
wow what's
thisall I have the St oh the stew the
special stain stew yeah is that you H
yeah bu ba I don't have enough stuff
though what stuff can I just give you
what stuff um I have parts of it but I
don't think it's could what what do you
mean I have like the beetroot stuff the
beetroot do you have the robit
too yeah that's a lot of golden carrots
um I don't need all
that I don't need all
that use use it to make it I have those
I know but make me
something I can't get everything else
why uh let me check let me check what I
don't have
[Music]
still
okay to make
more I need
[Music]
I need okay I have the golden carrots I
think I have more beetroot soup I need
more rabbits too I don't know how to
make that I need more stain Bones the
rabbits Doo you need ramit and a whole
bunch of extra things it wasn't easy to
make good luck I'm going to put my stuff
away I don't think I'm going to be able
to make it okay I'm just going to create
the ultimate milkshake and then we see
what's
next okay here we go golden apple melon
sliced slime Jam milk bucket I got
it let's see if I remember Golden Apple
baa melon slice milk
bucket can I get please slime down is
this right if I
press I'm not going to regret it right
yes
okay that's what KY was
selling okay it's very special very very
special wow why is the water
here what is going
on you having
problems water
I
[Music]
water why is it water
outside play let just let me
in H the reason why there's water is I
might have spilled it there oh you
spiled
it you CL no I did it on purpose why and
then it kind of stuck there I thought it
go away you know like into the
ground it did not
though I don't know how to fix
it it's kind of fled now so I guess it's
okay okay
I'm thank you I'm going to put my other
stuff I put my Construction Supplies in
here melon in here the bucket stucks the
buckets go in there I'm going to spill
some more water I think I didn't need
the water buckets in the end I thought
you know for soup you need
water apparently you
don't I got to make sure I spill it
outside should I spill it in the same
spot kind of floating away
[Music]
next
bucket okay oh it's a bit more watery
now I hope that's okay
M I got beautiful water
sounds okay and where did all my other
buckets go
did I put them in my cooking
bag I put them in my cooking
[Music]
bag this is good I don't have any more
ultimate recipes to make do
[Music]
I
okay okay I just want to make some more
B and Fri STS that would be cool to try
and make
that
by did I get a Little Bit Stronger oh my
gosh the pond is getting
bigger I was advised to dig a hole dig a
hole then dig a
hole dig a tiny hole a tiny hole maybe
I'll dig it right
here it didn't help what it didn't help
get up with the
bucket I don't want our
house don't have it flood into our
house I tried this is the chain sword
base it didn't work that's a 4x4 hole
right put the water in the hole first I
don't have any empty oh I do there's the
empty bucket I don't want to I don't why
did I put the bucket the water
bigger I can't put the water back in the
[Music]
bucket are you
drowning I'm trying to did I no no water
in the bucket it looks like it's getting
bigger no why look add the
soce oh apparently that's the SCE I got
one water bucket
[Music]
I'm trying to put it in
here it's not
working Pi another
[Music]
hole I will lost of water
buckets okay okay their house is okay
for now I don't want that much
water okay more
water more water
bucket
okay can't get any of the water I don't
know where the source is
either well let's hope it doesn't get
worse I'm trying my best here
[Music]
I only put a little bit of water and now
there's a lot of
water it's definitely getting worse
right
water can you help
[Music]
it I it's not making a difference is it
no how many sources like three buckets
worth wait what
fill it up with
blocks okay did it get better I don't
think
so it look like I took some water but
there's still just as much
[Music]
water I think it's just as bad
put more
blocks more
blocks like right here I only have four
blocks hopefully that does
it oh
oh kind of kind of kind
of there's still water over here though
I think it's on the other side
ow I did originally spill the water on
the other side
so well it's not that big of an issue
maybe we can just leave it like that
it's just a natural on that's fine
yeah nobody saw anything
I'm out of
blocks
and did that help
no oh
okay it's just it's just a water source
now and then there's just a little a
little pool right there
yeah it's beautiful
[Music]
what's the point of
here to get
married to get married yeah I was
thinking the queen could get married
here oh I guess I don't know if I like
that well maybe uh I'm
lost maybe this is where our journey
ends for tonight I'm going to go and
smells right here
yeah right here we
see
okay revolation
[Music]