[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
oh yeah we're rotating and this time
it's my turn to be uh yeah lack of sleep
and early wake up hello good morning
hey
[Music]
yeah
I will follow you I will be brain empty
but uh it will be fine
well let's do this then yeah we got this
first we should introduce ourselves I
think just real quick yeah yes who we're
playing hi my name is Maury Calliope and
I am playing this beautiful being from
God
um this half work Barbarian Berserker
Barbarian named Mario pay
um she loves to smash she's not really
good at work and she's not super smart
hey
yeah all right sorry that my character
looks hotter than yours
okay let's dramatized
I ran into a scene where something
similar to you was smashing and yeah I
know what you're doing
I mean in a bad way like yucky
but you are introduce
you uh
uh I am the I think I'm a ranger
I'm kiwawa and I don't have a POV today
but stream POV in my new album point of
view let's go
[Music]
let's go yeah thank you I don't know
I'll pass it to whoever takes a pass
catch Hyatt
I'm sorry
[Music]
and I'm playing as bagel
The Gnome sorcerer I'm uh what is it
yeah I'm a story sir right now and I'm
ready to get heated yep you look like
breakfast
yeah you do oh you're making me hungry
people no we're TV
okay you're your face is right where it
is
Raven Croft I am playing as narissa I
didn't realize uh when we made it that
everyone was gonna name themselves silly
stuff so oops but uh I'm this very uh
sexy uh looking deepling right here I'm
also uh currently a Bard might swap over
I haven't decided yet um probably will
stay as this so maybe but being a part
is so useful so far man I know I I just
look I have a plan now that I've played
through so much of the game I need an
item and I feel like it will work better
if I'm a cleric we're not we're not the
experts anymore
[Laughter]
the rest of us I think right wow
addicted yeah very addicted oh my God
but we have uh after last time concluded
to you know stay together a little bit
more right yeah we're going to go a bit
uh a little bit slower maybe yeah of
course we can't look at everything but
at least we look at things together
maybe this time yeah Kelly will take the
lead today right okay yeah I can be the
leader leader
what she looks at if she looks at a
cutscene or so moriope says team huddle
team huddle okay okay
how are we going to do this because
because we can make it a bloodbath or we
can try and be charismatic and kind of
like snake our way in there
Charisma Charisma wow can we be Charisma
first and then kill them later
yeah yeah we have the option to kill
them at any time so why not go in well
first so then we can uh you know talk to
their Trader and everything yeah exactly
yeah yeah
yeah how do we make our exit yeah go in
like an arrow go in clean pull out real
bloody oh it's gonna be awesome God and
gory all right so who's charismatic
forward I am charismatic I need a quick
one yeah you go
yeah
already at the end of act two oh my God
was there a druid amongst these
Intruders a true wheat I'll be sure
got one of them chined up below oh it's
involved are we are we talking about
Polo
not volo's human Druid is halson yeah do
we want to go straight to him and start
that or do we want to look around first
um
we should round a little bit yeah yeah
there's like a close spy Quest that says
rescue Volo
I thought it was about Volo oh wait
let's rescue he might he might be yeah
rescue
let's go
let's go all right I believe we take a
right okay all right
follow me ladies
oh they're doing some freaky over
here all right it's dangerous music yeah
the music starts
oh let's go help him
let's go help him maybe let's help this
guy be okay he's being tortured okay
we're about to find out
peace you know oh no
no don't whack him with your stick
nobody likes to get wet with a stick
thank you
no no no no no baseball
wow can you please put some clothes on
I'm begging you I don't think so I don't
think I will
look we can't handle your beauty it's
it's too beautiful yeah it's too much
for us yeah we use both this looks
interesting let me put him through his
Paces oh Jesus use your brain worm
please my brain worm we should use the
yeah isn't brainworm bad
says
food that is true you don't need them
for the election
in the future it's like a chain coat a
shiversary I'll use my my brain Powers
Mom I'm sorry can you say that again
please
just don't be too rough maybe all right
is that a challenge
oh what you gonna do to him I don't know
I'm gonna go talk to him now yeah come
take a look
hi
I'm really thinking about it now I do
like to smash
ing is is very powerful but uh let's see
we need information first what all right
good one
I lost sight of him
okay I don't know if he's still alive no
bear that's all it'd be easy to find
them
yes
think about it
keep trying you'll figure it out
wow Jesus I will help you
all right sleight of hand pick the lock
good luck oh here can I add something
here let me help okay yeah yeah guidance
thanks appreciate it big UPS together
[Music]
oh my gosh oh
fun
sorry I didn't see at the bottom whether
you could it's okay I I was I think I
was gonna try
um
next time next time definitely if you
willed this to happen you forced it I
sure did and now I have no Inspirations
and the Goblin's not gonna notice that
you just set somebody free you're you're
a true Soul what are they gonna do
before they catch us
um quick question do we share
inspiration
[Music]
inspiration comes from your different
goals okay yeah because we get like
separate inspiration I think right okay
okay yeah oh it is shared apparently yes
it is but we get it from different
actions yeah very sorry for using it up
I think we should ask it's okay let's
ask in the future I thought we had our
own inspiration let's not it's more
inspired more I wanted I wanted to let
him go we we really really want to say
that though I'm inspired I just gotta oh
yeah I got inspired too so there you go
we saved him
let's uh let's go over in the room to
the
to the left of where we entered oh okay
okay
see all right I see you're going this
way I love this guy I know me too hi
um
that's why you guys like this all I see
no there is
a character
what is he is he a companion no no okay
he's a freak
this man is
yeah he does look like he could be one
ah
are you also here too he's got nipples
he does he does he does
right there I'm surprised they don't
have clamps
yes
you'll see why
her face
these goblins seem to thrive on the
crude and primitive you pain without
purpose is a terrible thing
wouldn't you agree
go off I guess who invited you a goblin
what are you gonna do
I want him to beat my ass and oh
you are a match yucky trying to discuss
such can that happen these and you'll
seem simply maybe I'm not sure forgive
me but
look
something terrible
terrible to you
[Laughter]
imagine just saying that excuse me
you're sorry
because I just have some naturally sad
looking eyes
ah you guys are the same
trouble you're the same therefore we
should smooch suffered in these yeah is
he flirting with me times
nah he just wants to beat you up this
little one I can tell you
you've been angry oh you look so
concerned yeah I need some help you guys
please
I guarantee you a hug is nicer than
whatever he's about to do
is
the likes of which few experience God is
a woman
just like she said
yes Ariana yes oh
I have
I have Exquisite quizzes wow Divine
possibly
plants
[Laughter]
what is he gonna do oh you'll see him
oh boy he's gonna give you a big hug
from behind well what face of what is
that
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
wow getting my ass feed
it
gives me a permanent bust it does
yeah
I I talked to him because I don't
understand no
no wore that um
or we can add still
I I'm not gonna assist you in this one
my friend this is all you good luck oh
my god wow
[Music]
give me more oh my God Big Game of
Thrones vibes
[Laughter]
[Music]
I need the blessing
right now
don't kill him I need him I I don't
think he needs help I think she likes it
yeah
you look tired should I take over
so into this right yeah
[Laughter]
hurry up man
it's really okay
[Laughter]
welcome the pain let it become hard okay
all right another net
hey when he's done with you can I beat
you up like that of course if you'd like
yeah sure
why he got to be so freaky about it
he's like killing you that's okay
no no no no no I'm gonna get a buff I'm
gonna get a buff I am proud to have
served you this thank you for the tenant
they're much harder bro
yucky
don't be disgusted you have some acid
dummy
I'm getting a blessing you guys volcano
blessing
I don't know
[Laughter]
he's so crazy foreign
hit points or less you get a two uh plus
two bonus to attack rolls with and
wisdom saving throws for three turns
yum
and it's permanent you never lose it let
me get a hit in yeah okay okay there you
go okay permanent I I was gonna do it
with my fist but I was holding
experience yeah no I've I've never I've
I've I don't know if maybe it's a glitch
if you're supposed to lose it but I've
had it forever I I did it once and I was
like hahaha and then I was like oh this
will fade and then I was like it didn't
go away
and now one went away
yeah
oh it's you guys gonna get your asses
until the end of the playthrough oh
that's cool you lose it in act two oh
okay
oh can we all get it
I don't know did I ruin it for everyone
I don't want it
yeah
that's that's valid that's valid all
right well he doesn't seem keen on
giving it to others that's okay I'm
sorry I'm his favorite or something
now let's go free Zolo follow me yes
Volo
sorry my brain is on one piece right now
let's go
[Music]
age
okay well look when we talk to him it's
ah there oh let's just have a chat
you know are you a woman in charge here
by chance a friendly face
it doesn't look like we can chat can we
chat with him we could just kill her
we could well just can't I just feel
like that that's right here's here's the
thing yeah if we have if we have the
doors closed
they won't stop us but it's the
foundation I mean that's true
peace
[Music]
maybe we could strike a deal he's asking
really car and Lou to unlock herself
think about it oh if he's asking nicely
we should help him out right do what
your heart tells you Leon
all right I'll get you out bless you my
friend I'll wait nicely but
he's still daddy
does anybody have an unlocked a lock
thingy
can we just can we just smack the door
um I think so but we'll have to kill the
lady in here unless she left I don't see
her no
don't worry the door is closed it won't
it won't you it won't make anyone angry
uh
fight ladies yeah attack off attack
is this her this is her
take her down bam
too easy
yeah
for him now oh we got I got his keys I
can open the door oh okay yeah go for it
open it up yeah yeah
I'm quite safe
he does owe me
if that's your character
tell me where we can meet each other
once we slip the goblin yoke and I'll
offer much more than ghosts oh is he
gonna join our camera
no way
Theresa did you save him in your
playthrough I don't even I think I
accidentally skipped him oh my god oh I
know you I can't take him to Camp okay
yes go to
go down entertainment
[Music]
your actions
wait what happened it's invisible Jordan
invisible and ran away hi wait what
happened oh it's called we're now yeah
we now have to kill everyone here let's
go
all right
he's dead now we gotta fight
mm-hmm
oh oh no not the Wardrobe
you gotta destroy those
um
uh let's run
let's get out of here let's just dance
oh so do you want us to run
no we we we we won't win but we can try
to fight this
out of my way
oh you hit so hard that's so nice
yeah that's what I'm here for I guess
oops
oh man
oh yeah this is this is just one boss so
there's three different bosses here yeah
um if we kill them we get their brain
worms Oh brain worms yeah brain worms
and we can eat them kind of delicious
I gotta catch them all exactly if anyone
has AOE I feel like that would
definitely be the move here can you
please I'm sorry can you please tell me
what AOE means
it's like big big attack that hits
multiple people
I have one of those
kind of definitely use those when
they're grouped up together
yeah
rag slim aggroes the entire Camp I
wonder why these guys are aggroad at us
yeah
maybe they definitely figured out we
committed murder yeah
my wolf is somehow stuck like kind of
far away I can't move him I don't know
why
poor lupus no it's okay I have an idea
whenever I get a turn again in a million
years oh he's being attacked by the
goblin oh what do you miss no he's
having his own fight over there
okay your turn
which one which one let's go for this
one
foreign
nice
hit
so I'm gonna shoot something out and you
guys need to not walk through it or
it'll hurt you okay are you talking
about the uh dagger cloud of daggers
yeah yeah those are so good
they are we can push people off of stuff
and they'll take damage if they oh yeah
yeah but if you knock anyone into a
Chasm please know that you will not be
able to collect any of their loot ah
okay but it is you have no spell slots
that's it
they say I'm looking at your chat
they say you have no spells it's not
even my turn I don't know what that
means I
oh my God they're right it's probably oh
it's okay I have some I I might I
have an alien
um
I'm sorry I'm sorry run away
oh she's okay she's okay
we can definitely kill these guys don't
even worry about it are you sure yeah
yeah should be fine not with me almost
killing Kiana she'll be okay
all right get ready to feel pain dummies
do your best
yes and then keep in mind we have the
boss right behind me right right behind
you
yeah okay
she's got 40 Health yeah she came up
pretty quick
and she's very strong
a completely cheesed that Boss by the
way before so oh I killed her easily
let's go
on the way
oh my god there are so many but I feel
like you can do it we can do it yeah we
can do it we'll see
how I believe
okay I blame Volvo for this
Volvo Volo
[Laughter]
[Music]
she's a true Soul High Priestess of the
absolute well don't take an action jump
as a bonus action okay
okay yeah
kick her ass b-boom yeah is that the
boss sure yeah
I was still blinded
ah all right it looks like you should be
out of the smoke poke into the dark
I want to use a spell but I don't want
to use it when I have a disadvantage
will she attack me if I run blind
almost because you're awesome they have
the little thing poking at you and you
get out of the cloud yeah you just have
to walk but you walk slower
okay I will for now I'll do this
oh
nice
I was sick okay and look she's all shot
I'll work on her for a little bit until
I get out of the line
we will cover you yeah you got you got
any uh health potions yes I do waiting
for my turn to do it sorry for killing
you on accident it's okay
I'm so good
there you go that's not much but a
little bit yeah it'll keep you on your
feet
oh maybe the guy in front of you if you
can attack
I hope it doesn't miss
hey good job
yay
um
[Music]
I want to save you but I gotta
focus on frenzying Raging out I'll just
go back to sleep
okay we need you and your cute animals
I'll see you in five
okay
all right just sweet dreams
don't let the team be wiped don't let it
happen please no party wipes
it's fine oh
yeah when in doubt do a bar dance yeah
maybe the enemies will start to like us
I'll go easier yeah yeah wow
very smart let's see oh good we're no
longer blinded yeah
yeah sure why not
cool
nice yeah there goes another one of them
everywhere everywhere whoa
poison
ow Never Take Me Alive
the song of my people
Let The Bodies Hit The Floor
Let The Bodies Hit The Floor only for
strengths
it's fine okay um yeah do your best
try to
kill her
yes
that would be the move
I need to jump I'll jump to
Chihuahua
what careful there's acid on the floor
oh yeah cause you turn away from him oh
that's why he tries to hit you there's
like a red arrow whenever you turn away
from an enemy also I can't jump you no
you can you can do it again you can try
again if it's still
yeah I still have a bonus then you can
you can try again okay
nice
I was sick
okay
are you kidding me
[Music]
I was the percentage 60. Yeah that's not
really good I've noticed that 60 is
pretty much zero in this game yeah
can do it
Kelly focus on damage nice nice
okay I can't heal you though
sorry do you have potions Kiara I I
uh
you have one one potion yeah I should I
I still can't use it I can throw it yeah
you have to use it when you're in a turn
so
don't die just um is dangerous too yeah
yeah we're all we're all we're not doing
so hot gamers
we'll be fine
whatever disadvantage
nice nice oh that feels good
I should be fine if I can fly out of
here ah come on
why do they all go for me oh
[Music]
I don't think we're gonna make it
this is no workout for us if we just
it's just these guys
[Music]
no I'm gonna still try to get the boss
yeah
What if I
jump jump
dang it
um tried to hit you
jump
okay
nice
please
[Music]
have a big chunk of damage into her
she's almost down yeah
yeah and she's out of there okay and I'm
connected to her so I can hit again
hopefully nice
are you kidding me uh just plus four
okay okay
um
Volo
yeah me Volo if it weren't for us
freeing you yeah
yeah honestly this is all his fault oh
his fault all of it
I feel like their attacks aren't missing
us as much as they should be yeah
they're getting really they have really
good like we're we're missing a lot of
things
yeah
and I'm about to die maybe it's all up
to you too let's go game of the century
um
do we you know yeah actually
nice nice
okay now block my way hit Cali
people are you sure about that oh my God
oh my God she survived
I can't believe it
that's wild oh Mori all over again okay
okay
yeah suck on that
all right it's my turn
no it's not why only five dang it okay
um can I heal your life's so close
do I have a better heel
probably not
where the healy's at
fridge me
oh HP in a dream dang it stop it
kneeling her
oh I can always almost up succeeding in
my death froze
I I will not die what what
a companion yeah yeah 36 HP okay all
right and we are you will live for
breakfast compare that to my one HP wolf
and spiders nice nice nice nice
let's go
able to do it
yeah it's fine that doesn't look so good
okay well maybe maybe
we tried we tried okay
only short rest is available oh
we are trapped we are in prison um okay
well let's get out of prison
so short dressed at least
um yeah give us a little bit of Health I
can't see anything oh okay there we go
maybe there's a key somewhere lock pick
somewhere
um
wait what about the way the guy jumps
you know oh hey look what's in here
became less protrude from the hole
mysterious hole oh someone failed to
escape
okay yes
I'll pull it free actually
come on out I want to see some good
oh
[Music]
oh what what
is
it
okay it's okay
it's okay
oh let's go let's go we can do this
jumps
probably yeah
Good Luck Good Luck now we totally got
this they took all of our weapons what
ah yeah haven't you noticed we don't
have any weapons
[Music]
thank you
wait I have no spells either
yeah yeah they took your magic ability
away yeah yeah load it can we load can
we load a save maybe backpack a little
bit
uh when we started the Stream
no auto save nah we should I should have
been saving it
today can I go back into the hole is
that possible in the hole the other way
I don't see the hole anymore maybe it
was above us maybe we still use our
fists it's it's in the little it's
behind you
can't go in though
I guess we just punched them
it guys we ball we have to ball
okay items I have some bombs uh I have
no items now oh okay oh I still have I
still have some spells I guess yeah we
have nothing they literally wow
frenzy all right all just Frenzy
and we'll just punch him
today
[Music]
go away
no she's too far away okay uh
the skeleton has a candle and a ring of
poison resistance but that doesn't help
um
but I was thinking maybe somewhere here
there's a weapon or so
maybe the other sacrifagos we can pick
their their weapons up if we kill them
yeah
so good luck guys free money
all right just turned uh okay here we go
the one
What's it gonna do oh no
[Music]
we can still do it
what happens if we die here again do we
just go back into prison
probably
um
an Armstrong
no
wow really well if it isn't the
consequences of my actions because I
think this all started because of me
that's all right it's cool
you know oil then yes
okay I'll still try it even though
there's no oil
[Music]
um
55 is pretty low oh
I need to hold on I know I don't know
what happened but yeah yeah I mean it
hit I guess
that's
um most of what I can do
oh no worries it's fine
I'm taking it uh
we can get weapons if we loot them
afterwards yeah go just one yeah the
arrow would be nice bow
Nani
it didn't work it was super dead
if you get me up maybe you can use me as
a weapon
yeah I could throw you yeah so yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
but if I turn around now I'm gonna get
beaten yeah if someone could get me out
I can
run to you I guess
to get
enrage throw
leather boots
I was sure that would work
I was sure
well we tried yeah this doesn't look too
good for us
um however however
um well
you know we could just reload and then
what we could do is all the scenes that
we already did uh everyone can
individually go and do one yeah
we just go back in jail
you can we just we just won't kill the
lady again this time yeah we haven't
done much progress anyway yeah yeah yeah
so I say I say we just let's just get
out of here
let's do it let's do a long run all
right hold on a second what's up
hold on oh it just launches and it'll
it'll uh alert people it's so cool
yeah it's like it's like the sauron's
eye nice
who are you uh she's the one whose
underwear we need to steal okay there we
go all righty everybody we're going back
to the game quickly get beat yeah
yeah I'll get beat and then we'll do a
long rest and then we'll uh you guys can
free the guy while I'm doing that so you
don't have to walk yeah
[Music]
did you get something
no did you participate at all no
ah it is what it is all right now let's
onward to help Zorro
it's just another can you help a guy
still yeah take care of the guy the guy
yeah
right all right and I go to my destiny
again
is the guy uh the guy is not Volo right
you're not talking about Volo no not yet
it's the symbol nah he's just a random
dude cool sits through you all right you
you girls you girls take care of that
you'd rescue them how possible
thank you
let's hope you don't fail twice again
let me give you guidance I I was with a
group of adventurers
let's do this again
yeah hold on wait wait no game okay of
course no pain no gain exactly
can can we we can
nice little rescue bolo though without
getting in trouble yeah
okay cool
free
I wanna save all along
no we gotta save the barn
okay
and you I mean do you need savings no no
I'm good I'm good okay
there's a nice looking book here
be wary of your mortal limitations
nerissa okay
is tempting to allow Payne's ecstasies
to sweep you away particularly during a
delicious bout of self-regulation broken
bones Hindu worship avara made in those
pains
so don't go too far
eh don't go too far with the pain
what do you mean broken bones hinder the
Revelation or something like that
oh I'll be fine
where'd he go wait wait why is he
running outside
he's on a mission where is he going to
come back more pain
where is he going are you afraid
hello why are you frightening
them guys get away from him he'd be
frightened to me oh is he scared of your
dog yeah she's scared he's scared of
your dog
what a baby
I don't know okay why don't you guys go
heal let's go
okay it goes insulted by that okay go
save go save your little guy
Cali do a save do a save before I do
that
[Music]
oh he's running oh my god get yourself
okay he's not even in the room
[Laughter]
they ran away he ran away
he literally just ran all the way away
yeah he he went up an iron ladder well
maybe that was just my way of protecting
Universe why would you do that to me
because I love you don't you know that
yeah
that's the symbols
did I should I Authority this Goblin
lady
yeah I I encountered Raphael who's
Raphael is Raphael who is that
Satan Satan oh yeah that sounds like it
I
you climbed up a ladder and much Satan
hold on I'm a second dialogue
that doesn't look like Satan he's not
not yet pigeons all yours yay okay I got
bolo's key what what happened
conversation
maybe maybe he will give you the pain
that you need to gain
he's he's just threatening me but like
he's trying to not sound like he's
threatening me oh no oh no please no I'm
in the middle of something Rafael no
no
where are you going
[Laughter]
oh beautiful is this hell let's go wait
I want some food too so can you take me
too
what are you guys seeing
the House of Hope
that's a beautiful picture oh if I go to
oh I see a join conversation enjoy
yourself oh
oh
last
last no
no
um
no eat some food
laughs
[Laughter]
potentially an adversary
concealed conceivably
savior
that's
that's certain oh let's go ah
I don't trust him but
it's my compassion
Raphael is something something else
please I'm in the middle of another
cutscene can you hurry it up and dire me
I don't know why we just encountered
this time two tenants
and no
no he sounds really compassionate yeah
what a nice dude look at that oh cool
painting wow fancy house and what is
madness but a denial of reality still
I have a feeling you change your mind
before it's changed for you shut up
shop around beg borrow and why did this
happen to me every possibility until why
did I climb up that ladder he heard you
like evil people yeah aren't you a demon
too I mean yeah I mean in dream I'm just
a tiefling I'm not technically an
infernal you know
okay can you send me back
let me back such a jeez
this is what you get for for just
looking out for the pain
I'll be around
watching you squirm like a Deadpool yeah
he's self-interested but not even in a
fun way like hysterian is
manifested yet in a bad way he's just
annoying I knew he doesn't even call me
darling I knew it I know I'm so mad I
called it
sounded so sad in the beginning when
narissa was like I don't like this dude
you're like I thought you'd like him
because I know narissa I was like of
course
and she didn't believe me well here we
are where is my pain guy
why is he just gone
wolves okay
I have a I have the key
set him free hello
I'm here to finish my question
my blessings
and I didn't have to kill her this time
so they're not aggro to us
this is the good timeline
yoke and I'll offer how much more than
gold I got to skip like the other two
okay that's not too bad it's priceless
nice
oh okay we should long run oh you got
the pain after all girl yeah he just
like randomly re-showed up so um
wait to pick your brain
the buff isn't really permanent anyway
it's bugged is it really
okay we can rest now he he went away
yeah yeah this time he was really
invisible I really didn't see him yeah
he went invisible
last time all right let's let's Camp
let's Camp you guys want to go camp uh
yeah yeah let's go to camp
do you want to end the day yeah
yeah yeah yeah
oh and let's save
oh yeah okay
what's happening what's happening am I
okay I don't feel so good
it's not a tummy bug moist you're
gonna transform
sorry people you're about to become
you're about to become um you can't be
helped mind flayer we're gonna have to
kill you sorry boo the run's over for
you
your hands Shake as they reach upward
wet Palms spaghetti arms spaghetti wipe
arms spaghetti arm spaghetti oh no
she's here I'm gonna kill you no I
thought wait we're friends that's why I
hate it
well I thought we were
traveling Partners I guess
she hates everybody
and I hate her yeah I don't think we
really I don't think anyone here really
likes her oh no I really like her in my
run she's so freaking powerful
the vampire dude over here myself
[Music]
they're both really helpful on my teams
where
um I have I have persuasion I uh
use my wrist
I will say sorry uh guidance to
Advantage roll let's go yeah
is that spot When the Roll doesn't show
up probably I think so
big
I cannot trust my own mind all the
approach it seems I must trust yours I
Will Wait Marissa is lagging now because
it's above no because of the cutscene
okay
since I'm playing it alone I turned up I
forgot I turned up everything to the map
okay wait we need to revive a Starion
please before we leave but Marissa if it
gets too much
I'm in a dream no I I can I can turn it
down during that I mean because there's
a there's the the leak the thingy the
thingy hey it's Mommy
hey my other bearded friends oh my God
the garden
okay
the memory leak oh yes my fellow bearded
lady hello
dark man mommy wow
hello Mommy
wow wow I know your voice I've heard it
before
you have go I saved you mother
Mommy
my savior
mommy oh she's the one oh
can you romance Your Guardian I want to
romance my Guardians myself yeah
I made my guardian so hot like
mine you seems so nice
She's So Perfect
take the hand offer to you uh no Maury
the Beard's voice
[Laughter]
people are saying technically you can
romance them oh technically this time
nice
yeah let's go I didn't know that angel
within you within you it comes from that
parasite your instinct is to resist the
power itself
telling us wait is he actually bad I
will keep um don't say anything don't
spoilers
yeah no spoilers but the the point is
they're hot because we designed
them because I feel like why not because
the the worm in our brain is bad and now
they're saying to use the yeah yeah so I
feel like they're bad
so I actually uh I don't know so it's
not really a spoiler because I don't
know but um I don't know
I like them me too I'm willing to take
help from anyone who's willing to help
me in this game
because if none of the companions are
attractive for a way that you like then
you just make one potentially true
just like this
exactly like this I have to go
the enemy is closing in so is this some
kind of dream world or where are we
the astral plane
isn't that the place between death and
life I know I have charm no idea whoa
you'll feel better
I promise
that is true if hot then yeah it's hot
then why hot yeah it can't be that wrong
if evil why hot girls right
now
so I guess let's see
um yeah we're going back
shall we wait wait wait wait wait
no you have to finally okay you have to
talk to skele bro uh where is he he's
over here I'm going nowhere and the door
get on the floor everybody walk the
dinosaur I'm not giving him his clothes
back though that's fine I'm not giving
him his clothes back either
he's okay
oh
yep
yeah fashion stuff Run Deep for cutest
OG son he's all right yeah he's pretty I
mean he I wish he had more of a nose but
suspicious
let's talk about something else very
well wait uh I can only say change class
I can't choose Revival
go talk to him maybe maybe somebody else
talk to him I shall be here
um
[Music]
good morning
talk to me why won't he talk to me oh
she's talking to someone okay oh
citizen
he doesn't even mention it when you beat
him up
this is clueless
[Music]
you can always see the bite marks pretty
well
it's just ripped
even when it comes to mind a parasite
now was there anything else but Vic
lives it's Vic so tell cool I'm a
magistrate the one from a ttrpg we did
with myth
the vampire NPC there's always one
Grandpa you always way more annoying
than him though
Starion is nice sir I like it
fellow
I'll just make myself just be
comfortable please
of course
[Laughter]
is my job my friend if there's anything
in the world worth knowing
I assure you you do be everywhere
okay uh you know what I'll talk to you
more in my private run
okay
should we also talk to Gail because he
has yeah exclamation mark hello Cat Em
Up
yeah
okay most all the romance options are
pretty good actually but I don't have
time to do runs to romance all of them
I'm not really feeling anyone in the
game
companion romantic I have this
you like have able to fight with you
romanceable yeah I'm pretty sure
um
do I
I guess I'll try that thank you for the
offer
but the treatment for my condition is
very specific and what it comes down to
is this I know I know you want the items
magical item yeah we're trying to give
him a bunch of those and none of them
were good enough for him and he got mad
and ready wow
ing one yeah
[Music]
one worth helping him when we're not
taking him with us anyway really
don't worry about it
since before we were abducted
as early as possible yeah yeah Gail
she's annoying I really love him
intervention
Dale you have an addiction please are
you sure you really need that magic your
implicit trust is
at my disposal
for now for now we can let him scream or
do we do we have something Korean let me
see him no I don't have anything
green Magic
uh
one of us might in our inventory if you
click the tab you can see everyone's
emergency of the situation it only
showed mine it's okay we'll just let him
squirm for a little bit yeah yeah
we'll come back later take it he needs
to calm down from his addiction anyway
I can spare anything right now okay
[Music]
that's fine let me remind you that this
is not something that can be ignored
forever this is what made me not like
him
yeah pump him out here and he's like I
understand he's going through something
Jesus Christ Gail guys
uh yeah okay so it's Kelly's armor and
my necklace and then uh Bijou has an oil
of accuracy or those are just uncommon
like but uncommons are fine right does
should I give up my oil
is this oil right does that work I think
right
does that work you can have you can take
the armor I'm not using this
you can't get potions okay
oh okay
you wanna yeah it has to be an artifact
what's the difference what do you mean
an artifact I just gave him random green
items
yeah
that's apparently
yeah yeah I have a spear that I'm using
I could give that to him no no let's not
let's not do I mean Cali said we could
take her armor so why don't we just take
the armor
come on
I apologize yes yes wait don't quite
myself
oh it's not a strange cream
that's clamped its jaws
so what happened to you just don't get
on anything stay focused on the real
world problems of an easy solution he
dies that is most gratitude
take it all in enjoy it before you
glitch out more oh it's uh he reached
out his hand but nothing's happening oh
wait yeah
take it take it
take it take it thank you you're welcome
thank you oh it worked this time wow
weird little guy wow yeah he's taking a
hit
what an addict
oh
yeah
if you really like your clothes
yucky smells like you
metaphorical demon I hate the points out
but no dress
you're welcome I can stop anytime I want
yeah yeah yeah I believe you uh okay uh
yeah yeah I heard this before please
sorry my tower in water D was never been
so free of clutter
where's Water Deep I don't don't know I
understand I ask a lot from you with few
answers in return
it's not that much all will be told
addict
boundless see he's so grateful he's so
annoying
see at least Darian is obviously fake
okay we should say it I think
Australian's better I like it yeah I'm
not gonna lie let's get out of here
yeah let's let's save and make some
progress yeah let's do it okay uh save
game game is saved let's return uh leave
camp
Eagles Zone
all right where where are we what are we
doing we just freed bolo okay
yeah you want to follow me okay yeah
follow me right over here
I wish there was an auto follow right
Beach
all right these guys are chill they're
just gonna be chilling and we're gonna
go through the door oh okay
I'm chilling just hanging challenge
we're just hanging out uh yeah we're
just saying hello we're not doing
anything weird
and talk to these dudes real quick
hey guys
and here I'm gonna start the cutscene
yep oh thank you
[Music]
see what the hell are you doing
the Beast came in here with those
robbers killed me and minced
good things yeah
it makes funny noises you make funny
noises
you guys make funny videos you're gonna
make funny noises when we kill you give
me that Bijou excuse me she's ours
let him out I'll take care of the Beast
I just understood it took you a moment
the Beast
day away
yeah a badass yeah I know now let them
out deep within
he's taking some
sorry
[Music]
now open the cage
now all right get ready for battle guys
battle we still gotta fight
look at this bear who's like ready to
tear everyone apart unless we're first
let's find the bear I thought okay
where's the bear um leave the bear to
the door let me talk to bear I have
animals can you talk to him now hello
are you talking to him yes
attacking oops sorry
I don't know how to get out of this okay
wait wait wait oh there's an x button in
the upper right corner okay
Boo's talking oh okay hello
what
I can't listen in for some reason but
it's okay
um it's because Cali Kelly upper upper
right corner click the M I am using a
controller
[Laughter]
dialogue history attack for private
dialogue cute laugh
I'm just gonna let you guys
do your try B okay let me try B is not
uh working
maybe left button
all right let me go here
uh I can't use anything else
I have a dialogue on off
do you see the X
no there I'm stuck uh why don't you
can't you grab your because you're
playing it on your PC anyway right yeah
put down your controller and grab your
mouse for a second and click on it
does anything happen yeah uh there's
still no X oh I think he's stuck in the
dial it's okay
yeah yeah it's fine he's just looking at
me okay just let's just attack the
Goblins we'll be fine right
yeah
sure what could go wrong Welcome to The
High Ground Bijou thank you for taking
the goblin okay it's more
yeah okay we have a bear yeah we we've
got a bear so it'll be fine it'll be
fine also those spoilers but I really
think I think we can do this uh should
we save right now before we start so we
can at least reload from here okay I'll
make a save yeah make one make a new one
oh
okay
I think we'll be fine this bear seems
very powerful
that was like 90 For Real
nice
I suck my aim is that's okay it
it's fine
this is it the bug because it's like not
even on the enemy I know it's just this
I just they're too far apart I'm I made
a mistake okay
I made a mistake
we can push them in there
yeah a bad initiative role maybe
no they're running to get reinforcements
it'll probably summon about three more
uh yum like I can't get them from here
you want to try and dash and maybe shoot
shoot them something uh
yeah nice let's freaking go that range
legendary
[Music]
what's happening
I'm gonna go not
no I'll stay on The High Ground I won't
leave yet
we have a wolf tank up here oh and he's
leaving too okay
nice
[Music]
can't reach destination
nice damage damn
your crab is powerful maybe for having
two health
[Music]
attack
wow wow look at you
all the other ones running too
I I can get them destroy them
do you have I don't know I don't know
how that's gonna go oh nice one yeah
yeah it's okay he heals himself all the
time so yeah he'll be fine oh is that
friend bear oh no not friend yeah
maybe not there yeah
oh those dudes are bad yeah oh
um
don't think I'll one shot the kid
hmm
do you have anything to slow him down or
like
hold him I mean I I have I have
something that I'm pretty sure could one
shot the kid but I just feels like a
waste
oh wow you did it you saved us some
reinforcement ahead yeah
okay
we got a bear
cool door
um I love when there's no one for me to
attack
my favorite all right I guess we're
dashing I can just like water oh hold on
actually I can do a ranged attack
um but let's see no there's too much
stuff in my way what what is the bags
um there's one right in front of kiwawa
and then there's one right by me and
then there's the ones in the cage
bonus action frenzied strike
nope too far I need help with that now
um and rage throw
yeah yeah bro all right let's see
don't be sick bite bulb
well that hurt everybody I wonder
oh they're gone all right I don't need
to do anything
I'll just skip
okay and a turn
is on its move
80 Miss Hurst yeah I know oh
come on Cave Bear
we love a bear a bear oh
just can't bear loose no lord they're
coming
get him
ooh grease yeah on fire yes Grace let's
go
oh shoot the grace button
I want to
oh no
good idea yeah yes those are smart
I did a ttrpg thing yeah yeah yeah
you did that was pretty cool
I wish I knew like of more things that
are like possible to do because I feel
like there's so much but I just yeah you
have to kind of think outside the box
yeah
foreign
oh I can get both of them okay all right
here we go
who are we beating up there's just oh I
get these guys yeah do it
yeah
what
oh
okay well
again
good man again
way way with you I am burning
that's fine oh that's fine I need the
fire to help enrage in me yo you remind
me of Carla right now yes my job on fire
I can take both of these guys I can take
both of them yes you can I'm noisy what
oh okay that helps
that was pretty sick
but they slipped on the grease he's he's
spreading even more grease
a rooster
you heard her again
well the the grease can light fire so
it's kind of dangerous to be in yeah
when my my com my friends my animals are
there I wouldn't do it now
um
oh I mean he might light it on fire was
what I meant does the bear have to stay
alive because he just got 25 damage no
no I mean I think it's probably fine
yeah yeah
good combo yeah nice combination
all right oh
um
Snappy
low percentage is not good
oh cool she's zooming
I'm here to help go get him
super cool next turn I guess
[Music]
this is so much easier using friends
instead of
um
yeah oh the fun part about Druids is
they don't lose their actual HP when
they're in Wild shape it's a separate HP
pool ah yeah nice that's why they're
they're very very good tanks
[Music]
oh my God
you
oh yes why not
right
nice okay one more left
he's like behind the banner ah ah
yeah
almost there good thing good thing we
stopped them from calling reinforcements
nice oh what to talk to him hello
oh the dog is okay
I will start talking to him
I'm already talking to him I'm sorry
don't slip on all the grease
oh
this guy's great yeah I love him
either way big nice guys I am the druid
halson parasites in your head
so the dialogue is the subtitles
uh the game's a little broken
I gotta get this thing out of my head
house and
Reserve you Charles Big Papa
um
you're aware of the monster inside you
you don't bow to the absolute like the
true Soul we're special I'm a good girl
houses that's possible Marissa no leave
me alone
perhaps but I wouldn't want to place all
my faith in blind luck
you weren't speaking lightly when you
said you needed help
let me tell you what I know I've been
studying these parasites for a while now
ever since I discovered these so-called
true souls are infected with them
someone is using very powerful magic to
modify these tadpoles they're using them
to exert control over the infected
sorry to say I can't undo that magic
which means I can't cure you what did we
rescue him for then put him back into
jail because these guys you can you can
go back
you can help us kill the goblins
yeah yeah maybe
come from that must be where these
enchantments are placed on them
and it's where you'll find your cure hmm
hmm
because so all of this was foreign
[Music]
you must head there and discover how the
tadpoles are being manipulated okay
I wish I could but there's still work
I've yet to finish
[Music]
the natural order must be protected all
right that means you know what that
means we gotta kill everybody yes okay
so now we do it with his help yeah
there are three big bosses I lured them
help me away
the Hop Goblin drawers
[Music]
they are the ones holding these
parasites together remove them and
nature will cure itself
that'll be rough
my presence could make things more
difficult oh I can only restrain my bear
form so much
it's okay go wild but attack goblins if
I join you we'll likely have to
slaughter this entire Place yeah yeah
let's do it
foreign
[Music]
I guess we won't have much of a choice
it'll just be whoever we pop out when we
run into
um
let's do our best yeah let's do it
[Music]
I I want I want that okay
I already saved the game don't worry
guys yes
good ow don't you worry oh I'm dying
already
yeah it would appears so I gotcha one of
the Goblins had us stopped Bear yeah
it's freaking evil you gotta make him
pay for that
jeez oh hello
Oh you mean stuff like a cute stuffed
bear yeah teddy bear actual animal okay
what did you think of course a stuffed
uh Taxidermy is what I thought oh that's
what I like about carlax Camp is she has
a little teddy bear at it
oh
thank you mm-hmm
[Music]
Outlet
yeah no not bee boo yeah this is where
we were before
it's fine they can call reinforcements
we're gonna have to fight all of them
anyway yeah this is the first oh no not
her oh she's wearing his underwear we
need to kill yeah
um who's gonna heal those that have
fallen down we might need to focus a
little more on healing each other
yeah oh you're already dead yeah yeah
how they hurt me
I targeted her really hard
[Music]
I'm playing music
yeah push him
nice nicely done I have The High Ground
now
um if you push them into that Chasm just
don't do it to the boss but they will
disappear so if you have that option you
should move and push them in the
direction of where you see where that
bridge is
[Music]
um a hole in the ground yeah interesting
so apart from the boss if anyone comes
up there you should try to throw them
that direction okay okay
oh wait uh my my lupus oh
for me
attack
um boy look
good boy
just missing a little bit more oh no
it's always that one step
oh oh she's going oh she's gonna hold
you there
what what is that you're holding me
oh that's fine I don't like it though
anyway
but I can't take actions either
oh no you didn't
oh wait wait
[Music]
I wonder where the most likely is can
you do the lender hand or help yeah
can you can you help me Boo and then I
can heal her
it is not my turn
it's only my turn I see
um I'm not close enough
I think if you use the heel on me it'll
raise me anyway
oh really yeah
[Music]
come on bagel oh it doesn't oh yeah it
does okay
nice
oh that's good to know then I'm looking
super swampy right okay uh I am going to
go into hiding
hide out
and then I'll wait you can take care of
this over here
please don't kill Houston
nice nice mess
thank you
please don't kill her well it's okay
we'll just go back into Houston Forum
right uh I have to I control halson
oh really yum
so
not in my turn you're not in my turn to
strike get them
and
Reckless attack this guy get him
thank you
leave Allison alone
oh boy
oh no that's not fantastic
so much stuff
that was 28 HP just gone in one go yeah
yeah
what's he doing
oh she couldn't even come out with my
high ground
sometimes Lord of the Rings isn't right
about everything
over here
and Blossom I really hope I can blast
them
probably you can okay oh hold first and
make attack against you critical oh
thank you
yay you remind me of Gandalf right now
I got one of them
oh
so powerful she's got the power the
power
um
fly away I'm coming back though I'm
coming back I'm up here just to do that
I knocked one down
but I have less HP so I'm gonna die if I
stay up there that's fine that's fine
you've pushed him quite far yeah
hmm
okie dokie frenzied strike on this boy
oh nice nice
[Music]
do you want me to come and help you
oh are you okay
who hasn't even like have an attack like
I don't
I don't know how you can get how you can
get them yeah I'm confused because he
like doesn't he doesn't want to attack
so oh he's back he doesn't want to
attack like yeah no his his attack thing
wasn't lit up I don't know what what it
is and I guess I'll just buy this one oh
maybe since he's he has 38 HP you can
get bring him to save koala since you
know he's tanky yeah yeah I mean is he
tanky
um
oh boy
oh
oh okay
well thank you
closer to us yeah
it'll be easiest thing in Disguise was
that supposed to hurt me
I'm just being bullied by these enemies
today yeah it's because they're so cute
oh she healed him uh-oh 24. back to
full HP
they're coming down
these guys we can focus on okay who's
after me Marissa
um
I love you
that's okay we'll kill all your friends
she looks dangerous okay uh I'm going to
she does we should turn down the the
game mode to easy
oh yes maybe we should
do that mid bite make her that was the
original plan anyway right yeah let me
see
oh she created oh you did you do that
yeah I made her wet so I can hit her
stronger next turn that's sort of the
Sparks
Sparks like the flames
okay we're not on easy now right yeah
so I am going to hide back here for now
yeah we but we can we can always just do
that randomly you know we can just do
all the fights in Easy Mode
dummy oh you're running away now haha
coward
what do I do I finally get to do
something
are you kidding me
nice there we go nice
I'm gonna use
um
[Music]
I wanted to do it from a distance but
okay what the
she's gonna push me off isn't she wait
why do I why do we have so much HP right
now I just noticed it now I turned it to
Adventure Mode
[Music]
[Laughter]
is that even easier than easy
or is that easy
yeah let's go yay hacks
it's crazy that they let you do this in
the middle of a fight right your games
are not this nice
well I gotta be so real I I'm not even
good in Easy Mode either yeah
I don't believe that are you playing on
easy privately
are you playing on easy privately yeah
just because I'm there for the story and
for the Romancing you know oh oh it's
okay it's okay it's okay she's a really
tough boss
but I really want to steal her clothes
for me okay
oh we're having a party up here
I want to try pushing her though okay
can I hit her hey baby boys and girls
okay I'm just gonna interrupt it can I
go Target can't be restrained does that
mean she can't be pushed
chat what do you say
try try pushing her just try it
can't be restrained it doesn't even give
me yes
okay she can't be pushed ah damn it
try to get closer
for now
which one of the others
Nelson oh
um
oh oh I'll give her a try
yeah I admit yeah rattle them housing oh
there is I'm sorry I can't I can't
attack her or she will get thrown
sorry
um like there I can't I can't get up the
ladder
um I'm not in front of the ladder it's
the enemies
[Music]
okay okay it's okay
not me killing Kiana multiple times
through my run
it's romantic
oh well you tried to push you
shedding them lines
practically and shiny oh
she gets so many moves she does I know
it's not that's that's the one thing
that annoys me is I feel like I always
only get one move for everything
meanwhile
yeah yeah they get like endless moves
I'm like are you kidding me yeah it's
very silly
listening
can you Bonk the guy with one HP
yeah I'll try
thank you you can go 25 let's go
oh wow
oh what's going on
36 all right see so far
yeah
I also did damage 12. even though it was
only six I'm gonna do it anyway do it do
it go wait oh oh oh let's get her yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
noise
I'm doing it
sure are
we'll we'll go on a trip
but like I know my issue was she kept
killing herself which can be pretty
annoying so
oh
it's okay I sees me it's okay
oh no
not gonna let her get away with it it's
okay I can still shock her again
okay
so calming hi
yeah
nice oh what okay she's got one Health
one HP one HP
and the nightmare
um
okay good luck when I'm alive again when
who helped me out me ah I don't want you
to not have fun playing we're all in
this together we're just chilling
thank you can you kill that eye if you
get a chance so we'll stop calling
reinforcements I currently
whenever it's your translation
don't shove her don't you I mean you
probably could you could because she's
not as long as it's not in the direction
of the chasm
one day I don't think
anyway but I'll try Target can't be oh
she can't be shoved oh okay can you hit
her now oh
Something's Gonna do something to her
oh hey let's go again
[Music]
no more reinforcements please
hey leave Allison alone manager
you're so mean
it's okay we almost got it
so close
you missed this time die
nice yeah
[Applause]
hell yeah
okay on this dude
I said friendly strike on this dude I'll
take your stuff but I won't I won't take
her underwear you can have that no no I
think I think we have to pick up her
body and take it back to Camp to get her
underwear oh but her body won't destroy
I have her clothes right here right
no I'm talking about her underwear oh
can I take my stuff anyway yeah go ahead
take her take all of her stuff because I
mean we all shared the inventory yeah
but I'm going to just be aware I'm going
to steal it so from your inventory
her now
oh my God
she's just hanging there
looking for him
oh no
oh different color variation cute oh
that's cute yeah
appreciating the beautiful things in
life I cannot out
of the spiders liar do you want the
spiders liar you you need to keep that
it's a quest item we'll need it later
okay got it
mm-hmm
wakey wakey thank you thank you
okay you're welcome I feel like me dying
all the time today is just a reflection
of my real self from behind the computer
right now
okay so there's just the two guys left
the one who's hiding out like a big baby
and or do we just have one oh I know
he's coming through the door there's
just one oh yeah yeah it's the traffic
dude okay
that is close at hand I'm right here
I'll stay here I can't attack it
yeah that's good
corrupted
[Music]
excellent okay
okay is he dead no he's got one Health
left yeah thank you okay now we got to
be careful hey wait can anyone pick up
her body and fit it into their inventory
what her whole body yeah you need to
pick up
I can't pick her up she's too heavy
oh wow I love how she's hanging off the
side all dramatic like oh that's kind of
that looks like somebody's mixtape cover
yeah right
uh how do I pick up I'm in a cut scene
um you should be able to right click on
it and then all right
I think I'm stealing I'm stealing her
I think I'm stealing her tags
[Applause]
is she still underwear
yeah you know now we can take her back
to camp and steal her underwear wow nice
okay should we go back to Camp wait I'm
in a cutscene
I'm getting her
let's go it's mine
she is but I was already in the cutscene
so
that looks tasty let me just put it in
my pocket
oh you can Now consume parasites yeah
interesting you should have picked like
uh a few or at least one up off of her
no
from her inventory did I I didn't I mean
I don't know if it's because it's the
first one if it's doing it like this
I think I'm forced to consume the
tadpole eat it eat it sorry assume I
will consume
yum yum yum I like in my private run I
like to corrupt Astorian in his brain
only so I give him all the tadpoles oh
hmm
[Music]
I'm just gonna really quickly check
through the
yeah there's a bunch of stuff everywhere
so okay
okay thank you for picking up her body
yeah
yeah it was like on uh over where mint
flower originally was there's a gilded
chest that's like yum can we take this
um yeah no because there's no one here
they can't see it so you should be able
to take it just fine
what's in there I'm away now I love that
wolf climbing on the ladder there's some
shoes you can check in my inventory if
you want if any of it interests you oh
shoes
pretty water sparkers oh
what this is maybe something for Bijou
because it says free lightning charges
where
if when the wearer stands in water
during combat it becomes electrified
that's good for me taking free lightning
yay take it from my inventory it's yours
[Music]
I know I think with Freddy's do they do
they do more damage as well oh this is
good uh there is use these shoes
okay the ragslyn guy is pretty tough but
but if we go up to the rafters the boots
are striding it helps concentration
spells or something I got him nice okay
well we're probably gonna be doing the
Priestess first uh it depends where we
go so we can either turn right and then
we go into the guy and we can fight him
and the nice thing is once we kill him
there's a treasure Trove from a key we
can take off of him pretty nice but
there's a lot of people in that room and
it's kind of difficult alternatively we
can go and do the Priestess and clear
the front area that we're doing before
out
um honestly I thought that that fight
was easier than fighting him so we might
want to since we've saved we might want
to go do this first long way and then
long rest
I have no spells do we how many because
I don't know how our camp supplies are
looking uh I got one from the lady
well it was probably fine we can do a
long rest okay
okay sorry goodbye halson
okay go to camp
where are you going we have work to do
he's mad at me
99 of cases long rest do not affect
missions
be mad at me
[Music]
I know oh nice red or not nice outfit
Marissa thanks
oh wow oh we need to drop her body okay
let me figure out how to do that whoa oh
no we saw yeah okay I'll drop her right
here
I can see your bones
oh okay there you go oh wait
chat how do we steal our underwear
I don't think we can you can you
definitely can I don't know if maybe it
needs to be done when she's in your
inventory
revive her revive her
how do we steal our honor
General okay you can have mine okay no I
want I want her
but okay Cali put the body in your
inventory again
all right hold on just give me a sec
okay yeah yeah
all right let's stop doing that stop
stop crouching and we just got side boob
oh a very strong case of side boob
all right it's the sign booby
you have we have to we have to raise her
no no no no no I don't believe that
I'm pretty sure you can put it put it in
your inventory and then like can you go
through he's in my inventory let me see
uh or maybe maybe I can also do it from
your inventory
actions I don't know how to do it though
[Music]
I'm choosing loot it's not working oh
wait put it down for a second I dropped
her okay hold on let me see
how are you gonna do it
she can't be resurrected yeah she's not
she's not on our team oh but you should
be able to take it you have to know
lethal they say and we did not
oh
wait okay
put her in your inventory
again all right
and
go and then click on your underwear slot
can you put her underwear on from the
underwear slot well let's take a look
my under uh underwear slot I have no
such thing uh it's yeah it's on the
right side
below your travel clothes you do below
your shoes you have one there's an
underwear shot there's a it's called oh
I didn't know those were underwear yeah
okay mantra's underwear there you go
[Music]
hold on
put your clothes back on
okay
[Music]
um exhibitionist
great in those actually all right
holders those like this is like a she
looks great in anything a pop star
outfit all right hold on I'm figuring
out how to do this sorry for the weight
I just yeah yeah trolls okay
all right so put your clothes back on
first just in case yeah yeah of course
of course
um did I flash you yeah it's okay
no it's not the nudity was off but it's
like you know
it's still jump scare
really okay wait now where where has me
are you kidding me hey
there's no way I have nudity on
wait I don't have it on either but
apparently apparently your ass showed
but I definitely have it all well if you
have if you have the annuity filter on
it filters like nipples and private
parts but it still shows your butt and
stuff yeah I I have to worry okay wait
Polo summer survives YouTube then
there was like a leaf okay there's a
leaf yeah yeah yeah the underwear where
did it go because I yeah I think it's is
it still how do how do I do that huh
because only I can it looks like only I
can choose to equip it or not equip it
yeah well no can you drag it into your
inventory yeah yeah you gotta equip it
disgusting underwear for 10 minutes not
letting me this is important in Kiara
you don't understand
when you have
have her underwear clipped and then add
to where's
it's equipped okay now drag the
underwear into your inventory let me
just use a mouse let me just use a mouse
very amused
here it is I now put it in my inventory
okay and then the rest I can take it
right
thank you
thank you so much for um doing this for
me
do I need to put in my inventory yeah
thank you
I wish I'm wearing yours now that's all
yours take your let me see it I want to
see how it looks on you okay I'll wear
it oh my God I wear koalas then
[Laughter]
I guess I guess I should take my clothes
off too huh oh yes please save by the
way
yeah bloomers
[Laughter]
how things are so sorry move on and kill
the next boss correct we are yeah we
probably we probably should long keep
long rest and you know if
ah you gotta sleep
oh sleep
sleep we use a supply packing
don't do that to me
to work for me boy oh what's happening
so mommy again
the garden I promise it's your boy
don't worry
I have things under control
I see you've been using the powers the
tadpole gives you
good yeah not good but things haven't
gone as you expected you hope to Drew it
as powerful as helson might be able to
remove your tadpole but he couldn't but
he couldn't she pointed
you're Debbie rid of it
understandable what a lovely beard you
have but you're looking for Solutions in
the wrong places
mine doesn't have a beard I want to be
her when I grow up I don't think you
made yours with a beer
oh it's complicated
but I'm an adventurer you must be some
way
Beyond just like you I was infected with
a mind flayer parasite
just like you I seek to be free this is
so interesting hearing it hearing the
different perspectives because in my in
my regular one it's a it's a girl you're
parasite is unusual
it is wrapped in Magic that prevents its
removal
until the source of the tadpole's magic
is destroyed attempt to remove it will
kill you
you were lucky that Halsey knew this his
instincts are right
her parasites are merely a symptom of a
greater sickness in faerun
I am not sorry guys yet
to find the answers we must first find
the source
these pictures are more than a lifted
spawn
they are vessels
troll the infected hear the voice of the
absolute and believe it to be a god
interesting
is spreading the highest those eyes are
kind of great true Souls crazy tadpole
just like yours it is how they receive
their orders it is what makes them yes
when the order to transform it will not
be a matter of days there will be mind
flayers
protection
so would you
oh
some casual dad advice
powers
but know that we are alike
I've been trying to escape from this
evil for somebody I still don't trust
you wear my clothes back on I almost
succeeded
why am I clothed in my dreams but no
clothes
and I can protect you from that evil
if we work together
are you girls still listening to it yeah
yeah I just finished uh okay
yeah my guardian wants me to use the
power
yeah it isn't safe
the power I use to protect you I stole
it from she's not telling me dad they
want it back
she says go to moonrise Towers but
sooner or later I will be warned we
gotta go no difference yes we're going
you must discover this some of your
companions remain deep in their Slumbers
I'm sorry I'm sleepy
you are one of them
and when you find the source of their
magic
nice
oh ladies Girls Sleepover oh okay yeah
cute
Oh yay take your clothes back off get
back to how you look
there's a Canon look for my character it
is I only see you with the underwear all
the time in my mind this is
hmm
I don't need it
[Music]
let's go
let's go leave the camp
us
party time all right house where are we
going
okay so yeah who do we want to do do we
want to go do the easier fight that we
lost that or should we save real quick
I'll save
and easy
so I I here's the Strat okay
um yeah so on the right side when you
cross the cross right
um and then start going to uh if you're
looking straight across the bridge the
left there's that little entrance right
but you might realize in the corner by
that door there's also a ladder uh Kiara
it might be good for you to get up there
so you can do uh can you put a pointer
there I don't know which letter
um
I can walk over there but it might
trigger the fight well they're not
triggered on us yet I don't think right
oh my house
he's gonna do what he wants but if you
climb up there then
um it it might be good for you to do
rain shots
um and then me Kelly and Bijou do rain
shots too
oh it has command the battle hold on he
found us we'll take him out really quick
eh why don't I have
oh no is it the armor I can't reach that
enemy from here uh wait no wait never
mind I can I think I can now we're even
where even is we just have one enemy
where are they I guess I guess we just
kill this one if we don't kill him
you wait apparently I can't wear this
armor because I can't cast spells and
that is honestly the most devastating is
that the issue I don't know if it is
well you can
Gail then if you want if no one's using
no wait I still don't uh
I still don't have the ability to even
after I take it off why aren't my spells
working
that's really weird oh my God it's the
boots okay I can't wear the boots sorry
yeah you can go ahead and feed it to
Gail if you want because I don't need
them anymore okay we'll do we'll do it
later okay anyways are we ready yeah or
should we save since we just killed one
random guy okay I'll save it
for me
the people in this Hall that we fought
um yeah well we're we're gonna yeah
we're do we're gonna do the same people
I mean if you wanted we could turn over
to the right and quick kill off these
three people because that will probably
prevent um everyone else from getting oh
okay uh like over here where that guy
came from one second don't do it don't
go anywhere yet oh over there yeah yeah
I'll kill the chest roll of stinking
clouds
detect thoughts and scroll of cloud of
daggers
yeah but here's the issue we need to
close this door
um
wait
question is how
son don't you this up yeah you know
he's not hiding
okay
okay I have The High Ground okay
um I don't know where you are yep let's
kill him
right
destroy destroy time
it's over we have the high grounds
what does that even mean
my English not as good as your English
you must explain to me I I don't know so
you're asking the wrong person I am only
the number one myth speaker of English
so nice Okay
why don't you talk to this little Goblin
that's in the in the cage
you can talk to him I have a little chat
hey little dude
rackle
prize is ever played in action
s praise his throne of flaming iron
word a terrific
[Music]
followers
heck yeah I was scared of a real God
heck no I'm not Tom this is the rest of
them thank you you're the one in the
cage how do you how'd you land yourself
in that cage uh formless I'm not the one
behind bars yeah I get him yeah
you'll be wishing you was in it
you'll end up being suffered for the
spiders
whoa
wow
wow spiders and works are nothing more
open defend more self
they've all gone by me brain isn't
exactly my thing buddy but these
Rippling muscles
yeah your guy doesn't care about you
since I was near it or warped up
polished to this absolutely
isn't that interesting he he doesn't
like the absolute ah can I Fireball his
cage oh yeah but yeah yeah you can kill
him yeah why not
oh
I should have a health bar on it right
wow oh
oh good okay there's three goblins in
here oops
what they saw me they saw us
thousand it's okay they're pretty low
[Music]
uh uh
hold on what's going on over here
oh no wait we can uh stay up here you
can probably handle this if you just if
you just want to uh there's a ceiling up
here yeah just Skip it's mine oh wait
where but then we if we can just do a
short rest after maybe yeah
all right how's it going here
I wish I knocked him out of the cage
that
I wish
oh it's fine oh there's High Ground
not really
got me missing I suck
skip your turns
please
they're so far
why am I missing every hit
oh they miss you though
uh
nice
[Music]
you have to end it bear okay
my turn has ended
mine's ended too Chihuahua is it is it
worth dashing over there no no just
don't worry about it I'll do it I'll
handle it no I'll join you
this is eight health y we'll finish it
off please
my beloved Senpai coming to my rescue
mental support
oh wow see I really was only there for
mental support can I talk when he was
here yeah why not I want to talk to this
rat hello
in here
yummy things oh wait
what what Does The Rat Say
hello
small spaces oh we should say of stone
sorry saves coming close that's okay
you guys want to do a short rest or are
you good uh short short rest maybe for
me my house halfway down I do things or
a shine
oh the rat doesn't even talk did not not
do anything
oh hold on a sec
okay wait wait wait wait stop
I I'll do it God okay okay let's let's
prepare for battle I'm going up high
again yeah yeah go go up
me too
oh
and then when you guys are up me and
Cali will run out there and let me know
when you guys are in position okay the
middle I mean really if you wanted to
you guys could shoot a random shot at
someone well I'm gonna try to shoot the
boss if that's okay yeah which one is it
we've got right um yeah I got it yeah
okay hold on let me give me a second to
set up hopefully they won't notice water
on them I'm just hoping they don't
notice Allison he's not he's just
standing in the doorway yeah he's a
little out there
okay
so weird why is it raining in here
I don't give us a good question
oh boy
takes a fight the consequences
surprising oh my god well it didn't
aggro them
for you guys uh we gotta help
let's go
let's do this
where is she
nice
now for now Allison why are you chilling
join the fight
get in here bear I killed him oh nice
nice nice
okay great
um we'll they'll get reinforcements if
one of them can ring one of the drums so
we just need to try and kill them as
fast as possible and we'll have less to
worry about
oh
yeah you could destroy the Drone well
actually there's nobody around that area
so never mind yeah
but they'll run to it
sure will they're fast they're speedy
oh
um oh no
I can't even see up there
oh that looks painful
I can run out of here
oh man
no
uh-huh
[Music]
no they're not completely stupid
they're not
you're still gonna pay
oh next
um
shooting from down down there how do
they get you think you think right right
that's what I wonder too
every day of my life
yes kill that one he's probably going
for the drum ah come here
you're gonna have to fight me which
one's going on
uh this little guy down here but just
focus on whoever whoever you can reach
like uh I can reach anyone that warlock
grease warlock grease is a kind of high
health issue
he's over yeah
boom baby
you broke him
perfect perfect
one who's next
I'm evil guys
why am I so far away
nice
okay where are the rest of them
okay I'll try to kill the Warlock please
oh
dang
nice guys
[Music]
freaking go oh
oh there's one dancing down
nice nice nice who's left
um they're all like on the left side I
think right my favorite like by bee boo
yeah
bye
get them
you're so close it's okay
very close very close
and I fly to safety
nah
it's reached
bro let's stay here I push him
you are too weak I am I have noodle arms
here we go all right borax I wish there
was a way to Ping I'd really appreciate
being able to Ping things
look what I mean pink so I can be like
oh they're here here and here you know
instead of being like yeah there's some
around
oh you can though just marking something
on the mouth
oh I mean like exact location
yeah like in League
hey trying to push me too I'll show you
oh right click no you can
look like on the map is what they say
or something like that yeah
that's what I'm being told
yeah somebody marked something on the
map
why do I always miss
[Music]
where are
your enemies oh there's aha see nice
and you helped me
um
[Music]
nice
another one in the bed yeah yeah how do
I clear how do I clear this Bell
we just have to wait for it to run out
so we can get the body loot from True
Soul guts
um is there anything on the side like
the
right side of the bar that has the same
symbol
I found 183 gold get it away get the bag
yeah
it goes away eventually raid other stuff
in the meantime
there's lots of dead people around here
Comes the Money
time to get another brain worm does
anyone want to eat it or do you who
who's against the brain worms here
brainworm
okay so here's what you're gonna do
click on your little inventory and
equipment there will be in a lithid
Powers manage experiences and you can
pick where you want to build Fast Too
Fast Too Fast okay inventory inventory
look in the in the top middle you see
how there's the four different uh
equipment spell book Alchemy and illicit
powers
like a lipid powers
uh uh wait it's the far right one in
your invent no no no you don't need you
just in the top one it's it's the fourth
option
okay and then manage experiences and you
can just read about it and pick where
you want to put it oh wow yeah
[Music]
oh wait I do I have a brain work so we
all share we share them we share them we
all so I ate one because I'm selfish
yeah
yeah I don't know which one to choose
um whatever would make you happiest
just whatever sounds like it it'd be
helpful to you ah concentrate okay thank
you chant
where do I put it
um just pick it up and you put it over
the one that you want and then drop it
or you can click on disgusting okay
thank you oh so it consumes one okay got
it yeah let's get going
cool should we do another short rest I
can do it yeah
oh this is the hard fight so I don't
know if we want a long rest before it
actually I have um two spells left
I don't even know how to see how many
spells I have left did you see the
squares like the oh yeah yeah it's the
squares if I think it would be a good
idea to fight up in the rafters and I
think we all should be in the rafters so
that he feels like he has to go onto the
rafters and then we push him off Oh you
mean so uh go up climb yeah
okay awesome good luck really high up
yeah good luck buddy
I can carry him on my back we level up
not yet not yet I'm gonna level up in a
while
soon hopefully
gotta go all the way up
oh my God house and just turned into a
human why do you gotta make life so hard
it has a bear before I know and now he's
like no cute kitchen
ladders in this game you know
okay
so
let's see where are you guys you loot
this chest already yes
it was just some silver trays oh I can
barely make it after we do this there
will be a room from the Priestess that
we can go into
um and unlock yeah Cali knows
uh this is too high for all of us we
can't get there can you bless us with
jump Powers
um what Cali can you eat me
oh yeah
that's too high for you guys yeah I'm
short
throw
let me see I bet I can throw all y'all
why do I have to choose an item let me
see
is it help
bro I I want to throw a person
improvised melee weapon
uh it's not letting me choose you
um
hey
if you right click on my name does it
say thrall
just use throw it says okay
do you throw and then it won't let me
choose
the current screen all right well
if y'all teach me how to use the
keyboard tell me what I have to click
there you go just click me
okay
it's Waz to move around and then to an E
to move the screen around all right and
then your mouse all right throw wait
throw first there you go yeah
get up there
my turn can you throw me bro
looks like you're a little too big for
me okay it's okay me and me and Hudson
will just um
we'll figure something out
um halson maybe is not good here so I'm
gonna just move him to the ground level
so maybe don't start the fight yet
um
there's a ladder down there that you can
eventually climb up if you want
yeah we'll get there yeah
first I need to just get house and back
on the ground so he's not useless in the
fight I'm gonna drop these uh these fire
things on them yes on those goons below
can I try setting up again
yeah okay
okay halson's at the door so
um I'm I don't want to open it I guess I
can since I'm human house and I can
sneak it open okay let me know when you
guys are ready
okay I'm almost ready almost ready one
sorry one more moment okay no problem
almost there I just need to remember how
to turn him back into a bear
oh hell we'll do it later okay let's
let's begin
okay
bully that guy
[Music]
nice
stinky cloud
s yeah nice okay time to fire the arrows
or throw axes throw axes
bro
well they're nauseous yeah stinky they
won't be able to take action for a
little bit
I'm gonna throw a goblin Scimitar at him
yeah
yeah let's freaking go
oh yeah
thanks Bill
I have to get on the ground too I'm not
even close enough to be in the fight
oh my God he's almost gone yeah he's
almost dead already
[Music]
almost threw my main weapon but I had a
Moment of clarity
sometimes that's just how it goes you
know
okay where's the guy
did he die no he died
nice wow that was that was real good
yeah
was it
oh I didn't finish my turn I'm so sorry
everyone
didn't mean to keep you waiting yeah
yeah
oh he's just running away
I'm nauseous okay
mm-hmm
[Music]
sometimes I get lucky all the stuck
outside
oh
for God moved open doors
not that one I'll go to the other one
maybe I'll reach someday
oh no the war drum
oh it's okay are there even any more we
killed we killed everyone yeah
you go ahead and drum those beats
them all you want we've killed everybody
nobody's coming to help you yeah
prove that
yeah yeah wilding out
oh that's you sorry
I was thinking of attacking you for a
second
I'm wearing
who did that hit
um
half is interrupted he's got three
Health left someone please take him down
I cannot throw
It Go Bird go
whoa birdie time
okay die
what okay
dang it I didn't even see that dude
there
yeah he's successfully hiding
The Misfortune oh great oh angry
[Music]
oh I totally didn't see that that was
him yeah
wait run through the uh I'll run through
the dagger please he was so close
it's fun let's put before anyone heals
him Angie
oh
yes
gotta break the concentration
there you go nice
hey he's on our team yeah but he stole
our kids
let me do bear again I want to be a man
a man bear
all right okay only three left not bad
yeah we're doing really good on easy
mode
oh no we're still totally on normal what
are you talking about yeah
path is interrupted all right let me
move a little bit
if I move
Caitlin I hope this level
all right where's the other one where's
the other I only see one guy there's one
next to there and one next to birds oh
that dude path is interrupt you got me
is this Cloud still I think it's
dumb
the clouds it's fine it's fine oh
what am I supposed to
you'll just have to wait till next turn
that's how the cookie crumbles sometimes
calliope
who is calliope
you haven't heard that one in a while
please
[Laughter]
wow
we both missed
Callie I can't believe that caliope
cantaloupe
whoa
all the poor dogs
um
he's trying his bed
so he's arriving soon
okay nice guys okay one more
actually hits this time
[Music]
[Applause]
take a look
he's very happy
yes man get back to the Grove select the
feet
uh there's so many
there's like a million uh oh there we go
I know a lot of you let me see which one
I want for this
wait oh no
um
Sharpshooter thing you call it oh okay
there we go okay
maybe next time
now a team that we have oh yeah
[Music]
so anyway
additional 10 damage yeah but it gives
me a penalty okay
okay
[Music]
yay we need that
I could use that okay
yeah
just take all because you know what we
can always sell it later yeah
okay do you guys uh let me know when
you're done in here and then I'm Gonna
Make You Follow Me okay I'm the queen
now bow to me kneel to me I'm on the
throne
yeah
from Game of Thrones that's definitely
that's definitely a throne a throne of
all time
can I take it home
no
sad
I guess I'll stay with my
what's it called again
the fancy chair
the expensive office chair oh Herman
Miller yeah I love it
there's so many potatoes
and garlic and Curry
oh I can level up careful
oh hey
we cleared this whole thing now
yeah
no noise
only took us about three hours
hey you know
it can take a lot of time in here yeah
so that's not that's not all that bad
it's about as much time as like ttrpgs
take I guess yeah we're pretty good
where'd all the treasure go
and there was nothing in there I didn't
see it it's in my inventory oh inventory
yeah we all share inventory though so
it's it's our girlfriend again
[Music]
we're covering up the good stuff
I know how could I am
a spell when to wear a dashes or takes a
similar action during combat they gain
momentum
oh this guy has some cool stuff too I
will put into the inventory
rings and stuff
hmm
saloons
chosen can I twin magic Missile
that thing
I was asking out loud
why strength because I want strength
don't complain this is my run not yours
sorry my child's bullying me because I I
went with i i leveled up
I leveled up and I didn't do what they
wanted
okay okay except I think I'm leveling
now yes I ranged I just want to hit the
there we go they're almost gone
I took the shield and the Boost out of
your inventory yeah I hate what you need
and then follow me I'll fall into myself
okay where's Marissa oh I'm at the door
that we entered in well that I entered
in
we have one more fight we're not done oh
we're not done okay no oh okay
I would not like taking
his body you don't you're not interested
in his clothes
no
I mean if you want them
oh that's a bit early I'm so far yeah I
mean this isn't this isn't the fight but
I don't know what happened so we're just
gonna uh these must just be guards that
missed out the first time yeah
okay okay
they're they're sad they're like huh
what do you mean no we didn't get to
fight there's only three of them three
okay yeah
there's an Archer
over there
oh kill me dodging everything you look
like how masterful
[Music]
let's go let's go can I reach from here
oh I can but 50 percent
it's not gonna make it what's that noise
there's like a banging noise
not here too
don't tell me
I hear like wood banging like something
banging on wood
does it have a ribbon a consistent
rhythm
I don't know it just sounds like banging
on wood
not the ogres again
I think playing their game again
we are triggered um
I don't hear the banging where are you
hearing those banging well it stopped
now oh okay
um you have a headache
and then follow me over here
he he
come to me okay you've been caught in
there huh so much Perfect Crime
the the guy the guy I'm Gonna Save the
game yeah you should save the game
the guy the guy is mad at me polluting
your your friend your your guy who beats
you up
oh no oh you're still here no the guy
what were you trying to lose
he was still here
that's so funny
okay we're gonna have a giant lady to
kill in a bit but feel free to loot this
room first
yeah you're right
people where are you something weird is
happening on my screen oh my god oh no
that's the the sound that she was
hearing yeah it's a Blog yeah
[Music]
what what the hell what is that I don't
know
yeah you see I wasn't
you weren't crazy
I guess and nothing's ogre is doing
their thing and
I am yeah
all right coming through the door I went
into
it and be ready okay hello defile Temple
why is your attitude going down
what is it's a big League oh I'm going
up here
she looks familiar yeah
your drama
Sharpshooter all in
nice nice
oh we'll see finally
final bite
and he misses
no no
what's up
oh you're gonna pay you are so gonna pay
um
animal is friends I'm gonna shove you
just for fun why not too heavy to shove
all right
people your turn
well let me cast a spell
um
[Music]
but I have a spell
oh
ah okay that's how you do it
um
I feel bad for ganging up on here
no she deserves that
oh wow wow what are these what are these
things that my character is saying
I don't know cool bar disses
yeah
Wolfie got revenge in the end
all right and with that we've actually
cleared everything out that we can here
yay yeah now we can just look for stuff
that's good progress
yeah I mean we could go and see see how
the thing resolves in the um okay
um
what'd you get that's just some a little
bit of gold I know useless necklace
are you afraid to say ass no yeah you
don't have to be shy here
ask domination
likes to say
dominate the ass I love assets
[Laughter]
nice
[Music]
do we teleport out or do we walk out we
could teleport out where does this go eh
wait follow me
um
I solved it and it doesn't wait what's
this a puzzle are you sure you held it
correctly I really believe I did wait
okay wait I'm in a hidden room right now
let me solve the puzzle
okay wait where did I come in from here
oh good luck wait wait where did I come
in where did we enter from I need
someone with strong strength with me for
a second
Cali has that
Cali follow me for a second yeah well
well there is doing that puzzle okay
puzzle Wuzzle
what do you think
what do you think never stuff What's
Happening Here you go in here
um we need to match up things
match to one
you know I can't fit in there but can
you people oh you can't fit in here no I
can't God I'm not the puzzling person
oh never mind I can move stuff oh nice
one people she did okay come on let's go
oh hold on hold on okay we're holding
we're holding
oh yeah
well I opened the door so now there's a
chest that we can get
oh nice I don't know where you are no I
said do I pull the lever
um
I don't know there's a lever yes yes
try try it
one second
okay close we'll do the lever again it's
a lever for the doors once we solve the
puzzle
oh yeah nice okay okay I found 254 gold
okay I'm coming back let's go
[Music]
more money
okay I'm down to a ladder go through the
door that opens let me see yeah yeah
save save Kaylee did you go here
huh did you go here oh there's dialogue
no I think I think that I thought the
puzzle was what not what it was before
okay I thought I thought you had to have
all the black circles in the middle but
it looks like no this ladder is so long
you look very frightened
oh oh what's down here
Saloon night Outpost oh
whoa what's this
Holy Light whoa whoa
oh wow a waypoint
wow where are we
we're in the underdark it looks like
under dark
oh yeah that's what the Waypoint says
that's the I think that's the other path
that you can take oh there's a lever can
I press it
um yeah
oh I opened the gate okay wait no no no
no no no no no what oh don't do anything
don't do anything don't do anything
don't move
oh boy
well that's rough there's a Minotaur
here oh hey cute
a lot yeah
nice okay well
here close the game can I close the gate
okay uh close the gate close the gate
close the gate close again
yeah we can take him through here can
you
yeah well I mean you can because they've
already saved shut up I already saved
you guys could come up to where I am
oops
why why is nothing happening oh my God
oh he's angry
that's fine let him be mad
be angry see look it's because that'll
kill him if he's stuck I wouldn't want
to get hit by that
huh okay wow nice okay now you can open
it
oh oh wait but we might not want to move
through there because of that so let me
just
what does he have
I want to check this
whoa
oh luck
20 20.
oh 20 what
I can't get a 20. what the
wait can I add to your roll no is that
attitude Kiara
I'll roll again one time only I'll just
try one more time there's treasure in
there
oh
ah so close 18 out of 20.
let's see that's cool
um I don't know if I should try again uh
we have no lock pick available
it's gonna be even worse probably ah
and it's your fried yeah I'll give up
maybe a number
right I fly up there if I use a spell no
way
I would be you might be able to that'll
be crazy let me try
I mean you could try to break through
the door too no I can't I can't wait
wait I can't nice nice
no
no good try
okay
wait Callie can you throw me up there
yeah let me try
where are you oh you're over here okay
I will try medium toughness oh medium
toughness I feel like that
give it a shot
I was able to break for something like
that with with Carla what is that hand
and where do you want me to throw
um hold on
light pink
up there there okay yeah oh nice idea
actually hold on I see
okay wait a ladder to the lead through
the chest and the one with the highest
ramp can jump over it
oh wait hold on
might be possible 22 damage
[Music]
it's like dead that's inside one
get the chest oh it's locked
wait can I lock them yeah
if you have him
let me add my guidance
worth it you should use Instagram to be
able to do that can I do it again you
can use them yeah yeah you definitely
should use an inspiration if you haven't
been really using it
ah
fuzzy okay one more time yeah yeah yeah
well then you put it in your pocket and
take it out and then we can just look at
into it later too if we can't get it
open right now if this one doesn't work
yeah
let's see
[Music]
oh it's a helmet of smiting interesting
oh
um maybe Cali can have it yeah
oh okay the strength that might be good
when you apply a condition with one of
your Smite spells what's a Smite spell
it's might spell I don't think I have
any spells
um would not be good for me um
oh it's for paladins oh we can sell it
for money yeah it's worth a lot Honey's
good yeah money is good
or we feed it to Gail yeah
um should we go to the Grove and see how
that resolves oh yeah sure um we got the
Waypoint yeah we uh the way we are I got
the Waypoint I don't know I can't leave
um
because I can't I can't jump out of this
I don't think
I went to the emerald Grove okay uh
um
[Music]
wow we've been inside all day
inside that stinky Goblin Camp yeah very
smelly
I don't want to take a bath
it is good memories yeah yeah
there's still a little stuff there too
yeah
oh yeah what will or whatever maybe yeah
oh
escape this I took a collection from all
of us they're giving us some money
thank you
I guess
we're taking the money
just a while ago
we are not nice here
yeah we did something big we can't be
doing this for free otherwise everybody
expects us food free yeah
finally we don't work for free perhaps
we need not speak of farewell all right
they're gonna celebrate so um well let's
go see what's happening with kaga though
yeah
and we can also sell any any of the
stuff that we can yes oh yeah I hate
that he only takes one person at a time
I know yeah that is pretty annoying but
there's a is there a child uh salesman
around yeah
[Music]
um
oh the kid wants wants some business
give him some business I want to give
him business
yeah okay I'm in business what you gotta
do the business move
in the most say-so way possible because
that is a child yeah you see around here
I had some I don't know I'm just gonna
wait Troubles of those kids in my
private playthrough yeah no they're kind
of nasty little ones
that moved away oh well
Advance the story and then that seems
like a good you know yeah
we're gonna wait for you guys down here
or yeah we'll wait yeah okay I'm all
done all this I'll just sell my stuff
next time
yeah
oh yeah we can do it before we start
next time
no killing the cow
would I ever do that
all because of that croissants
sounds good
you do a good you do a great question
thank you
we do the story and then we can we can
go and do the tiefling party and then we
can end okay
silence the right has been ended
but consider yourself a novice anew I've
forgotten the ways of the dream
he's not having it yeah once again right
here
backslide I think we should kill her
Murray will crush you
as you wish
Master hell okay it seems I can sell
between streams if I want to do
bookkeeping off stream okay
okay
um you try to do imprison he did try to
imprison a child you were too lenient
we'll have your hands full with her he
shows great influence yeah but time will
humble her
see why
but enough of that for now yeah do you
my thanks
you're welcome stands
nature we owe him our thanks too though
he helped him yeah he did he did help us
out a lot speak to Wrath he will reward
you for your efforts oh
um
[Music]
that that entails
take some time for yourself tonight rest
celebrate
come morning I'll be by yourself
all right so we get our prize first and
then go to the party or just do the
party yeah yeah guys where's the prize
Ralph is in here I believe
oh now they teach me about the pink
system I already knew it
hello Ralph hello
you've done it you brought house in back
you're welcome no problem
no thanks it was fun
I cannot imagine taking on a camp full
of goblins it was a simple task
true
fair enough
I should not have underestimated you
um I also need to check something real
quick in the Grove oh okay where we
before we leave I don't know if we
grabbed it before place it among the
pedestals but I think there's a Wonder
wolf glows brightest there's a word
[Music]
oh wow
okay where is Neddy again Daddy's like
here somewhere
no Daddy did you guys kill her no I may
have no no
before before in my own place okay it's
gone there's um
okay uh let's do a long rest okay are
you guys ready yeah
wait what did he give to us as do we
want I have no idea
take off my clothes
well everyone's in their underwear yeah
that happened automatically I didn't
even do that
the
hi I wish he'd put his back on
I don't need those two things staring at
me
when you look at it from the right angle
it looks like he's naked and just
covering himself with the book very
elegantly
oh we're listening in on something oh oh
oh
we killed some goblins to save some
tieflings Italian lives didn't change
much well I'm not giving him as close
through my hard work yeah that's fine
and vinegar for wine
they kicked me do you mind
wow we have no connection we have no
connection wow okay I'll try my luck
with somebody else
there's a barn here I think is this
narissa's Bard friend don't waste a
night like this eh
time to spend for that I sense
ah you turn a risk of housing
yeah damn dude
I really want to get
sure there are
you strike me as extremely
resourceful resource but there are many
grateful people here who want to spend
time with you
help them please myself
though
[Laughter]
that's what he's thinking
no yeah go go enjoy it it's the party
talk to whomever you please well which
Gale should I talk to
choose from
everyone seems to be in High Spirits
they're strange
I know who I never thought I'd do we not
have will
we really never recruited him
this is the saddest
this is the saddest missing but not what
I mean
desperate people
like those refugees
okay I guess we try our luck he's gonna
say no let me not that function we can't
yeah we came through for them I'm risen
up Shadow High I mean yeah keep going
um
sounds like the wines talk in the shadow
heart
for my liking
she likes you oh
Shadow heart Trails off and glances
around at the party
mildly surprised you're still there
I thought you might have wanted to
mingle with the others oh trying to get
rid of me wait yeah you're you're all
the company ID right now oh my God
I won't pretend I'm not surprised
we haven't always seen eye to eye after
all she's so cute I'm sure there's
plenty of people who'll be Keen to
celebrate most thoroughly with you
uh uh maybe maybe I'd like
to celebrate with you maybe you would
yeah but I'm not cruel enough to get
your hopes up in spite of what
Dang It wait hold on
um
I think I could win you over
oh you do do you I'm not some dewey-eyed
tiefling Maiden you just said dang it
you'll need to do a lot more leg work
before I commit to any hip work
is there any persuasion
[Music]
um
let's see
what some advice on how to make me more
bearable
all right if you like I'm not the half
as mysterious as you might think
respect my privacy my opinion
if you do that well okay okay I
shouldn't get closer wow she didn't say
no she didn't say no say no she said
maybe later the savior of the Grove so
okay
Darian hates me
did he really just it's not you it's me
you
gross
get away from me
biggest bottle oh my God my now oh
drink is great he's great I love him so
much he's so funny he has the best
one-liners
always make our own entertainment
[Applause]
he wants you
a Starion does yeah
excuse me
oh geez I mean
no are we is there something good if
you've saved please make him squirm well
say please make them say please make
them safely
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
good luck streamer's luck
what oh you're winning
[Music]
good boy let's get together
no way
[Applause]
no way no way no she just ruined my life
can you get a room oyster I don't want
you to sleep with him
I am can I say just kidding
oh maybe we should end the stream here
we need some privacy as they like to say
I'm disappointed you what
what they came on strong to me you could
have said no it could have but it's like
a vampires
irresistible the idea of there being a
spicy scene between
a creature that I have created I just
couldn't say no
[Laughter]
oh my God yeah no one no one likes me no
one no one here is interested in me I'm
so sad I know oh my God in in my in my
solo run everyone was so mad at me
they're like you're not gonna sleep with
me tonight what's wrong with you I was
like oh I didn't realize everyone liked
me so much
wow wow all right well all righty wow
shall we sleep shall we end the day or
does anyone want to party hardy at least
do it here just get your screens ready
maybe make yourself big wait wait I want
to try I want to try bruising Shadow
Hearts real soon
share private moments as often
strange
I mean I don't have nudity on so I don't
really know how spicy could it be I mean
or do they just do it with the clothes
on
um it's a little spicy
oh
can I trade Mr can I give it to somebody
as a present like I made a mistake well
it's gonna be so he's so funny
hurt
kind of true wow turn it on Tower
okay you haven't always seen eyes so
pretty spicy
besides
shoulders plenty of people just get
ready everyone hates us I guess
um
for free
maybe you would don't know I mean you
don't know that you don't no I've never
seen anything have fun okay well
yeah I don't actually know how spicy it
is
obviously narissa has seen it so it's um
yeah it's it's a little
it's a little it's a little much
she thinks I'm done streaming because I
stopped talking oh
she's so smart
okay let me just um
I just have my screen I just turned the
game screen off but I still have the
game sound on that's fine right as long
as there's no obscene visuals
[Music]
it's time you want to see it all right
share private moments on let's
go okay hold on hold on hold on
I'm just gonna take measures real fast
I hit take measures I'm just gonna make
myself really really big
the one that gets this yes I think you
probably talked to people more so the
they probably get to know more about you
so since you're the one making like
choices they uh are more attached okay
I'm ready you know Super Evil I'm like
the nicest one why is he down to bomb I
don't know he liked me too and I was too
nice for him so oh I guess I'll go to
bed all right
let's go
rest show me your scene yeah
[Applause]
I
don't know if I want to see it but I'm
kind of with Cali's character amazing oh
my God
you don't have me yet say nothing just
let him kiss you
um just just let him do I am a poker a
few words
do what you must sire
let's go
Rising them up as always okay
yeah there's definitely tongue involved
oh they're in love
uh enjoy yours relax enjoy yourself
you're the one who pinned him against
the tree I mean moriope is you know just
a little a little frisky
you know
[Music]
wait I'm pretty naked in there you are
me well no I mean I'm still kind of okay
yeah you don't you don't have nipples
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah yeah
[Music]
so what how how did we think about that
sir is he humping you
nah nah he did not thankfully satellite
day you weren't that good
how dare you I'm in concert leather I
was holding it back if anything went to
which base did it again
they went all the way
I wanted to ask you about your scars
where'd you get them
again
tennis smash I crossed
discount
he captured me
kept me for years as his slave well sad
backstory sad past as we look at his ass
yeah and a nice ass it is napping
when the mind just snatched me up
not a great Improvement but no he loves
the ogre muscles
I mean how could he resist yes that's a
good point a poem to carry with me he
composed and carved that one over the
course of a night
he made a lot of revisions
never mind this is full booty okay never
mind
I can't see it you certainly can't
ever seen
just checking a mirror can I yeah he's a
vampire I can tell you what it says
whatever the bastard wrote it won't can
you read infertile anything he did to me
no let's go probably not we're probably
not if I was playing as a team
ah thank God
perfect yeah it was an okay evening it
was fine wow
green cheeks
asterion's very lucky he got to he got
to spend the night with female so
well uh great we made good progress we
finished saving the Grove which means
we're moving on to chapter two
yeah
yeah isn't that exciting wow we can
still go back and do some stuff from
chapter one though but especially when
we get to chapter three we won't be able
to go back so just so you know but if we
want to do like the Hague mission for
example it's probably better to do that
before we move on too far whoa hag
Mission let's go yeah yeah we gotta find
The Hags man I'm in egg hunting
yeah
yeah but everybody did so good today
crew yeah
yeah let's see gotta find our way
through
um thanks everybody for tuning in yes
thank you thank you for coming despite
the late hour yes it was a pleasure
yeah
it's a good time
I'm gonna take a huge fat nap yeah me
too how are you gonna go to sleep
um I'm sure some people have
announcements for example I know Kiara
you've got an announcement yeah yeah
well I released an album yesterday
uh it has quite a lot of variety yeah
some edgy Emo songs some happy bouncy
songs
some cool EDM songs this and that and
today is the release of the MB for DMV
uh a pineapple in in about seven and a
half hours so I hope you guys can watch
it
yeah
[Music]
yeah well so you guys should go listen
to it on iTunes because I see it yeah
it's crawling up the charts you guys
[Music]
whatever service you prefer I would be
um honored please Stream Point of View
Stream Point of View Stream Point of
View super good
super good thank you Kelly likes
retrospective the most huh yeah great I
don't know man great wander is also
really good those are the two that like
that's my favorite that's my favorite I
like great Wanderers really good I'm
surprised
I thought Bijou would maybe like the
cuter songs I mean they're all good but
like and I feel like sleep talking
reminded me of like a really cool like
poppy Banger that like I feel like
everybody can enjoy yeah
me too oh really
[Music]
I want a dressing in them
um so what else do you guys anyone want
to save what they're streaming next or
my memberships open today that's all
I've got
jail Birds jail Birds my one one month
anniversary month anniversary my first
month and uh then I open membership so
it's a fun day for me
not alive but debuted for a month
officially now babies
it's so exciting
what you you girls are one month and me
and Kelly are coming on two free yeah
[Music]
um I'm streaming armored Core tomorrow
that's it yeah I love that game
it's so fun I love it
um yeah that's about it for me and then
I I'm doing it I'm not sure if people
can do the thing I'm doing tonight for
music first
um I have an appearance that I'm doing
I'll try and retweet stuff about it if
there is something online you guys can
see then you should be able to find it
there and yeah that's uh that's about it
nice
first is that Japanese TV or what yeah I
think I thought it was TV but I heard
that it it's like an on online that's on
Japanese TV oh okay
gotcha um I mean I don't know I got a
lot of weird conflicting information
from money
I'll figure it out um
two buddy will be there
[Music]
um so check my Twitter for info about it
if you're interested yeah
[Music]
thank you guys for playing I'm looking
forward to the next time
next time different time again
times every time
yeah Rory's gonna wake up super early
next week yeah
like six a.m so yeah thanks a lot
everybody
yes
peace out everyone
[Music]
okay hold on hold on hold on hold on
everyone one second
boom
oh I'm back to normal okay that's fine
[Music]
Daddy can I move myself can I move
myself a little bit okay over here okay
okay hello everyone
I hope you have
fun oh is this the wrong chat is this
the wrong do I have the wrong chat on on
this one did I not change it I think I I
did okay hold on
rolling chat this is still this is still
from the other one
um uh
um
sorry chat why isn't it moving
why isn't it moving
it is good are we moving okay we're
moving hello
um I'm gonna get some sleep but uh for
those of you who do not know
um my membership
stream my first ever membership only
stream will be tomorrow and
um I put a poll up for you for the movie
that you want to watch in the membership
Community post uh the poll will end as
soon as I end stream because we gotta
pick the movie Okay so
yeah you have like a few more minutes to
choose so if you haven't chosen yet go
vote in that poll but
uh was it the movie that I wanted to
watch is I didn't no it wasn't on
Netflix
um I only have access to Netflix right
now but next time next time we'll have
more of a choice of movies but right now
I can only do enough like stuff so
that's why that's why I had to change uh
movie last minute without so that's okay
that's okay but yeah please vote if you
haven't and I will
um
what is it I will
post results on the Community page as
well tomorrow or today today after when
I hit end yeah yeah yeah
but
besides that
um I'm gonna get some rest oh did you
hear that crack I cracked again I
cracked like my shoulder
it's just ah thanks Josh long long
streaming day
long streaming day but so much fun
so much fun so much fun I had so much
fun playing Hitman and then Baldur's
Gate with everybody I hope you guys
enjoyed it too but I'm also kind of
tired now so I'm gonna go eat I'm gonna
go I'm gonna go get some if you guys get
some eat too
um the stream tomorrow will start two
hours after my normal time so I usually
start at four but we're starting at six
so that way it's closer to my dinner
time so I'll actually maybe actually
have an appetite to eat food
because I I wanna you know show you guys
that I actually eat food so I need to
get an appetite so we'll be starting at
6 p.m PST 9 pm EST
uh 8 P.M CST for tomorrow's first ever
membership stream I hope you can make it
and if you can't that's okay because we
have a lot a lot a lot of a lot of fun
streams uh this week and and I decided I
will probably stream a bonus stream
before Advent collab on Friday because I
have something to show you guys and I
can't wait to show it
um so I'm gonna show you guys that on
Friday because yeah surprise I'm really
excited to show you anyway surprise
surprise it'll be on Friday and then
that'll be it okay I'm gonna head to bed
now because my brain is starting to feel
empty no thoughts head empty and maybe
I'll eat something maybe
oops what time is it it's midnight oops
oopsies oops okay I'm gonna I'm gonna
eat and then I'm gonna sleep I promise I
promise I'm gonna eat and then I'm gonna
go to sleep okay okay okay I'm gonna go
I'm gonna go now
everybody thank you if you were with me
like all day thanks for hanging out with
me all day and I will see you guys
tomorrow and then if not I'll see you on
Friday and then if not I'll see you
later
see you next time thanks for coming I
hope you had fun
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you