I'm
innocent oh it's you listen we got to
act fast it's just a matter of time
before Elizabeth gets a full story from
that octopus and then she'll come here I
can feeling the walls caving in man and
it's not just me who might get in
trouble with Justice either you helped
set up the stall so you're an
accomplice but don't worry I have the
perfect plan to make everything better
by the time I'm done admin will be
taking notes from me on how to avoid
Justice
[Music]
meet
Jimmy when herb goes to take in the
takoyaki style owner she'll see Jimmy
don't worry as a loyal kfp employee he's
already agreed to take the fall
[Music]
right sometimes I even impress myself
with my
genius come on while jimy is playing the
scapegoat let's go get dinner there's a
pizza place nearby so we can scout out
our competition while hiding from
Elizabeth what do you say we can use
some of the takoyaki St earnings on the
food after all you help me set it up so
it's only right that we both reap the
rewards