wow
cali cali cali cali kelly kelly kelly
kelly
kelly's kelly's scared of halloween
there i'm here hello everyone yay my
stream is on ultra low latency now and
i'm very excited hurray
is everyone too quiet for you guys or
should i turn them up louder
how's the audio
i was muted thank you chad for letting
me know anyway ultra low latency
okie so should i explain what we're
doing
please yep okay so
and not we all have never played this
game before at least uh like
10 minutes before this unless we play
the ten minutes before the stream
however i think i have grass crabs
crabs grass grass basics
so i shall explain and
this is kind of similar to among us
and i didn't play it but coulda said
it's kind of also similar to dead by
daylight
right to me yeah in a way yeah
uh basically we are all children
and and then among us
wink wink is a secret neighbor like a
really old to do to scary dude
that's always in the screenshots from
this game uh
but he's also shown as a child
at least in the beginning until he
decides to just uh like show himself
so weird uh so we are trying to like we
are going into a big big mansion
and uh there's keys hidden up over that
mansion and we
kids try to find it and each kid by the
way has different skills
depending on which kid you choose so
the the old dudes eventually will try to
stop us from getting those keys because
once we get all the keys and open all
the locks to a certain door
then the kids win the game and i have a
feeling
that uh today in today's collab we will
never even once manage to open the door
but that's the steering
that's pretty much how the game works oh
oh [\h__\h] oh
i'm on low power mode well
i'll be fine are you fine
thank you for reminding me i should plug
in my my key movement
yeah that's yeah i think that's pretty
much the game it's kind of easy
um yeah there will be an imposter
among us
[Music]
mute ourselves like we didn't among us
because we realized it's not maybe
maybe not not necessary however in the
test rounds
was the imposter and she was very quiet
so
maybe action if you're a child
[Laughter]
just act like a child
is everyone ready to go into the first
round you guys go
to 10 minutes or do you want slightly
longer oh let's make 15 minutes let's
see
maybe because i i think we need my time
especially my brain i just woke up okay
ready up i'll find so i'll be the
detective are you a detective
i'm a detective but today i'm using my
fps skills for good
oh i guess i'll be the best wow
cool ah kelly you gotta return to the
lobby oh yeah okay here we go um
here's the big orange button button
yeah here we go
mustache i want a mustache too
okay cool
all right i'm going to take a pause
quickly all right
we have six keys to the little we have
to try to open next
you can open you're under the stairs
can't see anything
call her is predator for nothing hold on
press
oh no nothing in there huh all right
how could you be good don't throw that
pumpkin at me don't you do it
where are you oh he's
this one
oh
[Music]
right in the beginning so oh
okay that's drop and then throw as you
click oh
i i'm trying to throw okay you press the
other button okay
oh what's this what hey why did i take
damage mouse oh a key i found a key
oh oh take the key oh open the door
okay hold on look creepy here it is
oh it makes you stinky
why don't how do i know which door it
goes to
it's right here right here right here
right here isn't it try it right here
oh wait that's the card keep going
upstairs that's right upstairs maybe oh
that's probably
okay let me get away from you get away
from me
oh okay you pressed this button
got it nice gangster but you all knew
that all right here we go
uh what's up with this did you know
let me need the key card again oh
i found where the number two key card
goes to okay oh okay
and i guess you can't really use it
again huh okay oh
well we're opening doors everywhere
hello who's there who's that it's me
kelly hey you know what's going on i
don't know but i found the way
number two i found the way to number two
so if you find number two key let me
know
but look around
see
what floor are you guys on we're on the
second floor
oh it hurts
i was on the second floor lads in front
of the uh
in front of the entrance to any of the
other rooms
i'm saying there's no hiding it anymore
i guess
what do you mean the apex predator so
you drill farm good eyes show it to us
your
sexy body wait what huh
it's you huh there we go
oh
that's what i meant but also in the
practice rounded it was also
uh watson who was the only one who
stayed alive at the time like she died
but yeah what i don't know where i'm
going i don't know
yeah but i don't know i didn't know you
could get there oh
oh my god wow nice detective yeah on the
roof
wow
no what am i no she's in the basement
find anything
um they're carrying us as always
i was just impersonating a crowd
i can hear you
watson oh my god
it's creepy just watching you gouda
is she a kid or she is amelia breaking
the game where is she is she in the roof
somewhere she's like a good chat
playing the game she's glitched into the
wall she's amelia's breaking the game
are you hiding you're in this room
[Laughter]
oh i need some popcorn
[Music]
[Laughter]
what are you gonna do huh
[Music]
wait where are you come here no let me
try and turn my chair at you
all right i'm just gonna go get a cold
one everyone enjoy watching watson sleep
[Music]
did you put them in your truck with the
candy
no you know that's a little
i want to paint my character i want to
be the one who gets the clues
oh i'm going to be the detective
because we need to find those keys
okay return who should i i don't think i
was a very good detective i found one
key
um but i wasn't really pleased with my
job so let's see
um is there any is there a kid that just
beats the [\h__\h] out of
people that's scary all right cool
you need to shoot them oh fps
can i can i hit someone with a baseball
bat
there's a character with a baseball bat
but i don't know if you can hit anything
if you actually hit the ah man i wanted
to i wanted to hurt that guy
okay well let's try yeah oh okay
that's a counter strike
wait we want to get into the basement
yes
ah yeah what's our goal exactly there's
there's six guys over the lap
and then you open the big door with like
the six blocks and then you gotta
get into that we should stick together
aside from the killer of course
yeah let's chill ideally
that's a good idea let's stick together
this time gang up on him
yeah yeah get him dog pile on
so with the scout you only have 10
bullets and you can only
you can only temporarily
okay i'm gonna call it no it's amelia
all right and how do you
uh how do you press what buttons do you
press to shoot uh
q and then oh yes all right got it now q
and then mouse yeah
got it okay that's easy enough that's
milk
all right guys we're sticking together
right yeah yeah
oops i don't know i don't know if
they're just anybody anymore
i trust gouda because it's very unlikely
that gouda
got got to be uh imposter again
neighbor i don't know apex predator
melissa man whoa finally i have a
hint to a key it is in some
blow like oh i found it i found a key
nice a card key card oh what's the key
card dude
i don't have a pumpkin it should go up
to the second floor i think
yeah keycard opens together i also have
a
card you can open the other door over
here
oh my
whoa there's a coffin looking place
what's in here is that any like oh
what's that
can we pick up useless items what is
that throw them i think you can throw
them
here boys okay hold on so each no wait
don't give me that
each key card has a different number
uh-huh oh i found it
okay dude so we're like in there
who's in there oh
i died
[Music]
i think only like a certain character
can escape
are you are you upstairs or downstairs
i'm upstairs
okay then i'm downstairs
[Music]
oh
you got to stay hidden i can't
please talk oh oh oh wait wait wait hold
on wait
hello i can build a gun
oh no oh no
[Music]
people who are good at video games
wait what is the what is the goal now if
you're the last one
you gotta get some keys yeah find all
the keys you still have
all the keys yes yeah it's kind of
awesome
you can only hold two things at a time
so it's like yeah well there's the one
character that can hold more than
more than like yes um
one
[Music]
yes
i saw a few flashlights laying around
wait that
that cupboard
[Applause]
i know that was the one on my photo oh
you have to like speed run this
oh nice nice good oh yeah yeah wait
there's keys
they're not all up on you gotta match
the numbers
you got this you got this
you gotta find this yeah don't say the
number don't say the number you never
find out
oops yeah i mean one number one they go
to door number one good afternoon
what is this i don't need this oh wait
yeah
larry creep
wait what did i do oh never mind
how do you get on the roof
[Laughter]
i don't know huh we'll feel that you're
gonna win
you got those good ideas for the door
and like not like actual key keys you
can find them
in different places it doesn't matter it
doesn't have to be like in a specific
spot
so wherever you are you can still find a
key for the big door
huh yeah there's key cards and there's
keys
key cards are to open more rooms and the
keys are to open that
the big door that we
so please keep your distance
i need a one
you can't stay in the garage the whole
time girl you can't stay in the garage
the whole time
oh it's this oh that's clean
on the flesh
get out of the bag
i'm good as bad with numbers
[Music]
what is this
what's the big he do you put it in the
big door that's in the main lobby
oh god that's all the way over here
though
why did you just give away my location
[Music]
that's difficult man that's difficult
it's ina camps in front of the door yeah
so we i think we if we all stay together
and we have like one person who does
like uh
yeah and be a good bait i can be good a
good distraction
and he's gonna get lost that's about all
i can do you wanna you wanna start over
since we're not all here it might be
better if we're all here
yeah yeah hold on wait let me let me go
back to inado
i wanna test my i wanna test my how do i
get to you uh
if you throw enough items at the killer
you can temporarily kill the killer
oh get them down as well not only the
kids
what if i shoot spam
we'll use the slingshot next time i'm
gonna do it
contemporary kills
a little bit yeah i'm not sure how i
feel about that
okay
what are we talking about
you guys want to start over we can play
another round because this is a lot for
one person
you guys aren't getting
[Music]
that kid is really useful because you
kill him instantly
oh that's op wait i don't have a
flashlight what's that did you just find
the gun
that's a powerful weapon
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh oh you can rest oh okay you can
revive oh
i see like a little sticky
oh no this is sad to watch she's outside
i can crawl
all right
someone said my my screams sound like uh
cleats
or shoes on a basketball court i don't
know how i feel about them
[Laughter]
how do i throw stuff you press with
fried food
we're all done no cabbages no not
cabbages
pumpkins oh my god
you want this shark you're gonna have to
fight for it
um let's see i like i bet i can throw
pretty well so i'll be
i'll be this kid what are the match
rules maybe we can set it to like
because you guys said there is revive oh
oh
no there's auto remove on yeah yeah it's
on it's on
but we never revive
okay oh wait but one thing one thing we
can do is maybe
uh the number of locks maybe get them
down to five or so
that would be good five five
yeah that should be good and and the
character that guido was playing is
pretty op
if anybody oh then inventors wanted to
play i went to build
guns inventory yeah we have to build
stuff right
yes but you find it's really easy to
find the stuff to build oh okay
i'll be i'll be an adventure kid then
maybe we should also turn off key cards
so we can go straight to the keys
yeah yeah yeah we'll see how it goes
okay i think that makes it a bit easier
for us to win because other than that
i think we were it was impossible for us
to win yeah
wait question if if there's a neighbor
but they're an inventor does that mean
they're
uh i am they can shoot the kids with
their guns
cool
i'm a killer but i actually don't like
ballistics you all know chad chill out
chill out
now everyone who knows me knows they
don't like guns all right listen
oh yeah yeah i'll tell you yes
okay okay that's better thank y'all
should we turn off player name so we
can't tell who's who
that's kind of a good idea i should have
thought about that before i was like oh
[\h__\h] so it'll make it easier to hide
then because you won't be able to see
yeah yeah yeah wait how come chat is
saying in-game voice chat is it because
it's proximity based is that why you
guys are saying that
oh possibly
and stuff ah it is proximity that would
be cool
you can try that if you guys want
practicing
[Music]
uh the closer you are to somebody the
louder they
they are and then the further away they
are i'm sorry i'm sorry i don't need to
throw i'm sorry
i don't know how to play this game i'm
sorry
i don't know what oh i stopped fighting
what's going on here why are you hurting
me you hurt me
i accidentally threw my flashlight
i don't know how to play this game how
do i switch objects
wait okay hold on two oh okay so this is
the glue
what does this do what does it do
all right it's all sticky and on the
ground i'm gonna leave that alone
come with me yeah it's milk yeah okay
wait where did you go okay
i'm gonna stay with you wait what if you
are the what if you are then possible
by the way i have a i have a photograph
again of uh
where the key might be to oh and then
you can switch
items oh okay it should be a lower
lower cupboard not one like this in a
low one like a tv
cupboard oh this is the one yeah
kelly
money wait where are you guys like power
up so
cool why aren't you i haven't seen you
why
why do you want to see me what's in
sauce
[Applause]
quiet she's quiet why she's so quiet
usually she isn't so quiet yes
yes kind of suspicious
i would say
me yeah
no yeah yeah
i am she's kind of quiet i'm a kid i'm
just a little innocent
kid i see walton hello eyes on watson
over here wouldn't i have attacked you
guys already if i was the
killer
what does this do more clean oh you can
jump
is that another flashlight yeah there
was a lot of flashlights oh in case you
lose yours i guess
[Music]
whoa what's going on i'm scared
i don't like it what why are you guys so
suspicious of me i didn't do anything
that's exactly exactly
yo there was a snacks in here wait what
oh that's kind of suspicious she's
trying to lure us
are you talking what's this is it a
candy bar
hold on trick-or-treat
not my feet what the hell is it what the
hell is that
what i heard a bag what there's a
walking pumpkin
there's a clown huh it's cali
oh yeah callie
i'm scared voice chat next game yeah
and turn off yeah
hello
[Applause]
watch the door block the door what are
you talking about i didn't do anything
oh god you guys are thinking i'm suss
i don't know right um what was your last
neighbor you can also be the clown and
the clown can transform into
listening the clown can transform into
other eyes
ah that's not good
it's not great hey baby
thank you everyone for being with me it
was fun but i'm about to die goodbye
sayonara
[Music]
i'm working on it
i'm still alive i'm still alive
stay soon
how many years do i have i have two
probably why are you so quiet
callie why did i build this one
we're so close to death because i love
death that's it
that's it oh i see i see how it is i
don't know how to grab people in this
game
you killed them i know i i pressed a
bunch of buttons
basically we don't need the key cards we
only need the what what is that
[Laughter]
[Applause]
money oh that's not money
i'm doing my best
[Music]
where
how about that i don't know about that
no
not um normally i would like to we need
[Music]
by the way i already got two keys so
you know with the carrot oh doing she
saved the game
there's some nice music playing
oh oh yeah radio
that is creepy
look i don't know who you're going
hang on it's real dark
i wonder why it's so dark in here are
you lost kelly
no i'm fine i just got
i'm scared let's go
mom
oh i don't like it why do i hear sounds
[Music]
okay i don't need my i don't need my
flashlight oh
it's sneaky
what is this sound look at this sound
oh it's bugging out what the hell is
going on
the [\h__\h] was that it's my flashlight i
just
don't have one i lost it
oh my stuff that's a shame here why
can't i find any keys
oh do you even lift the crow the curl
marks where the key is
by the way oh where who is the grow
you see the crow in the oh yeah i see
that thing
[Music]
no
oh wait
i don't like that noise
oh boy wait who's the lifestyle
something that i
i wish i didn't oh my god where did i go
i'm above you too you know all right i
want that
i think killer is not very good at the
game apparently
i think the killers were really bad at
video games that's probably who
that's probably who it is the one that's
the worst survivors out of everyone
very that too because they're always
lost
in 999.99
all right
you know what are you riding on you're
writing on something on my screen
i am i don't know
what you gonna do with that killer
wait what happened
[Music]
wait hold on nice
no no no yeah right what does it do
let's go let's go we can do this you
guys got this it's only one
yeah only one left what no we need two
yeah it was only
two more okay two more my bag i just do
the keys and then look
only four minutes left
suddenly intrigued would be nice if i
had a flashlight
well
oh thank you for the tip i appreciate
that here we go found one yes
yes okay problem
it's a nice house there's a huge house
there's a hole in the floor
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
we gotta kill her
the killer instincts finally come out
let's turn punch punch punch
watch watch watch and watch fights
i'm only a little bad at video games
okay turn on your in-game audio
oh no okay
oh he's on okay voice chat
on uh let's always uh let's test it out
uh mute discord oh you guys are
recording the talking game
okay
oh hello oh yeah it's so
bad it's so bad it's so
quiet
but it gives us a retro effect really
fancy retro effect
halloween quality audio
wow oh yeah i understand
it just for fun just for fun
it's scuffed but we can try okay
one round how about it okay i'm gonna
turn off player names
for them 15 minutes key card off
all good let me turn off their names
wait i'll miss you something
oh i'm in
i also don't hear her head bob intensity
um let's see how do we turn off the
names oh no
it doesn't automatically it's the room
setting who does it yeah
this coin i mean i meant we don't hear
you
in the uh in the game
okay okay should we just
go back to this she's going to fix it i
think
and discord uh would like to let us know
that they liked it when discord company
was on
i'm not surprised i'm not surprised
really no like actually discord
this card's in the chat wait what
what what discord's in the chat what
i discord
listen we're doing this for the
experience
a discord like the real discord is in
the chat
i had a check mark next nixon's name so
i assume
well if people hear this audio they will
appreciate the score
more they say they forgive us
is almost ready okay okay
this is engine audio yeah this is
[Music]
however if it's the real one thank you
for blessing us with our presence
oh she's restarting the game i'mma is
restarting the game okay
[Music]
no problem
what what is everyone uh going to dress
up for halloween i mean for me and cali
halloween is kind of over but
oh it's kind of over here too really
yeah
what why are you just the best yes
i'm a dinosaur girl no i'll be a nurse
i'd be afraid if i saw kelly in the
hospital to be honest
discord discord came to my chat as well
oh my god
it's on my chat it's great
i'm saying hello to my deadbeats discord
why is discord uh
watching our
[Laughter]
i couldn't figure out how to do the
thing where you where you show
everyone's
big faces find it difficult because you
maybe plug that into discord options so
i don't have to use other applications
could you please i have some good ideas
i'm a good inventor or how you call that
i can make some i can send you some good
ideas
i'll send you an email discord
[Laughter]
let's talk business dispatch let's do
some business i'm a business woman
[Music]
but other than that thank you for your
services discord thanks to scott
very much appreciate it
for real why is discard watching why not
who knows we're having fun
they're spending the best halloween ever
with us
i just realized kiara sounds the same in
the game
she doesn't disco really
i don't think so bad or good i don't
know but it's why is this song
yeah the quality sounds about the same
hey really
i'm supposed to sound good on discord at
least now when i bought my new
microphone
don't tell me it sounds shitty on this
glitch she sounds like she's
like one of those mic uh megaphone
things
to me at least i bought a 400 microphone
okay 400 or 500 whatever
don't tell me it sounds like a
walkie-talkie
maybe maybe it's my brain remembering
how your old mic sounds
and that's what it is
[Music]
maybe we should just do maybe we should
do discord again yeah
yeah okay yeah that lasted
everyone appreciate the discord yeah
that's good pickups to discord
you can always rely on discord always
rely on discord
again sorry are everyone ready no one
was working
[Music]
on darling you ready yeah oh sorry i'm
an
idiot hold on here we're going
i'm with her party so loud
that's real turn the audio down oh yeah
just turn it down because i had to turn
it up because everyone's voices are so
quiet and now it's like blasting over
yours
i wanna be the imposter i don't wanna be
the impulse
all right guys i think if we spread out
if we spread out
it'll be better ideas
what do you mean you cover more ground
when you spread
oh my god the room's changed so a thing
that happens in this game
whoa wait what a ditch whoa what is that
okay now i can show me the way to the
root
wait who's quiet watson is suspicious
[Laughter]
oh can you
know is that you you're not gonna hear
me yes yes okay are you though
that's you right thank you okay stay
together
okay i'm here too i'm normal normal oh
money
yep wait there's only one person in
front of me
[Music]
no i don't see anyone oh i don't
see anyone only the killer would have
recommended that we split up
oh sam
definitely you're meant to be listen
[Music]
either i'm killing folks or i'm getting
killed that's how it always goes every
game
oh god in a dedicated relationship with
death i am
yeah why is anyone surprised
okay one key down monkey down
[Music]
i don't know lucky yeah lucky adorable
watson
don't touch me okay
i hear someone say with death you silly
willies
what is that weird to make it weird
getting rich
[Music]
hello
be careful gave it away right in the
beginning girl
[Music]
careful wait look at this look like
chiara okay
what does kiara look like she's the one
with like the the
pigtails is that big deals oh
he's coming after you up the stairs now
he's a child again that looks just like
you
[Applause]
amelia
[Music]
[Applause]
i got no chance against amelia
[Music]
well i was up against the top fps player
out of halloween amelia what then
what and i can't win we both fling shot
at each other oh my god
the end this
[Laughter]
ah that was rough is there any way to
make it less keys
make it easier for you guys less oh we
can get to three keys do you want the
three keys
yes okay but for the time limit to ten
minutes
okay ten minutes three keys no names
no keycards yeah speedrun i could run
this bad boy
that's my secret right now because
you're fine and then you win yes
i want to be this guy he holds a lot of
things all right you said spread out
because you were there
amazing i get it i understand
all right pumpkin
that's right you can hold many things
yeah we are standing up but we're not
splitting up ah
i guess we are splitting yeah at least
it's only three keys now
money what does the money even do oh
oh what does the hammer do
are you cool i'm cool are you cool i'm
cool are you cool
i'm i'm cool i'm chilling hi cool are
you sure
yeah all right i'll go i'll go with you
then this would have been the perfect
time for me to kill you
are you sure are you sure you're not
gonna you're not gonna i don't like the
way you're saying that homie
i think i'm suspicious you guys always
think i'm suspicious
listen man i'm like what was that
someone broke a pot
did i check that before
i'm chillin yeah gura is quiet huh
uh oh
don't waste it don't waste your rocks
don't waste your time yeah waste your
rocks waste your eggs
why would he be wasting my rugs wait
what oh god
eh wait what is it what's up
[Music]
oh
my flashlight's gone oh
can you make things with it
this shot's not reload yeah what did
yours do no they don't
you only have 10. where's kiara
i'm useless now i got one key girl's
coming after me
oh i lost my pumpkin
throw the box i tried to throw it and i
stopped anything
sorry that's not available right now
i'll get them next time i'll get them
next time
i think my channel is the official
spectator channel everyone
where couldn't you be yeah please leave
a message
[Music]
has marked the key where is that
i think one of us seems to be a
detective to make it easier
why oh yeah
uh someone should be a detective that's
a good idea yeah
wait oh i watched that happen no my gosh
you threw something don't die
[Laughter]
i know i said that before but really why
can we not
call the police yeah
please
nice inna nice when can i find any keys
who's still alive besides me and ena
as i said dedicated relationship with
death no one's surprised
it's too bad i know how that
feels oh what is that i have a dedicated
relationship with that
deaf as well very dedicated
uh-huh i heard that the word upon the
street
oh yeah yeah yeah try it girls
i am dangerous again i can fight again
a certain november wink
huh okay the girls don't get
who are you who are you
[Laughter]
i don't think she saw you
wait do i want to run away from her or
what do i run away from there
probably running is the best option wait
what
nothing's nothing don't worry about it
wait the crowd that
doesn't mark the key anymore is it
because i went too far away
possibly uh i think it is yeah
if you get the key oh
nice oh
oh no you gotta throw something at him
wait i thought i thought i already
unlocked throw the
you dropped it in the garage i'm
cheating you dropped it in the garage
i meant to throw it because i didn't
want to hold on to it oh yeah
i kind of want to see what happens when
you win oh yeah it is curious huh
we need one more okay well
i cheated and i told you where it is
let's me that wouldn't be bait someone
be bait
no yeah i can't let me bake holly's got
to stop backstage
from the grave kelly's gonna shut up
now beth see gaming from the grave wait
where's chrome
who's this who's this cute little tyke
come here
oh my god i hate that so much dude oh
my god
i think you know where it is
oh no okay how many of you are alive
um
oh my gosh let me do a gun oh jeez
[Music]
yeah you're pretty decent at it
i think uh one
no because it's uh uh
in 15 minutes is half past like half an
hour before kelly's
oh yeah yeah oh yeah one more
okay yeah let's make it one to remember
i thought i meant to leave one person so
they could win i thought there was two
people left
my best
at some point she was talking as if she
was one of us
oh cool okay i'll i'll be adventure kid
let's go who is it yeah
why is he so creepy i don't get it
perfectly
sculpted stash perfectly symmetrical
please don't play though okay here we go
pumpkin
totally different
[Music]
maybe not because now we have to find
our way around
that's not different
it's kiara by the way uh-huh
what huh i never dream
smiling when pasta talking i can hear it
that sounds so small
let's stay together this time
run away from me i mean i'm i'm not
clear
it's not me really are you from me why
are you following me
oh are you normal we stick together who
are you
and this is me amelia jumping okay
okay okay okay we must stick together we
can
i can uh shoot whoever the wait who's
that
i come in peace and i'm giving you money
here's you guys okay if you guys find
gears tell me
okay oh gears stay in the same general
area
maybe it'll be okay i'm gonna go
okay i'll follow you walk soon okay
what is this you guys seem safe
yeah where's kiara she's uh somehow
missing out
just trying to get my keys why are you
running away
it's definitely
[Music]
are you cool yeah chiara is that you
no i don't know like the adventure kid
who's the me
gura oh girl okay cool i trust you
who's this i'm really watching jumping
oh i can jump you press spacebar to jump
i just figured that out
wait are you like right here i don't
like this this is too crowded i'm out of
here
okay okay no it's good because then we
can
we can let's be forever girl i'm fine i
promise you i'm fine
oh god kiara's here help me oh no
let's help each other out let's fix guns
come back oh you guys okay okay okay
she's here she's here she's right there
i don't even know how to hit her wait
who's who
wait no no no no no
i'm going this way okay i'm just giving
you a chance to win this game at least
one time okay oh my god it's definitely
ah
i dropped my flashlight here we're good
okay
see oh maybe we can find stuff to build
things what
what is that what is that where's the
music coming from
oh i don't like it
where are you guys ron i'm i'm not kiara
i'm amelia okay you're cool
right everyone always has there's
there's a thingy in here oh gears yo
the jackpot i'm locked who's following
me
oh i can almost ah man i hope i can make
the gun soon where
am i stuck in here
where am i
[Laughter]
oh right party this is a secret
bookshelf this is spin
cutie little camper
oh hey people nice
[Music]
okay i'm finally getting the controls
oh man i don't have anything to help you
someone was here
well we are really high up i don't know
[Music]
how do i get [\h__\h] up i mean up what
does that f button do
f button hey there you guys are i found
you
kiara's taking the main door if you guys
bring stuff we can kill her
there's a crowbar and any gears up here
i wonder
can i make this jump camera
nope that is the answer to that question
oh wait i can help you well you can get
it
i have one too i think we have enough to
win but we just need to get to the door
all right i'll be bait i can beat
a distraction
oh wait why wait wait what
you're saying what can i do with that
what's going on
[Music]
is
no no no no no no no relax relax
she's uh oh nothing what
can i take hold on we're safe here we're
safe here you guys see any gears
i got a key i had a lot of gears i
wanted to drop if i dropped them
we just have to get back
find any gears you guys hey we're all
alive can you believe it
i
[Music]
is
okay show me the way i don't know what
it is
[Music]
leave it to me
um
oh okay you ready no no no nothing
nothing nothing okay
i'm gonna hit your chest nice nice one
more
how do you guys let's click left click
put your key on the
oh okay how can we
sort of okay oh wait oh wait
okay oh my gosh i'm not back yet
it's our journey i'm sorry she died
did you die again no no
no no no wait do we respond
oh i think she died somewhere around
here
what you doing callie waiting to be
baked
okay
do we have all the keys no kiara's got
the red key
all right let me pick up something also
has a gun
that's not great news that's just not
great news to be honest
well i'm ready for the fight i'm ready
to brawl
oh crow mark's key crow marks the key
who is alive oh we only have a minute
45.
all right hey
hey hi
to we're okay we can go out here we can
go out here
wait wait why is it making noise like
that
what are we wait try to please try it
here i can throw this
i'll throw this at him and then you can
grab the
okay she's still she's still outside
don't tell them you shock her
hey
okay all right what's the plan here oh
whoa
[Applause]
nice nice oh nice perfect okay oh do i
need to get the blue okay oh
yeah there's no way to find the last key
is
yeah we got two blue how do you throw oh
i see
hold the hold on here
well there is two i think
oh oh one more time when we open it
[Applause]
like i was pretty close to to dying at
some point so
at two points i think
can hear
[Music]
but i really didn't think like i was
thinking if i'm gonna be the imposter
i'm definitely gonna
die and this will be the only game that
you're gonna be able to open the door
i did it it's good to be the killer once
the neighbor
yay it's gonna offer everyone about to
do it yeah i think everyone did yes
oh nice that's lucky um
okay and everyone won everyone won when
they were the killer
uh yeah oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah at the end
definitely definitely yeah that was fun
more often yeah the clown was super fun
to play oh my god the clown
[Laughter]
basically everyone had a win we are all
winning
yes yeah yeah winner it's a perfect
timing to end but cali i think you have
something to announce
i do my new song is premiering in 30
minutes
[Applause]
[Music]
there's a party after that where we're
gonna make drinks i haven't figured out
what we're gonna make yet but i bought a
bunch of stuff and if you guys go on my
twitter
you can see the ingredients i bought if
you want to buy your own similar
ingredients so we can all get drinks
together and celebrate halloween
thank you guys how about you guys do you
have any do you have any other
announcements
friends i'm making food yay
mom how do you get out not ordering
mcdonald's huh
the only announcement i have is i have a
legendary collab with marin senpai
coming up next
over so who knows what's going to happen
callie are you jealous if i sleep over
at madden senpai's place
for you what you want
[Laughter]
wait does your friend's life i just want
to make it clear we're just friends okay
as are we
nope not last time i checked that's not
what the ouija board says
what ouija
[Laughter]
anything else anyone wants to mention
uh i have uh i'm gonna post a video in a
little bit uh because cali
is is uh gonna give you guys the last
piece of candy to the halloween
scavenger hunt puzzle
yeah and i'm gonna post the video after
her stream on twitter
and you guys can see the final piece
[Music]
[Applause]
thanks for like organizing this super
cute event scavenger hunt
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
thanks for watching
you