[Music]
w
he
[Music]
oh hello it's me and my Cape me and my
Cape just me and my
Cape hi guys it's me I have a cap
whichit are you there you
[Music]
are hi look at my cap look look at it
look I can do you see that
shine so cute
MH MH mhm it's shiny and I have a popped
color
popped popped color and then the back's
[Music]
blue hi everyone welcome in it is C
name
Sunday and uh we're going to be playing
some more and Rec any manic
Recollections I'm just going to jump
into the game I tried connecting a
different mic because I saw some like a
clip of yesterday and my mic was really
bad but it didn't work because for some
reason when I tried doing that it be it
like looped it and then and then became
eoy I don't know we're going to have
my quality is just how life is
sometimes it's okay I was well in game
so for for other people hearing me my my
mic here this one is just my normal mic
that I always use for streaming thank
you for the pops thank you for I'm going
to turn down a little bit thank you are
you guys are doing well I tried napping
but I couldn't that's just how it is and
uh I want to see what more is in Anya
collection let's see let's see I haven't
tested okay this way
move
nice okay let me
see is that going to work is that going
to work fine it's loading
[Music]
it's
loading where the heck am I oh I'm on
the cannon
okay hi
uhoh ow
okay so let me put down the music a
little bit
and still in the gambling area yeah is
it dark
outside
oo okay I wanted to change
the wait are there mods off I can't tell
man I can't it's not as sparkly as last
time is it no yes I can't tell is this
is this
vanilla oh you got this c as
well does this look
like this is not vanilla okay I believe
you yeah I wanted to turn off change the
GU GUI scale should have done that
before stream my bad
settings
oh okay this is
good
okay good
good let me see how's your memers doing
um
not that good all I remember is
pizza
pizza okay let me
see party call Private call let me see
who's online oh not that many
people I saw fa earlier was doing her
mall maybe I can find
her I wonder where though I wonder where
she put it
Scarlet
[Music]
wand
oh both of you beautiful ladies nice hat
uh I must say I am almost envious a bit
I do recommend the iron Quest highly it
was quite uh a good um sh
anything very useful not to startle you
my lady but there is a woman on a horse
behind you
start me dang it I thought I could sneak
my
way
hell yeah yeah
hello
yeah we speak the language of the Gods
what the heck yeah we did a side quest
and we learned a new language in the
side quest oh you guys can do it too
what oh really yeah it's a do that it's
a side how long did it take you it took
me it took us 3 minutes if you guys want
to join I can show you three minutes mhm
and we'll learn an entirely new language
uh well yeah yeah it's like a it's like
a it's like a video game
mechanic okay so it's like you it's like
an RPG you know where you have a skill
tree and then you already did you do it
did you do it already yeah that's why I
speak uh
German M I heard I heard her say
something oh what did you say oh say it
her name's Nam it's
cleop actually it's Darwin
Roosevelt Junior you changed it
oh I did not can I call you Junior for
short you can call me Junior for sure
Junior what happened with
free
who what happened with the person you
were
yesterday I am the person that I was
yesterday
names are but to name am I struck by
Amnesia once again we just can't
comprehend her Brilliance she's on
another level H indeed she might
be how to get my Ladi my ladies may I
interest you in a lottery
ticket a lottery a daily lottery
starting today in the first drawing will
be
tomorrow 10 gold coins you can purchase
a lottery ticket or however many as you
would like and enter for your chance to
win big
jackpots isn't the othero green lady in
your guild too why do I feel like I'm
being cheated on why do you want to oh
did she do the exact same thing IIA with
you she she did the exact same thing
with me are you saying
that are you saying that you're not
having buy tickets the bigger the J has
to be personalized FAA every single sale
has to be
personalized well let me let me
look your green eyes and whenever I look
into your green eyes I see the green of
money and I recall the time we spent in
the casino betting it all on green
remember how that casino failed us oh
this is so personalized I feel so
targeted like I am in the market that
was so that was so much more intimate
than what she you said to me what the
heck it's because we like a miror or
[Laughter]
something um what are the win rates FAA
deest um bet better oh well it's about
about 1 in 700 although you can buy as
many lottery in
700 raise your chances every time it's
way better odds than the real lottery I
might add yeah but you don't what do you
win if you win how much you win the big
jackpot just the big jackpot money well
well right now it's only 10 gold but the
more lottery tickets are bought the
bigger the jackpot will grow oh okay so
if I want to guarante low the chances
are if you guys don't buy it then it'll
be a really L Lottery and they like one
sucker you're trying to like guil trip
us into paying for the lottery it's
working my lady I would like four
tickets quite the opposite four ticket
four tickets understand me yes yes my
lady in green understand me I was trying
to save that will be 40 oh you were
trying to save me um I was trying to do
you have to use reverse psychology 40
Golds accept how do I accept I done this
right
click you press and click on it oh okay
I did it being transparent I see you
very clly okay I have a question um do I
get a discount for being in team College
spech understand I no but perhaps some
of the proceeds for the lottery will be
used for the betterment of our some I
watch it yes
Perhaps Perhaps 10% perhaps there's a
chance the 10% H okay okay perhaps 10%
perhaps okay what did I say four 40 I
made it the block I made it here you
go thank which what numbers would you
like would you like to choose your own
numbers or would you like randomized
numbers I want my own numbers what are
the numbers tell me well you could
choose any thre digigit combination but
each digit has to be different any thre
digigit com oh okay I would like so it's
three three numbers no
zeros oh three different
numbers so like yeah three numbers one1
and but the number has to
be7
okay five7 very complicated system a
general advice for like most people um
if they have like more than one step in
the lottery they they'll back out
because they have too much time to think
about it f you know they have too much
time to well I'll just I'll just make
sure that they won't okay there's your
there's your first ticket what would you
like for the second one make sure you
hold on to that oh oh okay uh on the one
2 three no no everyone would do that no
657 okay okay
okay 9
21 okay okay one one second okay okay
okay okay okay one okay uh and uh two 4
Six and 2 4
six yes
that's it I think those were four surf
GA VPN yes that should
be that should be
four popcorn
is what is popcorn I only no
corn do do I have to do
something I have sent you your ticket oh
oh ability oh wow this is legit you put
it in the mic that's right this is the
real deal guys it it really is you can
expect nothing but the best oh this is
really impressive actually it seems like
a good like good business model yeah
okay lock into to
tradeo thank you thank you for trading
with me our sponsorship has arrived surf
GAA
VPN oh she's
surfing that's the appointed point you
both have a point they both have a point
a lottery ticket lottery ticket would
you be interested in gambling and
partaking in a lottery so you buy a
ticket and I guess the proceeds go to
supporting the
library did you know that once you wear
the hat of the appointed Point your
memories are shared I feel like we've
already had this
conversation what no you're
what is this a scam did she try to enter
you tried to enter sevens but you had a
double seven you couldn't enter that
right I'm I'm a bit fuzzy I had a bit of
a compression
[Music]
earlier she
knows I was watching your Vlog and she
was watching her Vlog memories
perfectly it's like a high of Mind guys
can you read each other's in
mind wait okay wait GAA think of a color
F tell tell us what color she's thinking
think of a color she's thinking of blue
how did she know how did she know the
appointed point you know you mustn't
ever remove that hat you will
die okay okay how about you will you die
I will also die okay I know I know how
if I remove the Hat you die and if you
remove the Hat I die we both die C money
I will leave the Hat on forever then
gotta guys can you like touch like can
you like put your heads down and
fight I don't know if that's the same
gambling everybody talking you're
shaving an lless there's a different one
oh yeah there's a oh now we're talking
it's like a limbo limbo
[Music]
Bridge wait wait
sorry I did it are you
liing go mama you can do
it it worked wow we also
very
impressive very
very funa do you want to show us your
March I haven't seen
it I tried taking a nap yes yes it's
it's still a work in progress and we
mainly sell lottery tickets at this
point we all going bom is open wa open
please show us owe me a you owe me a
place to rest my weary head oh yes you
may rest your weary head in the floor of
the shop okay
that I love how like the the horses are
so fast that we just you constantly have
to turn around you're like yes
everyone's still
there oh try to observe it only from the
front
oo
o phart lottery tickets now available
guys this sounds like a good deal is
this entire March just for lottery
tickets oh thank you so far we don't
have anything else for sale really well
if you would like to buy some chry
saplings we could we could negotiate
um for lottery tickets yes what is the
benefit of a cherry oh you won't fit
through here um you can grow it into a
cherry or you can use it as decoration
Che this out
just
available I just have to but new then
you have to go out and get it yourself
is it is is that much trouble I'm not
sure about I'm not sure about the safety
of this establishment funa I think I
think kind of yeah it's well a work in
progress maybe if more lottery tickets
are purchased then that can go towards
the betterment of bomart I think for
safety measurements you need the lottery
would go towards the library not Library
towards the library was this mentioned
before well check check the fine print
of your
ticket I think you should put a a sign
down where it says like please wear hat
when entering like a hard hat you know
like on a construction
side of
all Excuse Me Miss the fine PR says it
says that you get 30% of the jackpot but
you just said 10% no no the library gets
10%
so 40% doesn't even go
[Music]
towards yeah the the jackpot is huge
huge jackpots big wins in the lottery
every
day okay then after taxes what well I
don't know if you have to pay taxes the
king doesn't know about this Lottery and
I'd like to keep it that way and I think
you all would
too oh you wait just wait until the
queen hears about this que the queen is
a queen the future Queen who treat her
as the current Queen the the the Tam
tenders lady
oh the K was trying to propos to her so
she's accepting his proposal then of
course a of course she is oh we have to
think of what what would we give as a
present for the like a betral present
for the king and queen C how about a
lottery no no no no no how about two
lottery cards I think two lottery tick
two lottery tickets I don't know I feel
like that's embarrassing I feel like
there's nothing you can really give to
someone who's going to be Queen when you
are the status that we
are well no no we're saving them though
like what like a blender if they can't
get one
themselves but it's the thought that
counts and you could put a like if as
long as you make it personal
you know aend I you should pleas please
no fire inside
of I'll put it sry sorry that's just a
phoenix happenings every once in a while
accidentally I'll turn the AC on wait I
can't
who it was the
[Music]
AC go to the coast any that's messed up
man
what you what what you're you you're
taking advantage of people that can't
read that's what the library is
for coming so we can teach people to
read you didn't mention
have it's a library of course of course
she's doing something for the local
businesses M what are you doing for the
local businesses why are you on her side
because we're Team Scarlet one and we
stand together also she's kind of
intimidating because of her hat sorry
what she was trying to scam you though
yeah but she's on my team as long as she
wins I
win know you're one of those people like
well but she's she's my mother she's my
brother it's okay if she takes all my
money we will expose this scam on her
Vlogs and then you will go down Expos
sounds sounds like free advertising yeah
just copyright strike it
write the paper so everybody
knows no one will know well I'll hold on
to my ticket I think tell the queen
about this wait wait before you tell the
queen would would you be interested in
joining the
lottery no it's only it's only 10 I
think it's a really good deal uh you get
a German discount it costs uh 40 44
three tickets only a ger German this
what the heck what's a German a German
is uh it's like one of the side quests
that I mentioned
earlier yeah I want I want to go on this
side quest to learn
Germany
Germany yeah I think that's for another
scam of theirs I can teach you Germany
privately Kar Kar by the ticket pie the
tickets don't we need think think of ger
es think of your language but if your
Germany isn't the right Germany my
Germany is the best Germany don't listen
to I have the superior Germany don't say
that don't listen to
her okay my Germany sounds beautiful
yeah that is true who's la la lying over
there okay I'll show you the quest are
you
ready no no no
no you're not ready cuz you haven't
bought a ticket yet right yeah if you
bought the ticket you
just come on buy a ticket buy a ticket
are we all going to are we all going to
about Germany now yeah okay um no not
about Germany we're doing the side quest
to learn
German yeah okay that's what I meant
okay uh this
way I Haven what am I going to what am I
going to come up
with okay step number
one you have to talk to this
NPC oh oops everyone get on
their I can be your Shield anything in
particular it says I can pee your Shield
if you want me to now he also says it in
German no oh look look closely it says
it right
there to um scam um this is just another
scam over there he it perfectly he said
I can be your Shield if you want me to
exactly I can understand German she did
it oh wow that is very impressive okay
next one next one right this way wait a
minute wait a minute wait I'm not okay
I'm I'm
absorbing Cara get on your
horse
no no it come with us
come
us why would we need these NPCs to teach
us German when I can teach her German
privately cuz real like this is a video
game and this is a shortcut in real it
takes too long but this way we learn it
like it gets like translated into our
brains okay the next MC is right here
[Music]
here go horse go oops every
time oh speak he's
saying did you understand what he
said I understood it what what did he
say I'm getting bits and pieces
here uh it says I'm supposed to be
working please don't where did K go
oh oh what was that yeah was
that was
that wow it's working it's
working wow I think M already finished
the
quest oh
work what does that mean um um she's
saying it
worked wow that's very
impressive it means that I speak German
she says wow M you you're natural I'm
really
impressed uh if you trade with me you'll
get the quest
reward here you
go it's
working here's your quest reward
[Music]
what do you get for learning
[Laughter]
German wow she got some
bread thank
you oh I'm so I'm so happy we did the
side quest
huh it's so easy to
learn
languages
okay that was
amazing I learned so much I'm so world
really has everything I'm so happy that
they implemented this honestly I think
it's very
nice yeah like they should they should
set this up with more language
yeah um um though yeah where did she go
is she still here
no I don't know she went backwards I
think or I have no idea I wish we had
like
a
locator like a radio that we could use
to call her and ask her to buy a lottery
ticket I think she was almost folding I
think she was very close to buying the
lottery ticket I think if we hadn't got
distracted by this Great quest I think
she would have bought a lottery
tickets you know who hasn't bought one
yet my fellow pointy I don't need to buy
one if we share the same I I
I but you have to support the business
think but in reality you do need to buy
one for even your contribution sweetens
the pot a little bit for everybody
[Laughter]
so can I can I get you down for four
tickets four for four tickets that's cuz
you know how much money I have of four
tickets get out of my get out of my head
hat wearer listen we got to set some
boundaries I'm very impressed M my I
think your pronunciation is very very
fluent it's very
impressive after yeah it's really good I
will buy
one
one I don't know I think it's from all
the exposure from the two NPCs and then
suddenly you just got it it's like
something clicked in your brain it's
very
impressive okay what numbers do you want
but I have to clear my throat a lot
before I do it so I'm not going to do it
again yeah it's a bit of a difficult
setup I mean uh I would like
yeah I would
Li I would
like that's sick let me
see quiet wait what number what to what
numbers what to what what's the maximum
oh one to nine
make let's
do uh
three three sorry I made it German n
four okay you're quite quiet wait I keep
putting you up M but you're so quiet
don't know quiet okay let's see we'll
send
you okay oh your lottery ticket I put
you the mail yeah it's okay now thank
you I you put me up I'll put you up this
I'll put you up oh that's why you were
I'm being put
uper understand now M can you tell you f
fun fact let's do five five entire no no
just one fun fact yeah oh just one oh
just one fun fact that's good okay thank
you for your the other day I played a
game it's called I mean the memories of
a forsaken life tells me that the other
day I played a game c
get getting a bit back right
and you know at the beginning when you
pick a genda sound very short when you
say yeah and then instead of like girl
or boy the options are you own an
Airship and the options are for the oh
baby I'm so high up and goodness I'm so
high
up know when one of us succeeds we all
succeed
right
Rising all
sh I don't know how I feel about I can
hear smiling when I'm
talking I don't
care are those the two options yeah so
inste of girl boy if you pick goodness
I'm so those are the only options they
give you yeah so if you say goodness I'm
so high up you turn into a girl and if
you say oh baby we're so high up you not
insur so don't worry no insurance SC
they try to say boys or babies not
insured no I think it has to be to do
with enthusiasm about
height but
it's have you ever seen the thing that's
like that's like boys love to drop
things from like giant Heights is it
based on that like dropping rocks from a
cliff my what it's
based I don't know what it's S I saw a
video the other day of like this group
of like 10 guys all carrying a rock just
to throw it off the cliff and got so
excited about it
yeah ice
breaking ice ice break boys will be boys
and she like 10 grown man throwing a
rock in
ice no it's a thing there's like
compilations of it like satisfying
videos but for
men fish PA be like I support it the the
pool fish they get their heads bumped
in um I kind of get it I saw this video
where this like these people were
bouldering and they had to you know
loosen up or get rid of the really loose
rocks they got rid of this one like part
of this rock and you it drops and you're
like oh it's not that high up but then
it keeps falling and it keeps falling
and you realize it is really high up it
was crazy I think the ice breaking is
really satisfying I think when you go
somewhere and it has snowed and the snow
is totally untouched and you put like
your first first footsteps that is very
satisfying yeah yeah
yeah especially when like no one's been
there so so far so it feels like you
know you're the first the first that
walk gross yeah it's so gross after like
enough people walk through it yeah it's
extra
seasoning not that wait like the dirt
it's shaped ice it's shaped ice real
real real real
snow yeah yeah I've never had it the
texture is better than what you can get
from the machine ooh and the nutrients
extra Nutri nutrients it boosts your
immune system eat some dirt o oh the
dir ladies ladies I have a question
would you so be so kind to accompany me
I would like to see if I can also get a
red a pointy hat I have 359
money do you guys is this a guild thing
no it's a gamble thing need money
okay I want a hat too yeah hey why are
you now so excited about gambling yeah
what what the what with the lottery I
don't care about money I only care about
hats you know can get you a hat money
but what about the library another guild
what it's just a library there's like
Barnes and& Nobles you can just buy
books now Kindles I got a Kindle is it
good what's a
Kindle I did it I haven't you haven't
touched like a month
ago touch you keep talking about how you
have a Kindle but it's still in the box
have you at least ripped off the foil
Kindle look it's there like looking at
it she's so I I bought a case you bought
a case you even put in a case no I I
bought a case and I and I put it in the
okay I didn't
activate turn it on did you did you put
on a protective
foil no is there one I think so
I still has the factory peelies on it it
has like the default thing on you could
turn it on and like read through the
instruction manual on the Kindle and
then you could traveled
with I had I had to take it out to
okay hey at least you have
one so you'll read from it I think let
us know when you use it yeah let us know
when you turn it on brought like a real
book with me did you read the real book
I did I read a little bit of it oh my
gosh so I could read no more use the
Kindle as a bookmark for your re
okay I don't remember where I think the
gobling was here this way I
think she likes it here so the it is
gambling just so you know M so if you
buy one there's a chance that you don't
get a hat I already bought two and I
haven't gotten a hat is it the surprise
box
yeah okay yes I bought it you want to
open it together I bought one how do you
open it okay so you have to put it in
your hand and then right click
it okay okay ready three two
one and then you have to pick one it
didn't
work wait you pick one you pick one oh
you have to hold your
bar hold up I think I'm doing something
wrong
oh oh there go holding
it you pick only oh shoot you pick
one and one of those has a hat behind it
only one has a hat oh four four of those
I
think what else can you
get a box I didn't get
anything dang it what are these I didn't
get the Hat I didn't get the Hat I
didn't get the Hat what I get I don't
know what I
alert what wait what get what I get what
I get what I get did you get the Hat got
the hat I got the Hat you got nothing
you got nothing I got about it doesn't
work it's not going to work no
no what there's no point in wearing it
what what's going on what's going on is
so ugly anyway did I did I get all these
things no you only get one everything in
here it's just showing you what you
didn't get it's
like did you wait she has to head ni
very hard before you put that on your
head think very hard wait wait a minute
why can't I put it on my head don't
don't do it don't do
it what
is what happens if she puts it on her
head
what the head of the the the head of the
[Laughter]
appoint okay now you guys have to stop
talking and only use uh tele
telecommunication
okay here's here's the deal
now the head of the appointing points
has been has been dawned by a member
outside of the guild which hasn't ever
happened before in the history of this
Carly
wand I haven't really for a day it's
fine it's fine it's fine um I knew she
was sorted into the wrong Guild I knew
it it has to be Destiny it has to be M
would you say you are cretive said
you're on another level
wait I now am I creative would you say
you're a
genius knowledge do you seek
knowledge I I do I mean you have a
Kindle I I do do seek but an unused
Kindle yeah but it's like she's seeking
it still you know she's seeking I still
seek it it's just I I got a little
distracted is all yeah because she's so
creative and creative types of often get
distracted yeah I was sleeping I was
sleeping a lot and
dreaming and I was having the craziest
dreams yes it makes sense the craziest
dreams I've ever had I think we have to
all three of us should touch tips and
and and finish
the the G of the the Hat of the
appointed Point
ceremony in the triy formation
okay wait a little bit back wait a
little bit back a little bit okay
okay down go look further down the way
down all the way ah there
you make a triangle give make a
triangle back
down
triangle and it points to C I mean the
green one can I go in the
middle yes you can now this is my
Tepe I live here W
double oh cuz it's well in what that TP
can I do that I saw kie where did she
goie oh I see the
talie I sensed a present no she oh the
present of death oh
the presence of death and Dean the
presence of death I see it I see it
right in front of me is that Park Fair
Fair Lady good tomorrow to you green one
do you perhaps happen to be the one
that's uh with the lottery tickets yes
indeed would you perhaps be interested
in joining to win big jackpots and big
prizes well you see I'm just a little
wary of you last time that I did the
lottery I ended up you know losing my
house my wife my kids this just a little
bit of a traumatic experience for me are
you sure that you can you assure me big
winnings well nothing is assured in the
lottery but I can assure you that even
if you don't win big the library always
wins for our Lottery supports local
education efforts via the Scarlet wand
Library what the what kind of
education books book oops and we have a
new German language course available oh
okay can I have some proof maybe oh yeah
uh
M M M did the German language course
side she's a she's very impressive uh we
can move to her if you so wish dear
Patron sure
yeah never mind I do not know where she
is okay
oh she's in here she's in
here she's in here I see m
m never mind she ran away I don't think
that was M actually I don't know um fa
fauna quick
say quick
say oh you can see wow she's so good
she's our second pupil our second star
pupil yeah I haven't completed the
course yet but I'm already learning a
lot and really it's about the journey
more than just you know the destination
or we as we
say yeah yeah yeah yeah so how you say
uh 10 10 tickets uh for 200 money 200
money oh let's see well I am a little
curious uh I guess yeah sure why why not
I mean I I have a lot of coins so
probably shouldn't tell you that but
yeah I have a decent amount of Co okay
yeah um sure tickets means more chances
true I'll start off with 10 10 seems
like a healthy
amount okay shall we just for 200 the
whispering coins is that Kiara
Holan I told you about this no no no you
have to understand I I was I was the one
scamming them I I was the one that was
going going to scam them for their
tickets and then I was going to sell
their tickets to other people oh that is
kind of evil though that just continues
to evil it would been hilarious
especially if you like make
enemies enemies we still in
the yeah that's just a pyramid over
overall if anything oh what did you say
we couldn't hear you our bgm was a bit
loud so we couldn't hear your Whispering
sorry oh really okay just trust me on
this Cura oh it makes perfect sense oh
okay okay I trust the bom that we have
yeah of course and besides it's me
that's losing money not you um but you
can say I told you so later how shall we
make the trade all right I will trade
with
you that's 10 tickets for 200 coins
please and you may choose the numbers or
I can give you a random assortment of
tickets if you don't mind the numbers
ooh okay um I'll take your actually
maybe I should choose nope I will go
ahead and leave it up to
chance
okay all righty let's see 200 wait what
wait what 200 coins no don't Kiara can I
see your special magic spell I haven't
seen you guys
yet no I shall not reveal my skills to
the enemies oh do you want to see
mine that that honestly it just looks
like a a tower that I've seen in New
York oh is
that it's my spear
Building New York it's my
spere oh are you sure you didn't just
take it from a miniature Recreation of
New York City no it's my spear it's made
from ancient tree an ancient magical
tree no okay I'll show you my you just
lock in you will find your
tickets my mailbox delivered already
what best impressive
Communications not as impressive got is
very that's so cool I mean I mean okay
Co that's nothing what watch this Take
Me Alive oh it has 30C cool down so it
was a scam run no hey it wasn't a scam
now I have to delete all these
tickets what's
that hey you made the
profit no she took the money wait she
took the money she took the money now I
have to I have to I have to take back
all the tickets I said her I can't
believe they would scam us like this
what color uh Guild are they from again
left
me wait is there are you in their Guild
who Guild we have a
spy what wait Scarlet hat adorned spy
I'm of the coin of Ember no Amber I see
and who's in your
guild uh the lady of the orange which
one the
B which which Orange
the Phoenix of the kiaha of the orange
the kiaha of the orange the oranges mhm
and the
ba and the really cute cat oh the really
cute
cat she's very cute she's pink super
cute cat she's very cute when you patch
her hat she purse
cat very cute very cute cat Okay well
that means that she can't be with the
with the messenger of death you can't be
on the messengers of death side because
they're not in the same
Guild so I personally don't think she's
oranges with
her oh was kiava the oranges with the
messenger of death
yeah well that's a little concerning for
me Isn't
it do you think they are unless you
convince kiaha of the orange to purchase
a lottery ticket to a the wait a minute
what did I miss you both now are for
this whole lottery ticket thing but
you're part of the Scarlet W now because
of your hat you are too the Hat about 24
hours and you'll come around what
benefits do I get now that I have the
Hat in relation to the lottery ticket do
I get a percentage of the percentage
that you keep of the 30% do I get a
certain percentage of that 30% there's a
chance well when the library wins
everyone
wins yes you got to sell me on this
Library a little bit
more it it looks like a laundering
scheme you can put your Kindle in it
given where all the where all the
resources have gone to and how little
books there
are but the lottery hasn't even had a
single day yet to benefit the library
but why is the library already so large
with so many riches except happened
before we arrived in this land we're
just trying our best to to repair the
damage that has already been done to our
education system but do you have trust
in this Library that's already so
sketchy or did you remove we change it
from the inside M we have to be the
difference we have to buy physical books
by encouraging people to gamble and
throw their life savings away yeah we
only ask for a meanly 10 gold
that's more that is but get I think this
is part of of the Hat taking
over oh my gosh am I feeling
empathy am I sympathizing for those that
fall into gambling patterns which I
canot relate to because I got the Hat on
the first
[Laughter]
try well wait the Hat has one more super
crazy buff whenever you're losing in an
argument you can say but I have the
point and then you win
automatically this is true
that's right this is true so quick you
guys say I have a point so that she
loses at the library argument yeah I
have a point I have a point I also have
a
point well we have two points triangle
one point so but I have the
point she's right she does have the
point kiaba of the oranges kiaba of the
oranges what a good point she pointed
did she pointed out the point she
appointed herself to be the one to make
the point it's very
impressive do we have to do a quest are
we
okay the D we don't have to do anything
right the dungeon opens oh soon oops oh
time flies when you have a point I wish
I had a hat what's the
point we'll get to your hat we'll get to
that point don't worry
it's a good
one maybe we can find someone they can
lend us
money but I only did
that heavy tickets and
then how dare you how dare you m leaving
our Guild behind to join this scammer
Guild I will never forget this I will
Revenge and that will tell the
queen uh-huh uh I understand everything
that just happened because I I was
reading your mind throughout that whole
conversation no don't
cry take my hat tells me these are not
real
tears no but why would she
li My Hat tells me that that that is
real
spot I wish She's So
Mean
um I she maybe she was jealous of your
hat true probably I said I said I look
look keep one the oranges I got a hat
wouldn't you say that I have the point
and then I was going to go and tell you
guys that she said I have the point but
then she she wouldn't did that
are you okay you sound like you're
joking I'm okay okay
I'm um it's it's okay I'm sure Kiara
will come around uh you just have to say
I've got the point more often it's like
a hot you're also taller than she is
which we gives you gives you more more
more
dominance higher higher much tell yeah
yes you have the higher ground you guys
get me I'll never betray you you guys
totally get
me that's right my hat says otherwise
but I appreciate
it is the Hat thinking further ahead
than I am further
ahead are these mind is very powerful
like I do have intrusive thoughts that I
think that's something you guys should
consider I think things that I don't
want to think sorry I just got a really
weird urge I don't know if I should act
on it are you guys influencing each
other in a
triangle like one person has intrusive
thought and then I the other person does
it that window looks so
breakable I wish it
was yeah it just looks it it isn't
actually I know
oh how do you throw stuff again cute
I don't think they even throwing is not
allowed in this ging you can't throw in
this game because you get fined for
littering did you know that oh really
five coin fine for littering wait how do
I test this I don't know but there is a
fine I believe you I believe everything
you
say I think it's because we are heroes
we are hardwired not to do
crime maybe there's like some Force
inner Force stopping us yeah a
conscience bad
things that's what it's
called yeah I think it makes sense and
also I thought about this since last
time M did you do the dungeon the first
one I did do you remember how in the
entire dungeon there was not a single
stain yes do you remember how the queen
and the all the people in this Town and
Country are like oh you have to defeat
the stains they are be really evil and
then they send us on a dungeon Mission
and there's not a single stain don't you
think that's suspicious did the
skeletons not count as a stain the
skeletons were not stains they were
skeletons they were just skeletons mhm
some other te maybe they were in the
wall the king yeah somebody does
somebody did say something weird to me
actually I can take you to them
oh weird things
a break in the in the Matrix or
something something like that follow
me the hottest part of the game
following a
horse this way this way this
way follow the beacon that is on her
head waa this guy you okay he's said
something weird oh
we saying something weird NPC a break
something is happening NPC talk text
Q3 I feel like this is a message for us
that we need to
decipher H NPC to.ex 3 what could it
mean I think not everything is what it
seems perhaps I think the three stands
for the fact that there are three guilds
that are probably in cahoots with the
King and that there's only one Guild
that is doing the truth that's what the
text stands for you know text as in like
scripture the the truth MH talk talk
lying NPC all NPC except for us
except it's funny together I
think in this Kingdom a mystery is a
foot
and it's to us the SK is one since m is
part of the sky one three
backwards
three uh ear h e
right wait the number of the word it is
e e
e could it be saying q t
[Music]
could it just be calling you a cutie is
it maybe it's not that
deep why would it be unknown well yeah
it's unknown stands for the mystery know
she's wearing the Hat I've heard of
people having names that basically mean
unknown like saying what the others are
saying yeah I feel like I feel like
she's she's putting us on a red herring
like on a wrong
path I feel okay I might just be wrong
I'm sorry I just I just and now she's
Bing I just won't contribute I guess
okay no
no noiz I don't know what's wor making
me feel stupid or making me feel like
I'm betraying you
guys it could be cutie make it could
have been cutie I'm sorry the Hat gives
delusions of paranoia and it does it
does the Hat the Hat oh the Hat yeah it
was the Hat sorry
it wasn't me it was the Hat I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry
too thank you I'll consider forgiving
you NPC talk text Q3 in the next
dungeon oh it just might
be perhaps it could be maybe it would be
worse the dungeon that opens in 2
minutes maybe it would be worth
exploring that dungeon so that we can I
was shocked get to the bottom of this
conspiracy perh dungeon time mayhaps is
for
enough I think I have to leave you I
will not be doing the dungeon today
leaving us to the dungeon I'm sorry you
already made a lot of profit I'm too
scared to go in there oh we'll Scout it
for you and then you can go in there a
different time know how it is with a
guide we'll write you a nine-page
document that
guide thank you thank
you we'll miss you healer oh God no
we're going to die no fun don't leave we
need
you we will miss you terribly but it's
okay can I can I lend you the
apple don't worry I wonder can you I
have something to
remember no where did it go did you take
it from me
oh it's in your trade
box my trade box the chest if you click
on the
chest that's oh what oh what
now go to Atlantis
with do we have food do you have
food I have I have a lot of okay that's
good I have some food too wait but I can
get more food if I can cook
it I think as long as you have enough to
survive the dungeon you should be fine
is 58 bread enough to survive the
dungeon I think
so are you sure is it me a 12 of them
have the German Buffy which makes them
stronger this I think this is the German
bread too mhm what's the machine called
that cuts bread in ger in German bu
Mach what
mach amazing Mach bread cutting
machine I think
yes that's it D how do you say it is oh
it that's that's
is that's is that is
[Laughter]
is is yeah yeah mhm
yeah is is f
is wow star student everyone she really
is the pride of our Academy I'm so
proud I'm like a
sponge she takes in knowledge yeah you
have three extra tear now to store brain
stuff in so take advantage of it hat sh
do I got to pick my next language
carefully maybe it's the whatever this
liis and
talks maybe that's an language of its
own you learn this language you might be
able to out of this you start cing your
own game for
me you make a different game any attempt
to understand him is ruined you guys
maybe not feel too good about about my
decoding T so
I
oh um I'm sorry the dungeon yeah let's
go the
dungeon okay good luck my fellow Scarlet
wands wi it for us thank you for making
money for us thank you for I for
us
scams NE wait next let's make a an
MLM
okay in the shape of our heads
true oh
yeah um do you have go to the coast and
speak to Corin of the Scarlet wand as
the next
Quest probably
not what say at the top go to the coast
and go to the oh I do oh I do I do okay
nice where is
people
noell okay it's this way
will you will you will you come with us
for are you oh oh
bra fwell farewell Fair Maiden farewell
farewell she's Galloping off into the
darkness
we must go to the next area to the coast
to the
coast in the coast we're in
the
surpr um
this it's this way
oh it's pretty far away all
right up left
right left right up right left right l r
no you hear
me
no okay it's here
before hor the horse connection is not
very good no it's not very realistic
though faster than the speed of
sound oops oh it's
this I
think
oh
um oh what you guys is this the coat I
see the co it's so
pretty this way
he's so cute it's one of your people
yeah he has the
Hat wait this is this this is your
people this the Scarlet one gu this is
our people our people I'm here to
investigate the mysterious lights you
can see it they're rising from the waves
the locals are quite Aur with curiosity
we are short something of great import
lies therein mayhaps a way to unlock
more of your
memories mayhaps but fear not mayhaps as
is our duty and our calling we have been
speaking with the locals and gathering
information in Intel to would seem there
exists a magical object known as a
rainbow Coral cluster which would allow
one to breathe underwater we believe
this to be no mere rumor as the Guild
Master was able to find texts among our
archives that corroborate this story
should one obtain such a she's talking
to the I'm not getting the same text
wait where am I wait am I just behind
hold
on should should should according to the
text you can be crafted from Rainbow
Coral shards and refin magical energy
you need not concern yourself with the
latter good hero our Guild Master will
gladly provide it but will you Aid Us in
the search for Coral shards that are
iridescent as a rainbow C so we got to
find Coral shards and bring them wait he
should have said iridescent such as our
coats you know a little cake very decent
too when you
move and they kind of look cheetah print
oh yeah that's
true they're
themed I'm going to pretend I understand
okay did you get wait we have to
find oh Coral 10 rainbow Coral shars
yeah let's see I can swim I can swim
okay
okay it's just this
oops I it's just this we all have to get
our own right oh it work yeah me wait
that's not that many
uh-oh get
here oh they respawn okay
pH I got them yay I got
them they respawn very fast yeah that's
good easy easy ow ow oh God I stood in
the fire it's okay F wait how do you
give him the how do you give him the
shars uh you you just talk to
him
oh oh oh oh we have to give it to rubius
the Guild Master back and talk to Rubi
too many people to keep track of the The
Guild Master RPG
he's right here
see R now it really feels like RPG with
a actual fch
Quest oh my ladies would you per chance
want switch to
ow um to to uh form a party so we can be
on call in the with the magical call
device sure that
sounds useful okay let's let's do it
once we get to
rubious do your best horse
bra no
there
go hello okay wow oh wait why is your so
little oh never mind it look like a pony
for a second it me
little tiny
hello oh they not behind oh there it's
okay okay and now we just got to find
our Guild Master which is here
oh
no we we lost a member we lost we
[Music]
lost she
went I can call her and see maybe we
have more people to add to our party
yeah let's see is anyone else online
from our
Guild oh sh sh is online okay I'll call
Shy
okay okay
oh she's already in a
call she's not picking up she's not
picking up she's in a call
already who's she talking to yeah who is
she talking to there's no no other guild
member of our is here right now oh FAA
is online still what she's calling I'm
going to spam call
her she will pick up wait I'll send her
an SMS real quick
Ruby is just build something into my
forehead what did he just
do
what he did something he did something
he wasn't reading what he said I don't
understand
what oh there you are a horse we were
scared we must have we could have lost
you to the you did lose me oh but I
found my way back that's okay that's
nice oh okay let's see what the NBC has
to say oh do you want to do you want to
read it out loud for me as well
Mo oh
okay she's a horse I can't tell what
accent this guy is this the British no
he's not the British no that's not which
one this is the Royal one oh Royal okay
mhm upon receiving word from my
colleague on the coast I immediately set
about making the necessary preparations
for crafting
with these shards you have brought the
preparations are complete now if you
will give me but one
moment ping ping ping what did he do and
finished I do say more Arcane prowess
astounds even
myself so this is that's okay so this is
a rainbow Coral cluster an object I had
only read of now brought into existence
but don't laugh at me but
but my very hand sorry that's
okay I can't hear him anymore rubius
please sorry
sorry sorry I had a scw stuck in my okay
but I should not should not
[Laughter]
[Music]
someone else do do you want me to put
like you know like hit your back
like yes
please oh thank you there you go ah but
I should not bore you with my exhaustion
you need this exaltation exalt
exaltation exalted s you need this for
your quest do you
not here you go this will allow you to
freely explore the depths of the sea use
it well and think nothing of payment or
reward as far as I am concerned
curiosity is its own reward oh no I hate
that I know it's so
overused ah but there is one thing I
would ask of you and that is your safe
return from this Quest I can think of no
greater way to repay me a now then off
with you I expect good news upon your
return Excel sir
exelia
exelia Excel
or oh what Excel Excel or what oh what
mov or that oh sorry
Junior okay oh W that was wo wo wo wo
that was that was weird that was really
weird Junior my name is Junior yes short
for know
that was I shall try to call uh shy one
more
time okay she is in a
callio
Jun wait should Darwin Cecilia and I
should we make a party oh before we go
back back yes if you want to been to a
party before you've never been in a
party before it tickles a little bit but
yeah it okay yeah I'm eventally
preparing myself okay you have to press
the T and then accept but there's
there's nothing I didn't mean to do
that no no no you started the Tea
train there you go
[Music]
what's your guys's favorite tea flavor
if I may
ask hot cinnamon spice ooh
w sounds
fun I don't think I've ever hadin
one I don't know what my favorite is cuz
I put so much honey in my tea it just
tastes like honey sugar water T dough
yeah it's basically sugar water sugar
water said that sugar water
okay uh investigate the Ocean Temple
dungeon then speak to the
scoler okay um uh I don't I don't want
to decide what we should do next so
someone else decide I will stand on my
horse and ready up I will let my horse
Grace okay should we do the dungeon do
we all want to do as three or should we
try and invite we can only have one more
person I think we can have I think two
long the dungeon can be completed within
an hour I can do um yeah I think
yesterday only took us like half an hour
and we were only three so hopefully this
one isn't hard yeah I'll try calling her
one more
time oh we can have five total five
total five total uh have to call for
the oh my God my throat I can't finish
the sentence you can do
it let me see we can shoot
of the Scarlet wand please accept my
calling now we can run to the here wait
here
where oh not here I meant I just meant
here in this
world yes she is she she is hello oh
that's not shooting dear oh oh there's a
lot of people online right now hello
hello hello please call again okay I
will call her again again
hello I want in on this
hello uh hello D ding ding ding ding
ding ding ding ding ding someone's
calling Oho hello what's up girl hi
what's up hi member of the Scarlet wand
would you like to join us on our
Expedition I am currently trying to
enter the dungeon of theworld which is
located think to say to that oh she's
doing the dungeon of the underworld uh
gaura of the red
head yes I believe it is called the pit
ah I see okay we will discuss I wish you
the best luck we will discuss and call
you
again thank you good luck good luck call
for insurance next time uh okay she said
call for insurance next
time um okay I guess she's doing the
other dungeon for now so
oh should we try it as three should we
try I think that's okay I think everyone
there's a lot of people online so I
think everyone will
find yeah yeah I think it's okay
yeah I think everybody will at least
have a group of three yeah because I
think two is too little probably be so
impressive and Nissa is online later too
and she's probably going to also have to
do that one again so we can see maybe
I'll be online and then I'll join them
again too okay let's go back to the
ocean shall we away away with us wait
investigate the ocean and follow yeah
this
way yeah three should be fine yeah I
guess that just happens kind of you know
when you start differ different time
zones I wanted to start a bit earlier
today cuz I'm so sleepy so
it is what it is but we'll get we'll get
to play together soon I think as the
full Scarlet wand I lost the
girls oh where did M go oh there she is
okay listen for horse
this
way yeah yeah we'll do a party okay are
you
[Music]
out
[Laughter]
hello I mean yes we could be in a party
call but I really like the the horse
stuff I think it's really funny to be
like driving riding past someone just
hearing the like did I a
hey uh it's
here oh
no must have lost
them I lost
them oh I have found you again this
one who I
landed oh boy
I guess I'll do a
Party Fair ladies the the had of
appointed
points same hat as the witch think very
carefully if you ever have given a
chance to Dawn the Hat of pointed points
the Hat of
Point very carefully oh de maen with the
red fiery
hair your that is I I Elizabeth oh
Elizabeth your hair is so long she got
them in chiny your hair is so short to
what is that on your head oh it's it's I
don't know yet sometimes it makes weird
noises but I forgot your is so pointy
what's your name yes and your hair is
very pretty my name it's green
Roosevelt Jun I I
think C J
you I was just being you can call me
Junior for sure no don't worry about it
I'm an ambivalent extra with a
four-legged star sign so I'm okay for
I'm just going with the full you know
see I see so what Guild are you part of
o i part of the Scarlet wand such as
your scarlet hair you would right
in oh yes I was also surprised I like
your hands a lot I have a family member
who is part of the uh the Scarlet wand
oh they spoke to me yes really said they
were my my father's
cousin Rel R Pops I see how you don't
have
thisen did I oh gosh did I unlock a
painful
memory I tried I tried getting the hat
but I failed
somewhere else but I'll get it again I
think I'll I'll take part in this
dungeon and then I'll try getting money
and buying another chance for a hat
pleas don't will you wish me good luck
on my quest Quest thank you fair break
you break have you break a leg
uh ma who up I
can do I I thought I could do that
already it's okay it's it's a nice horse
under water
okay it's a nice it's a
nice what is your name again my name is
cilia im
a long as it's in
my pleasure to meet you are you also
going into this dungeon yeah I think so
if we if I reach this part with my horse
yes let's all journey together to the
dungeon this way
neat this way this way or is it this way
it's this
way oh do you think it's in the
water I thought it was in the water I
think it's that gray point do you see
that I think it's
[Music]
here I can
swim oh her meat oh sorry didn't know
they were cooking I don't mind waiting
for them
cook swi twen oh
twen this sounds oddly
familiar is it not here oh no it isn't
I'm wrong oh it is here no it is here
look at that line do you see that line
maybe that's a bridge no no
no oh no it's just a never mind okay
[Music]
fine I think it is
here oh you are here hello
yeah maybe something here but nothing
happened I try again I think we have to
swim
out but
my my my my joints do you think this is
salt or seaw water my joints are very
very sensitive to sea water salt water
oh oh I didn't think of that
um okay you have any could I like grease
you up in a your joints I could if you
if you could oh I was called hello if
you could arrive
one called
me um yeah
hello temp we're both trying to get to
the Ocean Temple dungeon we don't really
know we are in like a little island but
we are on our way there so do not fear
we are going to be there soon where are
you but where am I I'm not with you
where are you maybe I don't know I'm at
the coast I'm scared are you with the
fire where you tried making
meat yeah should we come back to you
making horse meat okay we come we're
coming back yeah she was can't believe
she killed her horse okay we'll be there
in a second M you killed your horse no
no um yeah let's go
here um but yeah no you can't we'll be
there in a second
M okay uh you can't you can't grease me
up but if I I have a request if I turn
off at any point would you mind
rewinding me please of course thank you
okay then we're good I think okay let's
go find M but you you run on batteries
or no no no you are your crank power yes
not freeing up I run on crank power yeah
it's all automated I'm a
machine so sometimes um I can crank my
wind up key
myself but um sometimes I forget and
then if I run out of it's kind of like I
go into a
Kuma so a I see so if there's any
malfunctions like salt water then
sometimes I need
Aid so I I'm scar you you want me to
what if I can't revive you am I supposed
to be hear what
what it's okay I think I believe in you
yes it's okay M I don't know how to hang
up we we're almost
there here I'll hang up we have to crank
that soldja boy I'm that
that'll don't crack this m was like am I
supposed to hear this right
now I was hearing some things oh I just
I I you answer the phone you go no you
can't grease me up yeah you can't grease
me up I can't grease you no you don't
need to grease me up okay do you have
your meat are you ready for a journey I
have yeah oh I have a meat too okay
let's see I think it's just right here
if we follow those lamps maybe that wait
let's make a
boat Bo a boat that would be safer for
me personally oh you're
right
true I made a boat can I swim I'll swim
behind you guys I don't know how to make
how do you make a boat how do you make a
boat do you want to make your own or do
you want to sit in mine like a passenger
princess only two oh but only two people
can sit in one boat good I said she
wants to swim princess oh you want to
you want to okay be past your princess
okay what if it's at the bottom of the
ocean oh then we'll have to jump off the
boat we go for a dive we'll make it
really quick so the water doesn't have
time to S I'll cover your ears so that
the yeah the water doesn't go into your
brain yeah that's nice rested aaton
brain oh my boat on land okay I want
tole this
way give me Chipotle I want Chipotle
Chipotle I've never had cot how does it
taste
like tastes like salt
salt in a good way like
yeah the the spice tastes like salt yeah
it's Sal okay let's look at the map
good okay we're going the right way I
want Dunkin
Donuts Fe your passenger Princess uh
okay I'll get you D we can get you
Starbucks is that something you like
isn't that a thing I'll settle you'll
settle ding Donuts what's your favorite
donut I can give you plane plain and uh
that's perfect yeah that's good
yes donut I think we're going the right
way SCA still behind us can you look
back I cannot hear her I feel like she
would also be contributing to this donut
conversation could she hear us let me
see uh-oh okay let's be in a party call
so we all oh there she is
there she is there she is wow okay swim
this
way this
way they look like a
ship with the with a cone yeah with the
hat my gosh I can't remember my but
there's like a wall around it oh maybe
we have to dive okay let's try yeah yeah
okay how do we get out of the boat an
island over there is that is that oh
there's
[Music]
M I think we have to follow the light
down oh where guide us creature of the
ocean
please this way what this way w we this
way
okay how do you swim fast in Minecraft I
don't
remember I control like up down maybe oh
control it's control yeah for me think
control and space we can
up that's how you fly okay I'm going to
do a group call now so that we always
can hear each
other please pick up fair
maidens water breathing yeah they're not
picking up it's
over ooh
that's so
cool
shiny that's so cool I don't think I
have the right
pickax uh now
what ominous
here here ooh ooh
oh M can you accept my call so we can
have a group call so we can always hear
each other I I didn't get an invitation
oh dang it so I think you just go into
your own phone call and then you press
on group call on the right
side oh now we're in a group call GAA
would you want to also join the group
call so we can hear each other when
we're like a little bit
separated oh yeah yeah yeah how do how
do I uh so you click with the phone and
then you press on group
[Music]
call this is falling an awfully lot yay
thank
you very nice thank you
nice it looks really cool that was
really cool like the wall of water and
then we go into nonwater I think that's
very coolly done it's like add lamp test
why that word that does it mean
something
to me and my
brain
thees before we ready I just want to get
some water one
sec okay I have water I do have water I
have a lot of water there's lots of
water here how much water can you drink
at once can you chug drinks like water
and I haven't tried but I think it's
like 14 like red plastic cups of water
is like Max you can drink get poisoning
or something you can
drown you have water poisoning uh-oh
isn't it drowning like above water
drowning my
dry Dr dry dry drowning is a another
yeah it's like if you drown in a puddle
sort of thing no no no that's not what
that is dry drowning is like you get too
much nose yeah yeah yeah you get too
much water like up your nose or in your
mouth and it goes into your lungs and
then you die like after swimming in the
pool yeah brutal dry
drowning scary slurp slurp slurp slurp
slurp okay let's
up I'm
ready go wait I'm not I'm ready ready
ready wait you're not ready oh you're
ready okay ready yeah ready okay let's
go in okay Enter
dungeon oops did it work did it work did
it it work
oh
my Atlantis oh a pre- raade strategy
meeting moment what's your special
attack it's the Winds of
civilization
the DPS DPS DPS DPS and tanks
DPS and wa T good tank I believe I am
tank she has she has CC she has Crown
control not me uh CR control do what
does yours do mine is like a point I
don't actually know it goes like a point
automation attack she has a point I have
a point yeah guys look at my weapon it's
a it's a to wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait there can be multiple
points
made yeah because I'm also part of the
skullet wand so it's
fate this this world is too complex for
me
the noise is really deep it really is I
fell oh my
goodness look at this
thish once existing
civilization it's very Mossy I don't
remember that oh wait there's a book
here
oh in ages long past there was a land of
Untold prosperity it's Tech ology and
culture stood at the Pinnacle of
civilization civilization then I mean
who catastrophe struck and what had
taken a thousand years to build was
erased in a single night oh
no oh no for me it's still
rendering wow how did that happen it
start it's still rendering it is for me
too it's loading how did it happen it
looks nice it all oh my goodness are
those aircrafts or dolphins I think the
aircraft I think that makes the most
sense with the theme it's not air it's a
boing 747 I
think it's it's like a beluga plane you
know oh are these natural
enemies no oh yeah Dolphins wouldn't
dolphins be a shark's enemy are they an
enemy you would never put Dolphins at
the center of Atlantis that would be
highly offensive oh wait wait wait you
right
the the the fin is this way not the
other way no I think it's a boing
747 it might be shark PL it's a
Dreamliner I see I see oh my goodness is
this one a
hammerhead or no I think he's just shap
is this just ugly hey don't sick don't
call the plane like
that he not a plane
he's he's a perfectly normal shark wa
but rle me this if you hold on to the
fin of a shark back and it swims and
then it jumps out of the water and it
goes like isn't that technically flying
and isn't that technically a
plane don't you think I have a I don't
think it's flying I feel like it's
exertion and then immediately falling so
are you saying if you're on an airplane
and it crashes you it's not it's not
flying it is if it is going going down
it is not flying okay good point well
cuz that's why there's flying fish
flying fish can suspend themselves in
the air that's what gives them the title
of flying fish versus any other fish
that will breach
to uh eat something for example I mean
yeah that makes sense I see okay maybe
they are not
airplanes we we will need further
Evidence what's this lots of good points
here yeah lots of good points made today
what that what is it a puzzle um Arrow
key Arrow these look like baby blocks
and I'm not sure if I should be offended
you hey wa nice job oh the Rings the
Rings oh the
Rings they're baby blocks who built this
fre oh oh we have to like oh okay but
what are we doing what which way doesn't
I think it has to go to the middle so
you have to keep going you guys can do
it
too what can I do it I want to do it you
do it is that it we have to we have to
make a towel I think green bottom yellow
and wait that's suck our colors kind of
not at all never mind stack them
[Music]
opposite and I don't
I think it has to be so we have to get
one green
bottom how do you move it though yeah
how do you move the one from the middle
away that doesn't make any sense to me
it won't let you stack them the opposite
way it has to be the big one on big
bottom oh only one way to
go maybe there's another button
somewhere maybe there's another one a
secret button a secret secret button no
wait wait wait wait wait wait no never
mind yes yes wait I got it I think she's
got
it can this one go back oh
oh
oh goes there and this one goes
there and then you pass this one all the
way yay
you did it thank
you thank you for the brain power
civilization really has a point I
remembered I remembered how it how the
stack
oh Memories the memories the
memories I guess this is some type of
Lev that do is it just for is it just
for show ow I think it probably opened
the way
oh fly just the airplanes woohoo nice
just like an
airplane that
one the
entire audience clapped all the
passengers clapped when I landed have
you ever been on an airplane where the
passengers have
clapped yes
really oh yeah I always thought that was
like a oh okay that kind of makes sense
okay um please reach for us
SCA with the land sunk to the depths of
the ocean one might think this was the
end yet where one people had been wiped
out another took its place and lived a
new happy and peaceful
life ah this place is so
boring perhaps even a bit too peaceful
I'm getting out of here you'll see day
after day the little girl planned her
Great Escape cute little
little
girl
escape she really said get me out of
this town this place is
[Music]
boring I'm
remembering oh time trial no parkour
parkour parkour um one of the one of the
laws of the scallet wand is that every
time you do Park you have to scream
parkour oh my gosh this I I was doing
that yesterday it's like parkour meant
to be it was meant to me to meant to do
this dungeon this looks so cool to
be oh do you think this is the reset
maybe is this a dummy lever what does it
do maybe it's like resets it if we
fail Okay who wants to go
first wait but there's a thing that
might hurt okay wait no no no it's a
blue lever that turns off something over
there oh really they're color
coordinated how did you do that oh oh
then the yellow one is here oh okay wait
how did you do that what okay I right
clicked
it ah oh you can't have your item
equipped okay o yellow is open can I put
this back yellow's open right it is I
thought it was just a glitch for me
uh purple maybe it's purple this
one that's green or do you think that's
the reset oh wait wait that might be
green over there no what oh yeah oh oh
uhoh wait a minute okay so so we have to
split up
probably no I
see if you you see if you go over there
the green ones oh wait but there's no
wait can you turn the lever back because
I think I removed the blue I might have
done that well I might have removed the
blue oh dear okay I think oh but this is
now where do you see the purple
somewhere do you see over there oh all
the way there
oh how did you get over there it up cuz
I ruined the
blue can we okay I think no no wait M do
you stay
here you stay
there uh
no where GA is like in in her
Direction I press this button and then
the yellow floor should come back if I
do
[Music]
this now you can go to her or she can
come back no you should go to her mhm
are you able to undo the blue one
because I think that I didn't I make
this blue disappear I don't think so I
think that was just reset I can make the
blue disappear so I will turn on the red
now
and then
[Laughter]
no wait are
you okay okay okay the blue is on now
yeah so I can switch the
green so someone can go through
[Music]
there uh you should keep the GRE yeah
okay now I can turn on the red and so
gaura can go to the purle purple no to
the blue now you at the blue should I go
to the yellow do this yellow one um uh
let me see no I think no no no no no
just yeah do the purple no now go there
can I go through yeah I'm going to kill
kill myself please don't kill me wait I
I'm scared I don't want what happen to
girl happen me
yeah okay I'm on my way back one sec
please what about what about the pink
one over there oh I guess it's set up oh
I see I see then that there's three
doors oh that didn't work is it that one
if we get to the check if one person
gets to the checkpoint and everyone
kills themselves we could also just yeah
that's true we could do that if
somebody's at the start they could yink
the BL uh I can do the blue one yeah
I'll do it yeah it's like blue yellow
please don't stand on anything I'm
activating it did it work okay yeah
H is that it think so I touch touch
touch wait there's no checkpoint to
touch yes here okay okay uh it was nice
serving you can
thanks hello did it work yeah I'm here
I'm here with
you wo wow so smart marked Geniuses of
the Scarlet wand very
impressive and Junior and this reminds
me of did you guys watch that
show where legend of the Hidden
Temple is that is that the one that was
in neweon is that that is that that one
yeah I remember that is it like a
reality show or like the
faces yeah it's it was a yeah it was a
reality show where kids would
essentially do exactly what we're doing
right now and then wi really lame prizes
like and roller blades
yes hey that's
something oh imagine SP games but they
don't die and they're all kids tuna
sponsored by Sun and then they fight and
then they are gets really hungry and it
was called The Hunger
Games yeah they grew up in this they
became the hunger gam they became the
cast of The Hunger
Games in season 2 episode 4 Jennifer
Lawrence took part in the temple show I
saw her she was on the silver monkeys
team purple monkeys are are you guys
messing with me or did she really no she
was there you're messing with meia says
that it sounds like it's true so I know
it's not wait Google here I need to
switch out of deep l i mean what what
what's deep L what Jennifer laen deep
under the ocean
help can I blast through this lore real
quick yes pleas oh my gosh she is she is
good at
lying what
is ooh Challenger
approaches there was no nice way to put
it the girl was sick of the underwater
Kingdom and she tried constantly to
leave it behind no they got me
again yet with the guard being ever
watchful this was anything but easy
she'd probably been caught by 100 time
100 times by now oh wow even so giving
up was the last thing on her mind each
failure instead served as inspiration
for a new attempt am I just going about
this the wrong way yeah I know what I'll
do next and so another day of planning
begin your plan I mean this person is a
planner that young girl is
little girl little girl little girl girl
is a a planner I respect a plan honestly
sometimes you got to
plan what all this look at this this is
another
puzzle it mous it looks like you got to
do stuff over there to unlock stuff here
and then there's treasure over
here what's going on oh that's so cool
what is this so I think we have to make
the guy go here the the the the guy that
stands here in this little trap if we
press this button he follows the arrows
that's so
cool wait that is actually so cool so
now we have to make it so thaty mhm
where do we want him to go do we want
him to die in here uh we want him to go
in here I assume yeah but it's is he
going to die if he does no he probably
activates this that it opens and we can
activate it so it opens something else
oh okay okay okay can we interact with
them oh okay yeah what do you think
happens when he goes on the gold do you
think that's a
wall what if it try yeah should we try
yeah test round test round send him go
forth
Warrior oh oh has to light them up he's
stuck okay
so to light them up most likely you
can't have him go wait no he's going
over it multiple times and it doesn't
turn off
okay oh but this one we oh but you can't
do you can't do all of them oh no no
it's just because he's out right now how
do okay let's kill him he's an Atlantean
guard okay so we have to do it in
advance so he touches all the gold
ones my brain hurts I understand now so
should he go
which way you should go maybe this
way this
way here it goes like this and then and
here did I go through
here I can't remember what I just did
and then he goes like
this through the
gold oh this way oh but I think what
about this way like
here
here wait no no no what I do what did I
do hold on hold on no you're right
you're right and then he goes to the
right here yeah and then he goes here
yeah he goes through this one and then
he goes here and he goes here and then I
think he goes here then there yeah and
then you go there
and then here okay yeah send him send
him wait which but wa I don't know which
one s the one but the right one the
right one right correct the correct
one
[Music]
okay that's so cute
wait but
[Music]
still okay it opened this but there's
nothing in there maybe it opened it on
the other it's a it's a l like the floor
is a oh it's a it's a a
button is it oh oh wait does someone
have to stand on it or something no I
think it opened
this oh did
it no it didn't there's a chest
yeah can someone stand on the pressure
plate yeah I'll do it but I think we can
just send another guy and make him go
this way
instead I think you have to stand on a
pressure plate then I stand on this one
and somebody gets the treasure maybe
okay I'll stand on it let me see let me
know what what happens
okay oh are you standing on it I'm
standing on it nothing happened okay let
me try sending him again there's numbers
here oh numbers
you see this mov I think I'll try in the
first dungeon you remember this was like
you have to fill the thing
up
oh is it that again I think so cuz the
lights just went
out what's your number we need to hit it
five times to open the door 1 2 3 4 5 oh
did I mess up should I not have done
that blue two green we're missing
two let's see what numbers are you see I
saw it light up I didn't see the the
blocks are the numbers we have to have
all of them light up for that door to
open so 1 2 3 4
5 for now none of them are one
two there should be I messed up oh wait
is there's an arrow here maybe there's
something up here
too did it turn a light on okay turn two
there oh there's something up here ah
I think it's is it a maze what is
this oh it's another pressure it's
another plate pressure there but oh kind
of am is this the
water it's a water elevator these
no is it is it time
H okay so water comes out here so we
probably still have to do something here
where you guys were uhhuh so we
definitely did the first one
correct I think we have to activate this
what is this here let me see were you
able to do anything when you pressed
anything here I I think it's the the
thing over there is what made these
three light up can somebody come stand
on this so I can go up the waterfall
okay I'll stand on it I'm coming you
[Music]
please thank you
[Laughter]
what's up there you want go do you want
to try to I want a these yeah please
wait for all party members before
proceeding it's a door but oh is this
the last thing you have to do oh maybe
it's the last
thing now we can see what's up
there wait do we just have to make him
go in a
circle if he goes through the the dots
twice
oh the little guard man oh is that it I
feel like maybe we can make him walk
here and then we can make him stand on
the
platform wait we want him to go in a do
you want him to go in a circle can I can
I try making him go through it just to
see if it works at
all okay okay I an
idle oh actually no I'll hold it I'll
hold it I'll hold I'll hold
off um just let's see if this if he can
stand on it at
[Music]
all there's no way
what and now he stands on it now we all
can go up no wait but what about what
about this I think that is a treasure
there might be something extra but I
don't really know what kind of program
are you running here oh my head is
spinning I think I don't know how though
because like here is an arrow as well
but that Arrow automatically goes up
there so I don't know like I don't think
we can go in here right
ow no no we can't so can we stand in his
way so you can't oh should we try that
can we not switch this when
it's oh can you tell me what happens
when what happens when I stand on this
does anything happen
anywhere no oh wait do it again okay I'm
not standing on it oh never mind never
mind and now I am standing on
it no there's nothing does the pressure
point turn the arrow somebody asked yeah
can you wait pressure If you reset it
can these be
changed okay let me try like if we turn
them off yeah I'll
try it's reset can you change it m uh no
you can't okay well so there's L
lanterns here right here and when we
turned all three golden squares this
opened up and then on the other side
there's let's try what you said where we
like Loop it so he walks over the gold
more than
once make him go in a big circle
yeah he is in a loop oh no that didn't
work because earlier we tried making him
go over it and he kept walking over it
but nothing happened oh wait oh this
can't happen
wait no no wait
[Music]
what okay let me try standing on this
one more time what happens
oh oh ga can you check if the one that's
the Pink Arrow is now editable the one
that is like in the
middle it is not
oh we need to find more lights
yeah oh what about that
one what about this one
here well that's just a that's just a
[Music]
checkpoint I'll do some investigating
outside the
box split
up I'm seeing something
shiny
shiny oh there's a golden wall
entrance oh oh I think that's just for
the the backing of the treasure like ooh
gold oh uh girls what if we um reset we
make him turn on all the
lights yeah and then we stand on the no
I just don't know what it what happened
when we stood on the pressure plate you
know don't know what that did which one
on this this one cuz I feel like this
one opened up this
door don't get it
the pleasure pleasure plates have to do
something yeah I don't know what do they
do should we try this again let's just
see what happens exactly okay so let's
make him go through all golden ones so
he goes here wait did I m I I feel like
I edited it but I can't remember what I
did you guys fix it oh it's
okay um so he goes like this and then he
goes up here and like this and then like
this and then like this and then here
and then here and
then how many plates are there wasn't it
first he first goes through here like
this
way should I edit it goes this way then
he goes here then he goes here sorry for
making fun of the baby block game I want
to bring it back
[Music]
now and then okay let's try way wait
wait wait wait I'm sorry I changed
something I shouldn't have I Chang I
shouldn't have he he he goes this way
yeah can I press oh my gosh wait I can't
count okay okay yes okay yes the thing
is like we've already figured it out
we're trying to go for the extra
treasure right yeah we want the treasure
not everybody can get oh yeah you're
right yeah wait it's just for the
treasure oh this isn't going to work
he's in a loop I messed it up I messed
it up I messed it what I
do you think if we go through the
doorway it'll bring us to the next room
or is it in here I think so I think this
one is just a treasure so
let's
uh okay so I think it's like this so he
goes like this this this this this this
there's a button back here
one here and here press all the plates
at once this one I'm thinking but we
can't get to this one here up w
there and then there I touched the
shiny I'm okay are you
okay
yep okay if we can't make it we we just
keep going it's
fine we can role play getting the
treasure
yeah oh
no they hav't stand there wait did I do
that why didn't did I do this why is he
oh do we want him to Loop do we intend
for this to happen
um it only lights up one at a time okay
so it lights up three it's only three
um and send him in
here uh could I could you stand on that
platform for a second in the middle one
this one yeah just let me see if
anything
happens we have to make him stand in the
one next to me yeah but nothing happens
when you stand on it so I don't I know
if that's really it you
know yeah and when we made him stand in
this one all it did was open up this
[Music]
one well we can try
okay let me see somebody save him he's
in a l I killed him I killed him he's
fine okay so let's do this so it goes up
here want have we got have we tried
getting him to go in here in the middle
you send him in this one somebody stands
there he stands there does that make
sense does that make
sense um do you want him to go in the
which one in the side I don't know I
guess this there's no point because some
cuz somebody could just stand there yeah
okay let's make him go in the right in
the right
one he has he's like special in some
way my brain oh my god oh wait but if he
goes
okay so he goes he starts here he goes
here and then he goes here and then he
goes
here and then you go is he this one and
then this one and then this one and then
this one and then this one this one this
one okay I don't remember uh he has we
have not made him stand on the middle
but we have made him stand on the right
and when we made him stand on the right
the middle door opened
up but we can try it again the middle
yeah but do we oh wait but he's going to
Loop now didn't we want him to go into
the
middle oh is he going to loop again oh
yeah yeah yeah he's going to
Loop
okay sh
him everyone's
waiting okay let's see
this oh like
that wait wait
okay that was something we needed to do
it
did but nothing L up how come you didn't
how come you didn't complete the
thing wait wait undo undo oh does it
completely reset everything is that what
it does wait no it doesn't completely
reset it because otherwise the door CL
I'm stupid do that I we have to make him
he has to light up everything
okaying okay let's try that because like
I'm stupid I get it but he can't go this
way now if we want him to go through
here it can't be the way that I add
it so has to be here turn
here okay up here up here and then and
here wait am I okay to change this I
don't hold on wait what I think it
completely resets everything wait can I
do
[Music]
thing hold on you can't it we want him
to go through here I don't see how we
can go to the middle and also you know
what I mean also do the
golden unless we find a different
way go here go try
something how come how come if we go
here it doesn't do the ding but if he
does it it does the ding yeah it's
messed up he has
favoritism where is cooking hold on with
that okay
[Music]
okay
dinging ding
[Music]
ding
no oh wait wait it was
almost uh just reset it and then move
this
one I think you got it
[Music]
wait no
wait I legitimately don't
see I don't I don't see how he can go
through everything oh wait wait like
this okay do it again wait go through
everything and go into here to the
middle
oh he has to do all of them p p p p p I
don't think he can he's not going to get
that one though oh he's not going to get
that one
wait see it does the ding if he goes in
there but what is the ding doing it's
not lighting it
up I'm fireing in all cylinders and
nothing's happening what if we um um
light wait should we try working
backwards so this one has to be like
this
uh and this one can go like this this
one can go like this I don't think he's
supposed to go to the
middle but to the very middle I don't
think he's supposed to yeah if he goes
to the very middle then we can we could
just keep going we can't we can't get
all of them if he goes to oh that middle
If he if we do that middle then yeah we
can keep going we just won't get
treasure we won't be
cool what I want you want the treasure I
want the treasure okay okay let's use
our brain power okay so we want him to
go here in the middle so he starts uh in
the middle this has to happen this has
to go here um and then he goes like this
like this like this like this like this
was good this was all perfect the only
problem is I don't know how he can go
here if wait which way do you do you
want him to go into this one or do you
want him to go where you no no no the
the one that does you want him to go in
the middle still yeah okay but he also
should touch all the golden
ones oh I think it works like this no no
no I mean Chad says it's possible but I
don't I don't see how it's possible
because I'm to hit all of them and also
go into the middle
yeah yeah cuz you can't do this I don't
think it's it's I I think it's actually
impossible I think this is the wrong you
cannot change it while it's moving no I
yeah
um just does the ding thing for him cuz
he's special so he's supposed to go into
here and somebody goes into here and we
just have to figure out what it is that
both of us going into there
activates I hope it's not a thing where
you need more than three people no no
they said it's everything's doable with
just one person oh with one yeah okay so
actually I don't know how the puzzle
earlier would have been possible but I
doubt they would make it like okay I'm
going to reset it so that he goes into
the far right one okay about that one
though oh wait what was it he goes this
way this is kind of easy who says this
is
easy they think it's easy cuz they don't
actually get
it are they fibbing they're fibbing uh
guys did we try standing on this
platform while he's standing on that
platform have we tried that have someone
standing at oh I don't think they did
should we try
that do you want the story at all uh the
story do you want to try yeah I'll stand
on it at the same time okay let me just
uh move him
I guess it okay I'll try standing on it
and nothing happens I'll move him so he
stands on it and gura will be our eyes
looking at the
lights I will what am I supposed to do
send him uh no just look if the light
anything happened to the
lights nothing is happening nothing's
[Music]
happening wait is no oneing
here I'll should I do you want me to
send
him I was yeah send send him yeah yeah
yeah yeah
yeah wait but the do
no there's a third pressure wait wait
wait wa he miss it we didn't miss
it wait what happened what was that he
went onto the thingy is did it not light
up hold up it did it just doesn't no it
didn't why didn't this one light up does
anyone light up when we standing on
this wait what wait what happened wait
hold
on go this way wait wait wait he's
supposed to go this way why was this one
oh hold on wait let's try let's try that
again wait what why is it change oh no I
did that okay I'm going try again no no
no no no now this
works CU now yeah I am reading this is
the
S wait something light up by thing this
are you talking about
this yeah dude yeah
dude okay we
have three still just
three what is it wait wait wait
what happens if I stand on
this okay wait don't do
anything stand there now stand on the
middle one but mum is already standing
on a middle one the one
outside what one
outside feel like I my chat is
gaslighting
me I saw people in my chat that didn't
realize like
never
mind I think they thought we were just
trying to get the three of them to light
up but didn't realize we that was like
the first thing we
did wait what if
you the one that at the color B no the
one at the color just opens up this
first door I think I'm going to stand on
it anyways let's see you didn't mean
this one nothing
happens this is just for this
door I do the previous puzzle I don't
wait does it
have anything to do with this
one no it no it doesn't it can go when
you figure out this
puzzle he's definitely supposed to go
well I don't is he supposed to go he
must go
here but no this is just if you don't
want
that where is it is it even
that I don't
[Music]
know call wasn't this hard what the heck
man wait I thought people say other
members already cleared it no no that
would be too
complicated guys unless it's not guys
there's arrows in the Maze too we have
to make him go all the way around
here shut up
oh
stop I even went oh it's am but then I
was like oh maybe looks cool oh can you
reset can someone reset the thing the
guy please wait where do you
see can someone uh it didn't even give
us any hint that it would include the
previous puzzle though doesn't walking
through a door usually signify that you
know that puzzle is
over think so it's from out here yeah
okay okay okay we got this guys we got
this okay um so we make him
go here
we have to maybe maybe but how does he
okay so we make him go here
instead right is is he is he lined up so
he would actually walk here no he isn't
okay wait go where go where here where
could I standing so he goes this way he
goes this way you want him to go out
there my go but he still has to go
through the all the colors doesn't he
okay so he goes like this I can't think
I need to go to an okay okay it's okay I
can't think like this go go oh gosh
every sudden it wouldn't take an hour
it's okay okay I thought it
wouldn't it was too difficult it was cuz
you you guys have fun yesterday oh are
you are you going to go to wait sorry
Mastermind are you going to goog go or
you going to just take a breakmer oh no
I'm going to just put an is down okay do
you want us to wait for you no don't
feel free to consider thinking what the
solution could be oh okay we will ponder
G let's let's try going this way and try
if we can fix
it make this man walk through this hole
so we can get that damn
boxred like here puzle man puzzle man
walks I was wondering what these little
doors were
for and then he walks through and he
hits another light but he can hit the
light that's fine and then we going no
we want him to hit this one
oh that's what you mean oh yeah okay
okay yeah and then and then he goes here
I'm going to go here to see so once he's
okay I'll activate the
green hold on okay are you
safe I am
safe okay so he goes over
there no we have to get past the yellow
Bridge we have to turn turn the the
red oh this is
complicated okay um yeah can you
go oh oh can you activate the blue one
for
me and then I hit the blue again oh the
green right uh I think the yellow one
so you can go through are you safe so
you can go through I'm fine okay and now
go through the yellow one and then
activate the blue one there the blue
yellow one blue yellow okay so now he
will go here so we're going to have to
do that while he's walking I
think oh my God shall we just try let's
just try okay I think you should handle
these colors on that side and I'll call
I'll carry the handle the colors in the
beginning
okay uh I think I remember yes okay so
he's going to come in here he's going to
walk over here and we're going to use
yellow first where is Yellow can you
reach yellow where oh it's there where
is Yellow oh I can reach okay uh don't
do it
yet okay or or actually can you do it
once just so I see what
happens okay yeah okay okay okay that's
fine and then hit it again and then he
goes through ah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I think this is good isn't it yeah I
think so okay I'll press to go this way
I think this will work I will press the
button and I will walk with
him press the button please stand do it
close to the
colors he can pass through lasers yeah
he's very
strong okay I'm pressing he's walking
but he's first he's walking over the
first three golds
ooh he's walking he's walking he's
walking okay now he's going to come to
the
[Music]
Maze and then he's going to he's going
to go through the M oh my goodness okay
he's going to be where you
are oh and then he's going to go this
way yeah I think this is it no oh my
goodness that must be it I don't think
we have to do anything let me see if it
lit up
the yep yep that's it here just has to
light up one
more
s it worked it worked it worked wait a
minute you can come to a
SC I'm here oh you're already there so
fast
wait box it's lit up but
y
y scet one the B brains bigger than the
hats impressive for you it's what is it
my mix tape oh no it's for all us we all
get one
right we all get one it's reflex o wait
how do we use this is it movie
time no not yet not yet we have to go
through the middle okay oh now we have
to right that's at the end one more face
can you s it for us if you want to you
don't have
to just like a line do I remember how it
goes um oh do I
remember oh she has
Amnesia I have amnesia I remember so now
we want him to stand on the thingy right
because we all have to get up there yeah
so just turn that one I just send him
I'm sending am I is it
ready uh is it I think
so yeah it's ready is
it as long as he comes this way yeah I
think he's
coming I cannot believe that's what that
was no wonder we couldn't
I no I wouldn't have either I would have
assumed like why would it be stuff from
the previous
level but that door that or that opening
that AR shape iect for him I estimated
how much credit they're giving us I
would I I thought like there's no way
they would do something like from the
level
before no cuz I I'm always like it can't
it's not as complicated as I think I'm
like looking stupid cuz it's so it's
probably so easy but I'm making it so
complicated and it's making me look so
dupid no I mean to be fair it was a bit
complicated was was it it could be your
powers I think it is your power
revolation has I didn't download it yet
I got to download it you've recovered a
portion of your memories
stronger I remember she remembers um
okay should
we wait for mum oh so she's ready oh you
all want to play it at the same time
yeah yeah okay I'm downloading it
sorry that's
okay second
second puzzle it wasn't even that oh
when you think about it it wasn't even
that hard if we oh like what you know
what to do it's not hard but yeah the
puzzle itself isn't hard but using your
being like I guess we're so used to
playing video games this felt more like
a real puzzle compared to like a video
game puzzle you know
yeah there were no giant arrows pointing
Us in the right direction no ingame Maps
so I think it makes sense eyes just just
an AR Arch thingy perfectly sized for
him I guess was wondering what the mini
doors were yeah I didn't even register
it to be honest uh can I point something
out though uh again no stains just
saying the kingdom that's fighting the
stains and trying to make us destroy all
of these dungeons I'm telling they're in
the
walls they in the walls they wear the
golden Stepping Stones yeah of course
okay I'm ready if you guys are ready I
am a I am
ready I got to turn my music off okay
I'm ready everyone ready was ready for a
good
scene want to countdown yes please
you want me yeah you you come down you
no you first no you wait no I feel like
G should do it yeah that's good
okay uh a three a two a 1
[Music]
go this
stinks I'm out of here
yeah you can do that what the heck what
the what the
heck yep every time King's force field
is just too
strong Ah that's when I had an
idea I may not be able to break through
but I bet that Geyer's old could do it
bre breaking dimensions and then I'll be
free or so I don't
uhhuh
[Music]
wow I you so
fun let's see what this thing can
do wait does that
mean did you destroy wait did you
destroy l oh no
finally an entire civilization My Story
begins
[Music]
here oh my
gosh why did I think you were like the
queen of Atlantis you were just a little
kid that
stole that just stole the king's Trident
he wasn't using it anyway I thought you
were like royalty or something do do you
think that
Comm no that's not true didn't you see I
was I was I was in charge of multiple
different events I had to sit Banquets
and and organize paperwork and and Royal
meetings were you a
secretary no I'm I'm I'm just a I was a
baby I was a I I I didn't steal anything
wait so I could asked but I did you
borrowed just borrowed so you stealing
their their protection Weapon made it so
that everything broke
afterwards no I that's I don't think
that's what happened they didn't have
anything to protect themselves and you
made it really easy for the en took in
the end no they've got a force Fai
didn't you see they they safe but the ho
patched up
afterwards quick quick SA I have a
point
um you know I don't remember I wonder if
we're going to have to wait for the next
episode to uncover the rest of the
mystery oh she has a point good point
good point we have a point all three of
us have a
point
yeah that was fun I did I I my brain
hurts home it was was nice to visit home
oh that was lovely a little brain fry
but oh well and not at how simple it
ended up
being it's it's
complicated it's it's the colors it's
the type of thing that when you see it
you see it but when you don't see it
you're very
confused yes exactly I think it's okay
when you're in the thick of it yeah then
it's kind of confusing it all falls on
your shoulders where are we now oh we're
back at this place okay yeah we we want
to leave do we have to swim back out I
think
so yeah you want to go to the tavern
once we go to the tavern I'm going to
eat some mutton and then I'm going
to using a horse just to get to there
what do you mean time is
money time is
okay wait give me give me off the XP in
the world of RP
G oh you guys can hear me
R back here get hooking back
here I'm just reflecting on
memories just made reflect just like the
the present we found
a boat oh there's so many boats I don't
think we're the only ones in that
dungeon we weren't the only ones that
thought of boats no let's steal the
boats that's why I have the coral so you
can breath under the water can I be the
passer princess again what's the name of
the one who drives the
driver oh the I'm the captain please
call me Captain oopsie I laughed at you
for what I just did I laughed at you and
I went and did the same thing you think
these are other people's boats wait wait
actually I'm going to take this boat so
that so that they have to swim
perfect how do you use boats again oh
you right first ones oh there's no way
we were the first ones through that
now I saw people say others got through
it but did they do the extra stuff or
did they just keep
going no
clue I don't know
my gosh wait you're such a fast
swimmer first one's with the treasure
ah
yay okay I feel much better about myself
because we got we we could have finished
really early but we decided to go the
extra mile exactly we
got
collections what are we supposed to do
with it uh investigate go to the tavern
and we blast our Tunes until we get is
that what you do you can blast yeah you
can play it in thex or we can play it
here too or we could go back let's go
back let's go to the
tavern
Tavern you guys know after you work out
and then your your muscles feel like
tingly and weak mhm uhhuh that's how my
brain
feels hey i k it too hey but that means
that he
scarl doesn't that mean that like Al
brain is going to get stronger now my
name is Junior it should yeah think
further into the future I'm Junior lady
you are being ambushed oh my lady they
really love you
here my
queen okay follow the sounds of the
horses
this way we're going to go play our
Victory
music wait this the
previous the previous dungeon have a
song reward I think
so oh I did not but I didn't pick it up
I remember seeing
it wait where are you guys I lost
SC oh there are I didn't even see it if
there was one okay I think I saw
it the
is it's from
gambling where was The Tavern again it's
the gacha gacha I got it on my first
[Music]
try is
that all right let's play this bad boy
want to listen to some tunes yeah it
might be if you haven't in the dungeon
it might be a spoiler oh oh spoiler hi
Nissa hi S I think you can repeat
dungeons
it's okay I I have a party
later also have not cleared it but thank
you fair maiden of course Scarlet one
yes Scarlet one get us strong what's
this okay I'm going to mute my own
bgm wait I can't hear it oh because I
turned the we turn mus oh I
hear oh my gosh it's not a style it's
just
it let's go
I got good Sub sub wers here yeah no
it's a party God what is that beautiful
voice is this what clubing feels like
where the Str
[Music]
BL your light
[Applause]
oh that is so
pretty
okay that's enough Val you how much can
I sell this for a million dollars can we
sell it can we sell it
yeah oh never mind I was wrong I didn't
see the I didn't see U moris one I just
saw these the non-fiction and Stu again
so that's why bu buy them but you cannot
sell them W can we sell anything to be
honest don't know way we can sell stuff
shopkeeper
fauna yeah we should we should we should
ask her to come
back she's just selling lottery
[Music]
tickets n how much money do you have not
looking
895 coins do you want to do a
trade trade
would you would you like to give me 300
I can give you 64 mang gr
blocks no what I don't want M BL steal
what do you want I have 26 St slime ball
how many coins do you guys have I have
37 what how are you guys all so low
because we
gamble 132 I I haven't figured out how
to gamble we have never gambled in our
lives would remember I want I want a
cute hat like this like you guys have oh
got buy one buy one here points yes I
just buy them I just buy them no it's a
gamble you you it's not guaranteed but
you can you see that Bo surprise box oh
go
no this seems like a mistake did you buy
one yeah that's a lot of money do it
what you get what you get what you get
what did you get I I have to choose oh
oh God oh God oh God oh I got
construction supplies box
oh okay
Yay good job should we try turning our
money into more
money we should we try shall we try
before no I
haven't no I haven't it better not be
the lottery tickets no no no no no fun
do you remember the library I think do
you remember where it was was it
here it oh it was in the library oh this
is this is this is it is this
way yes I shall follow you you wish to
Triple your earnings yes I do that
sounds nice I wish to Triple mine no
quadruple mine join our party and then
you can join our party call
Nissa I'll have to leave later but I'll
now like
soon okay I'm in quick quick quick quick
quick quick quick okay where is she
where did she
go oh yeah I don't know I'm in the pit
okay okay I'm coming we're
coming okay come to the giant Yellow
spes
oh we're
[Music]
coming I was so ready to to gamble all
my money away yay yeah let's do it can
both you don't know that you could be
making all of your money back in then
some that would be nice I want to get a
cool hat too I don't remember what it is
I don't remember what the fit is what is
the pit the P not this right no no the
Pit's the other one uh it's yellow one
yeah the yellow
one the EM coin people one Fair straight
oh no I know who you are now F do you
know where the pin
is I'm going in a circle I guess I M
that's okay or Junior is is a horse
girl I
don't I I don't remember I don't
remember what you named me but my name
today is Darwin Roosevelt DiCaprio Jr
Darwin Roosevelt DiCaprio Jr oh there it
is pun was that it pun
[Music]
pun oh here it is bow bow Fair meens bow
bow okay we have arrived we are here but
M
isn't yeah she's she's
lost oh it appears that my party has
found it but I have been distracted by
your
beauty your beautiful Ramy fingers Ramy
popsicle Fingers um so let's see I must
now go bow bow should we wait for mum
really quick good bow bow good bow bow
yeah maybe bow I'm so sorry I cannot
listen to everyone at once where are you
we are calling for thou Fair Maiden
where are you what do you see color you
want a bed on I am around the
Coliseum okay Dy right around the
Coliseum try finding the white yellow
building the yellow big yellow building
around the Coliseum oh God how close the
Coliseum it's not at the Coliseum
started the first bet oh that's okay you
guys you guys do that and I'll I'll go
get her how do I choose what what's
going on done a full circle I'll come
cck stand still M I will come to you
come to me CH your
color where what do you
see I see Tre of green there youer your
in that and on the far right okay okay
oh I was not going to find this
okay yeah okay I I bet on
two hopefully this is the pit uh blue
and
red ooh wait both yeah
to you can just go for the next one
we'll we'll let them we'll let them feel
the odds out and see what they color
Cannon Cannon's firing okay oh wow
okay oh it might be over for me what
color did you go for I'm going to lose
my
mind what color did you
do I did red and blue I pick
Green Green always
wins it's uh it's in the cards
he seems like he seems like good odds
except if it's red I'm going to lose my
mind wait are you betting which one
stays green yeah oh my go oh my gosh how
much did you bet narissa just 100 wait
how do I get it okay M you can talk to
him you got it automatically you can
talk to him and then we make a bet and
you talk to him again select the color
you want to I don't decide how many
coins to SK we start firing four colored
sequences with shot after six shots only
one square will remain on that color win
winning players will receive a payout
based on the multi multiplier listed for
the color they bet on
okay
bet I'm going to
bet okay I bet okay so red is time 10
yellow okay green
I
greenen
GRE 100 on
all if if you go with all wait how do I
do this how do I do it I don't know how
Minecraft works okay so you right click
it don't ask and then do you what do you
see do you see the paper and the little
window I see I see paper there's there's
a little line and you have to type in
100 or whatever you have to be really
fast and then you just press on theit
that's that's it's over
you'll have to join next round oh okay
it's okay I'll help you it'll be fine
it's this one was the bad one anyways
them out and you take the paper take the
right wait grab from the oh I
see
green this is let's go any
color green
green color do
not believe
ooh green will win I believe in it
mhm now watch
this I'm watching watching very
closely damn it oh I would have won woo
500 coins I'm out of money oh Fair
Maiden narissa ravencraft could you lend
us some money maybe we are one become I
have to become rich join the game choose
color I'm sorry why do I but now this
time I'm going to do green I'm going to
try blue this time just blue I'm going
do okay I think I did it
green
so or should I do two should I do two
different
ones nah go all in on one I don't know
try
it I need me I'm so
poor how how did you all become
poor you're looking at ITA I probably
this the wrong way I reversed it GI took
all my money that's all right I voted on
Blue when it everyone El just lost 50
coins that's okay I did not do that the
right way that's all good that's all
good build character you if you picked
up the papers then you did it right no I
didn't know didn't wait you didn't
no oh
boy oh that's not
good oh I really I really I really I
really I really I
really what did you bet on what did
everyone bet on blue green and green no
what did I do I did green and
blue okay green CH
win come on
green if I lose this I'm doing one on
each color oh Green in the bag let's
I get I make some stuff back it's not
it's not totally over are you kidding
me no freaking
way I think if we give back our Quest we
get some
money I lost 50 I'm going to go and get
some money cuz I'm broke my go get some
money wait how much did I have before
this didn't I have I had like 500
something I think I lost I
lost what color did I just vote
on I don't
know
listen it's always
fun now now now try Mr Mr Big firing
Cannon surely I can't lose this time one
of each one on each color let's go I
can't lose now yeah you have to
win
surely I don't even remember did now
which one did I
do which one my last my last one I don't
know that's what I'm saying too I don't
remember what color I I think I yellow
or green I think you press T you should
see what you
did no it just tell me says how many
coins yeah never
mind okay
okay higher you have yes you are right
you I have been very polite to you
actually
well that was good I was just I was
testing you that was a misunderstanding
yes I wasting you
kidnapped who are you
affiliated I'm affiliated with
affiliated with the green ones cuz I'm
green the with the green ones cuz I'm
green are are you guys plotting a scam
to the world
no I'm green and what's going on is that
uh we're planting trees for the
environment you're planting trees with
other people's money I would assume I
think you might be mistaking me for
someone else that it might be
[Music]
green the queen sh Prevail I have never
gotten any money from anyone hot pink
Iris yes yes yes yes hot pink yes what
you say
I have a question is that red thing over
there are you dragging me away to scam
one second I shall boost your presence
in my mind oh okay oh okay uh uh this is
I wanted to apologize for accidentally
uh uh uh kidnapping you it was uh what
what happened was I was I read a lot of
books right when I gave my memory and a
lot of them were like uh Heroes and
stuff you know and I want want to set it
up so that you could be rescued or
rescue yourself uh so really I just
wanted to open up you know a deeper
friendship and maybe more for you uh and
it was an accident and I regret it sorry
oh there there oh it is
okay thank you I am of the empathy and I
am very empathetic oh are you an empath
I am an empath yes
oh you are a good girl I believe I I
feel I am in tune with emotions and I
feel No Malice from you yeah yeah yeah
yeah cuz yeah yeah oh wait let me say
something nice um oh uh oh I hope I hope
you have a nice
day oh wow I
also wish you upon you a blessed day yes
wonderful thank you I have a Parting
Gift oh a yes yes uh how do I do
this have some money I I'm I have zero
coins come watch the fight we're
fighting to the death in the arena oh
okay I will be right there okay okay
okay quick here I have this for
you it reminds me of you I can't give it
to you um oh can we role play I give you
a rainbow Coral luster it's rainbow
colored just like you oh it's a rainbow
okay would you like to in in
reconciliation would you like to watch
people fight to the death with me yeah
Mur let's go
woohoo
[Music]
wo I feel like we can't bond over our
shared enthusiasm for death as empath
think about it think thinking about it
it is I that was subjected to the non
consensual Touch of gums so I must fight
for my own rights oh okay then go then
go forth claim your own
destiny yes wait you are challenging me
oh wait why is your why is your weapon
glowing yellow wait I don't have a
yellow weapon I well you said you wanted
to challenge me let I think it is unfair
to use our Revelations
unfair I I think it is better a fair
game I I believe
do you P have money and yellow that is
unfair are you not of the Scarlet Guild
no I'm from Green all right who wishes
to challenge me you're from the green
Guild I joined the red team you are on
the same Guild as my it's yeah you join
a team apparently when you when you okay
answer yes to the duel how much money do
you need oh never
mind you cannot be two against
one I see hey oh was there two against
one Pearl okay I do not know yes it is
not 50 points wait okay you can't call
me Pearl I can give you some wood opal
oh thank
you my name's I appreciate itan oh what
how wonderful I thank thee no problem
for giving you're are welcome you are so
kind hband no problem I will now use
this uh which
one I will
I will now use this uh in order to bet
on the death of these Fair
people yes yes did you hear her I'm her
backup plan are you going to wait
what wait what well there's a lot of
plans what is happening my
PE oh oh I see I see I guess you are too
I just gave
some IR try to accept and it doesn't
work
the rest of
us you
would you cannot you cannot
out is pussying out what I do not know
such vulgar terms it is the scaredy
cat oh scaredy cat SC pussying out
pussying out I that to my vocab there's
something about that word that bothers
me you joined the red team what what is
it of that word that bothers you
okay okay are we ready are we ready to
duel is the queen here oh the queen yes
yes I came I came to support you D canel
the who's fighting oh yes I see you must
fight I want to okay join again join
again of course you you need to be safe
kept yes the queen must never fight
herself so I join again join again
oh you may not f yourself until prod a
male a to the king time why does it have
to
beting anyway they're fighting everyone
they're
fighting death death Death F fight fight
fight
death go for her head
lady
ex both r
[Music]
revolation i want to hear their
talking oh hi hot lady oh hi how are you
doing hot l
[Applause]
[Music]
I don't know what the hell happened but
I won and that's all that matter okay
just going to see if I can gamble with
these 50
[Music]
coins I don't actually know if this
still uh there if not I will do one
gamble go all
in h i don't know where it
is I should just there it is okay
shopkeeper
no
no I'm going to win
[Music]
no
no oh oh oh it's the other building
right it's the building at the Garden
this
one we have 50 coins at the gambler's
dream it is all
possible it is all
possible okay
okay
[Music]
green
50 okay oh I'm so tired after
this we'll see how it goes we'll see how
it goes first
let's go
[Music]
green I do like it it's fun it just gets
a little bit I guess I am a little bit
tired and it gets a bit hard when
there's a lot of people for my brain but
I think it's nice that we have the
option to be like in these little group
calls or uh in the little parties or we
can just do the proximity only I think
that's
nice okay accepting bets I'm going to go
upstairs to the cannon I
think it's
[Music]
time
okay go go
go have you made
soup oh hello soup no have you made soup
no but I am gambling want soup do you
want do you have soup oh oh I'm supposed
to make nourishing soup but everything's
trying to un nourish me do you want to
do oh good
God huh um I can join you for a minute
but I am gambling right now I shall tell
you of my that's okay no I lost
right I lost gambling gambling say okay
I lost that you know no I lost it's over
I lost I don't have even
money I'm it's okay I'm about to lose my
life I think I think I need to upgrade
my armor not I believe in you I I'll
I'll send you a belief beam
okay okay and then you'll do it thank
you you can do it person I'm going to go
sleep now I will end the call and let
you gamble okay sleep well
bye-bye this item can't be us okay there
we go okay um I feel bad going without
saying
goodbye
uh hello
oh she also left
okay guess I'll just find Thea and Say
Goodbye no it's fine I don't have to say
goodbye I'll say goodbye goodbye Fair
ladies
okay
okay it's okay I think I think it's okay
not to say goodbye especially since it's
kind of hard to find each other when
when everyone's spread out it gets
difficult to know exactly where people
are but I feel a little bit bad with
just leaving well it's fine it's fine
can you guys all say it's fine don't
worry about it it's fine it's already
fine yeah it's fine it's fine I had a
lot of fun I thought the second dungeon
was very cute I thought it was really I
don't know the moment where you go from
the water into like the open field that
was really cool I think the puzzle we
would have I don't actually know since I
didn't obviously I wasn't watching the
other people's streams but I think if we
didn't go for the present we would have
made it super fast but since we went for
the
extra we win I don't
know in my heart we won and hopefully
next time I can get a hat cuz I also
want a hat I lot of fun thank you for
joining thank you for joining our U all
of us and I hope you guys keep watching
the other girls are still streaming um
and I'll see you guys all
either tomorrow on Tuesday I might take
tomorrow off I might take Tuesday off I
haven't decided yet I'll let you
know but now I will rest and try to get
a really good amount of sleep a huge
amount of sleep okay thank you thank you
thank you thank you also sorry that I
couldn't look at chat that much um I
don't think I I think for me it's a bit
hard when it's a collab or like more
people but I had a lot of fun and I I
appreciate you help doing the puzzle
okay bye-bye
green member of the college team will
now go to
bed this way good night
[Music]
I