[Music]
yes
this is
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hello
[Music]
what is the difference between play
little nightmares 2 and play enhanced
Edition
[Music]
enhance looks better RTX videos do I
have an RTX video card
what is that
I don't
I have AMD so no
so no no for me
a gradient
okay
[Music]
all right
we won't notice a difference
[Music]
oh
why is it so hot
us let me change pants I know I just
arrival let me change pens I have my my
fluffy ones on
[Music]
so hot
okay
short pants
the same ones that
is
comes with short and long pants
[Music]
how are you
um
yeah I'm trying to get into Window mode
one second
adjust the slider until the eye is
pretty why can I not do Window mode
first huh
on the excess data period you please do
not switch up my hair okay
how I'm doing I'm quite okay uh best
experience with a controller okay
PS5 control
[Music]
oh by the way um I'm back
yeah yeah
we're not talking about that huh
[Music]
you
you little chickens
we need to talk but
um I'm doing I'm gonna do
a special chatting stream
uh actually let me put that in my
calendar because I guess I didn't
I'm gonna do a special training stream
stream because we have to talk
uh how you how you um have been unloyal
to me
yeah these hoes ain't loyal
um
okay so we'll do that
um how about tomorrow
I mean even tomorrow the day after
tomorrow and we'll decide after the
stream how I feel
um but
yeah
yeah it's that's a stream because
um I want to talk about how you guys
have not been loyal to me and also I
want to talk about uh and show you guys
about your connect presence without
making a whole stream about it or so
um
all I did was swim what do you mean you
swam chickens can't swim you only float
if anything
I can explain
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
um
make excuses yeah I guess you have more
than enough time to think of excuses now
uh we'll talk about it another time now
we're gonna get to business you know
um settings
windowed thank you small please
okay what's once again oh this time I
know better because I'm not froggy Wawa
I know that 1280 x 720 is 16 to 9 and
like 1280 x 1024
yeah
but this is really tiny isn't it that's
tiny what's the next equivalent what's
uh what's um this
ah it didn't get bigger at all
how about 1 600 x 900 what about that
don't you dare chat don't you dare
ask me what's 4 times 13. I know very
well what's 4 times 15 it's just you
know in a situation like that where you
hear a timer
eat you
you two agree with me that your mind
goes blank uh sometimes or not maybe not
everybody's but you can't fully blame me
for the for the fact that you know I I I
I went a little bit blank on that one
I I I make fun of me all you want you
think this is the right time to make fun
of me
when I just threatened you
with
that Sudan stream a dangerous dangerous
Saturday stream huh
chickens
don't know they don't know who they're
up against
you already in trouble
no no you're just making yourself
getting bigger trouble that's not smart
that's not smart at all
mm-hmm so last time
last time uh one year ago we played this
game
and how did it end
s
we we went through this this place with
a lot of really hungry
um weirdos and then in the end there was
like a lady right
uh and we we were fighting the lady
foreign
I ate the lady and I became a jetty
sounds legit
I ate her
we ate I'll remember that part at all
we hate her
what you showed her yeah I remember
something with Reflections yeah yeah
I hate her and I became God
looking good well apparently not enough
of a God because the fact that there's
little nightmares too makes me think
that we are in a little bit of um
yeah situation again
[Music]
still so hot should I do full screen for
like the sake of you know vibes
probably right it's probably better
yeah okay then I make myself a bit
smaller and maybe
have a little bit of a filter
oh
oh yeah
how how about this
how about this how about this
okay okay should I be left or right left
or right left or right left all right
left or right
maybe we'll figure out where the best
placement is later but you guys I'm
gonna put you here
Ryan
story wise is a prequel
just a prequel
oh oh well that makes a lot of sense
then
um
nah I was not I didn't want to set it up
sorry okay apparently this game is like
five hours long or so um I hope we don't
spend much more time on it because I
need to read a few super chats and then
I need to cook uh yeah that's why I
started
6 p.m hoping to get it done my game lags
what do you mean my game legs we haven't
even started
what do you mean don't trust spoilers
uh-huh
I mean I have yet to receive spoilers
don't pressure yourself to finish it
well it would be awkward to like you
know end it at four hours when I have
like one hour left
um
[Music]
I had a hard time using controller last
time
did I
maybe I did
uh is a x okay a is X
what's on the menu today what I don't
know oh wait no sound here
um whoopsie
do you hear the melody do you hear the
music
it's really necessary no I wanna no
we can do it together
this won't be scary right right
now
eerie
what's going on are We swimming this is
water
oh God I'm scared already
oh I hate Halloween
ah
I'm so scared I'm so scared already
but it's pretty
uh you know I was thinking of you know
making a
a a a
paper bag like this for my head and
attach it to my head but I figured you
might want to see a little bit more than
just the holes to my eyes
off my face it would have been funny but
you probably want to see a bit more
um
so is it lagging or not it should be
fine right okay I can jump
paperback friend this is this is mummies
mommy's bag
oh I can go not only sideways can also
go to the front yeah yeah there's like I
think in the last game until there was
like a certain
like you know
oh can I go back to the TV even
oh I can oh but I can't oh
okay I can how far a break can I go I
think it ends here now
okay can I run
what is this this what is this button do
I reach out my hand
this this button
yeah it makes me this button makes me
reach out my hand a little bit this is
ducking
both both of them are ducking okay both
left buttons are ducking
yeah yeah we'll get a tutorial anyway
okay well it's really pretty actually
this game count last year right I was
surprised to see that
did it came come out on Halloween
[Music]
I I remember I knew of its existence
back then already you but
I didn't play it oh the leaves
I hear it flies is there a dead body or
something
ill yeah okay
ah of course I can't reach oh what is
that
what is that a person
no no no it came on 2021 no yeah
February February last year the first
game came out uh 2017 perhaps that that
could be
gonna get up here no
it looks like a squid somehow but I made
it down why is my screen flashing
the screen is fresh and flashing black
three times now
you know what's up with that
all three of my all three of my screens
did you see that or is it just here
graphic problem
I don't know my something's weird do I
have to make that jump
close out the title
come on big jump oh [\h__\h] a Guinea
Guinea
you need to around to jump I did it
without running I don't know how to run
can I get in there
ah there's a button to hold huh
platformer
oh
yeah okay I'm holding I'm holding
did you guys miss me
you weren't loyal to me but you guys at
least missed me didn't y'all
foreign
which which foot does it belong to
ah
it's a big shoe oh
this will hold it
oh there's many issues I think you guys
need a shoe
um
wait a second who are you again ah
and then see you Allah
oh there's a hats what's there can I
change from my my
oh oh wait we got a face reveal later or
do all of these no no no of them cover
the face I would say
plant
dude we get more of this DLC
is
Cowboy huh
can't recognize
hello
oh my God my PC just out of nowhere
resided itself
like the screens went black and we just
restarted itself
I I knew the bad flat uh the black
flashes were a sign
you sometimes my PC is really weird
what worries me
what's that mean guys what does that
mean tech people
my whole PC restarted
I need to get a GPU replaced
I'm gonna forget about that in five
seconds
overheating
hmm
power supply power supply
Supply
what's up
[Music]
how are you doing power supply ah what
do I know what do I know about this face
I need to shake the magic eight ball
a Windows update occur I don't think so
it's a serious question
if it only happens once it's okay
this again it could be many things
look it up in the event video but if you
are capable
how do I open my Event Viewer
is that in in task manager
excuse me but so when exactly could you
please go play hashtag Yu-Gi-Oh Master
duel please
uh ah
searching Windows what was it called
again
what am I searching for
event event manager
no what was it called
I gave this antagon
yeah
oh
what what am I looking at here
uh
or Windows Powershell
Windows Powershell
system
um
[Music]
event manager
uh uh stream let's go just kidding no
I'll look at this later I guess
what's what's Powershell what's
Powershell you say oh oh oh oh oh
whoa whoa
what does that mean what's with fascia
[Laughter]
oh
reliability history uh
[Music]
I don't know where that is
I don't know
huh
[Music]
oh
whoa what is this oh when I open like
administrator happenings or whatever
that's translated to
I I see
I see a lot of error ever ever ever
winning ever ever wanting warning
warning ever ever era
is this dangerous
it within the last
[Music]
um
holy [\h__\h]
that's like
oh the whole day like
whoa
any critical uh why does it say critical
I don't know where it says critical
that's fine time for a new pc oh yeah
we'll play a game now sorry
uh
it's my PC dying oh no don't die don't
die I need you
I was thinking you know NPC is kind of
the night and weird
49 90 time how about can I stream over
steam deck because I was gonna get a
steam deck can I just wouldn't be nice
if steam deck has an option to work as a
PC and like just stream through the
steam deck as if it couldn't get any
better
steam tank I should be able to look
honestly it seems like a thing that it
could do
all right open little nightmares let's
see what happens if anything like this
happens again then we're [\h__\h] yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
the good fingers I don't have a schedule
for this um week so I feel not so
pressured about following up
with you know what we're doing
coming down
um
okay I don't know anything about
computers
I don't know anything resume game oh
it's saved noise
land game lagging oh don't worry it will
fix itself wait I'm gonna have to move
the chat okay
oh where are we oh here wake up
wake up
yeah my my PC was probably just trying
to protect me from danger
foreign
well that was too easy ouch
you need to work on your Landings little
little child
hold on yeah okay I get it what is this
you
disgusting
you you
[Music]
I forgot to turn it back on where's my
mouse where's my mouse
foreign
flies
I don't I don't think you'll hear it
push can we
can we
come on
oh oh I guess I was just pushing on the
wrong side
oh now we we drag it
okay okay
when we played this last year I had a
lot of issues with like some Escape
um scenes and so on
yeah
I remember I hope we won't have so much
trouble in this one
oh
the right button prompts maybe is it
actually X though could it possibly be
really
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
aggressive way how to run oh do I need
to get up there
can I go through the the bark
through here
um
or that um rope
I feel like I am
I I should maybe not hold on to that
huh
okay
Canada not just
it looks so ah [\h__\h] probably could have
made it
but mess it up
run run run run run your little [\h__\h]
I'm so sorry
extreme neck massager ah oh I really do
need a neck massage
my shoulder hurts so bad
but as always I'm scared
ah hey
okay the perception of where I'm jumping
to
is difficult to figure out
okay one more one more where is it
exactly
here it should be here
should I run maybe I mean I think before
I did it without running
so
can you jump further if you're running
yeah
and
for safety
what did that say on the bottom why can
I not make that jump
this is where we get stuck
doesn't say
nice make it swing stronger use Al to
swing
oh yeah I'm swinging it but it doesn't
any more than this
okay this time we made it
next okay a new mechanism
catch
oh Roll and Roll and oh maybe about here
to go lower
oh it goes back up
that's perfect
oh happy birthday happy birthday
keep seeing offline here is it just me
it should be fine now refresh everybody
tell them to refresh
refresh
same what
[Music]
refresh
hey yo I can make that jump
that's actually impossible you don't the
game does not expect me to make that
jump no way
I know I'm gonna fall down
[Music]
what
there's something down there huh
maybe let me just like try to
[Music]
that's hard to notice okay
okay
I didn't even use the rope
nope I don't know
[Music]
oh little mushrooms
cute
[Music]
I don't know why you but kind of you
you're freaking me out a little Goblin
you look like you look at look like you
smuggled
a tank am I like R4 our foot takes the
salt
pick it take it
okay cool um was that good or bad
he was morbing
wait are these feet down there
well I'm standing right next to it looks
like feet oh this is someone's grave oh
wait
this little bump here is that person's
belly
it feels it feels like there's no bump
for the head though they decapitate him
going for true ending
is that something that makes me go for
the true ending
oh maybe not
I absorbed a ghost down
oh this is a secret room
oh
well I probably won't find any others
this was probably just relatively easy
to find on purpose
to go
all right then I guess the Rope is maybe
necessary huh
what can I climb
oh okay it works good job
good good job
right
now someone here watching us
I wanted a tree no
those holes
disaster must be
something
oh my shoes
verb
what's this what's that
oh that's a trap that's a trap that's a
trap that's a trap you see that if you
step in the middle
that's a trap
[Laughter]
[Music]
Seasons knows it doesn't anyway
I didn't fall for it I just wanted to
test it to show you guys what not to do
uh what about this wood
this piece of wood up there
I'm gonna go around again no no
okay
[Laughter]
did gouda ran into this I wonder
because I I know she played it like one
or two days ago
did you run oh wait can I can I like
is this is this a rope
hi what do I do
I want to hold on to it hold
uh sure I throw a shoe in there
and then it will react to the shoe oh
that's a weak mechanism though
how do I throw
before
good job
hey
[Laughter]
I love scaring games come on Gable dice
[Music]
I love it I love it I just love it so
much can you feel it
could you guess
I'll never trap oh bear traps
just like rest
oh
you think
you're right in front in front of there
[Music]
oh can I throw something
or can I go behind
no no
was there another shoe yeah see the
stick too but oh there's a weapon hold
RT to carry the weapon
what weapon
maybe Oh I thought I thought it popped
up because of something in the back no I
guess it's just
that is indeed totally a weapon first
thing I think of when I think of weapon
is uh
stick the good old snake
oh hey there's another one
I guess we better take it
come on
it's real I can look do some
no I know it I know it I know it I know
it ah
stop
oh okay
okay hey
okay so far
it's pretty fun
what if you run out of this
[Music]
uh-huh
what about right in front here
no nothing really really
oh
foreign
[Laughter]
am I supposed to jump over it and hold
on to the ladder
all right
go up little child
go to safety
um
light
oh it's a slightest very says what's
gonna happen
oh
let me fix myself a little bit
okay
it's scary scary hello
oh why I'm even here but um what are
they hunting
oh probably judging by this game so far
I guess they're hunting children
no animals they're hunting hunting
children probably or like any kind of
human
what's in there
what is that is that a child
ah okay here we go guys this is probably
where it starts to get like really
spoopy spoop
[Music]
sing what's on
um
I hate these games
[Music]
no I don't like
open
keep open keep open
oh
[Music]
what's that picture
head down to the left down down I mean
down here
[Music]
hats
oh this one huh nice it's cute
[Music]
equipped collect the hats in the pause
menu
yes okay
it's cute it's really cute
okay
so we can see my face now oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah cute hard to see but
we do have a face nobody shaved it off
yet
tat
I I am Tanuki
there's a punk stick there
look look up for face
huh
interesting face not the prettiest face
should I go should I go here first
okay so we're definitely dealing up a
hunter but the question is what do they
hunt
children
[Music]
hello
what the [\h__\h] is all that
what is that
whoa oh
[Music]
it's not even a person
but I have a feeling once we get into
that room
someone will show up from the other side
can I go in
[Music]
yeah it's definitely a trap
there was a door in the right side too I
think wasn't there
can we take this as a weapon
[Music]
you clumsy little [\h__\h] that would have
been a really useful weapon
honey
what
is this
[Music]
what did I say what I said
what did I say
[Music]
what what
um
[Music]
no I don't want to play this game I
don't want to play this camera
huh oh
[Music]
my God
foreign
[Music]
don't don't touch don't touch don't
touch touch
see I do it I know what now he's gonna
tell his creepy dad or whatever
and I'm here
are they gonna come
I'm scared
why did I
why did I what did I think that I it was
a good idea huh
just because Halloween doesn't mean I
have to play games like this
yeah I know they may have been trapped
damn but still I don't trust them I
don't trust a child
[Music]
big noises
it's it's it's it's just there to trap
me
I hate those so much
they're not real they're not real
they're not real
you're not real
then they're not if anything they're
dead
[Music]
hi
Mario
don't look quinoa
what are you doing
what the [\h__\h] are you doing I need my
help or what
oh
what
you look like me
probably me for some reason
what a friend
in the in the yellow couch yeah oh oh
think I'm stronger okay okay
sure oh
did you hear that
I'm done come
on
so much
what are we doing what are we doing
buddy
going this way
I push no are you just gonna do whatever
I start doing are you just gonna follow
him Wherever I Go
this does seem to be my companion
is there something here secret no
no
can you find us in Co-op
help please I need some help
I can't get up there oh are we pushing
it up after all I think we're pushing it
well
and push
what if my fail Escape missions and [\h__\h]
just because this little [\h__\h] is too
slow to follow me huh
at some point we have to sacrifice him
probably oh there's a key
and dead bodies huh nothing wrong with
that
it's okay it's just a game it's just a
game it's just a game nothing to be
afraid of
mmm
how do we get okay
can you help me get up there maybe
oh you know what I want to do
yeah wow okay one more
okay
interesting
there must be something here to put into
the thing so I can uh
use it
not real not real dude not real we're
not real
they're not real
good
can I take
I can't take it
why
we're not pushing hard enough I was
playing so hard
how can I pull harder oh there's like a
rumbling a pull of this stick too that's
just a camera bro
why is oh
a bag oh it's going to the left side
arm man I pulled too hard
so not real not real obviously not real
that looks like oh it's a puppet isn't
it
because that wasn't a bone it's a puppet
does this person make like puppets
as as his friends
hello yellow I'm back ow
yeah you're gonna put it in nice thank
you at least you're helpful
oh and you're even gonna do that oh
thank you
more
why are you not continuing
work harder
give them a hand what the hell I'm
pressing the button to like push button
or like pull or whatever
yeah get on the back
stinky
so stinky
[Music]
sick what's with the key now
I don't know what that's for
when are we going back
help help
um are we coming back or was there
something over there still
um
[Laughter]
I guess not
oh
okay I don't know man about this Co-op
like so how do I know when he can help
me and when not
ah yeah I didn't even notice that
because
[Music]
oh we were able to leave oh welcome to
the swamp this is he even has an
outhouse
they're fresh and they seem to have gone
inside the house
so probably not in here right
right so many traps
here
a weird noise but I don't know what that
noise is
can we push this
go to the toilet
is there a hats in there
for secret like uh like one of those
ghosts
huh ah oh thank you yeah yeah
[Music]
there is indeed
I don't know if I want that
we'll just make it more difficult for me
though
ah
what that doesn't look like he's hunting
humans specifically
okay
what's going on what's going on
I see like ripping off the skin of
things oh
oh yeah
tell me what he's doing
I am not scared I
I'm not scared
what are you doing
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
put on the ring he won't know he won't
no yeah yeah hahaha
oh
I'm suffering
dude you're kind of in the light what
are you doing why are you moving
sweaty hands
okay hi
one
hold hands
our team
I don't know what's our tea it's not a
big button
doesn't work
are we holding hands
oh we are okay
why do we need to hold hands
why
even me it's just gonna slow us down
what the [\h__\h] do you want me to do
wow Crow it's gonna tell him that we're
here
can we walk around here
lucky
am I supposed to pass him should we
maybe go the other way wouldn't that be
smarter
run through his house the other way
do I have to hold the RT forever
can I run
please
stop there is some [\h__\h] stone or
something
um okay yeah cool cool sorry bro you
didn't see me
as long as I'm in the grass you guys
can't see me even when there is the
light on me
even then
I don't know man it stopped me before am
I supposed to run straight away from him
fingers hurt
[\h__\h]
you would think you would think I'm safe
right of course not it's just beginning
of a terrible terrible terrible
it's gonna be there probably yeah come
join us
come on come on
faster if you want to survive with me
you gotta go faster
jump what
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
can I do it first so I can look how you
do it
no
you don't wanna
okay
first
oh
that doesn't work either hmm can you
throw me maybe
just eat me
and you'll
see if he does something if I stand
close to him
Maybe
and he goes first baby
okay and then what are you gonna do how
are you gonna help me with that
it's the same thing over there or
do I just hey
I've gone first what you gonna do
why why okay I guess right is triangle
so
really
umiz I don't believe it
you haven't eaten for days like days the
way you have that energy for that
be careful don't step into traps
manual arms no my my noodle arms are
stronger than that oh he's back
hold on hold hands
oh
yeah
he was in front of the Box
you know
all right let's not hold hands
triggered the Krill but when I run by a
trigger to Crow
isn't that weird
don't you
don't you look at the [\h__\h] is that
what if I run with them
same time
got the hat first there's a hat
somewhere here
oh
[\h__\h] ghost
s
suddenly
ah eyes like a school child hat the
yellow one
[Music]
at least that didn't call the big guy
let's go ahead yeah it looks like like
what the Japanese school kids wear
come on
[Music]
yeah let's take it off of that job yeah
sure that seems ethical fine no problem
with that
I like my fluffy
I guess
oh yeah this is I guess fits the story
because yellow
eventually one of us will be wearing a
yellow raincoat I suppose
you coming now
creepy ghost
a great camouflage
where's your child by the way hello are
you now on the right side
he already there now
push bugs this one
I can't
okay
um let's see I mean there's some grass
over there I wonder if that hides me
well enough
um okay
oh hello
I'm the protagonist I'm the protagonist
yo
what a weird place
[Music]
good morning
this reminds me a little bit of like the
atmosphere it reminds me a little bit of
the game
is not myself unravel
oh I see at some point I have to do that
maybe I'll wait can we move on
or the last one maybe the last one
yeah I thought so
oh it looks like I have a metal helmet
now
okay don't let me know where I got you I
got you that's maybe a bad timing to
pass through but all is good all is well
and we move on
what is this
what did he put in the water okay so
disgusting also why is there a heart
engraved there
what are you doing
wait
he's gonna notice you idiot
Larry in my opinions
nope
I fought for um distraction I see
I don't think that was necessary
[Music]
yeah great thank you thank you Birds
little shits
birds ain't loyal that's what I've
learned from the past week
foreign
[Music]
Birds go off in three two one
yeah
um on a box or so
oh
yes
ears
[Music]
good good stuff glad I didn't uh do it
too early apparently
right on time no you guys are not
tadpoles anymore that was a
hallucination
you never wore tadpoles what are you
thinking of course your chickens
chicken tadpole oh all right I guess I
was going for a swim right
I thought I activated that
are we doing a Titanic
only one of us can be in this big
[\h__\h] ass store
no we're not okay
we're chilling
oh can I move this thing
is this like tutorial over
congratulations kind of thing
was this all the tutorial
tutorial yeah I guess so
I guess that makes sense
so I did that in a little bit less an
hour
no it's chapter two now oh so maybe that
wasn't I mean you could say chapter one
is just a tutorial
[Music]
no don't let go
what's her name again
Rose was it Rose Rosie little [\h__\h] we
all know it was space for two
or you could have gone into the water
for a while and you switch
[Music]
we're gonna drink some ice cream eat
well yes two people can share the door
but these are you have to give it to
them they're [\h__\h] tiny they're tiny
as hell
[Music]
guys tomorrow tomorrow I'm gonna
have a cleaning lady over
there but you know how I don't know if
anyone ever made use of that but I feel
like I need to
pre-clean my apartment
you oh a little bit ashamed is this the
world that we were in last time
[Music]
it's like it's not like um everything's
like super dirty it's just like I have
so much stupid [\h__\h] lying around
everywhere
so much clutter that's not you know
properly put away and and some things I
don't even know even know where to put
them
what have I not realized yet
come on
the uncomfortable stranger in my home no
it's okay I mean it's a professional
on it and it's a lady so that's that's
fine too
the ruins I was watching at the
background
oh there's there's a friend close friend
it's not mommy no no mommy is not coming
over
oh I was
um oh God
I might have
um a few friends over for dinner
on the weekend maybe so I was like okay
maybe this is a good reason to
um
to you know get a proper deep cleaning I
want the floors to be wiped and [\h__\h]
employees I never I never weapon I do a
vacuum them but I never wiped them what
is that
full body motion capture suit
interesting so that finally arrived
good to know
yeah
to go with the valkyrie connect stuff
so you know
I I saw you know setting it up before
but only like a small part of it
I don't know if I can do it alone but
I'll try and um
I'll I'll probably get a friend
to help me with like measuring
me and stuff
[Applause]
um yeah
oh
was that my pillow fresh
probably
Tuesday but I got a message that it's um
gonna be tomorrow because
uh holiday
I guess that was wrong
what is this
prequel right
this looks like a sequel like as if you
know after everybody melted
is gone
it is a prequel
hat it's a hat there's always many hats
I'm happy and we all have so by the way
guys you don't need me you don't need to
tell me like where all the hats are I'm
happy with having a couple at least show
my face also the yellow one makes me
stand out well so
actually good for finding myself on the
screen and not thinking I'm the other
child
[Music]
anyway uh I I already have a plan on
what to do but don't expect it too soon
because Lena I know how it is I I never
know
technical things I I was like I always
find a way to make things complicated
things never work the way they should
for me
I'm surprised I got
I'm not gonna come surprised I got
um
surprise I got the the froggy Wawa to
work in the first place
yeah Kiana art with uh 100 hats a
thousand
hundred
was it a hundred or a thousands
I thought I could hold on to the TV
Daddy got your hands on it yay
yay I'm excited I'm excited I hope I
hope it works should work
couldn't
kick it how do I kick it
huh
I'm supposed to do something here
oh
don't count my divs
different kind of I can't swing harder
yeah
oh wait maybe I can
ah
it didn't work with the other thing that
we were swinging on I couldn't swing
harder with the other one
[Music]
I hear you
give me a sec
yes yes yes I get you I get you
um I suppose push the kitty
so you're up there now
I am excited to have a clean apartment
tomorrow
let's go
oh nothing right before
[Music]
officially right before thank you
five minutes before I got the Final Mix
for my new song cover
for blood so it's ready and the Envy is
finished actually and uh
um mix is finished
now I'm just like
what is the best day oh
the best day to upload it Friday
Saturday Sunday hmm
[Music]
I was listening to it and it sounded so
good I'm so happy with it it's Fire It's
Hot
it's really good
[Music]
yeah
um hello sir um how come you're hanging
there but with no body is
that your clothes after watching them
in the Box choose the Box
how's it how's it hanging huh
[Applause]
[Music]
okay wow this is really it yeah
should I go towards it
just one TV too much TV does to you kids
[\h__\h] you up
and now
[Applause]
I've always got to come through the
screen any moment
it's out to turn to tune the
transmission
[Music]
[Applause]
is it wrong
what do you want me to tune it to
this is right okay
I could teleport
I'm falling about my friend
[Music]
yeah
oh honest from the beginning
[Music]
hi there you are thanks for kicking me
out of that I guess
foreign
[Music]
who knows maybe maybe in the end will be
enemies
[Music]
foreign
introduce herself to me and even tell me
her name how am I supposed to know
where are we going
and
further down there
it's weird in a game where normally you
go from side to side when the selling
wants you to go yeah like differently
but maybe not
spoilers
the fact that she's a she's a spoiler
I'm gonna die yeah okay okay so so we're
not going that way
life
don't worry Chad
I'm reading you I'm reading her right
now
it's my job
to read you guys okay let's let's change
the topic done if you you know we want
to escape spoilers all right
can you help me out there
no
I know
um uh so yeah full blood coming this
week
ah
I watched House of the Dragon
a push okay I watched Hustle the dragon
um before it's dream I didn't actually
watch it yesterday I ended up not
watching it
surprisingly
oh
[Music]
well I'm really pissed I have to wait
that's it oh this way oh I'm gonna
pissed I have to wait like two [\h__\h]
years
to watch more of it
I was hoping for it to like be continued
in 2023
like I said ain't happening oh this is a
school
can we use this oh this is always so fun
when I was younger
can we play I Wanna Play you stay there
[Music]
what's playing
oh man
cool the scariest place of all honestly
totally relatable it do be pretty
terrifying
to go to school on a day where you have
a test oh
that you know you're gonna fail
especially if it's a test that decides
whatever or not you're passing the year
or not
on garbage I don't need all that it's
okay
I don't feel like you know
going for everything
hats don't seem to be important
pressed memories I don't know if it's
repressed but what are they burning
something there
where is it
it's old
school bags
oh
portraits of the children who went to
school
self-portraits or
um
I mean honestly when children in art
school on an art school but arts art
class
es there's holes have to draw something
I mean usually it turns out like [\h__\h] so
I'm not surprised this is
this is realistic honestly this is
better than it should be this is
unrealistic
95 of children in school
and even adults
teenagers
no matter how old even adults are [\h__\h]
at drawing
the only thing they can draw is stay
figures
bunk beds those bunk beds are really
narrow
like when you wake up
from a nightmare or so you're gonna Bonk
your head on that I had a nightmare by
the way last night
please
oh creepy baby where are you going
why are you bringing that one
you just saw me
picking up something
I want to pick up something too
or does it have any special meaning
anyway I had a dream that um
police came to arrest me it was really
dramatic
see
really demonic
it's a corn cob
what is there something interesting here
hmm
crimes a CEO no I
although I felt I don't know in the
dream I was like really confused like
why why oh my God [\h__\h] my life is over
why am I being arrested oh my God it
wasn't very clear why that was happening
it was really stressful really stressful
dream
one of those dreams where you wake up
and you're like oh god oh thank God that
was a dream
sheesh
do something here
what what
can you let me like peek through
a ball to break the picture oh okay
that's a big bowl
a sauce
unresolved anxiety
oh no it's just a dream in the end it's
just a dream
or or it's foreshadowing of Subaru
police
coming to get me
uh
we're chasing you two oh in this case
not really
someone was trapped here too
oh
fun here friend
jump
yeah now you get it now you get it
[Music]
more more Grandpa
is this ever gonna happen
nice teamwork
[Music]
where are we
the way you look up there is kind of
creepy child
come with me
I'll lead us to safety Dayo
hmm
[Music]
so far the school
seemed pretty empty but there's no way
something creepy awaits us everywhere
let me push this
pull pull
and those away till 2 42 a.m oh no uh
trust me I wasn't awake longer than that
but is that when I did my last tweet or
what
stop it stop documenting that
burp
oh no
not long-haired man
oh God
not long head man
long neck long neck boy
yesterday
a bowl another ball okay
oh
[Music]
oh you got me there
you got me there okay so and if I don't
touch the ball it's gonna be fine
is it
wow
oh we just have to like kind of activate
it
I could perhaps still take the ball
if I wanted to
do I need it though
above then below don't you think oh
oh creepy child
creepy child hacking we found
a creepy chat but it's not as creepy as
the long neck boy so I prefer
creepy child
wait do we get up now
too
people on the cover so
it's just too easy easy logic
story logic
hello hello
welcome to my mental support team
AKA my chant
this is for escaping later isn't it
um can we just hide in the locker
maybe that's the this is what
um
remaining students build
to protect themselves from long neck
teachers son
sensei
oh hello
oh oh what are you doing looking creepy
the movement is creepy
there's a doll oh these things are gonna
come down if they're going to put her
maybe but it's just a spoon and a fork
wait but then what about the other door
now I don't know which way to go
now I don't know
because this one's kind of open
maybe there's just like
in here
or is it just before the purpose of
spooking me
I hate games I hate games
hates games it's official
foreign
I mean maybe the vet
maybe the vent is an option too that's
scary
but I guess I'll go here
let's play a spot
ah I was playing this latest fire
yesterday again until late at night if
you look two or three hours
um but you know at first I was trying to
clear it over the fact
and
yeah I got like
that's just funny I didn't get the ideal
deck I don't know things didn't go so
well so I kind of failed alone
and didn't work out
um but I tried like two times and since
that didn't work out I was like okay I
but I want a win so I went back to uh
the poison one
The Silent One
trying to get a win with that one but
then you know I thought oh oh yeah last
time that went really well because of
the poison but then I didn't get any
poison cards in the beginning and
instead got the the shifts cards and I I
read up on it and I realized that that's
a different build like poison build and
shift build I'm like okay I guess let's
learn
let's learn how to do the shift build so
I was looking for sheeps
but then I also didn't get really many
shift cards either
but I was able to manage to make a
relatively decent build
um but
I had the problem that in the very
beginning
um you know you get the choice
then like four different choices
sometimes only two
snickering
and I see some of you guys have a
problem huh
YouTube
um I'm telling you a story you talk come
on
this isn't one of the lockers oh yes it
is
I saying though
what was it what was I just talking
about oh yeah ah sound yeah yeah so so
um for some reason I there must have
been a relatively good reason uh why I
chose the option to replace my my
starter railing with a random rare boss
Relic
I did that and of course I get a shitty
one in return I got the one
[Music]
cool thanks for showing me that
game over this was supposed to happen
okay
oh my friend is gone I got the one that
um
makes uh let's kill him
uh makes it so that you can't stay you
can't rest in
you can't rest in in in in in fire
places anymore so there was like
basically no way for me to get HP back
again you know I was trying to block as
much damage as possible and it was going
pretty well until like
hmm
I think the second
the second world's final boss or so
I was trying really hard
also by learning how to fight with a
shift build for the first time
I'm offline
[Music]
I want that stream indeed that's the
spooky spooky Halloween experience
killed this one too
thank you
we not know this the sound
also that that floor panel that's a
little bit higher than the others it
says
[Music]
hey I didn't need the hammer I just need
to step aside
[Music]
and then without the hammer we go next
Europe seems fine and a is fun why
how about
um
[Music]
frog oh he was dissecting from [\h__\h]
this is how you do it guys
is there any marathon going back here
what's your problem hey
not that
we need a key for the elevator probably
foreign
not this one
can't open that one but maybe this one
ah would oh
what's happening look close to it I
guess this is the one
oh rats
some some Satan child
has been occupying this Locker
cool
stuff
[Music]
YouTube we're back you are
foreign
[Music]
oh
is this like a thing in American schools
like obviously this is old school but
having a little
like room to put up your clothes and
stuff right before the classroom
this
is
[Music]
really learning a new thing that don't
have a brain I think like I smashed one
some of them I don't think they're
actually learning anything
you can erasing your time honestly
1930s thing oh
we're learning some history
foreign
what terrifying things
a way to learn here
any knowledge is terrifying
the more you know
the less you can enjoy life after
philosophical Phoenix
knowledge will only lead to unhappiness
because then you are too aware
of all the [\h__\h] that I can throw at you
yeah ignorance is bliss
and yes we crave and we seek knowledge
to improve the world maybe we are all
just destroying it oh Phoenix
[Music]
that might be a problem
[Applause]
I'm scared
I should have hit like like I should
have ignored the key first
I'm scared I'm gonna die I'm probably
gonna die okay we can redo it
um
[Music]
in class I have um other things to do
oh here we are okay so
we
um maybe we can prepare and we can open
this will she notice or do I have to do
the key first and then this
okay this is not an option
no
okay maybe just a box
[Music]
especially with my yellow hat
creepy
[Music]
is this what happens to
failed students of Boku no hero Academia
what was it called again
Academia something something
[Music]
hahaha
wait didn't one of them have the power
to you know
lengthen their lens
[Music]
okay
right that's it right
we still have the key
you have to hold it or is it like in my
pocket now I feel like I dropped it
it's in my pocket okay
are you are and then people back
no no buffer
foreign
this is how school was in 1930.
[Music]
oh my God I did not go to school
I'm buffered as soon as I said it oh no
cool
[Music]
can I escape
even though I was nervous about [\h__\h]
up
knows she knows
now I hate the sound of chalk on
um
on blackboards
let's try yay oh that's good they are
very much in control
you know what he looks like
from Shrek those
um
the the wooden
little boys
was it just one
you know who I'm talking about
Pinocchio yeah Pinocchio
we've got hats and the way his body is
built got a big head on a small slender
body what about your nose and want to
show me your nose
it's a good time I'm ticklish
really look like a tickle attack
around him then is he drawing now that
looks like actually kind of cool
lots of eyes
well I kind of like well he's drawings
kind of interesting
abstract art
oh man people leaving scream because
YouTube buffer sound
hi boy
good night
and then there's something like they
have to throw something maybe that metal
bar over there
it's so close
but he will
[Music]
raise me
yeah okay
um sorry at least I have um saved you
some pain
because I think you're better off
just being dead
trust me bro
oh the little hats
[Music]
go up can you not you should be able to
chair
that's weird why can't I not go up the
other way
is that an hat option
I don't think so because I did not see a
silhouette like this
in the head section
done sets is that what they called
oh can we do a wall jump
[Music]
let me know I was trying to go up what
do you mean
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
uh hi
so this reminds all of us I think to put
moisturizing cream on our necks
early on every day moisturize your neck
so they don't look like this when you're
60.
[Music]
for real though like a while ago I saw a
video or a picture
of um
a comparison from someone who uh put
moisturizing cream on their neck every
day
and then all the lady who didn't do that
and the one who didn't do it had a way
more like
[Music]
um wrinkled really really wrinkled neck
when she was like 60 or 70 or whatever
um
and the other one had a pretty nice neck
yeah
and you know a really wrinkled deck made
that person look actually much older
so since then I've been
when I do my my skincare I've been
putting my skin cream on my neck as well
properly
[Music]
let's hope it's not too late
um push
I knew that she was gonna hear that
okay is she gonna get through here
though I feel like she could
[Music]
possibly could
oh well
Library oh no
same library now
but I remember the library from Little
nightmares when I hated it
extreme styling again should I stop and
do part two another time
like now it's still early enough to stop
and split it
um
it's fine with me well I mean most of
the people who is not fine for probably
already left giving up
no I kind of wanna
I kind of want to finish it today but
not if YouTube is such a little [\h__\h]
maybe it will fix or is it is it just
this stream though I kind of want to
know
um
and it's just problems with this stream
or others too
because if it's my stream maybe it's
like cursed from the start
sometimes when you make a new stream it
just works
uh
yeah I know good I finished in five
hours so that kind of inspires me to do
the same
only an am but I want to know which
stream I mean it's been fine oh some are
fun okay
all right
okay
[\h__\h]
she's stuck there
I won't manage it why am I too slow
my dad's look
also that looks like a hat
just jump on the other side
six hours you predict no
I want to go faster push that oh
push it
it's [\h__\h] like this it just doesn't work
on the first try can you really push it
oh from there but is it like logical
thinking that I would assume I push it
from the side if I want to go I want it
to go from side to side
hmm
let's get this hat I think that's a hat
pumpkin is that the bucket
no it's not an actual hat it looks like
it could be
huh
get used to game logic
I never do I never do
I guess it depends on the game what
oh she's not
broke
got the hat is what the [\h__\h] hat I
don't care about the [\h__\h] hats
we'll have time for stupid [\h__\h] hands
because my arm hurts I shocked myself so
hard my arm hurts
[Music]
what
as well it looks like I could fit
through
um
scared even you
doesn't seem like she wants to really
check it out she could just go around or
like she could go for that hole with her
she's looking at me though
it's scary
in the other game nice
oh are we going down I wanna go sideways
moving up
there we go that's what I was trying to
do
not higher okay
[Music]
foreign
practice with Catherine ah I really want
to play Catherine hmm
it is [\h__\h] creepy
hat
some teachers that I did not like much
but not not
thank you
[Music]
nice catch though yeah
what's up lady
I [\h__\h] hate this
where am I supposed to do
I waited before it didn't work now I go
fast and it didn't work
I tried waiting it out
okay I'll try waiting it out again but
just trying to go
inside
Maybe
hi
oh God
no
just wait a little bit longer until she
goes back to normal oh okay
same
okay uh
getting myself into these situations how
come
see that part
progress
yeah
you know
there's a box here to hide later
I'm not a chicken you should know that
um
oh wow we're going with this
burned away
require this
maybe the the door I mean it's not open
but
why why would this child want to open
the door
why
do you desire to find more terror
maybe run
okay is this for later is
maybe this will be in the way
oh oh
don't close again
I have to take my friend no at this
point we should abandon our friend
no no no no no not smart
oh oh that was the door
wow
what
survival thinking you know
I'm a survivor
[Music]
okay okay
um
laugh chess
I can't reach but can I
jump on this stuff no rage maybe not
stream is better now oh really
I can pick up the broken one
foreign
that we were collecting like this as
well
there was something
oh
is this the tower no why won't you undo
it I was trying to move it
foreign
am I supposed to jump from here
Tower how much is oh
one is replaced with the head of a doll
yeah fitting I mean why not you're
missing you're missing
missing the
the top part so why not
[Music]
oh he's so crazy ah
so we help him can we help him for real
top pieces up there no that's white one
I don't know
I'm a black piece
Black Eyed Peas there's a sword
okay I am just trying to not go to the
right side because it's scary
because the music changed I know there's
something scary here the eyes
the eyes
thank you
okay oh there you go I know
[Music]
I know are we
who's this oh
what does it help me to
put this on a different figure Maybe
[Music]
jump at the eye
ah
okay
oh chess
is my passion
okay certain only certain pieces
are to be completed wait that might be
the wrong one let me check again a white
a white top was there but which one
that was the right one okay so the other
one goes to the bottom middle
I guess
how do I reach
[Music]
mmm
why is it turned around
maybe it's maybe this is not the right
way to look at it
the rook's head
which one is a rook
these ones
take it this one
oh we're in the other room
okay
ah okay
ah the tower is called The Rook no no
don't place on there no I guess maybe oh
look
that actually did work
wait when we like activate the child in
the middle I feel like if I do this
right maybe it'll activate the child oh
no let me check it again
ah
okay okay
the last white piece on the right side
is supposed to have this top
[Music]
here
is the door closed
Checkmate ah it's a checkmate
so
okay
[Music]
wow dog pee
yes very meaningful did the dog pee on
the key
oh yeah
okay but we have the key
and the child did not come to life I'm
surprised
but there was gonna be a jump scare but
probably coming soon
[Music]
uh
I think it was downstairs
[Music]
something
teach me why
why does world even exists
the school container let's see what
these students get to eat hopefully
something healthy
neutral neutralizing no nutrient
nutrient
you know what I mean
hey see this one I can move from the
side
and probably even move it from the front
nutritious that's the word
I hear screams
these are screams
[Music]
I feel like I hear screams
really faint ones and dishes obviously
oh
the one on the right is he cleaning the
plate with a sausage
okay we're gonna kill that one
of the spoon
is the other one peeing into the soup
the doll how can he peek
s
[Music]
what about the top one you coming down
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I think I'm one of them oh because
there's probably too many huh
[Music]
I'm going
to school
kids
[Music]
[Applause]
being treated like
chicken
[Music]
I wasn't able to like do some like sick
tricks
but
I was able to go pretty fast at least
and the rope skipping exercise
jump rope yeah
[Music]
there we go
Let's Escape
where's it here
our food jar
keeping roughness down there yeah
I'm actually real that just reminds me
like because I was I've been watching
Malcolm in the Middle right I was just
at the episode where
um Lloyds
she's
um at her mother's uh
like
old people care place
what do you call it
and they were I don't know celebrating
some kind of
Festival
and then she was like showing off her
not rope jumping skills but something
way more deadly yeah nursing home yeah
yeah that was this episode where you
know and she was dressed up in this like
traditional dress and all that
and then she was instead of ropes she
was jumping through
like I don't know like knives kind of
and Big Blocks of wood and stuff
oh
there you go
yeah is that actually a thing I was
wondering
is this actually like I don't think did
they say any any country but I wonder if
it's actually some places
play Dance
something like that
he's trying to swing a bit more but it
didn't
it's different from the other rope that
I've experienced
I'm going to judge no I feel like the
game wants me to go up here obviously
like judging by the path
it
we can try that too but
how
how do I make it so that it goes
further what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
it looks sad
I hate this
at least it doesn't get tangled
I know I see it I see it the before
before we didn't have this problem I
still couldn't properly
how does
why is he looking that way I want you to
look the other way
no how do I turn him
[Music]
um
this is the wrong direction
[Music]
suddenly
big
big swing
so what are we doing here we're just
throwing this down
oh the empty drives we need the brain to
throw it
is that it
is
but now we don't want to die
doesn't it reset what we just did
I just fall down now
cool
I know it I was trying to land on the
thing the Hulk oh [\h__\h] man
I'm I'm impatient
I mean I saw the hook but
I didn't realize
all the place light aspire
fun
thank you
hey
where's my momentum
[Music]
uh finish oh well then I'm gonna play
something else but
if I really if by the time the steam
that arrives if I'm like sick of the
game at that point well there'll be
other games
why why I can't get the momentum anymore
trying
I'm trying
I'm gonna fall if I jump down this is
not enough
my finger
this is too weak to hold on to the
button for that long
come on
you can jump further than you think well
so far the game has really disappointed
me in that regard so
I don't trust it
I've fallen down from this distance
before
now maybe
not
I might just
Rachel quit this game before it actually
ends
Ralph
and now I guess we hold on
[Music]
I'm gonna be worth it
I've got the brain ew
wobbling good bro
oh no
no no
[Music]
crap what's wrong
he's making pickled frogs
about the fries see and
I know I took over and all that
wasn't very nice of her oh
is that oh God which way which way which
way which way but I have no problem with
her and with her companions frogs in
general
[Music]
doggy
oh but if I go there I won't see where
I'm going next
[Music]
what about here
yes
[Music]
you should hire more teachers because I
think all of this is just happening
because she's stressed out
I think generally she's a good person
[Music]
I was just
the doll
I'm saying oh they should hire more
people so you don't you don't have so
much work to do you know you have to
hurt the children and [\h__\h]
okay never mind [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you
[Music]
I need to go above ah to jump
uh I was wondering like when I was there
hmm how do I
get there
but when I passed by this section am I
just supposed to run
she doesn't seem to
go anywhere else
[Music]
maybe not yeah okay now that I'm up here
to see those different actions okay
wait
oh I can't take the other one
[Music]
take some more
songs
[Music]
your hands
my YouTube
foreign
[Music]
moving on
a little croissants
[Music]
all right
she's about to stop looking for me yeah
maybe I'm okay with this
okay can we not fail this jump this time
oh God
[Music]
but how do you know we just entered the
room for the first time man also why why
was that scripted I wonder if that
happens always
mean
[Music]
you're a shit's teacher
suck
[Music]
down
it's great to just below
[Music]
foreign
oh did she like just see me and then she
turned around at that moment
please don't come here
ah I see
um
[Music]
third time
why are they all drawing eyes
[Music]
get rid of them not the best way oh you
know what I'll trigger it and run back
here
hahaha
I won that fight bucket got him
thank you next
[Music]
who wants to fight
exciting music
and backwards
[Music]
you were not supposed to get me but hey
we start from here that's nice even with
the hammer
[Music]
it was not fair
come here
perception
perception problem
yeah
okay don't don't hit when you think he's
there hit a little bit later
there's even some wiggle room anyway
[Music]
someone coming someone coming from where
from where
[Music]
ow come on but I saw it saving um so
yeah at least we have the Chick-fil-A
here
I don't think we need to do it do we do
it
oh
wait I thought I think we need it
Hammer is our best friend now
game trolling yeah
they were trolling too with their butts
what are you doing for the child
[Music]
Next Level bullying
who
a
good job
what's wrong with me
thank God
[Music]
I thought it was a one of them and
they're just bullying each other but
it's my friend isn't it
here we go hi
alive
finally back together yeah
[Music]
how you doing it's okay it's me look at
my hat
I'm not one of them
[Music]
we're staying alive so proud of you
let's go we're a team again
[Music]
the games mechanics you are the reason
this game exists
nice
a break
oh it's not
okay fine with me
oh
why is the keyboard on the keyboard why
is the piano on a rope
[Music]
why
it does look like a keyboard a little
bit I I wouldn't be surprised if in
English you know they somehow named this
thing keyboard ah and and uh the
keyboard actual keyboard that could be
piano instead
who knows
it's a board of keys
kind of
oh
yeah
synthesized ones are
called keyboards why do they call it the
same thing
it's confusing it has no [\h__\h] and no
fake
oh okay
[Music]
assume that this is the right thing to
do make so much [\h__\h] noise
[Music]
and not not stealthy at all I need a
robot lighter in German
and in German we say thank you
which translates directly to
um
uh what's going on again
robbing prison ladder
the frog and the key Anna does not go
into the Frog upon against the lower the
leaves I know
I know you think Kiana was saying to
frog
it's not like that
little child
no no no she the thing is she ate me
yeah
ate me that little [\h__\h]
and then
I know I told you guys before that when
someone eats a phoenix
you know the moment they
what am I supposed to do the moment they
sent them out of their body it's too
late but I was still in her body she had
a slow really slow digestion system
[Music]
huh
how did it fit in there well I mean you
can if you properly munch your food
munch munch munch
then it gets smaller
just have to do this
do this you get smaller it sticks into a
frog belly also like you would look at
the snake and not believe what fits into
the snake's body either would you I mean
now we do because we're educated and we
know that a snake can eat a [\h__\h]
human
my dad but anyway so since I was still
in her body
and you know frog lure
um
kissed the Frog I transformed
back I was able to escape
the body of the Frog yes
it's more like I escaped rather than
from the other transformed
[Music]
dude you didn't have to do that not if I
hit I'm gonna hit you too
okay nevermind you did it good job
come on
you
are you having like a weird moment where
you're like oh [\h__\h] I killed someone
huh
okay do I not actually need
what is the hammer for
oh
I can't
[Music]
never mind I just thought about it
me some time to test things out
can I go with the hammer I don't think I
can
hold on to things
lovely music
[Music]
I keep on stopping
don't stop
just play the right key
is it long neck teacher is this what she
does after she's done with work for the
day or how relaxing
it's actually quite pretty
I thought you would if anything she
would play something more terrifying
[Music]
ah now you're helping me thank you
probably for you
now I need your help
[Music]
so who is it the big reveal who is the
Piano Master
what do you call it my soul right
someone someone who's good at that kind
of stuff
foreign
[Music]
but every time she does you know this
yeah makes a note
that's when we have to be quiet
[Music]
she plays pretty long Let Me Wait and we
went until next break
cause she's such a sophisticated lady
isn't she
[Music]
foreign
huh
[Music]
good night
squeak Spike
[Music]
oh yeah yeah that's what I thought
this is maximum
I wonder if the tip was always the same
or if they're gonna Boozle me and
suddenly make her
breaks like
more often
but I think it's so far the same
don't fall down
I'm scared
laughs
okay there's one enough time but I wait
anyway
yeah yeah
[Music]
trailer
okay
and a nice we made it out don't tell me
you're going back in is this chapter
over maybe yeah
we're done with the school I would be
very happy as we are
congratulations on your graduation
[Music]
congratulation party that's kind of sad
though
now comes the spooky chapter no what do
you mean now comes the spooky chapter
already spooky
that's cool
that's nice
[Music]
wallpaper material right there
yeah let's book each other ugly no here
comes the spooky chapter and then after
that comes another spookies out there
ah what
are we moving
I wanna
go up there
all right oh yeah no problem
yeah this is how far I can get that
really is like was that really necessary
bug
what the [\h__\h] yeah
[Music]
ah you're gonna help me up or do I need
to use the TV
that was a little bit too far away
move any footage in there
no
[Music]
I'll try
Oh you mean maybe like backwards because
I was trying to move to the right
and backwards
here
I guess that's a little bit closer
you go first yeah yeah show me show me
how it's done child no
need for somehow and sometimes we need
to learn to go first buddy
don't always follow what the others do
you guys need to be a little bit
original
find your own way your own cow
oh is that a hat oh no it's a
scary ghost baby child
[Music]
I used to know how to build those not
anymore though how do you build them
it's not so difficult though I think
she said the vein what did I say
oh
[Music]
so is that the character from the
from the from the sequel in that case
[Music]
same same person
do I die
other game
what's on that's not um think about that
now
I guess she abandons me or or
she kills me or I just die on my own
look I have the yellow hat and you have
the yellow raincoat oh okay
foreign
thing you need
in the puzzle to become God
oh helping me
no help
no not cold hand
foreign
it's the same button so
when are you coming to the sun huh
I don't want you
oh I need oh let me help you
there you go I feel like you could have
squeezed through there that was enough
of a gap for both of us to be honest
and
yeah
Evie where are we going next what kind
of world are we entering what the [\h__\h]
up world are we entering next
who are we to meet
walking in the rain storm
oh
I'm walking in the rain storm
oh I I've been schooled achievement says
I've been schooled and now somebody said
Hospital
there's so much
[\h__\h] up [\h__\h] they could do in the
hospital I'm not
very excited for it
at least we don't have to see long neck
lady anymore right
[Music]
an asylum okay Outlast let's go finally
playing Outlast hooray
yeah
oh
interesting structure I'm not surprised
your patients die when they're supposed
to sleep in such a dangerous structure
who built this
huh
up up can you go higher
no
well this time she's actually going
forward before me well I'm impressed
thank you
is it because of the raincoat she's like
black woman look at her but she's
zooming
this is my destiny I was always supposed
to be yellow
yellow is just my color I'm absolutely
rocking it let's go yes
get yellow raincoats
I'm so cute
oh we need something to put in there
doesn't seem to be here
can we just stuff the bandages in there
or maybe one of the bottles
finish then it's too big no
I feel is
that's not gonna be that easy huh so can
we go here do we want to
oh it doesn't seem like we want to
[Music]
use that door
I thought it was like in a hotel you
know where you can stick something else
in it and then we'll still do the same
thing you don't actually need what you
think you need did you know that in the
hotels
you know the the card slot
card
yeah paper any stick anything in there
and it looks
this one's not supposed to happen
game is super loud so
let's see
you didn't hear me oh
I was saying oh in a in a hotel the card
slot you don't actually have to put in
the the room key
to get the electricity away you can
literally put anything in there
even like normal paper
as long as it's thick enough
that's what I was saying so I was
thinking maybe this this here is the
same thing we can just put anything in
there and it will react yeah I know some
people don't know this
hotels have to let
sockets to begin but uh
what are we doing
I don't know like a business card or
something in there
that's only for electricity yeah yeah oh
I don't mean like when you put in the
car to get into the room I mean inside
the room
inside the room to turn on the
electricity oh
hey yo what the [\h__\h]
me what's B
uh
inside the room there's usually
and he's poopy time Mario
usually a slot for the card to turn on
electricity anyway so that's that
Mario
cute radio
is it wait is there a radio wait no
probably not
is that a robot
robot's head
oh hello
[Music]
scariest part
no
no scary please
do I have to open the door
go away
now I try the door
I think
no
she's not moving
leading up to the scariest part the
scariest part of the game
foreign
done
whites don't go
don't fade away
oh okay
just manage your forward looking sick
funny Hospital sick
something's gonna happen
something
is going down
take it
oh I guess we use it for something
[Music]
here we go
will you touch it again
foreign
[Music]
is this right I don't know
sweat this looks right
and another time huh
last time it was awesome
[Music]
what am I failing
here here it is there it is
yeah oh wait we lost a friend again
but no they're gonna pop out with us out
of the TV any second now
[Music]
I'm gonna cancel my Netflix subscription
so before I do that I would cancel my
Disney Plus subscription because
barely got anything good on there
unless all you do all day is watch
Disney movies
do it first try
why why do we do that why do we
I guess
marketing
[Music]
I watch more Disney than Netflix yeah I
only watch Disney right now because of
Malcolm in the Middle and I've got
scrubs too so whenever I want to rewind
subscribers or Malcolm in the Middle but
wasn't scrubs on Netflix too
why are you not helping
hey help me
oh [\h__\h] okay I need to fuses probably
fuses first okay
The Simpsons yeah The Simpsons I guess
some of those shows are on there but
besides that once you're done with that
there's nothing nothing of substance
really Disney plus just doesn't have any
shows that have substance that's a
problem
one key is in the teddy is that a hint
well can we go through here
oh will it show something if we turn it
on
fun yeah
okay so you have a skeleton inside your
body
surprise what about me I want to do it
too
what if what if I don't have a skeleton
can you push it
thank you
no I do okay
I guess that's a a relief
foreign
how do we open it up
turn knife
so far it's really not scary yet because
no no nothing has been
do we bring it behind telephone
nothing has been like
trying to kill me so far
I found one she likes oh I guess yeah
we're still children after all
right I'm not playing no no I'm not
playing around
oh there's nothing wrong Teddy then
okay
I was in the teddy
a lot to me what about the bunny
good luck finishing it thank you I hope
I will I hope I have the patience for it
and accept an ax
in the wooden horse
I mean I saw something but
I thought it was just wood or something
okay
[Music]
how do we open that thing
bro keep keep let's go
let's go
give it to me
why is he not give to me
maybe there's something else
what is that
can we get higher no okay okay
I don't see anything that would help us
take it apart
talk of each on uh it was fun it went
supposedly well but then unfortunately
told me afterwards that you know some
recording may have a problem so I don't
know how it's just gonna you know deal
with that
[Applause]
do this
throw it
uh
how am I supposed to do
oh
it's it yeah it was fun we talked about
some things like it's not as um in-depth
as Holo talk is
I'm gonna go somewhere else
elevator on the left but should I take
the bunny
a bunny
we should make
we should open them up and then like
make suits for ourselves you know like
big kikurumi's
I can I'm gonna be the bunny you're
gonna be the
the the bear how about that what is this
thing is this the elevator oh
God
foreign
[Music]
I can't pick it up oh man
so yeah it's not as in depth as a whole
talk
which I think is good because I wasn't
eventually gonna do like kind of a
reverse thing
are we joining don't join
gonna put it in there
no okay why not
it was nice to talk afterwards so like
after the recording it was like about an
hour but after the recording we talked
like for two hours
because
she was like so okay and I'm like hmm
you know what no I'm not
and then you know she was listening to
me
like you know open up it was nice to
have someone actually listen to you it's
not like you know problems could be
fixed or anything
some things are just the way they are
um but uh yeah it's very understanding
and she agreed with me and we talked
about you know a couple of things for a
long time like two hours I I was really
happy because I didn't have my breakfast
so I didn't eat breakfast until like
four hours after I woke up but I just
really wanted to talk to a John because
she was like really supportive of
Chit Chat
of opening up when is she gonna let go
of that stupid toy
now okay
[Music]
yeah she's really sweet
well yeah as I said the recording may
have some problems
it's like kind of a situation like you
know that one the whole talk oh open
yeah huh
[Music]
um producer but even worse
even worse you know I just lost
the video of myself back then I think
but I had no the other way around I
didn't have the voice
of myself
but I had the video okay I think huh
I don't even know but I know I know I
had the recording of the producer
then I had the kuchipaku I had to
lip sync the whole thing
over again and connect it and you guys
didn't even notice so that was okay
um something similar happened
[Music]
oh hello
I wonder if so far I found every one of
them
hmm
an amazing work wondering thank you
yeah the desperate situation is called
for desperate measures and solutions
let me drink some water I need to
hydrate
I'm a very good actor
to be honest I was trying really hard
back then to move my
my mouth according to what I was saying
in the recording uh but it's really hard
in a in such a long recording was like
one and a half hours right
you need to anticipate what I'm going to
say next
yeah
it's really hard but
then when I look at myself like this in
the live stream I already have the my
mouth movements are not actually
that's clear but I tried really hard for
um that recording I was like
muffin mouthing and mimicking
it's way more exaggeratedly than
necessary
uh okay so I'm guessing that from here
on
we're gonna meet some people
yeah
some some dead people maybe some alive
people who knows maybe some half alive
people
do we need to finish the body there's
like a lot of body parts
no
no finishing of the body
or
point
okay yeah that's okay okay that's
it okay
[Music]
what do I do what do I do
said go stealth
where's the hand
can I go up
no
[Music]
okay
hmm
[Music]
cool
it's kind of close
it's like a speeder
up
why are you waiting for me
[Music]
where I was going the hand knew where
the accident is
[Music]
so fast I'm really trying my best here
you know
okay and then run
yeah
that was fine
it's following me
[Applause]
uh
okay did you stop following me
more
it's all cool it's not scary
okay
thank you
it's like those tiny
cute spiders that can jump
so cute
um
uh
Hammer doesn't see a hammer
foreign
you'll be broken
[Music]
like this
oh
get the hands dead for good I don't
trusted
hey
if we um push this away I can open the
door
ah with the hammer probably
I should again just in case
foreign
's here
girl
are you
I you really huh
oh you were just playing huh
you good
scary the freak
killing me helping hand
when are you all
go
you know
being weird
I have nothing else to do here
all right there's a left left time
go this way
hello
I have to put it in here first probably
and then uh we get the second thing from
the end again then we can move the one
that we put on the left hand back to
here probably
okay
take
go
was the one from the first game the girl
full wrinkled
girl supposedly I didn't even did I even
know that in the first game I don't
think I was aware
[Music]
so far
the school was kind of worse so far
ah
interesting
[Music]
um
okay this is where that scene in GTA 5
happened
um we need bucket or so oh can you help
me okay it's good
oh
yeah yeah
I see what you're gonna do
no no no no oh God my head hurts oh
is there no way around it can I also not
trigger you is that an option
so I'm not gonna be surprised when you
move
I'm I don't know what this thing will do
will it open the door
maybe we can strap him to the chair
what my
my head
all right run
you did it
what's going on
ah it moves when the light is off so if
I just leave the lights on
okay
is always at the light pointed at him
but I kind of ah wait so that he makes
some space
can can you not join me here
so bad
and this probably counts for all of
these maybe are you gonna move
are you
no
probably my my light is probably gonna
go off the worst possible time it's
gonna break
behind me shut up
um
gonna go
the back door
okay run
everyone
oh hello
[Music]
this is the scary part you're like you
don't know
which one's gonna move
[Music]
foreign
they're in different directions
[Applause]
How can I
last night
Pro gamer Pro Gamer right here right
there
my
[Music]
got it
foreign
[Music]
I got them
oh that's awesome
[Music]
ah
sniped
sniper boy that's cheating huh
I might get done it's kind of funny this
game that we're playing
huh
okay I kind of made a mistake
uh yeah I'm walking backwards and I
guess it works yeah but
like I don't I'm not sure how
pink when there is an enemy
with them around me I the character
tries to aim it at them
protect I mean rotate
[Music]
now how do you actually go backwards
would be good to know
because I feel like I managed to do it
once before
that would actually make it too easy so
that might actually not be it
right stick no no
right stick doesn't help right I think
it's just a camera around
only when I'm with the Enemy
um
[Music]
I can't
how did I do it at first
no no no no no
[Music]
run around
huh
when the enemy is moving
ah
so
[Music]
I I can't do like a complete backwards
still only like kind of
sideways
well I don't know
maybe it's different when when the enemy
is moving but it's kind of hard to
practice that then
okay
uh
is the other one coming
oh [\h__\h] I'm done I clumsy
[Music]
can you even do it slowly though or is
the the way I did it the first time like
the way to go
[Music]
come around light light movement is kind
of tough
foreign
[Music]
from the start and maybe run first no
turn around
oh
oh okay
I wish it was a safe Point here oh that
was so close though
let's see
[Music]
and I know that here three of them will
follow me and first time I just ran
through and it worked pretty far I just
have to at some point you know
[Music]
is there more
I wonder if it's saved it must have
saved that section was probably saved
right
okay okay
[Music]
where where to go
all right
where do we go
harder now
activate lights
what there's light switches
ah wait here there's that so that's
where I go that's not a light switch
okay but at least here um by the latest
here it must have saved
good job
[Music]
okay
don't care about the line
everybody wants a piece of me
hey
bro
how
that
oh
yeah yeah yeah
I guess yeah lights okay
it didn't work on the hands but I guess
on the full Fuller bodies it's gonna
work on them right
sorry kind of
oh that's a sweat
um
I don't like it either
hey
the middle seemed relatively safe before
Hole In The Great Well grid
grid
being like in here
huh I can't get through
I don't know what what green
oh
yes
foreign
was
pretty decent
it was all right
wasn't so difficult
foreign
guys
I'm so tense
huh
okay and we're gonna move this thing
over there so I can climb on it
no
oh
from here
what is
it
do I need to soap
it's off
over there
I don't like the light
I like the light though
oh now they would move
are they actually alive
I don't think I can read too much today
my voice is gonna be dead by the end of
this
you have to redo the button
haha
[Applause]
okay
Lord back to the switch
ah
you mean then and then throwing up with
soap and then close the door again or so
does it work from the other side
[Music]
question I don't think that's
necessarily in the way to go because
there's no button on the other side
um but yeah I needed off the wheelchair
ah turn the light on again ah true
but interestingly it did not care about
my my flashlight
why does not care about the flashlight I
was obviously pointing it at it
um
[\h__\h] it's too big yo they didn't even
touch me
they did not touch me
foreign
[Music]
oh okay
okay
[Music]
good
are you guys scared
it's probably not scary when you're just
watching is it
because I'm all right I'm not having the
time of my life to be honest here
[Music]
as you guys said before Oh God I every
game is a [\h__\h] horror game for me
already from the get-go is this thing
gonna move
are you
hi
hey
chill
hey my friends hey
there's too many listen Manny and I
don't know where to go maybe I should
just run through first and figure out
where to go first
I need a plan
hey
I was trying to flash them all
I was trying
I'm just trying to gather them first
though
she's in that moment
Bean
[Music]
we'll figure it out
I'm gonna try
I think we have to go backwards they're
not not front
maybe we have to pass in the back
well maybe it's some better
[Music]
oh I couldn't move the stick anymore I
know it was being weird
go for the run and then fold that I
tried that first
I tried that very
but
they all surround you
it's hard
it's not easy
[Music]
foreign
how did you guys do this did anyone do
this before
anyone who played this
it's time to give up oh oh I feel like
you're challenging me
struggled to
spin
[Music]
this is so stupid
so stupid that can't honestly be the
only way to do it
thank you so much
so much
what did we do that for
huh was that are you trying to just
teach me how I'm supposed to get through
all right well wait a second
if there's more to that
can we push this
is
I think that's that's the the fuses we
cannot forget the ah wait no we don't
throw ourselves through that we throw
the fuse through there
and then somehow
oh
what do you call this in English like an
electrical
um breakthrough not climb
that's it we need sap
no no I did not expect that to happen
shortcut yeah like an Overlord overload
shortcut
now open thank you
[Music]
it's rough man
can't take
let's hear the accent
is it here
foreign
I'm so happy but the whole Hospital
seems to have that theme of
you know
having to stop the zombies
I did not think you would do that friend
Short Circuit
[Music]
my mask is pretty oh thank you
ah
come
on
I love this part maybe maybe 50 through
the hospital 50
Cent now Big Boss yourself
you like The Mask
thank you
where are we going to go
places the deeper you go and the scary
it is
that's why they keep the dead bunnies as
well right but I guess everywhere you
keep the dead bodies in the game
everywhere
[Music]
what happened
oh I hear a voice
a laughing
what's so funny huh
guys we need to watch that Joker movie
because I never
watched it before but I finally
understand the reference now that
everyone was making when I first was it
the first time probably went the first
time when I first revealed the whole
talk Studio
and people were like drawing me uh
like kind of like Joker with Joker face
uh
we're only on the way around maybe the
guests in Joker face I think maybe that
way
yeah sitting in the talk show set
and I think me as a host I was laughing
my ass off
finally understand the reference to that
now
it only took me like two years
um what what's going on
[Music]
oh okay
come on interesting that it doesn't
attack my friend with the plot armor oh
there you go one more hit don't sit
there that's my friend
[Music]
oh God it's gonna get me
getting another man there it is two of
them you were waiting for that weren't
you
you were anticipating that
I'm ready now
[Music]
before the second one comes out or is
this scripted
little money
[Music]
two hands with one bump stick yeah oh
actually the one that I hit was probably
and the other the first one because that
last hit seems to have done the trick
yeah
the highs one more
hands
let me help you
[Music]
the hands are just a [\h__\h] joke not
scared of the hands
laughing
what is that
[Music]
upside down
they're gone oh
an upside boy he's living in an upside
world
upside down
you're [\h__\h] insane brother
look at the look he gave us and the
camera was freaking
let's go to the other side no
[Music]
oh we're fine we're fine
we're seemingly fine where do we go can
we open that door
Lenny's doing surgery
I respect that
we need more people like you
what's up
you're so [\h__\h] creepy
[Music]
I'll move the bed
um can I request a different doctor
please
I think my insurance allows me to get
like a better one than this
I think I'm entitled too
I wanted a private doctor
that's what happens in public
hospitals
is there something here to escape no no
there's not I need to throw something
there
ain't wonderful
yeah
what are you doing what are you doing am
I safe
oh we're starting here okay so what
can I throw at that button can I throw
my friend
there's some toys back there with
reaching that okay
today
okay
too close for comfort
and then you can feel the love
potassium he has towards his job
he's so into it
he really only wants the best for his
patients
huh
he's okay to go
next go next so which toy do we want
matter hopefully not
breathing is so creepy
monkey head monkey head maybe make sound
and I know the the pony thingy makes a
sound too
but at that point probably he already
hears it just but when the door opens
oh a yellow girl
you're being a little bit too obvious
there
are we moving
awesome okay with that relatable
stretch stretch
[Music]
um we can go here too
and now
bro well I'm gonna wait until he's in
the corner okay
uh
[\h__\h] it up don't hook it up
[Music]
she's still there okay I guess you
stayed there too
no please don't pick it up
[Music]
don't you think someone went there okay
thank God
it would be so ridiculous if I wasn't
saved there I would boycott the game
you're taking your damn swim
gonna stay there
still be careful though girl girl
sure about that
that's what I wanted to do anyway
I hate the climbing in this game
don't like it
she knows where she's going yeah has she
been here before
bro he's just this is his floor after
all
he's just walking around and then see me
oh
okay
I'm here
click it
do we have a key did we pick up a key
okay
we don't have it do it do we
save here okay
God
no I guess I don't okay
okay
oh ideas two-sided London
can't
because body
what about what about here
can't on it
are we sure that I can't go through here
where's my friend
on the back door here
no
oh the handle ah okay okay
that was what I was gonna do next
[Music]
who wants to go in you or me
yes it's me
now you're just gonna stay behind yeah
yeah it's okay I'm just taking this up
this game you're the protagonist of the
next game
you're gonna work hard in the other one
right
yeah yeah yeah I got you
oh oh there it is yeah it can't be that
easy
I think we're gonna make some stairs
here
foreign
let's go
what about the door ah maybe when I jump
on it it's gonna like swing to the left
with lots of momentum speaking of
momentum next week next week I think
the the portal
that the game that's similar to portal
is coming
up but
I actually have a surprise for that
they offered
uh for me to do like some key giveaway
on my stream so you guys don't buy it
yet I don't know how many keys I'll get
for you guys but
yay it's not sponsored but yeah
why am I here
it's not sponsored but I I will get some
keys for you guys yeah in case you're
interested
I think
everybody here likes portal who doesn't
like portal we all like portal
so since we all miss portal and portal
free is never going to happen
let's be real
[Music]
to make up with other things to be
satisfied with other things
yeah you can you know once once you
stream and then
I'll probably give out keys at the end
or so probably
I'm not sure I'm not sure what the exact
routine is going to be
wait it's been a while since I was able
to do something like that but I'm happy
to give away some free codes
you know other YouTubers they do that
kind of stuff all the time they're like
oh write a comment and you'll get a free
iPhone and this and that and this and
that
and I feel like we've with like how
um how much audience we have normally
companies would probably be more than
happy to
give away some free stuff in our
channels oh [\h__\h]
but somehow
somehow oh so far
we don't really get those like offers no
like sponsored streams we do sponsored
streams stream streams but you know some
reason
those are called scams
I don't know I mean like not only that
not only a free iPhone if you write in
the comments
oh oh he's back
seems very busy we're occupied
[Music]
oh I see it
all right
there's one
one like ladder thing there but oh
is he gonna push it in
okay we hold on to the leg Maybe
he's moving and still
oh oh hey hey gentle
you freak
hmm what's on the left side more to Sims
4 please ah I don't know about Sims 4
but I really really want to do that
since one stream
soonish
because I got all the seasons one games
physical copies
CDs just have to figure out how to make
it run on a new computer like this
because like it's really hard to get an
old game like that to actually work
wait good question what
must be something to do here
put the bottle things over there
at six is gonna help me really
oh there oh
yeah thank you
[Music]
let's go
extreme hard monitor
so a live patient that's the miracle
who was dead here
ah you can jump on
me
[Music]
I think I'm supposed to go up high [\h__\h]
it's gonna kill me you see oh wait he
was supposed to run now
[Music]
oh God okay
you can just go alone why doesn't
it oh oh okay okay
is there time limit
get out there
[Music]
okay got it
where do we go we go
go go go go go go
why
okay he seems very busy over there good
[Music]
and yeah thank you for showing me
because I would be absolutely
[Music]
come on
you may cry
[\h__\h]
please
unbelievable
[Music]
okay
[\h__\h]
help me
[Music]
ah grilled pork chops
of course
life's so so warm and friendly
[Music]
yeah
yeah is he really dead like I wouldn't I
wouldn't really rely on it but hopefully
dead for good
is that like a boss fight for this
chapter I wonder
oh one more blue
[Music]
okay
this cremated I don't know man maybe he
has some Phoenix blood in his body
then being ashes wouldn't stop him
we don't know
uh I got an achievement so that seems
the end of it
[Music]
I'm gonna achievement so is there no
more Danger
accent
please
don't trouble please yes
always exit through the window on the
right side
chapter done
how many chapters are there like how
many chapters do I have left
[Music]
the free complete that was free
two more
behind
let's do this tomorrow last one is short
okay cool we've been four hours now hold
back well probably gonna need like five
and a half at least but
we'll finish it now we'll keep going
that there are like frustrating Parts
here and there but
it's got a brute force it and
never keep up what is happening over
there
what's going on
oh my God what's happening why they're
dumping dead bodies
yeah but you know what I wanted to read
super chats but even if we can't read
them today I said I'm gonna do a
chatting stream right to catch up and do
stuff like that
and we can reach Super Chat there too
and then we have a couple
all out
because I'm Gonna Leave
we'll follow
I guess we're following
let's follow the danger
I guess the TV was on but it's not on
anymore
you worrying about him don't worry he's
dead
yeah I know I what do you guys think was
running on the TV that made him so mad
what could it be
Big Brother
or
American
Britain's Got Talent or so
[Laughter]
how's the Dragon
no if anything it wasn't that wouldn't
that be rings of power because you guys
hate on rings of power all the time
or cats
foreign
[Music]
we had a school
in the hospital
is this the actual Asylum
oh normal apartment I guess
foreign
sorry
do they have a PC enough
for some playing games
sounds like they're playing games
nice
okay I don't play games in my bathtub
but
sometimes I will watch some shows on my
iPad
damn that's next level
do you guys play games while you're in
the bathtub
maybe with the steam deck on a switch
herself
um
oh
that was her
neither
well this apartment building needs
renovation
stylish elegant classic elevated oil
like you'll have a bathtub
not bathtub but I like never used it I
always shower so
I think it's okay oh
what
huh
oh no we don't know her
foreign
[Music]
retrieve her later
you say it as if she's an object wait is
this not actually the right path
girl can you
why am I supposed to be left I thought
that's where I came from
a wall jump ah
am I [\h__\h] Mario what
I don't know okay
now now you're thinking with wall jumps
right side
oh
what what
mom mommy yeah
[Music]
what I thought it was like it's so dark
it looks like there's a hole oh I did
that's a hole isn't it a hole
left or is the left side
[Music]
I had to reach the hole
pop
was there an apartment over there the
hallway
ah okay
yo she can obviously fit through that
gate
okay I will get you the key you just
stay here this is just a [\h__\h] excuse
for you to make me do all the work isn't
it
because you're scared but guess what I'm
scared too
if we were together both of us would be
less scared you know
[Music]
well okay you just make me suffer all
right all right you're selfish little
Beach
why am I up here
well
I don't see anything there
she need to draw
which one
[Music]
hahaha
oh
had to be something in this room
my fingers my hands are exhausted so
much so much tension
I finished this game even though it was
frustrating I want
I want Head Pants even though I hate
them you know what I don't want hat pads
I take it back I want I want some kind
of like reward nice words
be nice to me
where are we going
can I jump here no
you know what the [\h__\h] help me
help me
what
Pro me
I guess not
what
are we going to the elevator again
oh wait no never mind
[Music]
what happens
does it just make me go further down
[Music]
I'm gonna chill there again huh nope
how
how much well just the same way oh
we had more options
what did that what the pressing that do
I don't even hear any sound
brings it up
but can I eat
[Music]
now we bring it up and not right away
but when it gets closer to us we jump on
top of it
we jumped now we might die
and here it goes
okay nice
did you guys watch these shoes
I watched it so I had some YouTube
problems too when I was watching
for part of it
what is that watch tower over there
Sauron is this you
a little bit yeah it's like a cyberpunk
the background was sick you know
I like her hairstyle her hairstyle
[Music]
I'm excited to see the others who's
tomorrow
you'll be right yeah first silhouette
looks so princess-like doesn't it what
are those oh bats they're the bats that
looks like a mouse
yeah it looks like twin tails
long fluffy twin tails
door is open
you coming or not
I guess there's nothing else in here
you're kneeling
am I your queen
well if that's not the path then what
yeah
yeah I mean you guys kind of like after
a while it kind of stopped demanding it
anyway so that was nice thank you
can I climb up here I wonder
oh yeah it's okay cool
uh-huh
this one's for Halloween well that's
fine it works It's a Spooky game
is spooky game
it's all the same we'll be game
can you help me here
yep
a little bit faster next time please
we're playing this way
what
wrong way
sorry this is fun looks fun
do I go too
oh no okay you wanna
reach reach out your handle at this kind
of dangerous but okay
[Music]
yeah
cute
me
myself no this is
okay you know what how about
Fatal Frame bottles if this doesn't
count I don't know for whatever [\h__\h]
reason you guys say it doesn't count
makes no sense
um I requested a Fatal Frame like the
new one but if it doesn't make it in
time then we can play the old one
because apparently we have like uh
PlayStation
cool or free
like it's the same title as the new one
so I was like a little bit confused but
there's like a little little title
missing like a subtitle so I guess
that's what makes the new one a remake
or so
is it a remake
so if possible I would like to play the
new version yeah made another black
water
uh and we have permission for some old
Fatal Frame
yeah actually no we have permission for
two final frames two old ones but just
not the newest one
I think I think I think
yeah there's a there's a pretty girl
there
you guys recommended it because of the
pretty girl
Pokemon Snap but it's kind of
slow it wasn't interesting to me to be
honest
taking photos of something I hope
there's more to say no frame than that
oh yes oh [\h__\h]
I cut it open all right we'll do it
again
[Music]
not sure what to do here oh that was
okay
for a moment I thought we were supposed
to fall down
wait we are yes of course we are
she dead
now he's gonna be dead she's a
protagonist hi hi
[Music]
confusing action
yeah well we have a we have another
story to tell with you so don't die yet
it happened already but it's the future
um I know it's confusing it's the past
and the future at the same time because
the game came out in the past but it's
happening in the future so yeah I know
it's confusing girl but when you have to
stay alive
become a God or something like that and
eat your mom
I think
oh more of those eyes that's a soured
eye
[Music]
I remember this
they're all drawing the song Sauron eye
is that
Ah that's not the same like you know
Mommy
that's like watching them same as we
killed in the first game right
and we just don't get to kill her this
game who knows
[Music]
for mommy this one daddy sorry
Sauron let me drink some water
oh
mm-hmm
what am I doing here
what is we doing
gonna speed run this game now
just watch watch and learn
oh touch
[Music]
oh
enter chapter
yeah yeah a bit faster come on we've
done this a couple times
touch hats
[Music]
foreign
oh
are you coming to join us
[Music]
okay okay let's go
because at least his design is like way
less creepy than all the other ones
it's still you go here okay does that
feel a little bit like
when you wear the ring a lot of the
Rings oh
he's still here I thought it disappeared
because the mold was kind of
what's going on
scripted very much stupid no
no
how she was
for the other game
she got scouted in this apartment block
oh
she's gone forever now isn't she
[Music]
oh that the Scout decided
he will know
good for her I think she's gonna get
really famous with that role and there's
a bright future waiting ahead of her
where she'll become literally God so
oh interesting
[Applause]
[Music]
unfortunate
yeah this is exactly how I got into
whole life
a big scary man in the suit
just grab me
no
could have been Yago but no
um
that's on it
[Laughter]
okay wow origin story no I did not get
scouted like that I actually auditioned
so
haha
playing twice if you need help no I'm
good I am just like six Chun I am
becoming God eventually I'm sure of it
it will be worth it
oh we're traveling for all those TVs now
[Music]
um
and then maybe can we go for the door
so that I can teleport for the same TV
again
[Music]
well well well now you're thinking of
portals yeah
what
what are you doing ah
sweat I always like have the joystick
upwards
nosy
[Music]
I'm ever gonna meet her again and when
we meet her is she gonna be like famous
and not really care about us anymore
she's gonna be like a diva
am I gonna be like yo can I have a [\h__\h]
hologram
[Music]
now you always wear my ooshy
look
yeah we're just a side character even in
this story
this is just the point of view of the
side character
you can never be the protagonist live
this one is not long so I can't use it
right
[Music]
what
is going on I have to like push down the
TV from the top or so
it's fun oh
ah
what's tuning
[Music]
let's go
there's a camera
[Music]
does it just always teleport to the
closest TV
[Music]
okay we need something to step on so
that we can actually touch the TV here
do I have the remote forever no
oh
fun how fun how about that one was
useless for now
where's the horror where is the scary
[\h__\h]
oh
turn you on
first why is there this hole
huh there's a little ghost friend
[\h__\h] of being alone
yeah should I have gone for a TV first
would the TV have led me to a ghost
oh
wait
yeah it's a hat aha
I I I knew there was two paths one of
them must lead to a secret
it's not the secret that I thought I
would get
more scary pie is already over yeah
yeah I'm so happy to hear that
ah
is Fatal Frame really scary though I
wonder if that's gonna feel scary to me
the thing that I have to move
oh it seems so as a plot I see okay
so I teleport back I come back here and
jump over this thing
for you most definitely
I'm so excited
yeah
fine I wonder how long the pen is
because I didn't look that up
[Music]
I might not even finish
one for hours
maybe if it's too scary I can
get some mental support
do it for the pretty girl
well why don't you already have me
am I not enough huh
all right can we land on it
yes perfect
oh it's gonna be so salty
so salty
vertical Labs you like those kind of
streams where there's a horror game
going on and one one girl is being
supported mentally
ah everyone is like Fox killed by the TV
isn't like some kind of magic propaganda
[Music]
and what if I turn it off
foreign
[Music]
I'm like really mad right now because
they were not on a break
oh okay I turned that one on
I'll turn the other one off
yeah but then how do I
I still on
yeah
oh she's still there
I left it on for you
I need that
verbatim said she needed to break what
I have a very short time when I can ask
to be
um
let's just go there faster
that wouldn't work
[Music]
why doesn't she go to the other TV
turn it off
if I turn it off
go to the other one
now
I thought I had to teleport it
well let's see
and then before she arrives at the next
city I have to okay okay that's what you
meant with there's a short time window
done nothing
Maybe
[Music]
on the TV now
look that's a weird place for the TV
outside I don't think the water is any
good for the electricity
maybe put it inside
your kitchen just just not buy something
you have to listen to me I'm obviously
not the smartest person in the room
this is supposed to teach us something
about Society
what was the other game supposed to
teach us
if we're eating too much or something
like that over consuming confirmation of
food
oh that was easy
oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
what
good
I don't know eating something eating too
much fast food right yeah
so I wonder what this one's about
friendship magical friendship
um
teamwork
would be like easy guesses but I don't
think that's really the deep meaning
maybe maybe the fact that we should stop
watching TV
hey are you what's that
[Music]
where am I okay
I think today is fine
I'm getting free will you please help us
find out yeah
they surely would be able to help us
[Music]
let's go here
yes yes oh
is he going to jump
one day oh are they all going to jump
oh
that one is calling his Warriors
oh what about the rest hey
[Music]
I don't want to become one of those
me
it's all right
what and we're just gonna fall down if
we teleport for that
I'll push huh
easy thinking
of course not of course not
in fact
what what
a statement of unhealthy media
consumption well maybe in this chapter
yeah but what about the other chapters
we'll take the other chapters teach us
Chuck school stuff
oh
[Music]
um
sucks the world sucks
adults adults suck
so much
am I not supposed um you're not supposed
to turn it on on the way back when
someone's following me
who's there though
he did
what
what when did I die
I still killed okay I I thought it was
too close
all right one more
double kill
[Music]
not faster
good
all right turn it on
easy
you can pull a deeper meaning out of
almost everything
yeah I guess so
I guess so
open for interpretation
before we go let's see what is here
oh
huh
[Applause]
should I have used the TV
would it have even
brought me anywhere
is this
a post office no maybe not
it was just an apartment that received a
lot of packages and never opened them
wait the TV is here
[Music]
nice package
don't worry I get it I get it
yo I got so many packages from Valkyrie
it was like they came at the same time
as the you know the thing from cover
I think it was five packages in total
and I
the erotic thing is I have to pay
um
taxes for
or something extra that I bought in
order from Japan you know the thing that
Jen might help me with
uh
this is for any of the other things that
in value in total were much more
expensive I understand how they judge
that they came at the same time all of
them
they all came from Japan
and yet I only think I only paid taxes
um
um at the arrival
for the
uh
the one thing that I bought myself
they were gifts
I guess if they declare those gifts but
I think I've had things been declared as
gift before and I still had to pay it
for some reason
because I didn't believe it or whatever
uh
medium floor
what
ah I never mind there I didn't see it
jump onto me first and then
foreign
[Music]
or something
am I even going I want to get out here
but I guess now the door's closed
I well here it opens
leather than warp to top
okay
[Music]
some design
he took so much time to get back on his
feet
that little [\h__\h]
can I just
do the same thing here
do it when it's going down
a couch
good job
oh okay
why was I so desperate to jump for the
first hole
no one will know
but we're here okay
there's a bit of a pain in the ass but
cheerio
oh creepy doll
hi
eat
I miss my friend
I'll miss my friend Tomodachi
[Music]
maybe she's on TV right now
maybe that's what we're watching
okay so we have to get up on this like
platform
um
[Music]
isn't there water in there too
yeah
slippery slow
streams box
[Music]
maybe maybe I don't have to jump on the
sink
I
think what are we doing here
don't have to bother with her yet
probably
[Music]
the bathroom
oh probably
and then
I jump on the bathtub probably
okay then why electrocution
any faster than this maybe I can turn it
off from more of a distance though
not the bathtub
well the sink I don't know if I can make
a joke I think the bathtub is fine but
toilet what's on the toilet
you want me to raise a toilet oh I
wonder if we can
[Music]
I jump from here too then
electricity is dead too so
we can jump around all we want now
oh TV broken but we need to stool I
think
she did she's already old that's okay
[Music]
we freed her
this is not a lie if you want to live
right I mean let's be real
foreign
[Music]
oh this feels like a style section
who are we stealthing away from
oh maybe not yet
oh
what's these
well we have this car are we pushing it
down I guess so
push and push
yes oh
no my mommy would never let me sit
inside the cart when I was a baboon
I mean okay maybe as a baby but if a
child not really anymore
and I'm still to this day real [\h__\h] at
controlling these cards
as we're staying in Supermarket treats
before
and go wherever they want
yeah
realize that okay once again on top of
it they realize the electricity was
dabbing around here too you're streaming
Sparks everywhere oh my God
[Music]
so I get on right before
foreign
on top of it
maybe I just let it roll down on its own
and then later on I jump on it
maybe maybe
you go alone
okay
it's magically rolling into the exact
spot that I lost well that's a bit
ridiculous but okay
no no no
but it is
on that floor says it looks pretty safe
right but
I think I need to go outside
because this looks kind of too tall
mm-hmm
so we have to get in there from the
other side oh
the same kind of animals everyone's got
the same plushies huh
this this cannot be so easy it must be
someone
living here
I wonder can I move the chair
I wonder if we can get outside the
window and there's a secret or so
but I don't care
huh okay
that was so easy
why is this part so easy
electricity off right is it is there a
timer or
quit quit I think I need this box
or the shopping cart
oh we're having a lag now
is it EU now and then it's fine or what
what
time today
YouTube
I'm being so mean
oh wait ah this time I placed in the
middle here huh
let me turn it around
I wonder am I doing it right
or am I overthinking it
go from here and then on the cards
ideally
whoa
okay
and now
this obviously doesn't work anymore so
why did we come here
are you
what turn on the electricity again but
how
my computer
let me check it out again
if I were to turn it back on can I jump
over to that side
from there
possibly
[Applause]
should be the way to go
yeah
oopsie
there's been issues all day and select
parts of the world but I've been told
that it's only my stream but I had
problems today too so maybe it's just
selection streams and selected areas but
I wonder if the problem would have been
solved if I made a new stream I just
don't normally like to do that because
it's kind of metal side
oh and now
don't [\h__\h] up the jump because then I
think I have to do it all over again
maybe
okay first to the right side
[Music]
where are we going
come on
open door or open window
[Music]
oh hi everybody oh they wanna go to the
TV
[Music]
turn on the TV now no it's my turn
they don't care about me huh dude
what if I turn this one on
what if I turn them all on
connected to the electricity
or are they
I feel like it's telling me to do it but
what do I do then
oh
so what now what now
ah and turn the other one off and then
you're gonna go there
and then ah since they can't enter
that's gonna be good
but can you please ignore me though
what if they're coming for me
[Music]
I'm gonna turn this one on
it
suddenly they have the power to come
through oh yeah
okay now it's getting Lively now we have
an audience
I'm not scared anymore
on the on the edge of the joystick like
almost falling off you know what I mean
okay I have enjoyed
yay
my rail doesn't want to turn on off off
Eurovision
oh why would you do that now why would
you turn up your revision now to be
honest I've never watched
your original life except once I think
nowadays I don't have TV with live TV
anymore but I think you can watch it
online
think
oh oh friend hey
how's it going in your new job huh you
like it they have um like lots of
subscribers and stuff
you like it you wanna end it that's so
bad it's really comfortable job at least
for me if we do like oh I don't really
have to push inwards
oh my God
[Music]
what should we do
oh okay uh uh which way
I don't really see a path but he acts
it's too late it's late it's late
okay now I saw it
let's have to do it again
wait see now it's not here yet I guess
it falls down from the shock there it is
that's why I didn't realize it it wasn't
there from the start
[Music]
okay cute
oh [\h__\h] I [\h__\h] up
I did it too early like one one
millimeter closer and a little bit fun
the door
well I thought that was supposed to
fight him okay
foreign
[Music]
ah
go faster oh he's so kind to wait so
friendly
are we done
are we
as if we are I'm [\h__\h] up now because
apparently I can't [\h__\h] climb
cool
hate the climbing mechanic
all right
second to last right
because this seems to be just the final
boss so oh hi
feels like this is it
go away
Google
[Music]
oh
I'm so motivated
motivated to finish this
game
could have also played both games which
one do you prefer
like my little nightmares one or two
where the [\h__\h] am I supposed to go
just take some moments to realize that
so
two really
[Music]
let's go let it go oh
also wait once I'm up there I still have
to
uh push pull out the the wood but okay
can we be faster
I like games where you can fight back so
too oh
I guess yeah fighting back was not quite
a thing
um
[Music]
where are we going
let's go escape
everything takes as long as it needs
um
true yeah
and I drink
oh
foreign
make one tiny mistake
[Music]
I'm okay
I respect that
I like these kind of suitcases I have
one of those
you know not the modern ones they're
those old looking ones
it's not old though it's just had that
look but I've used it so much that it's
kind of like
falling apart
and also that one only has two rows two
wheels
didn't get to the thing right away like
I couldn't touch any music oh but
there's a okay check the point here
always only use four wheels because it
makes everything so much easier
sometimes I see people
there are suitcases even though they
have suitcases with four wheels
which confuses me because
um it literally takes no strength
if you just like
um like you know pull it with you on on
the side of you rather than pulling
behind you
know what I mean
that's why I get the four wheels one
because then like it takes absolutely
yeah one time I told someone
like why are you pushing it pulling it
and it has four wheels
that takes so much more strength and
then soon after I showed them they still
chose to pull it I don't understand
I don't understand I literally told them
a life hack that I thought everybody
knows
remote con broke
[Music]
Hi friend
oh don't go away
[Music]
um
you shouldn't do that like
you shouldn't play around on the tracks
don't do it
everybody don't do it okay don't don't
play on tracks don't play around on
tracks
dangerous
[Music]
money
even if you think it's safe it's not
safe dangerous another before it was fun
you'll think
you can get away with anything right
don't do that
I've heard of that story of the
three girls who took a selfie at a train
uh track and you know you can guess what
happened
do it again there we go okay
good then you apologize
I thought it was like
smashed by that thing
is this a new chapter
The Two Towers AKA only the one
I ain't got no power over you
I've got no power
what's happening
[Music]
this is Harry Potter am I supposed to do
something oh yes I am
um
never mind here I was able to do
something at least push against it
[Applause]
[Music]
cool fight like very cinematic
only with gloves
and even then kind of don't wanna kinda
creepy
how much is left of the game not much it
seems
hello
my stuff in the ground
falling down can I do something
I can't read your mind but I think it's
dead no can't be that easy is he up by
the tower
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go
oh is it bending
it's me
this time we can actually reach the door
properly
just pieces
my cars
all kinds of stuff where's my hat by the
way
[Music]
are you playing with me don't close
foreign
[Music]
this
gives me again Harry Potter verbs
no way
does that not give you Harry Potter
times Harry Potter vibes
what if I go back
[Music]
who's that that was a different kind of
feeling was it like Oh no you're wrong
is this a puzzle
thank you
Harry Potter
oh huh
[Music]
that was supposedly right
I understand though
here on the next one
okay that one
yeah we're just following the music now
[Music]
oh
there's not really much Choice oh there
we go
it's here
wait what about the door
[Music]
foreign
I think I'm supposed to jump from here
to the door handle
look at the floor
[Music]
well I know these over two are connected
but
I'm supposed to go for the one with the
music
[Music]
[Applause]
if I push it without going through you
mean
will it not reset
ah I think I have to go through kind of
open with oh wait
there I am
so confused
he was actually thinking so far that he
was really not supposed to go through
but just open it
smart boy
I did not expect that
kids
thinking with portals now faking the
door is toys
[Music]
hmm
hmm no oh oh God I didn't see that
hey yo wait is it that thing that's like
the plank
it looks so stable up there
okay can I push it
yeah okay
where's the music
I miss the music
hola
I didn't do that first because the music
is actually coming from over here but
I'll come out from there and then I'll
have to come back and if I didn't do the
plank then I'll have to go back and you
know you know it resets it and then I'm
[\h__\h] so it's good that I did this
first before going there
yeah because I come through here and
then go back yeah
[Music]
uh-huh I understand
foreign
[Music]
I have a brain and I'm using it
music is here
I think but kind of quiet
[Music]
oh the music
it's thought of a music box didn't it oh
look oh familiar
yours
because you were playing with it in the
beginning weren't you
grow a lot
you don't drink the shits on milk or
what
'd you get all that make from huh
can we share
oh she reacted
[Music]
you are actually going to follow me okay
I just you know
playing
[Music]
where are we going with this
you're not going any further huh you
were helping me to get up there uh
indirectly with that really [\h__\h]
really fast sorry
I thought I was supposed to climb up to
you
okay sorry maybe I'm supposed to climb
up something else
and then jump on you
or take the hammer
she's my friend oh sorry
I guess not your arm sorry that's the
music box sorry sorry sorry
breast didn't kill me at this point
[Music]
the first time hi
honey
oh [\h__\h] I think we're running away from
her nose it's probably mad
isn't she
music
[Music]
should I go that door is there a wrong
door too here oh [\h__\h] that was too slow
[Music]
every [\h__\h] second house
of it
[Music]
like me
you want to put your like reset your
thumb's position hiding
[Music]
go a little bit for one second
even that one tiny baby second is too
much
staying here forever
you get what I mean thank you after all
y'all our game is right you'll get the
gamer problems you get it
she knows I can't open doors like this
on my own like the other one where she
went through
no
I've only been under the table oh hello
why am I why am I following you
know why am I
following you you're still protecting
the music box
[Music]
um
what's up with this door
how can we make use of this
follow me
you gonna follow me no
oh
the [\h__\h] out
[Music]
so when I when I call her here
and maybe I can leave the ax closer
though
I'm like
here
bro and then she comes
I have to take this for a moment but
hahaha
I hesitated for one second but that's
how we do it I think
somebody maybe I can get the X even
closer
let's do it like this way
that kills me okay I maybe should not
get hit before it didn't kill me you
know in the beginning now she's really
impressive with those noodle arms man
just keep the ax
um all right come on
again but I think this could be okay
this could be it
[Music]
gold
you're getting up
what now I'm hungry
a little hungry
[\h__\h]
she's your one and only fat
why monster fight like this huh
which portal leads to which one
if I could make it but the moment I go
there
crap
[Applause]
so maybe
from the other side because this here at
least the platform is easy to get up to
it's kind of different
huh
yeah quick thinking quick thinking about
you
oh we're still not done hmm
other side baby
hello
hi oh I'm supposed to call him oh [\h__\h]
did she hear me
do I do the same thing
no I'm gonna cry like where's my where's
my where's my ax
oh wait what is it there
[Music]
first
um
if I run grab the ax
is
okay
[Music]
okay I get it so
Paul we're here
[Music]
so basically same thing right call her
here and go to the other side
uh we go up call her there go for the
other side
absolutely but now it's not so easy
anymore
one on the other side is either but at
this point yeah okay if I just run there
[Applause]
other side is easier now
jump though so can I actually like walk
up there or
hmm foreign
[Music]
guys
I was pressing the a button no but okay
we got the system
got the system down
testing since I was like we're already
here so oh man
[Music]
okay
and then the last one
felt like the last one
at least then put this pattern
[Music]
all right listen you little [\h__\h]
listen to me right now
listen to your friends I bless you for
this whole game I'm the reason you were
scouted the whole life
won't be such an ungrateful little [\h__\h]
now okay
[Music]
it's gonna
um push the call button because first
she was um
she was like
um
and I did that but I have to do it when
I'm closer
[Music]
surroundings
one more time
[Music]
I'm sorry
and we still be friends I'm your friend
I didn't because I'm your friend
really
I'm sorry
oh you're together oh God
oh [\h__\h] I [\h__\h] up and this is probably
not it
is
I don't normally make sense if I die in
this game
thank you
still here
so slow but this makes sense yeah
over there it makes sense
okay first I jump in the front and then
I jump in the back
all right
so I think
maybe I'm supposed to do the front after
all but yeah
hold on just keep on going
okay that was good that was small
foreign
follow her but then you get crushed by
the slime like that
oh I think I'm supposed to wait a little
bit there
hello
[Music]
the weather you make me so angry
if you don't make me perfectly happy
I'm gonna flip
okay
I think I jump normally okay okay
anyone would ever do this first try on
blind playthrough
advice say character-wise
whoa
whoa no she's already
did you drink like a speed potion
why do I fall down there now
this is an online game someone's playing
her right now
[\h__\h] swallow me
this is more like on the eye not the the
part right left
I'm gonna Escape
runs
it does not forget anyway
[Music]
him waiting so long for that
oh
she didn't do it there I would have been
so mad
you're gonna let go
you're not gonna why would you let go
[Music]
what did I do to you
I mean I knew I was gonna die I kind of
felt that
but not like this
remember your hands just because you're
[\h__\h] addicted to the TV
she's still full because of the music
box
[Music]
no she was not so no that was big big
six
what
what no that makes no sense I broke her
music box already in the beginning of
the game
and then she would have had so many
chance to kill me like why would she
have helped me
she's just mad while she's in big for
him wait oh
what wait
I'm alive
I don't think she can't be that evil
like right now because like she's not
normal she's good in the next game
huh
chair
what
big reveal
am I the evil one for the next
game that was the game that already
existed
well I'm becoming a big Slender Man
next time
[Music]
foreign
I am very slender
and I grow up a bit more
[Music]
that looks like him
kind of could be him
[Music]
how could I fight him then
this is like a tunic kind of thing
well it's not quite the same person but
kind of like takes over the world
came up because she's evil
there we go our final form isn't it
oh no that's the final world now we have
the Hat that's why that's why I was
going for so many hats in this game it's
about the Hat
is what makes
you who's evil look at me I'm not kind
of evil
[Music]
don't I
wasn't even one
the hat is controlling me
should have kept on the paper bag would
have controlled my evilness
the Trap because at that moment you
recognize me
I I can get behind the fact that I was
the evil one
of the chance that she's the evil one
so but then
we didn't break the loop so
how does this connect to the the second
game the first game
[Music]
we just ignored us the six just ignored
this whole thing she's like ah whatever
whatever
she just she just moves on
DLC
huh
the DLC of this game
you need the other ending to see
if anything explains ah you know what
I'm watching on YouTube
yeah I never played the first DLC that's
true
oh wow
I think I preferred the first game more
to be honest
oh most of you guys said you prefer the
second one but I think like judging by
how I felt after the first one I think I
enjoyed the first one more
it's hard to like remember because it's
a long time ago
maybe it's just because the first time
it was more special the whole like World
Vibe and atmosphere
that could be too that it's just like a
it had this novel novelty that was what
it's called
I enjoyed the first one more too
[Music]
which one was scary this one had a sad
story
yeah I think I was
married in the first one and more
stressed out
but like the the whole like reveal like
around the end like you know all the
eating
oh this comes extremely creepy and made
for quite the atmosphere
I like being stressed out no that's all
I mean but I think I did a better job at
being you know the kind of game it is
Maybe
[Music]
become what they fear most and continue
to cycle oh
[Music]
repetitive it felt
but this one I guess I mean that was
okay
um I think I would have had a hard time
figuring out the whole like order of
like
without you guys without you guys I
would have probably had more of a
problem in that like smashed the music
box battle
maybe I don't know how to tell
yeah the Geisha was spooky
this guy's Wicked
[Music]
well I mean in the end both are very
interesting games
aren't they cool games actually I got
some recommendations for quite similar
games
um that looks really great but just
because they do feel so similar to me
I'm not planning on playing them anytime
soon
um I forgot what they were called oh
yeah inside a limbo yes yes yes yes like
I looked at them and like it's the same
kind of like
like you go from like sideways and you
know you do similar stuff you know they
look really cool and they got good
reviews and all that I see that but if I
play it then not like now another time
maybe
[Music]
they seem to belong together because
Steve had a bundle but you could find
limbo and inside but one of them was
like way more popular or somehow
um
I think that's probably a limbo
uh-huh
so many of you guys know that one huh
made by same people that's what I
thought Lima was a breakout hit oh
but I guess a lot of you played it right
don't you agree with me that like I only
looked at like some screenshots and
videos but
it gave me like the same kind of vibe
don't you agree because you guys
actually played it so you can maybe tell
better
I
don't remember
good day
yeah the same genre
I'm gonna play the two
I don't remember now I don't remember
seeing that
[Music]
as a famous clip with limbo
yeah yeah but I think we don't need like
two games like this and in the same
Halloween week in a row right
um we're gonna have like a chitchat
stream we're gonna have a clip coming up
we're gonna have a song cover coming up
this week and then I'm thinking on the
31st Fatal Frame
baby
uh if I got the the perms in time for
the new one
then
this yes
[Music]
and besides that I'm not sure about this
wig besides of them kind of look still
mixed feelings
oh yeah right oh I forgot thank you for
reminding me out I did want to make a
rebroadcast of the karaoke
ah I forgot to put that in my schedule
thank you we broadcast karaoke
hmm
good very good
thank you genius
genius also is lagging because I tapped
out but
yeah it's all okay
Elena's dream oh yeah
that's
[Music]
more I haven't heard from her
when is it
Raina my name is John
Arena
oh
it should be tomorrow yeah
11 p.m oh
11 p.m Tuesday
after today
wait wait isn't Wednesday now or not
because it's one minute past midnight
and my schedule says it's Wednesday
which day is it it's Wednesday today was
Tuesday and now it's Wednesday right and
then okay so it's actually the day after
tomorrow okay good good because now I
was like realizing oh [\h__\h] if it's
really tomorrow like like you know you
know what would normally mean as
tomorrow and that would mean that it's
overlapping with my cleaning probably
that wouldn't be good but okay never
mind it's okay
it's Wednesday now officially but in
reality it's still Tuesday
and and the stream of Lena is on
Thursday so I think
um
if I stream tomorrow
nah I think I think what we're gonna do
roughly but don't rely on it because I'm
I'm taking the Liberty this week to like
you know move things around the way I
want the way I feel like it for a change
but my plan is uploading clip tomorrow
then Elena collab the day after tomorrow
and then we're gonna do chatting stream
[Music]
um
maybe Friday night maybe
maybe but as I said this could still
change
I don't know when my friends are coming
for dinner
um and then rebroadcast karaoke
every Saturday or Sunday
and there I might squeezing
let me just mansion
Maybe
I don't know I have to go through this
day by day I can't plan ahead this week
I don't know yeah and four blood
I wonder I don't wanna you know overlap
too much with other people's releases
but I don't know is anyone really
releasing anything
oh
I think so
um but I think if I upload it on Sunday
[Music]
um
Kelly has a song on Halloween well Cali
has a song always so it's kind of hard
to not overlap with her
she always has some release going on
it's hard not to overlap with something
and I know this is like like why I
didn't want to do something that aims
for Halloween because I knew something
was gonna happen on Halloween someone is
gonna aim for it and then
so maybe maybe I do it early because you
know everything's finished what if I do
it on what if I release it on
Friday night my night
yeah yeah I saw Saturday or like Sunday
Saturday to Sunday funa is doing
something releasing something
oh
I mean in the end it doesn't really
matter does it like you know
you can't
space it out too much I want to release
it too why do when do I have to you know
go around it
how about today yeah
oh
I'll think a little bit about it
um
now
you know
I like that Spirit of releasing it right
now but yeah
yeah oh
find a good timing
there ain't a song of Cobble
releasing something a song cover
do you know what it is
I haven't heard of that
hey y'all
on Google channel organic Channel
on Friday what are they what are they
releasing
you don't know what
oh I feel like they're like
top singers so top-notch singer so I'm
excited
I'm excited
to hear what it could be I wonder if
they're going for a cute song or a cool
song
this is even just you know en members ID
members who knows what the Japanese
members are releasing for Halloween
yeah this kind of like dates
everyone is doing something so generally
I don't want to aim for these special
dates anymore but
you know I also want to give you guys
something special for the special dates
but then I yeah
so much going on that's why I vote
sooner
you know the music video is finished but
I think I'm still like waiting for a
reply that it's like okayed by the
management you know
there should be no problem but just
waiting for that to be honest
I guess we could do it sooner than later
maybe Thursday night
I'll try Thursday night
okay
I'll try
hmm
I'm off
thank you for watching
[Music]
I am always talking about my time zone
when I talk about times you should know
that by now
and aim for later no another thing's
finished oh well not you're right what
the hell not hey oh my birthday it's
gonna be your birthday let's go
let's go
ah yeah after Arena Club I can like
yeah yeah yeah yeah
in in the Rainy Club talk about it I
think it was dream no thank you for
going through this game with me together
as always guys thanks for being so
supportive
of me struggling in these kind of games
it was okay and I was struggling
sometimes but I'm honestly gonna blame
it on the game
so exact and sometimes it's being weird
about certain things like no this no no
no no no no no no no no no no
I did much better than the first one
really
oh that would say in general like in
this one year I've improved with games a
little bit
also apparently I used keyboard last
time someone said that um last year I
used my keyboard and my mouse did I
really
did I really
you did much better than Google how is
that possible she finished way earlier
than me
that's not possible
I did I did use keyboard you didn't have
PS5 I didn't use PS5 now either but I
guess you mean because I have the PS5
controller well that wouldn't have
stopped me I would have had a different
controller probably
ah
especially cracked Minecraft
the ax puzzle
no I was faster that one I guess worse
at others yeah I feel like the first
half was
maybe a bit
rough
Maybe
um
oh well but yeah I think overall it was
was okay
it was fun decently fun cool game I like
games that I can finish in one stream
um
internet
but I also like games and I can make a
series out of who
ah you know one more thing I said I you
know a long time ago when everyone was
playing like uh
uh
[Music]
switch
the sports game what's it called
I said I don't want to do it because
it's meaningless in life to D
but maybe
if you know what arrives
yeah Wii Sports Nintendo Sports ring fit
that's the one
that's the one but oh it's gonna get
really sweaty that's gonna get really
sweaty
because you know that it's not like the
quality of uh like the the 3D
concert
that I did
so don't expect me to do like full on
concerts with that but
I'll see I'll see how good it looks if I
like dance um with it because I I do
want to at least use it for like dancing
a little bit maybe now I can you know
work on that takanasi Kiana Tick Tock
with like little dances but even if I do
it I can only use songs that we would be
able to sing in like archived catalog
streams for example as well
stuff that I can get rides too I'm not
I'm not allowed to use like you know
Tick Tock uh sounds that are unticked
out that everybody uses which you know
that's literally that's literally what
Tick Tock is but okay
yeah
that's literally what they talk is
no but there's like actually quite a lot
of like Vocaloid and anime songs that
have choreographies that I know so I was
thinking you know I could do like a
dance challenge or so if I remember like
Vocaloid choreographies from like 10
years ago
that one I will never get that one out
of my head never literally never
and that might be a little bit scarf
still
from what I've seen
when am I used it
because
um the one I got is the one that Anna
used on the stream sometimes
um
but yeah for a little bit of dancing it
should be okay and then another idea was
like maybe
um think you know coming up with a new
simple choreo for like a like a like a
myth song or so
um trampoline one um
perhaps it could have been that one
well uh I'm not sure
because she also has a bunch of
different ones
anyway
I'm coming up before Corey it would be
fun yeah but I don't know how I uh if
under pressure on the stream I'm like
able to do it because
even that little choreo I came up for
four blood and uh what's the other song
I forgot
um
that happened behind the scenes when I
was like you know
taking my time and like thinking I know
I don't know I feel like when I was when
when you guys would watch me on stream I
would get like nervous and embarrassed
about it and could not really like uh
unleash my full potential you know what
I mean ladylike yeah
I I would be like oh I want to do this
kind of move but what if it looks
awkward when I try when you guys will
listen
would be really embarrassed it's like
like dancing in a disco everybody's
watching that's why I don't go to those
kind of places like Freestyle oh no no
no if it's already a choreography that's
already like set in stone no problem but
I don't know embarrassing
embarrassing yeah
but
um I don't know at least the dance
challenge I want to do and then we'll
think about more like ring fit hey
no need to be embarrassed oh no
definitely need to be embarrassed
oh can we get a digital girl cover oh
I mean like a proper one like I'm doing
with four blood
I don't know like I'm already planning
for the next song cover and I don't know
that's that's the last song cover I want
to do for a while because I need to
focus on the album so
um for now I don't think so and I
already did like song cover with Ina and
Emma before I wanna
um if I do more sound coverage I want to
do it with people who I haven't done
anything with before
you know because I've we all got limited
time and I want to make use of the time
because making new sound covers like
takes like three months or so like
planning getting the artwork recording
mixing getting the music video done and
so on
so
thinking that way there's a like a
maximum amount of sound covers I could
do from my own planning in a year
uh
um yeah because of that I mean it can
work faster I guess if you like push
really hard or were able to do some of
the things yourself like the music video
yourself and don't have to Outsource it
I don't know but generally like as a as
a general
um guideline
I feel like mostly it takes like two to
three months
[Music]
um
yeah ID members yeah yeah
maybe even Japan members
my favorite one was when you knew there
was a trap in this button you still
watching this rap
Ed
to test it out just I'm an Entertainer
it's
for entertainment value
yeah
[Music]
okay
um
so yeah thanks guys for watching today
I'm gonna try to cook now as fast as
possible because I am hungry as hell
I've been cooking so much recently like
uh you know how I had that trauma after
that incident
I didn't want to cook and I was staying
away from it for a while but recently
I've been cooking a lot
yeah
I'm actually
uh
cooking the last recipe from the
previous week or yeah
now and then oh yeah I did all three
recipes for the week
there's a secret ending yeah there is
but I'm just gonna watch it on YouTube
yeah yeah I liberated myself from the
trauma
um I did I was so scared for stupid
reasons but
I mean you know
sometimes we humans be stupid or we
chickens or we Phoenix's
so I'm gonna make something weird maybe
you'll see it on Twitter later
making something fancy
seems to be vegetarian
hello fresh you're kind of forced to
cook yeah unless I wanna like waste
endless amounts of food but even when I
don't try to waste like the recipe I'm
making today
um you know I put the bag in the fridge
after it arrived but okay I I mean you
know there's things you have to put into
the fridge immediately and then there's
the other bags that are supposedly fine
without being put into the fridge at
least for one or two days
um and then I put those bags that don't
necessarily need to be cooled into the
fridge I guess one or two days
after it arrived but I mean that still
should be fine because what was inside
was not necessarily something you have
to
um normally you know put in the fridge
but but when I open it to like start
cooking it I saw that the
the the
cucumber in there there was a cucumber
in there and some stuff it was like a
you know they come in these these paper
bags the brown paper bags and they put
the stuff in there and inside was on the
bottom was the the cucumber and when I
lifted some stuff off of the Cucumber I
saw
like it had like Cuts weird cuts from
whatever was on top of it
like the Cucumber still looks like kind
of fine
but it was kind of damaged by the other
things so I had to buy a new one
now that's why I'm making it now not
earlier
um
yeah I'm just kind of lazy because the
the boxes they arrive really late at
night and then going for everything one
by one checking if every ingredient is
fine I normally don't do that but I'm
also after so many times that something
was like
um
uh I don't know broken or ewe I I guess
I have to start looking for everything
and documents everything but even then
I'm like too lazy to report it and be
like hey give me money back or or give
me more whatever
oh that's it by the way we watched all
the credits and it's so lagging because
I'm not in the same tab
what the Tekken was in this game yeah
something about Tekken what was that
a great after credits scene
sorry
sorry I can't offer you that
sorry sorry
uh
okay I'll go cook now thank you guys for
watching me playing spoopy little
nightmares too
and was fun I wish you all a nice
evening
and in German we say
tomorrow clip little clip coming up but
besides that I think I'll be chilling
and cleaning my apartment because I feel
like I need to pre-clean before the lady
comes the cleaning lady
I'm ashamed of the mess
would you guys pre-clean tool if you had
someone come over to clean your
apartment
would you pre-clean too
or would you just leave the mess the way
it is
nah yes no yes depends
I don't want to pre-clean too much
honestly yes yes okay some of you get me
but why why tell me what tell me why do
you feel like pre-cleaning tell me why
don't you leave it all to the lady
I is it because
remove anything shameful what shameful
things do you have to remove I'm ashamed
of myself understandable me too
we hide the shame right and yeah make it
easier for them to clean it's like when
when you get furniture delivered or so
and you know they would move it to the
spot where you wanted that so you have
to remove the things that are there at
that moment
because they won't do it
okay here we go tangent I remember lying
for example when I had a internet
installed somewhere uh uh and I didn't
know like the internet guy would come
but I didn't know like where exactly was
the point that he needed to go to
and then I was like oh wait maybe it's
here behind this big [\h__\h] table and
he's like yeah yeah you you move it
because I'm you know it's not my job to
move it but it's literally like I'm I'm
awake [\h__\h] little girl okay versus
him like a 45 year old strong normal
dude
okay I was able to move it myself just
okay it was heavy but and I understand
that you know you don't feel like
helping out generally if it's like too
much but I feel like it's kind of like
courtesy polite to help me when I'm like
living alone as a small girl
you probably had no insurance or you
mean what if if he would break his body
doing it I don't know even even then
even then I feel like it would be nice
to help a little bit break the table how
can you break it when you're just moving
a little bit
[Music]
I don't know I feel like I don't really
think about that but there you go this
is another example where you would like
pre-clean not really pre-cleaning but
pre-moving something for someone else to
do their job properly so that's why I
have to start uh cleaning already now
because I have all the valkyrie connect
gifts
opened up and scattered around
um because I actually made a video I was
thinking I don't know do I make a video
do I do a live stream or do I take
photos and so on and then I asked
General Gemma can I do like a live
stream haul and she was like uh make
photos and then show me but then I was
like ah but I want like to have like
this first opening impression when I
take photos then I already you know have
the first impression when I take the
photo and that's kind of lost there so I
was like okay just in case you know what
I'm gonna take a video now so I I took a
video with my phone where I was
introducing everything I was wearing the
gloves and all
and then after taking the whole video it
took like 25 minutes or so I was like
you know what this was kind of lame I
don't think I'll be using this so I took
photos of everything had everything
unpacked now it's all here scattered in
the room
and now I decided that I don't want to
use the video so I'm going to take
photos I did and then I'll show it to
you and we'll talk a little bit about it
but I'm not gonna do a whole stream
about it because I feel like that's yeah
but at least want to show you what I got
because there's some cool stuff
surprisingly
um yeah
yeah
yeah yeah
no I'm not gonna tweet it it's way too
much
it's way too many things
um
what do I see there Mr ayamachi I feel
like it changed your name
indecisive no I just want to have all my
bases covered just in case
um you know because Gemma wanted to see
the pictures before to check them and I
was like okay I can take pictures
uh after I take the video
so that I can still
uh I have the First Reactions on the
video but I'll send her the the pictures
to check and the proof of everything of
the you know products that's okay to
show and I still can show the video with
my first reaction on stream later you
know what I mean it was big brain
thinking
yeah but now I'm like I don't like the
video
and I don't want to edit it either
so we're just gonna do photos
at least I took it so I I would not
regret it afterwards that I did not take
a video
because I feel like even though I ended
up not using the video
if I would have not taken the video at
all I would now regret that I didn't
take the video
just in case yeah just in case I have
the video now but I'm just not gonna use
it
I'm back YouTube interrupted for ads
ads unbelievable
and now I have no regrets exactly except
for wasting 25 minutes of my life on
taking that video
oh well
and in German we selfie that's in for
real now
so bye bye
bye
bye bye bye
thank you for me
see you
oh ah oh well I guess that's okay it's
cute
enjoy
[Music]