[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
though
[Music]
can you kid ding again
hello everybody
Welcome to the long-awaited off collab
between yeah me and
attention
[Music]
my name is
hello everyone okay
[Music]
um
we will try to get her to speak English
a little bit uh maybe
perfect English okay perfect English
okay
so I will explain what we're doing today
if you guys can see I mean okay it's a
perfect Birds POV so maybe it's hard to
tell but this is uh the block game
that's not Minecraft
um
[Music]
she says she's never played this game
before we'll call it a Blog game just in
case you know and I also think I maybe
played it only like once in my life also
was so kind to set this up as a
beautiful straight Tower
so we'll be playing this but also do you
guys
know this game
I don't know don't know
uh I think this is really common in
Europe yeah it's called Mikado
[Music]
so this is a stick game so we have block
game we have stick game I have a lot of
these sticks and we will explain how it
works later but I played this as a as a
child about correct this is
okay I haven't played in a long time so
honestly I don't know either anymore 100
and then we have
um I have Domino's
um
like any of these I wonder what she
played as a child
um
very cute yeah she said that it's
anti-slipping so it's actually she's
cheating okay perfect
I I explained to her that you know
there's two ways of playing it and I
don't really remember the the one that I
wanted to do but you know we'll play it
lasts and and
um well maybe just make a nice course in
and then you know that's nice too but
there's actually a different way of
playing it right with the numbers and
all that but I don't remember how that
goes yeah
honey
uh maybe here do you guys know this
it's a it's an ice block game yeah
another block game
I don't know
[Music]
so ah um
I feel like I used to play without the
clock but I guess the clock tells you
um what you're supposed to do
um
foreign
another Circle what is that Circle what
do you do when you get the circle
not the red circle the white circle does
anyone know nothing no the red circle is
nothing yes
okay okay yeah
okay this is
moisture
I have one more thing for this block
game
so uh
we have questions if I can ah
okay I'm trying to open my phone code
thingy with gloves it's very difficult
[Music]
I'll ask her for a number between 1 and
30 and then I have a list of questions
and she will answer me a question and
the opposite way too okay okay whose
last Child Is This
uh
cute no no no no no
beautiful eyes
what's going on foreign
taco
okay
five five five five
it's a good question the question is uh
what is the worst grade you ever
received in a class uh in school or
wherever yeah
foreign
she said she said she never got anything
worse than one two three but she's only
been to uh well
um
no no
please
from one to five I had all numbers
before in end in like uh yeah in school
like math and physics
foreign
it sounds like it's just too easy to get
a decent grade yeah
she says if she went to Junior High or
high school it would have probably been
different because she's just talking
about before Junior High yeah okay this
is not even worth talking about um
[Music]
oh easy easy I took the lowest one you
guys can see me and I is
yeah okay
um okay
come on 14 15.
oh no yes
what is the most embarrassing thing you
have posted on social media I don't know
if I remember anything
uh social media
um
[Music]
okay let's talk about streams
but but if it was so embarrassing why
did I post it right but I mean it is I
guess it should be embarrassing maybe I
know oh
no I know
um
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
live birth
do you um
she supports Julia so much I just told
her the throat story
what do you do you do you yeah I'm so
happy she likes to you know
[Music]
maybe one of my upcoming album songs
because I fix you freaking love it so
much she's so into do you and I think
she likes K-pop K-pop schedule yes
foreign
[Music]
what is the weird food that you love is
the question
um
foreign
oh my God you guys know ponzu which is
like really uh sour she likes to drink
that too and and just bite into lemon
um
so she says she likes some really strong
flavors oh my God yeah that's weird
okay
um
[Music]
let's go
do
how do I do this
I feel like up here it's like really at
the higher levels it's like like stuck
you can't get it out smoothly but the
bottom layer is is that normal that the
bottom layer is so much easier to take
out yeah
okay number
um how about
20 20.
[Music]
come on
it's boring it said what's your favorite
book of all time I don't even read books
so let's go next
28.
um
if you could pick one other player to
take a player Oh
to take with you to deserted island who
would be well that's like I think for
drinking games so let's just say another
whole life member to a dessert Island
um deserted Islands
[Applause]
foreign
um she can fillet a fish I don't know
how you say how you say it but she can
get rid of like the bones and all that
but no I go for Amelia Watson
I think Amelia's
survivors because right she seems like
the kind of person who has survival
skills
um
National Geographic
Ally
[Music]
okay
yeah
wants to take the one that's left in the
in the Box
[Music]
I'm about to channel the inner Gordon
Ramsay and say you
idiot
okay
um
uh seven seven
uh
[Music]
you make me feel like eleven okay
oh
[Music]
um
read it in English what terrible movie
or show is your guilty pleasure I know
um
[Music]
there's a Tel Aviv drama Tel Aviv
television drama that she watches that
is a really
scary
do you guys know something called aloe
ah
sorry
[Music]
like Marvel is more popular in Japan and
uh yeah she likes that show but it's not
popular in Japan at all I don't know if
it's actually like a bachelor oh it's
awful oh okay
foreign
[Music]
what was the one that I liked of the
lady hero the um
um the pretty one one of the more recent
ones you guys know what I'm talking
about
Wonder Woman
I have Wonder Woman's sandals flip-flops
yeah okay okay
guys next game
okay
we're gonna play this you guys
some good times
there's a penguin and it's supposed
that's supposed to be in the middle but
as you can see it likes to like just go
wherever it wants
um
foreign
I don't know what I'm doing today with
rock paper scissors I don't know what
I'm doing at all okay let's go I go
first
foreign
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] wait this is so cool ah I
really missed this what a genius baby
game
can I do it again or is she next does
anybody know
when I do it successful I think she's
next
I think it's her turn
this is the best baby game ever and this
is like baby games
let's go travel size
[Music]
yes yes she has to go for those three
foreign
do we move the penguin
okay okay
a long time ago which is for teenagers
and young children uh where there's like
a big version of this like life-size
version
um
okay okay so you have to see you next
hello
oh
Freddy
okay okay
let's go
thank you
[Music]
often from what I've seen even if you're
in such a situation go with like these
ones it actually often doesn't fall down
you know
oh
was that okay is that allowed things
happen when she gets more than she
should
already know
was that okay
yeah I think it's fine yeah yeah okay
okay
next up
oh
yeah
next time
[Music]
it's getting dangerous
let's go
I want to do one more time
[Music]
it was an easy win
yeah I I I I think I used to love this
game and also the one with the frogs is
that magnet inside
not frogs fish
[Music]
[Applause]
did you guys play this this game in
particular as a child too
but she just didn't play any games I
feel bad for her
thank you
she was reading books and playing
origami
um
foreign
she likes to read books and like she
would read history books not only
Japanese history books but also like
overseas history books and I was like
what kind of books and apparently like
Edison there was a series of books with
Edison uh featured you know the history
of Edison she's she should learn about
you know my favorite history
the tutors
to design for kids I don't worry about
it
she probably already watches a lot of
things that are not for kids right do
you do you what did I say do you
just in the middle of a sentence okay
let's go again first I started
oh oh baby game baby game
which one ah white one white okay
[Music]
okay no problem
um
hey
Evie
easy let's go
okay Bluetooth
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
oh yeah
oh
blue one come on
whoa she got the one she wanted nice too
perfect again
I'm just kind of scared to because my
gloves are pretty short when I tested I
saw my skin which are a lot that's why
I'm not I'm trying to not go too close
over there I know
yes I have skin oh my God unbelievable
all right
where should I go okay
foreign
thank you
[Music]
she got four
that is a problem
this is dangerous
is
can I push him back no come on
what
okay okay
next game good game
next game will play okay
this game I I need to look at the guide
while playing this because I don't
remember the all the numbers the points
by heart but we're playing
[Music]
this is traditional game from Europe
yeah
I thought
foreign
put it on
the first one was 20 points the second
one was two points this one is three
points 7.0
then there's red blue red red blue red
blue red oh red blue red blue red
foreign
you take these these sticks
um
[Music]
you just let it fall and then you try to
pick up uh everything without moving
other
sticks at least I mean are they not
allowed to move at all because that
seems really difficult with some of them
what do you know guys tell me help me
out here oh
comes in
um
I've read that
after
I read a system that you have to like
just uh throw it again each time but I
remember from my childhood that you just
keep on going going what do you guys
know
um
you keep going okay
until there's nothing left
I guess
um
[Music]
successfully you can take another one
right I think
I think
um
but I already know this it's really
difficult with gloves actually
oh
yeah sorry because she has cheating
gloves
it's hard mode
[Music]
is there a good way to do it because
that was lame
I think I think it said like do it like
[Music]
um
because like it has to be more gocha
gocha okay
oh
yeah
twist them first
twist what do you mean twist twist
how do you twist it
is
either
foreign
oh
yeah
yes okay okay
let's go I got one
um
there is no more like
um single ones
you guys can't even see that when we
jumped in a little bit but there's like
two over there
ah
what
um
it like barely moved but I feel like I
should already give up
um
oh yes yes
it's terrible with the gloves yeah you
sticks ah I think you're yeah weren't
you only allowed to use stickers help if
you have the the crazy one or can you
use any ah
okay you guys are saying
um
[Music]
that one was just laying free now okay
so the side the things that are off
camera are gone now and this is
one more one more
yeah very difficult
[Music]
thank you
if we fail too many times then I will
lose
[Music]
I know
it's so difficult
oh
come on
[Music]
yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes
[Music]
now baby yes okay
mmm
Skies
[Music]
can I use more than one stick guys or is
it only like one stick and one finger
Korea
hello
I have to like go be careful with the
camera
[Music]
two sticks okay
what about you know Japanese people
doing like Chopsticks you know they're
frozen chopsticks
um
yeah a little bit skin and spine if it's
if it doesn't show you know
um
oh
yeah
um
it's hard to grasp it with the gloves
they make our hands much thicker oh
uchino
's I forgive me Honda I don't know if
you guys saw but it moved a little bit
but I forgive
okay
if it's too easy I would say no
[Applause]
um
[Music]
let's let's try I think I'm going for
the same one but I will use one one
stick
s
technique
[Music]
that's good points time
okay okay here we go here we go
oh
wow
as long as the others don't move it
doesn't matter
[Music]
come on
but I got one right that was my
um
[Music]
yes I forgive
Italian
oh my God
look at us we're good
yeah oh man not pretend having a hard
time getting some points yo it's so
intense scanned by physics yeah
[Music]
you could
happen
huh
I will forgive myself also a few times
okay
um
without moving the upper ones nice one
thank you thank you
oh
I gave her the next time
commissioner
[Music]
um
[Applause]
yeah I think you know if it weren't for
the camera and the gloves and everything
I would like I wouldn't have to be so
careful and then I would go closer and
turn around the table and all that and I
would you know I think it would be
easier but we can't do that so
boom
there's a couple over here that you can
see that are easy to change
it
yeah
there's some blocks over there
move chat oh
foreign
[Music]
yeah
she has to be careful with her with her
clothes me too but it's so difficult
it
shouldn't have moved because it was such
an easy one
the one
yeah there's one more easy one
um
yeah it's difficult from here right now
yeah there's no more like free
standing ones
[Music]
she's worried that it will like fall
down over to myself
you're done
[Music]
okay look at it
mama
[Music]
no
no oh
yeah
it might be easier but everything's
gonna move
um
I have one more
but how do you know you did not move you
all held your breath
that one is a big one I want that one
yeah
you know often it's better to just go
really fast right yeah
[Music]
progression
yeah I don't know she's going for the
same one of course
oh no
one that's like actually underneath
push push push push push
oh
goodness
[Music]
foreign
I tried that one too
[Music]
okay my turns Korea
either this one or the this one
[Music]
foreign
come on
I think you didn't actually like see I
didn't you know I didn't take it like
from the top I took it like like this
from the side to side
jump
oh dip
I will try I will try
they're so thin
um
there's Japanese Pokey right so
foreign
[Music]
I'll bring her Mikado sometime like the
edible ones we have uh Pokey Japanese
Pokey it's called Uh mikando and I like
it more riskyo
foreign
[Music]
oh
yeah
so what's up
[Music]
foreign
oh
okay
yeah what are you say guys what do you
say
was that outdoor that was maybe yeah
um
we should just go
quickly
oh three two one
[Music]
you need confidence yes confidence
she likes things without chocolate okay
okay there's Porky that's like basically
without chocolate too
[Music]
that might be good that top one
foreign
[Music]
I have an idea but I won't tell her
it's doing so well
okay get it
come on come on
yes it's all yeah
um
I was like why are you bringing it back
to um
I'm giving her so many passes
[Music]
look at it
nice nice nice nice nice nice
noise
[Music]
she only has long-sleeved clothes summer
I could never
oh it's getting all the points
okay I'll try this one I told her you
know I'm so nice to you you should give
me the next turn
foreign
thank you
oh it's easy
hmm
I'll be strict
Ness
smooth smooth very smooth
danger danger
stranger danger
yes
you learn from the best Santa
all right
[Music]
yeah I should have been worsted because
now it's like
foreign you cannot just take it too easy
now and think it will be a walk in the
park
um
you have to use two
huh
I said that so confidently you have to
do it right now wow
[Music]
I'm like bending around the camera and
the microphone
wow easy
um
let's go maybe left side
we're so close to getting the the
spiraling one yeah
[Music]
oh I'm so shaky oh [\h__\h]
she wants to 20 points one huh green and
green oh
yeah yeah yeah
one chance one more chance
[Applause]
she must have seen that like it's not
touching the upper ones that much I
couldn't see it from my side
um
okay
she would go for the bottom so she
probably sees something that I'm not
seeing so I'll try her side
um
foreign
[Music]
wow
let's go let's go yeah
she's gonna try my technique where you
push the tips with the tips touching
tips
[Music]
using the special one she's trying to
piss me off what
yeah
yeah yeah wow
[Music]
good evening
she's still going for the bottom I feel
like they're touching the upper ones
quite a lot though
risky risky
oh
I didn't see so it didn't happen
[Music]
I will give up on the bottom I'll go
left okay
[Music]
it's already here
yeah
no no no it wanted to be with me
[Music]
again
one more one more
I can't
I give up yeah it moved
I decide on my own because I'm an adult
she's a child so I have to decide for
her when it's time to go to bed you know
um
[Music]
oh you know
she forgave me
sure
[Music]
mama
um
sometimes I forgive her sometimes she
forgives you know it's so taking and
giving or whatever giving and taking
giving tactile give and take you oh
hi hi wow
she deserves that one damn
how did she do that
let's go
guys you gotta do the math for us by the
way in a moment okay
I think we gotta go this way
okay okay let's count
[Music]
um
you guys help us count okay I'll tell
you the The Point again
do you guys remember how many points
each was I'll tell you again
foreign
they might not naturally think of using
the sticks as Chopsticks and using that
technique I feel like
okay I'm done so
of course uh 20 points isn't that I need
you
the blue red blue 10 points I have one
two three blue red blue
okay can you guys count this for us
[Music]
20 points so 40 points I have uh 30
points or 610 310
red blue red blue red
red
blue red blue red equal to me too
that's five points uh so Watashi 40
um
[Music]
let me just tell you guys okay let me
really quickly uh I have one two three
four five six seven eight nine ten times
the two points or 20 points
um she has four times two
okay okay
three times uh three points these are
three points one two three four five six
seven uh
she has eight uh that give three points
I have I've said seven right I'm losing
right
foreign
[Music]
she won two
yeah okay but she's a she's a child you
know children are better at children
games
[Music]
in Japan and and our first like you know
interaction like this so I hope you guys
enjoyed it also you know we got some
interactions and translations and stuff
so you know you know it was good
I will let her listen to my album songs
and in German we say doors
and in German we sing without them
uh
[Music]
if anybody doesn't have streaming ticket
please get the ticket yeah I'll get it
before the servers are gonna crash last
minute yes
[Music]
um
streaming on Twitch on Twitch afterwards
uh two hours two hours 20 minutes so if
you want to see more of her she will be
on Twitch if you guys are bored okay
bye-bye
see you tomorrow
[Music]
foreign