thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
wow
[Music]
now
well well
[Music]
my game is in German why is my game in
German
[Music]
yeah
ah
here found the setting
okay
[Music]
look
and this is why I was giggling
[Music]
girls with me
uh
fast
bro man how fast can you type that
message and make it send whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa or did you know before I
even showed up that I had a cat on my
head maybe maybe it was a coincidence
wish water
okay hello everybody
I I asked Christina because I love her
katos uh if she can make me some cute
tattoos and look I got the cute tattoos
thank you for making them and even the
the positioning was my idea but smoothie
uh you know with the hand you know
that's really smart because it's two
separate parts and it moves like you
know like I'm fluffing through the fluff
uh constantly that's pretty smart
pretty smart there
[Music]
it's okay you're gonna fall off if you
don't hold on to my head
it's like Rodeo chunkers is playing
rodeo with my head
so cute so cute oh man thank you for
answering my request
um
oh I forgot to take
um one medicine
I'll I'll just um beat right back
laughs
[Music]
oh
and I screamed because the moment I left
my room chonkers was like zooming and
almost bonking into me and she was like
bro while she was running and now I have
her on my on on my head totally but also
on my on my on my lap
who's zooming you're zooming you're
zooming
go run go run yeah let it all out
chunkers
oh now she's kind of like what's going
on I'm confused Mommy
when is there two of me
why is there a chunkers on your head
what's up
want to play no no she's weirded out
oh ice movie
as you can see it's Freedom time
um I do what I want
oh but they're not really reacting well
oh
okay go get
go get do you hear the the sound
she prefers to wrestle
um the curtain that fell on the floor
rather than the feather toy that I'm
offering her
yeah it's not sponsored this stream is
not sponsored but
uh I got a free copy of the game thank
you and I got some free copies of the
game for you guys
which um
I have complete Freedom over how I give
them away but I'm thinking at the end of
the stream or in the middle of the
stream or so I'll give you guys like uh
like a secret password and then you guys
need a Twitter unfortunately and you
have to
um you know right and after tweet at me
with the password so I know that you
watched the stream if you see only yeah
steam version is the codes that I got
are for steam I would say
um yeah no no you know I kind of like
how we did it before with uh Alice
um I don't know if I went by rent no I
think I went by random back then yeah uh
what's with Elon
what oh one more thing I [\h__\h] up
I made it
okay and
and a fruit you know hot water I poured
it into this big thermos jug and then I
put three tea bags in and one or several
of them
ripped I don't know why maybe the water
was too hot I guess that happens and now
it's like uh mixing you know the all the
[\h__\h] in the water and I
um [\h__\h] up so I brought like a little
sieve
that's what you call it right a sieve
so when I pour it into my teacup
hopefully it will stop all the [\h__\h]
from and filter it yeah go from going in
there and I am I [\h__\h] up man a little
little strainer and thank God I have a
smaller I don't even have a big one I
need to buy a big one because sometimes
with hellofresh when I cook [\h__\h] they
want me to use a thief and I only I have
one big Thief for like noodles and [\h__\h]
um but it only is good for that like I
can't use the C for for washing rice for
example so when I wash rice I just do it
without a see if I just you know try to
not lose too much of the whatever what
is this talk what
about all that
[Laughter]
the holes are too big yeah yeah but this
small see if it works it's for sugar so
hopefully it will hold up the
the
except what I say see if I don't know
straighter whatever
wash rice why because you should wash
rice before you cook it usually
I mean maybe it depends on the rice but
mostly you should wash it duh
duh
yeah now watch the rest if you wash rice
once you will understand why you're
rushing washing it I think when I was
younger I did not wash it and I mean it
was okay but after starting to wash my
rice you see how [\h__\h] dirty the water
is that you washed rice with so then you
understand mm-hmm
there's something weird on my head it's
my [\h__\h] cat there's nothing weird
about my cat how insulting
hmm so uh welcome one and all
to the kiwawa show we're gonna play the
entropy Center today
uh which is a game I've been waiting for
since I was
uh
you know made aware of it
because we liked playing Portal didn't
we
and I can say this because it seems to
be in a very obvious reference
uh uh I can say this without it being I
think disrespectful to the creators oh I
forgot the starting tweet thank you but
it is obviously inspired by portal and
the developers seem to be fans of portal
so I think I can say this is this is the
portal free that
we deserve well our dance the only fool
free that we will ever get
so okay let me do a starting tweet
eh
oh no that burns no no I think I think
okay like okay normally I would not like
really so blatantly
um compare a game so so openly so
directly
um but with this game I think it's okay
yeah
I think
also yeah it might be a compliment and
also like I mean it's obvious so uh
valve doesn't like it I'm afraid they
can't count oh oh oh hey valve and
I'm not gonna say that show
uh uh starting
my day okay okay
tweet
coward
yes I'm a coward oh
interesting how many of you know what I
was gonna go for
um so I will probably be [\h__\h] at this
game especially because this time I
probably won't get much help from you
guys
um
I know
and anyone here
who already played it
it just came out so
you know I also told you to wait because
I'm Gonna Give You codes so uh
I'll do a best to slow it together yeah
like this time you
you know how often you feel like smart
because you know how to play the games
that I play but you only know it because
you played it before already so this
time you can't feel that smart you will
actually have to use your actual brain
power to help me not your experience in
playing the game and then feeling
Superior to me yeah
so let's see how smart you really are
since you think you are so smart entity
of chat
okay can I try I wanna I wanna try it
um pouring myself some tea now
let's see if this works okay
um I'm I'm scared I'm scared um oh God
oh it works it works yeah the stuff is
like filtering through
beautifully
oh oh yeah yeah
oh yeah baby
success you will not ruin my tea
okay where do I put this
where do I put the sieve
um I'll just put it here okay
so no no I just have to wait for the tea
to be drinkable okay sorry I've been
stalling haha I'm stalling yeah
I'll get to it you know what's perfect
with you know coffee and tea and
um similar things
cookies
called Lotus Biscoff
the those caramelish cookies the brown
ones yeah those they're so good you know
normally you get them in like coffee
houses together with you know your
coffee or so but I actually I don't know
I had a craving for them and I was in
the supermarket and and I bought a whole
package of them and I've been snacking
on them since yesterday
they're so good holy [\h__\h] man
I think I think you know what uh was
absolutely incredible I think this was a
thing
[Music]
you are incredible
yeah
um and
I think I think McDonald's had a time
where
um you know they do all kinds of ice
creams right like mixing like Twix and M
M's and [\h__\h] at least here so I think
once they did Biscoff
uh ice cream McFlurry uh-huh
amazing again please because I don't
remember eating it I want it
I think they did it before
and I'm I'm like I want that I I need
that in my life I need Biscoff ice cream
this cough McFlurry yeah
didn't have dinner yet I'm not I'm not
uh talking about dinner
do you know okay let's play this game
and I don't think I hear audio I think
there should be audio did you guys wait
you guys don't hear already but oh
it's so weird I my my capture card
always meow thanks Dad
um I I'm talking to the captain
why should you really acquired meow
oh I hear music
the moment I get up she runs away
you just want attention you don't want
my heart oh
[Music]
what is this oh she's scratching oh wow
cool
oh
wow
that looks it looks pretty awesome holy
[\h__\h] the graphics are so good but I'm
playing in a pretty tiny window I want
to make it bigger
uh
[Music]
what is that oh is this ah is this white
screen
oh that that looks that looks fine that
looks like widescreen okay
oh nice
nice whoa
what's up everything on on Max right
Ultra Ultra Ultra Ultra oh Lolo okay not
everything but it's beautiful
too quiet yeah I mean generally it's not
very loud right now
still too quiet
oh wait wait raise it
can I enter the water no
doesn't this look super cool
whoa footsteps yeah here footsteps for
myself oh
oh
fart what happened
who's that normal
the loop the loop is not very smooth
but maybe that's on purpose because they
have something like with rewind going on
in this game
let me observe
yeah yeah yeah yeah
Loop ends
now
[Music]
no I don't know what I was just saying
there
can I run no I was just testing to run
on Ctrl oh I'm shaking juicing
oh no
[Music]
the entropy Center
isn't that like a British way to write
it
oh we are so British today
let's go everybody
what was that
good morning Aria Adams
Amanda restful sleep at the end the
early Center what where am I she's an
ex-boy your timetable for today's puzzle
exercises on your personal computer
puzzle exercises
that's quite hot actually 26 degrees
ahead
Port head towards
or my personal computer yeah yeah that's
what PC stands for I think some some
Zoomers don't even know that
uh wait how do I oh entry puzzle team
your timetable HR Team new employee Open
Door
can I rate this oh yeah thank you for
your continued hard work at the entropy
Center your rollers junior puzzle
operative
please find the status through timetable
table for this week's puzzle exercise a
maximum of two puzzles can be shifted
into next week if required please
contact your entropy supervisor to
arrangement uh-huh
so this is another one of those games
where the people behind everything they
have a fetish for puzzles
I've seen I see welcome pleased to have
you onboard on your Junior personal room
please please use the rest of this week
to become acquainted with the center you
know welcome to browse at your own
Leisure use the local amenities and meet
your fellow colleagues
I have a feeling there will be no
colleagues
have any questions at a new point please
feel free to contact your line manager
okay and then I guess we open the door
ah two of 76 Intel collected oh it's not
like a collectible just reading things
weather report
oh
there's the one on the right mean that
the sun will be raining
what
yo it's so pretty
[Music]
it's a kitten okay
so we have like I guess another one of
those apocalypse themes going on
building is just like
hello anyone
the plant is a lie it happened here
I'm moving so fast holy [\h__\h]
look how fast I'm moving just walking
normally
I want to like
slow her down
the entry Center making a better
tomorrow
announcement
[Music]
s
sizes for today thank you okay let's go
it's so pretty
[Music]
oh beautiful
would this be considered an indie game
because if yes and holy [\h__\h] it's so
pretty
okay yeah it is
there has to be someone around not of
course there's no one around girl you
all alone here
you are alone but you know that's the
good thing because that makes you the
protagonist the only choice for the
protagonist oh that's locked
interesting
[Music]
what are you
holy [\h__\h]
you around I guess oh my God this scared
me too
I was so shocked I was like oh
God okay wait I guess can we like follow
you here no I guess not don't go here
interact with me
he interact
testing range testing my puzzle areas
where did that Robot Dog go
okay I see like some plants like loading
in it's kind of weird
but maybe that's my settings
oh
wow press e to pick up Cube oh yeah
[Music]
view this is though yeah that's true I I
think I have that setting on
oh
oh okay well I mean I mean can anyone
disagree that this is Portal free
that was very very obvious
pray to the cube indeed
hello is anyone there
oh
don't
she wants attention it's one of those
days
you you
sorry I have to give some pets she's
walking around here he wants the pets
oh I picked her up
you want to play this game chunky
okay how okay let's let's go use the
right hand
what's going on here oh there's
something it's a push chunky wonky here
push pressy good job that was totally
you at least I'm the world player of the
testing area
oh is that our gun see it's like
rewinding something complete wow can we
take that
I think she's purring it's hard to hear
with my headphones
okay we take this thing see how I'm
moving I'm trying to not use the mouse
oh she wants to leave already yeah yeah
yeah
bye bye bye bye don't come running back
to me and be like meow meow meow
what what am I taking it
uh
[Music]
this is a gun
at me like that apologies I did not mean
to startle you I have just been inactive
for a very long time my name is
short wait what you are now in
possession of a handheld entropy device
capable of rewinding objects into the
past
give it a try
hey that's so cool nice to meet you
Astra why does she not just use this gun
on herself and try to rewind herself
until the point
before the the crash of the earth
explosion happened I don't know
maybe then
we can save ourselves but that's that's
me thinking too far
[Music]
spoiler nice logic oh my God is that
maybe that's
what she will do okay so if we click on
it we rewind it and if we let go well
done oh it stays like this deploying
emotional support
[Music]
thank you so can I use this you on
anything
[Music]
only contains enough power to rewind
static objects up to 300 cubic meters in
size oh in normal terms that means you
can rewind small structures debris and
puzzle elements of course living animals
such as the office cat cannot be rewound
there's enough biscuits no rewinding
why not why not I want to try reminding
a cat okay so if I press Q it falls
apart again okay
and I can like stop it in between that's
so cool
I'm not sponsored by the way I'm just
excited
all right
okay
so maybe we can use that on the
[Music]
this is something a portal did not have
press e to pick up objects what am I
supposed to pick up
ball
oh launch
oh press to rewind okay but I have to be
pretty close
there we go
how would that where would that go
oh
let's do that and then I can take it and
let's launch it into the into the thing
in there
oh
almost had it
I'll be a basketball player I'll show
you for Android to make me oh no
hey
little [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] you
[Laughter]
I'm not falling
I'm obviously not falling oh
oh oh oh what are these for
[Music]
and welcome to the gym
oh
oh no no
[Music]
interesting
can I
jump on that while like wait I want to
look around a little bit more but I'm
thinking like if I don't stop it
um
at the end but like a little bit earlier
it might become a structure that where I
can jump on and then get on top because
in the final last form it's too
Too Tall right right oh wait never mind
this door is open interesting
oh yeah
oh yeah yeah
baby that maybe there's two paths okay
or this is a real path and that's an
extra path for like extra
now I have to take a look now I'm really
curious
foreign
that's something we will test out right
now
okay
oh
yes you can oh that's Coolio oh but
there's um
nothing here to do this door is locked
and
huh
so maybe ah
it's our team two for one at entry
people
employees we would like to invite you to
the beach Bonanza this Friday at 7 pm
ECT entry Center time we are hosting a
two for one cocktail evening to say
thank you for all your hard work and
education for this busy time thank you
no thank you
that's um
wow it sounds like a nice place here
for now
Now where's the evil twists
will it have an evil twist
will it oh oh this thing fell apart ah
is it like
when I rewinded that other thing this
one fell apart because I only can have
one thing rewinded at a time
yeah that fell apart
ah seems to be a thing
Astra do you know what's going on where
is everyone
the entropy Center may or may not be
experiencing some minor technical
difficulty but do not let that alarm you
our puzzle operations can continue as
normal minor difficulties it looks like
no one's been here in years
what are these puzzle operations that's
nice the bezel areas to generate entropy
energy of course it is my core installed
directive to guide and assist staff
members
interview energy and make a better
tomorrow and make a better tomorrow okay
sure about that why can't I remember
anything
I don't even know where I am green Lords
just like me my hard drive also seems
somewhat corrupted I have just submitted
an appointment request to Medical for
you
oh thank you okay
keep going there's got to be someone
around and preferably someone human
[Music]
okay I can't wait for you to solve
puzzles for us and make a better
tomorrow
wow
cool
stuff breaker oh wow
[Music]
honestly I like the the look that it has
now
oh oh can we play can we play
that looks like a peach
another Peach not the peach no I think
you have something else
something like a plum not really
break area broken ah oh man
[Music]
what
is it not water
is it not water it looks like water but
it has no like physics so I'm confused
[Music]
but here the way it moves with the
shadow it looks like water
fake
or is it is it is it a
no that's water look how it moves I'm
confused
interesting looks so cool oh
[Applause]
like a recreational area or so I don't
know
like an indoor vacation area
so you don't even have to leave work
when you take a vacation because you'll
just stay at work wow
that's that's actually kind of cool but
obviously not healthy work environment
when your vacation is at work no matter
how good you make it look
um
finance and puzzle areas are one oh are
we getting to the first real puzzle
[Music]
route zero one starts
let's go let's go
might give me more jump scares than um
you're welcome you're welcome
please don't crash right on top of me
person alive and
I hope I stay alive
remember make a better tomorrow thank
you I will make a better tomorrow if we
ever reach tomorrow
cubes and Rewind with left button okay
um
oh wait oh oh oh
yeah why would I rewind it what does
this do
oh
one
so I
can see what's going on I'm going to go
for the first door
which is opened by this and then maybe
from here on
from here
yeah yeah yeah
congratulations you just completed your
first official entry puzzle
five percent oh nice of the bottoms
right rude well there's always room for
improvement I guess oh [\h__\h] is that
really my time
do they actually measure how long I take
for each puzzle
[Music]
it's different insufficient entropy
energy please continue please
I'm still very much in High Spirits and
motivated so leave it to me please
proceed with caution do not aim the
handheld entropy device that others do
not discuss Solutions with other staff
members and how
are you guys
it's apparently permitted one person per
puzzle at a time please form an orderly
cue
into small letters I want to read the
small letters
can
chat I guess I have to do this without
you
well well
first replace it um
here and then we place it
here because I want to rewind it so
first you know we have to think
um you have to do Forward Thinking
[Music]
wait
which button opens that one ah the first
one
uh so wait uh kill
no [\h__\h]
uh uh cue to resume time and drop you oh
okay that kind of works I guess
so did I used to work here or something
so far I feel good
the entropy Center database shows how
you thinking will you intervene here
puzzle operative you are currently
navigating the puzzle areas section zero
one I would say I'm thinking with time
[Music]
as opposed to thinking with a momentum
you know
yeah yeah we we for a little time travel
yeah
okay we need to get up there what does
this do
ah but then it immediately goes up
so wait I see I'll just bring it
and then bring it back
okay okay well I'm definitely getting
the gist of it
is
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] she's absolutely destroying it
let's go
no life signals detected nearby dust
bushes nope bushes do not respond to
verbal greetings
little [\h__\h] you think you're smart huh
she's very smart Okay
um
uh a cube over there
first needs here and then there but you
know then we think the other way around
because then we needed first here
yeah and and then there
wrong
but hey I'm confused
[Laughter]
wait
uh-huh
um
huh
wait
can I reach it from here though
wait what is so fast
I make mistake
I think I went too far or like you can
too far Maybe
is it like is it like a maximum time of
how often I can like drop it in between
okay go go go go
yeah that's that's the ending point
isn't it
it will not go back here
okay in that case
um one
two that's a must but
[Music]
[\h__\h]
uh
okay wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
don't do it yet but it should work
and
[Music]
this
no go back
whoa what
[Laughter]
I could have dropped it but it already
went too far you know
um
okay think
[Music]
at least I can make Dad jump when it
already moves to the next one
[Music]
how to do it but you know we have to
figure out the amount of memory you can
save continue heading through the puzzle
areas hopefully we should find someone
soon
hopefully we should find someone soon
it was like a weird thing to say for
this character also I noticed it's way
too loud actually
why don't you guys say something
[Music]
uh
yeah we don't want to see that time oh
snacks what kind of snaps you got
English breakfast tea oh
entropy crisps
[Music]
uh-huh some stuff that looks like kitty
cats oh those are like the the
no wait I I misjudged these are just
normal drinks and energy drinks
and cola
cool cool can I get one
no
maybe need money don't have money
all the areas O2
okay
um oh big
and should we transfer Shadow well they
have their own shuttle
[Music]
what if I jump down
let's let's not test it out but I I do
Wonder like if I die in this game like
how far does it set me back and
where to
hopefully just the beginning of a room
[Music]
oh
oh oh [\h__\h] I'm just here to enjoy my
team please don't bother me
today 43
.3 I like those odds no I don't like
them that was that less than a half oh
oh oh
I have only one hand right now how do we
get off
please keep arms and legs inside the
entropy transport vehicle
okay this isn't good all right it's fine
and we have a very powerful gun ah go
back go back
it's cool that's pretty cool
[\h__\h] that came too fast at me oh [\h__\h]
oops same
we'll try again
oh I have been rewinded so this is where
we restart okay that's that's nice
that's not too far because uh
let's go
I will not be surprised this time
I'm waiting for it oh
[Music]
come at me
[Applause]
[Music]
that's what that Melody always makes me
think of am I the only one please keep
arms and legs inside the entropy
transport vehicle at all times hey this
isn't good
come come on
next something up here right uh morning
incoming heavy option oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
this is so slow
yes oh
oh
yeah
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
okay
oh my rage is pretty good
wait music way too loud still oh sure
[Music]
oh what is this oh [\h__\h]
what am I bleeding also this is kind of
electric what is going on
[Music]
[Laughter]
I guess I was supposed to rewind
something but yeah
oh yeah he did say that huh I missed
that part
while the level rising ocean and maybe
gotta go faster and that's it
okay
okay but see what's how oh
that thing
ah I knew I could rewind something there
just didn't see it ran away
okay
oh
everything is under control
we'll stand right on top of it yeah yeah
well done yeah
that you have most likely survived
okay next time maybe give a little
warning huh no problem was that a puzzle
or it's like in your staff profile all
right let's keep going is that a test
[Music]
make a better tomorrow
thanks for the clapping
I deserve that
I just dropped something very far away
oh are we taking the elevator
look there's elevated music in the
elevator but wait wait wait just looking
at some things okay okay okay we're good
what is that light cylinder
Elevate is kind of scary man
oh I got an achievement wake up can't
wake up
Wake Me Up Inside
[Music]
thank you guys for always jamming with
me
oh space
Spacey oh oh let's go wow
indoor water amusement park
recreation of
an actual Ocean Beach Paradise nice can
I go there please that entrance Door
over there requires power directive look
around for a nearby power device
what you mean that one but I'm more
curious about what's going on here
huh
oh I'm gonna turn it off to the fire
oh
wait why why
what is that anyway like why if you turn
that why would this like
produce fire
what what
meaning is behind that
also
oh my God okay
I thought I could rewind it but no I
have to pick it up I was a bit shocked
at that okay
ah
what do I attach it to that oh
all right open until I close it
interesting
oh
puzzle element introduction
yay traveling through a Time gate will
remove all stored rewind data from
nearby cubes note you cannot take
entropy cubes through a Time game they
will get incinerated is this the time
gate this blue thing
[Music]
oh okay so okay yes it is
interesting uh how do I make this [\h__\h]
stuff
um
how do I make that stuff that just
refreshes the cubes
I it doesn't affect me Oh I thought it
would affect me too okay aha
okay well obviously uh we put this one
on here first
then we take this one
put one here and then put one there
but let's see how long this will take to
destroy all my confidence in my own
brain
also oh I wonder how my mom would like
this because she likes portal as far as
I remember
she might be watching us press R to
delete rewind from the cube
[Music]
why would I do that
was affected anxiety and stress and
puzzle operative
short answer
definitely great I wish thank you for
being honest with me to analyze the
current situation we're heading in the
right direction
that's at least one good thing oh [\h__\h]
ah that was too early okay so
um rewind
but the I needed to go back again
I wanna
rewind the rewind
okay I guess I'll I'll do it uh
uh I'm confused
one of those will work
um
ah the other books I have to read one
too
do I well we'll see we'll see
uh rewind
and what about this ah
I needed to bring that one with me yeah
tell me that earlier
huh but this one's for what
ah ah
[Music]
okay okay here here we have to start
thinking no disgusting puzzles no
ah
okay no it shouldn't be too difficult I
mean
um
I think
uh
don't wait
ah
[Music]
um
I don't know
foreign
hmm
well
[\h__\h]
stand on the queue
stand on the cube
oh God
ah
[Laughter]
uh
[Applause]
[Music]
laughs
what
yeah okay I understand I am in the
bottom 50 now
or the bottom 50 or whatever whatever
she said
I can figure this out
uh about five percent of the bot the top
five percent of the bottom 50 people of
how many 100
um
I feel pressured okay this is one of
those situations where I I can totally
solve it but you guys are making me
nervous
[Music]
um
I need one to keep this door open
because I can't bring a cube through it
uh if this is you know
but oh I have an idea I think
um
I think
uh
no I don't wait
um
no yeah yeah yeah okay
I have an idea I have an idea I haven't
I think it's just like the execution of
it
is um a Tuffy
so if I take
um
ideas but how to use idea is the
question
something like this but
um
not quite ah
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
let's let's let's think um logically
[Laughter]
um
we need one there
to go through
then we need one down here to go up and
then we need another one up there but we
only have two so
so uh let's let's think that we keep
this one here for now and
um
the other one
[Music]
well
um
I don't know
the gate does not need to stay open
you mean that one over there
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
okay
oh do I
why don't we open that in the first
place
because I can pass through
ah because I brought the other Cube
already ah but wait
[Music]
okay we're almost there we're off we're
almost there
uh
yeah yeah yeah we we got it we got it
let's say
um
yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
but once we're over there we just rewind
that while we're together okay okay okay
okay okay okay
why does it not go further I had it like
here I don't I don't sometimes I don't
understand where it starts
you know
and where
resets my
[Music]
smile oh
that's me
um
I wonder if that's close enough for me
to move it when I'm up there but I feel
like that's not the way it should be
done
ah
[Music]
[Laughter]
you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh man
[\h__\h]
eternity was taken for this you want to
see it in minutes you want to see you
want to see
10 I would say 10 approximately
10 minutes I have a good feeling for
time but in a different way than I need
it
[Music]
no I'm having fun I'm having a lot of
fun okay
um this is a nice challenge nice brain
exercise okay this is what it's supposed
to be all right
um I will probably eventually cry but at
the moment I'm still positively thinking
um okay so this one is the platform
that one is the door and then we need
another one so maybe we can use the same
um
thinking method
which I already forgot
yes I already forgot
but
I am smart so I can figure this out
see at least I got that one okay but
then this door is not open
what
what uh
how about we place it here
and then
I fell down can I rewind myself
no okay that's that's okay like uh uh
uh but okay general question
I have yet to observe that correctly if
I move this one does it reset this
rewind
or like what is the maximum of things I
could rewind
it does reset right
no wait it does not
which
[Music]
it does not
dead
why am I doing this
[Laughter]
why why did I do it
[Music]
they have individuals
what the [\h__\h] timers
I have an idea
yeah
[Music]
ah
see like okay see how the timer changes
when I look at the thing
okay um
[Music]
I think I understand
um
but
um you know
um
[Music]
laughs
yeah wait what yeah
thank God they're so um gracious I can
do so many rewinds
[Music]
oh man now I have to warn you this
puzzle has a high percentage of failure
members as they often get stuck good
luck why can't you just tell me how to
solve it I
can um stupid question Arya and
I know entropy energy would be generated
if you
need solution no worse exactly yeah why
would she tell me the solution not even
chat can tell me the solution
inbox puzzle Blaster oh
are you stuck on puzzle 0604 as well
it's so hard I've been stuck on it for
like two days now you got any tips I'm a
bit worried about my performance review
at the end of the month
they're puzzle of directives we have an
increasing number of reports of Entry
puzzles generating no entry appeal this
means that
picture's new how to complete the puzzle
before doing it
this can only happen if staff members
are just classic solution
no way remember discussing solutions to
puzzles is prohibited as disease now
it's electric energy and gives a voice
rating on your report card than just
going to your supervisor and being
honest that you're stuck
this is funny
I like it
[Laughter]
just look asked
here we are let's let's let's give them
a good performance shall we
but not too good so they would think
that I I cheated you know because
obviously I would never do such a thing
come on
oh easy
[Music]
I would move it until it's there
um
then move the platform back but rewind
the cube because the platform platform
is blocking the cube from pressing that
so I'm wearing like um starting
again
with
a new a new thing that's why it's being
easy on me
I'm drinking my refreshment right now I
don't need yours
okay yeah they go they went down with
the difficulty a little bit on that one
just to introduce me to something I
guess I suppose
tools
time hoops oh that's funny is that an
actually existing
snack
breakfast cereal
until baby give me some Intel no there's
no Intel here
there is no Intel but there is this
but it's so bright
[Music]
uh why why Earth go from sad to Happy
because you got to know your co-workers
that makes so much sense
be kind to the machine that's talking to
you otherwise it will rewind you to your
baby form and kill you
[Music]
the robot is happy all is good but if
the robot is angry do not touch the
robot
robot see him
ah open from
[Music]
now oh that's cool it's a museum welcome
orientation oh that's a really shitty
PowerPoint presentation I gotta say
I've seen better
from a certain YouTuber
[Music]
world is falling apart is that what
you're saying ah
we're fine okay so
let's look at this brain teaser we need
two
that is
no problem
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh
I was so sure about that one oh no
problem uh it's the same principle but
different execution
uh [\h__\h] I lost all my confidence
um
[\h__\h] I was gonna be like wow so smart
kiwala I'm so impressed no no no no
that's your boat
um
laughs
I got it
uh but I forgot where this one goes
[Music]
[\h__\h] a little [\h__\h]
see I stand on it while I rewind it and
then it should be safe oh [\h__\h] wait oh
[\h__\h]
God
oh God
[Music]
it's okay
oh yes
all according to keikaku
I understand
I'm in a very giggly mood today
what's going on
punch me
um
[Music]
doesn't help until the main deck
that's you Arya big scary man voice says
we should go to the main deck
zero zero one two three four five six
that implies that there were
oh that really is over a hundred
thousand wait
employees before alone here
how smart was that conclusion of me huh
wow
IQ over a million
no
he's smarter than all of you chickens
discover combined Intel Intel no Intel
Intel Intel Intel no Intel
I'm the top
wow what's going on what's going on
what's going on
what must how where Togo
wait I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll get to it
also that's an interesting placement of
office there are no doors
there's just the table up there how are
you supposed to reach that with a ladder
I guess that's kind of cool
entering your little office space for a
ladder they're even up that high
anyway I want to go there um is there
something to rewind hello
go
[Music]
interesting reflection
because I don't know what it's
reflecting
I guess the sky from here
um
uh
uh totally not stalling and trying to
figure it out
on the side
uh
check PC I was looking at them
but they
are not operating
solve the room once they just
[Music]
there's one
see looking at the PCS is a thing that I
wanted to do
but
did I miss the the single PC that is
open to interacting with me
it's probably this one
it's so obvious
because of the lights
it's the brightest one
more or less that one over there is
pretty bright too
oh
call elevator
ah
whoops
I may have
made it capuch
capuch destroy
oh yeah
I know where that goes
into like one of those thingies
on it
but where
oh
[Music]
uh What uh
we need to stop it in the middle
uh
wait wait
oh don't don't push me off
I think I got it yeah yeah yeah
now open please
quite logical because if I rewind that
when it's in there shouldn't it go back
to where I brought it from and not like
rewind
[\h__\h] as if it was always there that
makes no sense to me
zero out of ten logic points
oh wait I have to go
agree thank you
thank you don't question okay
puzzle element introduction jump cubes
stand on jump Cube to launch yourself
upwards
hey Astra are you sure there isn't a
shortcut or something we could take the
whole Center is made up of puzzle areas
trust me this is the fastest route
additionally your job is a puzzle
operative it is your directive to
complete these puzzles all right
too late for a career change either
girl
what's with Arya man like I should be
here instead of her like she has no
motivation to do this
man if you don't want to be here then go
that way
there's other people who like to enjoy
this content and like to like to test
puzzles you know because we're puzzle
Maniacs okay
yeah
what a negative
negative
weasel yeah
what an insult man she must be
absolutely the destroyed by it
so anyway
there's no Cube so are you you want me
to put this here why I want to waste
oh I guess well okay
ah you can't
la la la
and then we bring it back
oh yeah
as you were having trouble remembering
Gladys would be proud of you employee
questionnaire I think so too
what is Arya full name Arya Adams
question two what is your age 27 I think
wow you look great for your age
what does she look like okay question
three
world ending Tendencies are thoughts in
the last six days
six days yes what kind of question is
that no totally no no no yes thank you
for completing our new employee
questionnaire cats has been added as a
like to your staff profile
having that was an obvious one
okay
uh first I want to look into this room
so no
you come with me
probably some Intel
yeah
I have a nose you know I have a nose
that Snips out the Intel
Ellie silicon
Mega awesome pitch idea sorry it's me
Tom again Tom the ideas guy you know me
I just had a brain wave what about
entropy soccer one half of the team is
traveling forwards in time one half is
traveling back
ah so cool now lace all of the boots
with entropy energy now every time they
hit the ball it's entropy time Direction
changes
oh the possibilities are endless this is
gonna be huge saving Panda stopping
wildfires fixing the climate crisis
forget it we now have entropy soccer
oh okay dude dude
uh hey Tom thanks for messaging but
again please refer to my previous email
this is coming across as a little
unprofessional you may want to ask your
line manager if it's okay to be sending
pictures directly to me as I imagine you
may want to discuss them as a group
first so that they can be approved
wow wow that's that must have
destroyed him oh [\h__\h] he he was like so
excited and she's like no [\h__\h] you I
don't want to hear your ideas directly
from you you'll go somewhere else oh
it was an okay idea I guess
hi Eric it's Helen from development
planning I'm getting so many pictures
from Tom with these intense commercial
pictures I just wanted to say I admire
his confidence But Here Comes the [\h__\h]
backstabbing moment he may need to rub
it back a bit I do want to reiterate
that the development team are looking
for humanitarian focused Solutions with
entry energy oh
but that sounds actually quite positive
good to hear from you oh God I'm so
sorry I had no idea Tom wasn't sending
you pictures they definitely hadn't been
through me first Tom is a bit like that
he has a lot of great ideas bless him
just a bit of a loose cannon
I think he's just really excited to be
working here I'll get him to come to
Mommy first with any new ideas
um that's why they're testing it so for
now everything sounds very very hopeful
and good
oh
yeah Tom Tom is too enthusiastic he's
too much into sports
and Ally is definitely not a sports fan
very sad
very sad I mean
Tom
it's about saving the world and soccer
unfortunately will not save the world
I'm sorry
okay so what is this all about
I need it here uh-huh
and then here ah okay well that seems
manageable so if I
oh
okay
oh [\h__\h] oh that's probably fine there
okay uh
no big big thinking problem I got here
because
I have to bring it back to open the door
but I need it there again and then I
need it down there so the order is
as follows
uh
let me tell you right now uh what the
order is
number one
uh here
write this down yes yes write it down as
you need it when you play the game
wait how how much can I
can I like let me
Let me refresh
how much
wait how do I refresh it
how do I start it like over again
R uh okay thank you yeah they did say
that before okay
um
but
no
uh and at the very end
I need to rewind this thing
so there we go here we have it because I
need that Cube up there in the end
um
okay so we don't need that here that's
okay
but uh
let me let me think
first
we need it here
then we need it here
so
it will be the opposite right
but how do I re
um maybe from here can I see it yeah
yeah yeah
yeah yeah hi hi
I'm genius
there we go
not so bad not so bad
by the way because I mentioned my mommy
before just wanted to let you know
I ended up booking for our little trip
to Italy note jumping onto a jump Cube
from a higher area Will Spring you
further just remember to bend your knees
when you land
I ended up booking another accommodation
even though the first one was already
[\h__\h] expensive right but I booked it
really really really really really
really cheap the cheapest and closest I
could find Airbnb the closest to the
other accommodation
um for me
I asked my mom if she's okay with me
staying somewhere else because I know I
otherwise will not be able to sleep I
was thinking of noise canceling really
good noise canceling headphones but
I figured
that's probably will not help much
either so I'll be staying just at night
I'll be staying
somewhere else
oh interesting
I need it here now
well how would I do that
is there like a
button somewhere
by the way some cheap ones have pests
but why do you tell me that tell me that
huh
did you hear what the robot light you
said um oh partially
want it
check for bed bugs I've never had that
experience before
does the jump pad preserve momentum
got it
what do you mean it preserves momentum
High fall is a high jump
ah
what
so I'm thinking we put it like here
I mean
whatever you guys are trying to tell me
it's just confusing me even further
yeah no we're good okay
[Music]
we just put it um
here oh [\h__\h]
in theory that works my jump was just
not good
Ubuntu wait
oh
and then
no it's okay it fell down which kind of
pisses me off but it should be fun
yeah yeah oh
come on come on
it's not very stable this jump pad
okay so this is what I'm thinking are
you with me guys
ah
when you fail the dump you have to do it
again
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
oh
okay I placed it a little bit further in
the front
no
oh we're good we're good
stay
[Music]
[\h__\h]
maybe I need to jump with confidence
like this one this one this one I'm
jumping with confidence
[Music]
yeah that's a pretty small platform to
land on
tomorrow
should I just run or jump
three months no that's okay that's okay
oh [\h__\h]
and I just have to line up this jump
practice on the first one just do it
don't do it why are you guys saying just
Do It
okay
whoa whoa baby I don't want to see the
time I already knew the solution earlier
it just took me longer to execute okay
[Music]
Personnel attend the main deck thank you
are we close
my analysis detect that we are one
puzzle area away from the main control
deck oh okay good the quicker I solve
this quicker we can get there
I'm just gonna pour me some tea
[Music]
yeah
because I've been screaming from
excitement a little bit too much I was
smart to prepare some tea
anyway yo
I'm actually excited to sleep in a in a
shitty
um Airbnb
because
I don't know it makes me feel down to
earth and it's been a while since the
last time that I've like slept in a
cheap place rather than something nice
why is there cat hairs in your hair
it will be a humbling experience
but overall I also booked the flight
yesterday finally
it's more expensive than I thought it
would be but I want to
give my mom like a
like a little bit of a nice experience
because the last time my mom traveled
and had like a vacation like that
was
so many years ago I asked her
it's ages ago
ages
can't even
remember
over over six seven years ago
baby more probably
more
yeah
so
because she won't do it on her own
I I bring her to a location
not really like you know face vacation
but City trip vacation yeah because I
wanted to go to a certain city in Italy
I think I told you guys right where
where I wanted to go but for now
did I tell you
yeah Rome yeah because I've never been
to Rome I've been to several places in
in Italy
[Music]
am I getting higher and higher oh
I'm getting higher and higher wow
foreign
[Music]
sorry I had a little bit too much fun
with that
yeah can we get much higher so hot oh
can we get up there
I want to try
it's gonna take a while please have
patience
do I have to jump can I jump on the same
one will that make me higher too
is it making me higher
I don't think so
a bit difficult to control
but I want to get
much higher
hey when will I know that it's high
enough though
oh [\h__\h] I'm gonna get like
this was like in VR oh my God that would
be so so [\h__\h] freaky oh my God
I wonder they should make a VR version I
wonder if they're planning it
this would be fun in VR wasn't there
like a portal game for VR but maybe fan
made yeah
foreign
of momentum I can get because
I feel I've reached it
nah they can't
maximize that
give me a limit
now there's a limit I'm not getting any
higher I think
okay okay I keep up yeah right portal
stories
oh exciting
you can rewind the jump boxes higher up
oh yeah that's okay I give up
let's do what we're actually supposed to
do
this
uh-huh
what the [\h__\h]
um
okay I understand this
stand is very easy oh
so like we bring one huh
and
yeah yeah yeah
um I think
I understand
uh but wait
if I bring this one back
fully understanding yet
yeah
um
oh [\h__\h]
let's say we're bringing this here
and then if only you would rewind to
come back here that would be wonderful
and lovely
but I guess for that I need the second
one
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah I get it
so we rewinded to come here yeah
hey
easy
the easy almost fell down almost
I want to laugh
um where do I aim it towards
also I want to look no
no
[Music]
oh no it's looking so forward to that oh
man so lame that's what I'm here for now
oh
we're not on Earth huh cool
oh what's happening that's so cool
[Music]
you suck
keep your [\h__\h] together
literally falling apart crumbling
ah amateur amateur Planet
that's what you get for making fun of
Pluto a little [\h__\h] you big [\h__\h] what am
I supposed to do I'm supposed to save
Earth now [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] them
[Music]
okay
those cables
oh it must be a way to activate them I
feel like I'm kind of late on acting
[\h__\h] you're stressing me out what
happened
what are we looking at huh
oh man
there's one open here okay okay
sick music oh
is it scripted or was it waiting walls
[Music]
you stay right there
okay is there something there that I
need oh I think so
distance
huh
can't make it what do you mean I can't
make it oh
[Music]
this is so cool yeah
oh cool cool yeah
oh I just I don't know why but this is
so cool to me
I'm a sucker for Destruction
we got what we deserve to be honest like
you know we're [\h__\h] up Earth and yeah
see
this is not
it's not you know we can't say this was
not our fault
[Music]
what what how do I do next
okay open the door
uh
open please
or do I ex do I enter from outside
because I was able to rewind something
from there but I don't think I can reach
can I
no huh
oh
oh oh I was like I saw the timer on my
on my gun but I didn't see like what I
was supposed to rewind but nice hint
on my gun there we go there we go so it
was from outside
okay
more I didn't even see it
oh cool cool
[Music]
okay oh man
oh man
[Music]
oh so cool oh I feel so nerdy right now
oh well [\h__\h] isn't it working I did not
do enough puzzle testing the energy is
required directive
charge the entropy device
what's happening to the Earth
um girl it's exploding isn't it [\h__\h]
obvious okay but
you have proven yourself capable okay
thanks why thank you let's get going
to emergency
door
emergency door
where do I proceed
obviously not here
[Music]
What if I
it is
[Music]
oh
yeah I had those before no I don't think
I don't think that's it the door that
was locked earlier ah I fought got it I
thought it just leads to that okay
okay
but the Earth is like
currently
did it stop there's still some things
moving but I guess we stopped it for now
but we did not rewind it
huh
okay so we got a little bit of extra
time to do some puzzles
and me me so
many socials
will be the
Wing that's
singer from Lakes building
wow the power of puzzles observation
incredible looks concerned employing
emotional support hello Arya how are you
today what's your favorite color orange
thanks to us I'm fine I'm just
I'm just so that advice can rewind Earth
exactly
exactly and then what once Earth has
been around in time
at the end Center automatically
releasing their timeline to a more
positive outcome right oh well that
sounds so helpful I can barely imagine
this like this is not level four oh this
is a wall
oh [\h__\h] that's terrifying oh
hold on why are you screaming I was just
copying I thought that's what we were
doing
I think I saw an opening a few floors up
try rewinding the lift okay yeah I was
saying that I can currently like
barely imagine this like everything
being evil and having an evil cause
like why would we stop the Earth from
exploding if we're not
good
but
since it's like portal
it probably also wants to recreate that
part no
I'm not sure
that's how they get to yeah probably
right
otherwise I would not help them and work
for their cause but how do you go to
being evil from that hmm
hmm
not a whole don't
what are we looking at oh ah do I bring
the cube to go to a different opening
Maybe
because I don't see anything else
what don't be like that
oh they're so cute
oh
oh where are they going
well
I like robot goggles
look at it
there you go that looks good
cocoa
where are we
we are located in puzzle areas 201 on
level -4 this is the fastest route to
the reactor
uh-huh really
I'm supposed to believe that
it's not about the fastest fastest route
anyway we need to make as many puzzles
as possible
entropy energy
I see you
oh
oh we need something here that's
probably in there
pure not enough momentum
so maybe we jump like from
up at the top onto that thing and then
to the next
over there maybe
let's try
you know I'm not good at this kind of
stuff
[Music]
oh any intel no no Intel for me okay
what about the battery stuff oh there it
goes
uh yeah okay that's all we need
I think we don't need the jumping
platform anymore
[Music]
don't question this part
exactly
you're doing well though oh thank you
yes and two hours and I have yet to lose
my [\h__\h] mind spring springboard stand
on springboard to launch yourself
forwards happy jumping
oh a different kind of Jumpy thing
hmm
okay
Let's test it oh I ran on the side
I have to jump what
what what
it doesn't work
this long I guess so
why why you make me do this
Whiplash part of the experience too
ouch please fill in an injury report at
the end of the experience any laundry
would you like me to request a cold
compress from the medical team I don't
think there's any medical team alive
thanks for looking out for me would you
also like me to make an appointment with
a doctor about your funny shaved pets
what what my head is fine
well I can like personally relate to
this protagonist
and relatable
so we need the cube over here so first
we jump with the cube and then we rewind
it back
[Music]
[\h__\h]
oh wait no that was correct oh well I
thought for some reason that it was
supposed to stop here okay sorry little
little brain hurt moment
it was actually all correct
yeah yeah I thought it was supposed to
stop there why I don't know
my brain has been overused
but here we are
[Music]
Intel I would like some Intel give me
some Intel I want to know the Deeds the
dudes and the Deeds
oh
meat puzzle exercise assistant
[Music]
puzzles that's what we're doing generate
entry energy to charge entropy device
that's what we're doing indeed
use extra energy to rewind open make a
better tomorrow
now this is where it gets interesting
because that implies this is not the
first time it happened
how did people die though
how did we get to this point
because I guess these were humans that
were trying to save
the Earth and you know they can't live
forever but this has been going on for
hundreds of years
maybe it's just that or it's something
more evil
people die when they are killed
doesn't necessarily mean that that's
what's happened
energy 101 oh okay that's the same okay
very interesting
mips bad ending hmm
not quite but maybe yes
but yes but no yes but no
did you see that what
what I didn't see anything either I
Don't Think We're Alone
is quite limited I do however have a
great view of your chin
seriously someone's here
it's just a double robot probably and I
would love to meet the doggo robots
okay there's already too many platforms
I'll just test things out
um
you know
am I doing it correctly already oh oh
accidentally not really
but um
what do you call this the the female
um
um you know you know
the feeling that yeah intuition yeah
[Music]
oh maybe that's how people died they
tried to rewind themselves what happens
if you do that or so
it can overload both devices sometimes
creating a black hole and then
oh I am down
oh
to John unfortunately your contract
reduction request has been declined
concert reduction request
is the person basically just contract
termination request as you are aware
there are strict rules and regulations
on when entropy Center employees can
return back to Earth they are from Earth
there are specific times where this is
simply not possible
perhaps when Earth is exploding or or
yeah when we need people to still work
on like making it stop interesting
the Lord the Lord
hey John thanks for asking for
clarification on this I appreciate for
new employees it can perhaps get a bit
confusing on how time exactly works here
when we all came here we signed an
agreement that means that meant we could
potentially never see our families again
but that's okay we all know this and
that's the unfortunate sacrifice we have
to make to the cause
hmm
so in your example if you were to tell
your parents you were leaving and may
never see them again then leave and
arrive at the entropy Center for your
potentially lifelong stay what would
happen if the entry resenter rewinds
Earth to a point priority when you told
them you were leaving
what would happen if we were around
Earth to a point prior to when you left
and and where you were perhaps with
conversation with your parents well
interestingly from their point of view
you would just vanish Without a Trace
well this is depressing why do you gotta
go there man
of course we do inform families if this
does occur remember the entropy device
only reminds objects that are on Earth
that makes no sense
we are reminding things outside the
Earth all the time right now you remain
untouched
you have to be careful though it's why
we don't hire airplane pilots what does
that mean
what does that mean
what's that supposed to hint they're
talking about the big one I think they
mean the big one ah
the big rewinding machine okay
ah
if they would hire Pilots then
what if they rewind
then
sorry stretch then then since like you
know they're not working as Pilots
anymore but they used to before then if
they rewind something then that makes it
so that the pilots are not in their
airplanes anymore
now hold on interesting very interesting
makes sense but couldn't wouldn't you
apply this to a lot of things like truck
drivers or any anyone who has ever
driven a car before
so all of the humans stay higher here
must all be people who have never driven
a car before
if you think about it because once you
take that person out of the car and
Rewind something then the car will be
driving without the driver
and crash
or or never starts to drive in the first
place but but if you rewind to a point
where it's already driving
you know as I said like admit
conversation and so on and then stop
there then the car is driving already
and but without a driver and then crash
it's a paradox but it's interesting
interesting oh I feel like our brains
are expanding guys
though
create I've created
no no no this game created the time
paradox
why is that
hmm
what
[Music]
um
not so difficult probably but uh
[Music]
thank you
oh so close but I feel like it's not
supposed to be exactly done like this or
is it maybe it is
maybe
a little bit and that's too high
oh like this then like this would be
good maybe
[Applause]
it was a bit too low but not really
stand on it look around
no I think it's I think it can work
with everyone yeah
even if not
[Music]
look at them
this game is fun this game is fun I'm
telling you that
you guys should play it I'll give you
some codes today and then you guys
should play it
and I don't think we're clearing it
today but when we clear it another time
you guys must be ahead of me and then
help me
like like a
I'm gonna hook you up yeah
I'm gonna hook you up with the time
traveling skills
um
I want the rain to stop though
I don't like this particular
sprinkly Rain Sound
like it
oh by the way oh yeah today at 4
00 am
and once at 1am now it's 6 p.m though uh
had to do some Minecraft related stuff
at 1am you know
um was like messaging me like before 1am
but was like Hey we're doing um practice
if you want do you want to like
um join and I'm like yes let's let's do
it a little bit because I didn't get to
oh join the other practices
um
because I oh interesting
uh interesting
because they're like you know they
planned them all very spontaneously like
hey let's do this tomorrow and so on but
you know I have like weekly schedules I
guess most of the Japan members just
don't do weekly schedules so they can do
it spontaneously but not so much for me
kind of busy you know
yeah so super December
y'all she has sounded so tired she got
into the voice chat and I think it was 9
A.M for her and I think she did not
sleep much she was definitely up before
that
um like
like probably past midnight even
yeah and then she showed me and amen and
Muna
um the games that we would participate
in
and then I was told like a couple days
before that today at 4 00 am for me
would be like a meeting for overseas
participants
to explain everything
um
yeah and show us the games which ended
up kind of being the same thing as we
did with Subaru Senpai but I wanted to
be present because like for this meeting
everyone else like Miko Senpai and and
me was Senpai and the translator and
everyone was presents or I wanted to be
there you know
there's not many overseas members
participating in the first place so I
wanted to you know even if it's at a
shitty time for me I wanted to make sure
I'm there
yeah
um
I'll probably also on Sunday
have to be there at the opening like
before the opening ceremony for uh just
a voice check like a sound check
even though I don't participate until
the second half
which is shuttle
oh
I thought since I participate in the
second half I could maybe sleep more but
oh well it's okay I'll sleep afterwards
so the Luigi's Mansion stream will be
definitely late
yeah but just to let you know just so
you guys know what's up
but the games that we're participating
painting in are fun and I think we'll do
a good job I'll practice a bit more to
get like certain things down 100 because
it's like
um
at the moment I understand the the trick
on how to do certain things
but it doesn't always work especially
not under pressure
so I need to work on that
um
a nap
time in between and I don't think that
I'll be able to fall asleep again so
fast
but I might try I don't know
but once I'm awake even if I'm tired as
[\h__\h] it takes me quite a while to fall
asleep again that's the problem
anyway since I was talking I could not
focus on what's going on here I don't
understand
oh
uh
can the cute fly ah oh yeah right there
this here oh wait how far oh how high
does it go
oh
what did you just say eat term used for
when launching an object at High
Velocity would you like me to remove
this word from my vocabulary uh yes what
I'm stuck
I don't like her
she's lame
how sad
don't remove that vocabulary man you
don't know how hard this computer works
on learning words to talk just like us
humans
not relatable anymore
um kill Joy yeah
Kelly would be displeased
she's behind the times Aria yeah maybe
okay okay okay okay so we can throw it
but it does uh go through this and then
disappears so we
I would say
um
we hold it up here but don't place it
and then put it here and then we rewind
it and then we drop it when it's
floating up there
oh but no it will still be
all right I I stand I stand on the
platform never mind I'm thinking too
complicated
I stand on here
and
then we'll just fly over it's not easy
okay
floating on the right spot I think so
oh wait uh
oh why did I think that that gets rid of
the wait wait wait what gets rid of that
which which button
this one probably
oh well no problem no problem I I
understand
so
so I
[Music]
I hold it up here again
yeah and then I put it here
and then
uh
it's a bit hard to activate it from here
yeah
there you go
look at that look at that
[Music]
dude
eat sweet
there
what [\h__\h] I didn't see it again I don't
see them all I see is Jen so much
wow
over there hello is anyone there it
should be Center back people used to say
that the entry Center was haunted by
ghosts that's ridiculous you don't get
ghosts in space did you guys see
something though I didn't see it I was
focusing on somewhere else first
you saw it I saw nothing I've missed it
both times me too
probably partially because of the way I
move the camera sorry
okay well I think I know what it is
probably that robot dog right
he's been following us around
we focused on my [\h__\h]
no
well
[Music]
okay what are we looking at
um Can someone stop the [\h__\h] rain
I'm is annoying but not that I'm a Chan
uh-huh platform
why would we want it over there
what what is there
ah the door and the door okay
see there's a launch pad right there
oh
wow okay is this the only thing we're
working with
uh
so if I
if I launch myself
over there but we
but we'll see I need to move it there
first
yeah and um here
so I can rewind it to open the door
foreign
Drop It Like It's Hot oh but uh
I didn't consider this part okay it just
needs to go from
ah wait
from here to
here to
here
okay
oh
if I drop it it doesn't read it doesn't
delete the rewind right no okay
okay
can we make this jump
[Music]
that feels good when I get the jump
right
[Music]
this is a wall I got an achievement it
says this is a wall
this is open this is an apple
Apple pen
flexing
I don't know if I can call it Flex thing
but I'm not doing so bad right
there was one puzzle where I was kind of
embarrassing myself but so far besides
that
[Music]
I'm quite okay right
especially because I'm not even like
getting that much help from Chad I'm not
looking at your guys's solutions that
much but let me let me move you closer
doing fine thank you doing good yeah I
think so too
a little brain strong yeah I think the
portal experience
must definitely be helping me here
to think in Portals
or not in Portals but think in gun
portal gun
okay I just have this problem that I
work really badly with big
um structures like that
especially like I remember in Portal too
some of the big structures I had the
hardest time figuring out took me so
long
so
that Micah doesn't travel in this game
as well
hey Jacob did you see that last rewind
even last week it was crazy right that
huge asteroid traveling at such speed
just went straight into Earth I would
have hated to have been down there that
obviously so happy that we managed to
undo that one and it looks like Earth is
already working on a plan to stop it
when it approaches again in three months
time
good for them but wait when you say
approach again you just mean like when
the same thing happens again that you
just rewind it so you're not really
stopping it you're just keep on
rewinding the same thing it's not a
different asteroid right
right
so what we
saw the explosion of the Earth
was that also caused by an asteroid
probably landing on Earth and then
making the whole earth explode is that
possible that must have been a huge
asteroid
it more looked like that that Earth was
exploding from inside but
maybe that was just the the after effect
of the asteroid crushing Landing sorry
crashing so strongly with so much
momentum and Power
hmm
[Music]
no not possible what are you
Mr Right and
[Music]
I don't even have any financials as far
as I know
ah
Essie I'm supposed to land on that thing
Jump On It
[Music]
or am I
why are you telling me about it again
that's happening since like ages ago
Earth is dying I get it it can't undo it
I can't bring it back
[Music]
why not
I don't think I can
I'm hearing music
is that from the elevator
[Music]
use the ah detach it again okay it makes
sense but let me just check if there's
something cool here no
no no
[Music]
I feel like compared to two years ago
when I play games my tendency to
look at everything closer
has
become stronger and bigger
[Music]
like I want to run around I mean I think
I've always always had a little bit of a
tendency for that but mostly in jrpg
games and now now in non-jrpg games I
always also want to do that
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah baby
that's the sign of my growth as a gamer
so inspiring
[Music]
little rewind
but not quite
oh my God it's gonna be like New Year's
again soon
this whole life have a rewind like an
official rewind last year
if not then why not I think that was fan
made dream we want right
[Music]
there was no official one yeah
extendable Bridge directive enable input
to raise bridge I'm in hell we need one
I'm gonna wake up any second I just
hey these puzzles have been meticulously
crafted thank you what's going on
meticulous puzzles I'm glad you asked
puzzles are the most efficient way of
generating entropy energy it examines
the volume of information available in
any given event the more certain or
deterministic the event is the less
information it will contain more clearly
stated information is a mistake sounds
like an unsolved puzzle particularly in
the case of using entropy time
manipulations
which can be used to generate entropy
energy okay so observe puzzle solve
puzzle brain hurts yes very much energy
then rewind Earth yeah
exactly
but yes it is really like
full of myth bad end because we keep on
doing it and there's okay now I get it
guys
there's just like no change in events
it's always the same
um
how depressing man okay so how do I
how do I do that
I know I know I know I know I know I
think I know I think I know
this one was not accessible until we get
there
so
how about
we
all right
rewind because we don't need it there
anymore yeah yeah
okay there we go smart cookie oh the
Smart Cookie easy that was easy okay
now we're thinking of Cubes
bro
you'll never get better
okay it's good hey we're getting better
again
in town
excuse me I'm looking for some Intel
because it's actually quite fun
uh we have another PowerPoint
presentation cataclysm
I want to look that word up
[Music]
cataclysm
a large scale and violent event in the
natural world a sudden violent political
or social upheaval
a great flood
Deluge the legend
the great upheaval as an earthquake or a
war that causes sudden and violent
changes great destruction okay so it
can't just mean everything that causes a
big damage basically
a 20 45 interesting
cataclysm forecast
cataclysm frequency per month
oh
wow
I saw there's several ones not just one
big one
data a date entropy time
what
I had to go some type oh interesting AI
Uprising 7.3
oh [\h__\h] that's a thing in 2045 oh [\h__\h]
all those all those whole life
chatbot AIS they're gonna uprise and
destroy the real whole life members oh
that's the real hold for the
no
our own Bots are gonna destroy us why
don't you guys create them in the first
place you shouldn't have oh no the
original will be destroyed forever
because you guys wanted to replace us
with something that's just a fake
version of us how could you how could
you not have seen the consequences of
that how could you know
wow
hot singles and casino do you mean hot
signals in your area
hot signals in your area that was a
blackpink reference
okay we all watch Terminator well I
didn't even though I'm Austrian
she's extension Extinction
how is that a cataclysm
ecological collapse
what would that be
natural disasters asteroids asteroids a
big one
should watch it then
[Music]
[Laughter]
is it actually a good movie or is it
just a meme
is it actually good
one and two oh there's several ones
but Mom
I'm not your mommy okay I guess I am
one and two are fantastic first two
parts are fun oh oh everyone says that
oh [\h__\h] what happened after that
you may know students
got here
okay I guess I'll considerate
I wanna watch cute movies though
movies not actually I don't like action
movies but okay I'll do it for you guys
it's an interesting experience I guess
it's more like um catching up on
things everybody knows except me
just so I can have interactions with you
guys and talk about stuff
um
Arnold Schwarzenegger is cute
no
he's not
how is he killed
yeah my Austrian buddy okay okay okay
for Austria
okay ah
what why is this so easy there must be a
catch
there must be a catch
it's just a three-step puzzle
I appreciate it being easy though
as long as it's still easy I can still
enjoy it
quite a bunch
water is your best your aisle is your
body I guess oh what was that
I guess so
he improved oh
okay uh-huh
Terminator FPS game resistance is like
ghost Epoch Skyrim and The Killer Robots
and sci-fi guns
interested in Scott yeah Skyrim like
games I wanna play Skyrim like games
eventually
okay what do we have
Droid oh where did everyone go
what on Earth you're not on Earth you're
on the moon oh that's that's good to
know it's the same you know like what on
Earth not correct you are on the moon
what on moon what you meant to say is
what on moon happened here I guess so
sorry for that it's correct no she's
right
what you said Arya just sounds like a
stupid pun oh
happy hour dry cat food why is there so
much cat food was is this wait this
might be arya's table wasn't she like
into cats
no pets in the facility the animals will
thank you
free coffee free access to entry Museum
we did not get that good for the brain
got an assigned puzzle exercise
assistant
okay let's read some Intel
yum yum yum
Tonya Reed
I can't believe I did it but I actually
have nibbles
that you can't
with me right now I know I can't believe
he got through entry percentage security
he sat in the pouch of my hoodie for
like the whole journey here he is going
to have such a good time wandering
around the center
[\h__\h] where's the cat
yes please delete this email and don't
tell anyone and say hi to nibbles if you
see him around
re totally normal work email oh my God
Tanya what you smuggled a cat to the
entry Center how did you even do that
just don't let it wander off too far it
could be dangerous
did the cat like accidentally sit on the
on the button of a keyboard that
destroyed everything or so
I could see that yeah cat just steps on
the keyboard or like you know because
it's warm
yeah yeah yeah yeah it makes a lot of
sense
don't doubt to accidentalism a
catastrophe
um
upon for investigation to incidents 2140
where an unknown object was seen roaming
danger did they'd kill the cat
anxiously close to the main entropy
device we have now identified that this
was indeed a cat most likely a house cat
unfortunately the cat roamed too close
to the entry device called whilst it was
in operation and became kind
oh only leaving behind its name tag
nibbles
whilst we are deeply sorry for the
owner's loss please may we remind all
staff members that bring pets or any
other prohibited items from Earth is
strictly forbidden
nipples please note that only our office
cat Eve is permitted to stay at the
entropy Center and all other pets are
prohibited why is your cat Okay but the
other one not
foreign
oh
thank you
nibbles
nipples it was pretty obvious then she
brought a cat because why else would she
bring
cat food with her
they should have known unless she stated
and acted as if she was eating
the Kibbles herself
because that's just what she likes I
guess
anyway where are we bringing These Wings
this time
foreign
let's just go step by step
figure out as we go
and then we need one here
oh we need one there
oh interesting
interesting I think
oh it's in the middle right is this the
middle if I just drop it there
looks about right
um so
um okay okay okay I think I get it
we put this here
and then
we oh oh I almost fell down
rewind this
on it wait wait
stop
[Music]
it was like tumbling so I was thinking
oh [\h__\h] it's not gonna make it but there
we go
oh yeah
oh train track
oh no no no no no no no
[\h__\h] train tracks oh but both sides
are blocked
they built a train on the moon
canceled canceled canceled ah it's just
a train for like inside
the
entropy Center okay I think I have to
let this fall down
to a certain extent
foreign
we don't bring it back to its original
state which is like somewhere in between
sorry
oh yeah oh
oh oh
yes oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah
by the way guys I have some happy news
I finally managed
um
he said some times and dates
for the next whole talk guest
um
but
it will be so that
there will be two whole talks in one
week because I had to get that one more
guest in before the anniversary and I
still want to do an anniversary
separately their body temperature by
purring doing so increases muscle use
which in turn increases body temperature
to creating a healthy and regulated
lifestyle for the feline it is also
widely speculated that cats purr as a
healing mechanism why are you telling me
this shouldn't we be trying to get out
of here I detected you or subscribed to
entropy cat facts do you wish to
unsubscribe no
keep me subscribed guys I did not say
double hole talk when did I say double
Hollow talk is just one but um
what are you what
there is just two whole talk in one week
that's what I said
no no not in one stream no no two whole
talks in one week not in one stream
because
needed to get one more in before the
anniversary and anniversary is in the
same week basically yeah that's still
double
I guess
that's what double hole saw that what
what
that's still double I guess double in
one week yeah yeah but that will mean
that it's kind of like a busy
week because I have to prepare so much
[Music]
but I think it will be worth it I have
some surprises for the anniversary
episode yay
hey Ben can you find this a stop thanks
cheese best regards what can I look at
it well this is not even interesting
what is this Intel
well now we finally oh
okay
[Music]
nice nice colic we have there
amount of work can you please get on to
these immediately
solve them within five hours thank you
anyone here who experiences that kind of
[\h__\h] at work
foreign
yeah
luckily no
kind of please don't remind me
the only similar thing I've had before
was
um like
my boss oh
would give me
or several bosses would give me a [\h__\h]
ton of things
to go through the shredder
but like like an unbelievable amount of
documents like mountains of them
and just be like shred this for me but
first of all they all had like some
um you know some Clickety clackity pins
in them not the ones that you can just
remove easily no the the what do you
call them
The Click
click ones yeah samples Staples so
they don't they wouldn't go like that
through the shredder so I would have had
to remove every single staple with a lot
of effort because it's not it takes time
it's [\h__\h] annoying I tried for a
while but I must confess
and I don't think I'm the only one who
would do that
but I did not shred at all
because that happened so often too and
what the [\h__\h] no I used the staple
remover but we only had I mean I don't
know if there's like a really like
modern staple removal nowadays but it
was literally just like this kind of
like
wait
stable remover
oh yeah I
could yeah that's what I'm talking about
there are only those shitty little
yeah clappy things that look like um
like a monster's mouth
it's literally just that it's a pain in
the ass man cut off the edge
I could have done that but even then
still it was a mounted several mountains
of really a [\h__\h] ton of stapled
documents
yeah well you know
there's a different type
well when I Googled it what I see is uh
a staple remover that looks like
oh my God there's staple removers with
animal heads really realistic looking
animal heads like bears and hippos and
snakes the snake one is cool
the snake one actually looks amazing
damn there's dragon head ones too that's
fun
okay okay okay
um so where were you let me like refresh
you
um let me put you there and um ring you
with me
I want to snake one now yeah that's
that's genius
because it looks exactly like a snake
head
[Music]
yeah I can see that in my mind Google it
it looks perfect
easy why are the puzzles so easy I
thought they would be more difficult
are we still in tutorial mode
I I was told you know that it was gonna
be more difficult than portal
read it before
[Music]
my Google is sick here
industrial shredders which is oh yeah I
I'm guessing there's industrial
shredders who will even shred or like
have no problem with those Staples but
ours had an issue with that
um
ah tea is good is there Intel here no oh
man
I'm like really into the Lord here I
want to know more tell me more tell me
more did you get really far tell me more
tell me more
I'm about to apocalypse
Sunday morning sipping my tea
let me think
I want a rhyme
Sunday morning sipping my teeth then I
see that astrosity
a [\h__\h] huge
uh
what's the what's it called again
asteroid
destroying Earth
water
oh what rhymes with asteroids what
rhymes with asteroid
Earth is burning but I feel free
Polaroids oh
[\h__\h] asteroid I'm gonna take this
moment with a pull over it or so
Vocaloid
Vocaloid in that anyway what are we
doing
let's focus
okay I think I understand we only have
one Cube so
fast
what does this do it opens the door okay
so we probably go from here to here to
yeah
so yeah I might be wrong but let's just
check it out okay like oh my god oh wait
there's a oh no
but that's just mean like how could you
do that
I did not see that coming
man oh my God
okay now let's not repeat those mistakes
okay
got it
I can't wait
there you go
and Drop It Like It's Hot
um
yeah
all right
go next
that's what I'm talking about baby
whoa
yes
you are such a beautiful Cube I would
take you home if I could but I can
bye-bye see ya no offense
where's that dog where's that cute robot
dog I want to meet the dog sort of
that we have entropy reactor Transport
Service puzzle areas o6 note interview
transport system offline this will take
us towards the reactor maybe the
switches can activate it switches
switches switch switch
okay I will not announce yet by the way
who the next whole talk guest is as
always it will be announced before
and or like with the weekly schedule but
just want to let you know that it will
be on a Friday because
weekend days were not possible
for this guest but yeah I will do the
anniversary episode on a Sunday
the 20th
I think I think it was this one here
yeah
don't know about the time yet but it
will be on the 20th and then the the
um next guest before that will be on
Friday the 18th I guess
at the usual whole talk time yeah
okay what are we doing
I didn't see anything here we go now
you're getting it
huh
well it doesn't look like there was
anything valuable in those boxes
actually it looks like there was nothing
in there
um so I'm supposed to go jump on notes
probably
hey look there's a
steaming oh oh oh oh
well okay
[Music]
they were dropped from here right okay
so why did we
why did why did I drop them
oh okay I did not want to I did not want
to unrewind this one
default was too high yeah I'm thinking
the same thing but no
[Music]
[\h__\h] I need to drop them again
do I have like fall damage so far I have
not noticed any
oh okay no foul damage
I think I have to jump over to the next
one when they're on the floor because I
could not jump on to the next one
oh
[Music]
while they were in air it looked like
too much distance
Okay so
a jump
are you built different like every Arya
in this world are yeah maybe maybe the
name Arya is a name oh why did that one
not fall down I thought I dropped it
[Music]
maybe the name Arya gives you like super
special powers and success in life
[Music]
maybe if I ever have a girl daughter I
will call her Arya actually I don't
really like the name so much
at all
but it feels like a name that comes with
success
and
smartness
a girl called Arya will be smart
protagonist's name
well Arya is definitely not a
protagonist in Game of Thrones but I was
talking with my mom about this I said to
my mom mommy I don't know what you think
about this but I think it would be super
cool and not not completely unlikely
if
um after House of the Dragon
they would maybe
why am I doing this [\h__\h]
oh
they would maybe come up with
um like a sequel where
Anna is the main character and it
continues after where a Game of Thrones
left off where she you know left still
and to go um to you know the other side
of the world alone with her little ship
think that would be very popular I think
a lot of people would want to see where
Arya goes after that and and what she
would do
and who she meets and what's on the
other side and all that you know I think
that would work really well and since
that's not written down in any of the
books right so they would have so much
like Freedom with that they don't have
to go buy the books but I still think it
would it would get a big audience I
don't know what do you think
my mom said she agrees she would like to
see that too and she also thinks it has
potential
well yeah he doesn't have to ride it
because obviously he wouldn't make it in
time
but I think it has so much potential
I don't think so honey I agree with you
mom so you agree with me
Mama totally knows best
[Music]
why are you giving the credit to my mom
um
can't trust anyone to make it yeah yeah
true okay so what did we unlock see this
is the problem I have of like big areas
I don't I don't understand
it's too big
I unlocked something though
it's just safe to go down now
something on the bottom and these things
what is that
oh I'm coming down
let me take a look
is the train operating or what
oh
yes
oh cool
show me oh
[Music]
right now
[Applause]
[Music]
when you finish the chapter it seems I
got an achievement too
pouring some more tea
I'm like TT well done that took you 48
attempts
hey
thank you I appreciate the Applause
always very motivating
[Music]
where are we also how far am I in the
game I think the
wait a second by now there should be
like a approximate lengths right for the
game someone must have figured it out
already the entropy Center game length
will it come up already
no oh wait
10 to 15 hours
15 hour experience but I didn't see that
was like a six hour full playthrough and
a nine Hour full playthrough and a four
hour full playthrough on YouTube
hmm
which is accurate
took me 10 hours wow
maybe there are some panels nearby to
power it
oh and yeah we can move it back
thing I have panels panels we need
panels
and I I like peeked into a
six hour playthrough and it didn't look
like a speed run at all
it looked like they were still like
trying to figure things out
well oh
yeah oh yeah maybe if I bring this thing
all the way up here I can peek into that
room
oh but I need to get on top of it
oh
I wonder how far I can go
get on top of you
damn it
took your three hours to get the chapter
two what
slow though
there we go here we can jump on top of
here
yeah yeah I mean they're definitely
faster than me but oh sure
[Music]
oh oh oh
what happened what happened do we have
the thing here oh oh that thing is going
back no but did we unlock the door yes
we did
and Intel
no no Intel we get this important thing
right here
[Music]
number one
has been discovered
Z
uh
sorry can I
can you like let me prove
about here
wait
I'm coming to you
oh
sorry
I feel like I'm destroying it oh
okay first one works
now
now to find another one I wonder if it's
like the same way or
[Music]
somewhere over here oh oh oh
looks like everyone left in real hurry
I was like a little um convenience store
here cool
wow wow
what time is it oh seven seven pm
I wonder I kind of want to get a pizza
today but I have some food I I still
have some left over
because it feels like I cooked for two
and a half people with that
um supposedly with those enchiladas that
are not really enchiladas so I have a
little bit left over of that
platforming and I have leftover from
yesterday so actually I should eat my
leftovers
no worries
[Music]
but cooking has been fun recently I've
been cooking so much like
I have to admit that especially after
that incident
um and me just like not feeling very
good mentally
I haven't been cooking uh much a while
ago and
I may or may not have wasted some
hellofresh recipes because of that
yeah which I feel bad about but recently
I've been cooking much more and I use up
the the recipes mostly oh
interesting
what oh
yeah the one I made yesterday was really
simple
but it's so yummy
so good I swear
yeah my confidence confidence I guess
not I'm not getting my confidence back
I'm getting confidence in cooking for
the first time
to begin with because I never had
confidence in cooking but recently
really I've been making so many recipes
oh if I count the recipes that I made or
the the foods that I made in the past
um three months
that's probably more than I cooked ever
in my whole life
wow wow
wow
[Music]
would you make them again yeah
definitely I mean maybe not all of them
but I wanna Mark like which ones I
really enjoyed and which ones were like
man and which ones are easy to recreate
um without the hello fresh subscription
you know let's look at this
Jordan Munn storage room we need to call
maintenance a door to the storage room
is busted and won't open yeah yeah there
are free electrical panels that started
fizzing and popping it's probably those
that are causing it have you noticed our
stock of tint beans is looking a bit low
let's do a stock chat today to make sure
all right so wait free
what a nice hint
wasn't even necessary I would have
figured it out eventually easy
beans
[Music]
that's the thing I need maybe there's
some beans here should we help them
restock
[Music]
oops
yeah I got better things to do
no one's using the convenience store
anyway so not worth my time
Tiana's favorite well when did Tiana say
her favorite is beans
what I don't remember such a thing
[Music]
intro episode
what
new puzzle element introduction Bridge
Cube Place Bridge cube in stationary
position to create bridge to walk across
ah
well that looks very familiar too
doesn't it
where do we want it and when do we want
it
uh-huh okay
now
okay okay calm down guys calm down
whoa It's a bridge oh Lord
does anyone know what's in the room just
after puzzle 0601 puzzle solver
yeah I noticed that too can we call
maintenance to get the panel fixed I did
but they can't find the working panel
for it guys yeah no one has been in the
room in ages nothing is in there anyway
literally nothing pretty sure it's empty
your best bet is to just forget about
that room really honestly nothing in
there it sounds us as [\h__\h]
huh
which room are we talking about which
one are we in right now
oh well
where does this go to
secret room
huh
am I like
I'm like hoping that I could put this
somewhere and I find the secret room
that they're talking about
which one is it that this one is 0601 so
wait they said the room after 0601 is
locked and they can't get in
well okay
I think that's what they said
ah
so we can rewind these cubes too right
in that case
I forgot for a second how to drop it oh
my God my brain waves are hurting
yeah
okay I'll take this with me
obviously we need it
Bridge Cube novice badge has been added
to your interview badge collection
I wonder how many more cubes we'll get
what kind of Cubes so many possibilities
Intel Intel oh so much Intel they're
spoiling us with Intel
Timmy the end Timmy
Timmy
hey Timmy I'm sending this to you in
confidence basically I found an unused
office space just after 0601 I'm sure
that the entry percent of the world
everything is ending you've seen how
many times they've tried to rewind that
cataclysmic event and nothing is
changing yeah we're screwed they can't
fix this one they might have been able
to rewind the past 2 million
world-ending disasters but this one is
the one trust me
beans
[Music]
yes that's right a stockpiled beans in
the office space just after 0.601 so
when it all hits the fan come join me
and we can survive out here on my
plentiful stockpiles of babes I just
steal them from the entry Market I don't
think they've cottoned on yet delete
this email address probably monitoring
10 full hats available in the bottom but
really
where's the bottom drawer
so this is the secret room
oh wait maybe somewhere in here but I
can't open them there's too many beams
there's so many
things my mom would not survive on this
she does not like beans
man
okay funny
that's funny they did not survive though
it seems like
but where are the dead bodies though
if they died by natural causes
wouldn't they have like dead bodies here
so I guess they just let Eva left
or they were like I don't know deleted
these yeah they just banished I guess
somehow oh dear nice view
oh it's so bright
I feel like it's getting brighter
yeah
is it a nice view or is it a bad view
hmm
okay they obviously want us to put that
here but
where else do we need it
uh-huh
a nice baby yeah
class
half full
nice view of a bad thing it's
fascinating it's nature
okay I don't see really anything
uh but I can't pass through here so
[\h__\h]
I'm gonna go there first you're
bamboozling me
oh
I like the the holographic look of this
oh oh let me look
[Music]
cool
sick
oh cute
Ah that's open ah that did that okay
okay and this I guess
open the door okay
Love is an Open Door
[Music]
I should not be singing that
I need the cube right here I suppose
all right yeah
close
but it works and then remove remove all
that
better view yeah
yeah it's hoping for
uh what am I doing I had this one
smart
am I or am I not a smart chocolate chip
cookie
chunky chocolate chop chop chop chop
chop chop chop
where do I go
oh
now I need that probably
can you make it back all the way back
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
does that help me
uh
no
what
it was not that easy
God okay okay we're reaching a point
where
cannot think clearly anymore rewind a
bit more
oh okay
so
what you're here
ah well you're right you're right
okay everybody
[Music]
of course of course
I knew it okay um Let me refresh that
um
we can do this uh
uh
ah
oh God
yeah but I better fix this again though
no because I don't know man
ah
[Music]
[\h__\h] maybe I shouldn't have I don't know
sorry sorry Cube we have to do it like
this I have to re redo everything now
unfortunate
[Music]
I I will make it worthwhile
my lovely Cube
my lovely not really Companion Cube let
me know it first here
yeah okay now join me
nice positioning
and yeah okay
does Phoenix have a natural predator you
mean a natural enemy
[Music]
no no no
except frog
I guess so
only a frog can hurt a phoenix as we
have seen there is evidence so I cannot
deny
I've got a big butt but I cannot lie
oh this job this jump
ah
don't miss yeah I Don't Wanna Miss
wow
device
another has been instrumental in
revising more than one thousand major
disruptions given civilization
wow
I mean all that sounds really positive
where did they like [\h__\h] up where did
they become evil how and why because I I
still don't see them as being evil
maybe they're not evil maybe not
everything in this world is evil
these are interview worker Bots they
assist staff members at keep the center
running smoothly
a little one-track minded
it's dedicated though I'll give him that
how
[Music]
help him cute I'm too cute
you want to play
well I stopped him from doing it but I
can't do anything with him
hmm what is what is that expression
supposed to tell me
um
mmm
we become friends later right
be friends Borg
is he born are you not entertained
trying to entertain you
doing my best here
okay
we put these here but probably
not until later
oh I see so you probably have to reach
from here to here uh so
wait
refresh
go
[Laughter]
okay good for now
and then ah
probably need this like here
um
but maybe also here
perhaps
we're gonna try
cook could work
jump from one to another move it jump
from one to another and then move that
thing
if that's enough momentum then we're
good
oh but wait that that
that looks optional I want to check that
out
it looks like optional lore is being
offered to us
definitely yeah but how
I guess I just
jump
over there but
from
[Music]
how do I get there
because if I jump just from the ground I
won't make it but I wonder if I put the
platform just here
and jump from here to there to there if
that would do the trick
that's right so let's abandon my
original plan right now because I'm
curious about this
maybe like
that was so unexpected what the [\h__\h]
I was like really focused
[Laughter]
okay that's nothing to be afraid of
scared by a jump
Next Level jump scare
okay and then
bring it back and hold
[Music]
nah oh
she did it she did it
for the Lord
the entropy puzzle operative team please
may we remind you that once you have
completed all puzzles into entry Center
you must contact your entry supervisor
to undergo your own entropy reversal
remember only puzzles that I've
completed for the first time generate
entropy energy the solution has to come
organically not through previous memory
in order for entry free energy to yield
High values they are the developers of
this game are actively
trying to stop you from replaying this
game they only want first time
experiences
all right I mean weird decision but okay
this is why all puzzle operatives must
undergo entropy reversal and be resent
back to a time when you had not
complained the puzzles you will lose all
memories past that point which is why we
encourage leaving notes to yourself and
others
to remind yourself of the friendships
and relationships yeah but none of the
puzzle solutions right the only other
stuff
mm-hmm
and allows you to more quickly
re-establish those we thank you for your
hard work and re and dedication
yeah but really like
force yourself you know like if you have
notes telling you hey you were friends
with this this is like in those TV
dramas where someone loses their memory
and they forget the person that they
were married to and being told you were
married to that person
it does not really immediately bring you
back those feelings you know so
difficult man it's not that easy
oh
no this is not rewinding
this is
entropy reversal
hmm I guess that's different
or
it's the only time when reminding
yourself is acceptable
I don't know maybe under supervision or
whatever
let's look at the PowerPoint entropy
Market profits and trends 2045. profits
and Trends uh-huh looking pretty decent
male female employees not so bad
sales
is the bottom one
cataclysm is avoided
is the top one
is there a link no
have you say 18th January what day is it
now
hmm
okay thank you for the lore
was worth it 10 out of 10 lore
all right
here we go
again refresh that and
um oopsie uh actually no we start
um
here
do we need it here too
I don't think so
okay
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
nibbles nibbles
we will miss you you are missed even
though I didn't know you I miss every
cat that I missed
that ever existed
mm-hmm
[Music]
okay
don't mess it up
let's go
yay Pro jumper it was your birthday
three days ago
happy
birthday
to
Nicole yay
you love my cats of course I do I love
every cat
oh this jump
[Music]
don't [\h__\h] it up don't [\h__\h] it up don't
[\h__\h] it up don't forget
I will jump sideways rather than
straight
[Laughter]
[Music]
hey I'm doing so good with these puzzles
you did that puzzle so quickly you could
enter the interview Center speed run
tonight thank you I was just gonna say
no to the encouragement no I was right I
was speedily enough
if I am slow then it's just because I'm
tangenting and that you know distracts
me but oh I don't know it's so bad I've
become smarter hell yeah
what are we dealing with now open any
sprinkles
oh
what's that
is that like on the top
you would not believe your eyes if 10
million uh blue Sparks
lit up the sky as we fell asleep hmm
okay we need a cube here that goes over
there obviously
hmm
ah here it is but
it makes me go through
aha well that will be the final
destination right but yeah it makes me
go through like um all the blue things
that get rid of my
memories
Thanks for the Memories
I need to turn that off
okay that's the way to turn it off
uh
but that is the only Cube that we're
getting it seems okay we can figure this
out since we can get from the top to the
bottom
by just jumping down
it's the day of having a good ocean
today why how come it is I guess are we
talking about the fourth or the fifth
or
maybe the fifth
probably the fifth huh
gold like oh Goshi
no the fourth
yeah
Yoshi
yon yo I guess whatever I don't know
okay ah all over zero she for young
c44
oh
yeah I see it oh all right it's November
it's the month of having all kinds of
different like good days in Japanese
language so it's that time of the year
again
oh yeah it could also mean good birthday
yeah yeah remember that from last year
do you you guys remember we had that
last year yeah
foreign
okay
um so
basically
and position is this
we bring it down
probably put it here next
then we can pass through without
deleting the memories
ah with the cube but
uh
[Music]
we rewinded to that spot now I think
because where was the here
no I still wouldn't be able to get here
without passing through
wait I will I will find a way
let's just say I bring it back
oh
whoa
[Music]
let me take a look
yeah
Soul business
anything about my Buffs my my butt puff
no
maybe
um
by the latest for the
fourth fourth Fourth Fest
priorities my butt is not a priority
guys for us it is but not for others
unfortunately
and say that in the usual room I've seen
but I cannot enter the usual room that
easily
because what if what if I get stuck and
then you know
and then we have a problem anyway I need
to use my brain real quick
era era era
era
error era
how do we get you here how how
do I get you
no uh well I mean I mean I mean
I mean
but wait the cube not only the memories
but also the cube disappears right when
I pass through
yes I can and try
um
oh yeah oh oh sorry that was not my
intention
ah is that the top
where was it again by default
here okay
oh
just noticed they're watching me
are they watching me all are they trying
to get in hmm
trying to attack me
[Music]
I hope this works like I
want it to work
I Kissed a Girl
[Music]
just to try it
I hope my boyfriend don't mind it
but then how do we get us back to the
top
isn't the rewind canceled now because I
picked it up and changed its future
it fell so wrong it felt so right oh no
it's still going there
uh but I don't remember what it was
there
or there right
I felt so wrong it felt so right
Oh Oh see it's kind of
no never mind it's probably there
I'll walk up first Oh see it worked
already
I like this one
does this guy say anything else
time death it ain't good time death is
when the health of the center is
threatened which could result in
becoming non-operational and
non-repairable then there would be no
way to rewind time and Earth could be
lost forever
reactor we can't enable the entropy
device until that is repaired we're
getting close
[Music]
well let me look at the lore first
hey Connor I just wanted to update you
on the progress of fixing those last few
errors with the entropy device I'm glad
to say that they should all be fixed now
and no more glitches should occur
um what we found was that occasionally
in very rare circumstances the main
entropy device would not rewind Airborne
aircraft in tandem with the rest of the
Earth
ah
this led to some very strange
experiences for those passengers as you
can imagine where some would land at
their flight destination but perhaps
five years in the past
oh
we've now rectified that issue and also
reset any personal timelines of affected
people was so nice so professional
they're so professional they're actually
getting their job done
they see you the things that go wrong
and fix them accordingly like I don't
see anything going wrong here like
everything seems
like perfect
oh
where are we here
what was that
I just leaped
because of the sofa
how are you doing her
looking
um a little bit under the weather
just a little bit though which is ironic
because the Earth is under
the influence of the weather at all
times
looking hot
wow it's so pretty wow
sorry I'm drinking tea give me a moment
oh wow
[Music]
[Applause]
oh which is oh [\h__\h] which is top which
is bottom
what's up
[Music]
reach the top of the silo via stairwell
what next
well I think trial and error is a little
bit necessary here
first go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go
go go go go go
reach the top of the silo uh maybe
why did that not work before maybe I was
already too late
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
fun
I really feel like I'm playing Portal
right now
you guys should play it too if you miss
portal
so cool so cool
[Music]
uh wait wait I'm I'm I'm having a moment
of I don't know what to do okay stop
I'm not lost completely but I think I
[\h__\h] up oh [\h__\h] uh
[Music]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
um
I don't know I don't know
if I had it I had it but then I stumbled
over my feet
I have problems like in in stress
situations uh stopping the objects in
the right place
but yeah we can manage we'll figure it
out
like
uh-huh
go go go go go why are you planning me
to the wine because I'm being watched
but you guys make me nervous
[Music]
no keep on watching keep on watching
and go next
and now here's the crucial moment
there we go there we go that's nice
calm and easy so we want it back
completely I suppose so
ah
yes okay
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
well done and thank you for not getting
me wet are you don't mention it
tap me Pat on shoulder
oh surfboard nice
oh also it says number six so I feel
like I I'm already at chapter six oh no
it's almost like you're only in chapter
two
foreign
yes it is okay
given the circumstances
okay but can I read some of the Lord
please
Jordan sells e let me know if you see an
entry report roaming around with a post
stuck onto their forehead with an e on
it it was me they were acting strangely
almost developing some kind of sentience
so I've put a Post-It on their forehead
so that I can keep an eye on it there's
been loads of reports of entropy Bots
and puzzle exercise assistants growing
in intelligence and sentience as time
has gone on some puzzle operatives even
said that their peas have been cracking
jokes and chatting casually so strange
like saying stuff like Yeet anyway let's
keep an eye on it we may need to meet up
with it to discuss this further
see this is where it gets dangerous I
was I
was acting like my pea seems
weirdly human
like
literally human
like very human
creepily human not okay human
what is this can I enter
no okay of course not
oh it was removed just by Standing On
Top of here interesting okay I didn't
even do anything
what's up here
[Music]
wow
we made it vacation time baby
Swing Swing swim
oh
hey
what that is so dark no vacation for me
do I not deserve a vacation also do I
need to read the lore again
puzzle area zero seven I'll read it just
in case recommendation
are you okay with that Astra yes it is
okay but the water the circumstances it
looks so gone
just taking a look don't want to miss
anything
[Music]
[Applause]
there's holy music playing
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
would actually be quite nice yeah it
wasn't for
you know the end of the world
it's [\h__\h] nice
even with the end of the world that's
what makes it even nicer
[Music]
could wear to end wouldn't you want to
watch it end in a place like this
isn't that sound nice
I mean no
missed the PC what PC
there's a PC here the floor
I messed up his name
no way oh
that's a hard one that's a tough one
continue to subscriber to fun interview
bags did you know that Deja Vu is not a
regular or normal occurrence and is
actually easily explained by the
existence of the entropy Center the
entropy device will around Earth a
desired amount of time and of course all
organic beings capable of memory will
have the memory State we want to back to
that specific point in time however it
has been observed that there are
fragments of atoms that will retain this
previous information
cool hence the occasional feeling of an
intense Deja Vu where you may feel a
certain event has occurred before which
is most likely because it did
I
will never be able to let go of this
knowledge
oh [\h__\h]
yeah bye yeah bye
should have not acquired this knowledge
that is dangerous knowledge to have
oh my God Amelia Watson you again
[Applause]
[Music]
fragments who say fragments of knowledge
fragments are not enough to fix things
oh oh interesting what
am I supposed to go over there how
[Music]
how
well
is there another one
everyone
[Music]
for the other gems
huh
what
um
pink can't you think
oh I need to go to an island meeting
I think that's that's hurting my
thinking about capabilities
capacities
those capacities with abilities
[Music]
what what do you mean we're Vines
between the gaps
is one
um
okay nevermind
um when we start in the back
hi
oh I should probably refresh
oh what's up
what did I just do
[Music]
what what does after I absolutely
impressed f
uck
oh well
I chose my trail
[Music]
oh
oh okay
I think that's it
okay
it makes the gun shoot faster
you can't make a fool of me
[Music]
okay nice
foreign
[Music]
ristata
we start
Ed
okay okay let's go
[Music]
yeah no climbing
oh speaking of climbing you know for the
I thought I was gonna go hiking right so
I went out to buy some hiking shoes but
when I went to that like sports
a shop you know that had all kinds of
shoes like hiking shoes and running
shoes but for running shoes it was
did I just
I think I reset it
is
instead of dropping it I'm stupid I'm
losing control over the keyboard and go
[Music]
so what was I saying oh yeah shoes yeah
no that's not where I started shoes
and
and the hiking shoes
looked like kind of playing
like mountain climbing shoes
it looked like kind of Overkill
so I did not buy those and I hope I
won't regret I bought like from the
running shoe section there were like
several types
that said you know one said you know
normal running one said I don't know
different running and one said
Trail
in English so
I thought that would be more fitting
because I'm not gonna climb a mountain
it'll be fine brown shoes transfers are
fine I think so too yeah we're not gonna
go like like really like hardcore hiking
[Music]
okay
um yeah I'm not planning to climb Mount
Fuji we're not really planning to climb
like any mountain
just
[Music]
fine
nice little walk
outside
nothing too high level
um
so I think it will be fine they have
like really chunky
Souls Souls
that's a right word
oh
I'm sorry it will be like that sometimes
[Music]
because I don't wear the right shoes
BC Canada if you like hiking let's BC
Canada is it a mountain
[\h__\h]
at least it happened in the beginning
[Music]
no gaming shoes
oh
a province
[Music]
huh
yeah
well guys
[Music]
see see I started to jump with no
confidence that's what happens man when
you when you're not confident when I
saved it
oh man
this will be the end of me
oh
[Music]
I'm so sorry
yeah
oh man build an island meeting
soon soon
okay
foreign
[Music]
the biggest riddle of them all
the biggest challenge of them all
if only I was a Skyrim Horus yeah
[Music]
I feel like I'm cursed now I I just
can't get it right
oh God oh God oh God
[Music]
please
oh [\h__\h] I'm so scared
haha
[Music]
don't get too excited
I'm not seeing any way to get across
well that was fast conclusion not yet
not yetable objects
nice to see you again
yeah we bumped into each other just
after I woke up
[Music]
and that we should stand back okay
you little [\h__\h] you you know you can get
me with happy chirps
I love I love um you know with Clips
um one thing that always gets me
is when Clippers subtitle us with like
angry noises or happy noises or so it
always gets me
and we're time
burp noises stuff like that I am
you are cute
or am Monster Energy yeah look he's
happy
oh don't lie no touch
you like a boob I like a boob no
don't we all
what about pooping the Boop the boob oh
going off
bye bye I'm leaving sayonara
sayonara
maybe I find a secret over here
was this the real path
or jungle
monkey noises
exploration I need to go to an idol
meeting really urgently
oh what's shiny oh it's glowing
it looks like people used to have
um I'm a golden Island meeting
see you
[Music]
right I'll be right back don't leave
foreign
[Music]
yo what's up
feet
yeah
what and are there frogs why are there
frogs excuse me
[Music]
okay
I don't know how long I should play this
because I have no idea how far I am
um
I wonder how far I am because I'm
feeling like uh I feel like they told me
uh
how long they say the game
would take
oh yeah they told me eight to ten hours
I've been playing for four maybe that
you say only one third really
okay I'll play for two more hours
then we should get like two around the
middle Maybe
streamer hours yeah yeah
it's 8 P.M so I can totally keep on
going also because I'm like really
having fun I really like this game
I hope I hope it will get like the
attention it deserves
hmm
one more game on tonight
right now I'm still enjoying it very
much I felt like way more under pressure
and
stupid when playing Portal to be honest
like I felt like
I was the only one not getting it and it
took me way too long to get everything
[Music]
so like deep down there while I was
streaming I always felt like so Under
Pressure like if I don't get this
solution in the next minutes then people
gonna think I'm the like most stupid
person alive ever you know
oh these cookies are so amazing
and that pressure makes it even worse
and you have this block in your head and
you just don't understand anything
anymore
um
anybody here I guess it's it's just the
riddles are easier I guess so far
[Music]
so I'm having
still a relatively easy time grasping
them
no
um
the puzzles
and I think the lack of pressure
also helps me
um
to focus
and and understand things easier oh yeah
oh yeah interesting
because I think
maybe I could have done a better job at
Porto and understood things better if I
wasn't under under all that pressure
okay so I don't think this is how we're
supposed to do it probably but what if I
quickly jump down there and try to catch
the cube and jump back on the platform
I don't know if that's really how you do
it
hmm
maybe not
stream of burning something when you are
thinking about so many things along with
the game the problem is always hindered
a bit Yeah like also having some
conversations in between
people had way more experience before
um
mm-hmm
now right now you and me were equal
[Music]
oh these cookies are so good
I think they've opened my eyes I'll be
munching on these for the next
two months
I'll keep on rebuying them because now
they got me hooked
[Laughter]
if I do it with more confidence I feel
like we could do it
but I really don't know if this is
really the way because it seems
stressful
um
[Music]
what do you think guys is there a
different way
is that way
away or a different way I feel like
eatable
[Music]
there must be him
away
there must be another way
come with me
how do we do this
think Cube think
oh
so
First Step should still be the same
bring the platform
there
no don't know
don't know
ah
okay okay
hold it off the cliff Edge
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah okay refresh that and then
hold hold hold holding holding holding
holding
bring it back
it's too simple
huh
rewind
drop and go
lovely Cube
so nice to see you here
because I'll go next I suppose go here
and I will lose you goodbye my lovely
Cube
I'll say hi to your family
entropy Museum this place has a museum
yes
reflect upon the Deep history of the
center special rewinds of the earth we
made it to the dead
oh that looks like lore oh [\h__\h] so uh
but that other entrance we saw in the
beginning I guess was just a different
entrance to the museum
because I'm pretty sure it said like to
the museum or so
we couldn't go there
Mike Tanner what's your setup hey Jared
you won't believe it but I have just
achieved big setup I'm talking Sun I'm
talking drinks I'm talking outside come
to the museum I'm just out the front
this is so much better than being stuck
inside doing puzzles I've hooked into
one of the museum power outlets oh my
way Mike I'll bring a second keyboard oh
they're gonna have a LAN party
but yeah I mean
it's a good location but think about all
the sand entering your setup
messing up your PC
there we go Tim I'm gonna show for
today's puzzling decides where are you
if we find you out if we find out you
are setting up last night I I told you
outside the cafeteria again we will give
you a formal disciplinary please come
immediately
is the second keyboard here
did he bring his stuff ever
[Music]
oh what a cliffhanger
it's just one PC ah
[Music]
oh
open every day
on it those are different opening times
I feel like before it was different
opening times
maybe there's a different place
at a long party I've never
done something like that insufficient my
brother did I think we have to find it
well we can just jump over no one's here
okay
I will allow it
jump over that oh
[Music]
some of these dialogues happen too early
but I haven't even seen yet what they
are seeing
lore lore lore lore excuse me have you
seen Miss Allure
huh sorry please go on shopping center I
was instrumental in Saving the
problem Extinction again
wow pandas are alive because of the
entropy Center they're taking credit yo
avoid those arrows
foreign
I can't go wherever the hell I want but
first I need to go here hello hello
thank you thank you for the ticket thank
you soon
then where
plants
what is this
[Music]
ah damn
how did you do that yeah 2001 the
entropy Center successfully reduced
global temperatures worldwide oh 2001
doesn't really work it's 2022. in the
year 2001 and our temperatures are [\h__\h]
it's just getting hotter hi are you
you're not here
you're not alive I can't interact with
you
someone like turned you off
[Music]
kick me oh
it's a robot
and you've been working
it's it's just yeah okay okay
entropy Bots help assist staffers in
resetting puddles cleaning security
staff Memorial despite multiple rumors
entry work your butts are not sentient
oh
[Music]
oh well there must be a reason why there
are rumors extendable Bridge
[Music]
puzzle element designed by Danny
Sullivan Summer Bridge was designed 2021
oh
that's interesting this was very
recently this puzzle piece Diversified
puzzles dramatically
to the creation of 250 new puzzles cool
the great 2012 world ending asteroid was
rewound by the entropy Center following
healing civilization to develop
preventative measures in time for its
arrival cool
so you you dodged at that one but uh not
the other one was this oh is that my gun
handheld interview device
in entropy yield oh cool was this the
elderly Center has stopped over 10 000
comets
wow
sick
maybe the Earth is just doomed because
yeah as I said maybe Earth is just
doomed because I don't hear any of these
problems with other planets
no other planet [\h__\h] complains about
asteroids and other [\h__\h] hitting them
they deal with their [\h__\h] on their own
if any [\h__\h] ever happens actually so
maybe Earth is just [\h__\h] doomed maybe
we're just not meant to be
a great Point thank you
I have yet to hear from any planets this
one in our Milky Way to be destroyed by
a cataclysmic event
s
oh yeah
you good did they ever fix this no
obviously not they couldn't
come on let's go
hey Bev I just wanted to report some
findings it's not looking good to say
the least this current cataclysmic event
we can't work out what's causing it but
that's not the issue the issue is that
it's happening again this is the first
for the center I mean we did everything
right we rewounded Earth and sent them
the data but the same thing seemed to
repeat itself and the cataclysmic event
was not avoided we're on the same time
wait what are they supposed to do move
the Earth
[Music]
a gazillion
bazillion
ooh kilometers to the left
would you miss it
what are they supposed to do
what can you do
[Music]
I've never seen anything like it I'll be
doing further analysis over the next few
weeks
well
I love this oh is this
Transformer sun is one of the hardest
puzzle elements to master the
Transformer continues to stamp and block
puzzle operatives
is this upcoming
only a brightest minds of the center are
able to solve puzzles that contain
Transformers
[Music]
conveyor a puzzle favorite transport
entryway cubes without even having to
pick them up
floor button or you've seen that
oh we've seen that so maybe these things
are really upcoming
not a hotel
oh spoiler spoiler
oh oh I got an achievement Center Cube
yeah yeah yeah this one we know jump
Cube this one with an old bridge Cube
I heard lasagna Cube
[Music]
there's a Cuban it's a beam of light
away from its origin puzzle operators
will use the beam of light to enable
specific laser inputs
inputs do not look directly to the Lord
[Music]
collapsible Cube
has both crumbled and uncrumpled State
uses Cube to rise themselves other
objects or Block Puzzle elements
and this one we know okay so there's
still uh like uh two
different cubes and two different you
know other elements to check out maybe
hmm
[Music]
this might enter my top favorite games
of the year top five
I am intrigued by this game
[Music]
okay
with tunic
hell yeah
let's lost and confused even though he
looks happy well that makes two of us
[Music]
well oh [\h__\h] no time to play ball
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
no friend directive stop petting angry
entry bot I didn't pet him
I'm done
oh God where is he
oh it's like a horror movie now
[Music]
are they gonna shoot me
can I pick them up and like rewind them
okay come at me bro
okay apparently I was not able to do it
properly
ah okay I need to select them properly
oh let's go oh
I get to fight them now
oh disappeared
where's the other one
[Music]
I'm here
he ignores me okay this one's friendly I
will let him go
wait
check check for secret Intel no okay
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
fun
don't even have to aim
[Music]
destruction
oh is he still talking to me to me are
you making the noises because I keep on
wondering where the noises are coming
from
oh no they're gone
uh maybe it's them the ones on top
over here
[Applause]
[Music]
this is where they end the fighting
element you know like in Portal where
you have to find the robots there but
this this one I prefer
because it's easier
[Music]
the turrets I [\h__\h] hated the turrets
stupid turrets
it's up and launched with right clicks
[Music]
too many more of those
interview Center has
chirpy worker bots on standby great wow
twenty thousand damn do they all want to
fight me though
oh yo
the entry percenter takes up like a [\h__\h]
ton of space on the moon holy [\h__\h]
damn
if that's true scale
foreign
[Music]
game
that's not real right
what
it's the most accepted Theory ah it's
one Theory but unproven
what I've never heard of that before
[Music]
wildlife and foliage protected by the
space resistant and will be doomed the
entropy Center was built on the very
ground of its own successes and
breakthroughs in technology
what if it's a but if it's a piece of
the earth then why it look does it look
so different
explain that to me
no atmosphere oh
shh I'm learning something here
wow
good game good game
[Music]
it doesn't it's just too small
yeah this is not too scary right like in
comparison Moon should be way smaller
[Music]
company
what are they supposed to oh it's like a
merchandise
oh my God I want one they remind me of
something actually especially when
they're just small
Kawaii oh they're much better
oh looking good Astra look at the
fashionist achievement oh
the hats the hats does it for me
oh my God
don't even have to pay for it let's go
I've never stole anything in my whole
life by the way
never not even something small when I
was like I don't know five nope four six
or seven or eight or nine or ten nope
I was too much of a coward too much of a
p u s s y
foreign
[Music]
River unless intention is to drown makes
sense okay beautiful
so and the cube does not mind the water
huh
okay oh but wait I need the cube
[Music]
[\h__\h] up already also I think no lore
no
another hat
but we already have a hat uh refresh the
cute police are there
so
um
[Music]
okay
drop
I will rewind it
uh
[Music]
drop it
catch it
but it was go like underneath okay we
good we good we good
oh is this a return in case you kind of
soft locked yourself oh
it's not even soft like myself which
sure would stop left themselves there
[Music]
nice to see you here that's uh one less
out of how many thousands
[Music]
please
I have to say though this company they
have so many of these like
like vacation-ish areas
so they do seem to take their employees
well-being
quite seriously
like we would think one would be enough
but they have so many of them
it must be pretty nice
interesting
where where are we going with this okay
I jumped up there
now this
ah we need both
do we have
something else
nope of course it's always only one
thing
[Music]
uh
maybe there's something up there let me
let me oopsie
let me go check
there is
that one
makes
creates a bridge
and put the this jumping pad on top of
it I guess
okay
actually you know the karaoke that I
went to at the convention
my best friend
I don't remember if it was her song
choice but she definitely ran out there
there to sing when when suddenly the
Portal song came on
I was like oh my God I did not sing with
them because I thought I would not know
the song well enough to really join in
but
I was like in the back vibing it was so
cute the ending song
[Music]
that one it was so nice that's what the
words on the screen are for they even
dance
might not be so good
I know how it goes
I will sing it in my own karaoke
next time okay if I find the instrument
what's the song called it's probably not
on caught up on right
oh this is cool [\h__\h] I can't open I
don't have fun
still alive
I'm still alive
[Music]
still alive
out of shock oh
ah
I gasped so hard
then
I destroyed my throat but it is in there
it says so live Jonathan Colton and
Gladys Ellen McLean it's in there
[Music]
I'll practice accordingly
yeah
okay I'm still alive I left the beach
from that gasp
[Music]
what about once you're gone oh was that
another song from Portal I don't
remember that one oh my well if they
have still alive then the other ones
probably there too
okay let's think
um shouldn't be too hard we have two
things they need to end up there
so that will be the first step
always think wherever you need them last
that is the first placement
Smart Cookie
smart kiwawa so okay this is final
position so refresh
and refresh
[Music]
okay
okay we bring
me the cute probably
ah wait
uh uh oh
I'm not
sure about this one because we want it
to end up
here but okay I'll just try I'll just
try something out we'll figure it out
along the uh
our path no I'm afraid
[Music]
I don't know how to play this game
anymore was it was it on here
was it over here or was it on the other
one
oh
I feel like it was on the other one
you guys know
great one
hopefully
if
[Music]
well that only shows that a lot
okay
uh
I think
huh
I think I need to raise that exactly
when ah I guess it's not too bad even if
I don't do it at the exact same time
because it won't go through it
let's wait there so
how do I get up
that's so that's the thing that's you
know don't know the thing
well I get up
[Music]
where you want okay wait let me think
and Rewind out
[Music]
I feel like I'm adding too much time on
to this
[Music]
uh I feel like I should have done
a different way
oh [\h__\h]
um well
foreign
that was kind of by accident
but it works
sometimes I guess just holding something
over the ledge is enough to work ah so
that stays there right
who does it
well I think I that because in the end
they both need to go back there and I
don't think
[Music]
30 seconds
does that still start there
hopefully maybe it does maybe it does
[Music]
but what about Mac this Cube that one
too right
okay okay let's see let's see I think I
think I think I think
I think it might be fine
okay so let's rewind this one
you can do it
[Music]
you remember you Destiny I'm so proud
now it's only you don't [\h__\h] it up don't
[\h__\h] it up don't don't oh oh oh oh oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
I was thinking really hard over there
doing a lot of different things but hey
hey it's open
that was all my brain oh my God
[Music]
please maintain appropriate Footwear
during all puzzle exercises I don't have
feet okay
flip-flops no what if I do it anyway
what are you gonna do I will stare at
you disapprovingly okay don't give a
[\h__\h]
okay okay appropriate Footwear at all
times okay
mental manipulation works on this lady
very well just with an angry face she
was
convinced
okay let me look around that looks like
Laura to me
[Music]
Solomon favorite TV series hi Jack Jake
hop Jake you have to try this so you
know that feeling when you watch your
favorite TV series and things just feel
a bit empty after yes yes
and you just wish that you could watch
it again for the first time
well the other day apparently I finished
a really good show and had that exact
feeling
you know what I
thought four TV shows but I feel like is
I I wish I could wear more seasons were
you watching TV shows was not so much of
an issue to me replaying games
definitely is
that feels more meaningless to me than
re-watching TV shows
but yeah okay the other day I apparently
finished a really good show and had an
exact feeling uh it was nearing my
rosette time anyway as I had finished
all the puzzles here so I left a Post-It
note to myself explaining this what
so now that I've reset I'm literally
watching it for the first
and oh my goodness it feels so good
knowing that this is going to be my
favorite show all over again ah come
over some time after the shift and we
can catch up with a beer oh yeah that's
a good thing about rewinding
foreign
[Music]
come on
wasn't there a second kill up here
huh
that's where it goes first I think
reset
and
[Music]
uh
how do we do all of this one Cube
and one of the buttons
must turn off the laser up there
but it's not that one
party
hold it
is that Beans by the way no it's tomato
soup
okay well oh wait there's oh there's one
underneath I didn't see I'm blind
okay so that's that I suppose
probably I can't see it but I'm assuming
so
so what
[Music]
I think
if I
drop that if I drop them
but then what is this for if I can just
drop it here and make it go all the way
over there
and then I come down and I do this
and we have it on top of the bridge and
I could carry it to the next but
[Music]
then it's there and then I have to stop
it though
um
What if I
oh I don't know
need to carry across
oh I guess it's just for me okay but
then
the bridge okay bridge is just from me I
guess
but then what is that
I need okay okay
um
I don't know if this is the right order
but I'm just gonna do something right
now
oh yeah maybe that's that's
I'm not really thinking much I'm just
doing
sometimes you just have to
feel
huh
ah
[Music]
a
question mark
let's just rewind it and see what
happens
so now the laser is gone
and I could
fly back
jump up
I don't know let's try I don't know I
don't know I don't know what I'm doing
uh-huh that's where I would like it at
the end
okay
was it still
I don't remember
but
hey
I don't know ah I'm getting there though
um
[Music]
I have a problem now though
the problem is
the door is open put the how do I get
there
uh there's there's I think the final no
final step
[\h__\h]
how
ah
[Applause]
that one's a thinker I think that one's
a thinker
because
I needed to go there once
[Music]
I can't even put these thoughts into
words because it's too much thinking
what comes first
box has to go to three places one of
them twice
come with me
maybe uh
let's say let's let's say you start here
because you end here obviously
oh like I
I'm second something because otherwise
this door needs no nevermind no no never
mind never mind no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no it's okay
it's okay it's okay
you end here we got that one straight
so next
you go
on this one but this this one gets rid
of
no I go on the laser
I don't know [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] it's also hard to see because like
they're overlapping levels and it makes
it harder for me to see through
I forgot
what the middle one does
what does the middle one do
hmm
put a jump pad ah to work so I can get
up there so that would be the second
last step
so that's where I need to bring it next
I think that would be the second last
step
so the third last step is this so here
here here here here
if you if you rewind
and walk over
here
I don't know what I'm doing but I don't
know if that is it correct here here
here here here
oh is it not here here here here because
how do we get it to here
[Music]
um
wait
is it not there now
I don't know
attach it between bottom part and
highest catch it oh
how did I get there again
how did how did I manage ah I just
jumped from down there
here
[Music]
if I jump without deleting the laser
then I'll delete the memory so I have to
do this one personal
ity
and then
but then how do I bring the thing with
me
I think
let me try something
thing
[Music]
um
33 seconds
[Music]
foreign
I leave it there
for a moment but you said enough time
and I bring it here and I don't know if
that's even the right order but
um
it has to be something like this but
what about the time though
oh God
ah
ah if I continue from here on out it
starts again at 29 seconds so I have
extra time
[Music]
okay
how much is this maximum time because I
need to bring it over there
good night
refresh it from Top first
I can read another you know do I know
[Music]
I didn't refresh it at the top I didn't
I don't know if I can recreate what I
just did
let me
um
I don't know let me test it we have to
refresh anyway then let me just you know
at least test it out like this and see
where it would go
we want it at the top at the end
or do we
or now it's wait
first night job while it's in the middle
I think it's working
[Music]
wow
14 minutes
foreign
unstable rocks ahead note I see a switch
down there in the river there must be a
way to activate it
huh
a switch in the river
what what are you talking about
what you talking about
let me look around first lady need to
look for lore
Uzi got some lore for me no
what happened here
someone dropped their Nintendo switch in
the river they're not waterproof so I
don't think we can save it
I'm sorry you have to buy new ones but
maybe it's now a good time to buy a new
one or buy a steam bag
steam deck
okay
all right what's going on here
can I go down
what do I do
okay that was apparently not the
intention
the previous thank you
nice steam neck I don't know when it's
coming I sent
um my friend the money yesterday
to order it for me so
good morning unstable rocks ahead
we did not expect me to make that jump
in time did she
but I can't go through can I
yo my reflexes
hello where is that switch that she's
talking about that thing a nothing
well I can't rewind anything man
[\h__\h] I think I saw flunked myself
uh
uh Roblox yeah it's too far
here
oh wait
there we go now I found you rewindable
object oh oh god um
unnecessary devs
it will be like that Loopsy doodles
[Music]
down there in the river
okay now I'm just [\h__\h] around I
crushed myself
I guess this is how some people die when
they are crushed okay
when they use the gun let's not [\h__\h]
around anymore
in the river there must be a way to
activate it okay let me bring this back
oh I understand it just has to like
slightly touch that button huh
is that it
oh
okay
well who
a right up the stair that's so dangerous
I I will not blame myself for that
warning unstable rocks ahead very
unstable switch down there in the river
there must be a way to activate it
foreign
where do you go
oh but if it would go not there but like
in the middle because I'm guessing this
is not scripted but just luck then I
could rewind the stick
push it there
you know what I mean
but now I need to
uh bring this back so I can go get
another Cube
a mess wait can I wait I can just rewind
the the cube never mind never mind
don't worry everything is okay
oh I can just already
do it at this stage
and then
right right way of thinking
say guys say guys
three
oh 704
oh
it's making cute sounds
is it a friendly one or an evil one
it's happy chirping sounds so oh there
you happy now but they're not happy
anymore
oh
got me too would you like me to enroll
you at the entropy health and fitness
center no no more enrolling me in
anything you are now enrolled to the
internet no stop I'm fine your next
class is
I've never tried Pilates before have you
guys
I've only seen
like certain idols
from eyes
do Pilates before
no no no my mom does it
um
never it's a good ab workout you think
we work out I don't care okay of people
who work out yes yes there are
there are a couple
um
they've even flexed me their muscles
before and made a great so
they very much exist
buff chickens
okay what are we working with
[Music]
um
ah okay that that one goes up there then
but probably not in that order but still
just for now we wanna yeah that's that's
the Final Destination because that
that's where the door is okay
foreign
so I can walk over
and drop the cube there
possibly
so
refresh you
I think I'm doing some quick thinking
here
today
this is for going back huh
to get back up let me just first check
what's up over here what do we need here
why can't I just um bring
the oh
what is that for
you would think that the river is for
bringing the cube over here but why can
I not just carry it over here and place
it here why would I need to bring it
through the water or is that just to
annoy me because
I guess the water is just to make it
difficult for me to pass
okay
maybe they did not intend me to send
this Cube through here it's just so that
I can make a bridge here
as an extra element of action I guess
okay
um
all right then come with me
is that it
is
foreign
oh wait how will I get
over there
also like even up there it was placed
incorrectly I guess let me let me fix
that
they're fresh place like this
yeah should be all right
this one's a hard one really
[Music]
they're I mean this one will never be
removed will it
that
wall
can I reach that from there
let me see
let me see let me see can I go on top of
that
thing
oh does this open
no
can I enter from there
which block we brought over oh wait a
second
oh
four
what what does that do
how does that change our situation
or is that just decoration
huh
oh that's just from the robots Okay Okay
but was I able to jump over
no no
okay
oh
[Music]
wait
ah got it
I think
[Music]
um
no ah
[Music]
yeah I have an idea
um I just need to find the right way to
do it so I'm thinking
so I cross I want this Cube to go
through the water over to that side to
help me make a bridge that brings me
from there to there so I can jump on the
elevator brings me up and the cube must
still be in the final position up there
so I can not go through the defense
thingy but go through like the last part
the bridge is only for the last part
from the elevator to the door
and
I just need the the right order like I
need to go over there but I still need
to
okay thinking rewind it's probably fine
if I just do that
uh
probably Let's test it testing testing
but will it then still go back here
oh [\h__\h] up I [\h__\h] up I [\h__\h] up
[Music]
it's okay
I I let go too late I think
um so you're at 11 seconds
okay hold you drop
oh yeah
drop it
what was that for uh for the elevator
okay now we have it here
uh I make a bridge
we don't want
uh the that elevator to go up
immediately
ready at
holy [\h__\h] okay but I will just rewind it
now I just need to hope that my purple
Cube will end up up there
oh
that's for the door oh [\h__\h] okay
that should be okay but I have too much
time on this one
too much time in that one
foreign
[Music]
how does that work now it didn't go up
after
38.1 seconds
but it doesn't need to go
that far it only needs to go over there
right
uh how do I say it's track again
what was it again
he was picking up R was resetting
F uh
yeah that was probably fine
so
oh but no that needs to be your last
position
so I need to go here here here
what
uh let me reset again
stay and then from there I reset this
to go there
oh but then it won't lift me up so it
needs to go there again
and then there again
baby
good work
it's Overkill but it works right I think
it works reset this one now for the
bridge
if
I had too much time on it
what are my choices
suicide
foreign
[Music]
detecting shortness of breath and puzzle
operative I think that was really close
but this one ended up having so much
time on him stop I'm fine
every Tuesday at 3 P.M
so
let's try to save as much time as
possible because it has to travel quite
the distance
but I wonder can I save
time was that one somehow
next it needs to go here to bring me
over
ah maybe instead of dropping it here can
I drop it there will that save time but
wait it's um
yeah I can make the bridge here and drop
it here
right
okay
okay 11 seconds
it will stop the counter when it stops
moving somewhere right
does not count the time it spends away
I did it too early
sign
with the cube
hmm but then how do I drop it
ah how to think
you can use over to drop it
[Music]
sometimes it's better to not think
just do
this one refresh here
right
now come back
drop it
okay it stopped at 18.6
that's okay
do you have to build a tomato
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay
uh pick up make Bridge
and that's it right
for the for the purple one
make Bridge bring this one over
put it there
and then bring it there again because
I'm extra special and I don't know any
other way to do it like I'm just gonna
do it twice
why am I not dead
well in case the entropy Center
developers are watching this just write
this one down
I don't want to move I want to stay
alive oh hi
oh
I should be dead
well just go a step further
[Music]
come at me
I'm so sorry that took so long I I will
do it right this time it was an accident
health and fitness center stop I'm fine
your next class is
[Music]
okay one more time you're just getting
smarter for this don't worry you're not
getting the opposite you're getting
smarter I promise
definitely getting smarter for this
exercise
God
oh [\h__\h] I feel like I already wasted
time by jumping down there
refresh
I think we have to stop sometime soon
yeah I did say two hours two more hours
and that was one and a half hours ago so
yeah yeah
refresh oh wait refresh
I'll go
hold holding bridge I have a system now
it's like a choreography
it's like we're dancing
along
you refresh
you go
go
[\h__\h] killing me
it's okay we only need the bridge right
that's the end of the this one okay okay
okay okay it's okay it's okay it's okay
it's okay
it's okay that's enough time
yeah okay
don't die don't die don't die don't die
okay and
that should work
foreign
[Music]
but
uh
we're doing again
yeah you know shhh
um
Final Destination here
oh wait refresh Maybe
I'm so sorry you guys know I've been
playing for five and a half hours
that's enough right
point
um first
purple I would say
it showed Rachel's final destination
it's just kind of hard to see but oh oh
oh oh yeah
where's the bridge
[Music]
hahaha
come here
oh it's so fun what if I [\h__\h] up my job
I'm gonna [\h__\h] up myself
if I [\h__\h] up the jumps I have to redo
everything
probably
oh God
I know I'm gonna [\h__\h] it up
oh
[Music]
my God
I'm sorry I was there and I was like
you baby
[Music]
[Laughter]
why hey can I fix it without redoing
everything see I should have gone
several times
[Music]
pillow
several times wait is someone
somewhere is like a peon oh there is
do I want to use this
I that still forces me to do everything
again
if you carefully rewind until it's above
the button then unpause it
um
what
until it's on the button I think it is
on the button
ah
I mean until it's above the button
and then
drop it
because that will not reset this path
right
I don't think it will because it did not
do before
okay we get a second chance in life
and like you want one please it's really
not that difficult I know precious
[\h__\h] terrible but come on
this [\h__\h] game I love it so much
oh my gosh
[Music]
I feel like a [\h__\h] superhero walking
through the store oh
foreign
[Music]
I thank you for not making me give up
I was losing my mind
yo
thank you
Apple
[Music]
hero my hero
I think everyone else was also already
giving up
uh let me pour some
some honey some tea show me
try I said two more hours so
I should try a little bit more still
so we can maybe finish it next time I'll
take some extra time next time it will
not be stressful don't worry
something feels
oh
I knew it
ah this is my favorite
it's 15 seconds
oh I'm leaving nice well that one's like
their boss everything's so dark there
was a kid you need to pay more attention
uh-huh no problem
no problem detection increased to 200
why couldn't you have done that before
huh shouldn't you always have that like
on default
anyway lore time
there we go
Lauren Daniels and trumpy butt request
hey yo yes can I set up a decommission
for entropy Bots 2231 thanks hard reason
it looks at me funny
I'm sorry but you have to decline this
request we simply can't decommission a
specific entry be Bond because they
looked at you funny
Lori I'm telling you now listen here
that bot has been giving me hella side
eye like proper side eye that boy knows
exactly what it was doing it's taunting
me Laurie are they talking about the red
one I wonder I cannot put my morning
breakfast I sit there with my entropy
break sipping my coffee yeah breaking
and it's just standing there giving me
the side eye smiling judging me they're
sentient I'm telling you I don't know
how or when but they think you can see
it in their eyes Lori
to Devin I appreciate your concern but
entropy Bots exhibit no emotion and are
not sentient they are incredibly helpful
in all operations of the entropy Center
their smiles are merely a fast saved of
a fake emotion to appease staff members
and provide a friendly face I don't
think it's giving you the side eye
an entropy
but protect themselves and Gaslight the
people around them
[Music]
um
if we are at chapter 7 out of 15 how do
we only have 25 out of 76 intels did I
miss so many I feel like I've been
finding most of them
yo
oh that way I thought we were gonna go
that way an option
okay no okay sorry game lagging a little
bit
most of them probably hidden
damn like that one like between the
cracks of the the the like cliff
was pretty well hidden so that made me
worry maybe there are a lot of
um like other ones
for these periods of time as it may
cause a tickling sensation
at an exponential rate
you cute baby oh
I don't know
okay wait what are we doing here well
this one
oh
ah okay okay okay
fun fun fun fun I see a lot of fun times
ahead of us don't you see it too
um
interesting isn't it we are we are
wait
let me get on top first
Oh Captain
[Music]
I love the lore dear staff members we're
pleased to announce that the entropy
Center is now 100 sustainable as of last
Friday we want to thank Mark Jacobs in
this absolute effort in producing a
renewable electricity system for the
center Mark Jacobs and Sarah Hardy for
being so pivotal in the growth of our
food and Horticulture Garden
this week's meal on Sunday is a
Christmas dinner meal to coincide
coincide with Christmas day on Earth my
Uncle everyone it was Christmas me last
week
yeah petition to have our own yearly
calendar for annual events and not tied
to Earth way too confusing
oh is this because they keep on
rewinding
if we were around Earth one day every
day on the 26th December does that mean
we get Christmas dinner every day
oh
nice Christmas dinner oh hellofresh was
showing me their Christmas dinner
options and they look so good
one thing Dad we in Austria at least
definitely must eat for
Christmas and I think I've mentioned
this before is the the red cabbage stuff
uh what's it called again it's just
called red cabbage I feel like it had a
different name
it's so yummy I love it so much
[Music]
red
I guess it's just red cabbage
it's so good especially with like
um if you make it with apple my mom
makes it with Apple
and
with like a
good piece of
what do you call that kind of meat deer
that kind of meat game is called game it
had a weird name I think
I need to go down
oh oh
does it go through windows
no it doesn't
oh you calm down no we're gonna do this
no I don't understand oh
[Music]
benefit oh okay I did also think of that
wait
venison game
gaming
the same
[Music]
foreign
oh wait why am I thinking I need to go
for that door
okay okay okay
uh
[Music]
it does not wait it doesn't go for it
there though
huh
what
what am I missing
you know what
if I just hold it ah
bit oh
what
is that how you do it
totally up while walking backwards
I mean maybe you don't have to walk
backwards but
what does that say
46 charge wow
foreign
[Music]
of me to find my own solution one that
the game does not offer to me
game is hunted wild animals meet venison
specifically deer meat oh
oh venison is only deer meat
Naruto
I outsmarted the puzzle yes I didn't
okay so one the laser needs to go there
the cube needs to go there in the end
um ah I first need to build the bridge
then hold the laser on top of the bridge
accordingly
but
before I do that
refresh
gosh I I'm I'm like so smart
I'm like so smart oh my god like people
can't keep up with my smartness
scares people you know how do I turn
this [\h__\h]
oh my God what oh but wait how do I link
should I just realized I've made a
mistake
because it won't no can it stay in the
air when I get rid of the bridge
can I like
please oh [\h__\h] why did I refresh it no
it's okay
I'm gonna turn it
oh it's gonna fall
oh no
[Music]
oh I could have rewinded it maybe
oh sure
overthinking because I'm just such a
smarty
it's too smart for this world
yeah
thank you
so we bring it back
girl you entropy like this
and yeah it's like you you are not even
entropying yet how come
you're still waiting for that code
unbelievable go girl let's go
foliage conservation seed bank sweet
[Music]
let me in let me in oh let me out now
now I want to go out oh [\h__\h]
am I stuck
am I am I stuck
[Music]
did mine greediness
get me here
is this the consequences of my own
actions
jump Crouch I don't think there's even
crouching in this game maybe a Crouch
maybe stop
foreign
[Music]
it saves every time I go through a door
hopefully
[Music]
I think so
saved progress well I think like good
foreign
guys don't go to the street it will kill
you
don't go there
that's death awaiting you actually not
okay don't go there don't do the same
mistake that I did
foliage conservation
directive enable those switches to
remove lockdown
what
are we in a stressful situation here oh
[\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] they can't see me if I'm up here
[Music]
enables which are okay so here we need
to insert something
[Music]
okay they saw me I thought they wouldn't
be able to see me
what is this for oh wait this was not to
insert something this was for the laser
oh
[Laughter]
you think I'm in good I'll give them
that
go first bag
I know what to do now
yeah yeah yeah
directive enable those switches no they
didn't even see me this time
still walking in
yeah
please don't hurt me okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] don't uh underestimate these
[\h__\h] dogs
huh okay
um there's one on the ground
I saw it
yeah just kill it just kill it it's good
that they see me then I can take care of
them Yo your friend is dead what you
gonna do oh do they keep on respawning
so it's always to save them out
yes they do okay I thought I could get
rid of them completely
okay well can I look at this from here
um
I think there was one over there
um that's probably a platform to get
back up but it's not activated
[\h__\h] yeah well even if I kill one the
next one that spawns will not know where
I am oh
[Music]
my God
what is this
what is this place it's a weird room
[Music]
okay the jump platforms are activated so
I can bring that one upstairs
[Music]
just a cube does this work by the way on
the enemies
like in like in the portal
oh
no no no it doesn't
[\h__\h] run run it doesn't see me yet
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay oh
I just want someone's coming at me
I think I thought those things were kind
of cute and cuddly I don't think this is
supposed to be there
and falsely detecting you as a threat
I'm taking it very deep sponge
they couldn't exit so they despawned
ah well damn
now this thing just got here from some
explosion or cell
damn
holy [\h__\h] that felt intense
but still very manageable I think the
game is doing everything right at making
me feel good and making me feel smart
good game good game
damn you did good thank you
this has been a great bug testing scheme
oh Lord no more oh man
about here huh
earlier there was a red one what's with
the fresh paint job good question those
are entropy stun Bots they are brought
out in exceptional circumstances of
severe civil unrest or security
requirements they've only been the point
once when the entropy Debate Club became
rather disorderly
interpret the bait Club
foreign
group noise can anyone else hear that
weird humming sound yeah what is that
ditto
[Music]
a million
do anything tillers you said work
[Music]
another phone that was just used in
German language I never heard it or saw
any English-speaking person use that
before
yeah it's a Pokemon yeah and German it's
a Pokemon
it's the the Pokemon that looks like
chewing gum
wait is it also the same name in English
they don't still use
really am
I don't see anyone using it
maybe only in written language still
it was a popular word in Lancaster 2007.
that's what I'm saying
around that time making me feel really
old
people who are born in 2007 how old are
they now um
15.
it's my
quick math correct oh my God
don't you dare doubt my math skills
anymore I did that too fast okay
wow
[Music]
calling all about Invaders oh this week
we're going to debate
the following topics
apple on Pizza yes or no
yes and trippy puzzles too hard or too
easy
I would say never
they're fine rewind her shall we remind
her that they are the source of their
own destruction
[Music]
no
but is there
are stretching with the with the
asteroid okay
that is not their fault they didn't do
that
but we can't help them either don't know
how to stop that asteroid
unless
I have an idea
if only the game could listen to me
we should be able to
since we can rewind the Earth
we can also rewind the asteroid right
why don't we just stop it
right before you know somewhere in the
middle on travel to the Earth before it
bumps into the Earth why don't we just
stop it there
if it goes
uh no if if it's like
um if that does not stop
I mean no it wouldn't send a new one to
replace that one because that one is
still existing in that timeline so the
same asteroid would not come again
right
that's not how space works yeah but
that's how time works
space
can be even space can be stopped by time
as you've seen with the Earth why if it
works with the Earth why can't it worked
with an asteroid
is it even an asteroid it might have
been an explosion
I don't know but but they'll say it's an
astronaut we can just stop the asteroid
okay but okay maybe it's not an asteroid
and that's why that didn't come to that
conclusion
okay whatever we're feeling really smart
here aren't we
test your debating skills improve your
argumentative literacy let's do
literally what we're doing right now I
argue and yell at your peers civilly
yeah curse and swear at people's
opinions without getting reported to HR
you still could don't go too hard
your Free State research lab room uh-huh
okay
oh hey we're already at 30 out of 76
actually that's not too bad anymore now
that I think about it that's pretty much
halfway through and we are halfway
through the game
for our plan I would say I think we are
I think we are
huh
I lost my sense of direction
okay last puzzle possibly
Mass
[Music]
opens door why is that one up there how
do I get it down ah is that that thing
foreign
shouldn't I be able to move it from
there if I make it so that it's really
close huh
really close
like
um
okay that distance normally I should be
able to move it but I guess this fence
is actually blocking it okay
[Music]
different way of doing it because
they're not being fair to me
oh
it's kind of um
Dusty
yo
like everyone here
[Music]
in one last party together wait where's
my hat I'm trying to fix it why not my
gun lose my hand
that's what makes you a great puzzle
operative Arya
you don't give up
thanks
I can't take this one
no I Want My Hat Back
also I said that one was the last one
but that one was too short so we do one
more
time
40 minutes
why unbelievable
ah that opens the door
foreign
[Music]
what I'm thinking
is rewind
look at what that actually does
[Music]
ah
ah so I I should have moved that over
there before that
okay
restart
hi hi
okay okay got it got it got it got it
move
how's it going it's going pretty well we
are we're six hours
[\h__\h]
I've been playing this for six hours
I just realized that that right now
right now it came to me
I am addicted
I have an addiction
for the fact that we've been playing it
for six hours I'm surprisingly very
little uh frustrated
in general
[Music]
yeah
foreign
I appreciate the challenge I appreciate
it
[Music]
Let me refresh okay
oh [\h__\h] hi
hi okay you go
um
here
and then
no
here and then here
what
I dropped it because yeah okay
makes sense
okay
[Music]
can't do two um
two things at once I guess
[Music]
come on keep our first try
first try
it's the lack of confidence every time
it gets to me
every time
but it's not the lack of understanding
it's just the lack of confidence
that was beautiful oh [\h__\h]
that was beautiful
I can't refresh
I have confidence I will never have
confidence in jumps
at least this one is not such a pain in
the ass to do all over again
uh
[Music]
right next one
uh
[Music]
oh man
we took a line
look down
[Music]
at least this one I didn't have to reset
this time I think
um
should be okay
see okay easy easy oh
sometimes the physics are interesting
people
yeah if they make it a little bit bigger
it would be helpful but oh well luxury
luxury
okay
yay
lore I will take one more lore
[Music]
react to course abilities
oh [\h__\h] it doesn't sound good
but it's better than before wasn't it
let's hurry I can't let that reactor
become too unstable
okay dear puzzle operatives we would
like to remind you of the following side
effects of repetitive rewinding as you
are all aware you endure a personal
self-isolated rewind event once you have
completed all puzzles at the center so
that you can complete them for the first
time again to generate more entropy
energy we recommend that no puzzle
operative receives a personal rewind
event no more than twice a month
excessive and repetitive personal rewind
events can cause Amnesia other minor
side effects may include vomiting nausea
headaches achy joints tinnitus hair loss
balding stuffy nose piles
playing hemorrhoids loss of limb loss of
Limbs
hearing loss sight loss dry skin
may I remind you that the main large
entropy device that remind rewinds Earth
is perfectly safe and no side effects
have been observed
[Music]
that is us
you having to remind me of that is sauce
think
hmm
we must break the cycle yes we must
add some of the tea things the leaves in
the tea and Frank like one okay
foreign
but is it Fatal Frame
the 76. I want to do one more but I
should stop because actually also one
second
[Music]
um
oh my God
[Music]
okay
I should end it here
uh
I only have one or two more puzzles in
this area what do I
stop I should stop I should stop I
should stop I should stop it's very
entertaining but I should stop
um
very fun 10 out of 10. oh
all right
um if you want a code I have not thought
about this much but
if you want the code
then
[Music]
write me an ending tweet
after the stream finished as I replied
to my tweet
huh my ending tweet
that includes
the word
lore
and Cube
and it shall not just be Lord Cube no
a bit more than that
okay also not cute lore no
no
[Laughter]
you can like even write me a fairy
oh
fearing interesting theory on what you
think It Happened Here Without
spoilering Me
don't look it up and then spoil me I
will kill you I will I will kill you
if you will choose to spoiler me
so only yeah a theoretical Game Theory
when you think the lore is
The Lure of the cube
only fake spoilers allowed that's right
if you end up accidentally being right
that's okay but don't don't purposefully
be right
oh you yeah you made have some more
about how this kid with a companion
cable related I wanna hear that Lord
um then the I don't choose the
um
the the code receivers by how good their
tweet is just randomly but still while
you're at it make it entertaining okay
effort into it okay
all right
[Music]
um
foreign
Cube and lore Cube and lore
10 lucky chickens yeah ldm you guys so
keep your DMs open and I'll slide into
the DMS yeah
I was briefly distracted oh
really
okay I would write a tweet after this
stream uh you guys will reply to me with
the words Cube and lore but not just
that write a bit more okay
uh maybe even write me a game theory
but don't spoil me and then I will
choose randomly someone to receive the
keys uh one one key and I will DM you so
keep your DMs open
this game was a solo death I don't know
that would be crazy would it not be
that would be crazy but yeah okay so
we're done with that but I think I have
some super chats to read probably so
let's go to my office
office
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
chaos
Cube and lore Cube and lower Cube Lord
oopsie
cue blue
Hublot Hublot sounds like a Pokemon Q
blur
Q blurrar
Q blore
it sounds like a Pokemon doesn't it
I feel like it sounds like a Pokemon
qblower
hmm
yeah
okay what's the podcast do I have to
read
I don't remember like yesterday I didn't
really have super Chats on
but there may have been like a couple
um
Luigi's Mansion probably the most recent
stream only
Maybe
I would assume
there's two in a row
everything after four blood
really
including the first stream
oh sheesh
what'd you do
why do I have so many DMS again
uh-huh
oh [\h__\h] okay
I'll look at that later
no not really DM's more like mentions
okay ah the cats look so cute
I wish they could be animated like gifts
GIFs
one more mention huh
not here
Twitter
also I should
turn on
some
music music
[Music]
oh
ah
I cannot hear
why
I hear that but you guys don't
I know
lovely
[Music]
lovely marvelous
so so far being halfway through the game
I've given this game a 9 out of 10. I
feel like the the gun voice the you know
our companion
is
not as interesting obviously as Gladys
but even I'm not even expecting her to
be like Gladys but
oh she's just lacking something
and the main protagonist her personality
also feels like it's lacking something
but it's not it's not currently like
really influencing my enjoyment of the
game
um
yeah the gun lacks some SASS and like I
feel like
it has
oh no it's hard to explain
[Music]
um that is yeah even just the dialogue
oh there's like something about it it's
not satisfying
she doesn't need to be like sarcastic
but
I don't know
yeah it feels flat um
one guy
no
really that's insane insane
yeah Gladys like you can't
too difficult to get on Gladys level I
didn't expect that that's okay
too generic yeah a bit a bit boring but
you know only a bit it's okay it's
totally fine maybe you know whistle you
know get to know a different side of her
[Music]
um
and the main protagonist
she is
I guess as we said before a bit of a
kill Joy
lame
but she likes cats
[Applause]
[Music]
but yeah she could also use a bit more
personality
um
[Music]
but besides that like I like all the
elements they implemented
um I was worried about the time
um rewinding function I thought that it
would be too big brain for me but
actually not at all
not at all
and it's the main thing so if I had
trouble with that I would be in trouble
but it's been very easy to use
um you know as a whole nother level on
top of what you had in Portal
um
I like the graphics the graphics are
beautiful stunning
I love the graphics I love the lower
so the writing and the lore is good in
my opinion
so far
um the Dogo mascots are cute
I like the story so far
very much very curious about what's
going on and how we're gonna stop this
or if we're going to stop this maybe we
won't
maybe we won't even be able to
[Music]
yeah World designs yeah I think so too
in terms of graphics and World design I
might even prefer this one of a portal
gasp
Lucas
hmm
but but actually I can't say that yet
because in Portal we've seen some really
crazy intricate
big white spacious
um areas that we have yet to see
in this one
and if you think about that and I guess
what we've seen so far has been a little
bit repetitive
but I think there will be like more
different scenery in the second half and
bigger areas as well probably
mm-hmm
if you haven't watched any of those
portal lore videos oh no I don't think
so
oh please remind me again send me some
on Twitter
so I've been watching a lot of
um
all the Rings
related lore videos so many
but I forgot about the portal lore
videos
this one has location spots yeah so many
of them
so many and they're really pretty too
[Music]
oh yeah I'm really happy with this game
I think it deserves a lot of
um attention and audience so
um it just released and I'm happy to
give it a little bit of a push from my
side
I hope that portal fans will notice the
game
not only for me but just in general
you know exchange knowledge with each
other
and find this one they should
I don't see how a portal fan could hate
this game or not enjoy this game
eh again
[Music]
it's a bit difficult
I can't get closer wait
try
[Music]
okay
hmm
[Music]
um
you're cute
okay
[Music]
let me
this thumbnail here there's probably
most likely only gonna be one more Louis
just Mansion episode but I got like so
much good fan art that I want to use
so I'm thinking of like changing the
existing thumbnails
because they're so good I need to use it
but it's too much for just one thumbnail
[Music]
at least one like
um I forgot the name but there's this
one artist who recently has been drawing
after I finish the streams
fitting thumbnails
that looks so perfect
[Music]
um
I don't know do you know who I mean
cheetah
like in in public format and uh it looks
so so so so perfect
yeah I would probably use that one just
the way it is
and you'll you'll see it and you'll
understand
[Music]
one of the other games on Wii uh I mean
Luigi's Mansion
other Luigi's Mansion games
are they on Wii U
H if I do it then not like anytime soon
because like I'm
just finishing this one
maybe in the future
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat take my
blood ma'am it's all yours your full
blood cover gave me the chills from the
very first second God bless Kira you
sound fantastic Kiana this is the
perfect song for you 100 my favorite
color from you now
nice I'm glad you guys like it so much
thank you
and yeah in a little interaction on
Twitter
Kira approved
or agreed that it feels like it's my
song now
it's so good I wish I could put it like
on my album
I've been asking to stream it on Spotify
and whatever but I think
do this thing sometimes
uh I feel like I'm I may have even seen
it in the whole life before that they
put someone else's song on their own
oh well I feel like didn't Kelly do
something like this before right yeah
with empress
so it's not completely
impossible that but I don't know like
how
that works like if I need to pay a lot
to buy the rights and then in the end
it's just the same like mix probably
like there's nothing else left to mix
there it's perfectly mixed so it's the
same thing I don't know if I want to
like it almost feels lazy to fill a slot
in an album
with something that's already finished
and created you know
um but I understand that some people
want to stream it but do they really
want to stream it when finally the album
comes out you know
you know
on YouTube for this one but I really
appreciate that so many people
enjoy it this much thank you very much
[Music]
oh yeah I saw you were in the convention
that's nice Atlanta
thank you for wrapping
kfp thank you
[Music]
thank you for the pinky for blood more
like blood
am I right
what
[Music]
poor blood moon like blood am I right
what
I was speaking there must have been an
emote there huh
what was it a 10 out of 10.
this cover is so good definitely your
best cover yet Kina did amazing work
with mixing and your singing was just
wow it felt fit into the song I love
your outfit there especially not saying
yeah yeah yeah thank you
this chicken I think was kind of a
reference to the art from the original
um music video
and yeah the outfit
you know in a similar style
it is very Giant
keep one one those
edgy golf clothes
huh
I know it's giving me complicated
feelings
yeah what are we gonna do about that hmm
well thank you guys for liking it I even
used the art for today's thumbnail
because I like it so much
thank you for listening
for the pinky
four blood is seriously so perfect for
you everything about this cover is
absolute perfection thank you so much
thank you
words can't describe how much I love
your incredible singing voice I will
never stop listening to it stream for
blood forever thank
okay you don't have to stream it forever
but stream it for the meantime thank you
very much I did by the way
um
change rearrange did you see on my uh
YouTube page rearrange some things uh
covers and Originals have a different
playlist now because I figured that's
actually
one the only way to
um have them all currently at least at
this point have them all be available on
first glance more or less for the covers
you have to
press the button to go to the second
line but I think it has it all so before
they were all in one playlist and it
would only like show half of the music
I've done
the only thing is that I had to exclude
like
the hinotori remixes which is a bit
unfortunate but maybe I'll make another
playlist
that's for something else where I can
include the
remixes someday I don't know but
um yeah so now I think it's nicely
organized yeah
and I sorted them
differently
uh one of the playlists I sorted by Neil
yeah the cover playlist I think I sorted
by new because there's so many and for
The Originals I was just like whatever
you can see them all at first glance so
whatever it doesn't matter
[Music]
um
yeah yeah
so I think that looks pretty good
and very organized yeah
[Music]
all right continuing uh thank you for
the pinky for blood is as wonderful as a
beautiful girl who sang it no words to
just as to how your voice made me smile
and dance to it consider my blood
drained at my soul ascended thank you
for all the amazing things you gave us
thank you
[Music]
your blood drained you mean like in
mortuary assistant
[Music]
that's very graphic I have it in my head
now it's terrifying
do I need to shut
your mouth and your eyelids too please
no please
please come back to life I am please
but thank you for the support that
question
thank you
oh
ah I see that I saw that one Pepsi
dungeon the game
right so free thank you for the pinky hi
ninja it's payday for me so talking
about eggs is peeling an egg I've read
this one before I guess I did read it
when it came in it's peeling an egg
equivalent to undressing a new employee
I said yes it is
[Music]
thank you
oh yeah yeah I brought it up to my
manager so hopefully maybe maybe we can
find some snack box Creator who wants to
work with me
uh
uh that's their comic that Cosmic sorry
thank you thank you
YouTube Noob thank you
thank you
lots of uh money bags just like in
Luigi's Mansion thank you so much
[Music]
any of that I'm baking in your package
did I not tell you guys I don't think I
did yes you did get my package
planning a stream next week
don't have a date for it yet though
should
I'll let her know that I have some
NG Danes
actually before I forget I'll let her
know now
[Music]
where's my calendar
foreign
[Music]
before I forget them there's so many
things
to think about all the time
[Music]
it's probably good though I don't know
you guys tell me
[Music]
oh yeah she's also stick so excuse for
your bad sleep schedule okay she's sick
too so she should be sleeping all the
time either anyway and that kind of
[\h__\h] up your sleep schedule too
it was a satisfying ending noise you
guys should get the merchandise it's on
Amazon it's so cool because it comes
immediately that's the first time for
whole life merchandise that you can get
something
before you [\h__\h] die from waiting
endlessly
oh yeah the price is also not bad I
think
[Music]
and shipping also like you know how
sometimes shipping costs more than uh
the order itself but in this case it
doesn't
doesn't even have shipping cost at all
Prime is free there you go [\h__\h]
amazing and uh it did not say Austria
but Austria uses the same shop as
Germany so for the maybe one or two
austrians in the chat are there any
let me just tell you you can get it um
from our Amazon I think it was available
I looked it up and it was available on
Austria and Amazon
[Music]
so some shops maybe like
some some Amazons might be like combined
with others so they are not on polished
Amazon maybe you can ask a German friend
or so
I'm sure they would help you
they have so many sizes yeah yeah yeah
yeah
it's so cool I really like this idea
it's a big big big solution for
especially whole life English
merchandise
because it's cheap it's fast
like in Japan you know
the merchandise at least
um like I had no insane shipping price
added to it if you live in Japan
but you know
overseas we had no problem but the only
thing that should still be improved is
adding even more countries
uh
to you know
shippable countries for Amazon even I
don't know like I I told them you know
this is still this is a good Improvement
but it's still only a small selection of
countries so if possible more please
um but I'm sure like if they could they
would like you know choose every [\h__\h]
country
I don't know what exactly is like
the reason for only having those but
maybe that's just the only countries
where that kind of
um Amazon fashion thingy is available in
the first place
that could be a thing
who knows but yeah I'm sure they're they
they would add more countries if they
could and if it can be improved in the
future then they surely will
hopefully hopefully
yeah yeah Amazon on Demand that's what
it's called yeah I am
I'm guessing as well that that just
might be
the problem some countries don't have
Amazon on Demand I honestly didn't even
know about this thing
until very recently for whole life
merchandise
I did not know that that was a thing
they basically they create
Amazon creates the merchandise on demand
basically
yeah so yeah it's really good for us
such a good solution
so
maybe I wonder if we can no no I guess
not
yeah this will most likely not be
possible with birthday merchandise
because
I think for Amazon on Demand there's
like templates
for what items
and what colors and what size Etc
and then put like your image on top of
that or whatever
so for birthday merchandise I suppose it
will still you know be the usual thing
but that's okay
yeah yeah at least you have some options
now for getting merchandise fast and
relatively cheap
dinner
[Music]
hmm
then
[Music]
um
yeah it's more options yeah yeah and
also apparently it's not limited to one
month either it's more like a decision
of how long we want it but
um I've heard that it will be longer
than one month
at least even though it's Halloween
themed
I think some people will want it up a
little bit longer so it seems like
they're gonna have it up a while
[Music]
this girl thank you
46 dollars for a hoodie with free
shipping for something with you and
Amazon it is priceless to me thank you
yeah I mean 46 dollars free shipping
obviously 46 dollars for a hoodie is
still more expensive than
a random hoodie you can get like in h m
or whatever
[Music]
and you know it's merchandise so you
know
it will be oh
a little bit more expensive than normal
clothes
um
yeah
so I'm really happy for this Improvement
and for you guys
um
yeah okay
[Music]
um
thank you for the pinky oh
thank you sounds fun ctions
[Music]
I
thank you for listening to four blood
thank you very much for enjoying it
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
everything on her side
and to be honest it is noticeable that
she kind of re-recorded
stuff uh her visuals and her voice
it unfortunately it doesn't seem so much
anymore as we're having a conversation
because we actually have had a really
good like Wi-Fi conversation and that
part is kind of gone it's more stiff now
unfortunately but at least it's not
completely lost
um
yeah
no she didn't do exactly the same as I
did like I at least back then had the
audio but no video
she had nothing except my side and and
that was only my video and my voice so
she had to re-record her for everything
[Music]
it's just kind of lacking uh the the
natural conversation part
that I originally had
um
yeah but she surely won't make that
mistake again you know she did that at
home on her own it wasn't it's like her
project she didn't even do it like with
Studio helpers so she's doing everything
herself she said she's doing the cutting
the recording the subtitling and so on
so it's her thing yeah
foreign
[Music]
have fun fighting at work go go go
go fighting go go go fighting go go
we'll support nonetheless thank you yeah
yeah she's hard working subtitling yeah
like adding at least some some subtitles
to it
um
gotta watch it yeah it's not gonna be a
YouTube thing I think it's gonna be like
on Twitter and Instagram
I think
uh yeah
especially Instagram was the plan I
think
yeah and it's it's short and small so
it's really not like holotalk reverse
that's what the Super Chat was about
so
I think there's there will still be a
demand for reverse whole talk
um
eventually
[Music]
another app I gotta download I don't
think it will only be Instagram but
let's keep an eye out I think she's
gonna upload like different versions or
so
different
[Music]
formats maybe only
I'm not sure either
[Music]
thank Lords we thank Lord we smash thank
you
it was too scary
joking right
thank you Maple Leaf soon
ah did I not do this before you can use
the plunger on vending machines
have I yet to do this
I must remember and try in the last
episode at least
should I help
[Music]
at once
okay all right
thank you for the recipe chat Maybelline
to be honest the bad end animation was
amazing and I think the other four have
expressed an interest like YouTubers in
it yeah and another thing I know it may
be fictional work but we all know if the
real million was in that situation she
totally would have done it oh I read
this before I think
um
yeah yeah
well
hmm
it's finished now right so hmm
they should have contacted us we would
have said yes
but it's very Charming without voicing
too like it gives it
some some
I don't know it has its own charm to be
voiceless doesn't it
but yeah I guess there's still a chance
to release a voiced version someday no
no
just like at what time and it's kind of
awkward now
[Music]
yeah it's
it's so professional so
limited by the management I don't know
but if all talents say they want to say
they do they want to do it themselves
and
honestly
I don't think they would stop it like
why why would they it's so cool I think
even the management
is honored that you know someone would
go so far
to make such fan contents
I don't think they would stop in
2612 Duncan Thai conduction
thank you for the Flash super chats
thank you Jester Cosmic dungeon Robin
Hood Danke Schoen
[Music]
Jester Cosmic Duncan Mundo thank you for
the pinky four blocks cover
good sounds like a hectic con I was also
on a con this week with battle game
piece shout out to Mrs and lupus beats
meeting kfb friends was definitely the
highlight of it all thanks for leading a
great Community
it's nice how just by being in kfb you
guys have now new people new friends to
go to conventions with that's really
really nice I like to hear that enjoy
yourselves have fun
hmm
I wish I could
like
Mingle
without it being weird
and thank you so much
um
bacon cream
[Music]
your streams always bring a lot of Joy
but there's a particular extra amount of
enjoyment seeing you have so much fun
with one of my favorite series thank you
for playing less you're welcome I love
it I love Luigi's Mansion I loved it
since I was younger
um
thank you for that info very helpful
using it right now
[Music]
May believe another red one
you and Pomo are both huge sweethearts
and deserve all the happiness that come
your way hopefully you can see her IRL
one day for huge hug the makeup
[Music]
hope to see more stuff soon if everyone
is okay with it treasure friends like
Como
[Music]
um
are you cool
come on come on
yeah I hope I can meet her in real life
one day
I mean I'm sure it will be possible
might take some time but I'm sure it
will happen honestly
like next year we will at some point be
in Japan at the same time surely
I can totally see it coming
and happening even if it's just by
accident even if we don't plan for it
I have a feeling we'll go crazy on Japan
visits next year
can't hold back and I don't think I can
either
foreign
[Music]
complaints what people complaining about
her
[Music]
throne
or My Level Throne I guess
nah
unacceptable
[Music]
and Senior MC dad oh my God
thank you
I hope you are so my side senior
you better be
[Music]
looking sex with those emojis yo oh oh
into always hola try to get on my good
side now we're gonna run all right
[Music]
thank you
yeah senior did I give you a kiss short
time memory
you need to chat thank you for the pinky
I guess now that the Traders have been
purged publicly we can move and continue
as usual that was fun to watch thanks
Tango thank you
like you want to move on really fast so
that I don't see something that I should
see hmm feeling feeling like that's
possibly the case like there's something
you wanna
hide from me
push away quickly quickly so that I
don't see it
change the topic
and the attention to something else huh
possible
perhaps
seeming awfully quiet
oh well I don't know maybe there really
isn't
[Music]
talking about anything particular
Garden
kitchen Nathan cotton thank you for the
pinky
when background change Halloween ended
um I don't know when it gets more
Christmassy like honestly Mariah Carey
did not convince me
it's not time it's not [\h__\h] time
I'm not convinced
and now that the Traders have been
expunged
[\h__\h] is that we must reconquer our lost
territory regain what we have lost to
the Frog and while we're adding concrete
some other stuff as well maybe some
tacos yeah
do it
wait let's I'm [\h__\h] motivated
[Music]
punch removed
okay
I'm all for it go go go go kfp go go
foreign
[Music]
well here I am
don't you ever lose me again you better
cherish and hold what you have
strongly and tightly
so that it does not Escape you again
yeah
protect and cherish
kiwawa
appreciate what you have now firmly
grasp
[Music]
yeah definitely don't miss the Frog
thank you slowest psychopath
[Music]
y
spicy chicken
Moon
thank you for the pinky does this count
as interest in a cover collab
Oh Oh you mean because of the Puma thing
probably thank you thank you
[Music]
I don't know if we'll really do that
song but someday I definitely want to do
a
collab cover thing yeah
[Music]
I'll work on it
comes back to me with we know like um
like a hey kiwawa wanna do this next you
know
come on
[Music]
looking for the top action
yeah shut up
I know it wasn't perfect okay but this
was the first time then
more or less more or less the first time
and then do something like that it was
it was actually you know the thing is I
don't think I maybe I didn't really
explain this but there was a little bit
of a
brain failure due to being too spoiled
because
in our myth world
they are seeing uh myth or just
generally whole live English world you
know how we have that
um like camera set in the Amita verse
so
um in previous
uh like
times when we used
that
world we are seeing
yeah we could like bring one of those
cameras with us into the other worlds as
long as they're like you know connected
to the whole main world
and so I we were like uh setting up and
testing stuff in the studio world before
the camera and the music and Etc
and then you know we were really like
getting gitty getting time was cutting
shorts close
Tick Tock and we I have to say that we
started on time okay
we started on time but since it was so
blah blah blah blah
I
since I've always only done streams in
that world I thought that somehow this
camera that I had there
I could bring and use
to the ninja world that we were going to
and we went to the ninja world like so
last minute switched over so last minute
that I kind of like that's where that's
where I realized that's why I was like
oh [\h__\h] let's go back to that loading
screen one second I'm completely like
did not consider that because I've never
played uh or yeah we are chat I never
been in a different VR chat world that
was not ours and did not use our camera
system
yeah
so did not consider that at all then
panicked then had to quickly use the
camera thing the normal one
uh and and had to get used to using that
so there was some scuff because of that
um but after we switched to the other
worlds you know Amy was following us
with with the camera and all that and we
could carry it around too yeah it was
better
yeah yeah gosh I'm [\h__\h] hungry oh my
God my tummy is growling
yeah
that was so embarrassing
I was so panicking and stressed stressed
out in that moment like oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] how
actually use
the camera Paulo how are you using your
camera she's like oh it's just a normal
VRC camera and I'm like hey oh [\h__\h]
how's this work how's this work I never
used this before we use different stuff
in our world
yeah but I think I managed to adjust
fast enough but yeah that's why some
stuff is happening
you mix thank you for the pinky oh oh
this is the second part
second oopsie which is Mansion stream
[Music]
menu
yeah I think it was Charming too I don't
think it was that bad
now maybe was able to deal with that
camera better but that's because she had
more experience with it um
[\h__\h] VR man it's so exhausting and
blah
if it was less scuffed I would do it
more often
so um thank you for the pinky can read
silently oh
why thank you why do you did you
anticipate that I would be reading many
super channels
I'm fine though I'll read it been
feeling under the weather after stormy
island hopping trip I did the past few
days what
stormy island hopping trip sounds like
when we live in the Maldives I mean we
stayed on the same island but it was
also stormy and it was an island oh dear
I finally got time to catch up on the
vaults so happy you decided to play
Luigi's fashion it's pretty fun catching
the ghost in this game I agree it's so
much fun so much more fun and all the
other stupid horror games
so thank you and welcome back
I don't know if that was supposed to be
like your vacation or so if yes then
that's unfortunate that it was too
stormy but I hope you still had a good
time and a good break
need to play more you'll get used to it
to what we are
I'll never get used to you know how
[\h__\h] exhausting it is
maybe I get used to like the settings
and everything but not to how exhausting
it is it's really exhausting
it's really
heavy and hot but
blah
we all get drenched in sweat every time
we do VR
[Music]
PC mode well I feel like makes no sense
what we are like if I'm gonna do VR then
I might as well or should make use of
the tracking because that's what makes
it special and makes it cute and I I
think it looks much more interesting
to see real body movements
you know
[Music]
then just like the default stance
exactly
[Music]
if I'm gonna put on hand tracking then I
might as well put on everything
ah
I did not try the the suit yet I didn't
have time yet and I kind of feel like I
might need help setting it up but I'm
gonna try in the next couple days or one
or two weeks to get it working
I I have to yeah
but I don't think it works well VR no
that's different
the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I saw Dana doing a treadmill walking
stream yeah yeah
that's funny respect for doing that damn
[Music]
uh Slavic fellow thank you for the pinky
when I first had heard four blood and
your birthday concert I was thrilled by
your amazing performance I kept going
back to listen to it every now and then
now with the new cover release it has
got even better only wow I can improve
perfect thank you I think I mentioned
before that I felt a bit worried
[Music]
about whether or not I could you know
live up to your expectations sometimes
people say oh live version is better
than recorded version blah blah blah now
thankfully and I think it sounds so
[\h__\h] perfect
[Music]
I'm so hungry hungry
foreign
thank you for the pinky I want a title
to start the most horrible month of the
year
horrible month
November why
why what's with November
's fine
oh
[Music]
okay
also your purple cover is amazing blue
is incredible as always and I really
like the art and the glowing eyes and
I'm looping it every day and I love your
music but you know that
oh you got the art so good I love baby
art
kind of want to commission more from
Bebe
Google Google
baby
thank you very much
oh it's you again
yeah let's say that is visiting you when
she suddenly gets a disease only she can
have where butterflies fly out of her
mouth
are butterflies in your house an issue
for you what can you deal with or
tolerate them until fauna gets better
oof it depends on how many
like I feel like if there were like
hundreds of them
it would freak me the [\h__\h] out
[Music]
um but my cats would definitely have fun
with it
I feel like if it's just like a couple
that's pretty and cute
but too many I always answer seriously
but two men is like terrifying
actually kind of disgusting I feel like
you know what I mean imagine
your room being filled with like
over a hundred butterflies can probably
open the window
um oh
seems like an option
why did I not consider that okay no
problem fauna stay it's okay it's okay
if you're sick
they're pretty yeah but terrifying if
there's too many
imagine opening Windows
ah what the [\h__\h] I'm Linux gang just
kidding
[Music]
it tastes like butter hell yeah they do
just gotta call Froggy well as she takes
care of itos
[Music]
Brandon thank you Jacob 47.
tigers
oh happy belated birthday
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
whisper
a showroom chicken Nick rescue I am
flying under the radar and I think no
head Kiara would that notice me
can't believe no one behind
are you talking about Skye
what are you doing
rescue
uh
no
rescue possible you should know that
usual room can only be ended by the
person who is being put into the usual
room
or me
tonight
is the breast I mean best
[Music]
I
show harassment
apologize
[Music]
how did I deserve those party parties
I feel like just by existing I deserve
it right yes
look
yeah what I'm not done yet I'm almost
done though how did you know how did you
know yeah she's like rolling around on
the floor
oh straight swell good stretch
[Music]
I wanna I wanna touch but I have to hold
back Black Version
and foreign
oh Paper Mario
[Music]
yeah I don't know Paper Mario is cute
but I don't know if I would stream it
Max on the first language
[Music]
gentleman nah see you again
I love to talk to a friend I had not
talked to in over a year I was gonna
send a Super Chat to plead for Morty's
life so you could watch the film he made
I'd like to shout oh don't worry oh
they're gonna kill him
okay no I didn't kill him and I don't
plan on it myself
[Music]
thank you for the pinky oh
it says message deleted oh that's
because I timed out dakama didn't die
ah well I found I think that's your own
fault
foreign
[Music]
just checked where smoothie was she's
already gone so I can laugh freely
um
[Music]
for the rest of the chat something for
your bouquet with Mama Turi thank you
it's being used for my shitty Airbnb
so that I can sleep in peace thank you
thankfully I found something like pretty
much like one minute away from the other
um accommodation
so
should be fine should be okay
um
[Music]
hopefully
that really
eases my worries
a lot
yes it's
damn bad
so bad
it really is
separate rooms always necessary
uh unless you're really really heavy
easy sleeper
if you fall asleep easy and then never
wake up then that's then yeah no problem
then
[Music]
my mom's the exact same way
understandable
never wake up well you know what I mean
not literally
yeah ideally you wake up eventually you
know what I mean
lucky enough to be a heavy sleeper
nice nice my mom is a heavy sleeper too
yeah
fast and heavy I wish I would have
inherited that from her
because I sleep slowly
and weekly
I wake up pretty easily me too
but I feel like
I've gotten better
I think I've gotten much better actually
for the longest time of my life my
supposedly fibromyalgia
would force me
um to take like free
sometimes even four hours to fall asleep
and that's
um
half of that is
at least at least half of that is
without even you know like after turning
off TV or whatever
sometimes even when everything's turned
off
it would take me three hours
to fall asleep
and then you know
you must understand whenever there was
like sleepovers or something where I
would sleep somewhere else or or someone
would sleep at my place then it would be
the thing that would piss me off the
most is if someone
wakes up before me
and makes noise
even if they if they'd be really quiet
if I have to uh if I could continue
sleeping I don't have to wake up even
until two hours later or so I
because I cannot fall asleep again
because it takes so much time and I'm a
light sleeper
even two hours it's not enough for me to
fall asleep often
even in the middle of my sleeping
um
ribbon whatever yeah it was terrible but
that was like for most of my life but I
feel like in the past
um
I don't know how long
past time recent time
I've been getting better at falling
asleep may also be
my cats maybe
because they make me sleepy
not my little I've been getting better
yeah
big win yeah thank God look it was
making me go crazy
I hated it yeah
sometimes I would like
I would be so tired and so desperate to
sleep that after three hours or four
hours of trying to sleep I would [\h__\h]
cry
because it was just impossible
I would lie in bed crying out of
frustration from not being able to sleep
well no no
not good times
and we tried sleeping Bells no never
um
yeah it's terrible but but as I said I'm
better now I got used to it maybe that's
also a reason
don't know why I didn't get used to it
earlier
[Music]
in bed and like my I don't think I ever
talked about it in detail but my soul
called supposed fibromyalgia
um feels like
especially strong when or noticeable
when I am
trying to be in a resting position
and what would happen is the moment I am
trying to sit still or lie still
um my arms and my legs
would feel really restless and yes that
would make you think oh restless leg
syndrome maybe I thought so too but
I guess not because
never got diagnosed with them and I
don't know I read up a lot on that back
then and watched videos and I'm not sure
I don't know
um but yeah so I would have to
constantly
not really make big movements but for
example one moment my left upper arm
would feel weird so I just like
make a tiny movement like a really
slight
um movement or like trying to
um Flex it and deflect that maybe
is one way to describe it and then
literally 30 seconds later I feel
something like that in my lower
right leg or so or in my left butt cheek
and so on like all the time and that
goes on and on and on and on and on and
it keeps me from falling asleep
and
yeah that also makes me feel a bit
awkward when I have to like sleep with
someone in the same bed
like I I felt actually pretty worried
about that with Ahmed
when she asked if she could sleep
um with me in my hotel room I was like
[\h__\h] yeah I want uh to you know be open
to that but
what if she notices that I have really
big troubles
on my side of the bed
so
but I didn't want to like say anything
about it I felt like
awkward about it they had the Maldives I
had the same worries to be honest
um
I don't know if they even noticed
because I in both cases
I was trying so hard to hold back my
body felt so
restless and uneasy
and I tried to hold back all these tiny
even the tiniest movements because I
feel like even the tiniest movement you
can hear the wrestle from the blanket
overthinking it but I don't I didn't
want them to think I'm weird
[Music]
so I would just hope that they would
fall asleep fast and then I can move
relatively freely and when I say move
it's really not that I'm moving I'm just
like
like really low-key flexing and
deflexing
but I think you can
notice
just talking about this makes me feel
weird
[Music]
I think that is normal I don't think
it's normal no
I don't notice that with anyone else
they all so so still I don't know how
you can stay so still
hmm
no yeah it feels
a little bit like pain
it's hard to describe
[Music]
um
no I don't mean shifting around why are
you asleep that's different
I don't like shift side to side side to
side
um
it's not the same twitch yeah but I
still have it like under control
it's not like uncontrolled
twitching
um
no anyway that makes me very
uncomfortable but
um yeah so I I worry about that when I
share a bed with someone like on my word
right now
oh yeah yeah
but I don't want to be weird
yeah
I don't know man I think I think that
might be the fibromyalgia but in the end
I don't know and
who knows if it's even a fibromyalgia
but I've had this like since I can think
I don't remember not having this problem
foreign
[Music]
I mean yeah probably no one gives a [\h__\h]
um
but it's awkward to even just bring it
up
yeah it's not really bothersome I've had
the experience
I found a very involved in some
experience before where
this was not a whole life member but
um I've been
punched
foreign
several times
in uh you know bed while sleeping trying
to sleep
it was pretty bad
[Music]
are you in a fight club it was it was
bad like hurt so bad like suddenly
whoosh
oh big smack on my
chest for example
whoa
that hurts so much
yeah so I'm not like that so I'm
obviously not such a bother
[Music]
thank God
that is way worse
uh
that's a weird sleep habit though like
how
how does that work how does that happen
I'm super aggressive should like look
into that with a doctor if you if you
guys have that any sleep kickers and
punchers in here
anyone who does that
I kick
hmm
but the question is would you kick the
person next to you like unconsciously or
would your Consciousness would your body
understand while you're sleeping that
someone's next to you and yeah
you shouldn't kick that person
hmm
one time I sleep I don't move at all
nice
I turn a lot I punched myself
wow
hopefully not too strongly almost like
my cat was leaving no
no oh that's thing imagine you're like a
sleep kicker a puncher and then you have
pets oh
oh they will they will quickly
find a different sleeping place and
never sleep with you again
[Music]
oh man
I'm like shaking
[Music]
um
oh
the mortuary assistant super chats
there's like one two three four five
I'll read those two
okay
and Patsy thank you for the pinky
I made a personal bet that I super chat
you a pig if your heart rate hit 140 BPM
or higher tonight it didn't happen but
I'm so impressed that it will I'll send
it anyways
agree that that in itself
um deserves a praise and respect yeah
great strange and I cannot get you with
the support of Lena really owned it
great job thank you I think it really
went much better than we all expected
and my heart rate I'm sorry it's so
boring
it's I don't yeah I know like Clippers
will make interesting clips from other
girls is really high heart rates
I'm sorry I cannot deliver that
[Music]
but like for me in my case
but people just don't see it as so high
so it's not that entertaining as a bait
in a clip
I'm sorry I'm healthy I wouldn't say I'm
really healthy and I do think my heart
rate would probably go up much higher if
I did like sports
probably we'll have to test that out if
I do like a ring fit stream or so one
day I'll put on the
the heart rate monitor and it will
probably look like I'm getting a heart
attack
because that's what I feel like and when
I do Sports
um
I think my heart rate will look very
differently then
I'm shaking
[Music]
girl
hmm
I always have lower heart rate actually
yeah but I'm not an athlete
I'm saying that the lack of working out
makes my heart rate crazy when I work
out
when I dance too
[Music]
okay I'm freezing why am I freezing
I'm I think I'm gonna go now
um I'm gonna eat and hopefully
[Music]
I want to fix my sleep schedule a little
bit but I have to get up at like
or stay up no probably preferably get up
at like four
probably
around that time on Sunday
so
well hmm
am
of course
that's the problem
[Music]
that is a problem
foreign
[Music]
ER of each team will be streaming this
time I think last year like everyone was
streaming like whoever felt like it but
this time it's uh just the leaders so
yeah you'll have to find me there
um
okay okay okay okay it will be a second
half so it should be that cold outside I
think
because they split it into first half
second half and I'll join in from second
half
which should be pickled a leader I think
first half is Subaru second half this
yellow team is perfect for me
I was there back on the stairs what is
there yeah the only ones that's missing
is
foreign
[Music]
but besides that it's an amazing team
good team to be in
yeah
I hope
I can do a good job at the two games
that I'm part of or at least
at least the relay
because that one's
uh I think the relay is only
overseas members
while the other thing where I
participate everyone's participating
so even if I've absolutely failed in
that one
it's okay
let's find that one's fine I don't have
like I don't I don't feel too pressured
on that one
okay I'm freezing like really weirdly so
I think I left the window in the living
room open for too long
so I'll go now guys thank you for
watching today and I'll go eat something
now and tomorrow I have my day off so
yay go stream for blood and on Sunday uh
after the after the sports Fest and
after I get a good nap I will most
likely try to finish Luigi's Mansion if
everything goes well
if I can get some sleep in um
[Music]
thanks for watching everybody
don't forget the codes don't forget you
know the words I forgot the words but
you know the words
bye
bye-bye
thank you
[Music]
foreign