[Music]
so
huh
[Music]
good evening good evening everyone
welcome um
i i just woke up from a nap
so i might not be very uh
energetic right now let me drink some
water
hmm
i had a very productive day
but with a productive day i must also
stream
yes yes yes we can hear it in your voice
yeah
yeah okay so we're gonna play
like maybe one hour of mario kart not
more
are you guys ready the thing is like um
i'm still very bad at this game still
still still i
i don't know what i'm doing every time i
play this game i have no idea what the
hell i'm doing
[Music]
welcome to the membership um
which one was the one i think the speed
one is the one i always use this one is
from a lamy senpai the other day she did
a mario kart stream
and i wanted to join um
but i tried so often and i couldn't get
into my lobby
[Laughter]
but yeah and these two are because of my
collab with inna i think
yeah she made those two and this is mine
so let's go
i hope i can get in wait i don't even
know the code uh
oh yeah let's go wait did it just say
the code
did you see the code guys okay i didn't
see it
goddammit i think i have to go back to
show you oh wait how do i go back
goddammit i don't think i can go back
right now
wait wait wait wait wait yeah i know it
showed the code but i bet no one wrote
it down
i mean it's still the old code i the
code is not changing
the code never changes please wait
there we go maybe oh oh they made it it
anyway the people who already
participated still have the code
i think in there somewhere wait let me
go guys sorry i have to go back to get
the cold
i think they'll drive against each other
good job trying to get in though okay
so let me let me pin this now i better
get into the lobby though
oh five nine four three nine
nine oh okay okay
what if i don't get in now what if i
don't get in now
or or or every time i go out does the
tournament end because i'm the one who
opened it
[Music]
okay now
i have pinned the comments of spirit
[Music]
so yeah guys did you
did you just uh stop watching uh
kelly's one million stream did you did
you
[Music]
yeah it just ended right
um i watched uh a bits of it
oh what what what's going on are we
gonna watch them
is that those two people who stayed in
the race and the rest um
is mpcs and everyone else just left
why germany go germany
germany germany dodge lodge dodges land
torches land
yes i watched it all oh my god now
you're gonna watch me oh god don't worry
it's only gonna be one hour race though
but she tried so much singing your song
she tried so many times singing a song
yeah why did she try so many times
what happened what happened
i missed that's hard i was actually
quite busy today um
i was doing some business
technical difficulties ah
i understand hey germany why are you
number eight now you were just over what
what i was running for you
germany how dare you lose against npcs
go germany come on but there's another
one though uh how do i
look at the other one either not peach
not luigi not toad no
ah got him i missed it
oh it's germany versus australia
she had the acapella she sounded like
capella what
what she's angle thing acapella well
that's something new
that's something that i didn't do up
until now i sang a bunch of different
versions
what australia wins number one
oh wait is it still going
oh no it's still going oh that's the
last round
australia what nice car you got looks
like a shoe
[Music]
so yeah for the people who watched her
stream what what were your highlights
to her uh how many hours was that in
total
11 hours i think she wanted to do a 10
out of
10 30 but now she's doing she did uh
even more than that i think but did she
end on time
11.5 oh my god guys we have to
do you know what that means right you
know what that means
she took my record away but
i'm not i'm not going to do it right
away i'll take my time with it
but you know what that means
24 hour but no it has to be like eating
eating like
12 hours or something oh my god kelly
why did you do this to me
why why would you do that
i don't want to stream for 12 hours
i don't want us well welcome everyone to
the race
nice to see you uh let's do cheeseland i
don't know
maybe i don't care i don't care
yeah maybe i'll just do it for my 1
million stream one day hey that looks
like me
there's an imposter among us guys
i'm curious what's what country flag she
has
okay isn't that one ah i think i
remember that one
wait which one oh
i'm the one from japan i'm the one from
japan
[Music]
how do you drink again okay okay there
we go how do you
throw an item again
[Music]
oh there we go
okay yes we real smell looking sexy from
behind
oh she could have taken the two items
almost almost
did he just fall down
[Music]
hey
why would you do that
this is his map is really beautiful
let's try this here
way way let's go
it just led me to that side i didn't
even want to go there
well okay
[Laughter]
did you see that you didn't see that
[Music]
magical you for real honey see
why you trying to down i'll get you
look at that drifting scale bell eat it
eat it
[Music]
[Applause]
can someone turn this [\h__\h] up it's not
letting me go where i want to go
but at least it won't let me fall off
the edge that easily huh
yeah i didn't even know i had that item
oh my god look at me
wait a second one second is it already
over
what the no i think
yeah the the kiara on number three
that's me
i i think i want the other steering to
be on generally because although
i think it really helped me with not
falling off the edge in rainbow road in
so long
thank you bye bye guys thank you please
leave the game and let the other people
win thank you
very good bye bye
nice first round uh i think it was
really easy for you guys so unfortunate
indeed
very indeed
so next up i'm not going for the rainbow
road
um actually is this the one that's nah
nah that's probably not probably not the
one i think of
i thought for a second i thought what
what's what's up
what the [\h__\h] is with all these weird
faces the one on the right with the kiss
oh my god oh my god the kiss face the
one next to me
and the one on the very left what are
those faces
[Music]
oh my god i don't want to race with
these guys too scary
too freaking scary
what remember to collect coins because
what
it makes me does it make i notice that
it gives me like a tiny tiny tiny tiny
tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny speed
tiny tiny tiny no no
really really gerber king
and burger baby
five percent faster level only for like
a moment right
it makes you fast in general what
okay
spin getting all that money now
[Music]
me
why is there so many australians i guess
it's a good time for
australians right now
[Music]
dressing so good today hey i lost mine
and where am i gonna go
where am i why am i number eleven not
the company
[Music]
then
i would probably have fallen off like a
million times already
[Music]
they're so good cause they they always
they always uh stream snipe the other
hello live girls
and they got some of them are pretty
good
bye bye guys please leave the race and
then let others join thank you
everyone's following the rules i'm so
proud of you guys
[Music]
you want me to use that i don't even
know that race maybe someone else can
choose it
oh i see a piccolo stream snipers
[Music]
too
their chin did you see that one
nice drive
i've seen those names before
did you see that ass chin though at
least i don't have an
ass on my chin at least i don't
but usa wait wait i forgot
for a moment
always always in decorah streams
in the mario kart screen
okay no i'm not not bad though hey am
drifting way more than usual
okay i almost said something really
wrong there
almost said it don't worry i'm not
saying it
you can't see me but i'm dangerous and
there we go again now i'm a real ghost
not a real ghost sorry i might mix some
things up
[Music]
come on give me a chance to win
by one of them eats it oh right oh my
god
this did one of the bakura fans just go
back
to not eat that blue shell
because he didn't he didn't get the blue
shell
oh is that some tactic like you see it
coming and then you just go back for a
little while
but like it's uh like there's no one
around me that i can use it on
stop sending me friend request there's
no way i'll accept them
[Music]
is that my own bomb
wait why am i where i found the shortcut
i didn't even know about the shotgun
okay at least that wasn't 12 foot
what's what's happening what happened
with the other
japan bros from pecora bye
it's so unfair i'm using things called
tilt controls did i actually run into my
own bump
sasuka i want the water park
oh what the [\h__\h] come on everyone play
with me in the water park i pulled out
my swimsuit
i'll put on my swimsuit
[Laughter]
i bet there's people trying to get in
but it's like probably not loading
hard and i magical
do i have internet problems right now
are we having internet yeah problems
sure it's loading yeah because it's not
letting you guys in
[Music]
hiding also should i try to get in
should i try to
boy what's going on
i'm just all alone yeah this is probably
going back something's wrong
no one can get in it's okay
now i will probably have to watch
someone play again
meow you know what i got myself for
for dinner and on the way back home
as take out i got myself
i think this is uh something you guys
might like
i got myself an angus steak
ha why don't more consoles are not
responding what do you mean
i got myself an angus steak
[Music]
yeah with uh
with some salad some rice and some fries
looking forward to eat that tonight
we see steak
[Applause]
[Music]
from the left side looks like what's
yeah charlie i was just gonna ask you
guys
what that name was again charlie
[Music]
that's the snoopy guy right the snoopy
guy
and the guy on the right side the fourth
from the right side looks like a
male version of aytan
charlie brown i
i have to say i i wasn't really um
much involved with uh snoopy uh when i
was younger
wait we're missing one people oh against
carmel sanders he's my boy
colonel sanders
[Music]
let's go oh
we have a loser with us
can you while you're drifting like is it
not possible to change
like directions like but i mean like
completely
because i know i can like i don't know
no i i
i can't maybe maybe professionals can
[Music]
but you didn't let me go
i was doing so well what the [\h__\h]
i was doing so well
i was doing so ah that's why all the
stare is bad yep
exactly go eat that
is is is what is that waluigi guy number
one right now
unbelievable should be colonel sanders
if anything
why did i just not get to speed
[Music]
yeah explain to me
i don't even know how to jump
what the hell
same button is drifting
then am i always oh wait it doesn't mean
i'm not allowed to drift over
wait is that what it is i'm not allowed
to
[Applause]
[Music]
trip
holy [\h__\h] where did that come from you
didn't see me coming there
that speed at the end i'm never going to
get anything better than that
[Music]
that that was the best i'll ever get
the best ever thank you guys for
participating let the others
in please thank you
[Music]
for that
is that person not old the one with the
glasses
that one looks so much like look
wait one looks like shields empire the
one on the right looks like shion senpai
now
[Music]
uh
wait a second i guess maybe it looks
more like okay
oh actually that's i mean it could be
both
is is okay senpai supposed to be so
small
[Music]
because size wise i think there we go
okay
[Music]
is as good as first place as we all know
it's the same thing four equals one
um but also wait what the hell
we got off of that start what the hell
was that
something weird happened with my
controls okay someone manipulated them
someone sabotaged my controls okay
yes yes come on strip floyd
drift more beach
springs
actually like supposed to be the best
item but it's kind of the worst item
make it better come on
[Music]
look at all those coins i'm making
hey number six hello
you can cross the road yeah no but the
the game is currently stopping me from
doing any cool stuff like that
[Music]
that went right through me but i had to
start okay so much for
this item is useless i take it back i
take it back
i will take my uh my arguments back
[Music]
did you is shoot that did you just try
to shoot that at me
wait why am i so slow
[Music]
come on do something cool come on come
on
okay let's [\h__\h] go this is about
life or death which both doesn't matter
to me because i'm a phoenix
[Music]
what is it with these these japanese
brailles they're just too
good um
[Music]
why is japanese so good are you leaving
now because i feel like okay
thank you next ones come on try
modifying your car but i don't know you
guys gonna tell me
i said well let's let's use like i don't
know maybe even the character is bad is
it can the character be bad is that a
thing i see a lot of people using like
volumizing but i don't wanna because
he's not cute
well which car maybe this is better i
don't know splat buggy
i heard that the
ah let's go for this one because i heard
the bikes are faster
you guys gotta tell me
[Music]
that
is my is my car not good
characters effect weight ah
oh that's why people choose uh wario
because he's fat
and having lots of weight on your car is
good is it really good
is it really good
is that it
what the hell
this race
i think i might have to turn off the the
auto steering again but then i'll fall
off so many times
you know what this reminds me of my
super mario 64
game place and i hate it i hate it i
absolutely hate it
oh my god it's exploding
oh my god
[Music]
excuse me excuse me
call this that
[Music]
just give me some of your items oh my
god oh my god get me a damn it
huh a [\h__\h] coin that's what you give
me
a [\h__\h] coin for real
okay okay i see what we have here let's
go
ain't got those highs
why am i so far behind already i was
just number six and now i'm number ten
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
this was crucial crucial okay
i'm so [\h__\h] slow again unbelievable
okay i need a good item
[Music]
oh my god
without like trying what was that
that was a shortcut i didn't even try
i didn't even want to go there i didn't
even know it was possible see i don't
even know any of the shortcuts in this
game
yoda wait i have the crown though
i have the freaking crown wait why do i
have the crowd
thank you guys please let in the next
people thank you
[Music]
hope you had fun ah
oh yeah uh how do i turn off all the
steering
not like that
plus doesn't do anything
why oh
wait is it is it like wait wait a second
[Music]
i don't understand ah wayne's picking a
card okay okay okay next time next time
but
for probably for this road i'm probably
gonna need the auto steering
[Music]
is that it is that i don't know
chewbacca or something
on the right uh bottom
isn't that some star star wars dude i
don't know
yes it is okay thank god i wasn't wrong
with that
and owl you are trying to look like an
owl wait you're trying to look like an
owl
no it's an owl oh my oh i um
i deeply apologize um
oh i hope i didn't hurt your feelings
you look a little bit like chewbacca
though i must say
[Music]
it's going quite well right now
oh yesterday by the way i uploaded my
schedule for the whole
week did you guys see it i think it's
pretty uh good
i think we have a quite quite nice
schedule for the week
[Music]
very exciting for that very very excited
so i can't talk obviously and now i just
bumped myself again oh my god it's
horrible
okay this is a really bad race it's kind
of like um there is not much space
here frog and yeah
we have a we have a full whole live
english member
um collaboration this week the last one
was at christmas
so i thought it was time to have another
uh full member collab and it's gonna be
an enormous channel because we're doing
some
art related streams and i
i i said how about we do it on inna's
channel
because it kind of fits her whole theme
on her channel
[Music]
by the way is this is this item time
based or is it like
how many uses like is there like a fixed
number
of uses you can use it you understand my
[Music]
it's questions still some time it's
still some time time based okay okay
okay okay then i'm going to use them all
what the hell is with the owl why is it
so far away from us
oh because it's number 12. what the hell
[Music]
one oh i wanted to go to the water park
wait i don't i don't think the people
changed why is it already starting
that was so quick
[Music]
wait that that that that was so [\h__\h]
quick
[Music]
that was so quick help ow you get
another chance so this time you don't
have to be the last one
she gotta prove that she's the better
bird i don't think that needed proving
i'm a phoenix
oh guys i remember when i was younger
we once visited at this water park i
think it wasn't in germany either
i don't know oh i'm number two look at
me
oh maybe it wasn't in germany i don't
know
[Music]
it was pretty dope i missed the item
where is everyone
why is it so peaceful
[Music]
it's
kind of suspicious what's going on i'm
scared
where is everyone
why did you just wait
wait i missed an item what's going on
[Music]
this is weird wait what's going on
when are they going to take my happiness
away when when is it going to happen
[Music]
when are they taking my happiness away
okay i'm i'm protected i'm ready to
protect myself what's going on
i'm feeling so
why am i so slow right now my nose is
itchy
okay i got it i got it without uh
releasing my hand
i don't face it
[Music]
what's going on visible confusion
what's going on
[Applause]
wait am i gonna win is he gonna prank me
in the last second
what is this [\h__\h] race what was
fan looks very scary are you are you
bleeding out of your
eyes wait there's also innate on
hina is there too guys if you
participate at once then please leave
why did i that was so weird what
i'm still so confused
i'm so confused what happened
why is this
why are you bleeding out of your eyes
i feel like they like after a while
um i think at the beginning it was not
on purpose but after a while of me being
number one
i see a few new ones though but yeah
there might have been some people that
didn't leave
can't
[Laughter]
uh what was i just trying to say i
forgot damn it
i saw a bunch of new names though um so
i was trying to say that
i think after a while they were like oh
wait she's she's so happy about being
number one
let's let's let her stay number one this
is kind of peaceful we like it
[Music]
yeah i think they just
felt like helping me out for once what
the hell
where are we going game where are we
going
oh this is nice this is fun
give it back to me
turn off all those teeth i will never oh
my god oh
who left those bananas here who left
those freaking bananas and you don't
just leave bananas on the road
okay i have to turn off a lot the
steering i have to turn it off
oh santa
is someone right behind me oh there he
is ready
this looks like some nice uh holiday
vacation spot is
i wonder what country what what city
they
had as their inspiration for this
when nothing helps anymore use this item
really you think so
come here
[Music]
you saying that was staged no it was not
that was a legit victory from my side
obviously obviously
it does remind me a little bit of my
last holiday which was actually
in japan only only the the side when you
see the water
okay
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat by the
way
oh we didn't hit that one dammit
[Music]
can we still like get anything out of
this
come on come on
okay ah so this is how it is huh
this is how it is is this
and once again the pekura fan is on
number one
mata
okay guys leave please bye bye thank you
bye bye thank you thank you
thank you for participating
[Music]
which one was it again was it why right
okay i know that's 10 10 till control
wait
is that not tilt controls hey that's not
what it is
isn't this one oh
l ah okay almost turned on until
controls
dear lord
[Music]
yup uh what am i what am i looking for
i don't know what i'm looking for okay i
guess we're going with that
let's go oh someone someone looks like
me here
hello and and something that looks uh
i don't know very strangely roughly like
gooda
we've got with her hood on though
[Music]
or isn't the name
from japan that's kind of what the hell
why is there someone called chicken
with my face rude
rude nanny got sick
in fact we cannot let that dude win guys
we cannot we just cannot let him
what was that ridiculous acceleration
that was nothing
okay let me show you my drifting skill
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] the other steering is
turned up and i feel it
[Music]
i need that all those steering but it
[\h__\h] me up so often
i have a handicap now guys you better
help me what the [\h__\h] was that
[Music]
maybe yeah maybe i have to get worse
before i get better maybe that's just
how it is
okay come on we can do this
we have the better than the chicken
where the [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
totally wasted totally wasted that item
oh god i'm so far behind from
everyone i'm
so far behind
[Music]
please wait for me
you're chicken waited for me
thank you i appreciate that very much
i appreciate it you probably knew that
you were gonna get fired if you wouldn't
wait for me
thank you guys
the time is passing by so quickly that's
still like maybe one or two more races
oh my god uh yeah without all the
steering
this is quite difficult let's see
um
oh that looks pretty good
the stats on that one look good has a
lot of acceleration and handling
[Music]
or this one oh that one looks pretty
good
okay let's go with that one for now for
now we
have to keep on adjusting i don't have
time to adjust
i have money take online tiny wheels
yeah i have really tiny wheels right now
yeah it looks uh no that doesn't look
like cali it looks like the that girl
from that anime
that's not really cali there's no way
that cali made it in
cali is probably um dead right now
low speed zero speed
[Music]
do i have zero speed right now
she said she must have got rap
money kills when he must hate fun more
after people taking lives
the real murder concerts in the ruins of
helga
the more that says custom my surprise
totally is snatching lives candy nice
dry stuff in the [\h__\h] dimension
of human eraser can't stop the face that
makes her make sure when stepping up
and my rhymes play first general pain is
out there high five i see you know
what's
[Music]
uh
something business lady getting sit down
um uh
taking souls or something something
industry nanosuckers
not for suckers for one [\h__\h] i can't
remember
[Music]
um
eight i think a lot of people waited for
me there oh my god
i'm so bad right now i'm so bad at this
race about all the staring
hey another one waiting for
oh come on
[Music]
did you wait for me wait no that was
mario
a bunch of people waiting for me i'm so
surprised
i guess i i remember a lot of those
lyrics because i practiced so hard to
to nail uh the wrap
[Music]
gun
oh wait are we waiting for um wario to
end
the race why are you
oh come on
well guys um
well
[Music]
that's okay though because we are going
to end it here anyway it's been one hour
it's one more okay one more okay
okay if you guys want to let me in
[Music]
it's currently closed open it up open
the gates
open the gates let's turn on it
[Music]
no i don't want to spectate i don't want
to look at these people
i don't want to look at them
you better be fat the number one out of
three oh no
please be fast come on
[Music]
is the stream dying is it some people
say it's
uh my stream is dying
no no no okay at least not for everyone
okay that's good to know
good in n a okay
okay stream is fine thank god
like um yesterday's stream
was it yesterday was it yesterday it
doesn't even feel like yesterday anymore
i was i was kind of pissed off because
of youtube
bitching around and and uh
minecraft also bitching around
but yeah at least i got my trident rta
no one's gonna beat that record in her
life hell yeah
stream is dead in europe what
[Music]
only in europe
well i'm good that i'm not in europe yet
which by the way
um
i had a little bit of a realization
yesterday night before i went to sleep
um i asked my roommate
in australia where i'm gonna
to i'm going to move back in
and i asked her for like
uh like i wanted her to speed test
the internet and she did it
because i wanted to know about me able
to stream and i was like ah it's gonna
probably be like at least somewhat
decent right
what she sent me as a
screenshot and now this is only with
wi-fi not with actual cable but still
i don't think it's not gonna make i
don't think it's gonna make it much
better
um
basically at 6 00 p.m
which is not even prime time
i get download 35 mbps that's already
pretty bad but i guess
you can lowkey work with it
and upload 9.5 mbps
meanwhile right now i have something
between 400 and 600 mbps
like constantly it just depends on the
time of the day
so yeah it's 35 and nine and that's
going to be
a big problem that is going to be by the
way last race
everyone who was here before please
leave and let the others join unless you
just uh
drove that race alone that's okay uh
yeah um that's going to be pretty bad
because
even if it's gonna be good enough to
stream like
like a normal like talking stream
i've had issues before with minecraft
when the
download speed is too bad and i've i
also have issues with collaborations
and yeah um
i i'm pretty worried
and i i asked my internet provider
already if this can be improved
by any way with money because i said
money
is not the problem oh [\h__\h] can it be
improved in any way
and he said no because
in the city where i live every building
that was built before 2015
is gonna have the shitty internet and
like even though i'm paying for you know
high-speed internet wink wink officially
like openly publicly it might they call
it that but he said that
inside it's not the real uh glass fiber
thingy
it's not the real deal even though i'm
paying for it
funny thing huh um so yeah
and the the thing that i would have if i
want to stay
in the same house
and and and not move but yeah
but have better internet then i would
have to
pay like 30 to 50 000 k
to do a renovation where i
uh get you know the
the the real glass fiber finish
well that's not going to happen i'm not
going to pay 30 to 50 thousand
dollars euro whatever not not a big
difference
um that's quite ridiculous
i am addicted inside i'm i'm panicking a
little bit
yeah cause i don't know i don't know
what to do guys
i don't know what's wrong
so i was thinking last night obviously i
couldn't sleep with that in mind i could
not sleep
i was thinking i was thinking like um
but we will let's talk about this in the
super chat raining
a little bit more
[Applause]
[Music]
come on
oh wow we got them before yay
hey got number four two times
hey thank you guys
thank you for participating that was the
last race
way way way way yeah that was what that
was with all the stairs
all right that was fun
us let's move over here and
well one second thank you everyone who
had
um fun together with me i will be
reading super chats now
and you're welcome to stay
we'll have a lot of fun i promise
let me get the chat working
on and by the way tomorrow we are
finishing
riser actually arrives at number one
we're finishing
it tomorrow i would be very happy if you
would come
tomorrow to the finishing final stream
oh yes do you guys know
well which which are the most recent
super chats that i have to read
which are the most recent ones
so we have to read super mario super
mario mario kart
yeah and then we play uh rizza too right
away ah the minecraft uh
super chats yes yes yes is that is that
it
no museum oh how about this one
would you like to listen to that
yes okay yeah it's only the minecraft
ones nice
okay okay okay
let me share this uh beautiful thumbnail
of you
which was not the original one but it's
it's uh very fitting now
okay i love that
art that artist is so
[Music]
thank you final count on mentions of the
thumping art has been confirmed at 179
ish oh my god you guys
really really you needed to mention that
so many times
oh yeah wait before we continue let me
continue my my let me
before we continue with the super chat
let me continue my internet worry story
[Music]
he got um my story about
the the problem that we might be facing
so i'm moving in like about a month
and um
so the thing is that
my room basically
so my roommate um
she first of all okay keep this in mind
first of all
my roommate took care of my cats for one
year
and some another girl um
was like renting my room for also a year
that
it was um decided from the beginning is
only going to be one
year and but yes so they did they did
that for me right
so if i if i
the problem is okay i i do want to move
back in but
but internet connection
is like super important to my work i
might not be able to work properly
if i have such bad internet
so what i thought is okay
i guess i can i don't know rent an
office space or another apartment but if
i'm gonna go that far
i looked at the prices if i'm gonna go
that far
to to get better internet by getting
an office space where i'm not gonna be
really sure if that's actually really
gonna do the trick because first of all
walls are gonna be thin second of all uh
i might as well just get my own
apartment and move there right away
um same with if i get a second apartment
just to be streaming there
then i might as well just move in right
away right
like instead of paying two rents
i might as well just move in there but
but then again i feel like
um like uh first of all my cats
um for one year what they had
that was familiar to me was my roommate
and that apartment so when i come back
i don't want to suddenly like drag that
away from drag them away from that
apartment i want them to first get
familiar to me again
like for like one or two months and then
bring my cats into a new apartment but
yeah i guess that's something that they
would have to deal with
but okay then the other thing that like
i i just kind of feel sorry that
i made her
wait kind of like for one one year
yeah i have to discuss that with her
because the internet is just really such
a
such a big like issue
like imagine the internet can still have
bad days and be worse than that
it can be worse than what i just
mentioned and even with the way
it was at the point i got that
screenshot
like imagine me using the internet but
at the same time my roommate using the
internet
why didn't you check beforehand what the
hell do you mean with that when was i
supposed to check
when i was not a whole life member yet
when i never had the idea of joining
uh this and becoming a veteran when i
didn't even know about youtubers when i
moved into that apartment
generally in my city
unless you get a really really really
new like renovating
newly built apartment unless you get a
newly built apartment your internet is
going to be
pretty bad there is no super super super
good
apartment but yeah so even
even if i uh super super good internet
sorry i'm getting confused
but even if i move like into a new
apartment
right away like from the get-go
then think
uh i feel like i'm not even gonna get
one because first of all if i'm gonna
get an uh my own apartment which i was
gonna do anyway at some point
um then i kinda wanna check it out
before i
i before i choose one
i want to see it myself in person and uh
i also feel like if i'm gonna apply for
an apartment
to move in while i'm in japan
and like first of all i think that's
gonna throw them off
because i can't even go see it second of
all
like when they ask like usually
they ask for your like proof of your
income
like if you have a stable stable income
and i mean i guess i have a stable
income but
officially i guess not because i'm a i'm
a fr um
like independent uh
i don't know uh like the
the it changes my income changes every
month
so uh i mean it's it's more than enough
to afford an apartment
but like how do i even i don't know how
do i even prove
that that it's gonna be fine in the
following months
i might have it might have been fine the
last few months but how am i gonna tell
uh the owner of a house that
i'll be fine in the coming months as
well
like do i explain to to that owner that
i'm a youtuber and
that it's it's uh it's okay they can
trust me
for the next few months i don't know
i don't know if they're gonna if they're
gonna buy that
six months history may be fun well the
last six months
ah guinea guinea
well but it's gonna be japanese
if i if i show them my last six months
income
is going to be from japanese bank i feel
like they're
they would be like what the [\h__\h] this is
i don't get this girl she's like she's
like in japan she sends me documents
from japan
i i don't even know if i can judge that
i don't know throw money at their face
uh i don't know it seems like
everything's like
kind of complicated now it's getting a
little bit of
a little bit complicated i don't i don't
know
i i feel like having i feel like flying
over back to australia and then having
uh my own apartment right on from the
first day is not exactly gonna be an
option
if anything maybe the best option would
be to
stay um in that original
originally planned apartment for one
month
try to stream um it
i mean it it it at least has to work to
stream normally maybe not no online
games and no collapse
but at least like streaming normally
like karaoke and chatting streams and
sliver dot io and [\h__\h] like
maybe not even maybe not even slipper.io
but yeah
i mean some simple streams like drawing
streams and stuff like that they should
work for one month and
then in that one month i could i could
find an apartment
uh but then it's like okay
then then we have another problem so
that one girl that rented my room
for one year i'm gonna like she's gonna
leave
and then i only take that room back for
one month and then i'm gonna leave my
roommate
again for so that she has to find
another new roommate that enters in
there
i i don't wanna i don't wanna
like i mean maybe she doesn't care but i
feel like that's uh
yeah i i would have to talk to her about
that
but and she said she's very kind and
she's very understanding
but yeah i'm i'm in a bit of a
difficult situation now because every
option
i talked about now doesn't seem ideal i
don't have an
ideal option right now um
offer your roommate to move with you
i don't see that as an option either to
be honest because of various reasons
on yesterday i mean we kind of started
talking but i had to sleep i
i we just started talking about how that
internet sucks and i need i need better
internet for
streaming um
ah man
pay her rent while she finds a new
roommate yeah i guess that's something i
could do
although i mean she would know she would
know
well yes i did see that cali hit 1
million thanks for telling me
things that are very obvious um
what was i just going to say
uh oh yeah she would know at least one
month
before um
i move out she wouldn't know early
enough but still it seems like kind of
shitty for her that
um someone moves out then i move in then
i move out again then someone new moves
in again that's like
so much tanjo is savage today
yeah yep sorry
sorry i'm sorry
i
kelly just replied to my tweet oh my god
what did she say
let me see let's see
i anticipate it what
oh i seeing you i mean i do not know
about that last but i look forward to
i don't know shaking your hand probably
hmm
am i supposed to be happy about this
recently it's been a little bit like a
roller coaster with me and kelly
got my hopes up a little bit when i
asked her to
get the cats together with me she was
like hell yeah let's do that and then
then the next tweet i sent to her she
was like
nah have you i don't know i don't
remember what that was about
and now again she's like kind of kind of
dead and did it to me
oh yeah the thanks friend one oh my god
friend zone was tough that one was tough
that one hurt me
that did hurt me
now while we're talking about kelly let
me just say
for um all the people who don't read the
rules see now i mentioned cali so
every time i mention some other youtuber
you were perfectly welcome to jump in
that topic
and talk with me about that other person
but in
if i don't mention someone then uh
read the rules you also don't mention
anyone unless i mention
them okay it's in the rules
i have this so often recently and
uh i guess depending on on my mood
sometimes i don't care
um but like as for example yesterday
i saw in one minute in my chat i saw so
many different names
of people like also don't please
please don't tell me to go to other
girls streams
during my stream or to to call up
another member during my stream
or don't tell me about things that
happened with other members during my
stream
first of all i probably already know
about it second of all
[Music]
it's not that's not what the the whole
stream is about so
you guys need to read the rules
it's it's so simple it's so simple
i love talking about the other girls i
do it on my own so
often so just
um wait until i mention cali gura
ame you know whatever peculiar i
mentioned them all so many times just
wait for that moment and then you can
get
all of that out of your system because i
know you guys love talking about
other people so much i like it too
i enjoy it too oh
i enjoy it you know you know i love
talking about cali
but it's not always it's not always the
right time to talk about someone else
just have to say that once because
recently it was getting really really uh
a lot of that
okay we understand each other okay nice
nice i probably um have to repeat that
every now and then because not everyone
is watching right now
probably will have to say it again and
again and again
but this might be a a good start thank
you for renewing your membership thank
you
okay then let's go
let's go suzuki
ark
powerful god cursed kelly with eternal
sleep and the only way
to save her was a spell that would also
wait uh i read that one before
i read that one before so
um i said before i cannot answer such a
question that is ridiculous
that is ridiculous that's just uh
no thankfully thankfully i will never be
in front of such a choice yes
it's also a clip what really
check it's monkey donkey i submitted an
origins of casper fanfiction so
i'll get started on the jasper one now
you wanted both right
with some spicy romans oh hell no no no
no no
but what you submitted an origins of
casper fanfic
where i want to see it i want to read it
thank you monkey gabriel chronos thank
you
uh
[Music]
yeah i have
i had to explain it in japanese because
i feel like my japanese viewers might
really be lost on what's going on with
these mice
[Laughter]
oh thank you thank you thank you for
coming over through some club stunt
kitchen so that's kimberly thank you
sharon ace crown thank you sean
and daniel this is kfb they say it's the
biggest fast food chain in hall alive i
used to work here
well i was really a slave like all the
others now i'm dead meat
i crossed the most yeah by boss in the
world kiara the phoenix
why does that seem a little bit familiar
to me is that a reference to something
is that a reference
[Music]
you guys are laughing
you guys are laughing does that mean
it's a reference
odd world noir opening
skyrim
which one thank
[Music]
good morning gentile can you do your
version of inna's cabin experience
oh yeah such a cute little chicken made
his
way over here oh
hmm
such a cute little chicken made his way
all over here
is that is that what you wanted
i i i i bonked my table to try to make
it sound like i just uh
covered on you i don't know if you heard
that did you hear the bunk
i know that that um someone like
animated
uh that someone drew an animation of
inna
with that uh that cabardon
and it looked so cute we heard it oh
okay okay okay okay okay
that looks so good oh you guys saw it
too you guys
are so well informed
thank you wow thank you i hope you liked
it
thank you for your support jackpot
yeah well next is thank you involved
next time
this is
is
thank you for the pinky sorry if it was
rest for rick quest for rich i don't
know which one it is
thank you for the pinky oh wait the
pizza i'm sorry
okay there it is again sorry thanks guys
thank you
thank you soon just for it for the
support thank you i appreciate it
shadow thank you soon
[Music]
i can't read half of your name so i'll
read the last part
comfortable daikon duncation oh anime
gamer happy birthday by the way it's
belated it was yesterday but still
never too late for a belated happy
birthday yay
i just cut my thumb open trying to open
this bottle of dr oopsie remind me where
the first aid kit is
under my skirt
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah um i take it back i take it back
[Laughter]
[Music]
but no one will get it i'm the only one
with access to it
i'm
i'll take it back i take it back i'm the
only one with access to it
the first aid kit
orange belt that you wear
it's not a belt there's a belt on my
belt otherwise no it's a belt on the
skirt
mama i cut my thumb no you didn't
and if anything you did it on purpose
unbelievable
oh no oh no
i think i cut my finger too oh
oh my god what did i do
what did i do i created some really
really
cursed lore that i will regret forever
10 so i got an
ouchie
that's all you get i'll blow on you and
that's all you get
we're dying boss oh no no
no no no i don't buy it i'm not buying
it guys
[Music]
you're making it worse no i'm not my
nose fantasy started bleeding healthy
well that's just a
that's just natural that's not something
bad that just happens
to some people every once in a while
thank you cameron thank you so much for
the red super chat i'll get to you soon
hopefully lucy and sandoval thank you
while next tuesday
[Music]
thank you for um the advice by the way
on the lectern i
i will maybe one day get that done
alexis
thank you thank you
thank you so much i just discovered
rituals last night and you and kelly are
my faves takamori for the win
wow just last night wow people
people oh yeah let me remove the pin pin
message thank you
people getting into youtubers like just
yesterday is like so surreal
funny welcome to the fandom i guess
and yes you you chose the perfect
pairing
to support
it
[Music]
best couple in the world
random collusion thank you thank you oh
that was when my stream started to loop
oh no
glowstone thank you
wait while we're all here what's your
thoughts on me
am i good enough as a light source i
need validation
oh that's so funny
glowstone you are beautiful
you are beautiful don't doubt yourself
you are a big source of light for many
people who
really really need it desperately
remember it always you're beautiful
and easy to get
which might not be a good thing but
thank you give some love to the
glowstones in minecraft
i mean it's definitely easier for me
like to make a close
glowstone instead of a lamp i hate
making lamps
i hate it needs like iron and [\h__\h] and
then
and then you have to make the chains to
make it look even prettier
the sucks
snaps or signups synapse wait which one
is it
synapse right it's synapse right
not synapse
synapse right
the first okay okay good good
thank you what synapse
what really no it's synapse
for real oh
really okay signups not kashin really
really really are you guys making fun of
me
no it's synapse what the [\h__\h] evil ways
correct really
really carlos shaves thank you
patrick chen dankeshen well next to
sanchez thompson thank you
looking for the top thank you and today
by the way these are i think from the
second stream
of minecraft yesterday uh around
seventeen thank you sean looking for the
top ten kishin well nexus thank you so
much
thank you for sending that red super
chat welcoming
me back but then i had to end the stream
because these things didn't want to work
out but
thank you i appreciate it thank you
thank you so much i'm sorry i'm sorry it
had to end there
i'm sorry i'll make up for it
help mama i cut off my leg by accident
you [\h__\h] [\h__\h] just kidding
i'm not gonna give you the first date
kid oh hell no
[Music]
also sorry you said the red super chat
but then the stream ended
sooner soon late later soon soon soon
later
what what sorry
um i'm sorry um
but yeah i'll make up for it thank you
for the support though jesus i
appreciate it
thank you thank you
jason oh wait she does i think i forgot
your kiss there you go
since youtube decided to eat this stream
exactly when i wanted to post this maybe
it's decided but i'll say it anyway for
the stream schedule
for the stream standstill and faq
youtube
hell yeah alex v duncan swimming
coconuts
thank you saying it's okay boss ian tech
curse is strong we will beat it though
i mean generally in the recent weeks i
think it has been quite
stable um i think things have been going
quite well i don't know what happened
yesterday but generally
generally things have been going well i
would say
thank you though thank you and just
sometimes it comes back
like a like a little nightmare that you
get every once in a while and you're
like oh [\h__\h] this nightmare is back
[\h__\h] hell
well thank you anyway jesus
thank you for the support hopefully the
ian tech curse is uh
not visiting me anytime soon again well
next time
really
that was uh from this stream
and now we're gonna read the super chats
from the current stream
which i guess i'm gonna put the
thumbnail up as well
oh i don't want it where is it
am i blind where is it
i won't see it what
oh there it is
okay let me drink some water by the way
um i think i've retweeted it so you guys
probably saw it but then there's this
this person who makes like
really funny animation for example he
made a lot of holotalk animations
and uh the whole bird's animations
and all that this guy called uh james
chu now he made this uh
pretty animation
uh of like a super chat reading me
me reading super chats yeah and i was
thinking maybe i could use that as like
um
like after the main part of the stream
ends
before the super chat reading starts
like like take like a like five minute
break or something but
yeah like usually i go read the super
chats right away i don't really take a
break
so generally i don't know
but i just want to use it because it's
so cute and it's so fitting
i just want to use it even though i
never take a break
i feel like i feel like it would be cute
though and
it would force me to take a little break
which could be a good idea
to have like a little transition in
there
where i can maybe go down and go to an
idol meeting
or get some water or get some food or
whatever
downstairs and rest my voice a little
bit
but i just wonder when i do that will
you guys leave
during the transmission transmission
transition
what do you guys leave i don't want you
guys to leave
no not me not us no way
but you guys already know what's gonna
happen in super chat reading streams so
you guys would never leave huh
ah you don't leave that easily bye
sweetie pies i love you
i love you my loyal employees
i love you
i will have to i will have to pay back
my love to you guys
again soon and uh trust me i will
trust me i will
not with the first aid kit though
[Music]
nice snack crack okay reading the super
chats from today's stream let's go
flintstone kitchen lazily altered on
kitchen
i hope more people can see how cute she
is i think everyone already knows
my dear pickle pea fan my dear miku pee
i think it is public knowledge that miko
senpai
is hella cute and hella funny
but yeah everyone was so excited when i
announced
uh mikko senpai as the next guest
it's gonna be interesting because this
will be our first whole talk guest with
um 3d
so um i'm not sure
wait did i mention i feel like i
mentioned this before
yeah i mean obviously she's gonna be in
3d uh
yeah uh i'm not sure how
it's gonna look when she sits on my
couch
yeah i i um
i'm i'm wondering about that nana miko
i mentioned it in the membership ah
that's why i felt like i mentioned it
before
so
yeah but yeah um
will be interesting yes you'll be in 3d
so
i have the thumbnail by the way i didn't
show you guys the thumbnail right i'll
unpost it
i'll post a thumbnail when i uh ask for
the questions
and i'll i'll ask you guys for questions
soon
i'm so nervous guys
i also never talked to her before
so yeah i'm pretty nervous
like recently all the all my all my
collabs
all my collabs with people i never
collab with before
are like like we talked for the first
time
before right before the stream like
in the back in the days in the beginning
i would ask
them to like like a talk with me on a
separate day before to just like get to
know each other
but recently there has just been no time
neither on my side nor on the partners
side
so yeah uh
there's just it's always like first time
we talk is
at that collaboration so holo talk as
well
uh is um yeah
always like first time we talk
um but so it still goes
it still goes well but it makes me kind
of nervous and
uh with mikko senpai i don't know
i i i i at the moment i'm still like
when i when i
write to her i'm still like in japanese
um
respectful speech like in very pool i i
write to her very politely
[Music]
i think once the stream starts um i can
throw away that kegel and she will do as
well
the polite speech and we'll just like
yell at each other
and and throw [\h__\h] use at each other
yeah that's actually some people
um like
said before that the way i speak with my
senpai's
is rude or so but i think those people
don't really understand japanese well
like only a little bit or
or so or only watch like clips or
something
but first of all
it's for example with super senpai when
i
when i like tease sugar senpai she
teases me as well like we tease each
other it's just like a fun interaction
yeah and uh outside of the stream
we don't like we we get along perfectly
fine
and uh yeah it's just uh i feel like um
[Music]
we just we're just having fun you know
not only me and super simple but just
generally generally with these kind of
collabs
uh also with uh lena senpai at least
senpai
wait a second elena tong
lena morena
dad was in no way like me being rude to
her we
were just like i was just trying to you
know
get the stream a little bit like
hyped up and funny and you know stuff
like that
readw kia oh my god guys guys guys guys
guys
there's this there's just one dude
there's this one dude um who
ever since their re-debut is like
following this conspiracy theory
um of me being like actually like reborn
and generation two now
and like he replies to me every day
and to other fans as well every day like
what are you talking about she's she is
a second generation she should be
respectful to her senpais
and all that and like i saw that for a
moment i was like
it's you for real and i checked out that
dude's uh
profile and and like everything he's
like
so so deep into this conspiracy theory
like he has he makes like graphics like
like um
he tries to prove people he sends them
like videos of my re-debut and then
people like start a fight with him
and are like um no um i mean look at
this
her original debut she actually debuted
that like in september
so you need to really get your [\h__\h]
together and then they actually start
fighting but he
he stands his [\h__\h] ground he's so
dedicated
he keeps staying true to his conspiracy
theory
he keeps going and going and going and
going
and every day like when i collab with
gura or ina or anyone he's like
oh you're collabing with your senpai
again yeah that's nice it's nice to keep
interacting with your senpai
it's so funny like i was like oh my god
this dude is so dedicated but some
people actually believe that
that he believes it but like he's
obviously trolling but
it's so funny
it's so funny like he's so yeah he's so
into it he's he's like actually picking
fights with others and they believe that
he
actually like like believes it and try
to
prove the point and try to tell him how
it actually is
well yeah i i am so amazed like i can't
i can't even
be mad like it's so funny there's so
much dedication behind that
oh my god oh my god it's so funny
it's so funny
i'm so funny
so yeah guys don't don't pick a fight
with him he
just just just go along with it just
don't don't pick a fight
he some people really think that he's
serious about it and get really mad
just go along with it okay
is so funny this is this is the thing
though with my
with my viewers you guys are like really
into
role playing
like i mean the whole casper thing stuff
like that
you guys are really into that [\h__\h]
and i love that i love that you guys are
all taking up some kind of role with you
kfp something something
i love it this is us this is our
community
flickering light bulb i mean what the
hell kfb
flickering light bulb what is what what
what
kfb second pope kfb bonked mop
kfb space fleet admiral kfc secret agent
kfb dining crew kfb never admiral
kfb puppeteer kfb looking hat smith oh
my god like these
some of these are so ridiculous ksp
pineapple taste tester
kfb onion there's like simple
simple like food objects
can't be timekeeper kfc chair okay if we
cash register
it's it's so ridiculous i love it
thank you casey that beat put the red
super chat don't worry about it by the
way my finger still hurts
you will not touch my first aid kit
oh my god thank you though for the red
super chat
[Music]
thank you for watching thank you
all right let's continue
is that like when i die in your supply
and new kiana
i supply myself you don't need to supply
me but okay
you you're the you're the kiana meme
supplier not the kiana supplier what the
hell
kfb bucket buckets you're the bucket of
the bucket
what what we got we got we got double
buckets
everyone oh my god
oh my god
oh dear oh dear yeah i mean
wait how do we how did we get to this
tangent we were talking about mikkelsen
by coming to holotank
[Laughter]
[Music]
we've updated the curriculum at kfb
college to include
mamaloni 301 intro to casperlord
fake fives 201 and writing a message for
red super chat
what the hell and have also made cooking
101 optional well who needs cooking all
these other ones are way more important
thank you very good we need that lure we
need those lore updates thank you
that's very important for newcomers they
don't understand what's going on
is it guys is it is it possible that
we scare off newcomers
wait we gotta look at what the people
without a membership say
no way yes
maybe it's really hard to find uh
non-members
yes probably
no no no
what i think they get confused but
curious
i guess that's good yeah getting people
curious to getting to know me
and the community better because they
don't get it
might be a good way to make them stay
i just what i'm here i'm not a member
i'm not afraid
i'm new and i love you i love you too
i'm new and you scare me oh you scare me
too
didn't scare me off to be honest i found
it endearing oh
i think they'll find it fun i remember
but we've been here since the ogw oh
thank you
well then you know what's going on you
know what's up
i like you since the start tanjo thank
you i've been here for mom's instinct
forever thank you
i appreciate you guys even if you're not
a member i i understand like
you might be broke or you might just
don't want to join maybe you think yeah
the
the benefits are not worth it which is
kind of weird they're definitely worth
it but
but um i understand like if before i was
uh a member of whole life i was broke as
hell as well
so i i get you guys all of you who can't
join the membership
all of you who can't send a super chat i
know that even
even one dollar is like important to
some people i get that totally
um so oh yeah and i guess it's also not
available in some countries
yeah or you too young or whatever
definitely don't feel bad about it i i
understand
so thank you guys thank you i wonder if
i can
you know how there's a setting where it
allows to only let
members uh write in the chat i wonder if
there's a setting to have
only none members right in the chat so
that i can give them some more
appreciation
i don't think there is such a setting
but you members just will have to shut
up
no no
just kidding just kidding just kidding
guys
i mean if you're not a member and you
really really really really want me to
read one of your messages um
i do like um
[Music]
faqs every once in a while like the
marshmallow streams i do sometimes where
if you're lucky
and ask an interesting question
then you have a chance of getting picked
up you know
and i i do try to reach the chat a lot
i do try
that's okay no not pra nate brown that's
okay
been here since the day we would have
enjoyed the membership story attention
and broke as [\h__\h] really don't worry
about it
really it's okay it doesn't matter to me
thank you for the membership though
new member thank you and thank you for
renewing your membership thank you
what no questions just love for albus
thank you
thank you guys same here so here's this
debut thank you
i'm too young to send super chats and be
a member okay
now don't be sad about that uh
one day when you're older you'll miss a
day when you're younger
uh and yeah you gotta follow those rules
there's a reason why there's an age
uh restriction there's a reason for that
you should you should save your pocket
money and
and use it on other things not on me
found potential from a recommended
takamori video ooh
i have to say i really like you ever
since your debut and you always make my
days happy and brighter thank you so
much thank you thank you too
that makes me happy
thank you guys okay let's continue
reading what about baby xander well
it's not it's not the baby super
chatting it's um
the papa so that's okay
i'm not you but you still actually scare
me boss
sometimes though most of the time you're
very cute and beautiful and hot and yeah
you're a fun and energetic person love
love
did you think i would not read your chat
did you think i would not read that
you still actually scare me boss
explain yourself you thought i wouldn't
read your
chat huh
why do i scare you what's scary about me
huh are you serious now like is that a
joke or are you serious they
actually scare you like why what's so
scary about me
i mean i know that this face is scary
but other than that i would say i look
quiet
i look quite nice at night i have a not
so scary voice
unless when i do this
ah
are you crying no don't cry oh my gosh
[Music]
i'm sorry i'm not sorry this is not this
is not my normal self
this is not me normally
that's what every second is like in the
usual room yes
indeed that's how i really
that's how it feels to be in the usual
room
what do we call the usual room in
japanese
[Music]
explaining the usual room to my japanese
bros
[Music]
we got a member because of this welcome
being the villain is my job oh yes it is
oh yes it is you understand perfectly
is that as i see wonderful
do you know your place
[Music]
[Laughter]
name said that he doesn't deserve to be
put in the usual room he hasn't done
anything
i had to remind him what he has done
until now
[Laughter]
i said senpai again about about kelly
susan loves kelly um
well um this is gonna give the dude
with the conspiracy theocy a lot of uh
a lot of proof that he will use against
me
oh no oh no he will cut that out and he
will use it against me
oh dear lord what have i done
what have i done okay continuing
so that's keyblade wait oh there was a
continuation to that tweet however due
to those recent so-called revolutions we
have found that the
you un unsavory single units and
liabilities room
wait that's the usual rules
what the hell
that's the unsavory single units in
liabilities room is seeing issues
keeping up with re-education however
with a stamp here we can
increase the budget oh
nice one
approved i
there you go please spend spend as much
money as you want
to the re-education is very very
important
[Music]
random but thanks for convincing me to
buy the yakuza game just finished it oh
nice though i need to play that again
too
patrick chen danke shin happy australia
dai
you mean which which australia are we
talking about it's the 26th of january
here down under and then what
and what better way to celebrate than to
raise our hearts out
which australia are we talking about
i guess you're australian not my
australia real australia i mean real
australia is obviously this australia
what do you mean you mean my you mean
not australia it's not the real
australia what the hell
the real australia is in europe
[Music]
thank you this is my first superchat
thank you
and serve blackburn
happy birthday i guess i got some money
for my birthday is it
is it today happy birthday definitely
there's a vault thank you soon second
wolf thank you
k1wt9 thank you thank you for the fun
attacker for youtube thank you
i need to reset all of my thingies
foreign
i'm resetting my my my effects
oh there you go there you go
okay i'm ready
[Music]
what
oh you mean was that the moment where i
had like connection issues in my
cart thank you
jasper it's so funny you guys are so
funny i don't get it
how can you guys be so funny how can you
guys be so funny
mamma mia unbelievable
thank you
thank you when are you gonna do a 12
hour stream
someday someday maybe maybe uh when i
get one million at the latest
at the very latest i'm going to do that
jay drago danke kitten
[Music]
and thank you thank you cat for real oh
oh yeah
cat for roland's are definitely going to
come in action again soon
actually i guess i don't really need to
use them if i don't go outside why would
i want to get rid of the
the cat hair on myself it's just it's
it's it's honestly it's um
it doesn't there's there's no meaning in
even
like trying when you have long hair cats
long hair fair cats then
you you don't even have to try to get
rid of that hair off of your clothes
it's impossible it's impossible like
when i
when i go to go to the the bathroom and
i wash my hands
and i i dry them at the towel then i
instantly have hair cat hair on my hands
again
and if i just air dry my hands still
there's cat hairs in the air or whatever
i don't know
but i instantly have hair on my hands
again
can't confirm it is impossible right
exactly this is not about me being lazy
it's just uh
you guys don't even know like i need one
of those sticky rolls i
i do have those it's impossible to get
rid of all of the hair
impossible especially when there are
um shedding oh my god
and my cats are like shedding like every
every day of them
here unbelievable
gd kfb thank you for the pinkie thank
you
caddy was ready to sing hirotoyi for
free 30 minutes to get it right she was
asking if she can do a cover of pinot
noir to give it justice
why was she having so many issues with
only with hinotohi but the other
songs were fine
ah was it because um she
played that one the instrumental from
like an actual music player and the
other songs
the other songs weren't fine oh
oh all of it she didn't get the timing
at all oh she had too many issues oh
oh too bad
oh next time next time tell her um
i currently have a
i currently have um desktop audio or
whatever the
the source is where you play the audio
tell her uh
when she has that problem again uh 30
milliseconds
sync offset i figured it out it's 30
milliseconds it's pretty perfect
and the rest is on zero just the desktop
audio
30 milliseconds remember it you've heard
it here first guys
yep she was doing like 200 to 300 what
oh no no no no she said it to 250 oh no
what oh my god
that's way off yeah it should be like
about
30 i mean i don't think it should be
different because right now she's even
using the same
um she's using go xlr just like us
she did not use the go explore i even
done it i don't think it matters
uh ah maybe i don't know
but she did buy a gold solar she wasn't
using it why not
interesting oh well i don't know she'll
uh she'll figure it out for the next
time she does the live show
she didn't use the girls laura it didn't
sound as good yeah i love my going
it's amazing it was fuzzy
she should ask um ammo for the ghost
solar settings i think everyone
everyone in whole live english now has a
go xlr
and everyone used the settings that amma
gave to us
like she sent me uh she set me up with
her settings
when i got my go xlr um i was like um i
don't know
what to do with all these settings and
then she sent me um her
her usual settings
which is by the way i now know why every
time i record something on my soundboard
i know why it is
gone the next time i restart the pc is
because it just
goes back every time to the settings of
ahmed to the original settings
which don't include that soundboard well
yeah anyway it doesn't matter
amelia texan
i'm attack tips she would have to
restart obs to fix it
ah
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah if for some
solutions you might would have had to do
that and that is indeed uh
annoying yeah oh well anyway i mean she
had a great stream anyway as far as i
know
so uh thank you jdkfb
magic thank you how are you doing today
i bought the whole ibn t-shirt yesterday
oh yesterday
was it because i reminded you to do it
i really wanted to get it because it has
your art on it thank you that means a
lot to me
thank you thank you
have fun with the t-shirt let me see it
when it comes
brian hichner relax thank you so much
i thought that if someone steals my
record again it's gonna be ame because
she always streams very long
but it was calling that was so
unexpected like normally she would never
stream that long
never it was only because that marathon
damn man damn it
oh well swan
[Music]
so how many kfp employees have been
fired today oh
[Music]
today yeah i didn't fire anyone
damn it i missed the chance i don't
remember the names
thank you thanks for being bringing a
small joy on my food poison day oh [\h__\h]
hope you get well soon
zelda game could make it your marathon
game to win back longer stream
oh 12 hours zelda huh
i feel like i couldn't play a zelda game
for that long because i would probably
like
um i feel like
i need a break because like i don't know
maybe i don't know maybe we would have
to try
[Music]
rage quit yeah something like that
probably
12 hour rise or two on release day i
think release day is tomorrow but we're
finishing rise on one tomorrow
and we're gonna start rise or two on the
next day though so that's fine
riser too finally finally round the two
is out yay
i'm excited hope you guys are too
brazilian
thank you for the pinkie i remember my
word congrats on making fourth quiet
out of my word what what was the word
though
thank you
thank you thank you there's a vote for
the pinky
shoes what the hell we what's up oh
because of my title i guess my title is
weak
thank you for the super chat thanks for
uh joining stream
[Music]
if you could only brush your teeth with
either hot water or cold water for the
rest of your life which one would you
pick
how hot are we talking i would say hot
water to be honest
um if it's like i mean if it's the
maximum hot water
that my current tap can do
i would go with that
because i i do that already actually
i do that already i don't think we're
talking boiling that's quite extreme
all right thank you for your support and
that's a really good question to ask
in the red super chat but thank you
thank you i appreciate it
uh the pro card racer has proven herself
once again on the track
with a solid uh first is um
uh what how do you call it it's uh
it's like um when there's a line in uh
in the middle of the word what do you
call that
english please cross out thank you
first cross out fourth place
congratulations on a massive improvement
and i hope you
come first in the future there may be a
super chat with that too
ah wait wait wait i did wait
in one i did wait i did become number
one in this stream
i have no idea what happened there but i
did get number one today
let's see if i get another super chat
for that later on from you
mulderman thank you
can't believe after all this time it
would be in the kiana maya card a stream
of all places to get clear footage of
bigfoot
what are you talking about what are you
talking about that
that owl
thank you
this is the moment where i got number
one
[Music]
yay well done my queen
first place wink are you well i don't
get the wink
thank you hell yeah i got number one
dude i got it i got it
i got it i often got it
that was so undeserved though i don't
know what was going on there
i don't know what they were doing what
were they doing in the back
i don't understand they didn't even
they didn't even like like have the
possibility to talk behind my back about
about like rigging the game or something
they couldn't even do that
hey let me eat some pistachios
nuts are good for your health right like
i haven't eaten like nuts in
like a million years but i picked up
pistachios
at the supermarket and
they're i love pistachios actually
pistachios are so good pistachios are
like the only
kind of nuts that i would eat as a snack
hmm
don't you agree pistachio oil
do not the only kind of nuts that i
would just
eat like this
yummy
why are they so good
okay so so aren't they super healthy
please let me
make my and please help me make myself
feel better about
uh being healthy
what does what do not skip to oh wait a
second
i was wondering why the chat was being
like chat don't make it weird and stuff
i was wondering why you guys were
getting so crazy over it
i see now i see
you know where you're going guys you're
going to the usual room
hey that's interesting um daily
consumption of nuts like peanuts and
pistachios can facilitate
the brainwave frequencies linked to
cognition healing memory and learning
a new study has confirmed the fact what
that sounds like some magic or something
oh my god i'm gonna be a magician
bird brain fixable shut up
hmm
they can lower your chances for cardio
vascular disease what is that is that a
heart disease
i have a heart disease
it's being endlessly
in love with cali
i can't do anything about it no matter
how many times i die
actually yeah my love for kelly is
sometimes is the cause of my death too
isn't it when she when she
how to say when she um
when she i can't find a word
when she puts that
can't find a word and she when she
thrusts that scythe into me and i die
that's basically when i die of loving
her
so yeah that's my heart disease
shut up shut up stop it stop it stop it
mmm nuts this is so weird you guys make
it so weird
nuts
hmm
you guys are going crazy and i'm just
eating nuts in peace
now who's that who's the thirsty one me
or you you
you guys are bottom left not me oh my i
forgot i have an
angus steak downstairs i shouldn't eat
too many nuts
well i you guys glad that i don't have
english as my first language
maybe maybe i would talk the same way
even if it was my first language
i have to say though everything i said
today
that is somehow weird was not even
intentional
i'm not even trying it's just like
happens i don't know
so yeah jdk thank you one more time
thank you for coming back disabled thank
you
thank you for the pinky doubters make
claim this first place win was staged
that is fake news tensor is a winner and
she wins big especially at mario kart
just hey time only though in my whole
mario kart career
that might have been the first time i
ever got number one
i think maybe thank you for the
membership
logo account name thank you for the red
super chat
all of you stay cool latin to have her
victory flip sealed
you didn't you didn't stage anything how
would you have done that
i think just after maybe like after the
second round people were like oh she has
been
up there for so long let's just give her
a win
i feel like maybe at the end they were
like that like everyone had the same
thoughts
um but in the beginning it was
definitely
not on purpose
[Music]
to fix your net
[Laughter]
okay
okay okay let me refresh my super
titties
super chatty super titties did that just
sound like something weird to you guys
that was not on purpose i just wanted to
play around with my words
i feel like anything sounds weird to you
guys now
um no it was fine okay
all right now we're good okay okay okay
okay
thank you guys for the memberships thank
you
okay let me scroll down where did we
stop
i did i refreshed my super chats
[Music]
um
damn you guys send a lot of super chats
during the reading huh
um out here
pier pyronius thank you thank you
i think those numbers should still be
okay to stream dental
i think yeah generally for streaming
normally
might be fine but um
anything that has to do with
collaboration or like minecraft or
any games that rely on internet i think
are gonna be
problematic to be honest
but i i think the most reasonable option
for me
would be just move back into my room
test it out it should be at least good
enough to stream
like like noble like chat chatting
streams karaoke streams
uh drawing streams worst case if if
that's all we can do that's the worst
case but okay
um do that for if
if the internet is really bad and do
that for one month and then move
or like maybe two months if we can
[Music]
do that but at least uh i wanted to move
anyway and i told you guys recently
about my realization that we don't have
an air conditioning in our room and
only the new expensive apartments in in
my city
have air conditioning usually we don't
have air conditioning in our apartments
um but i want an air conditioning um
for summer because now that i work from
home i feel like i really really need it
otherwise it will be very rough so
i had a i wanted to move out before
summer
anyway but yeah um i'll have to
talk to my roommate i hope she's okay
with it but
i really really hope i mean it's not
like she's financially
dependent on having a roommate not
really that's not exactly the case
but the room will be wasted if she
doesn't have a roommate
oh well we will see and we'll see but
the the other thing that that might be
the best option that i can think of
right now
but that means that i move
then i stay there one month like i move
from country to country then i stay
there one month and then i move again
after one month so that's like moving
two times
two two huge moving moves
in like one month
and that's gonna be for me very
stressful i think
and we might have to deal with many many
problems
yeah rough times ahead yes and i hope
i i hope you guys will support me anyway
because i
i am already stressing out right now i'm
kind of scared i feel like it's gonna be
super stressful
and i know that things are gonna go
wrong i know
it we're gonna have you guys remember
you guys remember that time when i had
to stream from my manager's place
it's gonna be like that but but probably
worse and longer
with lots of lots of games crashing lots
of internet problems lots of streams
crashing
i don't know thank you guys
it's so stable right now i wish it could
be like that forever
but also like the whole packing like i
have to i have to get started to pack
all my [\h__\h] that i have here in japan
and sort it out and throw a lot of stuff
away get rid of the furniture blah blah
blah
because i can't bring the furniture over
there now that's a bit difficult
so moving over back to australia first
of all this is gonna be very stressful
for me behind the scenes
and then moving again in australia
[Music]
um
i hope you guys will stay with me and
support me for those
difficult times i see it i can see the
future
gonna be tough let's read the super
chats thank you guys i love you
thank you thank you you all are so
supportive i love you
and this will vault thank you soon thank
you for the thinking conference on
another fourth place generally we've
seen much improvement over the past
several mario questions really
maybe i should play it more often and
i'll get really really good um
just need about 5000 more of these it
would be more
it would be cheaper to move into my own
apartment
that's newly built and has good internet
it would be cheaper
but also oh my god um
one last thing that's internet related
and moving related
so right now i have um decent internet
that has like i told you it's like
depending on the time of the day
it's 200 to 600 700 mbps
download and upload really depends on
the day but it is really good and i mean
there were some times where we had
problems during the the pre uh prime
time but that problem seems to be gone i
don't have that problem anymore
so yeah this internet is super good like
even the upload
is often like 500 600 mbps even the
upload
what uh so i told my
uh friend who works for the internet
provider that i'm using in
australia i told him that i have those
numbers in japan
and then i just pay like a normal price
for my internet
and he said he said
oh in australia
getting that speed would cost you just
for the internet
300 to 400 dollars per month
just for the internet and i'm like what
the [\h__\h]
for real um
what so yeah um even if i move to a new
park a new apartment that has the
possibility of getting that speed
i would be paying three hundred to four
hundred dollars for good
internet per month and he knows what
he's talking about he's worked at this
huge internet provider for years now
yeah that's insane
i but what choice do i have um
it's i wonder if i can write it up as
business expense
she did also um
suggest that i should switch to a
business
user contract um
if i do that then i can probably write
it up but i don't know how writing off
stuff even works
i don't even know how that works i mean
it is i do need the internet i do need
the good internet for streaming
it's my job
well well well you only have gigabit for
just 30
per month what maybe that also depends
on the city nah
nah i think it's only the country i
guess the provider probably doesn't have
different numbers depending on the city
just
on the country
finland pretty good
definitely write it up on texas but you
also don't need internet
that is that fast yeah that's true but
um
i think the other op i think there's no
real in between i think the other option
would be getting that shitty internet
that i would have now
but yeah anyway no that's
that's another thing yay
so many problems going to
[Music]
you gotta try and ask them for monika
tips or a collaboration oh yeah
they'll guarantee to break oh yeah i saw
i saw oh my god i saw a clip of aqua
senpai ago
where she would at the beginning of the
race she would drive backwards
to be the last one i guess to get a good
item
then she would by the way in the yoshi
island
uh yoshi island map then she would start
driving
uh from uh like normally and
get a she got the no this is also with
uh luck
the luck is important there too uh
because she got the just the right item
and i think she wanted the bullet i
think the
bullet and she got some some triple
uh mushrooms and stuff yeah yeah and
then she ended up being number one
but i i
[Music]
i'm often number 12 number 11
and get a bullet but i don't get
anywhere near place number one
nowhere nowhere near that
i get nowhere near that also that was
without any
other players by the way so i don't know
if that's going to work that easily
or that smoothly when there's other
players in the game
so so so across the final marriage
happy birthday elvin
she's amazing she's built different
is she is she always that good at games
she plays like uh
like even for the first time or
or or is does she also suck at games
sometimes
oh my god
i mean yeah she can't be good at a game
that she plays for the first time can
[Music]
she
i i i challenge
alcohol senpai to playing
chess against me onion versus onion
come on aqua senpai you can't be good at
every game
[Laughter]
i challenge you to play
onion chess with me and the loser
has to eat an onion oh my god no no no
no
no no why did i just say that
but actually i think i can win against a
class and fight
i think i can win there's a glass
no no no it will happen one day
you've been here on choco senpai's quiz
oh thank you for reminding me
that that is true that
that is true and chess is
might be a game but it's a brain game
and if i
beat i did beat
aqua senpai in a in a knowledge quiz in
an iq quiz
so i might have big chances
for chess because that's more about
having brain and
okay even if i don't have much brain
i might still you know
half you know no you know
no
[Music]
i doubled her score yeah i buy one
yeah yeah you got two points and she had
one point yeah
but i have to say i was quite
handicapped because that that that quiz
was kind of
japan themed and it was in japanese
and for akwa senpai it was about her
country
in her language so if i would have
gotten the same kind of quiz in my
language about my country
you know understand
i'm just saying yeah
looking forward to collab with aqua
senpai one day
i respect her insane gaming skills
though like really that's
uh i wish i was that good at gaming
donovan comes duncan
rennie versus thank you life sucks and
then you have to move again i remember
the two years i had to move six times
because of life planning ahead and
expecting changes is
all you can expect children yeah wow
that
six times in two years yeah that's rough
um i had that before too
i had such a situation before as well
where i moved also like six times in
like one and a half year or so
that was a long time ago but
really annoying all i was oh i oh that i
wanted was just to settle down
yeah abby another club thank you so much
rachel thank you for client
i just started hatching but the world
outside is cold and cruel made this
little chicken snuck up to you and
embrace your love forever
oh
yes that's so sweet all of you
oh if you want to stay with me forever
i'll warm you up forever that's so cute
come on
of course no it's so cute you guys are
so cute sometimes
no ah thank
you're welcome yeah well i'll protect
you
but if you're so scared of the outside
world being cold and cruel why
why did you make yourself the kfb
punching bag
it's not gonna make it better party up
thank you
wanted to say this fall guy's stream
make the world a better place don't
stream snap to phoenix during her race
keep the smile on kiara's face
oh i see because we're rapping a lot
during that stream
i wasn't able to watch hawaii for 21
days and i really missed this
i'm grateful that you've done your crazy
fun mario kart stream was what i came
back to
welcome back i think you've really
improved as an entertainer
thank you so much that's very kind of
you thank you soon
can't be usual room night shift thank
you soon thank you
thanks for today fun mario history mama
but i have something sad to say which is
semester 7 tomorrow
no i will not continue reading that
super chat i don't like it when people
say goodbye after all i don't like it
noticed you well out of thank you
enjoy to insult thank you cameron thank
you for your first super chat thank you
for the
rat for you first of all being around
what the hell
cameron thank you so much hey get my
first super chat but i felt it
like it was about time to send some
support to my favorite oh
thank you wow
that's very very generous of you your
support
definitely definitely reached me thank
you so much i
i appreciate the [\h__\h] out of it thank
you so much
function i hope you're enjoying my
streams
now and also in the future i'll do my
best
to to um keep you in the kfb
crew thank you nano flight so fancy
coupe thank you have you gotten any
physical fan mail no still
nothing i don't know why but i'll
definitely annoy
my staff to give me something before i
leave japan
because there has to be something
because you guys said you sent
it so much like ages ago
i'll i'll definitely uh remind them
yeah sorry guys
sorry guys i wish i uh i wish i could
have like you know
did you write anything weird into your
letters did you did you
did you write me like your your your
private
phone number or something because maybe
it got confiscated because of that
did you write anything weird
no
okay well
i'll check up on that definitely
someone must have tipped off the step
about the cold activities
you think it's because of that
you could
[Music]
oh no they definitely know my address
okay
okay we will get it eventually the
japanese members recently have received
something as well it seems the
the new year's cards some members have
received the new year's cards
and some of you guys sent me letters
before new year's like
like uh christmas or even thanksgiving
[Music]
yeah help i heard my eyes looking
directly at you
what's your account name [\h__\h]
what how
oh oh wait i guess uh
i don't know man you're a bright like
the sun
okay because you're so radiant huh
okay okay
okay
chicken fingers are just another term
for chicken tenders are these on the
menu now it seems like we're
like there were a lot of offerings
tonight
true yes let's put them on there i mean
you guys
you guys cut off your legs to get my
first aid kit
well i'm gonna eat your leg
kristen lozano thank you willow of the
winds andrei dankeshen
trevor g duncan thank you i'm glad you
enjoyed it
thank you skye dankeshen
thank you thank you i hope so too darf
shemain dankeshen
ellis thank you for the red super chat
thank you mwah
i know you were bottom left center but
with this under my skirt thing you just
went off the chart but i like you just
layer thank you but that was not on
purpose
[Music]
thank you ellie's name thank you very
much for your support and thank you for
not giving up on me
thank you
villain thank you shannon kfc that beat
also thank you for the red super chat i
already already uh answered it but thank
you once again
thank you and you're even gonna catch
the archive wow sasuka that's
awesome uh uh
how to say a perfect uh
picture book employee how do you say
that like
a sample sample employee
a textbook not picture book i was so
close
i was so close textbook not picture book
i guess i just don't read books well
maybe that's why
back on my dance
can i be a villain again because you
don't want to be a troll
how about how about you gonna be kfb
good boy
how about that why are you gonna be a
villain i don't want any villains you
got to be the
the kfb good boy there you go that's
your new title
swan flyer thank you
[Music]
don't put yourself down thank you though
rezzy does it thank you
skull skull dankeshan and the kimberson
show thank you for the red super chat
looks like i actually enjoyed the cult
whelp viva la chiara
yay
[Music]
thank you mom the camera is in show
no no we are not the cult but i agree on
the viva la quiara part
you're welcome to be a part of it
yeah thank you and i appreciate your
support thank you so much i hope you're
enjoying the stream
looking for the top thank you london
thank you
talking young london
what reasons you were scary the usual
room number one number two anybody going
after calling is so far dead
that's not true number three the ghost
mouse
genocide but that's not true lego
it's just not true
that that concert oh
abby is alive exactly ava is alive
ollie is like well she's a zombie but
she's been a zombie even before she
pursued
cali hmm so he says senpai is alive
they're all alive but maybe not much
longer
than thank you
visiting from time to time you really
grow strong and beautiful
dragoon nights thank
[Music]
in
by the way in light staying at the hotel
is not really an option because
hotels have shitty internet um
probably shittier than my my
apartment that i would be in uh hi ron
says um
just wanted to say thank you your
streams align perfectly with my working
hours and having it on the background
really helped me deal with the anxiety
caused by toxic customers
oh dear i can imagine those tanzanite
tangents are blessed well thank you i'm
glad it helps somehow thank you
cyrus big stun
yes very much avoiding
very much so
let me refresh one last time
oh there are so many again aren't they
there we go
and a good albedo thank you hello kiana
i love your stream today
and although you didn't win any races i
could really see your improvements
throughout the stream thank you so much
for the amazing and
funny entertainment
little video picture is upside down oh
my god
vanguard is
thank you stream from the library
and thank you because you're there for
us too don't worry one bit about rough
times we'll stick with you no matter
what you're out
until what
you're out potential or you're our
attention yo is that my kitten
i thought you told me like i'm not cool
anymore
[Music]
moving is going to be stressful but
we've been before and care if we
survived yep
we will survive thank you soon cowboy
arnold
[Music]
um
thank you thank you i would watch paint
dry if it was you well thank god i'm not
paint dry
oh god the nuts are stuck in my throat
mama almost fell asleep and smacked my
face on the table
stay awake we're almost done come on
[Music]
um
could be considered a business expense
and would be deductible in your taxes
for a year something to keep in mind
it's not entirely lost thank you
i don't see up until now i never really
had to do
such a complicated stuff
i mean i'm gonna probably hire someone
to do my taxes but i don't really
uh know what what what it does
like when like how i understand these
kind of things
but yeah thank you
just some stormtrooper duncan
you said you would label your super jets
in the future you said you would label
them
you didn't though that's why i got it
wrong
do you love 67 dan kashan
i missed the stream due to work but
judging by how kfb trader is reacting i
may have to go back and watch the
archive
um i don't know what you're talking
about
citrus please thank you
and another refresh another one and
another one
and another one it's hiroki dankeshan i
can't be a good boy my entire entire
identity is around being a villain i
could accept anti-hero
though maybe so as long as i get to take
over the world
yo
[Music]
you for the red superchat oh my god that
is um
very very very generous
[Music]
thank you so much for your support oh my
god
uh that finger yes i need my taxes done
in the future
i told my japanese pros that um
since we are kind of a little bit of a
fishy
uh restaurant dad which is funny because
we sell
phoenix but anyway because we're kind of
fishy that um
if you go into the user room if you
don't want to wait until you get out
then you could pay for getting out and
super chats are the way to get out easy
so they're sending red super jets
i mean i don't know should we have a
fish option
are we fishes now no no no no
no no no no no no no no
don't worry don't worry you are not
fishes uh you are chickens
um oh
no logic necessary thank you for the red
super chat as well
wow are you trying to save yourself from
the usual room
well you just got yourself one month
immunity
let me approve of that real quick
thank you for your support thank you
really
i hope you enjoy your time outside i
don't know i don't know why you just
i don't know why you guys don't like the
usual room it's it can be fun
you just have to see the glass as as
half
full not half empty you know
jrc thank you okay that's it guys uh
i'll see you guys um
tomorrow in the riser stream
the last riser stream damn it i said i
would i would grind but i
oh my god will i have time
will i be fine without grounding um
damn it
[Music]
thank you
you can do it you won't be fine oh [\h__\h]
oh damn it do i ah oh yeah bye
cam is nice thank you for the red super
chat that was kitty kitty that was very
uh
the best part of this stream is the
super chat reading the usual room legos
will leave
oh wait is that a wrap
the best part of the stream is the super
jet reading the usual rooms legos will
leave backwards fat feet bleeding chaos
coming down we'll steal our hearts and
send us reeling
all kiana's gonna do is try it out kelly
with some feelings chevy vang
thank you so much yo
yo that's and that's a good rap thank
you you know
you know your way around words don't you
thank you fishko thank you for the
membership
traverse night thank you for your
support and your generous donation
really
the good albino duncan
everyone should get one day immediately
a hell no no
uh not happening
yes guys let's go let's go
oh yeah
tomorrow last final stream of uh
what's wrong judas thank you wonder
what's wrong
what happened
chimipah thank you what's your rapper
name
i need you guys to suggestions for that
thank you lord evac thank you
okay okay bye-bye i'll enjoy what we say
auf wiedersehen thank you guys for
coming today
a little bit of a short stream because i
had some stuff to do
but tomorrow we'll have a long riser
stream probably because i'll probably
have
problems with finishing the bus
i need your help tomorrow my dear rhizo
fans i need you
thank you soon bye bye
thank you oh i'm happy to hear that
thank you thank you judas
that's very sweet
i'll be there oh i need you i need you
good that you're gonna be there
bye bye thank you
enjoy the archive bye-bye
[Music]
m
you
[Music]