thank you
[Music]
foreign
assistant
[Music]
foreign
Christmas
[Music]
s
thank you
[Music]
this is
foreign
[Music]
oh
okay okay okay
welcome welcome welcome mama
[Music]
cure stream yeah
are you guys excited to see what's up in
the new update
we want to see the opening do you guys
want to see the opening it starts it's
starting right now but I think it's the
normal opening
let's see let me capture the game the
game
okay
okay I I closed the opening I I have
been blessed with
um
a pre-release
version
or like I mean it is just a final
version but I've been blessed with uh
the opportunity to stream it a little
bit early
yeah thank you very much can you for
letting me do that also why is this no
not showing on screen come on
come on don't you wanna
show yourself
I know you can do it come on
I played a little bit before the stream
to
um well
uh to get some money
for the for the shop so we can gotcha
yeah the game is shy why won't it show
uh maybe it's not game capture but
window capture
that's fine with me there we go okay
yeah that works
[Music]
there we go let me fix the size
window capture all right I got you
I hope it's been too long it's been a
while when was the last
whole cure stream I don't remember the
last one I did I think I did like two
streams on Hollow cure before
um and as you guys may know why I uh I
had one stream where yes new silhouettes
I had one stream where it didn't go so
well I didn't win so often except maybe
once at the very end and then in the
second stream I kept on winning
I won every match that I did I got to 20
minutes every time yeah so that was
Improvement but before the stream
um while I got a [\h__\h] ton of coins
I was not able to clear
it was one time when I got really close
with Santa
and um I was in the last like 30 seconds
or so but the last rush in the last 30
seconds was oh man it's um yeah once
again killed me uh the thing is that you
see
um
I'm also still missing two characters
but that's okay uh the thing is that
um
there's a there's a new world and I
can't access it until I uh cleared the
game once
but oh yeah well yeah so here we we are
going to have oh wait who is
pleasure
uh if you're like I don't care for my
cats I'm a gamer I can rock it with
anybody then it's a randomizer yeah yeah
but we are gonna get gamers
and we're gonna get Japan gen zero I
have a lot of coins so we can already go
into the gacha and then we can try them
out I have a almost 12 000 coins so we
can do the Godzilla like 12 times
yeah so we start with that we'll start
with that we'll put it all into these
two so that we get as many of them as
possible today and then we hopefully at
some point hopefully clear the the first
stage
uh so then we can also see the second
stage um I already did see some some new
things while I was playing
off screen I did some I did see some new
things uh then you guys will hopefully
also see
Okay so from the beginning
cool will we get oh was it like last
time when I played it I I criticized
that the gotcha is not so like what's
the word
it's kind of I'm anti not anti-climactic
but it doesn't build up the hype I
wonder if they did something about that
is that is that new
[Applause]
I don't know if they changed anything
about that animation but but I'm really
excited about the bookie Senpai yeah
nice oh I wonder what kind of attack she
has this will be interesting okay so a
thousand coins went into that
let's go to gen zero and try one
at least right now we can't get any
copies
oh yeah
that will be a thing at least on the
first map I don't know if Ubuntu is
surfing on the second map I'm guessing
not
um
[Music]
with a pretty bloody weapon uh that I
can see even though it's pixelated
those already feel like too strong
contenders to be honest
yeah
okay we'll do it until I ran out of
coins maybe and then we can obviously
get more if we still don't have all of
them uh in theory I wonder
if I was super lucky and get no copies
if I could
get uh no I guess not and I would have
needed like 14 000 right
oh well okay
go another one from Gamers please uh
strong one stronger strong strong police
I don't know who is strong
we will have to find that out
yeah yeah if you could get no copy at
all we could have gotten pretty far but
let's see let's see so far no copy yet
nice nice nice okay so we have for book
yourself bye foreign
another one from the Gen zero come on
new
news
[Music]
also curious about her attacks probably
a lot of like singing related attacks
like music related attacks
um
I'll do another one over here
because there's five over here to get
yeah okay come on gotta luck
don't betray me
foreign
[Laughter]
HP attack speed by one percent up to 20
and get one tier okay wait tears one
word
what we're tears for
I see them on the top left of that
screen the tier is all right mom what
what are your tears the thing before
redeem how many do I need to redeem them
here's our new seven tiers one free oh
okay okay cool cool cool
well I'll go in again come on come on
oh yeah there's a redeem button no
really
important
three times that's a piece and five
okay I'm unlucky here right now so I'll
go here
I'm super loud oh sh oh really
oh that's weird
I didn't change any settings but I'll
lower myself a little bit then
[Music]
okay
she likes me not surprised
okay Gamers we need two more gamers
no copy please
[Music]
almost completed the gamers yeah
yeah yeah music bye oh I wonder she must
have like maybe tarot card related
attack one at least
that would be cool
a tarot card related attack who knows
who knows who knows I'm really just
guessing right now I guess you guys
don't have any idea at all either right
there was no not not much information
besides like a little trailer I guess
oh I saw a specialist he said ah her
base attack is there oh perfect perfect
wonderful
I'm gonna put one more in here
come on come on come on come on come on
come on okay okay okay
stay safe
[Laughter]
oh probably there must be a robot
related attack you know finally her
button in her back of her neck might get
some actual use who knows
and I got three more pulls for now but
I'm close to have some having some more
okay I'll go in one more now we're
getting into scary copy uh to territory
but
um
it will be danger but I have tears yeah
but I need seven right
ah oh you can actually choose who you
want if you have seven tiers
very nice pretty system
actually very very generous so
that is kind of dumb
okay I'm going in guys
yes
yes the game is redeeming Itself by not
giving me copies anymore thank you thank
you
okay so just missing soda said bye not
bad not bad not bad
oh very lucky Elite pulls only yeah
hello
I need two more I'll I'll have a bad
feeling but let's do it
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
we're done with the gamers I did not
have a single coffee in here what the
[\h__\h]
oh
yeah
that's that's absolutely amazing wait if
we're lucky we can't get all of them
uh okay even if we don't that's fine we
have to try them all out we'll get a
[\h__\h] ton of coins anyway
okay here we go here we go let's go here
we go so that's Senpai last but not
least
come on
[Music]
it's fine it's fine it's fine it's fine
that was to be expected
um but I do have like a little bit of
money so I kind of want to get oh is
this new a hardcore
Oh Rapunzel perch oh
these are new I think wait all of these
four are new I think
enhancement rate up increases the chance
of success during enhancements by three
percent per level but so far I I don't
quite understand that one because like
enhancement
so far I never had like a a failure
always 100 but I guess if you maybe if
you do endless
challenge
maybe then there's um
and was past max level oh I never got
that far
oh defense app increase the defense
reducing damage taking my three percent
per level oh
what's that's good
and grg rank off turn off bonuses gained
from G ranks what what are G ranks
T-Rex
yeah actual defense
um hardcore ultimate Challenge HP is set
to one gain massive bonus scored and
longer you survive in Endless mode
[Music]
that's a
h ah no gotcha chips ah I see I see okay
and the rest is the same I think
wait grants the use of rewall when
leveling up
one per level
what
gotsie
that's not new oh I completely ignored
that one so far okay well
in order to help me to clear the first
stage what should we get I got some
stuff in HP attack
making an attack or
[Music]
um
what do you guys think
so I should uh
you have hyper chat on
attack and it's a true exp XP always
good which one was the XP
hey here this one the man of XP gained
by four percent per level
oh the pickup actually I realized it's
actually pretty useful to
um
wait wait it's four first 100 never mind
never mind I already spent a lot on that
okay oh 1 800 is there anything I can
get maybe pick up range you know what
that's it's not that unuseful
oh I can buy well another one nice okay
okay okay now we go into the game
look at
that oh I is part of Gamers just kidding
um a fox tail swipes tail in front at
the close range oh that feels like it
might be like a similar type of attack
to Cali's side
we have the turret cards yeah wait wait
let me finish this one actually a
football store I'm as a special someone
many katanas flurring around for five
seconds during this time bubble dot
fubuki Dodge is all attacks
oh interesting special so we have tarot
cards for a card that quickly returns
back
um so that's not just one like left or
right direction right that it would be
written there I think oh for the people
that just came in this is just a
randomizer
and not a secret character almost fun
song
and then we have the Hato Towers summon
Hatha towers for six seconds and
continuously punches forward well so
as a companion a limited time companion
during this time Mio takes 30 less
damage
okay interesting I want to see that Hato
Towers in action
and we have onigiri from onigiri had an
arc Ike an arc what an arc
welcome for six seconds okay it was
invincible and increases speed by 50
non-boss targets touched will be eaten
ah an egg like a curve ah okay
number's targets touched will be eaten
healing five percent HP
oh oh it doesn't count for bosses
interesting
they will be eaten
just just swallowed
wow okay
and then we have Oreos
ponds towards the front in a random cone
random
okay and uh
really ending making time create waves
of giant exploding UVS targets defeated
get their UB stick
and here we have oh Sakura go hey
that creates a verse of Sucker oh that
sounds beautiful oh but then the
specialist demon Lord's domain create a
Zone around Mikko for eight seconds
summoning hot flames that burn
everything Targets in this Zone take 50
more damage wow double damage
wow okay
um we have the ax swing you know this ax
looks familiar swing of bloody ax and an
arc in front uh-huh and then oh Tetris
Tetris blocks seven books some of the
rainbow falling blocks that deal 300
damage each for five seconds oh I wonder
how many I'm gonna fall down flattening
targets making them unable to move for
five seconds wow wow wow cool
cool
and we have this one uh shoots a few
times in aims direction oh wait this one
doesn't have a name
we got some that's something they forgot
to add here can you write it down write
it down I'm like a better tester yeah
I'm the beta tester
there's no name the No Name gun
uh then High spec mode oh release a
discharge that deals 300 damage wow for
eight seconds rubical gains 100 attack
Speed pickup radius and 50 crit and
haste damn those are quite the the crits
yeah I guess
yes almonds and in terms of shooting but
she can actually aim
what says that about you huh
I only have as example Diva songs and
the flying musical notes in front
okay
in front of where she's facing right
full concert Chinese circle of brilliant
stage lights ah damaging all Targets
anyway for six seconds okay yeah I knew
I knew it would be very music or idle
focused that's nice okay so who do we go
for first I don't know if Chad can help
me with that decision you guys are just
gonna spam a million different names
right who do we try first who do we want
to see first
random yeah but random chances I get one
of those as well unfortunately I don't I
wanna I wanna
um
go with the new one so
okay I'll stop at football
wish me luck
um I I really want to finish a first
stage ASAP so I might need your help
with the I guess I know you know guys
never played this character but at least
maybe some combinations for the for the
weapons you can help me out with because
the whole office gives you also more
coins
then the grassy Plains
yeah
yeah I need those coins
they look so fluffy also I don't think
this wasn't a normal game I don't
remember if it was but here if you
destroy those statues
um then there's like food coming out of
the statue was that originally in the
game
because then I never noticed
ah okay well that came was out of
nowhere that's new oh so then you can
actually like why why did I get to
Rainbow one immediately that way you can
actually for once like aim if you and
and know that food will come out of it
if you find one if you're so lucky to
find one also this is new when I was
playing off-screen
this is new
um I was playing off screen I I got I I
oh no maybe it's not new in the game but
it's new for me
oh maybe it is new in general okay
increased regular fan spawns and fans
become five percent strong I'll gain one
whole no coin for every five targets
defeated uh since taking this item oh
this is this helps you get more coins I
guess
um
um I think however I want to go for
something else uh although we do need
but it there's more spawns we don't need
that right now we need to focus on other
things I'll go for idle song
here's the food yummy
a careful bookie step by show me what
you got oh already an anvil
so
Sasuke kind of buff that increases speed
by 20
on the next hit take and consumed above
to dodge the attack and gain 100 speed
and 100 Dodge for once one second okay
oh there's more written here the buff
returns after 12 seconds
aha so that's one of her things and then
foxtail increased damage by 20 okay
let's try it out
and then I will
and I'll upgrade idle song for now
I have not really use idle song much yet
is that one new because it feels new I
don't remember seeing that in the
original game
oh a lot of skeletons coming already
oh he missed oh wow what did you see
that for a second that was really fast
that's the that's Neil okay the island
song is new good good cool then maybe it
was a good choice so we see that in
action as well
okay the 10 chance the Dodge attacks
nice when dodging there is a 40 chance
to create a noise burst feeling 100
damage ooh always the limiter is not
only for Sana I was playing sana a lot
off screen and then
um I thought the limiter was just for
her I I guess not obviously it's a
defense item okay cool cool cool
um
they were either song is old what really
I'll go for
um
[Music]
okay sorry the chickens I couldn't kill
them in time
I'll keep them alive for a little bit
longer you're welcome kfb
I
yeah she left her limiter
it was very useful when I was playing
off-screen thank you should we get exp
um I think I want to get exp getting exp
early on I think is a good choice
yeah
yeah yeah
I've been making a lot of independent
decisions off screen guys without you
what
what is
a lot of independent decisions off
screen box ing another one increase
speed by 10 while moving all attack
damages
oh this increased by 10 for each 10
bonus speed currently speed phobia
currently has up to 100 wait what what
what wait what what increased speed by
10 while moving all attack damage is
increased by 10 a half for each 10 bonus
speed the book he currently has up two
what okay no matter how many times I
read it it's confusing but it should
make it makes it makes her faster okay
okay that's good so she's a speed Fox
oh oh look I'm sorry
wait there's a lot of shrimps coming for
me
um
uh I thought from Fox oh there we go oh
well well now I'll go for
I think I'll go for study glasses this
time
oh yeah okay
oh wait my special is ready mommy
should I should have activated already
here we go
whoa
it's cool cool cool
okay wow
yeah you should use that when there's a
lot of enemies on the screen
ah
oh I might want a new attack to help me
out a little bit and I love the lava
bucket so
in combination with whatever it was that
might go boom
that's my fave
keeps everyone away from me
Swoosh
oh my tail will become huge let's go oh
oh oh we're we're getting the sunglasses
so often
[Music]
yes accent bucket so if I see the ax
I'll take the ax
okay but yeah we'll go for the foxtail
[Music]
well that will make us um faster
uh in terms of forgot the awakened One
faster
[Music]
Dodge attack speed by 25. oh God
are you ready
one of the reasons why I wanna see the
new stages because I'm guessing it comes
with a new soundtrack so
even though this one is still sick
especially after hearing it for the
first time in a long time
no matter how often I listen to it oh my
God we're getting study glasses again
[Laughter]
still suspect yeah
so far so far and me we're having a good
time
the mask
oh it was damaged by a favorite Ace
button oh
wait take 40 more damage no but I guess
since she Dodges a lot it's it's not a
bad combination in theory but it seems
dangerous for myself
I'll take the study classes maybe maybe
at some point
whoa the speed this
week go away guys thank you
speed
okay
maybe at some point we'll get the mask
again and then maybe I'll take it oh
[\h__\h] was my special already when
okay let me try this can we get them can
we get them
and we tried
which right
um
I will improve my bucket
ah with the I don't know I wonder what
combinations we can make
[Music]
I want I still want to combine the lava
oh wait no it's hopped out oh my God
wait what oh it's a Japanese
okay okay okay okay
no
okay
for some reason I switched to Japanese
keyboard that's really bad when that
happens
I survived don't worry
I stood my ground for long enough whoa
whoa
thank you that was good that was huskata
oh please oh please
yeah
the stone is too strong
[Music]
oh kill the taco Dutchess
kill them
Kill Them All
oh come on I need more damage I need you
know dodging and all that is good but I
need damage too
come on stop stop cornering me
cornering me
oh there we go oh
free it's Ripple let's go
nice okay it improves everything already
half so I'm happy with that thank you
um
[Music]
foxtail awakened okay
so coming
oh look at all those exp on the ground
yummy
[Music]
picky man got buffed oh is that so
I didn't realize a change in it
okay should we go for the whole bump
what a glow stick I like the glow sticks
too but I want to have a combination
between glow stick and idle song would
be
okay
if that's even possible are any weapons
uh like um combinable
um
come on
hey here's my desired football standby
collab that I wanted
finally that's the one I was hoping for
even though you know we also need Fox
King I guess but
[Music]
um
song Wonderful
and
bring me okay well we'll hopefully get
the ASA Coho
again
sometime holy [\h__\h] she goes so fast
I'm I'm on purpose on purpose not using
my special attack right now
I'm waiting for it to get a little bit
more busy here
the shrimps are coming so it's getting
busy
foreign
I love spider cooking
wow
um I feel like you know previously the
characters they were already in the game
were kind of like focused on you know
where some some were focused on being a
tank you know healing themselves and all
that
um
oh hello
and then there were some that were more
like damage dealers but I like I don't
think this has been there before but I'm
just gonna use it now
but I feel like
um a character that's focused on dodging
is new and I like it
yeah dodging and speed
uh
okay what do we want to improve we
already have the fox say on weekends so
we can ignore that one oh gouda was that
too really
I didn't quite
um see her like that but that might be
true
oh
I'll go for buckets
yeah yes um someone just mentioned
quinoa in the chat
and
I did ask wow
I did ask about you know whether or not
in this update there are some
improvements on kiwawa and I was told
yes
but today I want to focus on the new
characters so I'm not sure if we get to
check it out but
eventually but Julie this won't be the
last time I play hold up here
um
[Music]
thank you
Little Mix already nice nice
looking good so far
showdown of football and football Senpai
will be marvelous
it will go into the history books it
will be recorded as the most tense fight
ever to happen before oh yeah
investigators are around now cute
investigators yeah
yeah they're so cute it hurts me to hurt
them
um
[Music]
because last time I ignored that one
I'll give it a chance now
okay
[Music]
oh wait what my health my health oh my
God
hey how did that happen uh increase size
of pool stick or laundry detergent
now that was was there one big hit or
what
I'll survived don't worry although so
far I have like no methods of healing
myself
oh let me find food or statue to break
down
oh
[Applause]
a coin I'll take the coin oh wait I'm
healing back up okay
mmm
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
don't look at the Chucky lava oh oh big
boy is coming oh live he's coming
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh thank God I'm so fast but are
the enemies faster too or am I imagining
things
uh
I will go for
you
[Music]
yeah loves burgers
oh no no those I hate them so much they
killed me uh several times the army of
oh no oh no oh no oh no oh no oh no oh
no
[Music]
yeah
I'm outside
oh that was a close one
oh there we go food food food food
please thank you
[Applause]
I hate Shield Deadbeats
oh
I need healing skills yeah should I
increase my maximum speed by 10 percent
no
time between attacks yeah we want idle
song to go up oh oh wait oh
ah
okay that's good that's good that's good
that's good that's good that's good
that's good any feeling any feeling any
feeling any healing
I need healing I need healing I really
need healing oh my God the [\h__\h]
chickens
um
[Music]
free even more EXP
o stick
my tail is going
360 now so that's wonderful
range increased
okay I'm gonna go
to look actively for food now
[\h__\h] I never get like HP Help
[Music]
food oh oh I got healing I got
you scared
a little bit at least
and
[Music]
um
we don't need even more movement speed
that's for sure
I am going for this kind of cooking
games
[Music]
I think I got it I think I got it wow
oh
ah see here is the healing item should
we got that one
[Music]
yeah cause like even though she Dodges
and that's nice and all but when she
doesn't Dodge then she's pretty um
okay I know how to deal with it
I know how to deal with her
oh my God
stay cool stay cool
stay on there for Godzilla and you're
safe under the shadow of the big fluffy
bugzilla
foreign
Beyond
oh okay it's getting really busy again
I
so now we have two things Max right
uh but
those are not the ones I want to combine
I guess
we can try does it work
the rats the rats are out who let the
rats out
they are very weak they don't have much
HP so you can take them down fast but
there's so many of them
so many of them you can
you can squish them easily holy sh oh
there we go
oh my God
[Music]
that's a tough choice that's a tough
choice
squeak
squishy squeaks
thanks guys for guiding me to uh success
so much xp they give so much XP
everywhere
I don't know how to get all of it
by zooming
um okay
[Music]
if I have those choices I want to go
with asakoku a nurse's horn
oh no on the clocks ah they also killed
me sometimes
not now but when they get more and more
so I'll keep my I'll keep my special for
a little while longer when it looks
really bad
um not now
soon I think
oh
yes
okay
um that's this one you guys might have
to help me
um
[Music]
yeah bandage is new right just bandage
I tried it off screen increases Max HP
by 10 after being hit heal 10 HP every
three seconds until you guys say 401
it would be another healing skill until
80 of the damage settings were covered
it works quite well in my experience but
I also like the limiter because it it
helps too but we need to survive in any
case we need to survive
oh God okay not the best uh
not the best chances right oh there we
go healing healing is there
[Music]
okay okay okay oh oh look at those
dances yeah but I'm gonna use it now
or maybe I wasted it did I waste it
oh big big clock Tick Tock your time is
up is what it's saying to me I want to
get to the boxer
[Music]
I'll get there I'll get there I'll get
there I'll get there eventually oh God
oh God oh God oh God oh God
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
not the one I originally wanted but uh
it works
and leave cooking collaboration spider
cooking
red
and
yeah now we have to work on the second
second collaboration which I guess will
be glow stick and
hmm
maybe idle song
oh it's dead yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
I wanted to go for me Comet originally
[Music]
foreign
good choices uh good choices I
in order to survive
I am doing this
was a lot of food thankfully
no it's not it's nice nice nice
um am I better in this game on screen on
stream
[Laughter]
and it might be like that if we clear it
this time on the first try before sample
and it might be true
if you say
you better may have made the right
decision
oh it's getting busy again but my
special is close
it's coming close
oh God oh God
they're cornering me again okay okay
yes
[Music]
I survived that part but it's not over
uh
I often die around here I think oh
then because I'm so scared of dying I go
for the just bandage again
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] run run
foreign
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
no
look at the [\h__\h] fans
I'm sorry
it is
ah
I'm sorry I didn't see the fence
there was like something's there but
like what it was pretty long
ah okay
that was all however a good try with the
book sent by the first try you guys want
to go for a different one so we get as
many as possible at least once
fence could please uh these I needed
more defense
oh
my Sonics okay okay tarot cards and hot
dog Towers let's see if we
can get for stage one please please
okay so tired can't they go any
direction
I really liked football games attack
because I don't have to worry about the
direction too much the main attack
because it covers quite a lot but yeah
this is a
I just gotta get good you know
[Music]
I would like a level up now please
there we go okay increase damage by 20
percent I'll do it
let's get those tarot cards awakened
mm-hmm
Osa your Senpai python
music
[Music]
oh love a bucket mama
every 40 seconds here one percent for
each Target within 100 pixels oh
what
up to 10 percent
what oh
I feel like even though it's just one
percent but that will go higher oh my
special is ready let's look at it
it stays right next to me it doesn't
just walk around okay
what oh 10 chance to create an old man
dealing 20 damage to targets if a woman
defeats a Target the special meter feels
like it's sick that's sick
so yeah
strong
a two terakats he has placed in the same
direction oh yeah roughly oh
and I saw the omen
I saw the omen was it a good or bad omen
a good one for me
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] okay I need some like different
attacks to help me out soon
I'll give me that food please
EXP
o
oh hello
nice to see you here again hope my
attacks reach you
[Music]
oh
wait my special is ready
[Laughter]
damn
one attack
oh no
no no
haircuts okay oh wow this one's new
cheerful love oh the closer Target is
within 150 pixels the more damage I
receive up to 50 oh
wow so a lot of her attacks are like
range focused
he wants them to get close to you for
cuts broader and further increased
damage by 40
but I do want the I do want the lava
bucket I'm sorry guys I need another
attack
laughs
there's a lot of them coming now oh
I'll get there I'll get there oh
look at there eventually
remember it's on the left side
I'm too scared to go for all those
enemies
ah
push back push harder
oh there we go
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
with this whatever
that evil fence look at that evil fence
uh-huh
tacos please now please be kind thank
you
[Music]
special looks great it does
very very nice animation
[Music]
do you want to get another attack guys
uh
yeah
yes yes yes
we need the help
look at all those muscular
hot hotels
intimidating
you said that would be a great card
dealer if she can handle those cards
that well
I'm keeping my special until we're in a
situation that calls for it
that doesn't quite look like it yet
oh [\h__\h] oh oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I
walked oh
oh wait study glasses cover cards
awakened
I think a tiger is a 40 percent chance
that the target may lose 20 attack speed
uh or take 20 more damage nice
and boys love and now we need to get out
of here oh
[Music]
man okay
nice
that one's really fun
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah so I still feel like I'm really not
doing enough damage like
oh [\h__\h] it's my my aiming as well though
sucks
suck at aiming I don't even notice
but I also need a glow stick maybe
should I get the glow stick
don't you
okay
oh wait I'm ready
please
not upwards okay that's fine oh
by the way yesterday
I wasn't streaming because my mommy
came for a visit
that was nice oh
we did a lot of things in my apartment
we got a lot of [\h__\h] done
thankfully
for one I recently noticed that my
washing machine was like
um
kind of
not doing such a good job because every
time
[Music]
uh every time that I watched something
the moment I opened it the whatever I
washed in it kind of like the clothes
didn't smell very good it smelled like I
let it inside uh as as in in wet form
for like way too long even though that's
not the case
um yeah that was that's actually only
recently like since a week ago or two
weeks ago and I was wondering what
happened with the
with the
washing machine what I did wrong
[Music]
we have it on max
oh God
so my mom basically just looked inside
the one machines she opened up like a
tiny opening where
um
stuff like
stuff that gets stuck would go and it
was one tiny bobby pin stuck
in there and that was the reason
apparently why it was yeah the filter
why it was like not properly letting the
water go
hmm a stupid bobby pin
so cyclop was a difficult nicenet
[Music]
yeah and then I tried washing some
clothes again it was perfectly normal it
was back to normal
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] where am I shooting
oh God
oh
maybe not the best timing for that
um
yeah this is why I'm bad at characters
that have like an an aimed weapon
all right maybe some
spider cooking
or improve the tarot cards
[Music]
okay we'll improve this one oh [\h__\h] I'm
gonna die I'm gonna die I'm gonna die
[Music]
I wanna die
pick it up you want to survive get that
coin get a coin though get the gotcha
money
priorities
okay I'm gonna look for food
[\h__\h]
food oh thank you
bless Yago
that is not the only way you can
encounter Yahoo now in this game
as I've seen for the Stream
maybe we'll be blessed by
the same opportunity on stream as well
all healing is doubled oh man
I don't know
yeah I'm saving the old because I have a
feeling something bad is coming again
soon we're at eight minutes
oh big boys coming
and Anvil uh uh oh God the damage
I need like more healing
handle on the left side remember
[Music]
I'm trying to go for the spaces
no
oh God yeah I'm dying I'm dying I'm dead
okay
[Music]
stay alive stay alive okay now we need
we need to go like up left or so
Michael X I was waiting for you
okay
oh my God okay we're going uh in that
direction hopefully oh chicken's not now
I know you want a hug from Mommy
but now it's not the time
[\h__\h]
oh God
[\h__\h] I swear to God
leave mommy alone right now okay be nice
oh God
I have a bad feeling with me or
something I like her skills but maybe
not my my style
character oh finally we have arrived
um
I'm gonna go for even one of these I
think
I need to get more exp so I can get
stronger fast
[Music]
duh
oh
we can Max poison
at least something
to hold on to
[Music]
look at someone's coming you know what I
actually feel kind of relieved about
that oh [\h__\h] but um okay I guess we're
going above her
oh
okay aim down aim down and down
let's see let's see how fast we can get
her down I could use had the towers but
he only goes sideways and that's kind of
I mean he might reach anyway but
uh
I I'll keep it
[Music]
I think he'll reach we don't need him
it's for fun oh God
okay I'm using him now though
the fruit is mess oh should we get
headphones I think I want the headphones
hahaha
oh
[Music]
tough choice for oh
trips oh lots of healing stuff like
helping me out with food and healing and
and negating
oh
much appreciate it
[Music]
okay oh the rats are coming again
Mr squeaks please please please I don't
mean yourself but it's cute I know you
two will get along well surely but now's
not the time
oh oh oh oh I need to get down
um
go Shield everybody maybe more bandage
or or headphones 25 chance
a little free
two
yeah you must go
God squeaks is driving me away from
where I actually want to go
no don't be strong don't be so scared oh
[\h__\h] an army of Mr squeaks there we go
now I'm
um why am I in control
oh
up
okay I will improve the cycle Lux I
think
okay okay it's getting it's going better
now we're out out of a kind of critical
phase
now we just need to get our
collaborations going and then we're good
hopefully
I don't get don't get your hopes up
everybody
close Six yeah
we're gonna get our beloved combination
hopefully soon
oh the clocks are here those the ones
that killed me before no it was a fence
it was a fence that killed me
cycle x max
no I'm not ready
foreign
I'm not mentally ready for this
oh
by the way if you guys are waiting to
play the update it's coming out on the
9th of September which is uh
knowing how many days I can't look at
the date right now
but wait now I can look uh in today's
the sixth so very soon in three days
yeah then you can play it for free
I know that this might be good too but
since we're already like working on this
continue working on it
holding back on the alt
oh don't get stunned
oh oh God offense oh God my my worst
enemy
oh big clock oh
shall we use I don't need it we don't
need it for this kind of enemy we don't
need it what do we
okay I'm using it
survived
not only the common ammo but an idol
song okay and
I saw this
um
two
oh
um
[Music]
there's someone golden Anvil thank you
for coming to the rescue now we're gonna
combine these right I could also combine
the cyclics those boys love
and
accent book two and three huh
wait how do I there you go
wanna see that one okay
yeah I really got that one it's nice to
say it again Corporation of voice love
book encyclics endless boys love how
Shameless is on you
there's a whirlwind going around me
surrounding me holy [\h__\h]
oh there's so much food around here
blessed can't be is sponsoring this
stream tonight
and
doshio
[Music]
stream dying really
no
what
she's fine
[Music]
oh no oh no not them oh no
it's okay it's okay as long as long as I
as long as I
[\h__\h] offense
ah
I want to go for headphones or bandage
but
too early yeah
it's fine it's fun it's fine it helped
us a little bit
wow what was that damage oh oh no no
no oh my God okay that was that was such
a close call I really [\h__\h] up there oh
oh
what's ready again
oh oh
you're still not dead
[Music]
okay we're going down once again because
I think there's a lot of being speed
down there
somewhere there
yeah yeah
upwards come on oh
we can make it make it because we can
make it
okay okay
I'll come back
don't get too far
okay I think one one is dead um but not
all of my eye and I still want that [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
oh God what am I doing
oh
ah The Horde is finally
dead
The Horde has finally been defeated
oh thank God
uh if we get that choice then once again
I'll go for the nurses one because I'm
I'm apparently really bad um
it's not
she had like two HP left
receive okay
I need all the food I can get
the heels are so powerful oh
maybe I should increase speed
increase speed and travel with wait does
it it means the speed of my character
right
to me this is oh I guess oh wait I can
go for this one yeah me Mr slope
through that
so much xp here thank God
wait is there still a box left somewhere
or did I get everything
I'm not sure
uh go even faster or
all right
free okay
oh sheesh
they cut style cut style
[\h__\h] there's so much going on on the
screen
I think the survival this is gonna get
tough
gonna get real tough
no I'm trying to aim downwards but it's
really hard
okay oh love he coming
my special is ready again
um
now now or never
push back push back push back push back
push back push back
wait there's a there's an animal
somewhere there's an animal I see it's
very much on the left
oh that's a problem I'm not the dogs not
the dogs
oh dear oh dear oh dear
oh dear oh dear the bro this this is
this is where I died with Sana
the satellites were the end of me
maybe speed I think we need speed now
but also spider cooking
I need both
damage yeah
okay
oh there it is there it is there it is I
found it I found it
uh
glow stick I would uh let me um spider
cooking
okay
oh mama
thanks please please please please I
think we got enough healing going on now
at least
it's insane
ounce of enemies oh
[Music]
the food I can't reach it
just need to survive I just need to
survive I just need to survive too close
I can't I can't
come on just one more minute
oh this this area is actually pretty
empty Hallelujah but now oh I'll just
keep on running just keep on running
wait there's so many animals down there
really for real zones okay I'm going
down
don't stand still yup yup yup yup yup
yup yup
no exp around here Eva but that's fine
let me go to the handles oh look at this
little area
[Music]
look how look how much HP they have holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
whatever
oh trouble right at the end it's Ripple
oh
okay
whatever whatever wait on it I thought
it was I thought it was over at 20 oh no
that's one the the boss comes oh wait oh
[\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] um
[Music]
afraid oh God
please be kind to me I play more FPS
games I swear I swear
I'll improve my aim oh oh I won't be
such a hard have you wait anymore I'll
practice
be nice
well we can be in OverWatch duo or
whatever game paladins paladins is fine
I love paladins little paladins famous
announcer Amelia Watson
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm
so sorry
okay we're safe though we're safe this
this can't this this is fine it's fine
this is fine this is fine this is fine
this is fine
it's hard for me to even get close to
her because I need to get away from her
struggle is she getting down myself she
just has a lot of HP right
please
let me show everyone
new level that you stage
at least I'm always aiming upwards for
this one I can do it I can do it I can
do it oh [\h__\h] I got some damage here
but don't worry I got a lot of healing
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you for having mercy on me
first try with me yeah you're gonna give
me big ups for that come on come on it
was was not an easy one for someone like
me oh
oh that was oh it's just two of the new
characters
but that should mean now yes new stage
unlocked Hallelujah we did it but we
also got a little bit of gacha money so
I can't don't wanna go into the
character gotcha
um we're just missing Sona Senpai so
oh I stopped moving and why
yeah new stage we're gonna check it out
immediately I wonder if it's more
difficult because it does say there are
more coins but we have to look at it
okay so let's say bye I can give you
free tries
[Music]
I got them all them all I got them all
them all that was easy
[Laughter]
now I have them all gotta catch them all
gotta catch them all I got them in my
pocket I'll put them in a special
Pokeball the tears for the people who
don't know yet let's hear um the the
rainbow tears there if you have seven
you can choose who you want so if you
had too many dupes it will give you a
choice to choose yourself yeah now
actually I can fill up my consoles
because I don't have all of them yet
sure
sure I think I'm missing fauna and Mommy
piggy system yeah
ah come on
okay
that's fine we're focusing on other
characters today anyway so
are you guys ready for the new stage
and
um well I guess we'll just go
um you know in that order
perhaps
Moga Moga time
so to repeat uh she froze in onigiri at
an arc okay that already helps me quite
a bit
and Arc is okay
um
for six seconds
invincible and increases speed by 50
non-bones targets will touch will be
eaten okay
we won't do it enough Hollow office
where we get more coins on your music
music
[Applause]
it's literally one of my favorite whole
songs gonna go under the table no that
blocks oh [\h__\h] that's up
oh I see I see I see this is quite the
challenge this is definitely more
difficult oh
yeah
more game audio it's too low okay okay
there you go
[Music]
should we go for sensitive voice
increase Crate by five percent crits
have 10 chance to charm targets ooh with
120 pixels for four seconds where they
can be eaten two
um
that's very
yeah everyone
ah it's so loud now [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
I love this song
increase damage let's see how long we
can survive I feel like 20 minutes and
this will be tough oh dear there's like
barely any space to go but they can just
walk through the table I can't was this
oh
I saw this place hi
[Music]
hi I love it that's easy
increase food traps oh when eating food
gained 40
attack 50 speed and five percent crate
for eight seconds
[Music]
oh that one was red why
foreign
[Music]
oh God
super strong on what's going on
probably goes onigiri's
keep them coming keep on coming
this is difficult the stage is not so
big and there's a lot of obstacles
I'll retry
oh look ah
I have some stuff going on on the TV
I guess there's a little bit of a
sightseeing area
[Music]
oh nice okay
I think if we want to survive we
definitely need more weapons but I don't
know if I should go right at it I'll go
right at it whatever we have to try
different tactics
Tony
come on
everybody shall we dance
[Music]
let's bro
you know what I'll go for the bucket
I respect everyone who survives this on
first try
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] that's a lot coming
good timing
kiwawa TV was on the TV s on the TV
[Music]
there's a six percent chance to drop
other types of food that heal other
types of food let's here for one for you
five or 20 hp oh
dang
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I thought I was still
eating
it ended right there that's a little bit
dangerous
oh it explodes Sonia
if you're in the middle of oh God
oh in the middle of eating in in the
middle of like a lot of enemies
it gets dangerous when it ends
[Music]
oh
cookies
ice cream oh I'm frozen oh that's what
you mean
I didn't realize
okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I'm gonna die
increased food drops I'm getting more
food
perfect
a pizza salami
[Music]
pepperoni pizza
I need to get the rainbow but there's
not that much XP on the map anyway I
think
[Music]
oh come on come on
whoa that was a roasted chicken
yeah
[Music]
I'm surviving way London before let's
eat some let's have a piece oh okay that
counts as a boss enemy so we can't eat
that one oh
[Music]
oh God
why did I go here oh I can go over here
you know I mean I still need to get to
know the new map as well there's the oh
oh god oh okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay wait that's okay I corned
myself
oh
yummy
ski
come on
a whole Army of them
shall we retry one more time
bye and then we we would change the map
or we change the character
because this map is this map is good for
good players to challenge themselves but
and if you want more coins
[Music]
but we want the feeling of success at
some point don't we
[Music]
here too that you can destroy
oh I didn't go for the one you wanted
guys
sorry
um
I'll take the ax oh yes oh yes oh yes
oh yes
these are so adorable
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay save distance again
you have to keep our hunger under
control
all right should we start dropping the
food
[Music]
oh yeah we uh speaking of food
me and my mom made the Tongan to
actually hit a katsu yesterday
's like uh if you don't know it's kind
of the same thing here because it's just
like an undercategory
of a tonkatsu
es like for filet
and uh it's like a
pork pork cutlet or fillet and oh [\h__\h]
what did I think that was by accident
and it's like you know in panko breading
oh [\h__\h] that doesn't that do damage on
that one I forgot
and you eat it with some rice and some
chocolate and the tall cups of sauce
typical
sauce
come on
can we survive five minutes at least
[Music]
yeah it was quite
quite stressful for my mom even because
the oil got so hot and it was ah
it was spilling everywhere the oil
I stopped moving again this is really
hard it's not just me being bad
this is I mean that may play a little
bit of a part but it's actually
difficult
[Music]
I think I will go back to the normal map
so we can see more of the character's
potential
oh
yeah yeah it's definitely more difficult
[Music]
yeah you have to really get strong
really fast otherwise you won't survive
for long
first stage is a tutorial stage
[Laughter]
[Music]
on a normal grassy plane so we can see a
bit more from her you know gotta do her
some justice
upgrading hotel okay
I can't stand maybe that's that's what
they expect you to have like already a
lot of upgrades at that point
since I don't have many points I'll go
actually 14 fans to know
sounds interesting
and or maybe more more food jobs
five I only have 500 points
or attack spin pickup range
[Music]
okay let's get some haste
girl since
the upgrades down
stronger
oopsie
so let's play One More Time
foreign
let's see what she got
this is not a waste of food
we're feeding the grass with rice
so that we will have even more rice Let
There Be rice
[Music]
there we go
fertilize the kusai yes
Let There Be rice
okay
food drops why not
we'll get okay as strong as possible
stay with my mom as we went to Ikea Ikea
it's been a while since the last time I
went to Ikea but there were some things
I needed urgently no yeah yeah pretty
urgently
it was nice
love again
I didn't get any
sadly
I wish I did
but the plan was to eat tonkatsu later
so
oh
chicken however
um my my aunt Phil was really [\h__\h]
shocking
I don't know how much I spend at IKEA
Wanna Know
it's it's pretty shocking
um
no
I spent 2 000 Euro which is like two
thousand US dollars
well a lot of it came from uh
the um
what's the word montage
uh
I beg your pardon yeah
I mean I had a similar reaction I didn't
think it was gonna be that much but
yeah assembling because I I ordered it
with some assembling
well it's so
silence skills
strong
broke yellow yeah it dropped some food
[Music]
okay let's fight this Beast of a shrimp
the meter is
oh yeah maybe also for all the food
traps right because it takes up the
bootstraps too
sensitive balloons increase crit by five
percent crits have a 10 chance to charm
targets with infinity okay yeah yeah
that's good to me
[Music]
next time I see a limiter I'll take it
let's go
oh [\h__\h] uh I got the uh I didn't see
sorry couldn't wait too fast
[Applause]
[Music]
highest quality of materials oh
I think it's just normal Ikea quality
but yeah it was some stuff that I really
desperately needed so there was no way
around it yeah
but yeah I ordered it with delivery and
because I forgot the word again they
build it up for me
ah
um
[Music]
yes people forgetting it
keep on thinking of the word
Construction
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
okay
a 12 hour marathon
on Sunday leading up to the anniversary
it will end
supposedly around midnight my time so
that's when I would have reached
let's just say I would have reached a
two-year anniversary
I think it's good to spread it out a
little bit more so we're not doing it
all in two days
so I chose to go like kind of one day
early
was it bus Charmed oh I don't know
in this case I will yeah actually
rail this this is a rare occasion but
I'll go for the attack increase because
the other ones didn't really quite like
those choices
oh
[Music]
wait I can eat
foreign
yeah and my plan was to play a little
bit of total cure during my 12 hour
12 hour marathon as well since I'm not
sure how much I I can show
today of everything but by next time it
will all been already be released so you
guys can obviously already look at
everything with your own eyes by that
time
oh
whoa
[Music]
yeah that's new
[Laughter]
and then he just explodes there's so
many coins I wanted to show you the the
golden jungle
oh unfittingly enough we get the Yago
body pillow
oh I saw it down there don't worry I saw
it that's on
[Music]
more Charming
oh that one was when they turned purple
they're Charmed huh
maybe Jenny was still terrifying no
don't ever damage
I think
yeah he's very random
no no it's not about the statues no no
very very random
golden yellow
see how that's actually uh a reference
so really really really really really
old collaboration that we did where we
gave out golden jungles as uh Awards
right it was a whole of myth
collaboration
made some golden juggles if I remember
correctly the good old times
foreign
again
I think it's the first collaboration
yeah every
Africa golden yellow you get a golden
yellow
you want to go for one
as if we don't already have enough food
this will be all about food it's a
mukbang
oh look at the roasted chicken
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
it's going pretty well so far oh [\h__\h] I
feel very strong right now
even though my attacks are not
um that far yet
you know I guess it's all the food
because they they can't get me down I'm
like Invincible I feel like we might
clear this one
oh [\h__\h] I gotta stop a tree
I wish I could eat the trees
[Music]
are you ready Jinx no
Jinx that word doesn't exist on my
channel we don't jinx ourselves here on
this channel
I don't know what you're talking about
what do you mean Jinx what does that
mean
I don't understand
[Music]
okay I'll keep the specialist done until
there's a few more
surrounding me
one more thing we 've been with me and
my mommy last night
we watched uh the new episode of Lord of
the uh House of the Dragon
together
[Music]
you guys watched it yet
you guys watch it
disorder
House of the Dragon
it's a collaboration like in the game
you wanted
did you want it did you watch it
when it turned pink I oh I didn't I
didn't realize oh [\h__\h] oh I said I
wanted to get the limiter but that was
on a different map maybe I should get it
though
[Music]
oh those [\h__\h] oh it's time for those
[\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] why am I in the middle of all
this oh no
by surviving how is that possible
[Music]
oh this is fine this is fine
things with Polly I've been watching
that too
[Music]
yeah
just
just ignored all of whatever just
happened maybe there was just so much
food around I didn't even see oh there
you go there's all the food
yeah my mom actually
um liked the half of the Dragon episode
so far
and I like them too then the most recent
one was so pretty good I would say I'm
not gonna spoil or anything but
um was pretty impressive got some good
action
at the end especially
sketching tense a lot of uh
a lot of conflicts are building up
sake good with okay
[Music]
some pickup range hell yeah
wow the sandwich is really good too huh
[Music]
yeah and I am starting to like diamond a
little bit more I guess
than before like
he's proving himself to be an
interesting
character while in episode two he's not
alone it's still an episode three still
seems like a little bit of a baby
little baby
good combo with the foods you have food
still coming oh
the time goes by fast
I'm going fine so fast
enough
where are you
okay I wish I could eat you but I can't
wait but she goes
she being Charmed I don't know but if
yes and only for a second
but not like I could eat her for real
right
fast Yahoo
[Laughter]
hi hi oh okay it was really okay yeah
you just can't die
oh [\h__\h] I could have gone for her
almost
Uber sheep yeah
pictures have endless amounts of food
this is uh so far kind of the easiest
run
in my life
my whole life
easy peasy lemon squeezy
yo I was saying my mom she really liked
the house of the Dragon episode but
she told me she tried watching uh rings
of power and she
really did not like that
all right this is Pat's coming on the
ninth
this weekend
oh oh this is coming
[Music]
keep them coming coming
yeah she was I think she was ranting
about it for at least an hour if not two
hours
we're sitting on my balcony late at
night and my mom was really passionately
ranting about rings of power and I'm
like Mommy
Mommy I get it but then she was like
flexing her Lord of the Rings knowledge
because of course she read the book
books and um told me something I didn't
know at all like
um the fact that
the rings of power
they didn't get the rights to the books
so but they wanted to make something out
of it so what did they buy you guys
maybe know it they only got to buy the
footnotes of the book books so all they
were allowed to tell
in the series
was the footnotes
that's why certain characters
are not even allowed to show up
in the show like candle
because Gandalf in all of the books
never showed up a single time
in the footnotes
[Music]
however Galadriel did and yeah the other
characters too
[Music]
interesting info right
that's why you can already tell
at this point that there will be no
Gandalf I'm I'm kind of sad because I
was like oh [\h__\h] I was like wandering I
was hoping
even though it's kind of a very hopeful
thing to hope for but you know that
um that big ass character for for anyone
who wants rings of power but there's
this this mysterious big dude right
and I was wondering is is that maybe
can't help
[Music]
because I don't know is that what
candles came from
you were faking it too oh thank God I'm
not the only one because I just I just I
was wondering who is this character that
we don't know yet
um
I was trying to find an explanation
holy [\h__\h] I'm just too strong
oh there he goes Ellie
oh it's Dumbledore
could be yes
that's a big boy too if I've ever seen
one
[Music]
okay
well I hope we'll find out eventually I
don't want to get spoiled I don't know
if that's a character that I I would
know if I read the books but so far I
have no idea
come on
yeah
[Music]
destruction suffering
suffering everywhere burning burning on
fire
oh look at look at that doesn't that
look so beautiful
um this is such a cheese run this is
such a stretch
content is
ah
do we want more food
no hey stop okay yeah more action
or action baby
oh these clocks got nothing on me oh now
these boys are coming down
see let's see if they come too close
I'll just eat them
but they can't even close to me
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my God
ah these are all good
okay yeah then I don't have to move so
much but if you guys suck at this game
like me
just play okay
it's a no-brainer also see look at those
dodging skills oh oh [\h__\h] oh oh yeah oh
yeah
easy
[Music]
clap holy [\h__\h] what
what I've never went through this stage
so easily before
my God
[Music]
I'm frozen yeah what's up today what's
up with that Japan
is EXP
[Music]
and oh my God
I don't understand
[Music]
a lot off screen because I was trying to
grind as many coins as possible
it's not taking the damage for five
seconds increase crit by 10 percent
on both ends of Home receiving diamonds
if eating food oh that's what
that's what a good combination
[Music]
oh my god this is my favorite character
in the game now
it's just so smooth very good for
grinding coins as well because we don't
have to like try so hard oh
hollaback so it's plug type as a Coco
let's go maybe the buff yeah they did I
was told they did we have brief in
asakopo now let's go I'm invincible
I could I actually could do endless
modes Senpai for once
oh my God
I'm not even I'm not even using my
special
what
[Music]
what I'm getting insane amounts of ears
here like I got two cold apples
and I'm still not stopping
I got a [\h__\h] ton of Buffs as well
oh my oh my God
what
kind of survive too strong
above to open
four seconds just people drinking the
second
yeah nerfing coming next update
oh God no please keep it like this this
gives me confidence I need to have some
confidence don't take this away from me
oh oh the birds
foreign
she's fine
oh my God I want to see okay Senpai
playing okay senpai
I'm sure she will
all the Japanese members were surely
play their own characters soon
dangerous too dangerous
um
[Music]
assistant is this all you got although
we did have trouble on the other map but
now look how we're rocking this one holy
moly
call me macaroni how fast can we get
this sapling down
let's go like this way again oh that was
pretty fast
okay
it's a party in the USA
you got sapling down oh the Lopes are
coming the sand lines are coming and
this time I'm actually not scared of
them unless offense stops me once again
uh I don't need
I don't need any more I'm just I'm too
strong
any of this
oh [\h__\h]
I got too close I want to eat them but
there's too many
welcome
welcome mama
[\h__\h] I'm almost sad that it's ending no
I am sad that it's ending
whatever is mad
come give me more
I want to see more
now we're talking
okay now I'm scared I'm scared I'm
scared
oh but I'm surviving I'm [\h__\h]
surviving
foreign
no I won that one I won that was just an
accident that's
um I ate so much that my my tummy
exploded
level 54 we got to level 54 we got 2 200
coins
selling piggy bank gained one coin every
second and every second
an increased speed by 15 however reduced
pickup range by 50 another way of
um getting a [\h__\h] ton of coins if you
need to get more gacha
if you need the gods app
I will with these two thousand four
hundred coins buy some upgrades
[Music]
she already is go ahead
you can get something expensive now
you can do it like attack or
pee
oh I'll go for
one attack
um 600
[Music]
.
next time I want to go for you speaking
so
let's wait for that okay we're gonna go
for it
punch towards the front in a random cone
and ending making tanker and waves of
giant exploding newbies targets defeated
get their uobs taken
are you ready for UB time
I'll take a throat candy
dude my UVS no not my UVs
I will go for the grassy place you guys
have seen the other one and you see it's
really hard
to showcased the characters in in the
other one so I hope you'll forgive me
[Music]
um
first time at your stream welcome
[Music]
I hope it won't be the last time
throwing punches
I don't know
some boxing gloves
[Applause]
new boss yeah I don't think I'll get
there today
a lot of new upgrades
[Music]
um
Corona brainwashing every 12 seconds
Corona brainwashes targets defeating
brainwashed targets grants one you'll be
maximum 30. what there's a maximum each
tube increases the haste by 0.5 for
seven seconds
oh
okay oh then we have the oriole
okay well why not
oh oh look at the ubis
and now you see on the on the bottom
left it's counting the ubis
um I did not quite register everything
that this said but haste was
um increasing the speed of my attacks
right endurance
streamer reduce damage taken by five
percent every 20 seconds
uh on taking damage getting retaliation
increasing attack by 15 and forward
damage reduction temporarily
okay
I'll go for this one first though
hopefully the other one will come back
to me and you'll be
[Music]
to take them all all
I don't think this will be as easy as
um
let's go for some study glasses
we're gonna stand by with some study
guys give me your yummies
[Laughter]
giant
uh juby statues coming out of the ground
and exploding ah
increases all healing my 10 targets can
drop
eating a Chocolate Hills five HP and
increases maximum HP by 10 for 10
seconds
interesting oh more food
I like how they're both uh they have
like their own Foods going on very food
related food focused
don't we all love food
[Music]
I want to have it
it's kind of pretty crowded in here oh
[Music]
I got it okay maybe it's time for an
extra weapon but I only have the fun BM
and the magical music notes
I want to get them Together song because
I want to see it combined with something
we have the accuracy combined with
something look at all this
[Music]
um
amount of conscious by one increased
okay
combined with glow stick all right all
right
I'll see what I can do
nice that cleared the area nicely here
we have the glow stick so I'll take it
while I can
so far easy but she feels really slow
kind of want to speed up but let's go
for the glasses first
got strong fast
[Music]
okay almost awakened
oh
[Music]
I can have the limiter now because she
left it she said she didn't need it
anymore and she just left it for
everyone to use that's so sweet
I make the most of it
well attack speed is nice yo
reduce delay between combination punches
by 50 worth combination
[Music]
oh and they go in all directions
they shouldn't really have human fever
but okay
they must be purple yubies
pickles actually we just call them
newbies for now but they were getting
some tentacles
[Music]
and once again like corn apple as fast
as possible so I'm doing this
I hope you guys are not tired of the
song repeating yet
foreign
music not yet okay it's surprising how
long you can listen to this song
[Music]
oh wait this works well on corn on this
Empire too because she eats all the
corner the corners
this will work well on her too
you got a lot of crits
well we want to get the Idol song first
oh
[Music]
song
I didn't realize I activated that oh
[\h__\h] I'm so close come on come on
[Music]
there we go
let me see let's have some conversation
what else did I do
really happy
he woke up and mommy made me um
he made me uh pancakes but like
Australian style pancakes which are more
like Crepes but like a little bit of a
thick kind of crab
um and I I put in Nutella and bananas so
that was like it's my dream
S no
could have that every day without having
to cook it myself
but this time I took advantage of my
mommy being there
hmm
yeah sweet pancakes
I ate like three of them today two for
breakfast and then one more before the
Stream
[Music]
oh I can imagine
my mommy didn't eat the sweet pancakes
so she made herself a
like a Savory pancake she filled with
some some egg spread and some salad and
some cherry tomatoes
fine too
it looks very yummy also she actually
she brought me a [\h__\h] ton of her cherry
tomatoes from uh her garden
so we used it in when we were cooking
the day before yesterday as well because
she stayed over for two nights so we had
one hellofresh meal and one tonkatsu
um
yeah she has a garden she has a huge
Garden yeah and she has like a [\h__\h] ton
of vegetables so many vegetables all
kinds of vegetables and and fruit of
course and flowers
and yeah those are the flowers that I
showed on Twitter I got those from my
mommy she brought them from her garden
weren't they pretty they're still alive
I'm gonna keep them alive for as long as
possible I hope
[Music]
oh
special meter
well
is Corona related
special
[Music]
but most people say what okay
maybe if we have some you you
we have some extract XP leader we can
get picky picky
I would like to thank you
yo I barely have any attacks going
what's up with that
oh there we go now we're talking
[Music]
so almost there almost there
oh and speaking of flowers we also uh we
didn't only go to the IKEA we also went
to like a gardening
store and we bought some new stuff for
my Planters on my balcony because
everything's [\h__\h] dead
unfortunately
yeah but now I got some nice stuff I got
some flowers because planting fruits or
vegetables now makes no sense because
nothing's gonna grow anymore throughout
the the fall the Autumn and the winter
so instead we planted some nice looking
oh [\h__\h] since oh
it's a nice looking flowers
[Music]
that will survive the seasons
relatively long okay
why do we want to do
[Music]
okay yeah again food food is the way to
go
[Music]
let's see this one
also progressing in all directions that
explode into a song wow
beautiful
I love that that's the first time I saw
that that's
it
[Music]
yo this one protects me very well oh
maybe I did that too early oh well
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
is so precious isn't it
such a cute laugh I wish I wish I wish
there were sound effects of her love in
this game 40 haste is no joke
[Music]
left
foreign
okay this is this is looking very strong
already we're not even at 10 minutes yet
[Music]
already looking extremely powerful oh
[\h__\h] oh God get out of here get out of
here get out of here do you guys ever
let's just like stay in this like in the
middle when these come or do you
trying to escape like me
I'm already very powerful right now but
I still don't feel confident enough to
face them
you're always this game
I Savor got the right build uh-huh
Escape Escape okay everybody says
escaping I see okay that I don't feel so
so weak and so cowardly anymore
[Music]
increase all healing
bucket
four okay yeah for the next
collaboration to get that started indeed
oh one more thing I bought at the
gardening house was um you know those
things that you stick into the pot and
that they tell you if and
um if the plants need water so I got a
couple of those so hopefully my plants
are wrong
gonna stay alive forever
smart never heard of that yo it's so
helpful if you have plants because you
stick it into the pot and it measures if
the soil is wet or not
foreign
it feels pretty rare doesn't it
wasn't that called a finger well I guess
you put your face
too [\h__\h]
then your finger you you'll be you'll be
as we're talking about you because we'll
always get dirty oh [\h__\h] focusing but oh
you're right
ah it's fine she's no match for me right
now
oh there she is okay let's get down
and that's no problem she'll be down in
an instant I'm telling you
okay maybe a little bit too early
to do some damage in Kabuki Samsung
oh that must have been a record time
highlights just like okay but yeah
they're both
extremely strong
super strong cheese Duo
and we we now have an offer of the piggy
bank but that
I don't want it
I don't need those coins
I know it's new and all that but I
currently don't really need the coins
but it does also increase the speed
um
I do okay for updates upgrades okay okay
oh God have you seen this game fee are
you seeing this
it's too easy
[Music]
wow
standby we're not this easy out of the
four I have to say I had the most
trouble with meal senpai
in that order
wow still missing two members of country
that's true indeed
a special cooldown
I mean less cooldown
and one would be and that's true but
it's still you know felt like um I was
struggling a lot and close to dying so
often
that it felt very stressful for me but
once again maybe that's just been on a
play style issue
a lot of people they might not have as
many troubles as I did
oh okay stand fine
strong
[Music]
but overall they're all really
interesting characters with interesting
attacks and
really powerful and fun to play so
I'm also excited that after this we can
try Jet zero
hopefully as many as possible with them
[Music]
ugly
oh they got me but it's fine it's fine
oh you wanna know one more thing my
mommy got me
because she
she was wanting my stream as she usually
does
oh God
and she um
[Music]
one
okay
and she might even be watching now who
knows even though she might still also
be on her way home I'm not sure
uh but oh Big Clock
since she was listening to my stream and
she was listening to me talking about
rings of power
and once again mentioning how I didn't
read the books
um
really old
personal
uh um
Lord of the Rings book one number one
number one
a really old one you look at it and you
see
it's really old
but no it is in good condition
but it's still like you see that it's
like ancient looking
I don't know what Edition it is but it
doesn't even have like a fancy cover or
so
it's just the book
yeah the green one no it's um it's
hardcover yes and it's uh it's like like
a red
color
and she's like braid it
because she is as I said she was flexing
so much Lord of the Rings knowledge to
me she was like complaining a lot about
how Galadriel is being depicted in the
in the rings of power series
she doesn't need a sword she's like the
most powerful
uh swisherous I guess
in the world he doesn't need that she
could easily blow all these enemies away
in the instant
she's a big fan of Galadriel it's always
been I think
yeah so she was pretty unhappy okay
let's see this this Army compared to how
okay you Senpai did with it oh God
golden Anvil and I can't reach it
I will go there later
um
that's right
Story Time reading stream
oh I was I was kind of you know when she
gave me the book I was I was thinking yo
why hasn't anyone done like a book club
stream yet where you can ever you gave
her a good amount of [\h__\h] oh God you
gather oh God you gave her a good amount
of whole life members like maybe five or
so you choose a book beforehand you give
them like a week or two or a month to
read the book
and then talk about it just um
just talk about it don't read from it
that's not what a book club is about not
necessarily it doesn't need to
stop about it oh God
oh God oh God
holy [\h__\h]
but still manageable
oh hello
okay let's try to get around them now
okay and then go kind of downwards
I think that would be it like actually
kind of fun
the book club
um especially if it's Lord of the Rings
I wanna I I've noticed that actually a
lot of Japanese members don't know Lord
of the Rings and just recently Miko
Senpai watched all three movies
on Twitch yeah and I was so excited to
see that but the fact that she didn't
even know loaded the Rings before that
just shocked me so hard I guess it's not
as popular in Japan
as it was overseas
men culture shock
culture shock
hi I need that I need them I know the
animal is down there I know I know
I was trying to get there
we can watch Lord of the Rings yeah
lettering is very European
oh
shush okay oh one more thing
um
[Music]
oh my God
okay where was I oh yeah the one concern
I have though is that
if you give them a one month deadline
unless unless there's a lot of members
who really like reading a lot
I don't think I know you could rely on
them to really do their homework and
read as they promised
because everyone's also busy you know
very busy Japanese members especially
but I want to share my love of Lord of
the Rings and Game of Thrones and all
that kind of stuff and also I want to I
wouldn't mind reading a new book or two
and I I want to read um Lord of the
Rings myself like let me read the books
even though I love I love the whole
world
and his story you know from what I know
but my mom did make me pretty curious
about all the things I don't know
like she was geeking out so hard for
hours and hours it continued endlessly
Lord of the Rings manga I feel like that
might may even exist
[Music]
maybe an idea for the future if I
um find some members who like to read
maybe ask like okay cool here let's be
open to doing a book club collaboration
once a month or
once in two months or so I don't know I
have to be generous there because
[Music]
going down
come on
yeah there we go
that's how I like it
okay let's get a little bit out of here
get some distance two more minutes
are coming
they're looping around
don't stop don't stop just go your own
way
oh my God
but we're fine we're fine we're fine
mmm
we have the situation under control
I don't know if we have time to get that
one more collab going uh we already have
to collapse I never had three collapse
before
in 20 minutes I mean
that would be insane it's kind of hard
to get the EXP now
I just want to survive you know
I just want to survive today
we collapse is hard it's fine I think
well I'm satisfied with what I have
although my nose is itchy and there's a
lot of oh God okay keep keep on going
it's kind of laggy
keep on going
yup I escaped it and let's do this
look at the numbers
they're moving so slow wow
oh the lag oh dear okay
[Music]
keep being a good distance
nice nice nice nice nice nice job
let's do this
oh wait there's one more oh right there
right I keep on forgetting it doesn't
end in 20 minutes
nice to see you again oh the line stop
nice
you will not ground pound
s not today
foreign
yes I think we got her I think we got
her oh
baby bubbles are coming for us
we're gonna win this we're gonna win
this
we're gonna win this I know
thank you
yes I feel I feel she's almost dead I
feel it
escape the bubbles Escape Escape Escape
oh
ah
nice
necking nice
beautiful oh X potato for a potato that
bounces around the screen before
exploding into an X
potato so then I'm a reference what a
reference is that
we only know potatoes from almond
I said for everyone oh
I love potatoes
okay we have 4 200 coins I guess we can
give Council gotcha a try
still missing two characters come on
I think I didn't have homemade yet
yeah yeah
and for now please
please okay
double mommy
um
one more please let's see if we can
finish the whole lineup today and again
I get so many sanans what the hell
yes
one more
[Music]
foreign
okay
we can go to the Japan gen zero now I
kind of want to start from mikochi if
that's all right
oh yeah
yes
so she has a soccer swing I'm going to
create the burst of Sakura blossoms and
creative Zona ramiko for eight seconds
summoning hot flames that burn
everything tarzones don't take 50 more
damage okay
let's clear a stage with Mikko Senpai if
possible oh go oh oh [\h__\h] is huge
already
normally it's not that big
foreign
[Music]
to create a new dealing on 50 damage and
confuses targets reducing attack and
speed by 30 for three seconds
hmm
confuses targets
it feels the targets I've never seen
that before in Hollow cure
[Music]
I don't see them confused yet because
they die so fast
I'm gonna attack area increase
destroyed the jungle statue
oh oh do you want to see the special
attack guys
um I'm saving it a little bit
[Music]
wow
I won't do it yet that was too easy
saving it a little bit where where's the
vacuum
baby language level two
I should put on my pacifier for this but
I would have to change outfits
maybe we'll sell also get a [\h__\h] you who
knows
if you want then don't worry I'll give
you a [\h__\h] you
[Music]
okay okay
okay here we go wow
oh wouldn't that be amazing in
combination with me Comet uh
yo what when Miko conquers or Target
conkers
for four seconds of Edda heal 2 Hp every
two seconds each Conquest resets the
timer
hahaha
interesting
so it's the heel
that special attack looked really strong
too
what Pokemon trailer coming tomorrow
the release is was it is it in the
November December or did they not say
yet the exact release it's at least
we've been in the state they're probably
going for December right because
Christmas Market
wiper
holy [\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
wait there was Elite glasses look at
them again
okay okay it didn't kill a boss but no
no no he's dead
[Music]
oh good I'll go for whatever
so I'm gonna go away
oh no my house is on fire for many
healing Miko games a four second above
that increases attack and speed by 20
and the elite weapons are elite weapons
so anyway
um
related weapons
maybe are 10 larger or any weapons
[Music]
the lava bucket
only that
because there's any elite weapons then
there must be more than that
Elite lava and Elite cooking
okay those two
uh-huh
Odo
then we shall get those
[Music]
okay
oh oh my special is ready again
we're not right now nothing's going on
so
swing twice okay
else
it's like a
[Applause]
never mind I can't think of it brain is
Frozen
[Music]
I love the way she attacks yeah it's
pretty forgiving for people like me who
can't aim for God's sake
[Music]
oh oh The Tackle Dodgers
[Applause]
[Music]
their helmets are protecting them pretty
well huh
I almost got all of them
available
okay
I'll increase the bucket this time
a new weapon would be nice though
there you go
[Music]
I did get them all oh I usually never
get them all
two okay
thanks guys for thinking for me when I
can't use my brain anymore you're like
my second top my my second brain my
third my third brain
what
oh there's the piggy bank again
should we get them
look at the piggy bank
yeah
I'm new here welcome
two okay
[Music]
sent by streams and Conquer amen
I'll do my best to get you to small
Amadeus all I can that's the best I can
do forgive me
it's not quite the real deal but close
enough
small pixel Miko she gets small pixel
amen
I think she'll appreciate it
she'll be ground pounded
by the one and only small army dream
come true
come on
so strong oh I should have I should have
put them to Michael hey
[Music]
um
speed
Co
ah limiter
I'm going for the limiter
time is going by really fast with
Michael simply
it's getting hot in here it will take up
all your clothes you know Miko senpai's
most recent outfit is so cute
those cute little shorts
oh baby
oh baby I love her new I like all of her
outfits but her new outfit is wowzers
it's incredible
[Music]
agree of course you agree I know
you're gonna have to tell me that
everybody agrees
[Music]
oh hello I didn't see you guys here
where did you come from suddenly
circling me
foreign
[Music]
well it's not coming to me
oh no man
when I say it I'll take it
I missed it really oh damn they will
come back
um
let's see is there anything else I
wanted to tell you guys
[Music]
I'll have to look at my notes but I
don't have any anyway I'm looking at my
notes now on y'all
[Music]
Nico look good in the second map what
you think she's easy on the second map
huh
I don't know I don't know about that
[Music]
um
how big her weapon would get with
night's milk oh yeah increase it even
more
[Music]
what am I streaming tomorrow I forgot I
think Members Only
you guys remember help me out here in my
brain
memory is only oh I actually didn't
decide yet what to do for Members Only
potato I get the new item for a potato
that bounces around the screen I could
prefer exploring into the X oh
wait I wonder if we can
what we can collab that with
it's new right it's completely new so
um
I wonder
[Music]
I feel like you could come combine it
with a whole bomb I feel like that would
work well
but I don't know check out menu oh you
can see it there
anyway holy [\h__\h] uh let me get out of
here actually see
to escape there but I'm skipping for my
safety
I don't want to embarrass myself so
the special attack in a good moment
where are all my experience
[Music]
boys love Max
but we want to do me comment all right
those can't even combine anyway right
[Music]
all right all right all right I'll take
it
[Music]
I'm doing Ellie's cooking yeah sorry did
I miss it again I hope it wasn't there
I'll upgrade the potato potato
I mean what what else could I do yeah
we'll find something to maxilla
it might have new collapse that we don't
know about true
true
[Music]
maybe is there something specific I
should aim for
I'm looking at my DMs
let me know if there's something
specific
Parkside I need teammates yeah
investigators
[Music]
they remind me also so much of um
what was the game I played with them
with the alligators I see you later
alligator wait was that the actual name
one coin every second
[Music]
oh wait what's over 10 minutes
yeah later alligator not see you later
[Applause]
that's that fluffy tail on the Fire
I feel like I just set another record oh
should we go for NightLight milk ah oh
I see I see I I did I did get a DM
okay I know to keep an eye open for I
guess um that was the answer to what
combines with the potato
it's uh not here right now but you know
we want the milk for now so
ah
ah I got my potato
okay
yeah but someone's in the chat said you
can actually look it up is that really
so
beautiful
yeah no I understand by milk
it only logs the one you discovered ah
okay
well I know what to look for now so
let's make it happen
but so far it's an item that I have yet
to see
all right
okay
that should be it
oh wait stop moving I'm fine I'm fine
I'm fine
thrilled rat is what I'm serving today
Potato song yeah apparently
[Music]
potato
ES
[Music]
honestly Miku Santa is also really easy
to play so far
pretty easy
all the clocks okay okay sometimes I
have struggles with the clocks so I'll
be careful
[Music]
baby mode
bubble bubble mode
okay
[Music]
a baby could definitely play this is
that what you're saying
definitely you can't be baby
we have some KP babies
[Music]
I'm just gonna use it now
saves me some trouble or does it they're
not dying
but they're also not hitting me well
enough so
um should I heal should I double the
heel
I've got a new new weapon
oh yeah cyclists
I don't want to focus on that though I
want to focus on the potato on the Idol
song but it's uh
I'll just get attacked up
I like the idea too
there's no wrong way of doing it right
[Music]
okay okay
I love me comet
[Music]
nothing that I was specifically looking
for oh
maybe the bandage
just bandaged one one two one crit
one okay
okay come on come on more of that please
more from where that came from
and
[Music]
um level two body pillow
be honest
I personally only own a dakimakura cover
of some kiwawa fan made merchandise you
know
but I I did not make it into an actual
dakimakura
Mimi yes not me
yes oh oh maybe I should should have
kept it uh
[Music]
I needed to sleep otherwise I wake up
and back when oh wow your actual making
like practical use of it because it
helps your sleeping
I used to have like
[Music]
um
that you guys are thinking of
um but I did I did have like it was like
a lengthy really long
um oh God oh God focus focus focus focus
focus just stay here just stay here
really long
um pillow oh god oh wait haha it's ready
[Applause]
and that didn't help me sleep because
like I would I would hug it oh God
I would hug it to sleep but that's a
long time ago I haven't had that one in
a while
okay I have a situation on the perfect
control and I think I I heard something
I see something I'm gonna make my way
I'm on the way
oh the golden anvils here You've Got
Mail
there it is there it is there it is
look at this
look at them
an ex-potato becomes
rap dog
yo yo caught another rip dog a
collaboration of X potato and Idol song
drop some Hobbits hell yeah oh we should
have had Corona standby got that one
cool
oh I hear the beat
I hear it's bouncing off of the enemies
[Music]
oh
now I wonder if there's any anything
else that I don't know about any
of your collaborations then let me know
but if that's it then okay
[Music]
may I thank you oh
is there still more there must be more
there must be more
[Music]
asking for spoilers yeah I know I'm not
asking you guys
I'm just trying so this is an early
access this showcase as much as possible
within one stream
so that you guys are ready to play it on
your own
afterwards
already at 16 minutes only four minutes
to go
yeah it's like
uh original song
I really like that one
called doggy Godsey
I don't remember the title but it was
really cool that's
um genre
Street
cute
I
might and crazy
yeah okay
one glass of milk Dental milk
specifically per day keeps the doctor
away
but it doesn't keep the Furious Senpai
Senpai is coming for you if you drink
too much of her milk
to make Korea Senpai mad
you cannot give the impression that your
possible rival
I want a little bit of Footers advice
and energies then cheese
um today
nice and then I got into a little bit of
a conversation with energy about how we
should do an original song and actually
it was very very motivated I wanted to
do that for a long long long long long
long time
original song
[Music]
I mean it's just an idea now so it will
take a long time I still have to really
current upcoming
new original song coming soon for real
now
in the in the final stage
so you'll hear from it soon
it will be legendary it will be
life-changing
stream something something that we don't
know yet
thank you
[Music]
I got an interesting hint thank you I'll
keep it in mind
yeah
interesting debut
um I will go for the milk whatever
[Music]
something I can't do this time I think
but next time
[Applause]
[Music]
I'll go around I'll go around
yo here I am
that's a good question but kurukami has
kind of been around already for a long
time so yes even though the debut just
happened
I would say it's a senpai she's a senpai
been around for quite some time
[Music]
oh yeah she she kind of showcased her
Freddy also before yeah I think so
toast we're getting toast guys
I'm just so that I can survive I kind of
want this one but okay
[Music]
oh my I didn't notice the emerald
I didn't notice it
thanks for paying attention
[Music]
what wait no I should have gone for the
cooking wait sorry brain is slow
[Music]
together
that was close that was close [\h__\h] where
did all this come from
okay kind of laggy again at least on my
side looks less laggy on obs
[Music]
keep it moving keep it moving oh
a little bit long and it's a little bit
longer almost there
I should have the damage to stay inside
the circle I'm not confident enough for
that if I [\h__\h] up
then you know it's gonna be embarrassing
but I'll bring it
melt those clubs burn the saplings
okay it's really they're really fun
but this is looking like another clear
ever body
um
where the [\h__\h] did you come from
time
[Applause]
[Music]
every time they had some kind of
interaction it's so cute
the interactions with like small Mikko
Daniel and small amen like conventions
was really cute too
[Applause]
it's like actually best the best
OTP
it's like a romance that will never
happen
but we still love it and support it
because Miko Senpai is like basically
all of us
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I didn't see her coming
Miracle I'm still alive it's a [\h__\h]
miracle oh
[Music]
[Applause]
another win in the back for
takanashikiwawa
[Music]
cool how much coins two thousand point
you know what I'm gonna keep them I'm
gonna save them
this time yeah
okay okay
make some water
and we're gonna go for the next
character
[Music]
perhaps we say senpai
oh
stage two uh okay but we won't get far
we won't get far
I hope you're aware of that yeah
son of stage too
oh yeah I have like a [\h__\h] ton of dupes
of Santa so she should be stronger right
try movement I'll never use Moomin
before
[Music]
foreign
I think this place
um
works best live maybe you know
[Music]
okay even though I failed but you know I
just
survives and survives blocks Master
Critical Hits have a 50 15 chance to
summon a falling block from above that
deals 150 damage let's go
I want to see
ah
Critical Hits have a 25 chance to
increase attack by two percent for four
seconds up to 10 if activated all
Targets within 75 pixels take that
critical hit
okay none of that ends with my brain but
let's go sounds strong
[Music]
without food this is impossible
now that I could actually kill them
maybe we need some uberships going here
yeah oh thank God there's some food
here come the botan Senpai Sonia
[Music]
um
how do we survive the longest
[Music]
so it's damaged
yeah
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
come on
okay more blocks Master maybe or
more food more food maybe yeah
bomb okay weapons weapons always good
oh they disappeared I endured long
enough
why do we only have a chance now
um
safest to stay in an area where you can
actually move around because you may not
be able to move but they can
okay
yeah
whoa It's Lucille path the feeding
Tigers increases increase the crate by
four percent for four seconds
after 20
oh nice crits
the fitting targets with axolated
weapons um has a 10 chance to heal free
HP
okay
[Music]
healing and crits
okay this is going
more steady
and I thought it was okay but now now
now oh God okay I I did that to myself I
did this to myself I did this to myself
I did this I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm
so sorry
you have to
know where you're going
[Music]
I I need some food
I need to put the spawn behind me oh
there it is there there's some food
oh
okay okay we can use this as a chance
[Music]
that's what I'm saying
okay okay okay okay
over for a minute I don't think I've
ever survived for this long here okay
but now I'm going to die I'm going I'm
yeah
[Applause]
there's so much for me I need baby mode
easy mode
okay now we will give her a chance in
the grassy Plains
yeah
maybe another time when I have a [\h__\h]
ton of upgrades
this is for people
who have been there and done that
but I like this place you know
this place is fine I like this place
and I got like a rhythm going on here I
I know what's coming
I can see the future and that makes me
feel safe and really like a baby
okay so there's one item that I'm
looking for a one one attack I'm not an
attack like a defense item
[Music]
so I want to clear the stage with it
man the what I'm looking for I unlocked
but wanna you know if I cleared with
that then I can unlock something new oh
those chickens oh man I almost feel
sorry for them
that's in the chicken
stage one is gonna learn your character
stage
wow
when you when you put it like that it
kind of undermines all the victories
I've had so far
it doesn't sound as impressive anymore
that I did it
oh God
stop stop no no stop please no more
[Applause]
my wings on
foreign
[Music]
I kind of want to help myself with some
healing also need a tax bill
yeah okay
[Music]
and my my main weapon is still too weak
as well
wow
oh
I by the way suck
absolutely suck at the
Tetris
I wish I was as good as soy sauce
number one in the charts okay let's get
this cycle ax because it will be
stronger web series don't sound fine
any ax related weapons
strong and buffed
[Music]
Petra's Queen
yeah they did change a little bit of
Chihuahua I'm not going to change like
the skill set but they improved
something I don't know what exactly
[Music]
and I and I have that burger no no okay
okay that's fine that's fine
did you guys see that yet that that's a
possible thing you can get Chinese I
kind of like skipped the whole super
cool animation but yeah I had that um
off stream I got like a shiny body
pillow
foreign
so like you know they are stronger and
they're shiny
whatever you get in shiny is stronger
than it normally would be
cool
but it doesn't happen that often it's
pretty rare
[Music]
[Applause]
oh they're still alive how's their day
I got another one ready what what
you can stack them or what
[Music]
how rare well so far I've been playing
uh including
including when I played off screen
I've been playing them up for five
at least five hours and it happened
twice to me
[Music]
Ah that's right
are you ready
oh my God
ah it's just not coming to me what I'm
looking for it's just not coming to me
anyway
get crushed
by the tetris Bluffs
addresses
nostalgic old game huh
you know one more thing that's no
challenging that I thought of yesterday
I was I blew my own mind by reminding
myself of something really nostalgic I
played with as a child
I was thinking of iron beads
I think many of us played with iron
beads when we were when we were young
one more thing
one more thing that I played with a lot
when I was a child
I don't know if you know it by this name
oh Play-Doh well that's a book no in
this case I'm talking about
something called
uh wait wait wait wait wait I'm not
missing misremembering right
yeah yeah okay something called
Scooby-Doo please tell me someone knows
Scooby-Doo and I don't know if it's like
a
thing outside of my country too but
can we do
maybe you have to look it up yeah oh my
god let's go
no I don't mean it no I don't mean the
dog I don't mean the dog um it's written
as see oh you
[Music]
s-c-o-u-b-i-d-o-u oh man you were
thinking of different things so sad
no I don't mean the dog
second
Google it yeah the weaving thing you
basically weave
um
uh uh you read the like some kind of
plastic
um Reds yeah and you can make them into
little keychains and bracelets and
whatever
I I used to do so many of them and it
was such a typical
um
like like birthday or general present
that kids in my school would give to
their friends and to their their parents
and they had like really cool fancy ones
like plastic
um threads that were like see-through
those were really sick
[Applause]
the see-through ones were sick
and the sparkly ones
I love them so much
when I suddenly reminded myself of them
and I'm like oh my God Mom do you
remember when I used to play with those
Scooby-Doo things
it was so popular everybody played with
them but one of you guys
um
like I have a different name for it
I remember I think I still have mine
and patterns of how to weave them and
they will come out like totally
differently and they can like become
really intricate actually they they
actually do get pretty complicated as a
gift of friends in the zero zeros yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's the right name I just forgot
about it ah okay okay
okay everyone everybody thought of the
dog personally yeah I know what you're
talking about the dog Scooby-Doo hello
Scooby-Doo no why does it have that name
why does it have such a similar name
well I was wondering I kind of want to
do that again maybe even for handcamps
try to remind myself
oh God oh God I'm trying to remind
myself of
of how how it worked
and get some cool color combinations I
was thinking since you like to make
those into
um keychains combine that with my iron
beads uh chippies pixel chibi keychains
and then you have like a double
double keychain as a present even
fancier
guaranteed crit yeah we're getting a
[\h__\h] on the little crits
I would need some food too though please
Hussein
[Music]
Gohan yo
sorry sorry so we got too close to you
[Music]
where's the balls
I wasn't a big fan of uh that Scooby-Doo
[Laughter]
oh hello there
oh please don't hit me with that big
long stick please please don't
move
[Music]
but um the sake is healing me thankfully
okay okay
get that out of the way
[Music]
let me spider cookie we need more
weapons
or glue stick
one
two eight
I wonder if you can combine the ax of
the potato probably not
hmm
oh
[\h__\h] they're all coming now it's okay I
got my Tetris ready
okay okay here we go
they'll thank me later
oh there should be like a
like a Cali and suse collaboration
weapon
maybe next update you're welcome for the
inspiration
[Music]
right
250 damage sounds sick
Death Star yes wait wait wait wait did
that exist it doesn't yet right
I'm having wait I'm having a I'm having
a
[Music]
what's the French word
I feel like we talked about something
like this before
Deja Vu yeah
really strong days of the red now
maybe that's to keep Waba from a
different timeline trying to tell me
something
foreign
[Music]
okay I kind of wasted but
like clearing the area oh what
baseball
okay wasted wasted
what already 10 minutes
go straight up
she was she was white she was flat and
so cute
so cute I just wanna fluff that whoa
how am I so good at this recently
wow
no
would you guys be mad if I took speed
o
yes no
no maybe no yes very okay that's illegal
man
oh glasses
it's a miracle that at this point I
still don't need glasses in my life to
see things clearly I would think my my
eyes would be already so damaged
I do like some fashion glasses still
just wearing them
because they're cute
[Applause]
especially the round ones they look so
cute
foreign
that well though
glasses are versatile yes
okay don't need to only wear them see
better you can just also wear them to
look better
what
different meaning
versatile
[Music]
oh my God hello
how is everybody doing tonight
[Music]
okay I want a new weapon Zone we're
going for the beam
[Music]
I still don't need them damn some people
I just built differently aren't we
[Music]
make me look like a big dog no I'm sure
you look good with them
[Music]
it must have dropped some food though oh
okay
oh God there's oh oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] I almost died I'm so sorry
um um
[Applause]
oh God
get away from me
I'm hungry
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
where the [\h__\h] is the food
foreign
[Music]
nothing here helps me I'm probably
upwards
I'll try to Circle them now
um but it's getting really close
I got something
okay okay you've got the
um
[Music]
keep that clock away from me
spider cooking because I need to focus
on one thing
[Music]
poor oh sorry guys if you can't have
everything in life oh dude oh no they're
coming oh no no no no please go away
please
here
it's okay I got one more of the special
attack in the dire situation and it's
gonna come soon
okay I got I got some food
hi
never give up
oh oh oh oh God no it's not it's okay oh
God it's okay it's okay it's okay it's
okay it's okay oh no not this oh
I hate them oh no they do so much damage
okay I'm struggling a little bit of
suicide sample compared to the other
ones oh but look at the damage oh
big boys coming
downwards okay
okay okay
everybody's under control now no
long time
did it spawn yet
I got like three things on level seven
okay
I'll collapse yet that's why yeah I got
so many like different
weapons and didn't focus on them
fast enough
oh God
[Music]
oh dear oh dear oh there's so much going
on um
why not oh my
[Laughter]
[Music]
never-ending oh okay okay okay okay
um obviously in a cycle X
is that possible have I ever seen this
before
[Music]
do cooking yeah because I've seen this
combination a million times x is gonna
voice up yeah I've seen that one too
before
I've seen it
um
[Music]
okay okay okay whatever we do this then
okay
[Music]
no I think the ax damage stays and you
can't access plus cutting okay I'll get
but I think the ax damage will stay even
if I collaborated with someone something
anyway let's go for the voice level
with the X
yeah that's a good one
oh crowded this face is always very
crowded
yeah the clocks and The Burbs and the
saplings
council is out there to get me
I'm trying to escape here
okay
um if I don't get food right now I am
going to die
she needs all
come on the socket is healing me up
alcohol do your thing
only in this game I will endorse the
alcohol
[Music]
oh
well
it do be like that sometimes we already
got a lot of clears this is fine now we
saw enough of suicide Senpai we don't
have to clear the stage of suicide
standby
I I still want to show you these three
you know
I have to make the most out of the time
into the pillow yeah a pillow or
something like that was not the best
lineup of weapons I guess so
so she has a gun that shoots at any
direction that you aim for and she
releases a discharge that deals 300
percent damage wow for eight seconds
Robo games 100 attacks Speed pickup
radius and 50 crit and taste and and not
or insane
okay
oh yeah okay
so a more flexible Amelia Watson
although I know for a fact that Emilia
Watson is already pretty flexible
you do know what I mean shoot one more
bullet
level two is that supposed to be really
no name
[Music]
get him
okay now I'm improving my FPS skills
even while playing Holo cure
my FPS career is finally starting
I'm gonna be the new shining star on the
FPS sky
night sky Shannon Himmler
[Music]
although I'm playing her as if I'm
playing Amic
like I can only shoot sideways
oh
it's ready
Robo discharge every level apparentum
electric ring around roboco standby for
five seconds dealing
damage
plus one percent discharge damage for
each level rubical has
what what uh is that oil
robust discharge
no downwards down here okay
oh
yo you kind of interrupted me here but
okay whoa
she's into some guys
high level the book of gains one percent
attack for each level Rebecca has oh and
three percent crit for every 10 levels
[Music]
everybody
of quick characters with a set
[Music]
roboquoise Tesla
what
[Music]
I gotta level up then and then I guess
what would be good is like an exp
increase
so that we can get as many levels as
possible with double plus I'm fine
just it just
eats them up like the mogu mogu
it's too strong
oh wait I didn't really look at that
sorry I hope it was a good choice
yo
it's like I'm sending them into
another world
yeah AOE version of okay yeah
they don't even know what's happening
um
all the weapons I picked up so far
maybe not the best choice
picometer
can potato collapse yeah uh with um the
idols not the Idol song the the song the
music notes
we saw it already
[Music]
maybe I'll do it again
this time if I get under it is if I get
the right item yeah
it seemed
strong enough
although I have yet to make
scientific studies about what's the best
choice
[Music]
how you feeling today oh
thank you actually like yesterday I was
so tired the whole day
because my mom she wakes up so early she
doesn't sleep much
she wakes up early naturally and you
know I usually have all the doors open
in my apartment because I need my cats
to be able to reach the other rooms
oh
defending a target has a 10 chance to
drop a battery batteries gives an
additional 50 exp and shocks newer
targets are in 0.5 seconds
oh
see now this ties in with the level up
that we need
let's go
play snare
yeah I was saying huh I need my cats to
be able to reach the other rooms like
the toilet and the food the food's in
the living room
and so I keep the doors oh
I keep the doors open while I'm sleeping
as well normally you know I'm alone
so it doesn't matter
but when I have someone over like my
mommy and she wakes up early and she
goes into the kitchen she makes herself
some coffee and she starts cleaning like
a crazy person
but she can't she can't not suddenly
start cleaning everything
and then once smoothie sees that I'm
awake
she won't let it go either
[Music]
like my mom
special bug out no no no damn really
give me some money
whoa wait it's kind of hard right now
who's here
he's giving me my my pocket money
oh I feel like he even dropped coins
when you don't hit him but I have a
feeling that he drops more coins when
you do hit him I'm not sure though
I wonder if he has like a timer or HP
um like how he actually disappears I
haven't I've been trying it out holy
[\h__\h] so many coins
[Music]
oh my God
oh my God the coins
because you guys also when you were a
child do like um
your own uh what you call it
[Music]
what do you call like a like a kind of a
market
and a second hand Market
a floor marked in German
blue marked
you call that
Liberty said no I never made a lemonade
stand but ah flea market yeah garage
sale flea market
and when I was younger I would
um I had like I feel like I had a lot of
like trash things I wouldn't use so
every once in a while
I would um I would go to like the local
supermarket and
um where they have
whether when you can park the bicycles
there was some space and I would ask the
supermarket owner if it's okay if I do
my little loan flea market so I would
put a blanket down in front of the
supermarket and I would put down like
some stuff like I don't know Barbies and
[\h__\h] like that
and some witch magazines
uh which books or whatever
yeah all kinds of like stop that
um I mean there was a lot of use useless
stuff in there too I think but I can't
remember what exactly my stock was
usually
[Music]
did you make that not really I think uh
my sales weren't really good but you
know when you're a child even five bucks
is a [\h__\h] ton of money
thank you
and I still remember that sometimes
adults
usually like even animals that I knew
like parents of my friends or so they
would buy [\h__\h] I I'm pretty sure it was
out of pity
out of beer pity because like they would
come out of the supermarket market and I
would be like hey you want to buy
something please find something from
cook I have a lot of really valuable
Goods please buy
make me Ranch I need some [\h__\h] money
so I can buy the new witch magazine or
some ice cream or whatever then add some
new little merchandise
oh thank you to all the really really
merciful nice kind-hearted adult step
one buy [\h__\h] from Minecraft
junkyard
you know yeah I think this is something
that um English speaking people may not
know
um
I need Osaka
um but in like German speaking countries
what was really popular also I know that
just wrapped but I'm gonna take some
distance first
oh [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] this I just
noticed the blast
wow
[Music]
um what was I saying wait what was I
saying what was I leading up to
them I don't remember
what was I saying
oh yeah thank you the last German
speaking countries or like Germany and
Austria maybe Switzerland I don't know
uh well it's really popular was
something called diddles
it's like a mouse
I think is it a mouse
with
really really really big ears I think
it's a mouse yeah a little mouse but it
doesn't quite look like a mouse
and they have like a [\h__\h] ton of
merchandise from that
diddle yeah d-i-d-d-l-e
[Music]
no without the e just d i d d l
hmm
it was mostly popular with girls but
also some boys would um also collect the
merchandise I think I mentioned it
before but
it's um
it's like usually like blocks of like
memo
sheets that were most popular for
trading and and they all have like
different
uh like art on it illustrations on it
and I would collect them and I would put
like each new uh piece of
paper that I had until
oh the handle
uh I'm taking the pickup range whatever
oh I'm zooming I would put it into a
folder to organize them and then we
would like compare at school how many we
had and then who had some new ones that
no one else had yet
really exciting in school
I had a lot of little stuff everyone had
yeah yeah
tomato
you know but kind of like how popular
Hello Kitty is yes yes exactly
oh
[Music]
oh oh [\h__\h] okay let's stay uh above this
time
[Music]
I guess
you record maybe no because I don't have
any like really strong weapons here
except like my awakened gun oh [\h__\h] off
[Music]
oh no
where was I going with this I'm not sure
oh
very fast
anvils everywhere
[Music]
please no
all I had to do was ask
the orange Mouse from TV ah yeah I think
I do
that one was [\h__\h] though
streaming children's TV things
I'm not sure where I was going with the
diddles [\h__\h] but yeah I kept on
collecting those and I guess those were
probably also some things I would sell
in my garage sale in front of the
supermarket
oh
[Music]
I was eyeing it and I was waiting for
your confirmation guys
[Music]
McDonald's collection oh yeah that's
also one thing that I wanted as a child
always wanted those Happy Meals not
anymore not now but nowadays if I am if
I'm in the McDonald's and I I'm like
standing at the counter I do sometimes
look at the
the happy meals that they currently have
and I'm like eyeing then I'm like
actually that doesn't even look so bad
it kind of want it
a part of me I have desires to a Happy
Meal but
I'm an eternal Phoenix I look old I
can't I can't order this now
yeah
um that's just me though you guys are
welcome too
order Happy Meal even if you're 40 or 50
years old don't worry about it do it
just do it don't let your happy
needs be happy meal dreams
yeah
those Happy Meals
happiness
the happiness that I couldn't get
I want you to have it
buying it for my nephew
I don't I don't have a nephew I think
okay it's looking really fancy now we're
already at 12 minutes too
bye
so your name
[Music]
is it me or is it just the characters
being super strong
now here we go finally sorry I have to
get that one
I have to get the osaki
my Toto
the character is cracked there yeah they
all cracked
ah
[Music]
what was it
um
is there any other way of combining the
potato I want um no but we're doing it
with the music notes never mind I forgot
about it okay headphones and
phones
are you guys hearing Zippity tappity
Clickety clackity on my keyboard
my mommy was really impressed but Dana's
keyboard she looked at it she's like
whoa what's that can I touch it
you know my mom my mom said oh thank God
my mom's a
um
PC geek I guess so to say as well
[Music]
maybe one of the top ones
or improve the bomb
wow
yeah I don't think she has a keyboard
like this
it probably just has normal keyboard
then she she tried typing a little bit
with it she touched it she was
fascinated
[Music]
maybe need to get my mom a keyboard like
that
how I have right now could you stop and
stand and see what happens this is
looking pretty good but I'm too scared
to actually do it
actually I survived that pretty well
[Music]
foreign
go
drop those sick beats here
oh my God I'm too strong oh [\h__\h] wow wow
um
[Music]
foreign
holy [\h__\h] when he comes late and you'll
run
so much damage from the bombs and
whatever
dropped so many cool
that's actually insane
is he still there
no no he's gone he's gone
I'm so lucky I killed him
oh my God
foreign
[Music]
I have like three more no more probably
four more minutes considering Amelia
comes
and 20 minutes
you might be able to do it
ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
body pillow
all right
a second okay
sure
whoa whoa
oh wow
[Music]
I want to be faster
oh I could use mine
especially when I'm Gonna Keep it I'm
Gonna Keep it I'm Gonna Keep It
wow I went right through that it was
kind of dangerous oh
[Music]
yeah yeah well I didn't see it
oh you're shocked oh be careful there's
a fence
[Music]
hmm
dogs are coming
McDonald's okay
[Music]
uh-huh
okay
[Music]
kind of Haunting them by staying pretty
close and not running away from him
um
thank you
should I do it yeah
[Music]
oh yummy I love bread
Sunrise are so cute yeah honestly
might be oh God oh God I should have
kept it for now oh god oh no no no no no
no no no no no no
no no no no no holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
the satellites are one of my favorite
mascots okay keep on moving keep on
moving Keep On Moving
what about you guys which ones are your
favorite basket
and why is it kfp chickens hmm
oh God oh God oh that's not good that's
not good yeah
I mean I can't even see your answers
I'll ask you again in like uh three
minutes
foreign
how are you doing
I say hiyamas if she was in a chat
don't confuse me
foreign
I feel like we're doing incredible
damage here
[Music]
FPS Pro Gamer versus another FPS Pro
Gamer
a headshot
oh I see food I can't reach
[Music]
we clean it again
look at those coins
so many coins a big thanks to Big up
soon Yago
for the old coins the super chats
kindly appreciate it
oh
oh it's getting late but I want to show
you all characters
I think we got a good inside Insight oh
that's what I
want create a splash of London water in
front knocking enemies back unknown
mommy water
well me water
Mommy so is this new or was that in the
game before question mark I think it's
new
I think it should be new I was told to
get this one
has a
lot of
water it's new
oh I wonder what wait I wonder what we
can combine it with
[Music]
is it something I can already do I need
something else
or you see me
I've got the Deep Skies I've I know it
all
I have the info
okay we'll try that with we have two
more characters to try out we'll try to
answer key standby
let's get ready to ramble ask yourself
has a Diva song sense of flying musical
note in front
the the full concert for her
yeah because it fits so perfectly shine
a circle of brilliant stage lights
I mean the the pen lights
damaging old targets nearby for six
seconds
so wait the the those pen lines they
were made out of the
the pen lights obviously
okay so let's try for that and then the
whammy water
with secrets I'm not telling you yet
oh
[Music]
she's singing
she's constantly singing
it's nice
I like getting ghost in a wavy motion
that way and get a good range
you'll have to be so exact
ly this
[Music]
is but now there's still not many
enemies so you can tell me who's your
favorite like whole life
mascot
[Music]
taco
they are really damn cute
[Music]
yes
um
it's not exactly the mascot I meant but
friend
the blue axolotls
bamboo shoot thing whatever they're
called in English yes
osagi ssrb takodati
for ssrv
yeah yeah
okay so let's see every seven seconds
create a burst of song dealing hundred
percent damage
for every Target defeated in the last
seven seconds oh Plus
10 song damage oh that'll be really
strong later on
oh when we kill like a [\h__\h] ton of
enemies
[Music]
Shockwave
uh reduce time between attacks by 15
percent
[Music]
let's see how easy she will be to clear
the game
performance for each second while moving
oh plus two percent speed maximum twenty
percent and plus two percent Dodge
chance maximum 20 both Buffs loses loses
free Stacks if receiving damage
so they want you to keep on moving with
azuki senpai tomaruna tomorrow night
non-stop whole life story okay the the
stage performance is already ready I'm
gonna wait I'm gonna wait
are you ready
[Music]
like your dance ability a true true
and Idol song of course
you stand by that's just in character
down down
[Music]
okay
you want that all right incredible it's
possible I'm not watching the front
dogging enemies that interesting let's
see how that works oh
but upwards too yeah okay
splash
we can do a wet t-shirt contest now
um
[Music]
ATA
I'm really curious about the code down
below I want to see how it looks
oh that was fast
just bandage okay
[Music]
I want the limits everybody we also want
the nightly milk don't we
limiter next time I'm Gonna Get You also
I think
maybe now
[Music]
does not receive damage increase haste
by one percent up to ten percent buff
results zero percent of Africa takes
damage okay
okay that needs to be activated when
there's a little bit more enemies around
and it will look cooler
hey spilled yes
gotta go fast
like Ina's tentacle spin
[Music]
I really like Shockwave attacks it fills
me it feels me it makes me feel safe
I'll go for the pickup radio
mm-hmm
a combination of kiwawa and crony oh
Naruto
[Music]
yo when the when the game comes out for
everybody you have to also try out
kiwawa again okay guys promise me
Wawa plays differently now apparently no
no completely different but there have
been changes I've heard check it out for
me
let me know how buff I am now
[Music]
Lincoln Bob maybe it was Christian a
complaint last time did I I hope not
how inspiring
gorgeous
[Music]
um
ah
Divine exquisite
they look like they're dancing
tackle that jeans
oh trust me when they got down on the
Dance Floor
it's way more impressive than dead
they can do breakdance I've seen it
before
Michael that's your breakdance
they were featured in Just Dance and
just haven't seen it you just haven't
noticed
I'm still waiting for my Carnival item
for the mommy water but also the music
was with the glow stick right okay
[Applause]
gotta work on that one
I have to get one quartable item as soon
as possible
to assert dominance
[Music]
um
Awakening soon
foreign
[Music]
like some kind of pajama onesie like a
baby onesie
you know what the butt flaps
ah I need all of them
whatever anything is fine
what's up
trying to take some notes for when you
can play hold up here you can learn from
my stream
everybody is taking notes right
[Music]
I know some people are like skipping
this stream because they say they want
don't want to get spoiled but like
there's no sorry
there's not really anything it's a
spoiler
but okay you do you you think
you don't want to see it all right all
right you're missing out though
gameplay is spoiler
everyone who came anyway oh everyone who
was too curious for their own good
who just really wanted to
what's up in the game
[Music]
it just doesn't show up are they
maybe I missed it once but it just does
not show up
potato
I don't need to cut
come out here
them along
let me show you unlock it yeah yeah yeah
it's a base item base skill
I think
[Music]
yes I'm looking for boys
and ah
a
cute
boys
[Music]
yeah boys love is uh wait when you say
boys love is good I love it what do you
mean the item in the game or
please what do you mean why are you
trying to tell me here
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
water is ready when we need it
um
[\h__\h] it's almost almost 10 minutes uh
we're fine we're fine
foreign
[Music]
yes I saw it in that one instant okay
running away I'm definitely not built to
stay in the middle here
yeah
[Music]
it is unlocked down
okay
it's weird
when you look for a specific item it
just she just doesn't want to show up
but normally in normal gameplay you just
take what you get and it's fine
it's gonna work out wow wow they all
missed
[Music]
oh
she's gonna go for the nightly milk then
[Music]
oh God almost time for footballzilla but
like damage wise I think we're doing
enough damage it's just uh
I don't have what I want
um
thank you
there she is
cat must touch
yeah yeah
[Music]
there you go
boys laugh boys
okay okay now now we're on our way
to something amazing
I need to be respectful Senpai was the
first Home Live member all live streamer
that I've seen
be respectful
to my standby
[Music]
nice cleared away make
win
okay when I get the boys love of a fast
[Music]
should I go for the limiter
Max water yeah oopsie doodles
I've been kind of waiting for it because
I need to get up the book anyway
but yeah yeah
oh
that wasn't even that much
idle song
[\h__\h] I didn't move for one second
[Music]
Keep On Moving
oh
more nightly milk
I'm getting so much of it no
one two two
three four
old numbers all of them we want all of
it
foreign
[Music]
oh
glow stick
we're gonna get like two collabs at once
at this rate
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
politely
you're demanding that's not the way to
do it
[Music]
okay okay okay
oh please
please give me Michael up
foreign
[Music]
she keeps on like falling on the ground
and stretching
[Applause]
Big Stretch oh yeah she stretches
endlessly
oh no oh the clock should already be
dead at this point I messed up
[Music]
but it's not going so guys so and when
we got the glow sticks Max what
[Music]
um
if only the bunny water would go with
the glow sticks but no oh oh I have to
go down
ah
I'm gonna try
[Music]
oh
ah thank you lag it's actually helpful
there there there
ah
uh let's dance
foreign
[Music]
level UPS hate you this run yeah yeah
that's what I'm saying it's not it's not
me but it's because I ain't like aim I
aim for something really specific
oh okay oh no I'll take a free Idol
costume
book would have been even better
thank you
ow come on I might actually take another
another Idol costume
[Music]
yes there are new collabs welcome we're
trying to get one right now so stay
tuned
[Music]
or did I no no no no no wait someone in
the chat said that's because you got
mommy water not second no no no
no no no no we're combining mommy water
with boys love book as far as I know
it's fine
no no I'm not doing anything wrong
enough damage numbers
I could but it's fine
uh
okay
[Music]
clean this [\h__\h] up yo thank you oh
finally they're listening to me
finally now
roundings
how how how how how have we come so far
and yet
don't get what we want meow what
what
[Music]
give me give me the money give me the
money give me the money
whatever I don't care about you
I want the boy's love
come on
call myself [\h__\h] Rich
he's loaded
[Applause]
ah what was that
y'all go exploded and create an
earthquake
come on
call nine months
I cannot believe it
come on come on
wow
one more boy's love
okay that's fine too actually
oh my god oh [\h__\h] oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh let me just
get out of here no no no no no no no no
no no
I don't want to die now
all right
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
decided
at this point
I don't know what to tell it's not
coming
I'm getting so much exp and it's just
not happening
you never get up never give up
I was like oh at least at least that one
don't worry
don't worry don't worry guys we'll get
that one too
[Music]
but you know we have to get this one too
because it just does as we stand by so
much Justice
I'm so encouraged
I'm so cursed
we will use it against Amish
I promise
come onto the damage to the damage to
the damage
foreign
from the office uh
well bestie
[Music]
foreign
uh golden anvil
golden animal
got it
[Music]
first level book we won't see much of it
but
it becomes
Frozen singing a collaboration of voice
on [\h__\h] rummy water endless waves of
ice that slow enemies
oh
yeah I see the ice icicles I see the
icicles
you guys see what's going on
it's happening
oh mission accomplished so laggy on my
side perfect timing
yeah
I've been waiting so long
let's get out of that hell
or maybe not maybe it'll stay a little
bit longer
well we're almost done so we might as
well spam the idle costume
please slow because of my leg they're
all so slow because of the ice because
now right oh God hi hi amen hi
oh it's suddenly so much faster
[Music]
you can show them too
when you show off what I got what I
worked so hard for
eign
let's do a record time
kills all element RTA any percent
[Music]
really
did it oh
amazing oh
bibs oh
oh yeah let's bring home
lose Freehold coins every second if
whole coin is more than zero
increased damage by 30 percent and take
10 less damage
what
so this is if you don't want any coins
eh
do they really mean more than they are
not less than zero but again because it
can't be less than zero but
if Holocaust is more than zero increase
damage by 30 percent
uh so you have to combine it with some
items that give you a [\h__\h] ton of coins
and hope for Yago to show up pay two but
wait what what about like does it also
take the coins in your wallet uh outside
of the current run or only the ones that
you have
gained in that current run I would hope
it's only the current run
oh it's pay twins
yeah
oh damn it's a good buff but only if I
guess only if you already have all the
upgrades and all the all the characters
you want then you can take this and
yeah
you can say [\h__\h] the money I'm throwing
out the money out of the window I'm
gonna burn all the cash I have
oh
yeah coins is RNG too I guess with piggy
bank
wow we cleaned one once again we'll have
one more story this
the one and only top eye doodle soda
senpai
her skill her attack is a bright star
shoot forward with a spring star
and forward spread idle Wings is the
idle dream increase attack and healing
received by 50 for 10 seconds wow that's
pretty long
but wait should we go to the shop first
I have 50 000. oh
[Music]
what should I get
attack I can get several things when we
attack EXP
[Music]
oin
I'll get attacked too maybe
Opana
's there
oh no
easy
well finally my roster is complete
time
yay it's that easy sometimes
Maybe
I don't know
[Music]
get the Grove bro
increase the damage of character main
weapon oh wait there's only one level to
this one
oh okay 4100
[Music]
Maybe
the heel could be helpful too
and
take pickup range whatever
oh wait a second
what
salt and set the redeem menu I think
this is why what
princess and
Alex wait is it a Christmas outfits for
everybody oh it's just Iris because she
hates Santa she hates Santa Claus
a puzzle
[Music]
oh
no wait ah because ah because Iris has
no okay that makes sense also everybody
gets the key one
oh cute
we're fate oh my so cute
oh
I'm sure once she gets kimono they will
add her kimono immediately in the game
and then
the casual outfits ah
I see I see
oh
oh the Triton is kind of in the way but
cute she has a cat ears too
oh rapper of the cool the ponytail let's
go I don't want to see again
[Music]
last but not least kiwawa
and also the cat ears oh
is my castle outfit I want to buy it but
I have no tears at all for a myth
um
come on yeah
no I think it's only I've been told only
myth and Council so far
oh wait what I've been lied to quite
possibly Bamboozled there's Google
[Laughter]
they they don't have anything
what about
gen zero nothing nothing
okay okay so that's so special because I
guess you know just today she got
could call me debut I wonder if that was
on purpose
Easter egg
yeah it's just a palazzo so I guess it
was easier really yeah
yeah that's that that one's
easy
sounds easy to do but I'm sure they will
add some outfits to these ones the other
ones as well okay now we have one last
mission
I did not think I would be able to do so
much today but okay
it's been five hours but we have to do a
little simple
I don't dream Dyson bye
let's see what kind of attacks you got
and if she can help me survive let me
drink a bit more water
[Music]
[Applause]
since I got my hands more or less
freeing
I don't dream
brain's short yeah for now I know but
that's surely Gonna Change
[Music]
I wonder if there's any more collab
items I should aim for or if so far I've
seen everything I can see
I wonder
uh no no personal item here
wink
well then we'll go for the limiter yeah
yeah why not
[Music]
probably some weapon unlocks in stage
two oh yo that ain't happening for me
today I'll leave that to you guys if
that's the case
because oh there you go because I I I'm
not getting anywhere we're stage two
at least I was able to show it to you
guys that's all I wanted
okay so we have bright star increased
damage by 20
we look at the others later
huh
[Music]
moves around and tags enemies
anytime like will he be there waiting 20
chance to follow he might be around all
the time like Bubba
I just chill oh look at him walking
around so happily
it's a coin
it's so good oh my sister there was two
is that a bug was there supposed to be
two
Peter pet I wonder if that works he's
cute yeah
foreign
[Laughter]
chance to heal 2 Hp when defeated
okay cool
I want
[Music]
I wonder if we have time to pet him
playing Pokemon we have to be really
close right if it works
I'm pressing PPP so if you use the
button to do it then you can't pet him I
think
don't think so
idle healing when receiving any healing
enemies within 100 100 pixel are also
healed healed in quotation marks taking
125 percent
an X percent damage where X is two times
the Healer Mound
it's so complicated for my brain right
now but sounds good also especially
special what does that do again
I'm not sure I forgot
[Applause]
it looks beautiful though
[Music]
think about 10 seconds something
something more attack and more healing
okay okay
um more damage to everybody in range and
10 more healing or so or was it
something else
I think that was it
okay now we have two sides
[Music]
I am the Enemy No you're the enemy
oh we targeted the perfect enemy
that's exactly the one I wanted
yeah
[Music]
oh we can we could almost awaken it
that's fast
no stress girls we have all the time in
the world AKA 20 minutes
[Music]
oh okay nice oh
pushes them back too keeps them away
from me
ankimo just chilling
awakened Stars end with a burst
oh
explosion there and oh nice oh it shoots
them away too
so you
oh no oh no don't do that don't run into
them that's not that kind of a skill
okay Angel
[Applause]
okay maybe we can think about you know
other attacks uh how about I mean it's
not very I don't like but
she she doesn't know what it is
stands for
um
[Music]
bus
love because we love and it's about how
much we love traveling with buses
no
big basic language that makes more sense
that seems like something she would
reach basic language for English she's
just stunning studying English
[Music]
she's just studying English that's in
character okay
[Music]
basic language
don't get it twisted
go
oh ballet lessons
oh but a lot lessons both of it works
too
[Music]
beautiful that's so gorgeous that's one
of the most beautiful attacks oh
shots record are you [\h__\h] kidding me
also shiny or just one
I don't know wait no
no no no it's just triple no Chinese
never mind I thought it was a shiny
triple
normal triple it felt so special
I wonder if you can get a shiny in a
triple that would be insane
it's RNG swim it must be possible
[Music]
[Applause]
uh-huh
do we want them
the idle concert thingy for her as well
I think those are really really strong
they were it looked pretty powerful to
me
really infected and once again it really
suits her well
healing
um
oh I should do the idols it doesn't
matter yet
I look onto one of the strongest
[Music]
stars are repeat yeah they look kind of
weak in the beginning but now look at
them now
whoa whoa whoa
[Music]
song there you go wait is that what I
wanted yeah yeah
I think so
this is just it's
having a normal walk in the park
it's all normal
nothing weird going on here
um
so I need more water also I'm getting
hungry
foreign
[Music]
bad
it really wasn't bad I just had some
troubles like getting to meet
um like fully done
um because the slices were pretty thick
and uh yeah when I like took out the
first ones
like in videos and tutorials it was all
like they were saying it takes like
maybe four to five minutes and then you
can take out the meat out of the hot oil
but when I took it out like I don't know
after eight minutes or so it was still
like super red inside so I was like
what's going on why what am I doing
wrong
but in all those tonkatsu cooking like
tutorials that I've watched on YouTube
they all like mentioned the temperature
and I was wondering maybe I should buy
like a like a and call it
um
temperature measure wrap for the oil and
meat and all that
cooking
cooking firmer for thermometer
[Music]
and then it shouldn't be so tricky
anymore because if I can get it at the
exact
Ness that I needed to feed and it should
it should work right it should actually
be the same as in the video I would hope
I would hope so
yesterday too we also one day before
yesterday oh yesterday we also kept it
in way longer than five minutes and it
was it was still like a little bit
pinkish and I know people like they're
made to be pinkish or red even
but
but that is
not supposed to be like red you know
it's supposed to be
like all all white inside
[Music]
um
not with pork Oh
okay okay then my mom was like ah this
is
pork it's fine it can be red I like it
red a bit more red at least like at
least pinkish not red I guess
[Music]
Heavenly blessing and be on your way I
shall not hurt you I shall only heal you
wink
healing quotation marks
no mascots were harmed in this whole
cure playthrough
none at all
oh dear uh what
oh
I need to go back up
okay okay okay okay moving back up
[Music]
[\h__\h] you guys are so fast
I'm doing so much better than earlier
yeah
[Music]
it's a warm-up even though I didn't I
did warm up off stream for like
one and a half hours or so
I even kind of low-key missed a meeting
because I lost track of time
and then I was like I'm so sorry I was
playing hello cure
I lost track of time it happens because
like you know you failed don't get to 20
minutes and then you're like next time
next time we'll be the one and then you
start and then you can't lose it you
can't look at the time because like
there is no time
you get stressed and ah
it's just
I can't look at anything besides this
game and I kept on retrying like um next
time next time because I I wanted to
unlock the second stage before the
stream would start
so that I would be able to show it to
you guys immediately so try it again and
again and again and again
what time of the year
all right 10 minutes let's follow up
here
yeah but oh it was good no one was mad
it was just a small meeting with jenma
oh my God oh my God oh
[Music]
show me dead what
how
oh yeah
the [\h__\h]
how the [\h__\h] I was so shocked I thought
I was gonna die because I got too close
to her
you're sorry
[Music]
she's fine it was kind of a spontaneous
meeting anyway
more or less
could never be mad at me
it's a party glad you could catch it
yeah welcome welcome
um we're doing the last character now
we got everybody early on and we tested
out everybody
so far this is the last one actually I
haven't tried
yet but
I'm thinking I'll just do that in my 12
hour marathon on Sunday and you guys are
all welcome to join me on that one
I want to play some whole cure
during that
some other games too but
um
yeah
oh
first corner
here we go
beautiful
[Music]
oh my God
you guys ever go to an anime convention
where whole life challenge will be
present make sure to bring some glow
sticks we will be very happy about it I
know it's not so much to
like a part of
culture in
maybe non-asian countries to bring glow
sticks to concerts and all that
feels like I'm mostly
Asian country
culture thing
do it in Europe
um but do it and if you want to get
quinoa and color it should be orange but
there are glow sticks that can change
colors so that's actually the ideal way
of doing it adjust depending on who's on
stage
foreign
I'll make my own yeah you can also make
your own that's also possible
and there's like throw away ones and
there's also high quality ones that
called King blades
those are the ones I
I would oh God
uh I would recommend oh my God
[Music]
seems like sound intense
to import them though I don't know if
they're on sale in stock anywhere in
like Western
stores like I guess maybe
on Amazon
they don't sell them in Europe oh no
one whole life light stick
oh yeah that's that's a way of getting
them um I think so far whole life
concerts always had
um some kind of light stick in their
lineup as well for merchandise for
official merchandise
if I ever do a concert I want to do that
too I want to get I want to make a
chihuahua
merchandise
official light stick
of course only orange would be the color
that you could choose just kidding
though maybe I don't know I don't know
what's possible and we can do more than
one color I'll put that with the idea
why would you need anything else an
orange huh
take your entire stock thank you
rainbow
[Music]
oh oh they're coming oh let's see how
well
[Music]
it does again there was an accident I
would never call her that
her in a Japanese language
does often sound like a mix of of R and
D and L
um
so I totally get out like where people
coming from why they why they hear
the the D
um
wait I'm not sure why I got that one
because I guess we're combining the the
boys love sorry the basic language book
but it's the Mommy wants her again
because oh we haven't seen that much of
it yet
oh
yeah
oh no not that was I hate them so much
please no more please no more
I want to go back down please please
okay okay okay okay okay okay
I have the upper hand oh oh
oh uh
[Music]
healing even more healing do we need
more healing five more minutes yeah
okay let's do more healing we're gonna
safe side
um I want to say you know one thing my
mom was like really insisting on last
night and insisting on telling me
several times
she said because we were talking about
Game of Thrones
she said I
I 100
one on one
look
like Amelia Clarke
hear that hear that
[Music]
you're lying that's so flattered
very flattered and she said it's not
only my face it's also my expressions
and okay I can get that she was like
you're doing it right now but my
mom these are not as exaggerated
as um Amelia Clarke I have to say that
like in Game of Thrones I thought it was
fine there was however one movie that I
watched with Emilia Clarke in it when
she was like she was taking care of a
guy in a in a wheelchair I forgot what
the
oh [\h__\h] I forgot what the
um movie was called maybe you guys know
it
it wasn't very calm and insanely long
movie
and in that movie I honestly thought it
was too much her expressions
were so but that's just her but I
thought they were so exaggerated her
eyebrows are so funny and then she has
like all these um what's the word
folds on her forehead I can't reach
foreign
acting that's just the way she talks
like even when she's not acting like in
interviews and so on
it's so funny
ah I got it
oh yeah yeah oh wait what's this
I'm like crazy I'm insane what why did I
do that
yeah
for some reason I thought I was doing
the quavo
sorry it's been um five and a half hours
will count what I've been playing
Upstream
my brain is melted I'm on autopilot
and there's boxes up there really huh
oh monkey
at least we have one full level
and they are
um
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
yo those are really up high
where are you oh
not shiny triple
huh
oh
not bad it was worth coming back that's
for sure
nice okay
[Music]
oh I think that the golden Anvil is
coming soon
wait can we still collab it if it's
awakened plus one wait I'm so confused
um anyway just ignore what I'm saying at
this point don't don't don't even listen
to me don't listen to my Rambles oh God
coming
oh no oh no oh oh no oh no
oh no oh no oh no oh no
oh no
[Music]
we're fine
100 fine and whoever it feels like the
bread Loops are here too early
to get here too early
[Music]
should we increase pickup range maybe I
don't know we just do the headphones
[Music]
[\h__\h] right
was it already somewhere and I'm just
not seeing the eyebrow oh God oh God oh
God oh God oh God oh God yeah yeah I
make way make way make way for the queen
oh well I mean we don't need it
I was just hoping to show you more of
that one corable
not like I need it
I can win without any collapse if I
wanted to Pure gamer skill
s
maybe maybe if I say I don't want it and
I don't need it maybe then it will show
up
[Music]
why does it sometimes take so much time
to show up I I want to know the answer
okay oh okay it's time baby where is she
there she is
the crown found her
[Music]
where's she huh
there's all the bubbles protecting her
oh
shame where is she
has so much respect for me she tries to
stay away from me
foreign
[Music]
am I blind
there's no Anvil what are you talking
about
other
up there I just don't see it but I don't
think oh God I don't think we need it um
but I I can't afford to run up there now
oh my God
we don't need it
it's fine
golden arrows oh
but I also see a different Arrow oh my
God
hello
[Music]
oh there she is
you're so peaceful
Nagina
finally
I don't need any more of these
[Music]
I hope the map is endless because I've
been walking kilometers
it's weird like she stays so far away
from me
um there's more Bubbas than ever I feel
like
um but I'm like barely doing damage I
guess man oh god oh there's a fence
that's gonna [\h__\h] me up
foreign
get away from the fence
ah the Stars keep her away
I hope they're doing some damage because
it's like kind of an endless run
come on
kill him
should I just should download
okay
I was hoping to do some damage on her
too you know oh
[Applause]
um
did I break the game uh what
[Music]
come on
[Laughter]
Circle back
oh
[Music]
this is fine oh my God even the rats
have become huge
it's not just an endless run is this
what happens in
tonight like after you kill Emma
everything just spawns in in humongous
sizes
um yeah oh cool
did I just I just use the wrong mode
all right let's let's go see if we can
get the Anvil but now you can see us and
by the top number one Idol is invincible
no one can get there no matter how many
enemies are coming at me
[Laughter]
foreign
world no one dies
it's because she heals she doesn't kill
she heals
um
[Music]
is it impossible to kill Ahmed when your
Surah senpai
it's impossible
hahaha
one I know because the line is 20 minute
run I've ever had they just don't want
me to end today
is she booked
like she must have walked over my
[\h__\h] everything like a million times
the the lava
okay let me let me go see what I can do
maybe I can get my whammy water
um the basic language book
oh my God it's over there oh wait oh
[\h__\h] how do I make a circle
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
it was a long [\h__\h] Journey oh please
please kill a man please oh
oh okay I'm like actually so relieved
kind
[Music]
going on
beta tester finding all the bugs I'm not
sure if it is like how
I know I'm keeping them away but not
that far away like
I don't see on it but
there's so much going on
what a bug
Circle okay
I'm no no oh oh oh oh
ah
um no no no no no no no no no can't end
like this oh oh oh oh
[Music]
thank you salvation has come to me
[Applause]
this is a record I've never played for
so long before it's a record time
Hey where's my extra coins what the [\h__\h]
20 27 minutes
what the [\h__\h]
oh
my damage was all on screen you were out
running on it
what the action [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
YouTube
[Music]
got on it
yeah I even eat then I feel like that
must have been enough damage to take her
down eventually how how come
my damage really that low I don't I
can't believe it
legendary fight though I must say and oh
yeah we've got
um
we got all of them look at this
yeah
with all of them
[Music]
I got them all I'm so exhausted now
my son's gonna die I'm going around okay
I'm gonna do one more in the in the um
please I will I will die soon anyway but
let's see
I don't know
[Music]
that this is the Run no it's not
how do we survive maybe with headphones
actually but
[Music]
mommy water okay
why
specifically that one
foreign
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
oh it's going pretty well but it's gonna
change soon
[Music]
the shock wave really helps so
oh no
[Music]
oh
we need a strategy
is that our strategy okay
[Music]
oh no the new beans
is this also 20 minutes I wonder is it
always 20 minutes
I should have used that when it was more
busy
[Music]
always gets wrapped
oh that's not good oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh there's a wall there oh
[\h__\h] hell
um
[Music]
okay I got fruit
dance dance
give me something
[Music]
there's nothing bad anyway not quite
unless they give me that membership
thingy and I don't need that right now
wait can you oh can you get that even
though you don't want it like if you get
into one of those random boxes oh can
they just force that onto you and then
you lose your [\h__\h] coins I would rate
quince
oh you can drop it okay okay I never did
that before so I didn't quite stay in my
head that that was a possibility
[Music]
I'm surviving
oh my God okay okay
okay
a little membership of course
[Music]
yeah stay away stay away
maybe four
um
[Music]
I need healing just in case something
happens
[Music]
okay
the stones
walk too much into areas that make you
wanna give you no room to run away
okay I think this is the longest I've
survived so far but that's the drinks
definitely
cool
is that a bucket
should help a little bit
uh and
I
[Music]
focus on one weapon
and one weapon no bucket what's the
wrong choice
[Music]
I'll show you
wasn't the wrong choice I mean I won't
clear it I'm not saying I'm gonna clear
it but oh God
oh God
foreign
[Music]
okay
yo wow
[Music]
they're flying
they got wings now oh wait was that
pretty awesome
we're second I thought it was full you
sound guys mascot
huh
the Flying Fox but maybe it was put out
sometimes because they do fly it was the
monkey Santa okay okay
[Music]
wow
what I'm actually doing it
[Music]
foreign
you guys can see what kind of enemies
you have to prepare for
oh dear
[Music]
they're so cute
the [\h__\h] are they flying
mmm
[Music]
okay
this is like the final test to see if I
learned something today
um even body pillow
no one okay
[Music]
dangerous dangerous okay I'm gonna do
the really dangerous thing and go this
way okay
at least now I have a good amount of HP
[Music]
oh I'll get there I'll I you know what
my my strategy now is just keep on
circling this table
full or at least for now
oh oh oh uh never mind never mind
never mind never mind never mind
[Music]
[Applause]
Uber sheep I would go forward by sheep I
need more food
no there's a food thing right there
where the bombs are gonna land so that's
a problem
hey
no no
no no oh [\h__\h] I can't aim
[Music]
okay
different
oh my God if I get to 10 minutes that's
a huge accomplishment
[Music]
idle costume would be great too because
um
oh
[Laughter]
what well it was like there was a hole
there sucking them into it like a black
hole
Nummy
what was that what was that huh
I was just trying to like get through
the wall of um me with senpies
because there are some gaps there yeah
that was broken
stage a bit tricky it's a bit tricky
it's very tricky
uh
well
I'll give you one more uncle
I do a randomness twice
how how
did I do that maybe it's Destiny
I'm tired though I'm tired oh I'm sorry
guys I'm gonna end it here no need to
endlessly torture myself but that was
fun and
thank you very much guys
um we're gonna try Mooney fauna and the
updated kiwawa probably during my 12
hour marathon and some we can you know
we can try that stage a few more times
hopefully maybe we will get to clear it
at some point
but I hope this was a good insight into
how the game looks now
and what awaits you there what
challenges awake
we saw some new collaborations and some
new weapons and stuff and we had new
music too
hope you enjoyed it check it out it's a
fan made game for free
yeah Caillou as far as I know it doesn't
earn money from this but support them
tell them how how much you love the game
thank you for creating such an amazing
fan game that everybody enjoys it's nice
it's nice that that you know
a fan made game is being welcomed and
picked up so well by everybody
you can donate is that so I don't know
about that but in that case go go
go
deserves it
such a big update man
really big I I would only expect like
one generation at most but
no
look at this wow
okay so I'm gonna
uh what was that now and I will not read
super Jazz today because I'm tired but I
will however bless you with
uh it's been a while but I'm gonna bless
you with uh
rendition
of
the song that we kept on hearing oh
don't ignore that maybe even
um
maybe also suspect
oh [\h__\h]
hi it's a Mickey Mouse
[Music]
it's ending times
let's see where is my
um
where you are my
instrumentals
I've got oh there it is is that uh
that's suspect I'm gonna sing The
Originals I guess that the Lo-Fi
Arrangements I've sang the Lo-Fi
and other arrangements before
you curious uh there are archives of it
oopsie that's me why did I go here
shut up
I need I need lyrics though
[Music]
surprise
surprise nope sorry the hell is a
different in fact that's not what I
wanted
okay
you hear the new keyboard
okay it's been a while since I sang it
so there might be some mistakes but oh
also my voice is is kind of
uh rough right now but let's try
oh I'm gonna stop saying that
Moonlight go round candy gold I'm ready
to go love humanoid
[Music]
thank you
Everybody Clap Your Hands Up
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
who's there
foreign
[Music]
go down
hey
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you that was not perfect but
just wanted to give you guys a little
bit of music to enjoy
my voice is so dead
I got one more
one more one more
this one's a favorite from you guys
Mickey Mouse
I really need to go to an idol meeting
[Music]
tonight
I [\h__\h] up I was like confused
mama
[Music]
tonight
foreign
[Music]
upstairs
are you ready
[Music]
foreign
I gotta find myself
[Music]
are you ready
I'm so ready
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
thank God
foreign
[Music]
oh my voice is so [\h__\h]
oh
I'm dead
I am dead thank you forever
six hours of hold here in Connell okay
that's right
that's right that's exactly what I'm
giving to you take it take it or leave
it no take it
living it is no option hope you enjoyed
it everybody I'm gonna go eat the rest
of my tone Cuts now and tomorrow I have
a members only not sure what to do yet
oh no some game
[Music]
you guys can help me choose perhaps
maybe yeah
maybe you guys can choose
I'm making a new game or iron beats but
I feel like I want to take a break from
Iron beats for a little while
the skylines oh I wouldn't mind doing
some more skylines but we can do
something else too
um
we took a sign and for all the members
in here in case you missed it there's an
animated wallpaper that's really hot up
on the community board
um downloaded within this month
otherwise it's gone and it's the
animation of the this week's schedule
art
and the the weekly schedule is up to
uh when was it September okay this one
remember it's only tomorrow then call to
the land finale which I know I've been
told I didn't notice at the time but
I've been told that there's really not
much content left but we just threw some
sidesteppers so I I was thinking if
there's you know a lot of content left
and I'll just uh grind club members off
screen but I guess I don't have to do
that so I'll do it on screen
oh thanks
thanks
oh thank you for Super Chat
oh kiwama better than Taylor Swift oh
oh thank you thank you and then um I'm
taking another day off on Friday because
I I have something important to do and I
was thinking you know leading up to the
12 hour marathon I might as well take a
take some more breaks an angel of
Empires it's really happening this time
I swear I promise it's really happening
something crazy has to happen to not
make that happen
knocking on my table which I don't even
know if that's wood or probably not that
feels like plastic
um or metal I don't know
yeah
okay guys I wish you a lovely evening
yeah thank you Caillou for letting me
play early
um
[Music]
that's right thank you
oh my idol meeting
by idle meeting I'm coming
bye
bye love you guys bye-bye
Holo Ian gamer mic drop I'm out
[Music]
foreign