[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
cookies
okay I'm super excited
Yahoo
Mama good evening hello good morning
how are you guys doing
I'm so excited I'm so excited we're
playing garlic phone today with super
special people
talk about tonight
and Gothic fullness foreign
we have people from all over the world
um and I will introduce them to you
right away uh are you curious did you
guys see some hints on all the an OBS on
Twitter
multitasking did you see the hints there
were some hints there were a lot of
hints
for Apple no present to you my Avengers
all size team of the people who are
participating and then I want to get
right into it because one person will
only be there for half an hour or so I
think so I want I don't want to waste
too much time
let's go okay
number one participant please welcome a
James two
and he did a lot of artwork a lot of
cute animations and stuff for me already
a great artist with a very unique Style
thank you for joining yay
second person
who participate today is drum roll
please
eh
[Music]
a lot of fan art for me but also drew
the cover art for good as reflect a song
yeah the album the song cover is by
mozizan
I'm really honored to have muchisan
great artist amazing ideas thank you
next up we have
is participating last minute because I
realized in garlic phone you can either
do 10 or 12 people but not 11 people and
otherwise we would have been 11 so as
long as that person who can only be here
for 30 minutes is here Christina
Manzanita will be joining us well for
this time thank you for your spontaneous
participation
she made my emotes my memory emotes my
recent ones thank you
we have Mr or Mrs Oak proud welcome from
Brazil uh Oak proud did like really cool
like Simi semi-realistic art for me for
example for my
um World of Warcraft streams uh no no no
no no no no no no
uh uh Diablo Diablo speed
yes yes yes yes oh my God
really excited to see some of your
drawings and next up we have hopefully
we've been working drawing tablet
hi son thank you for coming again
last time I contacted him spontaneously
to join the crew but uh he did but his
uh tablet didn't work and later on we
found out it was just not plugged in
well hopefully this Vlog didn't decide
that's so fun and next up we have
he's the also the artist of my ending
screen of my current ending screen and
um is just really really an amazing
artist that I love the art style so much
oh I love Akira
foreign
[Music]
is participating as well unbelievable
yeah yeah
and I'm so honored to have her as well
yo let's go
these are your [\h__\h] Avengers oh my
God amazing Rosary did
um I mean you you guys are all probably
know those of these work but uh for a
hollow yeah she did uh for example the
artwork for the Country Roads cover
for example yeah
and next up we have also very very uh
big in the fan art scene
[Music]
he draws the cutest like animations in
like chibi style ever like every day he
eats out another animation he really
does a lot of stuff and they're so cute
so I'm excited to see what he draws
today
yes
and next up we have
welcome also the thumbnail artist for
this uh stream in particular thank you
for drawing uh I mean it was not
supposed to be that thumbnail originally
but I'm I'm using it and really happy to
have Anon because last time I think Anon
was like sleeping and was uh actually
regretting that he wasn't able to
participate he or she I don't know so
welcome this time
eat and
and I think now
we're down to two more guests guys
I wonder who could it be
well one of them is none other than
[Music]
you my dear dear Mama lonely she has
drowned millions and millions of artwork
of me and also Kelly very often too a
big takamuri shipper and and I just I
just love my mother she also Drew um the
artwork artworks for heart Challenger
and uh so I I love her and
last guest will only be here for like
approximately 30 minutes so who could it
be Saigon or guest I don't want to waste
so much time so let's just do it
[Music]
oh my God oh my God oh my God yes
the other artists who are participating
did not know about it until they joined
the garlic film room so it's a big
surprise to them as well
he will only be here for 40 minutes and
then uh he will leave which means that
Christina Manzanita will also leave
shoes since she's the last one who I
invited and you can only have 10 or 12
people in Garden phone apparently so
[Music]
um
we play with
um infinite time because uh I told the
Japanese speaking participants to take
their time to Google translate the
English prompts
[Music]
you're just going to
continue
[Music]
okay uh let's write my first prompt I
was thinking about this a little bit
um oh
uh oh it doesn't get shown
uh oh yeah this is infinite by the way
so wait let me know
[Music]
you guys don't see it
this is like my password
oh do I have the wrong settings
secrecy is on well will it um
how does that look
secret mode
oh well will I will I see it when I'm
drawing it though
did I do the wrong settings
let it be on it's more is it better
then how do I know what I'm drawing it's
like hard mode
we'll see it eventually okay
okay but the first time I will see it no
um okay well let's try it out uh well
I'll be riding
um
but now I don't now I don't see a
my keyboard if it's a y or a dead Okay
that wasn't that uh
okay
so is this someone the hook
is this a prompt from someone
or is this like being Secrets summer ice
cream so yummy
this is a problem
okay okay is someone ice cream sword
wait I feel like they're talking about
my sort
okay okay no problem uh I guess I'll
draw myself then
why is it so black and white what is
this
why does it disappear
what is this
I changed the settings it's not the same
from usual
pretty mode well I don't see what I'm
drawing
[Music]
but then I have to get everyone to join
again right I don't like this
foreign
[Music]
do it again
is it because I did custom settings in
here ah oh oopsie I didn't I
misunderstood that
infinite
uh but this way it should be fine right
turns all
this one is fine right
okay uh well wait I'll send the link
this is the normal settings right just
changing to infinite
okay links sending out links right now
but Twitter when they send links like
that it always like [\h__\h] around
your [\h__\h] sorry
sending sending try again okay
I
okay okay
[Music]
I think that one worked okay
um
okay okay okay
is there like Twitter DM groups is
anything that you can do sorry
no I have to infinite like I mean they
will have to do their best to be as fast
as possible but
um I have to do it so that they have
time for Google Translate
hi
there they go okay
[Music]
um
foreign
groups oh God damn it
[Music]
um
sorry sorry my son
hi
did I miss someone
did I miss someone I think I think I
sent them all outside
please check it out love it ah this one
failed to send I'll kill okay now I
think I got them all nine out of the
twelve
um
rosuri
Mama Lonnie and who's the last one
missing
okay let's go
Rich frog in the center of the earth I
kind of like that but we're changing it
uh so the one that I wanted to write is
a
um
[Music]
let's go okay now we just gotta wait for
the others
um
please
even even when the time is infinite
please don't use up like
all the time
[Music]
what what will be the first prompt I
wonder
ing
and you know I felt like you know Kelly
the game with Kelly would have been a
little bit too boring it's just so
obvious there we go oh hold on this
[Music]
whole milk on the usual weekend what's
the usual weekend hmm
all right
these These Are by the way uh artists
who are participating please mute my
stream while the lights is cheating
and okay this these are computers
supposedly and we are behind them
this is straining that's the usual
weekend
I kind of like this more with a time
pressure but uh we gotta do it like this
because otherwise we'll just take too
much time a cookie
okay
people will not understand this
because what the hell is the usual
weekend
two two broads of a description
ah
that's Amish
with colors it will be better uh
yeah that's that's Cali uh
that's gonna
and
yep
[Music]
cute
okay now add some colors oh I wish it
was more like a purple purplish color
gotta mix the blue with the purple
oh no
I know well this is this is why we got
all the great artists today so that they
can draw the good stuff
and I'll just draw this shitty eye
I'll leave it to you guys
um
okay I wonder what they will think that
this is what we're doing okay okay I
don't want to waste too much time is
because if this was a normal garlic
phone I I probably would be done by now
I can still edit but I already sent it
in
I already sent it in
carrying boxes
yeah if he would see this what do you
think that this is
this is Hollow myth yeah there's no Iris
in homo myth
yeah they they hopefully cannot hear me
uh they shouldn't wait what if I have
time then I'll add a head because the
top of her head was open
we don't want Cali's brain to spill out
scuff they look like scuff bodies oh I
guess so [\h__\h] oh well I will not I will
not edit anymore it's cheating Columbus
Movers
oh uh we will help you move from point A
to point B don't worry we can do it in
the very short amount of time
uh we'll only take about
two or three days
um to finish your move because we all
have broken bodies and we don't work out
at any time
uh Alienware logo on mine uh well like
an Apple logo or so could help out but
we don't wanna we don't want to cheat
what I feel like I feel like all these
great artists they will like take time
so that they can draw the best art ever
oh we're gonna get the best
illustrations except this stuff though
if you guys are
such time
we have four out of 12 now all right
four to twelve four to twelve
come on
Holo Cube oh oh maybe it's us
introducing Iris
and her
children I guess because it's more than
one Cube
one stops and edited
oh
we gotta be a bit faster than that guys
Hollow Cube Iris has to I mean I don't I
don't know ask her I was just assuming
because there's so many cubes
pray to the cube
or they could also think that this is
like a Christmas scene where we're
opening presents this could also be
something
um
I wish I could have set the time limit
uh for
[Music]
um
um writing prompts only like no time
limit for that but time limit for art
but I didn't see a setting for that
[Music]
um yeah
infinite is I guess too long
or they are are they waiting for no six
seven oh there we go we're getting there
oh no
yeah they want to make pretty eyes but
okay Papa can only be there for a while
well I know okay
I know
okay papa wants to go to sleep early I
think so we don't want to destroy his
sleep Circle
oh
um
okay I added something
but that still might be confusing also
where I think none of us is using Apple
but like what do you I could have
written the window sign like four
squares ah
what does this look like I've been good
at confirmed casual
an apple pieces considered a casual
casual thing
Emma would never use apple yeah me
neither
I'm just kidding my phone is well an
iPhone so
my my one on my phone my my private
phone is uh smartphone
okay 11 out of 12. I hope the last
person
uh knows how to submit
and it's not being like confused right
now and can't find the button to submit
here we go
describe this well that's me
eating ice cream as a cat
do this
cat eating
ice cream that's pretty easy
yeah yeah I think it's that simple
done
okay
Kiana rubs the ice cream shop you guys
have so much fantasy
summer ice
oh wait maybe that's the prompt they
reused the prompts that they gave out
before
I should write that down no no I will
not go back summer ask yummy summer ice
cream sword yummy
uh but if it was that they should have
drawn my sword me licking my sword I
think that would have been perfect
I know like people like to compare my my
sword with a popsicle it is not a
popsicle
let me be clear
it is not
there's no way I would be a popsicle
it's very sharp it will cut your tongue
I mean if that's the kind of kind of ice
cream kind of popsicle that you like
then okay
but be careful not to cut your tongue
we're waiting for one more person after
a story
come on you can do it Google translate
goes
[Music]
Google Translate
please there we go sniper armor riding
on flying geek
okay that is an interesting prompt
um okay
so this is me
yay this is my flying heart
and
this is my hand
I don't know if you can see my vision
already but
so this is this is my body
super hot body okay so on top of this
and
I could take so much more time but I
want to be fast I want to go bro so that
way don't waste too much time
this is my hat
this is another hat
okay
on top of this we draw Ahmed
with I guess a rifle
but this is difficult
yeah
it is
why do I start drawing from the legs
[Music]
oh I forgot the rifle oh well oh my God
this is so bad
laughs
musukasi
her thingy here this will make it much
easier to recognize her
well she's not a sniper anymore then
looks like sniper gouda no no no no no
no no how how
sure it's very obvious
you're her necktie and uh
you you
I wonder who came up with that idea all
right anyway it's a skirt skirt
okay
not now you cannot tell me that that
does not look like a man
I'm not gonna wait
wait wait wait wait
the Green in my hair don't forget about
that some purple
yo oh my God creepy help
to help me out
yourself
okay okay I'm done
I hope this is the worst
drawing that I've ever seen
gone on her back okay okay we still have
time uh
and that's that's a gun that
that that that is a that is a rifle
I guess
oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh okay okay
sniper performance timer yeah there is
no there is no timer unlimited time
because we got some Japanese uh speaking
participants slash non-english speaking
participants so
um I want them to be able to like
translate the prompts when they see them
go on Google translate first
foreign
but I hope everyone tries to be a ASAP
yeah for the next round if we can do
another round
and I will
um make the timer into like
maybe two above the normal setting two
there's like two settings uh after that
and then infinite I think we'll try that
out
um
I'm a grandfather and Kiana nah it looks
like
[Music]
um wait I guess all right now that I
will get it with what you've said
kind of does look like she's ground
pounding me and I'm just happy about it
well no I'm not going back because if
they see it oh someone went back again
and then they will take more time
I will I will I will I commit to this
piece of artwork I'm committed
clouds would have helped yeah yeah now
didn't you say it no no more clouds
no no I'm not going back
no
hey
um
[Music]
the one or two clouds add clouds now now
see we only have eight out of 12. if I
go back and it turns into seven then
they're like oh they still got time
no no
no background no if this was normal
normal garlic foam then I would already
be out of 10. No Going Back not on the
12 let's go
come on come on
let's grab the scene oh
why is the taco
not happy about being ah
this is like a kfp situation huh
because it they have something like that
going on there as well
the thing that we have with like you
know chicken
s are the tackle that she's scared about
that as well cannibalism is that a thing
that you guys have going on
enough feeding
what is that aura around Inna
um
yeah yeah
there's no Taco and taco yet
I mean you can definitely make takoyaki
without tacos but
I think the reason why the taco Bachi is
so scared and sweating is because
there's
Taco in it maybe his best friend maybe
his mother
maybe his brother
maybe his girlfriend
hahaha
no of course it's vegan takoyaki right
you're right just like at kfb vegan
chicken
don't worry
sniffing the screen
what what how did how did that look
what's the origin of that I wonder
okay
why am I sniffing the screen
maybe I'm looking at a
beautiful image of fried chicken
oh
I have to draw a nose though
if I want to make it look like I'm
sniffing
[Laughter]
uh that's a beautiful nose man
hanada
don't forget my fellas recently I've
been always forgetting to draw my own
feathers unbelievable I just want to say
I just want to remind everyone
[Music]
um
that my feathers are not an accessory
they are part of my body hair if you may
wanna
say it that way
it's actually pretty good
um
how do we know that this is a screen
though should I I don't
um this could be like anything
I could use the filling tool for God's
sake
[Music]
okay let's add some color quickly I
think we would still have time
we would still have time if this was
normal normal rules
what
how did I make it look like a monitor
add cables
but it will just look like strings
coming Apple try I will try it I will
give it a try
[Music]
let's make it somewhat pretty
sure okay and now that definitely looks
like me
um now
you're sure
because also be I don't know a
PlayStation maybe I don't know or hmm
what do you guys think does it look like
a screen now
like a monitor
um
I think yeah closer
uh maybe that could have some color
a logo kind of logo at Aces Maybe
because I got Aces right in front of me
hashtag not sponsored
okay
why though why wow I was like well first
you want to do well yeah no no writing
um
I don't see a lot of people who follow
that rule but okay
again
okay then okay
I don't want you guys to cancel me
new car smell
I really like the nose the nose is so
nice
please give me nose job I want that nose
just kidding I have a nice nose right
now too
so
figure nostrils
huh
you barely have a nose excuse me
look at all the whole life members there
are people who have less of a nose that
I have
quite the known
yeah not as much as Coco said by after
her nose job but still
um
cute right
have the least nose
[Laughter]
of all of the members
oh sweet
Aki knows
no no no no no no no
oh
Iris has a prominent nose yeah yeah yeah
well this is a well a matter of art
style
a matter of Lifestyle I would say
I mean let me write hook it Papa uh a
message so that he doesn't feel bad
about leaving if he has to leave let me
say
ETO
but while I have some time here
he got a need and look at it
okay I told him even in the middle of
the thing if if he needs to leave he can
leave no problem because it's like
a girl 11 P.M
11 15 PM right now
I respect that healthiness I wish I had
a healthy sleep schedule like that man
today I woke up at like 12 30 though
even though my alarm was set for 1 30.
I could have slept one more hour but I
don't know
I I couldn't sleep anymore like I I I I
I had to go to an idol meeting that was
kind of what woke me up the pain of
having to go into an idol meeting
then I went back to bed still tired but
like
I don't know
my cats were purring so I had to pet
them
I don't I couldn't sleep anymore though
damn it I probably take a nap though
afterwards because today I actually
admit that at midnight for me right now
it's 3 P.M but at midnight the hollow
mythical lab is had hold on Yen collab
is happening for me and then at two two
a.m I have a 2 am yes right after the
collab I have a rehearsal
and I don't know how long that will take
so I will probably have to take a nap to
survive the night
yeah it's it's bad time for me but
yeah these things are almost inevitable
let's go
girls like Christina lands Anita Style
eyes the way she draws eyes where's my
mouse where's my mouth where's my mouse
where's my mouse
there it is
and oh why am I munching Buddha wait
actually no it might not be Manzanita
because I see hiragana uh letters on the
left side
wait a second
don't be I I
energize it might not be between a
manzanita's art
um okay uh Kiana munching on gura
Kawaii
[Music]
Kiana eating Seafood
if I wanted to confuse the people that's
probably what I should put in yeah
let's see munching on a shark
to give them a little bit more of a
freedom
Seafood
I think I think if I were too much I'm
gonna like that she would maybe giggle
first you would be like
unless it's like a real
real like biting off her head Munch but
no way I can do that I don't have the
teeth that she has if I had her teeth
then I could maybe do that but I have
normal normal human teeth
sorry I can't do much damage anyway I'm
just nibbling and I think good I would
enjoy if I would nibble her head let's
ask her tonight
if she would like me to nibble her head
I mean
foreign
[Music]
that sounds like Google Translate
Maybe
stabbing
stabbing or am I stabbing someone with
ice cream what is this dream about ice
cream
what's going on there
[Music]
um
maybe maybe I stab ice cream with my
sword
okay
it's summertime yeah they're really
putting out these summer themes right
now
um
[Music]
how do I draw this
ice cream
ice cream ice cream cone
yeah
um maybe
pink
uh and then
um
[Music]
ah
I don't know how to draw poses
I don't have space for the head again
when I draw like that God damn it I
gotta draw the head first otherwise I
have no space
okay
um
for some reason I'll be just very very
angry
um
[Music]
okay
you should don't forget the feathers
okay the warrior in me is coming out
I don't know what the ice cream did to
me though I love the ice cream
hmm
uh how to hold a sword
oh how to hold the sword I just don't
know how to draw it okay
okay like that
sword
and uh
um
let's color it in a little bit so you
know that it's my sword it looks a
little bit like that and then with some
blue on the side
blue yeah
yeah there's some more randier and then
a little bit of a yellow here yeah
yeah what the hell are you guys talking
about
okay
looking looking good I wonder how many
people already submitted
uh what does my top look like
take some time to Draw Something Good
[Music]
okay
should we add some quick color
s
[Music]
okay
okay done almost wrapped that pen
[Music]
[Laughter]
scream
oh well we like the confusion we like it
two out of 12. these artists are
perfectionists
uh
artists artists probably don't don't
work well if there is no deadline I also
don't work well if I don't have a
deadline I need a deadline in order to
do things what about your lies if
someone doesn't give me a deadline I
will probably do it one year later
hmm
oh five one okay let me add them
one more ice cream and then I think it
will be obvious
yeah okay
or is it less obvious now
better do it in a day but if I have a
deadline then I often do it in a day
yeah
you can rely on me foreign
[Laughter]
by the way I prefer uh creamy ice over
like watery eyes like a popsicle I
prefer like like the creamy type of ice
like I guess wait how would you like I
said if you could say gelato
but gelato isn't all kinds of creamy
eyes milk face
cream milk milk that that dire they they
were dying right there that
you know what I mean
but oh
like water-based ice cream is easy to
make though I remember when I was
younger I would make
um like ice cream out of like juice
also do you guys know Volkswagen the
Volkswagen exists overseas
probably not but full swag is like a
children's yogurt thingy that we have
and I think like people try to make it
into ice cream by putting it into the
freezer and one day the the factory
picked up on that idea and thought it
was genius so they not Volkswagen
they thought it was genius and then
released an actual like
um version of uh like like the
Volkswagen yogurt that you're supposed
to put in the freezer
and they added like these these popsicle
sticks to it yeah they're really yummy
mmm
these things that I ate when I was a
child I should I should go out shopping
and then like just buy everything that I
was eating as a child one day
and then eat all of that in one day
um
you have no idea what I just said right
the there's a cake there's a cake that
um it's like oh
I'm a sandwich
wait I'm a hot dog
why did I why am I hot dog
hey
[Laughter]
oh what was I saying oh yeah there's a
there's a cake uh that is like modeled
after a certain kids show
and which is about an elephant who's
called Benjamin Benjamin Bloom hen yeah
and that cake is really yummy it's
pretty small but
there's this fascinating thing that you
know children's love it but also when
you get older everyone still loves that
cake
it's like the one thing from your
childhood that you cannot get over
I'm a hot dog ah
the chicken scent hey
now
there's a chicken sandwich
I guess a chicken burger wait oh this
could be a burger
[Music]
um
you don't want to eat a phoenix I told
you guys before that Phoenix says if you
eat them they don't they're not able to
revive themselves that is one of the few
ways
to basically kill a Phoenix forever
so please don't do it
piano teaching kfb employs integral math
whatever
it is
what is that prompt well I'm glad that I
got that another Japanese member because
they would have to Google translate that
and that does not look like fun okay uh
wow didn't
a big head for some reason
stick
one
is that integral mouth
[Music]
you sure
what is Instagram
needs a symbol what what kind of symbol
ah
how about
how about that that looks more
looks emotional man
that's the kind of map that I feared at
school
oh man I hated math so much I have like
real like from trauma about math
[Music]
I don't know about you guys but
yeah it was really traumatizing man
I do too yeah
bad math teacher I mean I wouldn't
necessarily say they were bad but
it was chicken how does the chicken look
from the back
you know
uh another chicken
I also had this issue that like
um I changed schools and
classes and all that so the teachers
changed as well
and yeah then like to change the
teaching style would also change
and that was just I guess also confusing
because like when I got to the point of
finally being like okay maybe I
understand that that's when
they will change but I don't want to
completely blame it on that it's just
I'm stupid I don't understand math
so let's be real
and yeah
okay beautiful classroom
beautiful
does it look like chicken so that now it
looks like chickens
cute
big fluffy fat chicken I'm done
so did you guys solve what this is what
is the what is the result of that
did anyone try to solve my my math
problem should I call Ollie
two two slash seven uh two two sevenths
two overslept
who's
that's a seven it's a two eh no that's
those are both twos the top there's a
it's a one and a two and a five and a
two
yeah
two two seven two over seven
two sevenths what does that mean two
over seven
all right but it seems like you all have
the answer good job wow I I don't even
want to try it
I'm solving it
it just reminds me of
sad times
um
with the 10 out of 12 on the top left
doesn't mean there's only 10
participants left or is it the 10th uh
thingy to solve out of 12 like two more
left or what
hmm
that's the round okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay
let's go
let's go tell people submit their piece
of art
I didn't expect this to take so much
time when I give them the infinite time
but okay
we'll see what we get from Dad at the
very end
[Music]
don't forget to up download after yes
yes yes yes yes yes will do will do I
will do no problem
yeah no deadline means no rush next
round we'll do some rest if there's it's
always been a full hour though I don't
know if the others want to do like one
more round okay papa will definitely
leave but if the others are open to one
more round uh I would be I would be
excited to do one more
I think they they are muting My Stream
right now so let's ask them when they
unmute my my stream hopefully at the end
yeah
yeah I'm not one more I want to do one
more one more will speed with move time
limits
thank you
and ah a setting where the timer starts
after half the people are done I I did
not see a setting like that now
yeah but we'll do one more of time limit
eight out of 12. we're getting there
guys
somewhere here why
there's nothing about gouda Kiana is
teaching KFC employees
although I don't know why I would be
teaching you math out of all things I
should be teaching you German or
Japanese or English
but not math that's it
[Music]
thank you
best math teacher
no no well I would be teaching you the
only things I can teach you the only
things I remember are like really the
simplest things ever oh my God and what
is this it's is it us wrestling
is it no or is this is this
because we don't
um do I look angry yeah the eyebrows
kind of say I'm looking angry otherwise
I would have said that this is like a
reunion scene but my eyebrows look a
little bit angry I don't look happy like
if this is a reunion scene then they
would definitely draw me like over the
moon super happy
uh but ah it looks like babies should we
do something funny
uh takamoni babies sumo wrestling
how about that
I am
ecstasy what comes uh out of what I just
wrote I hope someone draws that
so I think we only have one more drawing
left
the next thing is one drawing and then
we get the results
it's a perfect description right yeah
we're wearing like onesies too
adorable 11 out of 12. we're pretty much
there we're there guys we're so close
we're so close
[Music]
looks more like Chibis yes yeah I
thought we were just Chibis well we want
to create some chaos
[Music]
Teletubbies
is something I watched when I was
younger yes
Teletubbies Teletubbies
[Music]
I was in German though yes Teletubbies
existing Teletubbies exist in german yes
yes yeah I mean they of course it does
because they didn't even they don't talk
in the show today the only thing that
changes is the theme song you only have
to translate the theme song oh yeah
right yeah of course it could exist in
all languages
foreign
don't think so much just feel it
don't think feel
don't think
[Music]
ol Kiana and pickle are working oh well
it's like it's like office office worker
okay
working
[Music]
look like we're working
um
I could draw the computers again
okay
oh old old computer apparently
and then behind that
I guess
and mouse this is all that would mean
it's a left-handed Mouse oh well
okay
[Music]
yes
although if you say that you could think
we're just streaming maybe that was the
original idea and okay
does pakura have real ears too
I just follow that I don't remember
because she has bunny ears but does she
have
real ears too
yes okay
the logic
don't ask me about it I don't know
[Music]
oh it's kind of cute oh damn
maybe maybe we'll give her like an
office hairstyle
well now let's in order to make it more
obvious let's just keep it this way this
is how you quickly easily drop and uh
twin tails
you show yourself
uh but oh wait where where is the office
lady look [\h__\h] you won't see it
black
black suit yeah yeah yeah yeah
ah it doesn't look like
this one okay
oh well oh well I tried her head is too
big now so not much I can do about add a
carrot she's enough it's okay she's
trying to be serious no carrots in the
office
okay now
um
cannot focus at work when she is in the
same office
is pecora
this is the last the last of it so let's
just draw something cute
um
washing blushing blushing
[Music]
Michelle
pack ears ears yes yes okay ears
pickle ears I was talking about that and
I completely forgot them okay here they
are there we go
my hat
okay only one hat in the office no
cooking hat in the office
[Music]
oh here we have some more space so I
could draw like a suit
okay by the way I do not know how to tie
a a tie tie a a what what's that tie
tile next time next time
I don't know how I I like if I do it it
will look very very shitty
okay I think I'm done
should I add some colors
well I miss it and it looks worse now I
don't know the face shape was weird but
okay
you'll
have some eye color is like orange
yellow right
I should know
whatever I know
okay okay
I took way too much for this last way
too much time for this last one red
orange yes like yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
and we we are waiting for okay half the
people have submitted
business chicken I'm not a chicken
only five no six six people died looking
fine we're fine it's the last one the
last one
[Music]
oh my God
should I pick some things
by the way I'm left-handed but I I would
not be able to use
a mouse with my left hand because I'm
just so used to
I started out by using it in my on my
right hand so I'm just so used to it
glasses carrots glasses please
[Music]
well glass is all very versatile so
okay
glasses up versus out remember the time
when I had fabuki Senpai on whole and
talk and she gave me this
didn't it didn't she wait am I imagining
this
did she give us the glass of speech
I think she did
did she do it
wait did she not do it did she do it did
she say it
she did yeah some people seem to
remember it okay you guys have better
memory than I do
left hand Mouse yeah it just kind of
happened
from the angle couldn't do much about it
um
Reddit glasses but and I know the the
Reddit pickle five bought
pickle
well what happened what was that
what was that
sauce
oh my God
we're done ah this was okay
exhibition flow to learn from the
beginning I think the rest is fine and
okay let's go we start with Kiara Kiana
talking game with Amelia
little apple I learned yesterday that
Manzanita means little apple
I was hoping that they would like be
connected this looks like like a
cigarette now ah
hooker please don't misunderstand piano
is covered on by almond okay okay okay
no more Porky we're still okay rosary
oh
oh wait I look like Callie a little bit
oh but the orange the orange must give
it away
as expected
says that and thinks it is
okay okay well yeah kind of yes
oh that must have broken mom alone is
hard to draw that oh
well let's see was she crying when she
was drawing down
um
yeah correct hockey completely
disappeared though
yeah
correct you are correct if I would see
that that is exactly what I would think
it is
oh my God oh my God that's in like what
do you call that style
[Laughter]
foreign
oh cute
cute
oh cute wait can I hide the screen for
one second and see what happens if I
save it I forgot like if it's dangerous
no we're good okay
okay next
stop I saved it
precious album okay we start with a
prompt from Oak proud here at rest as
pecora oh
oh this was uh picked up by a Japanese
speaker I wonder what Google translate
did with that
Kawaii
that is Google translate good job first
of all
[Music]
cute
Manzanita sees that and that's
yes yes
I love Mama Loni's Chibi art style
[Laughter]
yeah hi it's easy and says
oh that might already add some confusion
but I don't
I think those two are friends perhaps so
they they understand each other I'm sure
there's some
um no not MP3 telepathy
oh
cute
I can't
I'm doing the the the the post the the
bun pose
it's coming
yeah we're back with our mama suit Mama
suit
mama
look at that
look at that I think that's how we
turned into business ladies
soya
funny
with fake lips as office
oh no oh no
no Google translate fickle oh
I'm coming wait wait he threw it the
same way as I did almost
come on
no fake lips though I don't think that
translated well
oh well Kiana and pekola are working
hell yeah I think that's the one I got
yeah yeah
[Music]
let me save it
I'll save it I'll save it hold on yes so
what's up
on to the next album let's go
what do we have cookie Papa's prompt oh
funny face cute
okay papayo
you couldn't have come up with a better
prompt than that
um
okay
no
I take it back I guess that was a good
Pro
foreign
[Laughter]
oh my God
calm down calm down Kiana
oh wow Emoji sounds so good
foreign
[Music]
haha
oh
okay okay at least we're gone from these
faces at least I don't have to see that
anymore
it's canceling your new monitor Aces not
eye listening
I always
listen Christina Manzanita you cheater
I'm feeling sick oh my God
there's no way you would know that I
have an Asus monitor and I never I never
mentioned that before if I have morning
I have also have a Samsung monitor
[Laughter]
oh my God
sauce
[Laughter]
is also very confused by reading that
Akira I think um does not speak Japanese
or English I think Akira uses a Google
Translate for both language and so that
might be troublesome
y'all
ah see
no matter where you're from no matter
what language you speak
we're all connected with one brain cell
so we play it again
sometime soon just this is really
um straightfor apart from what it
originally was supposed to be
[Music]
[Laughter]
very far away from the original but
look at Bubbas chaotic simple but simple
request
really did something nice
I'm sitting on her back sniping ah
oh I did not get this one but I got a
very similar one so also he must have
done the perfect drawing
I wish I could have brought it like that
[\h__\h]
that's so much better than my attempt
and there's clouds there's [\h__\h]
clouds
uh this is probably the best the best 10
out of 10 understanding that we've had
and then there's
a quick quick quick
Emilio of entering into enemy territory
on Kiana's back wow
wow Google translate hello it's a proper
sentence actually
from oh crowd where did the come from
noise yeah because Emma always has a gun
Emilia is riding on Kiana with a gun
I'm close to the original
Sky oh cute style was so cute
[Music]
where is the chicken don't don't make
this into something it's not
oh yabbit
oh no
it's so good this is so good
[Music]
I'ma with guns of a sword chasing a
Caribbean boy very specific very
specific
no misunderstandings possible oh okay
Papa sees that probably probably
translated oh God I think hookah Papa
speaks some basic English
oh yeah that's like pretty much the same
scene good job even
[Music]
let me save that one too
I don't I don't know why I keep on
hiding the screen just I don't know
because I I feel like
gotta be 100 safe although nothing
happens next one
um nickel Callie patting baby Kiana
interesting combination
the perfect person received this prompt
Ed
oh sweet
cow you patting baby Kiana no more cat
ears but that's okay
oh you baby bubble bubble bubble bubble
Kelly does look a little bit flattered
is giving baby cat a head pad so cute
and really uh describes it very
specifically
[Music]
no no that is very different
what happened it wasn't Google translate
oh then hookah Papa want to make some
trouble on his own
Kelly arm chokes Kiana Gone Gone Wrong
oh my God
so I'm not sure if that translates well
oh my God what
nevermind not Japanese but like uh
non-english speaker what the [\h__\h] is
that
what happened
epic playing wrestling ah now I get it
now I understand
[Music]
baby sumo wrestling
oh
God oh my God how did oh
it was hookah Bubba it was
[Laughter]
I like it I like the chaos more chaos
please
I need more
motor
next up
next is album
aha
oh cute
every time I see Anna's eyes I'm just
saying oh good
enough
yeah yeah yeah that was the same
sentence pretty much yeah okay okay ah
I love us art ah the one that I saw oh
of course I understand what my papa is
trying to tell me 100 you know feeding
tacodachi takoyaki oh really easy
oh yeah yeah
everyone understands it just too well
feeding takodati
the takoyaki is gone the takoyaki is
gone
oh cup noodles it turned into cup
noodles yummy well
have a problem with cup noodles do they
but they don't it's question my question
my question they don't know what's in
there
is this cute foreign
[Music]
is
oh how good uh Hyde is using his full
power weapons drawing tablet today
Ramen to a takodachi yes yes
I like the bowl it's very pretty come on
off until
craziness that much
saving okay
next up
we have Manzanita
when you come up with
that was you that was you
oh dear okay well this this can only go
bad
oh addon what did you think that this is
Cruella
um
[Laughter]
yeah it did look like we're selling
something or delivering something yeah
but actually it might be good to start
off with a very very generic wide uh
prams it might have to be a good
strategy to get something funny out of
it yeah
something that's not too specific oh my
god wow
thank you
I want someone oh my God
what kind of situation is this
oh I am selling laptops yeah oh my God
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm so sorry this is because of Me piano
selling gaming laptops in the Indian
girls
yeah now that I got my own gaming laptop
I'm like this one's really good go go
try this one now try try this one
food well that's that's an expensive one
uh
that's like 2 000 2 000 bucks
oh
God
I think I would be in theory I would be
a good saleswoman so I like this image
of me selling it to the girls
I can't even
increase nice
Kiana's showing off her new ladder yeah
actually
I see I see that yeah yeah yeah I'm like
hey I got a new pc look at it look at it
look at it look at this
oh they're like oh
[\h__\h]
but what is that it could look like a
drawing tablet what did hookah Papa
think that is
showing images yeah yeah it could just
be like a tablet and me showing like I
don't know sexy images sexy takamori
images
[Laughter]
okay okay okay wow
what happened to Iris am I showing
sensitive pictures
wait that's not I resistant
I fought because of the purple that is
Iris they both have a similar color
color scheme
they do actually
okay save it saving saving saving these
precious photo albums
uh next up
oh my God
how many do we have left we still have
so many okay let's go a little bit
faster
and Oprah draws
[Music]
yeah yeah but it was really just he had
a cat eating ice cream easy
I feel like he drew this before but
maybe it was with a hot tea a hot cocoa
I feel like I've seen her before this
exact drawing
ice cream
knock it off get outside
eating whole heavy and ice cream special
oh
that looks yummy on my face also
sorry
we we safely were able to escape from
the yabinas
and they're here now
yay
[Music]
so cute with lots of ice cream
okay today I'll be eating ice cream for
sure
I'm liking an ice cream land
oh it's like an ice cream Dreamland
Psycho Cycle
wow by the way to everyone of these
artists I hope everyone is listening in
if you wanna if you're if you're up for
another round I would be delighted but
if you don't have time you're welcome to
leave we can see how many people we have
left at the end a short round is fine
too
I'll I'll do the time limit uh
definitely this time there will be a
time limit this time
I forgot to say no I didn't I think I
saved it
foreign
[Music]
in front of the fridge ah
Google Translate Google Translate son
close close very close subscribe or see
or see
I need more of those misunderstandings
Google just Google things
next up we have well it's loading so
long
I think you have a connection problem
[Music]
that's why that's probably the that's
one of these pop-ups have been happening
do I have internet
you guys see me
wait did I last term is okay did I did I
crash garlic phone it
did any one of the other participating
artists save the others because I want
to see them
I wonder if there's any anyone who saved
them all
um
this seems like it's not gonna fix
itself
if anyone's answering me in the chat
maybe someone ah
Rosalie said she didn't save hers but is
it down for the other participants too
reload the page I don't think it will
come to this point
because the the URL is literally just
guardingphone.com book
on next there is no next album
cookie thingy I can't click on them I
can only scroll
uh
no I can't I can't do anything
click on the person I've been clicking
it
I'm cooking I can't try I can click on
home but yeah it's probably gonna
disappear
uh
is it is it is it broken for the other
participants maybe write me a DM one of
you guys
now can you tell me if it's broken for
you too or only for me
invite link
the invite link
okay I'll give it a try one second
can you if if your ungodic phone already
reviewing things
and someone leaves the group and then
someone joins it do you get to see the
album no I do I use the I use the link
and it just leads me to the main page
it's already over
uh it's broken for me too
ah it's the same forever
no
garlic phones phones for real
young
I wanted to see the others they were
free left free in the house
[Music]
we went through another round
we will do another round I cannot accept
this
Alyssa
what the hell
katana
[Music]
I know dude if anyone wants of these
artists wants to do another round I will
send you a link
oh write me a DM if you're up for one
more round
[Music]
if you don't have time don't write me a
DM refresh
uh reload side changes you may may not
be safe it's telling me that what
reload
no it just leads me back to the main
main page
is it back here
rip she today
oh is fine okay
no no
um okay we'll do we'll just slow no
normal
it's normal so let's do we did infinite
how about wait what is dynamic though
ah
this you were talking about the dynamic
option triggers the clock only when the
majority press is done oh
[Music]
Dynamic best
okay okay yeah
it seems good yeah yeah I know she can
say again
[Music]
um
was able to participate there's a bunch
of people who are up for one more round
okay I'll send you guys a link
everyone who's up for one one more round
please send me a DM let's do one more
yay
yay I'm sending the links right now
did I say send me a link sent me a DM if
you wanna do one more round
I'm standing out URLs IMA okay
[Music]
saved them all
wait
oh no
oh they say it went through
ah toscato they're sending it to me
and uh some others they stayed on the
site and it uh it refreshed now
ah noise
okay okay so some people might be
leaving but uh
one more
okay
ah I can't I can join the same link but
host would be someone else oh oopsie oh
I've already been giving out new pages
at it uh and I want to see
oh
oops sorry I'm really confused right now
okay the new one
New Link
okay so we have no Sony
oh the game skipped and continued the
album nice garlic phone is back to life
a new link
and New Link
and uh
YouTube
and one more
one more
and more
[Music]
oh we got uh six
okay okay
James two Manzanita
is also participating
foreign
[Music]
yeah now I think
uh
oh yeah
okay
now that would be everyone except um
amaloni and toke Papa I think after
multi-san joins
okay
yeah let's do one more
round
thank you for spending your time your
precious time with me the special guests
all right let's uh do one more round I
think we'll complete with 10 players out
so let's do 10. okay
okay
settings okay
please mute my stream dear participants
okay what are we doing I want I want um
yeah maybe maybe a broad
uh prompt is better than a very specific
one okay guys help me out
what do you want what do we want to see
[Music]
what do we want to see
um
[Music]
man again
okay
[Music]
but I can only rely on everyone else's
cool prompts now I hope they got
something nice
okay
I didn't I saw the time ticking but I
didn't think it would go down that fast
[Music]
wait I'm probably not the only one who
messed up then
no way that in that short time
the Japanese speaking participants were
able to
write their prompts
[Music]
okay well we still have time now
he
would approve this
it's square glasses I personally prefer
like rap big round glasses on myself
um
but
I don't know
um
maybe that's just my point of view and
from someone else
those kind of glasses I look stupid with
glasses glasses are indeed very
versatile yes yes we've had that before
fixing my jawline
okay yeah I'm done I think I'm done uh
yep done
grass is all versatile
I look chubby nah no way
that's that's just their chibi salad
makes me look a little bit chubby maybe
I'm pretty oh no you guys are so flirty
all the time
looks like I'm saluting
well anyway just this piece of art I
think there is not much you can
misunderstand about it so
not enough chaos
not enough chaos but the the prompt
doesn't give me much option for chaos
there we go
hi Mr King
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go fire in the background
that would be quite challenging my own
destiny
everyone proceeds to misunderstand yeah
oh yeah do people get a blank prompt
from me
or does that just get skipped totally
and then there is no album at all
questions
why what is this
in a desert looking for food
is
what I get from it but what is that
keeps you swearing
prehistoric
caveman it's Jurassic
how
because there's a diamond dinosaur
Jurassic how do you wear Jurassic
Jurassic Park no no I only got it from
you guys so I will not add it
yeah present the camping
mm-hmm
[Laughter]
oh um
[Music]
Will Smith balls do I have time to draw
the Will Smith balls
Will Smith pose is that how yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
hey
[Music]
I love space
[Laughter]
good God
this is so bad but it looks like it was
simple at least
let's give myself a suit uh how many
draw suits I don't wear suits I don't
know like that because you're just
uh maybe a sexy uh
a pencil skirt yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
this is me representing the new menu
um
what happened imagine it was you know
that kind of squeaky chicken the squeaky
chicken that goes like
[Music]
oh or something like that the polka
chicken the one that polka Senpai has
how about some
socks
long socks
long socks yeah
looking good okay
understandable have a nice day
let's see tomatoes
and some salad
mm-hmm
and Beak
that will not you will have to eat a big
too it's a bit crunchy but you don't
like it trust me
full
okay that's oh that's yeah that's a new
menu item
don't worry guys
this is not you guys this is a different
you guys are you guys don't look like
that you guys look chunkier
did you break your leg no
I said like oh
okay guys
we look more plump exactly
[Music]
looks like a chicken but it's not it's
not one of us it's not a kfp chicken
it's an outsourced chicken what is that
goodah
good on
vacuuming oh [\h__\h] no I'm coming vacuum
vacuum
eating
chicken and that's is that turkey I
don't know I was gonna get into turkey
because we don't need we don't want any
chickens to be eaten right
[Music]
back to meeting us in she's like it's
just like a vacuum cleaner you know
gosh what do we have here eating pizza
pizza I said that very German Germanic
pizza with pineapple pizza will sign up
oh hell yeah oh hell yeah
how about we used some filling tools for
once how about that
and we use it yeah
necessarily look like pineapples though
um
now it shows I feel uh I'm sorry
yo yo okay okay
yeah it looks like cheese
why is it red because of the tomato
sauce
I'll probably add this like as cheese so
the pineapples will look more like
pineapple
but I maybe I should make it like a
thick Big Slice
maybe that will make it more obvious
okay I don't know I don't know
like that
yeah
no no it's okay now it should be fine
[Music]
why am I just drawing the mouth before
anything else this is not good this is
not gonna I'm not gonna go well if I do
it like that
um
Pizza
what's your favorite pizza everyone
mine is a
mine is
um
pineapple pizza but I also like
[Music]
um
a pizza
last time I told you guys my favorite
pizzas you guys are really confused
why what is this face
what is this
fake God
it's not cute
I don't even look like a
like myself
[Music]
okay a hand here wow beautiful hand wow
we're not trying to throw masterpieces
here that's not my job that's the job of
the Avengers All-Star artist I'm just
here to be here I'm the host okay okay
don't put any pressure on me pressure
I'm just here
does it look like me
orange quick
quick quick
done okay
at least that pizza looks nice
but pizza looks good
the [\h__\h] is that thing
oh what do we have here oh
um takamori
[Music]
well good is eating chicken
but why is Kelly in that thing
baby
let's write that because it will make
for something more funny uh instead of
writing takamuri looking at good at
eating chicken that's so specific
okay
The Prompt in this round are a little
bit lacking
okay okay
oops oh I wanted another brush
you
you you you you you okay
okay
soda does this look like a soda cup at
this it does it does it does we'll be
fine
okay
that's a big soda cup if the if the face
is dead
small
[Music]
now my favorite soda is by the way not
Santa
although Cali says so it's it's not true
my favorite soda would probably just be
Coca-Cola
um or or like it's not a soda but I
drink iced tea all the time
also I guess laminate for example would
be a soda too I like diamond more than I
like Fanta
coke coke for today
no Pepsi or Dr Pepper also good
yo yo yo
okay
finally some okay inside
yep
how do my clothes look again I thought I
forgot damn it
should I just drawn my my blouse
because at least I have a reference
right in front of me
cherry vanilla Diet Coke oh whoa that
sounds so good
yummy
I never see that being sold anywhere
though
but this is like I don't know I want to
create more chaos
um
how to create more chaos guys
give me give me some idea
[Music]
oh
couple straw
I don't I don't really
[Music]
who is this
York
your choice
I leave it up to the artist's
interpretation to draw someone uh no
wait a second someone is gonna guess
this will text and not just draw seeing
that
anyway so I'll leave it up to your
interpretation
interpret interpretation please add
something interesting to this go it at
the first one to finish
hahaha
come on guys
foreign
Speaker gets it
um well then they'll probably just write
something like well Kiana is drinking a
a drink a Coca-Cola yeah yeah we're fine
we're fine that's okay
I'll see you in the chat
you're cheating
you shouldn't be in the chat right now
um
should I should I Bonk her into Infinity
into the usual room
M Speed yeah you're already done yeah
but but but but but but
you basically hear what I'm talking
about the art that I'm drawing
usual room for you
I just inhaled iced tea
yummy okay let's go
[Music]
let's go
why that's so cute so cute
but there's no room for a
misunderstanding here I'm inside
manoka session
[Music]
it's it's so clear what it is
very cute
thank you
yeah of course of course I said my
artist to the usual room too no mercy
no mercy you have to follow the rules
um I'm not going easy on anyone spare
Christina uh Christina has uh this is
not her first crime actually
I forgot I already forgave her once
[Music]
before
I think wait no she was involved in a
crime but was she the one who did the
ground I don't remember anymore
okay imposter why imposter
sauce
impossible
like that
[Music]
a knife
with some blood on it
um
let's fill it up with orange
and orange
wait how do they look like again I
forgot what they look like
Among Us
uh-huh
okay they do have legs
okay at this point Ina is already dead
it's a cute Flappy Wing flappy flappy
ear thingies don't worry
we'll color it purple easy to understand
you do this do that
and some bleeding
bleeding puddle
it's blood everywhere
[Music]
I would never do this
something like that my hat
you think it's not obvious enough okay
um
uh no problem I shall add my hat and I
will add the other hat UPS as well
we're looking at this from a different
angle right now so it has to be on that
side
oh my God don't
we cannot forget the blue part all right
already I could add her a little like
this thingy
the
angel Angel what do you call it again uh
Halo Halo
I think it's it's very obvious what it
is
um
[Music]
number one
okay I can lay back and relax yeah are
you guys looking forward to Holo Ian
garlic phone tonight later today for me
it's later today for me but for others
it might be tomorrow I don't know
but I think most of us are on the same
day yeah it's
hanging our first full collab with Iris
it's remember collaboration whoa
I wonder how chaotic that will be
normally when we're only five it's
already chaotic but
when we're six although iris is more
like a little bit more of a quiet type
so
maybe it won't be much more chaotic than
usually
however
however who knows how she acts when
she's with all of us
it's gonna be interesting
yeah bye
yeah virus
there's no such thing as your virus
no no no no no no no no only say soris
these these something something I
something word ending with i plus I wish
it's just too simple guys
that's not even a challenge
um
oh you don't know and what what's your
buy about Iris what did you say until
now that's yeah bye I thought she was
like super Sasol
have I been bamboozled am I wrong
what happened what did I miss sent me
the clips
say song she eats things I mean we all
eat things
oh man
there's nothing yeah bye about her
eating animals in Minecraft come on
ew already the level then
like like sends you into the yavai
group then that's just too simple too
easy
to kill the horse well that's like
nothing
that's not thing
[Music]
knowing that everyone is yelled by
anyone who
needed a baby the baby
[Music]
wasn't that part of the game what were
you done oh
okay okay that was much much faster
okay manually let's go
them
oh oh it I gave out the it gave out the
automatic front
oh well I guess that's better than
nothing but can we include some Whole
Life theme in there
Goldman
I might not be the only one though hmm
okay fat woman looking at a painting
yeah all right all right all right oh
[Music]
to me
pascara
[Music]
thank you thank you for reading the room
you saved me
Batman
just turned out more interesting than
many of the other
well it's
very cute adorable bad chicken s Robin
salad I
I
God
on it
ah I see what happened there she she ran
Robin's Army
Umi Tony is bound to happen
it's it's fate it was meant to be
Robin's Amity
cat Batwoman and I'm a robin yeah and hi
drums that like that what a nice scene
wow we look like we're ready for some
Adventure let's go
let's go
I will save this hopefully this time I
will not crash garlic phone
okay
next up we have okay I just actually
I will just leave it like that go
Ikea
those are that one was from another
story
okay I drew this
simple simple but very clear I think
intellect
okay uh Christina manzanita that is not
wrong but I am always intellectual
it's the teaching stick it's so cute
turned me into a teacher again
with a burger stick teaching us that's
not
and do you need glasses that is
hey
guys
what
do you need glasses let's let's sponsor
Adam some glasses
I mean the the the the green stuff
probably look look like salad leaves and
this looked like the the burger bread I
guess
oh no oh oh
interesting
well you know what this just makes it
better it makes it even better because
we get more and more confusion I'll wait
wait introducing the new kfb menu
probably next round oh it's YouTube
YouTube uh it's fine now okay we're back
okay you didn't miss much welcome back
everyone we're pointing at the pick on a
hamburger
what what is this
thinking about new Cafe that is still
not the not the prompt that I got
interesting
that was actually not the one that I was
thinking about nope it's the one where
I'm introducing the new kfv menu must
have been something else what happened
on on the what do you call the the thing
the red thing on top of the chicken's
head when you call that I think in in
German it's like a cam
or something like that
ah the gravy just don't worry I'm just
licking off the gravy
[Music]
I'll be back I think that's the one I
got
it no
it's just that obvious that I got the
same prompt probably from that
oh
yummy oh there's something again drawing
it much better than I ever could oh
again
Kawaii
it's it stays the same throughout the
whole time this is the one that I got
eating a pizza with one big spot no the
other ones are careful too but okay I
get what you mean I was trying to make
it more and more look like pineapple
slice of fire this is like basically
pizza or the pineapple you know oh you
know that meal
that mean picture Pizza on the pineapple
let's turn it around let's go okay
pineapple let's
go
what
how did you know
not the pizza tossed on the show
he knew it he knew he knew I wouldn't
just eat I do though I don't eat
pineapples um just like that sometimes
um
next stop
yummy pineapple pizza
you chicken Kiana
kinda cute
ah I can't represent the kida-san just
wants to
kill off chickens I think I see a
pattern in akirasam's prompts
it's not the first time he's trying to
kill off chickens laughs
oh that's a good one
[Music]
okay come on come on it's like an anime
scene
oh
did you actually wait was Jacob Burger
the one with the pineapple or was it
Phoenix Burger
I think I was actually Phoenix Burger
yeah was uh just a
pretty basic one I think
beef burger yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
wasn't like the Phoenix Burger was the
chicken burger with a pineapple
inside of it I think yoga Burger is
a secret oh it has a secret sauce yeah
yeah yeah
anyway oh my God
yeah
and for this we have to thank only
Christina for giving out that idea to
Anon
what a nice
yoga Burger it looks so realistic oh my
God idle company yeah
I love it I wouldn't eat it because it
scares me but I still like it Kiana's
eating Yaga Burger
oh my God wait that's a good idea
because you can like like grit with like
like you can print like something on a
burger patty by like grilling it with a
specific like shape thingy right that is
such a good idea we could do that on our
yako burgers at kfp
brand of buns yeah
y'all kids get the meal
what a great business idea I've received
from this game
yeah kind of looks like the red bird
from angerburn
what what is this specific prompt
the red bird you got the right person
for this prompt it
wait what why did you end what what why
did you add a mogul's
I think James too wants to play a round
of Among Us after this
she drew that scene it's so perfect
what so what
comes in neat
but on piano mongoose
[Music]
laughs
yeah that also happens that's also how
it looks like is that by the way is that
the like tongue of and a mogul's
character or what is that that like
because I think it really looks like
that in the game as well
is that supposed to be like a dagger or
a tongue I think that's supposed to be a
tongue yeah
load Among Us
Lucas
Among Us kills
Among Us oh
with my
foot my rainbow dagger it's a it's a
dagger version of my sword
my sword is a little bit bigger than
that so it's a dagger version
you guys are damn good I kept it quite
simple in comparison to that yeah there
there I am
foreign
thank you
the amorgo stream stayed until the very
end
we we all love Among Us don't we
Tiara okay
you read through that a bunch of times
oh
it is
[Music]
probably had to look up the designs I
wouldn't even remember either
it's a little bit of a different
difficult prompt oh I want to have Mochi
understands that
yeah
might not know about the ttrpg
characters oh
good save good save all ground I am a
preview for that save
We Are the World okay let's go
Eva ran all the time or was not sure
what to do with this
ah but James too must have gotten wait
that means James two got the r as well
I think so
dang
you too amazing
wow that that would you needed a lot of
fantasy for that
I've done it forgotten if I would have
gotten that prompted photo
wow
[Music]
guys no no they are not singing but okay
[Laughter]
very cute
session oh
we saved it we definitely saved it oh my
God that is so cute
no Siri has been giving it like 500
today I love it
so cute next one hide let's go could I
return too much oh
oh that's what we what we saw that's a
monkey okay why is there why is there a
dinosaur
oh
[Music]
and I'm just like
and a dessert
desert looking for food
[Music]
oh man hungriness yeah okay
oh my God don't leave a shark in the
middle of a desert there's like no water
she's going to die not only because of
being hungry but also because of no
water this is the death sentence of
Gouda
when you're hungry oh I don't know if I
should be flattered or scared
[Music]
lost in the desert Kuda is hungry
yeah she is I can hear her stomach
growling
oh it's literally guys that's only her
last name
[Music]
Akita
oh my mother
he did it again
[Music]
once
it's all too
Dyke
[Music]
foreign
members
she still died
the sacrifice was worth nothing
chapped rubs Halloween hats
that's the Cecil version
wow Rosary has such a say-so heart
she she doesn't think about the fact
that gouda has eaten us no no that does
not even come to her mind because she
knows we are tete because I would never
do such a thing
this is kind of cute
oh man why
to hide it was because of hide
I love it oh oh God I'm scared
I'm scared
I cannot be the only one noticing some
ulterior motive
ah
didn't I see the same scene but with
Cali in it
we're not eating chicken
yeah
why does this look so familiar to me
did he get to draw twice
I'm so confused
funny God I did right
whoa
wow okay
could I think why did I
I'm so confused
okay
[Music]
that is so cute I think I think he drew
something like this before too
good at eating a Elena okay okay okay
okay I'm still so confused about this
about this one
they did like get cut off but like why
did I mostly it's the one answering it
so I I didn't see that one
maybe he drew the almost the same thing
in the in uh in the previous in a
previous game
oh this is cute though this is super
cute
I love those those are really cute okay
let's go we have two more left Taco
money watching a movie in her room
oh
[Music]
we're probably watching Shrek I know
there's a shark here but we want to
track together so we're watching Shrek
every time every day it's just our thing
you know
ah
[Laughter]
I love that drawing but now I understand
piano it must be hiding yeah
stand on to it he just added Cali to it
you just
oh my God very effective yeah as an
artist as a busy and popular
on-demand artist you gotta work
efficiently you know
mm-hmm that's what he's doing and I come
up with this great idea of takamoni
babysitting gouda wait this really
changed already
[Music]
oh
my badoni would like this
if she's I think she's probably still
watching I'm sure she would love this
one
foreign
[Music]
because I was able to speak more proper
sentences than in the first five minutes
of her debut
I'm sorry for that sick burn
she just said ah even though she was
older than she wasn't a baby as a baby
something must have happened
shots fired
is is that that must be an automatic
prompt but even then I'm surprised that
something like this comes up
oh dear ah
wait how the [\h__\h] did that turn into
Kiara drinking a soft drink
soda how
you're not implying
okay
okay we're not there yet
this is so cute
how did we get to Kiana drinking Adele
Okay so
[Music]
how did they even I wouldn't even know
what that is I wouldn't even how do they
even know what that is like I wouldn't
know the English word for it definitely
oh my God
[Music]
[Laughter]
but it's better it's better this way
because at least there's Halloween
included now
a platypus is a what's what's the German
word for that
surprised it didn't turn into Subaru
yeah right okay I I did a thing there I
don't know if it even continues there
[Music]
okay well from the point of view of
Manzanita who is me let's see is it
Manzanita
yeah
you could have put yourself in there
hey you didn't take the chance that is
so cute
same soda
[Music]
[Applause]
that was fun thank you
wow we had um some interesting
interesting drawings in this round and
in the previous round I actually really
want to see the wait can I put in the
the gifts that the gifts the gifts that
they sent me well I'll just upload it on
Twitter the ones that we missed I will
upload that on Twitter them on Twitter I
cannot speak anymore if you guys want
more garlic phone there will be more
organic phone in
seven hours from now I think
yeah yeah yeah yeah we will be doing it
on all channels uh six point of views we
decided on that uh at the end so you're
welcome to watch it on my channel
[Music]
um
include some usual guests some fan
artists and some
not so much fan artists but my own Papa
okay Papa it was a huge honor to have
hooky Papa in this one thank you
everyone who who took their time and
even though I think for some of them it
was really really early in the morning
and yet you you participated thank you
so much we got some really cute art out
of that
but we also have if you guys want to
participate
um at the end of the week on Sunday I
think I'm doing uh members only a garlic
phone where my members can participate
yeah yeah yeah yeah well you gotta be a
member so I'm sorry about that but at
least some audience participation is
possible in that case so I'm looking
forward to playing with you guys soon
hope you guys can make it in but I hope
I hope this was um a little bit of a
funny stream for you guys very
interesting things came out of it
unfortunate that garlic phone crashed at
the end of the first round but still we
don't worry we didn't lose the we didn't
lose the gifts the GIFs it's all good we
saved I think I will quickly quickly
read some super chats
and then I will take a little break eat
some food and stuff I actually haven't
eaten anything yet I woke up prepared
the stream and then yeah
uh here I am now I'm so hungry hungry I
could go for some Yago Burger now
um hungry more stream of artists do you
guys want to see more like that
this time
um we only had what two two people who
participate uh previously before
everyone else was new and I still have
some ideas for other people who could
who could participate so we might want
to do it again once a month oh
don't forget to download them do you see
this bar I downloaded each and one of
each and every single one of them
[Music]
yeah that yeah yeah we're gonna ask
Tacoma
to participate next time
the last one I think I did
well if not then I just downloaded it
again
okay
yeah I hope you enjoyed it
that's what my other screen
[Music]
leaving that's okay if you want to stay
with a super chat rating we usually do
some tangenting and [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] and all that so you're welcome to
stay if you don't have anything else to
do
um
[Music]
I think because I didn't eat food yet my
brain is not really working
uh
oh okay
my brain is not like oh [\h__\h]
I love it actually I I really need food
uh
I only need food
yourself
uh
I feel a bit sick from not eating
oh my God
Oreo shake no Oreo shake doesn't fill my
belly like that
I actually
made some bread before the stream but I
couldn't fill it with anything yet
you know what that could be quick I'll
I'll put some salami in it I'll be back
in two minutes okay wait let me put the
chat on the screen at least before I
leave
before Ally otherwise I cannot function
uh
okay
I'll be right back
don't know
[Music]
foreign
hmm
I'm back
it's not so crunchy anymore as it is
when it's fresh out of the oven
but it's still good yeah
[Music]
breakfast
yeah breakfast and pasta
it's not my first time
I woke up at 12 30 though
I just took my damn sweet time to eat
breakfast
yeah
thank you oh
yeah just imagine I live in America
then everything I do makes sense perfect
sense
I'm just an early streamer
thank you for the membership welcome
hmm
yummy oh I love salami oh my God
[Music]
so many different kinds of salami on
this world and they're all so good
[Music]
um
hmm
sorry it will not take too long
for me to finish this food
sorry
where are you guys as surprised as I was
about hooking Papa participating I asked
him but I didn't really think like
when I asked him I didn't I didn't I
didn't think that he would really
participate
I was so happy
[Music]
I'm so glad you participated
I wonder how the other artists felt to
be in the same game with okay Papa
a freaking Legend
oh
[Music]
and papa always retweets my streams so
that wasn't much of a hint
um
[Music]
only was in the first round not not at
the end
um
what was I going to say
I didn't
I forgot damn it
you gave a Hint by saying legendary
artists but all of them were legendary
honestly I wrote special artists in in
um
in a plural because I felt like every
artist that's participating today and
last time as well though they're all
legendary yeah
we hook it up
but yeah I mean
I wonder how they felt about
participating together with hookah Bubba
I wonder if they were nervous when they
saw the name popping up there because I
kept it a secret to them as well
until the very end I didn't tell them
they found out the moment they saw him
join the room on the list
okay Papa
so happy he took his time to participate
yeah because this is oh yeah now I
remember what I wanted to say it's kind
of the first time that I like did
something together with hookah Papa on
my stream
yeah we wanted to play Minecraft in the
past but that didn't really work out so
here we are now
playing guys
it was inevitable it had to happen at
some point it's
hmm
um
[Music]
everyone
please check out um
please check out everyone's Twitter
every everyone who participated has
really really amazing art
so please check out their Twitter I
showed it all in the beginning of the
Stream So if you were not there and at
that moment please watch the archive
you will see there uh Twitter comes
there
Christina posted the Gibbs on Twitter
already
so fast
[Music]
also posted one I wonder which one he
chose
hmm
review the remaining ones
um
I can do that
foreign
[Music]
oh my God
okay okay
many misunderstandings here
now this one is Kiana cooking kfv what
whoa okay I'm like good okay cooking for
the kids because okay
I'll teach in case we had a new recipe
okay
[Laughter]
hey
I need to watch that again what the hell
[Music]
um
I see okay
[Applause]
what happened at the end
I have to watch it the first time now
hmm
oh
because he wrote in the usual room
[Music]
next one can't sandwich into a pineapple
Burger
thank you
can't be pineapple chickens
sandwiches in Kiara
[Music]
that is a hot dog I'm hot dog cute
that one's cute
not bad you make me very hungry here
sword ice cream so yeah what Anon
foreign
oh my God oh my God oh my God a slower
slower please
angry I can't I'm stabbing an ice cream
oh my God where did the ice cream go
boys oh
[Laughter]
cute
very cute
mm-hmm
maybe it was from hookah Bubba
that might have been his most detailed
drawing hmm
I want to see it again
the next item comes is from him
this one whoa
but hook it up I threw it so now it's
Canon no no hold on there okay okay
um
[Music]
thank you thank you for sending me dolls
thank you
[Music]
okay give me one more minute and I'll
read the Super Chat
[Music]
ah
a I know
mm-hmm
[Music]
some of you guys understood it just of
me being like ah
[Laughter]
a I don't know
what the hell YouTube
why
why why
[Music]
are you taking so much time how many
employees does YouTube have huh can I
Google that is that like public
information how many employees
does YouTube have
oh that's why you guys
you guys Susan because
like a joke like how how people say
Karen
the CEO is actually called Susan
oh
the complex has 50k square meters
of space and can house up to 2 800
employees okay just in the like main
branch and I'm sure that there's way
more branches
and and people working from home as well
working for YouTube
so it's definitely not just 2 800 but
even with 2 800 Man YouTube has it
YouTube has ten thousand estimated
employees
I feel like it's even more than that
but I mean
and they can House 2 800 but there's
only three people what kind of joke is
that no [\h__\h] way
where does that Meme come from
no no I can't read them yeah the one
that I was that you say Alex was using
was probably stream elements and yes I
have been reading it through stream
elements since yesterday but it only
shows the ones that came in ever since
you signed into stream elements and I
have the first time I signed into stream
elements was yesterday because I thought
that YouTube would fix it earlier but
they did not
so the ones from Saturday from the
waiting room stream and from Monday and
from Tuesday those are still unread and
I hope I will still get to them
I really hope so because I I really I I
don't I mean
it is they I will not read all of them
but especially the ones from Saturday I
want to read because they have your
messages about my dokumi performance in
it and I feel like a lot of you probably
wrote really wholesome messages
so I really want to read those
damn
anyway let's read the super jets from
today shouldn't take too long yeah
where does it start
um
here yeah here okay
oh [\h__\h] at this time I didn't write the
pins uh comments that everyone please
should add pink or red into the Super
chats if they don't donate in
um US dollars so I might be missing out
on some Maybe please let me know
soon tickets monkey thank you soon
I saw you put the stream up right before
I go to work and I sure hope I can get
back home in time to catch this one live
so good morning pencil and in case I
don't see you good afternoon good
evening and good night thank you oh yeah
today we started this stream a little
bit early
so I hope maybe also for the people in
like sea time zones I hope those were
able to watch the stream today
because the past few streams I was
streaming
um in the late evening on purpose
because
that's a Truman Show reference oh okay I
I was streaming so late because I
thought well Ina is on a holiday so I
might as well make use of that
um time slot if if you know wouldn't
stream
um at 10 pm my time usually then I would
probably make use of that time slot more
often
yeah
um
uh so normally normally I try to not
overlap but she was on vacation so I was
like all right I'll stream during this
time until she's back
um
I have to say
I don't understand
that criticism
uh because like I stream at so many
different times slots
today was very different from yesterday
and the streaming time that I was
streaming at yesterday is not not even
that different from what I the time that
I usually stream at
and I cannot make it
perfect for everyone so I'm sorry if you
couldn't catch the stream yesterday or
so because it was too late but
you can always watch the archive
there's always an archive you don't have
to you don't have to watch it in live
stream
there's always an archive and I also
just try to stream at a time that's
convenient for myself first and foremost
and and uh for you guys
to provide streams at like different
time zones
which is mostly either a stream in a
time slot like today
or in a very late time slot like it's
not even that late for me it's like 8
P.M 9 p.m 10 p.m something like that
salt salt
well if it doesn't fit one person but
then it still fits other people so
[Music]
now nowadays I like I look back and I
feel like if I want to always stream at
the same time then I might have a more
stable viewership now but
it's okay
because that would have put me in
trouble anyway at the time at the moment
where I moved from Japan to Australia
that's the moment where I would have
been uh effed if I would have had one
specific time slot all the time from the
beginning on
because I probably wouldn't have been
able to follow through with that now
yeah
without wait no I wink did you not see
it oh Australia
I have the most worldwide audience
I'm not sure about that
but yeah because I switched so many time
slots all the time
I guess we do have a lot of people from
a lot of places
Mrs worldwide yeah
I'll always be there live you just give
me a healthy sleep schedule eventually
thank you for trying to always be there
thank you but please don't don't force
yourself there's always an archive but
I'm happy to have you guys here as a
live audience as well of course
I love your tensions thank you
South America gang following me oh
when will the banner change
which Banner you meet my YouTube Banner
ah I wanted to make one myself a while
ago but it's like really annoying
because
you have to consider the different uh
the different sizes
um
uh like yeah so I kind of like also
I'm not good at graphic design so I want
like oh whatever I do it looks like crap
so at one point I was like guys please
help me
and you guys were very open to helping
yeah
uh yeah we should we should do something
but like could I recently got a new
banner and like YouTube profile picture
from Her Mama just drowned for that
purpose that that's really cute I really
like her her um YouTube Banner
well the previous bgm ever come back the
previous
do you mean
listen I can totally changed to this one
yeah yeah
the other one was just the one I had on
um randomly
this one is nice too
the intro medium oh that's that's
something
somewhere else wait a second let me you
know what for those thousands are
reasons I can try to dig it up again
is it this one
before
[Music]
no
I didn't
haven't heard it so forever I mean like
four forever
wait I don't I don't I can't I can't
find I can't find I have the Christmas
medley
what about this one is this with audio
oh wow
nostalgic
oh
my God that's so nostalgic
[Music]
I wouldn't mind
replacing the super hype fall guys bgm
that I have nowadays with this one again
[Music]
you're right
please replace
ha ha
huh
we can switch between the two depending
on what kind of stream is gonna happen
[Music]
really brings me back to the time I
spent New Years on my own just watching
you guys oh man it's okay I was on my
own too like I was at home streaming
that's all I did
oh that's nice all right I'll I'll try
to use it again it's really nice I
should use it again
it just makes you feel at home doesn't
it
ah
I'm gonna cry
please meatballs you know the Christmas
one and the Christmas one is really nice
too but guys it's freaking summer time
this one is so pretty though
it is so pretty
oh
[Music]
that really makes me feel
oh my God
this is so beautiful
it's so beautiful
[Music]
the fan made this version
I'm so beautiful
[Music]
foreign
use Christmas music recently
[Music]
so cozy
she has been using it all the time oh my
God she always uses Christmas music why
nothing is
Monday
it is jingle and these her default bgm
is Jingle Bells
no
nice everyday Christmas hell yeah it's
more lively oh
yeah my name is
[Music]
but that's why we probably will never
see a collaboration between Corona and
Iris
just kidding just kidding I don't know
why I don't I I
don't mind on Santa when I'm I become
Santa and give her presents
he'll change her mind
[Music]
oh yeah we could ask her uh
you know what you know what I'm gonna do
in the holy and collab every prom should
I just you know when I say for example a
prom like an image where I just feel
like good at eating like salmon
I will I will add Santa into every
answer that I'll just be trolling the
whole time how about that so that it
reaches Iris 100 percent
at some point so I would write instead
of good at eating salmon I'll just write
Santa gura eating Christmas salmon or
something like that
but then every time every time I join it
will always be about Christmas now maybe
I shouldn't do it all the time maybe
maybe only for the first prompt but then
there's no guarantee that it will reach
okay no I should make one prompt that
that is very clearly about Santa that no
matter who follows up on it will
definitely always add Santa into it
so in my first prompt it will be
something like
Iris getting a hug by Santa or something
like that or Santa stalking Iris or
something like that oh hell yeah oh hell
yeah that will be my prompt I
know it will be
it is
[Music]
on the ceiling fans oh very good can I
remember I have to write that down uh
Santa Claus talking
uh Iris on a ceiling fan
that'll be difficult to draw though they
might they might
um mess it up until Iris receives it
let's just hope she receives it early on
nice all right
oh Santa Santa gifting Iris a ceiling
fan oh that is wonderful that is
absolutely that I have to write that
down I don't have anything to write
right now
I have to remember Santa gifting Iris a
ceiling fan that will be my prompt Santa
gifting eyes the ceiling fan Santa
gifting iris is ceiling fan remember
remember it
Santa
all right
um
you know what I'll keep this music
for the super jet reading
alrighty tell me if it gets too loud
because like now it's really quiet but
later on it gets really loud
where was I oh yeah I wasn't Felix
zowell's super Chad how they got tangent
so much thank you
[Music]
thank you
and fake or Fates thank you
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
it's Sonos tiles are great yeah
look akita's Twitter oh no
oh no thank you
what is it
[Music]
oh
wait wait thank you for inviting me to
play together thank you but my friends
call me Holo yeah Nemesis that's a big
mistake that's the latest painting
forgive me tanto
[Music]
about their participation
is right he's writing garlic phone
instead of garlic phone he must have
picked it up from me or she I don't know
which one it is
[Music]
foreign
of course you will
take it
son is writing about like how happy and
honored he is to have played together
with Juke Papa
because he really likes his his work ah
kitten
wait why am I already tangenting again
cute all right all right all right back
to Super chats
[Music]
is
any more Among Us ah I mean at some
point
maybe yeah
I'm sure I will
Callie oh I think she will participate I
haven't heard anything about her not
participating
I think she would have told us
[Music]
hey
she put up her reservation well there
you go yeah
I shall do that soon as well
[Music]
because thank you for the pinky haven't
been able to catch many of his streams
live lately but I've been enjoying the
vods glad your trip to dokumi went well
and I hope and hope I can make it to a
future con you attend I hope so too I'm
sure you will I don't know where you're
from but we have a lot of conventions
coming up in America one uh this weekend
I'll be on one convention I mean not in
person but I'll still be there and it
will still be convention exclusive on
Saturday there's actually a stream for
it too but you have to have a ticket in
order to watch The Stream So it's not
free of charge but still I think uh an
option for anyone who really wants to
see it but cannot be there in person
Megacon Orlando I think yeah yeah
Calgary Calgary
uh sorry I don't quite remember if that
was in Canada or in America but we have
a list somewhere of our of our
participation so I'll be in person
Orlando really
yeah that's so cool
that's so cool please enjoy and be
careful and take care of yourself but
have fun
hope you can meet up with some uh whole
life fans there
try to socialize
[Music]
too bad you're not going to Toronto yeah
I really just chose randomly to be
honest because I don't really as I said
I don't really have any
um connection to any of these cities
yeah
I I wasn't sure like which one to choose
and I wanted to also like spread it out
a little bit I didn't want to
participate in every single comment
because I knew it would take up a lot of
my time I don't know how Ahmed does it
I really I really aspired to have the
the energy that amen has I mean I guess
statistically I still have the longest
uh mostest streaming hours
but I have a feeling that ama is just
like a machine yeah she does so much
she so often has two streams in a day
she does also a lot of gorilla streams
[Music]
um she's very close to my streaming
hours I just do really longer streams
and she does more streams but shorter I
guess
oh she uses time travels she cheats so
bad oh that makes sense
[Music]
I
foreign
hmm
Modern Problems require modern solutions
and she also just has so many original
ideas like original projects very very
original streams unique streams recently
she's been doing these like reviewing
monkeys and reviewing what was it like
what was what was the other thing she
did
bug review yeah what's going on you yes
he thinks outside the bar of the Box not
the Bugs the Box
bugs and sea creatures yeah
I I I really wonder like how she thinks
of these things
end up reviewing chickens
she kind of review kfp employees
Pet review yeah I'm planning it but yeah
but like I'm it does it just so well
I really really like her ideas yeah the
classical music stream too yeah
yeah
so
I don't know if you guys uh watch I'm in
streams but if you don't then do it
because I think you'll enjoy it
um
[Music]
oh yeah the 3D streams as well
do that but then I would have to you
know get
um
it's a 3D model and a suit and all that
to wear at home and get all the
technical stuff and all that I was
thinking about it because I may kind of
talk to us about you know
stuff that she got and I was thinking
about getting it too
[Music]
but yeah I'm getting it on my own
um I wasn't so sure about it and it's
just more than that like I don't even
think I can set it up on my own I don't
trust myself with that
um because I I can't I can't even
broccoli set up a monitor sometimes
and I can't even change a [\h__\h] light
bulb on my own that's a joke I can't do
that I can change a light bulb on my own
but the whole 3D thing seems like next
level [\h__\h]
yeah so I will wait until cover the
sides to help us out with that
what if the light bulb is really high up
I actually put princess because now I
have this new apartment and all that and
I'm getting new things
uh the whole time I purchased a ladder a
while ago I have my own ladder so no
problem I can reach the light bulbs no
matter how high up they are
[Music]
just be yourself yeah but I mean it
would be super dope too like be able to
do do those 3D thingies that she does
even if it's just like a chibi version
of myself
that still would give me like
some opportunities that I didn't have
before
[Music]
thank you for the membership thank you
welcome
[Music]
yeah
I just wanna the things that she thinks
of man and like she prepares all these
artworks and all that for for it
um
I just don't have the space in my brain
to organize so many things because I
already feel like I'm handling so many
things juggling them
um and if I were to get like to
commission so many
backgrounds from artists for several
streams that are probably only going to
be used once or twice and all that yeah
and whole talk as well you're you just
reminded me I really need to start uh
planning out Hollow talk for next week
you help me
all right let's read some chats
typhen Bank Ison
[Music]
s17
thanks for the red super chat thank you
poor ice cream it deserves a red super
chat from the usual room
all are you currently in the usual room
junkie chunk
I don't remember why I put you there but
I guess you probably deserve it
thank you for the support thank you for
watching today hope you enjoyed it
lots of lots of us are
well you guys have to be
more careful and reflect on what you've
been doing
oh thank you I didn't thank you
Frank Ocean it was very nice today thank
you
I'm at random Koreans since you also
have phone talk yeah I guess I guess
like
we have a little bit of a different
style I guess
a script to download all Super Chat
messages
from what day do you need them
script to download them all
wow
like
what do you need to do that just the
streaming link
but does it also download the ones that
came in before the stream started
[Music]
from pre-chat because I also get a bunch
in the preach at the actually the the
Saturday theme was pretty much only
pre-chat anyway so yeah there was no
actual stream for that one so it would
have to be able to pick up the the
pre-chat as well no preset yeah I
thought so we have to wait for YouTube
to fix it it includes pretense I can
take the links from your channel yes
if it works then please do it and send
me a link on Twitter I guess
because I I don't know how to use
scripts probably so if you can save them
in a word file or whatever and send the
word file in a I don't know link on on
Twitter
that would be amazing
um ah but the Saturday stream is
privated
uh wait
I can I can provide the link for that if
what you say really works then I can
provide it
[Music]
um
does the script also work on private
extremes that you're not able to look at
just by having the probably not um it
must work with unlisted links though
right
[Music]
foreign
language where do I change the language
again
[Music]
that's dangerous
but
by just acquiring the streaming link
no no I'm not gonna run the script I'm
not the one running the script
[Music]
I wasn't planning on running the script
foreign
do it and then put it in like um public
doc file uh like on on Google Drive or
whatever
and then give me the Google Drive Word
file you know what I mean
or Excel file I guess Excel axle Excel
then there is no danger I don't see a
danger with that
[Music]
foreign
well I'll I'll just give I'll just give
the unlisted link for now it's just a
black screen for nine seconds
and then see what happens just by giving
out the link I don't uh there's no
danger so
um just for now uh yeah
and then I can still ask my manager
yourself
[Music]
oops
that works right
that Lincoln
don't wait is that
is that unlisted now
is the link on listed
it's private god dammit
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait
uh that was the wrong set and then this
this one should have been fine huh okay
refresh now it should be unlisted
now it should be understood
[Music]
foreign
which one is that
which one what the hell which one is the
unlisted setting
huh I need to change the language to
English otherwise I don't know
anything here yes go back
YouTube Studio where do I change the
language again
[Music]
foreign
yeah I know it's the one that says
unlisted but my YouTube is currently
Japanese
YouTube please
no the kanji for unlisted is not too
hard ah there it is
but um it just makes no sense
okay okay I changed it to German German
[Music]
sorry I have no energy today
that's why I'm probably a little bit low
energy right now
okay let's get listed
okay
[Music]
now it should work
save up for the collab yeah I'm
definitely gonna take a nap anyway I
still have a lot of time for the nap now
it should work okay then do your thing
and um
I would really appreciate it if it
actually works out that would be amazing
although I cannot believe that Susan is
taking so much time
[Music]
stream elements super chats now thank
you for your help Yoda school you'll be
you'll be a kfb hero if this really
works out
[Music]
oh manager son said she will help me to
download the link later so I don't worry
it will be safe
we'll be safe
[Music]
where was I JMT
in the case
[Music]
perfect material
wait which one the one where I was the
hot dog
foreign
you're talking about
because I don't know what else
you could be thinking of
[Music]
I can't I can't remember anything when I
was lying on the ground or so
at the Funny Piano face the funny faces
ah oh God the faces
that that might have been the current
most cursed thing that came out of today
those faces
I have to say though that was that was
high quality art
amazing they really showcased the
artist's skill
thank you this sluggeria I will not
release that dakimakoda though never
surgeon pendulum thank you soon
uh Ezekiel Ramos thank you sir and um
the sword is the way to go really hurts
the teeth when you get shotgun pellets
in your game meet
foreign
you prefer if I cut the meat with a
sword
because if I shoot it but I don't I need
the context for that but if I shoot it
then there's there's
pellets pellets you mean the thing that
comes out of the gun ammunition
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
hunting of a sword is better than
hunting with a gun hmm I wonder what
Tiara would say about that I think Tiana
does not agree with you this little
Arena but Kiana does Kiana's choice of
weapon is a sword yes Choice a weapon
however is a gun or a rifle or whatever
anything that shoots
[Music]
um I wonder what would happen if you put
Tiana and Kiara in one room would they
like each other at least they both like
verbs so
we both like birds
he likes she likes burps Alex boobs I
don't think she particularly likes
chickens but I like chickens and birds I
like owls
ah
we both speak verb the language of the
verbs yeah
I am boob I can I can turn into any
animal as she wants me to be
we might like each other then
yeah maybe Titi
blackford's
thank you for the pinky a whale of a
Time
what are you trying to tell me
thank you for the support foreign
[Music]
gets converted into USD so I'm not sure
was this was this really a pinky it was
probably a red one no
does someone know if the one that suika
sent was a red one
yeah it probably was okay thank you very
much
I appreciated
thank you hope you enjoyed the stream
today see you in the next one I hope I
hope you're doing fine please take care
of yourself
lovey fluffy chicken
[Music]
Anonymous 247 and thanks
for the chat oh you're back
thank you as I expected I got home super
late tonight and I have an early meeting
tomorrow morning oh no so I guess I'll
see you tomorrow in the archive that's
fine too very busy businessman huh
anyway it was already a blessing for me
to have heard her device Voice once Live
this week have fun with the artist thank
you thank you I have lots of fun with
them this was really cool I'm so glad
that we did it and last time it was just
supposed to be you know a spontaneous
thing to invite one artist but then I
invited a full group of artists and that
turned into this stream so yeah
I like this timeline that we're living
in
it's it's like
like we we often do like collaborations
with other YouTubers
and we often do like like streams where
the audience can participate but there's
not really any other times where we can
really showcase fan artists that much
on a stream so I think I have found the
way to do it
yeah nice
thank you Felix yeah good luck and have
fun
don't overwork yourself okay
always take time to take a break every
once in a while when you need it
[Music]
then Jackson FB dangers should imply to
this video when oh I have no idea what
sound the Platypus makes
I will try to find out
[Music]
breaking new grounds for stream ideas
hell yeah
art competitions
mm-hmm
well I was thinking of
um
doing something like that before
um like request requesting Kiana fanart
for a contest
but I don't know I don't know I don't
know maybe one day
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
Christmas Version yeah
I now that I listen to it I realized I
missed it too I just thought it was
illegal to play a Christmas version of a
song in the middle of summer
but here I am doing it and I have yet to
be arrested
I have I have I don't know also somebody
has not tried to arrest me yet even
though I've done a lot of things
we keep on getting away with it guys
[Music]
thank you for the pinky I guess probably
a probably a pinky
convert it I suppose
it's always Christmas here at kfb when
you're streaming Kiara sincerely cave me
and the broken thank you
ah sweet
I have to say it's the same for me
every day every day feels like Christmas
there's always so many sweet people
whole some people surrounding me
and there's always presents
thank you
like half of you to go though
less than half a year until the next
Christmas
so this year I hope
maybe we can exchange physical gifts
between the girls
oh
I hope so
maybe we can do something like that
oh
let's hope for the best Christmas
[Music]
were really funny though like drawn and
written reasons last year actually
everyone came up with such original
ideas
I really like the ideas
the hats that Cali received
I think Cali receives that one right
with the the drinking the the straws and
stuff
I really like those
but your arm is present to you know
with it
oh my God
oh man ah Halloween is something special
yeah
[Music]
dancing
and Ellis thank you
hosting a whole life mama papa garlic
phone oh
[Music]
yeah
good it would be difficult to get all
the time zones working though
because even without Mamas and Papas we
live all over the place
um
yeah but it's a cute idea definitely hmm
Star Master I already read the ones what
what fine what fireflies
ah
the waiting room link has no super jets
in it oh [\h__\h]
I mean yeah I guess it doesn't pick up
the waiting rooms after all
the pre-chat ones
damn well at least at least we can save
the other ones
in case YouTube takes another 5 million
years to fix their issues
then at least we have the ones from
Monday and Tuesday
yeah but I I Won't Give Up My Hope yet
just yet not yet
never give up never gonna give hope up
never gonna let Hope down
please
and wait there's a Korean Daniel
let me guess is this is this is this
violet
translate Korean I might be wrong just
guessing
no it's not Kim Kimbo
thank you so much
thank you for the pinky
hey boss I was happy to see you enjoy
your trip well surprise Cafe from us
made it to the meeting group yeah wow
that's big inspiration to fly the next
con you're at P.S my friend finished
your drawing last week but I got excited
and posted the day you flew out
[Music]
foreign did I not
favorite it
if I missed it I'm sorry
but I'm not now I'm curious I want to
see it
but yeah flying out to uh Germany from
us
that has quite a dedication wow
wow wow but guys you don't have to do
that okay don't don't don't don't don't
do it
that's like really expensive and time
comes consuming
maybe uh especially like in America
there will be I'm sure there will be
more opportunities I missed it ah maybe
tweeted at me again
instructors instructions unclear
definitely time consuming yeah
but but I think
um like I was very honored and very
happy to see that
um
anyone who came to docomi
definitely
experienced a very very special moment
for takanasi Kiara and kfb that we will
all never forget
[Music]
so thank you for the pinky Wiki Tunes
looking forward
to just tweeted at me again
yeah
dude thanks for the pinky cool room you
have there what's your drawing
bro
all right
I feel like you should still be in there
look meme dude still needs to be in the
usual room for a little while longer
but no wait I remember so it was
something about chicken
something chicken related
live sentence Oh yeah right
did she get a life sentence nah nah no
way
was it a life sentence
did you get a life sentence
[Music]
you got the life sentence why is it
writing in past tense it sounds like he
escaped there's no way to escape though
there's no way he could have escaped
he's still in there don't worry forever
don't act as if you're enjoying the
usual room that usually the room is
torch out for everyone
[Music]
um looking for the top donation
your message like makes me think that
you're not Slowpoke but you're fast fast
poke and already like like try to wish
me a merry Christmas 2021
in advance
[Music]
where is the fast poke
already giving me presents and saying ho
ho ho
[Music]
2002. thank you for the red super chat
yeah I dream of gravestones today my
friend said it's just a dream but I
should send super chats just in case
it's too late
I think he made a solid point
so glad I was able to catch some of the
stream live today it was really fun
can't wait to watch the archive for more
drawing thank you I I feel like like
right now as well I feel very exhausted
so I'm sorry if I wasn't that
entertaining today but at least at least
all the art was entertaining right
um and thank you for coming and enjoying
and don't worry it was most likely only
a dream
you still have a long long beautiful
life ahead of you I'm sure
[Music]
thank you for coming today thank you
I like thank you as well and don't worry
about missing it the stream is ending
now so you can watch the archive
yes yes yes I'm gonna leave now because
I'm so exhausted for some reason
I'll take a little break and I'll I'll
see you
um a little bit later I still have to
make the thumbnail though all right
[Music]
there you go changing your name
immediately fast poke really fast thank
you
yeah oh yeah looking forward to that
bye bye everyone and in German we stay
healthy dancing
[Music]
like I don't I can't even move my mouth
yet that's why I've been stumbling over
my words so much
my mouth is like
[Music]
I I don't know the word for it
and my face hurts
bye
[Music]
bye bye bye thank you
thank you you lovely lovely people for
joining today
hope you had a good time
bye bye
[Music]
foreign