[Music]
good morning afternoon evening everyone
tacos chins chins all over the world k
k hello there's no s check so we can go
back to Mario oh H hurry H hurry hurry H
he was saying hurry hurry wait wait wait
wait chill chill chill you know chill
are you sure yeah we got the world to
say no no chill first of all we should
like you know introduce ourselves no not
introducing but like saying why we're
what are we doing you know that we're
the same room we's in the same well I
can't say why here
yet it's a mystery big
mystery you guys will find out soon
enough though I think soon soon and then
you'll be
like you it will still not really make
sense why I I came here though like it
it wasn't necessarily necessary was it
NE not necessarily necessary but
necessary no bo I wanted
TOA has come to Ena house a my first
friend my I'm the first visitor you know
you didn't watch but the rock right no
but when I tweeted out that gift of the
party hat and the in the art that's
exactly what happened where bii invited
her friends for the first time to her
house she didn't know what to do so she
was just
like there was none of that here that's
exactly what happened no that's not what
happened there was no poop I mean I
tried but I was like I have to clean
that up
after yeah well we can um I I have I
have lots of things I would like to talk
about with you w talk
about and but we're going to probably do
that if we can if we can multitask while
playing this game I mean you got to meet
two people in my life that are very
important to me yes oh you want me to
talk about that now I I this out the
tangent right now chy is curious a quick
early tangent early game tangent that's
they're used to it I'm like 30 minutes
in talking fun gladly U especially
considering how short this game is
anyway we want to do it in two streams
not just
one uh yeah I met Ena Ina
parents mama papa Pap which is rare he
was like on his way on a business trip
and then we had to go nearby the airport
today so uh we're just like oh yeah M
can drive us there so I know M
and's fine I know I know we're not you
used to call mea but's fine when I say
mama and papa N I have to say enan or
daughter daughter daughter and M picked
me up and mama was very nice she's she's
really sweet she's a quite the mommy
she's a
somebody said she's
fabulous I don't know if I agree that
she's cute she's cute and fabulous I
know and and yeah we talked a lot and
they're they're both really curious and
I I I think they like me of course they
do they seem like people who who who are
so sweet they would like anybody
do I mean I think so especially since
you know I don't have any
friends no not many IRL friends me yeah
not any IRL friends they're like you're
bringing a friend over to your house it
does does mama watch your streams
sometimes does she ever did she kind of
know what who I am yeah of course of
course she knows a lot about um I don't
think she knows much about Advent yet
cuz she hasn't really watched their
streams as often she knows about like
promise and of course myth a lot about
myth yeah Mama is very sweet papa is
very sweet we had conversations and mama
nie she will cook for me yeah I think I
don't know tomorrow or the day after
tomorrow I don't know I don't know if
it's going to be tomorrow or the day
after tomorrow but she will cook for me
yeah she's her food is absolutely
delicious I mean you already have mama
food in your fridge I do you do that
that's from
Costco that the meat stuff it's from
Costco and what about the the red stuff
oh yeah yeah
yeah okay that's not really F it's like
side dishes that's so M food yeah but I
didn't try it um yeah so I'm I'm I'm
here for a short time M um getting some
something special done and then I'll
return home to to austa soon but I
thought I should come to to Ena because
I want it was really last minute to all
she was just like everything spontaneous
she just like hey AA can I come to your
house I'm just like what I I said I I
mean I can stay in a hotel too and
you're like no no come to my place I'm
like there's no way that I have a house
that people can stay in it's not like
I'm going to tell you to get like a
hotel
air okay if you ever come to me you can
also stay on my guest bed okay of course
well I bought I bought an air mattress
yeah the air matress is comfortable okay
that's good the blanket too very
comfortable that's my softest blanket
it's nice I'm so proud of that blanket
it's cozy it's very cozy that's the
blanket I sleep with when I sleep on the
floor H the floor blanket it's my floor
blanket oh there's so much we we could
even just do a zon stream but um
maybe we can do after one level we can
do one tangent okay okay all right I
have some notes by the way on my phone
too you do so we won't forget things
she's taking notes so this is a local
co-op only game uhuh and I'm Toad and
your Mario Mario can you give me yeah
give me Mario voice they're just going
to say it sounds like Michael
[Laughter]
moose it's difficult to do like a
differentiation mom mom
there we go that's Michel loose there we
go
yeah
more I wish it was like Luigi cuz like I
Envision you more as a Luigi I'm more
what Luigi yeah W Luigi of course
[Music]
iigi and sadly it's Mario and Donkey
Kong but you can't even play Donkey Kong
instead you play toad in I can do toad I
got toad too Amed does a really good
toad yeah she's basically toad she she's
toad reincarnate yeah you'll probably
hear um toad impersonations throughout
the stream and we have kind of like a
hard
uh deadline of ending the stream yeah we
have a we have a meeting in like two
hours well hour 50 minutes so maximum
two hours but tomorrow we'll continue
the game and probably during uh during
the normal Ena hours tomorrow yeah yeah
yeah today is not normal Ena hours it is
definitely not I'm taking a nap by this
time if I'm not streaming yeah but we
had a another interesting thing to do
before the stream that's true yeah
because some else happening someone else
came to visit very shortly yeah but it's
not a not a
member I don't know if we can say yeah
so we'll we'll we'll we'll say the Z for
later I mean it tells it tells them I
don't think it it says anything about
what what we're
doing that's true it just makes it more
mysterious like what the what what what
but yeah we can keep
it
about I doubt would come here there no
he SP to like LA right like not for he
wouldn't come for this probably no
yeah but oh they they already
guessed but but I don't want to I don't
want to say exactly who until you know
they're out of the vicinity okay okay
okay okay okay it's
F yeah okay okay then let's get started
with the game um Ena has no idea what
kind of game it is I have no idea I was
just like K was just like we're just
going to play yeah and I was like okay
okay I got it on my switch I have no
idea what it is yeah so we'll see yes we
have to play it cuz it's only local COA
okay you can retry you have to press it
cuz you stopped it wait Did that no oh
wrong button I'm to use to Playstation
controls right
now uh yes oh no uh yes we have no
progress okay we are we
retrying yay ah oh
jump and jump jump is B and D what is
that grabbing I think grabbing is ex
like top both of them oh both of them
okay and ducking okay so you see there's
uh two keys I think the the silver key
is only because we're doing Co-op oh
pick up and throw objects okay we got to
try to get those keys I think you could
always try to get the golden key and I
go get the oh I got a gift can I go
down what's the question oh I have to
grab this like this oh and try to get
the hey T get what' you do
no I have to get the silver
key you also want to come up here I
guess so can what the what are the
question mark boxes on the right side
what's this I I don't know oh my door
what about your keys I need the keys two
keys it's the same door come up here oh
wait no no no no but then I have to I
have to go can you climb with that I
have to go on the on the trampoline and
then you also press the okay I'll press
it for you
oh
who is so cute okay I have to press oh
no no no you have to press it oh where
do you jump on the should I be
there but then aren we stuck I can't
aren't we stuck though what if I'm here
too spring jump okay
now we did nice first rle already
struggling I think we need a bit longer
than 2 hours for this we we have
a we're both a little bit tired so there
a garbage can ah uh the capsules are not
a must to get I think but they're like
you know an extra like a collect
collectible I can't believe it climbed
onto wait what the there's another gift
clear one oh no the purpose is to get
the toy but we have to get the gift
collec yeah and we ignored the rest of
the level we didn't get the gift oh well
well let's try to get all the gifts so
we spend more time with the game all
right we we go back we you okay ooh this
[Laughter]
T foret
me of course oh let me I get that
quickly the this one at the gift okay I
got confused T taco t taco t Taco Taki
okay get over here yes you go do your
thing Mr
Mario oh wa so what what are these ah
tutorials yeah all right I'm
I'm I teleport
okay let's go okay there's the blue one
I don't know how to get there though
okay let's not get the the doll yet cuz
it will stop everything oh you have to
grab the grab this oh whoa I can do
handstand I can walk in a
handstand nice gift oh you can pick up
and throw enemies but now we now we can
just go I mean yeah we can technically
do that you you jumped on my
hand I
do
nice okay wait so these small small mini
Marios Donkey Kong had his eyes on them
yeah but we are taking them so that he
can't have them I guess I guess he
destroyed the factory and exploded
and Donkey Kong it's just like that
where it like all flew across the world
and you got to collect them all I don't
know
in yeah the the little be is that like
Dragon Ball no the bead bead like I
forgot what it's called but it like
split into shards cuz cuz shards okay
they collect shards she shot it with the
bow and then like you go around the
world collecting the
sh no idea all right what are we doing
here let's go up there's a
hammer it's exactly there yeah
there's another one oh ghetto and stop
it okay nice one key
ghetto what's next
yeah a you have to go down and then get
the get the get the gift gift and then
you can get the key ah stop you
little two keys you got gra can only
have what's the oil though oh okay okay
the oil well you shouldn't uh touch it I
suppose
really oh it's time limited they went
back up there oh can you get the silver
one yeah and then I guess just come down
here come Ina come here okay easy nice
nice so easy wait is there one more gift
in the other room yeah yeah yeah
the blue one there it
is
MHM all the way
up you we need I wonder if we need that
trash
gun I'm
scared you hurt me
too let's go and then can we go go
down that was
fun oh I can break this destroy
Amina It's Hammer
Time go up
go we got two of them yeah they're so
cute nice I wouldn't mind giving them to
donkey con no only one he wanted
everything I've noticed that like cuz
this game is originally really old
back then Donkey Kong was still treated
as a villain nowadays in newer Nintendo
games or in the movie for example they
treat him more as a friend oh there he
there he is there he is here he's a
villain evil monkey oh wire Spin and
jump he was just
misunderstood
how woohoo yay GI woohoo give give me
the
gift oh that's rough how am I going to
get that gift is there a a red
button there's only I see only a yellow
[Music]
one well a sacrifice has had to be pleas
catch
[Applause]
mey how do I get you grab no jump on me
you did it
once I'm sure you can do it again I
don't you have to press a
button
bab Al is she saying Al
her help get off the platform can we
yeah I guess I follow you maybe we got
to
really
Maga okay he
oh but then oh okay I will open oh you
took
it you you open the the the silver one
and I go take the golden
one or you want both go go go
go okay teamwork nice you just stay
there I I'll I'll do it I'll bring
the oh the time is sticking
can you
jump okay okay
nice finally a Mario game where I'm not
super bad at let's
go wait we still have 18 seconds oh oh
no okay okay we got more time thank
goodness scare me oh there's an extra
life how do you get the blue
one maybe the ah the ah no I know how
the trash can
but
that's
[Music]
oh I I changed Direction in air let's go
let's go hold I'll get this yeah oo okay
I'll get I'll grab
the go get the little Mario get your
little baby get your mini Mario Mario
mini Mario did you guys see on Twitter
the mini W on the big
[Music]
taco is so big it was watching me while
I was
sleeping the big
taco it's like really sturdy I thought I
could like fall into it but it's
extremely sturdy and it's like so big
that I can't just like sit on it I would
have to like you have to climb on my
couch yeah on the couch and then on the
takachi wow and then the that this is
the one for the people who don't
remember cuz I saw a lot of confusion
actually that one is the one that you
got from the valkyrie connect
collaboration and the ones that some of
you guys might have is uh ena's what is
it birthday marriage yeah the kitty
kitty that one is smaller Ena has that
one too somewhere it's in my oh there we
go yeah I saw that one
too that's more like a bean bag right
yeah can I drop this down oh I guess I
can write this this over where do we can
I the giant T the T oh there's a time
limit tle of
all is the it's the
tacle
tacle of all times the greatest Taco of
them all oh I don't care about I wanted
to get the
gift hey speaking of go go
gos uh speaking of
treadmills Ena has like I was so
surprised you have so much workout of
things like you have a treadmill I have
a personal gym yeah she own Gym
treadmill and then the the RO machine
and a bicycle and a walking thingy I
don't know how that's like it's just
those those little a treadmill thing
steps Steppy thing is so actually you
know do you want to say how you found me
uh today in the morning you were just
like
yeah move you just heard
ah no you lost the life you have to pick
me up again I have to get the gift first
okay yeah I was just like kind of bored
at some point so I I I was like I'm
going to I'm going to use the rowing
machine now I just rode for a little
while and Ena at some point heard it and
she comes down just like are you using
my rowing machine yeah it just heard
like the
S how do I get there I did not skip
shoulder day
today I might have to like step on you
to get on here oh there's a oh I out
here
somehow I need to go to
the I need to go get the blue what how
did you get up there I don't
know then it's on you oh if he's hand
jump you go a little high hand how do
you do handstand
[Music]
again
oh it's like down and then the jump
button oh
oh
okay I we need to go oh oh if you spin a
lot even
more okay we need to get the GI I got a
gift oh we need to go back
yeah well you you go get the gift I'll
I'll be ready for the the mini Mario ah
wait what Mama it's a fake help
[Applause]
me help
me
okay I need to go back yeah go get the
get the gift the blue gift there okay
okay okay we have 92 seconds surely I
make this that's enough time okay I need
the SP thing to go
okay um nice okay ena's ena's place is
really cool it's actually really
organized and and pretty clean I was I
was uh quite ex yeah excuse me it's
pretty clean and and she has like she
has she has so much like merch and like
mangas and art books and all that but
like she kept she keeps it so organized
in like certain places that are like
tucked away you know like it's not as
obvious yeah yeah the only obvious thing
is the big takachi in the middle that is
kind of hard to guess or get rid of yeah
oh there's like a extra life one should
you go for it how many empty red I
didn't see any empty Red Bulls but I saw
a lot of closed Red Bulls I could use
another one no no we can do it Ena we
can do it without Red Bull go without do
you go for the extra life
uh yeah
okay
it's probably the same stage
right is it it seems oh oh oh it's bonus
stage oh 30
seconds I got get I got one up as long
as one of us gets in there yeah 30
seconds you you too much time four five
we got five new ones five lives let's go
can we get nine cuz there near me a
today you're not ignoring me huh but you
can you can defend yourself now that you
legit did not even
realized I was climbing the stairs right
and it was the same stairs that you if
you guys know where I like cut open my
toe so I always pay attention no but I
started becoming a cat after the stairs
you know but I was talking about
something and you but I was right next
to you I guess cuz I was on my on four
knee on four knees on four on my knees
on four limbs
because of that I was so low that you
didn't see me at all maybe and but I
meowed too but she was like so focused
in her Zone talking about something that
she just did not did not register what
was going on at all hey I'm
stuck thank you
um please open the door with the
key hi thank you she thought it was an
actual cat I've been tell the only
reason I did that let's be a not because
of P between Cara and me who acts more
like a
[Music]
cat excuse
me well wait why can't this open
who right I think we the red button yeah
I'll go get it
hi you
know I
mean yeah she's she she the cat in front
of me out of all people who here is
wearing the cat ears and the tail who he
is rocking those it's not the visual
it's about the soul wa H well you didn't
even hear my meow so I don't know about
you being a cat lady I should have
probably not done that that's fine we'll
figure it
out get him get him wait I want this one
I can't jump oh no jumping okay well
then it's okay I got the gift okay know
but help me don't hurt
yourself okay popping the
bubble how I couldn't make the jump for
some
reason you can do it
nice but yeah I just want to again say I
I know it sounded really weird and I
kind of wrote that tweet purposefully so
it sounded weird it was on purpose but I
really really I just thought like when I
when I saw ena's home and when I saw her
cozy bed and her being cozy in it I
thought if you had cats around you you
would be so happy so really just trying
to convince her I mean I am already
convinced it's just that I don't want
like my cats to be in a situation where
I'm away from home a lot even though if
I have family like still like you
honestly I've heard about people who
like instead of having people come over
to take care of the cats you can just
bring the cats to your parents then it's
basically their cat no no I don't think
and my parents don't really want pets in
the house that's why we haven't really
had
pets so but you need a cat you know I'm
telling
you
hey
hey what is
it
a
no go go go not
really wait I need to
climb the with the
key what is this
level
see don't squash me and then you
can get down okay go
go wait wait be careful when you're in
the handstand uh they won't hit you look
look I can't can I I know that
from I have
the yeah
[Music]
woohoo do you need one person to get the
the blue button to get oh okay okay gift
nice get and then we need someone to
press the okay I'll press this I got the
strats that was in the trail I don't
know from the trail I never watched the
trailer I know it from somewhere no I
jumped on you jumped down
you
okay okay go go
go I just wanted to do it because you
did it a few times to me sorry sorry
sorry I'm sorry
sorry oh my my toad Japanese
toad
[Applause]
a are there two more gifts here oh
there there she goes using my hint and I
just
die what's this hint backflip whoa huh I
know
I yeah W skill
ah can what this trash canun for why you
can throw at the enemies wait am I not
right I stop
him
woohoo no way I was going to take care
of
everything I want to I want to redeem
myself hi hi
[Applause]
no I should have waited till you came
back have a problem if someone didn't go
bump themselves at
the
well I'm making it more
interesting that was that was on
you okay okay
okay
yeah all right all right all right H I
can't jump there you go and you can have
the mar
go there go all the lives got to collect
on the next exra world
five if every time I also die a life is
taken yeah oh my God okay is it next or
is it just me I think I guess it's both
of us next extra world we got to get
those lives yeah be all right ooh
oh ah is this the one of the boss fights
like Donkey Kong fight there's a there's
a boss fight mhm like Donkey Kong oh we
can get three Marios from here that's
what it is
yay let the go let go I look get the
maros let's go guys where's the to Army
letter blocks oh we got to get the
letter blocks
oh we got to guide them to it how can
we duck and walk duck and walk duck and
walk walk you can do it
Ena duck and wall you go
wait okay we can't duck and walk but you
got it but they they they just always
stay down there
or I don't know maybe they follow me
does this
help no how did you get there oh no
idea oh wait maybe I can get that key
no I I I I would probably need a trash
can a button if do they only follow you
I think so oh man okay I guess that's
why they're mini Marios oh we have to
make them jump maybe
M ah ah they will jump on the trash can
okay cuz it's not too high so what about
the key there maybe you're if I can jump
on you that would help okay you can jump
on me okay okay okay okay I'll I'll go
here
hi one more time must be possible no or
it's
really here here you can go to the oh I
think oh oh no I should have pressed
that when you were up there
already Oh I thought it was y you okay
okay okay I I understand lives I will
help you with everything how do you get
the tea
um stay
there oh I guess never mind never mind
you uh actually first you have to go up
to the red and then I
change oh there you are oh okay uh and
now you can yeah okay okay and and
another the the yellow one again I guess
yeah so they come
up but make sure they go all the way up
little Marios yeah good job Mario what
about the key the key I guess I no no no
I have to press the yellow one so that I
go across and they'll follow me
yeah once you're up I'll press the red
no no no don't
it once you on the purple I'll press the
red you have to go all the way across oh
so the Mario will follow me okay get it
like that okay okay but what about the
key man
yeah we can go get the key
time yeah okay can we possibly do it
from here or you could
try yes
okay run run run run
run okay okay okay
[Applause]
okay oh that was
clutch and it
what do you mean what one of the last
Mario didn't make it in or what I guess
so oh we know what to do now okay okay
okay oh my God that last second
though what the
hell
okay oh you could probably grab the key
yeah should we do now it's probably
better now we did it from oh you did it
from there I mean this is clearable solo
right yeah I I tried though couldn't do
it no
skills okay we now just running after
you I'm just one of the mini maros I'm
just one of them one of them is not like
the wait what only three of them get
sent in oh I think the thing we didn't
do at the end is pick up cuz it just
gave me a prompt to pick up the box X or
Y and we didn't do that this was like a
minimum of three Mari to Shi out
a wait so did you wait you didn't let
them all in no no it closed on its own
really
huh I don't know I don't know but I
think you might have picked it up early
I was I I I I uh felt that it closed so
I thought I could open it with X or Y
but then I just picked it up I got
confused I think I closed it by jumping
on it okay we got to throw the the
things on them oh careful I need to I
need
to ah now you bring it there
you die over here over here I now it's
gone does the handstand thing still work
uh I think so how do you throw it
no okay one more you can do it ah while
jumping okay there you go easy Donkey
Kong's so weak he's so weak easy he gets
a little bit more difficult later yeah
it's just the first time the first
world
yay oh I'm sorry Donkey Kong you're not
getting those mini Marios no no but they
got
more oh Mario toy company cleared oh
that toy
company this whole thing a toy company
yes the Jungle jungle world two in the
jungle guys there's eight World donke
Kong Jungle Donkey Kong sleeps tonight
if there can can you guys confirm
there's eight worlds and I think maybe
an extra World maybe
uh I think that's right T time tangent
time okay stop stop stop the game what
what do we talk about talk about what do
I have so much um okay I wanted to say
the snow is so
beautiful the snow is like different is
it it's different like Austria we get
snow and and we're supposed to be the
snowy one of the snowy places in uh in
Europe mhm but first of all it doesn't
really snow much at this time of the
year what if I told you all the snow is
fake nah it's not fake i t T it I
touched it what if it's flake it's it's
yeah it's clean but I mean it's more
like like a powdery it looks so soft
like it looks like cream it looks like
whipped cream before you like a little
bit before you finish the whipping like
it's not quite whipped so maybe also
kind of like shaving
cream I don't
know it's it looks so sof I what's
special about snow but it looks so
smooth
it's so beautiful I want to like lie in
it and I want to touch it I want to Bath
in it I touched it with my bare hand and
of course it was cold as
hell yeah Cara was not she was about to
go out today and she was like wearing
like really thin jacket I was like no
wor I brought my skiing jacket too I
want to rethink that option she of
course did not regret it because it was
snowy very cold yeah snow but the snow
is so
beautiful and and and one thing I
noticed by the way don't don't worry I
got I got Ena permission to say these
things I made
sure one thing I I'm like like there's
two things that are absolutely
fascinating me when Mama is is driving
us around the snow and the
houses the houses look so different from
what I've seen before I mean the house
look different in every country but I
think
like the houses just look like I mean I
call them like Matchbox houses cuz
they're all just ah like matchboxes oh
oh they're really pretty and they look
so clean and I don't know they don't
have a they don't have a European Vibe
and and I haven't been around much in
like you know North America but it
doesn't look like anything I've seen
before m I feel like it looks so nice I
don't know how to explain it they're
they're pretty I'm glad I'm glad you
like them and ena's house is also pretty
inside and
outside and oh oh yeah I thought I I saw
a lot of whole life members houses until
now or Like Houses Apartments whatever
and um not
saying like I feel like everybody has
their own style that's true and and I
can I really like your style I like your
sense of like the the furniture you
chose and the lamps that you chose
honestly if I had the choice well I kind
of was forced to put up like frames and
stuff in my house but I don't like you
were forced to put up FR like literally
I went to Japan you know like I was in
Japan like for the 3D stuff I came back
and Mom is already put up frames and
stuff cuz I told her don't put up stuff
on my walls which is why I don't have
any pictures and stuff yeah I only saw
like but then the ones that are up there
because M's insistent I had some Pi is
insisted oh just like I like to keep my
like furniture and stuff really clean
and like
minimalistic cuz I just like it neat
yeah like I noticed it's not like
there's it's not in like too intense
like it's not too cutesy it's not too
dark or not too I don't know it's also
not tacky like this whole place it feels
very cozy and and calm calming soothing
that's my life I like my health yeah
yeah and and yeah you have like so much
cool stuff I love I love your
workspace got to like it I've been I
need to switch these though cuz they
were white they were white before
they're completely like potato fry
yellow I don't know what do you mean how
did they I don't know like did you put
them up only after you moved in yeah how
do they turn yellow I don't know the
place is so clean they I think it's like
the sun or something or like the
material just like yellows it's like
toxic it never like white never stays
what like before in my parents' place
like I used to have like um black and
gray like checkered so I was like did we
say what we're talking about the foam on
the wall yeah the the the acoustic foam
on the wall um
but then like it made the room look a
little too dark and like too small they
were not in the sun guys there's no
there's no sunlight hitting them right
not directly but over time just the air
and stuff like I think it just changes
color but like I came back from the 3
month trip is in for the 3D o I entered
my room I was like were they always just
yellow no it was white it was literally
white it just turned yellow I think it's
just the material itself it's just no I
mean that was your fault probably where
they was just yellow yeah I was like I
they were literally wider than my walls
but then they turned this yellow so I'm
thinking of just getting rid of them one
day and actually installing like boards
smoker Ena Ina smoking confirm no I
swear she doesn't I do not I hate I
really hate cigarettes also Ena has a
lot of um cool keyboards that I want to
take home she has so many mechanical
keyboards they all have like different
key cabs I didn't know you were one of
those key cab people I mean I like my
stuff to look kind of cute so it's cute
yeah she was eyeing my copy bar and I'm
just like not that one that one no I
like the colors it matches with my
current um I'm just like I can build you
on but not
that that one you probably find that
kind of hard to use cuz it's a it's a
brand called wooting and it's like
really sensitive like key wise cuz it's
like for gaming so like you can
literally press space bar by mistake by
just going like this I yeah I can build
you yeah C cute isn't it cute oh
cute Iris was impressed Iris saw your
copy keyboard yeah I sent a picture
after I buil well okay well okay let's
do another world get more tent gun let's
go what is this we're in the
jungle Donkey Kong in the jungle where
he belongs to In the Jungle the Monkey
Jungle is Donkey Kong a monkey donkey
konga monkey a monkey they turned to
Monkey here we go here we go I'm
guessing we can climb the Rope okay
yes oh wao what was that jump
oh you do that I got it I got it
all wait you're too far
up I'll help you here does that help you
it does not it blocks me okay you know
I'll just go the wrong wayout hey
there's the I can get the I can get
the what's happened turn into a bubble
thank you you kicked me up what do you
need what do you need there we
go we need the silver one first right
okay was right there no oh
sorry
okay okay I got it I'll open that one
first now okay you get the golden one go
go okay I will
try actually yeah the yeah and then I go
down and activate a different button so
you can go for the blue H where was a
different
button uh I didn't see
one oh can you go from above yeah you
can go from above back down no I don't
know oh you can't is there another
button there's no other button oh I can
jump yeah okay okie dokie oh
good mhm nice 30 seconds left easy oh no
problem oh no not the piran plant ooh oh
they're shooting fire oh
no can we jump on them do they no we
cannot it's okay I got an extra laugh
for you just cuz you I know you needed
it thank
you oh what did that do oh it opened the
thing at the bottom
okay oh
good
oh good climbing skills enough oh this
is already I don't feel so good oh oh we
got it we got all three gifts huh H did
we get all three gifts yeah okay oh nice
nice I was feeling too
good I was feeling my impending doom
free lives we only have three lives left
I wonder who used them
[Music]
all oh yeah we only have three left I
wonder I wonder who used the most no
you
you I
mean we'll get more we'll get more are
you sure no I literally got a life on
that stage and we started okay there's
another one over
there
oh okay that
works I need that life I'll get it for
myself then there you go and I get the
key oh golden key but like
[Music]
even oh something
dropped I think now I can go go to open
the the the silver okay you can move to
the left and right yeah no yeah okay I
know but space too
big
okay
um
perhaps
ah I think you can jump on the the
barrels t t
well you can also jump on him by the
way help me I need to be on Solid Ground
come here Mario
oh you got
it oh platforming let's go let's
go hey but then even from Den can
we how think we we need to
okay
okay the music is not making it easier
it's kind of stressing you're doing it
IB believeable I'm redeeming
myself
Yahoo
monkey the
monkey oh these they're so cute what do
you call them in English rhinos rhinos
cute
[Music]
[Applause]
rhinos I'll wait for you okay go on
ahead no the camera will cut you off I
don't like that oh you guys can
see come on
yeah
[Music]
oh yellow gift blue
gift
can the if you get the yellow gift I can
get the
Mario immediately I wonder if I can
throw
the oh I should use it on the other one
the yellow just get it quickly okay and
then run away from the
Ral get it get him
get
it worked okay it worked all according
to
Kaku oh cute monkey music monkey cute
they're scary in the horror games
they're the one that
goes yeah I can imagine
here we go here we go oh they
break did they
return ah I have to go down
anyway
sorry how did I know I okay they do
return I'll make up for it uh go away I
don't want you go away that's fine okay
okay I'll work on this then
okay okay I got
it you got to get up before
oh
monkey oh you can hold on to his
tail oh wow he's got a
interesting tail oh you got the golden
one yes let's
go do I need those I think I need them
to come
back go go
go it wed
okay teamwork teamwork so good we're
we're just meant to work together you
mean together T strong T underrated
combination actually not quite true I
see a lot of kfp stop pooping hey that's
just
a not a
kfp kfp totally wait that's not poop
that's eggs oh it's golden
eggs that
so
me me I'm sorry I'm clumsy
clumsy we have two lives can the bird
help us somehow once's he here for how
do we get to that side distract us of
course he definitely distracted me with
his golden
eggs those are
very oh nice all right all
right duing no did you see my tweet
about the I mean you never on Twitter
but did you see the dingo bir uh tweet
that I did with his um Brazilian butt
lift I think I saw that one are you
aware that Dingo like has the craziest
social media PR team they do the
craziest things and they did this like
one video uh where the bird in his big
costume he goes to a plastic surgeon and
gets a Brazilian butt Li and the surgeon
is like acting so excited about like oh
my God yeah I'll give you the biggest
butt ever it's going to be so great and
I don't know I want to learn
about I
know and he walks out with hand in hand
with the surgeon super happy with the
biggest smile
ever
and no
no I'm so sorry I was thinking no okay
it's okay you're in Fall
okay I was thinking about big butt wa I
can't go down I need I need you to press
the the color button okay okay oh which
one on the
side oh Dodge the egg DOD the egg EAS
EAS easy and this one there we go we're
good leave me behind I'm fine here it's
okay you'll be you'll become a little
of light to follow me everywhere I
go you only have one life you have one
life oh my God
yumy I mean what happens if we lose that
life anyway
well um I don't know okay there's the
blue one I think we can get too Blue
[Music]
Button like this oh oh
oh and then you can get the yellow gift
yeah nice I'm so scared there's a
there's a boot gift over there too oh oh
so I need to do
this oh
no I think before was
better was it yeah can you go to the
yellow butt
wait bang no it was not better when that
red button oh there it is okay
Buton yeah gift ghetto and button do we
need no uh we could use the blue button
is that up oh no no no no uh can use the
yellow button try yellow again
okay I I don't know the logic of this I
just let it happen just press all the
buttons
eventually eventually he I'll be
faster that's fine see I mean I may die
a lot but I'm also like very fast wow
your speed
M fast cat she's
B let's go let's go okay think two more
levels until boss o oh those are oh
extra Les we e that okay we got to
remember speed we have to
okay cat the key get the box catch the
key it's about life or death literally
quite literally okay it's so pretty H
can you can you jump on me and get the
first one I guess that's not even
necessary go go go would have
worked speed speed
[Music]
speed down
[Applause]
here we survived to stay another
day beautiful I want to live a many many
nine lives with you there's there's
crocodiles on Nine
Lives I think we use more than nine
lives already by the
way there's going to be crocodiles on
the on the oh fruit they're so cute
though yum oh
oh now hold up oh
[Music]
uhoh okay I got the got the the red one
okay what's
the I guess we were too far apart we
were okay about we got
the how many lives did we get I
we went from 1 to eight I think oh we
got to get the no the
key I'll let you get
it and then I'll go down but not yet got
to wait for you a little
bit okay okay and then we need a golden
one I didn't even see a golden one where
is it there's a
lot well that one's not on me
time
okay she collected it right before she
died do you think I can jump that no do
I believe hold my hand I'll catch you
okay we
did we are good we are good
trustful not very trustworthy here are
the oh okay the the seems simple enough
wait wait wait wait for it
to
[Music]
gift
nor okay I'll get the blue gift okay
okay to wait for this one and then you
can get the doll let's
go
y yeah
I may take some lives but I also give
some
lives we're good we're good jump jump
jump jump
jump did you guys play this game when
you were younger I I think I didn't even
know about his
existence me neither until like to like
when you told
me I did yes I did yeah tons back in the
day yeah oh
back in my day they all know it this
just I think I I never really got much
into the Mario franchise like except for
64 Super Mario 64 and my Super Mario
Sunshine what can't I oh there we go did
you play Super Mario 64 nope I didn't
have
consoles oh my God which is why I suck
at Mario games well I played them and I
still suck at them
let okay there we go monkey monkey
monkey monkey monkey monkey monkey cl cl
cl monkey monkey make music oh what that
wait let me up let me up what are you
doing what are you doing down
there come
on
what's okay I'm good
go
oh yeah right I wasn't I I genuinely
thought that you could land on them and
then destroy them by doing
that like in other Mario games you can
do that
no okay got the
key what about that though
uh ah can he walk can we
no oh maybe
no you just got jump
it we have to we have to carry the key
back the red button what does the red
button
do nothing much huh
no I totally knew that I totally knew
that yeah did wait but how do we carry
the key
back we'll figure that one
out once we get the
key maybe you can climb with the key we
just didn't think we could maybe we
underestimated oh
Mario I know wait on on him somehow does
he walk over there if you on him for
some reason I don't think so there's 20
seconds
left yeah I can't
really the you know what wait take it
take
it
sorry my back flip went I can throw the
Rhino oh oh what well I guess there's
something we can
try who would have thought that you
could throw the Rhino I wouldn't have
thought you could throw the r who gets
that
idea nowhere I guess it's probably in
one of the help notes I don't see the I
didn't see I guess we didn't really read
it oh we have to wait for it to be on
the red thing okay okay first one open
okay easy
easy as soon as it's on the red thing
I'll will drop it down nice oh okay am I
the one this time's going to do it okay
throw the Rhino first
[Music]
okay oh you
can't
[Music]
no I I legit can't I I got really close
to
him ah from standing on top of him ah
okay okay yeah cuz yeah we had that
before when you stand on top of things
you can pick him up yeah you stand on
him and then pick him up yeah
yeah can't do it from standing right
besid but can pick up while
standing
okay
[Music]
a don't me we both didn't know we just
experimenting yeah we're
learning learning by
[Music]
doing bro landed on his back on his bik
I feel bad for him he's a good boy it's
okay they're you know you know that
rhinos well not rhinos but hippos are
like one of the most dangerous hippo is
it not yeah is it is it hippo or Rhino
is it hippo hippos are the Dangerous
Ones most one of the most dangerous
animals in the world
[Music]
oh mama likes to play with fire all
right does this help
you come here come
here
let's go here looks interesting you get
the oh uh this there's a need for a red
come Ona come
on I feel like I could do it if I turn
back during the jump I did that before I
shall want to try get red
buttons
[Music]
um I I can't really get to the toy I
want to try this jump oh maybe I have to
go other side
now don't do it I want to try don't do
it you can stop me if you bring me the
red ones the red buttons and the red
open
it I'm scared of the fire it came out of
nowhere I had nowhere to go you should
have crouched but we got the gift now we
don't lose it you die press the the red
one no uh the yellow one yellow where is
it where's the yellow oh here
oh okay nice okay it's okay I got it I
got it yay
woo suddenly teleported up there magic
I'm everywhere everywhere
magic this is harder than Ty's
principal have you played that a little
bit oh that was too big brain for me my
brain hurt after one stream I can
imagine okay we're going to put all the
Mario in before picking up the boxes
okay I I'll try I think we get an extra
life if if we do that probably we need
to
okay hold the Min get the
toy let
go I'm just decoration I'm just trying
to blend it oh I think I know okay first
we go here
right easy easy easy easy and then we
have to press another button wait I can
press the red one yeah yeah yeah so that
we need them to jump on the yellow
box yeah yeah yeah yeah okay okay come
here sorry I made
mistakes it was no you locked them in oh
oh
no I'm so sabotaging so hard okay I
wonder if they'll come jump okay they do
okay oh oh we already and then need to
press the red button red button okay
okay
I am happy to be Mario's
servant so everyone jumps over here I
have to go
here may I press the button for you uh
hold on I need to get across this m oh
there's the silver key key I need to
wait for it to come back here
to ah so close there we go nice okay did
you bounce off of me
why can I
okay follow to no no no no I want them
to follow me yeah he likes me what he
legit likes me guys they likes me
too they actually follow me now okay now
oh I was just joking you got to do the
job now oh yeah 17 seconds bring them up
the thing oh yeah right oh
no the
key wait to get the key finally I felt
the love of the toads for once y it it's
not it's not it's not got the key but I
one
cost that I didn't know they will ditch
you start they run our lives no way it's
okay we got oh 10 lives now what okay
easy H all right all right all right I
got
it mhm number one and then get
the nice you don't have to press the red
one yet okay okay I'll bring them across
again M mhm okay and you press the
red oh okay I I need to get them up here
first okay and then you can press red
okay
let's
go Min
Mario I can jump on
these your
minions
toy it's almost like it's a Toy
[Music]
Story oh no
okay give them love okay okay I'll save
you it's good to I me oh wait oh
no I can just go here okay maybe I can't
fit I can't fit through H maybe open
this for one first okay you can do that
no you have the key you have the solver
key okay you can press the red or the
yellow what I'm up here oh I guess I
have to press the
red a
a ah oh I could I could come down if you
want me too oh
hi okay I'll go down I'll go down oh
turn the
way okay uh uh can you can you press the
red the red
Okay Go Okay
[Music]
uh don't give up yet I believe in you 10
seconds do we need
yellow what
sorry
intrusive oh my it's Mari over it's so
Mari
over I
can't no can you okay I'll go here can
you press the yell
[Music]
pleas
okay while I do this press the red
okay press the red don't
[Laughter]
crya I'm waiting for you command me know
my is off the
floor I will not act rash rashly rash
what
rapidly ra rash rash
what help me English rashley rationally
okay irrationally rashley works too IR
irrationally or rashley but rally also
works kind of it's just not how you say
it right rap it fast I will not act too
fast I guess so recklessly
oh okay we got this we got this all
right
donkey I'll show you oh we got to drop
the I'll show you the power oh yeah
oh
that ow he so
fast at least you don't die from this
nice o
oh oh oh it did hit him oh let's go
let's go wow thank you thank you thank
you dony Kong feel bad for him I mean he
was being greedy greed is the end of all
he just wants
friends
cleared wait what about the two what
about there would have been two more I
guess so how could we have gotten two
more of the mini
Mario but yeah new new world I mean we
can we can go back see new world tangent
time I think I
have we can't we didn't get out the yet
guys we oh okay okay where oh I guess
there's two that one wait we didn't play
that one no we did we just did it
why is it not perfect you got hit those
were ah there the HP the more mini Mar
you bring with you the more HP you have
yeah okay okay tangent okay okay I just
have a really random small
one me and me and Ena we we've been you
know sitting on the on the dinner table
having some chitchat a lot and uh at
some point uh we were talking about
anime and uh somehow I don't know why
but we talked about one piece and then I
said I watched the one piece live action
what about you Ena you said you didn't
watch it and I said you should watch it
like the one piece live action is
actually really good un like
others and then you Che a full metal
alist try that's
great yeah but but you know where I'm
going right
yeah and and then I said because this
it's really recent so I was like like um
I wasn't sure if I was saying it right I
was like unlike you know the Avatar life
a never mind Avatar is always AC oh you
didn't know it and I took it back while
I was saying I was like no never mind
Avatar is always live action it's not
like a live action thing but uh what was
the other what was the other one the
last air Banner yeah yeah and so we had
another
misunderstanding with Avatar and last
AER and then you told me that is also
Avatar and like ah yeah right oh yeah
they're both Avatar but the one Avatar
that I first metant was the blue people
Avatar and the other one is the other
one which isn't even Avatar to me to me
in my brain that is just the last air
bender I guess I'm just like they're
both Avatar we had this conversation
like a couple years ago yeah the non the
non blue people and then there's the
blue people but the blue people one is
always live action yes and the non blue
one get got a live action
adaption which was not taken well by a
lot of people apparently apparently I
didn't watch it I don't I don't really
watch that much Netflix is it live
action if it's all CGI M I don't know
there's still liveaction actors right
yeah I thought so yeah there not only Bo
people in the movie there's humans too
[Music]
a it's mainly blue people right that's
just how I make the
differentiation yeah but yeah it was
really funny it was funnier you had to
be there guys you had to be
there okay and I I this reminds me of um
what weall it the the cat tweet you made
I remember someone saying Ena didn't
take the cat's movie lightly she didn't
take yeah I saw that I saw some comments
about I was just like I mean this true I
can't believe you made me
watch there was nothing wrong with the
cats movie I mean it was interesting I
leave that you like cats I do I just
didn't realize I was I like cat but I
don't know about the cats bracket 2019
bracket
what bracket like the movie
what I
know I understand I understand and
you this is a little
Troublesome
scary what I thought it would go to the
side oh okay you got to get get the KE
get the KE get the okay now we got to
wait for the middle one
what about is that a
gift no no we already what we have
okay okay okay okay wait for the middle
one and then jump on it I'm on my
way hi hi thank you for waiting for me I
mean I oh my
God oh my
God this is uh taxing
they're like Ninjas
Oh I just learned a fact yesterday while
I was like on my
iPad that it's a
hisor it's a histo it's a historical
misconception that ninjas wore that
typical ninja outfit that people think
of when they think about a ninja they
weren't wearing that outfit at all oh
cuz I mean obviously as a ninja you want
to you want to not stand out you don't
want people to recognize you as a ninja
they just wear normal clothes to blend
in like you
know yeah where's the gift is it on the
right you so focused on the game did you
did you register what I was saying yeah
there is yeah if
anything if
anything
two lives lost one one received it mean
they would wear blue clothes to blend
into the night cuz blue Blends in nicer
than black apparently anyway is it
darker than black
but that was a nice anime oh can I just
say I'm sitting here I'm going to break
the wall I hope it's okay I'm sitting
here in cozy fluffy m m pajamas right
uhhuh
and
yesterday when you know I arrived and
I I changed into my pajamas then you
know also changed their pajamas into her
room clothing uhhuh and even though it's
like generally so
cold I was surprised to see you in a
very summery light cute dress with
grills it's not
[Music]
that
yeah was I'm like damn that's cute
that's an Ena I didn't expect okay I
need I need to go here
okay
yeah sorry I'm focused on the game it's
okay just I'll just look at you we
probably better off without me on this
level I always need you oh I was free
I've been freed from the
bubble the bubble okay this works
a hey I died exactly there now you can't
judge me
anymore no we have no time okay Speed
come
on
damn okay jump on my
head wor you go get the mini Mario don't
think about me just forget about me
Priority is mini Mario okay
got ky ky does it sacrifices have been
made worth
[Music]
it this is only the first
level of this world guys artists let me
describe to you a little bit above KNE
length um what do you call this pattern
again Checker Checker Checker really
Checker check I don't know check check
pattern Japanese school girl skirt P
mainly pink but a bit of gray and white
it's you and white Frills around the
collar um and a ribbon in the middle of
the collar there you go artist also
sleeps until elbow there you go I I'm
looking forward to what you can do it's
me I have my eyes on the on the art tag
oh my God
Ena
well while you were
flattened if we die we die together
together wait I don't even need the B I
just jumped on you wait never mind I do
need you no don't what the hell I'm one
of
you oh oh thanks no and then and then
how do we move on from
here yeah I don't I don't understand
where we're supposed to go I think we're
supposed to go left but like it's too
high
know also there's spikes up there no
like down below there but like how can
we make the jump can we throw the
block can we maybe one that that would
be
crazy but wait first the
key oh yeah you can try n no okay well
then we got to just um ah
Co he wants to kill
me okay uh uh uh okay okay I'll wait for
that
block okay but I'm too early
um get the get the
key
no no I was too focused on the key it's
okay we amazing
okay got it easy
easy I I feel like you have adjusted
your skill level to me out of kindness
are you sure about that oh no oh
no okay you sounded like toad
there he was he was cornering me he was
cornering me thank
you do you want to get the golden okay
I'll get the silver one
okay focus L Focus
monkey
okay that's the evil evil Wawa
Phoenix it's a cousin of
mine good
jump all right I'll be careful of the
bird I go down cuz I'm scared no no get
the key get the key
a I was like maybe I'll try to jump
maybe it could
work
ah it's fun to fail with you
yeah what
happened I was distracted by our
beautiful
posture okay H yeah I'm scared uh okay
okay
oh
wait scar no no don't don't pop me pop
me okay po
po
okay okay you got to try to get you know
what's going on my hit box is too big
here you can get me out here okay go get
the silver key you can do it
hi oh no okay okay yeah
nice
guys why was this such a
challenge it's still hard oh YouTube die
it'll be finally back soon ruin that's
probably just YouTube YouTube come on oh
no oh some people saw okay we good we're
good M what is this
about is there a button somewhere we got
to get that
live hey
oh okay that jump was high can we get
the gift
too okay nice
nice get on this one mhm okay okay mhm
you still need
a blue gift or is it in the next World I
think it's to the left oh there it is
okay don't don't jump on
the oh you didn't have to join
me you didn't have
to you stay here I I want to look if
where the red button
was was it on the right side I think so
okay it's okay as long as I get
the where's red
button careful careful then where is red
button you get you have get okay okay
okay oh I thought I could open it up for
you magic the platform I I thought I was
the only one I was just thinking to
myself the platform look like a
burger yeah yeah did it Burger it's not
just
[Music]
[Laughter]
me we get distracted by the sign of bger
M
okay I think uh are we in the world
number three yes okay I think I can end
it after this world sure if we could bra
juice is running low okay
we're oh there goes
the
oh there's the red one you want to go
left or right uh I'll go right okay
can I jump on
them well I guess I didn't have to oh we
got to go we got to go we got to go the
glove is rising Glo is rising that's a
shortcut I just want a shortcut to come
to
you careful careful oh it's okay we got
the extra life over
there
okay I'll go for the oh you want to you
should from me you should go on the
silver
one yeah okay nice nice just get here
the lava's rising I'm scared to mess
up there was actually no jumping
necessary you can just walk from one to
another just got to time it okay we're
just missing the blue one now lava's
Rising floor getting
hot I love playing
don't stress don't
hurry I love playing the floor lava back
in like elementary school or like Junior
High
School
oh well but I can't do anything here sh
okay I need to press on the blue
button okay you can help me get to the
Blue
Button okay uh not sure if this is how
you're supposed to get it
okay get the oh that's a lot of okay
that works yeah nice okay oh we have
everything I can just get the Mario jump
okay have you played the Flor lav in
school not really not really I don't
really have friends to FL not it's not
about friends we just played it as an
exercise and physical education
no guys have you explain it in the chat
in
school cuz I wanted to ask like what is
your go-to obstacle to like hang on to
when the floor is lava like usually we
had mats like mattresses on the floor or
the um uh ladders on the on the side
yeah that seems too advanced I thought
it's something you play like at home or
like on the class where you climb on the
desks and you're just like the floor is
lava oh but we would also play it in PE
class the be big big Hall and we would
just use everything to like jump on to
like platforming I never did played by
myself I'm playing my
job he you guys don't I guess PE is very
different in Austria than it is to other
countries how did I
live
oh didn't you didn't we have a meeting
yeah but it's um it's it's fine we still
have in Fe we have half an hour okay
I well never I guess I don't really need
press oh we do need the red afterwards
though for the
platform oh here's the key Oh Come Oh
maybe if I do this no no no no stand
stand mm where the red is well I don't
have the key yeah don't don't don't
worry you could stand there and I could
press the button you stand there
no wait you go there but now I what is
the silver where's the silver did we
miss it now it went back I
think saw oh nice shortcut nice actually
nice I'll get the silver one no it's
okay I'll get the silver one okay you
go uh okay yeah nice nice and now now we
both got to get to the door though okay
you just stand here here okay okay okay
okay and before you had both so you
could stood there there oh okay okay is
it still with me is it still with
me away go get go get it go can you get
it from here like I
guess no what are I doing Panic I'll go
get it I'll go get it keep it open keep
it
open okay I can do it I can oh I think
you can't get it if you have the big key
oh
so but can I not have she oh wait I
really can't have Focus the L okay no no
we know that we know
that we know now go go go go didn't we
have like both at the same time before I
don't don't think so we just had
different ones maybe it's okay we'll
work it out
okay
it's okay you're going to give me the
shortcut thank
you oh become as flat
as
hot guess I'll just
die stop dying you're not I can't give
you endless amounts and supplies of
Phoenix
feathers have you ever given me phix
TS and right now constantly you're just
dead in the moment so you don't notice
it when I give it to you not
all so what do we do okay you press the
button okay I unlock it nice and then
you just got to go back down and then
bring the key
[Music]
over should I leave it like this or blue
button I just leave it yeah cuz if you
press a blue button you can't get up the
red stairs you just got to get to the
other side
I thought I was far
enough 9 8 seven
six you can get it yo y yo
you get
up okay don't press the blue b
okay I'm waiting for you at the door
Ena get the key get the
key I died I got
squished okay we're good
[Music]
go go
[Applause]
go what are you doing okay we fine I'm
happy that we're in the same amount of
brain empty right now head empty very
good very good H see we're in the same
wavelength nice oh
careful
oh I like your four4
emote cute brain empty yeah okay and
then we just got to climb on the head
you got that I got it okay I'm trusting
you
s all right all right
believe
they make funny sounds they
do they're Shakira they're fans of
Shakira should I throw
it you you want to get over here before
I throw this uh I'm scared to
jump okay
okay
uh that's
it
one where's the gift
is down below next world or we we have
the blue gift left oh it's there down
come down come
[Music]
down okay got it got it got it
it m
all right we're good clap clap clap
thank you thank you so much Shakira
Shakara Shakara yeah there's going to be
a lot of these platforms here aren't
there have mercy on us Donkey Kong
please we can share floor is lava just
don't steal them if you steal them we
won't share okay oh oh you want to come
up here yeah got
it oh yeah platforming I'll get it I'll
got
it I forgot can you climb with
this no you can't okay oh so maybe I
should go ahead yeah go get the red gift
the still
land
okay I'll get the key
I'll get the key and you ran past to get
the the the gift the red
gift
y we start with a handicap that's fine
that's fine I got the key oh here no
nice it
sorry wa do it spawn oh there's the
silver key okay if you pop me here then
I'll go get the uh golden
key yeah where's the golden key oh it's
gone is it in the lava no gone um I
can't get it it's in the lava it's gone
wait the door it's gone it was gone it's
gone jump into the
lava soft lock or what is it a soft lock
game's over it's
time we can't die how can you you can't
you got to get it in the time Mom Mom
Mama all right
okay I'm just like not
thinking oh I pop you here yay okay you
you get that stuff yay
yay
yay easy oh that that stopped my okay
come on over
come on
[Music]
over I'm good
nice oh oh no it's the
firebird firebird again oh two
Firebirds okay free
Firebirds
it's like when you crossing the road and
you only look left then you get you like
I CH from the right you you you you
sound like you're talking from
experience
shry we're not even trying anymore we're
like zooming for the level there's no
need to rush
[Music]
okay are you okay I'm not okay let me
let bird bird burn okay just come up
yeah let me pop your Strat
oh
okay yep yeah
yeah where's the blue one okay I'll get
the blue one okay you go to the
puppet good all right yeah first try
this is how the pros do it guys first
try feel free to use our stream as a
tutorial for these levels if they're too
difficult for you
we can help you out with that we like to
teach you how to do things this is how
you
g it's okay don't feel bad about your
skills guys it's a skill issue sometimes
if we can do it you can do it by only by
watching us so yeah yeah only by
[Applause]
that oh it goes down don't tell me it
comes back up wait up here in oh it goes
down all the way
okay does it go back up
again sry sry
sorry Mario Mario patience Pati child
where are you oh we have to
press no no no oh
okay okay and then we need to get the
get the blue okay I'm
here okay nice nice got it now up or we
we have to go down still don't down
still oh no no we have to go up now will
it come back it's coming
back you you have to get on the jumpy
pad oh
okay get on the jumpy pad yum
okay
red
[Applause]
for wow all right all right all right
all right we know what to do now we know
what to do okay
wait that's okay we have two more lives
that's
okay okay eel e
bre I hope not wait patience okay fast
oh got
[Music]
it golden key is
mine and now platform Burger but uh do
we want it to be on on that button right
now are we F yeah we need to we need to
get on the red Ascend Ascend okay and
then do we need we just I guess just go
okay I got to wait okay do I have
to it's okay open okay
calm
PA
[Music]
M all right all right yellow's pretty
easy we need two gifts yeah you say
pretty easy all right let me see you do
that yeah
yeah got to be
careful okay where's
the okay I guess we got to okay okay
okay okay okay one up let's go and oh
here's the Mario blue is all the way
over there I'll get the I'll get
the well what's down there is it safe to
wait do is it safe to land over that way
yes it is get the mini
Mar hi T Tac go let's go nice parkour
that was good that wasn't too bad the
pee and parkour stands for
potato all right we got to put in the
Mari into the box
okay I you did so well last time with
the box thank you so I might leave it to
you oh yes yes yes yes we can do it
quick okay okay time speed Perfection we
are speed speed is my middle
name got to go fast whoa what is this oh
no I got I got this first one I got this
one that's
the it
okay where are you
going
trying to get the
key okay uh the key the key he's down
there the key chase it over here okay
nice okay you got I got all the lives in
the key one no I should have done
something sorry okay can we try this
again do we get a second try I hope so
please please see
please it's still over I should have
tried to get the key n over over
over wait did we get the free L well we
got the extra ones right okay okay I
think okay wait we got to press the blue
okay let we get
across
[Music]
o okay we got the key what's up there oh
I guess you can get the yellow button up
there right but what's on the
left I'll go with oh okay I think we got
to go there first
anyways
man
oh and then if I go up here should I
open it
already no no no no wait wait wait wait
wa wait keep
it okay I mean you could go right now
and get
it I'm just scared to mess something up
I'll just I'll just keep the key with me
[Music]
okay we do
this uhuh right right she's doing it
guys she's doing it she's working the
mini Marios we need them to
drop down
below
nice but the blue but the blue but the
blue they're going to fall where you
press the blue press the blue press the
blue okay okay they're safe to go
they're safe to
go
no nice wow so
quick we are gen tou the box I not touch
the box I'm not touching three four
five I think the last thing is donkey
donkey okay then we'll make it in time
for the meeting yeah easy perfectly
cated all right no hit run let's go oh
first try first try okay going be nice
to us
please oh no not the
firea oh this is kind of like before but
I don't know what to hit it with
[Music]
oh good job good job I'll be the
distraction I'll be the distraction okay
okay it's going to come down here oh we
fell off what is this
RNG he just went like hey
wait what a voice Donkey Kong I didn't
know you had it in you oh oh
R careful
J okay careful
careful
how you Hur like that I guess don't
stand like right underneath
the I got hit okay go go go go
go go go go
go
blocked you just got to be careful for
the one that's on okay I got it okay in
the end all the hits will
be it's okay we didn't lose am Maria
though
okay you can you can do it believe okay
it's your chance
nice yeah Rejoice Rejoice beautiful we
did it t t chicken taco taco chicks Taco
Che taco t chick Taco chicks Taco chicks
Tac chicks let's go go we lost too many
Marios on the way but it's okay we lost
in the we were the friends we
made that was good though we made the
world four that was so fun that's fun
can I have to play tomorrow tomorrow
we'll continue this on the W Channel
guys
yeah hopefully Until the End should we
should we have time tomorrow so yeah and
we'll start um at usual Ina time in t
time which I think is 2 p.m TT 7 jst and
the usual one more time in in one more
time zone that's 11:00 p.m. I think okay
yeah Tacony
time
tomorrow okay
[Music]
uh water water water see you tomorrow
bye isn't like w pronounced like V in
German yeah v v v okay byebye take care
have a good rest of the morning after
see you guys tomorrow on R's Channel
okay byebye by
bye