[Music]
so
do
[Music]
you
oh
[Music]
please don't come too close or you might
catch
my cold
hmm
[Music]
how am i feeling
good question
next question
nah
i'm okay i think
um hello
i'm i'm okay i'm confused why am i here
i feel a little bit weird
maybe i have a fever
i don't have
i don't have um
you know
those fever thingies
um
[Music]
but
when i put my hand on my
forehead it feels hotter than yesterday
and my overall body feels
overall
a little bit feverish maybe
um
but
um i want to do some
super chat reading
because i feel
bad if i don't
why why not if i don't have one i don't
know cause i live alone and i never get
sick um when i used to live like my
family
we had one
but now i live alone so it's not really
here
usually not i need for it i just
oh this recently i've been getting
i got sick this is the second time in
one month
ah good excuse to get one now yeah
uh
well i mean it's 4 p.m now and i just
started streaming so i don't think it's
happening today
yeah it's it sucks because i need to be
fit
and healthy right now
oh i have music going on here this
doesn't
it doesn't quite fit the mood
but
yeah
it sucks it [\h__\h] sucks because like
recently i didn't stream much
because i was at dokomi
and then i was
of the night and i had a visitor aka
kelly
and then of course
the moment when i wanna get back into
streaming a little bit before i get busy
again right before my birthday
um
that's when i get sick that one week
where i could do something
but i mean i was gonna take it somewhat
easy this week anyway because i wanted
to
learn my dances
now even though i'm sick i've been
trying
but i'm scared
i have so much
so many songs planned
for my birthday
and um
and it was such a fight such a fight to
get get it all like you know approved
that it will actually happen
[Music]
it was such a fight
like there were many moments where it
seemed like it was it wasn't gonna
happen
so
now i finally got it to a point where
we're forcefully making it happen
with
with other
other
people's strength
[Music]
yeah i think i'll recover quickly
i yesterday
hmm
the day before yesterday it started
right at the outfit reveal
yeah my voice was feeling meh
and then
i feel hot [\h__\h]
ah [\h__\h]
and then today
uh no yesterday
um
i woke up with like really really really
strong pain
in my throat like i had trouble sleeping
too
and then
and then i got a friend to bring me some
medicine because it was sunday and you
know
pharmacies aren't really
open but there are a few ones and so a
friend went to one and got me some stuff
and orange juice
uh
what do we know
i don't feel well
[Music]
and then honestly yesterday after taking
like a painkiller and eating something
and sleeping some more
and then
walking around in my apartment
i felt pretty decent yesterday
so i
i
also was able to practice some dancing
[Music]
yeah
and then
now
now that i started streaming i feel
worse than before i started streaming
why
i think it's because i'm talking
[Music]
is it i have the humidifier on by the
way that could partially be a reason why
i feel
so
weird
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
um
then don't no the thing is i just
started feeling weird once i started
streaming
before i started i felt okay
but but we can um
we can try like reading a couple
superchats cause that's what i'm here
for
not gonna do too much
i'm not gonna do too much
stop talking chris like that
no it doesn't smell weird
i oh it's at 69
guys i turned it all the way up oh it's
oh
now um
to describe my throat situation
it feels like i have a frog in my throat
that's what we say in german
uh um
it's gotten better though
and then besides that
nothing much i feel a little bit like
weak overall
but nothing much besides i don't really
have like a cough
i just sometimes cough like once
uh
like a small cloth
when
my frog gets too close to
my
mouth huh no it doesn't hurt
it doesn't hurt it just feels like like
when i
cough that like um
i'm
[Music]
uh
choking
a little bit it's not so bad though
it's not so bad
i'm okay
uh
[Music]
i gotta frog someone else to get rid of
it was that me what does that mean
[Music]
yeah okay so let's read some super chat
so i at least get something done here
um
but where the [\h__\h] do i start
what was that thing what
what was that being called with
you guys
you guys showed me before when my super
chats didn't load
that there was like this website
right
this website where i can look at my
[Music]
my super chats
hello eliza okay
how do i colonizer
analyzer
colonizer kiara takanawa
[Music]
it doesn't come up
what's the website name holalizer.japan
oralizer.com
sir
eliza dot
started fall of train
net okay
ah
thanks
[Music]
oh my sub is already there kusa
um
where do i go
uh here's bacha oh
nice
okay
holy [\h__\h]
what how far behind am i
how far behind am i really
[Music]
i wouldn't read the ones from the
waiting room
um but i guess i have to read the ones
from the german crash course maybe
stanley stanley okay
all right let's meet stanley
sorry the cough is really just because
sometimes the frog
makes me
cough
because it feels like i'm choking okay
because that there's no air coming
through
don't worry about it it doesn't hurt
i'm okay it's not so bad it's not so bad
it's probably not so bad
i think
i'm okay i can dance a little bit
uh what was i gonna do oh yeah
thumbnails
there you go
work hard
wait where did the video
i was playing a video took the month
there where did it go
here here here
look
there it is
okay
those are really nice
just to keep going tomorrow
i know this is from the top or
no this is from where this is from
this is from the top
i think okay
[Music]
even i had full freeze that's perfect no
i had to cut something anyway
i had to cut the sides anyway
but it doesn't feel like there's so much
cut
as in comparison with the others
um
you know
i
i want to get something done so i won't
be tensioning much
i need to keep tangents for wind waker
anyway let's hope that i'll feel better
at wind waker weekend wind waker weekend
is so [\h__\h] cursed
[Music]
it's so [\h__\h] cursed
i don't know why i love the game but
like
me streaming the game is so great
[Music]
it gets cancelled so often and it gets
interrupted so often
by docomi or whatever name stick
oh man
oh yeah it doesn't want to play let me
play my favorite zelda game
it's not supposed to be spent on
weekends
is that illegal
[Music]
uh i have tea by the way and i have
orange juice and i have water i have
three different drinks in front of me i
also have some
some something that i can lick
and
i have two different things that i can
lick
and just before the stream i
i did that with some
green liquid
that
is very disgusting
yesterday it made me like
almost throw up because i almost
swallowed it
a gargle yeah
gargula
garge
let me try to
see
i just lifted the lid off of my
firmness bottle
and a little
a little drop of hot tea
landed on my thigh that hurt
all right let's pour
[Music]
tea
let's go
[Music]
that's nice
all right
we got some tea going on
it's a tea party
no no short pants
very short pants because i'm feeling oh
i'm feeling a bit better
i'm feeling a bit better than five
minutes ago let's go
okay
[Music]
let's go
these are a bit hard to see the red
thingy is so small
congress on the cover collapse
is amazing thank you
thank you
maybe i should stop looking so sad
i'm trying to look sick
okay
thank you very much er right ghana yes
it's been a while
did you all listen to the song
oh louie is in the ball
ah
[Music]
there you go
it's a blush and this is this is uh oh
my blush is not on this
model
this is my blushing
this is my normal face
and this
is only it only changes uh my eyes
i always have to ask them
to add the blush
[Music]
see there's like
very no difference
ah except that like if i have this face
on i can't make an oh mouth i'm just
always like ah
while this oh i can make a oh
[Music]
bedroom eyes
yeah if it was a little bit
a little bit more like my hearts hearts
would be nice hearts in my eyes would be
nice
[Music]
on the the closed eyes
oh [\h__\h]
closed eyes look a little bit different
you see
you see that
[Music]
elena has hearts on
ena
i want them too
a sick kiss i hope you're wearing your
mask though because i'm not wearing one
um merry favorite duncan
thanks for the hospital funds you meant
for them to be for the beatdown coyote
gave me in clubhouse but now
they're finding kind of a different use
mary
uh
induction
now they're even more useful than
back then
thank you appreciate it
at least they got used yeah
mr casper
radio sound oh wait what this shows the
memberships
[Music]
when people join the membership oh where
oh i can turn it off
oh it's just membership gifts but we
don't have that yet right we still don't
have it
[Music]
what's milestone
what's the milestone option 25
milestones
is that the the green messages the
membership greens
are the free ones i see
oh but that's
the only way i've seen so far to see
them
[Music]
huh
because like i looked for a youtube
studio but i could never find them
like
somebody told me i think
that there is a different like a special
window to see them
but i never found such a
window
and now whole mizer can show it though
wow and like that
thank you thank you maftin thank you
gibbles
[Music]
this is pretty good
thank you
but um for the sake of not dragging this
out for too long i'm not gonna read them
okay
oh
oh i can even even sort out the
oh i can even sort out the colors
i could i could delete everything but
pinks and reds
[Music]
it's been months since you got the fancy
herman miller chair how's your back do
you feel like it was the way foreign
i want to praise the chair
because i'm sure it's a great chair
but
i mean i feel like
the chair alone cannot
um correct my chronical
pain
i heard gouda
said that it helped her a lot
but
and i envy that
but i don't think a single simple chair
can really make such a big difference
alone
so
are your feet down
well
my left foot is down
so two chests yeah because i need to i
need them to heroin militias
[Music]
one of
how do i say this
there's at least one foot on the floor
how do i say this so that it could imply
that there is both
on the floor
um
there is
there is a foot on the floor
i'm sitting better than usual okay
don't you thought that that mean
[Music]
um
thank you for the pinky
in the style of an english football
chant we love your tension we do we love
your attention we do we love your
attention we do oh thank you we love you
is that how you would say it
how would you say that
we love your attention we do
know
we love you
love you thank you
we
where are the clubs shouldn't there be
some clowns
drunker and louder
i can't be drunker
and being louder at the moment is a
problem too
and shirtless
we loved and jolly
i only know that one
[Music]
you guys say that too
or do only germans say that
[Music]
oh
i guess olay sounds spanish i guess so
okay
thank you
for the pinky scratch pack me off thank
you and optimus prime duncan oh wait
scratch with me up says have you watched
the new trailer for pokemon style i
scarlet and violet no i haven't
i don't know it came out when i was busy
i think
i was doing something i was not i think
i was a dokomi or before that i don't
know
but
it didn't get much better did it
but what what did they
what's there to see
they didn't improve the faces of the
protagonists right
i wanna watch it yeah
i did professors i didn't say i did see
um
pictures of the professors
yes obviously i'll go for the girl
obviously professors i mean trainers or
whatever
um
yeah the professors look fine
i don't i i feel like
the others look fine just the
protagonists look like
they're from a ds pony game
[Music]
look fine
yeah i don't know they lost something
with the art style when making it into
3d
which is
unfortunate
optimus prime
[Music]
10-hour bus trip damn
thank you for coming
alina thanks for the rest of the chat
let's go
thank you
thank you very much oh
[Music]
sometimes for these like
stupid games i have to bring out small
kiwawa
the moon dog thank you for the red super
chat oh
i was able to represent cafe proudly at
least at the clown near me recently i
think i saw
well it can't be a document i can only
uh wish both you and all of kfb going
have uh go all of kevin going to have an
amazing time i'm super happy to see
everyone excited to go you hear the
sunshine every wednesday voila thank you
it's already been over a week
if not two
[Music]
was last was it last weekend
yeah i guess it was last weekend already
feels longer
it's already been a while
oh
this picture
[Music]
oh you shook on michael
oh man
good times
oh good times i want to go i mean
partially good times
wanna go
back oh see you guys again
i want to see you guys again the crony
flies yeah
ronnie stop lying get down here in an
instant
[Music]
well thank you moondog
i also saw the cheering video it was
great
thank you so much for the passion and
the love
one day you'll cheer like that
in a real audience with the others all
right and then you'll fit in just right
just perfectly
i can see i can imagine
one four two oh five seven darker shin
another wire and duncan
[Music]
oh my god
fascinating hololizer
is able to pick up my membership emotes
and any other emotes
unlike
the
youtube's owned
super chat
uh
thingy where you can read the super
chats
where i upload
the
the emotes in the first place
[Music]
i upload them directly onto youtube but
youtube is not able to display
the emotes in a super chat in the thingy
where i read them afterwards
but hololyzer is able to do it
[Music]
interesting
so now tai chi is notance is so
still not saying much in the super chats
but taiji at least
is now able to show me
his emotes
you
nice to see you had a good time at the
stream
[Music]
oh mario duncan met from
the map tron 5 000
[Music]
gas can dance
chris thank you
thank you
[Music]
skye thanks for the pinky
what does that mean
you want to want to play
me
you trying to push the play button on me
don't worry i'm currently playing you're
skipping me
no no no no no no no he's double playing
me because
he's so eager to play
my streams
no no no no no no you guys have no idea
[Music]
would never
skip me
no
no no
sky wouldn't no
i know skye
are you feeling boss better
better than at the beginning of the
stream
[Music]
i'm okay
it's just i'm not gonna go for too long
i i have a meeting later and i have to
practice
dances and in theory i have to do other
things too
ah
[Music]
um
amazing
thanks gentlemen
gemma wrote me something nice
i pressed the great
[Music]
is
there's like three free korean names
that i feel like i can read and then i
switch them up
i'm sorry
i bought it come sign me
i've decided on the month when i'm going
to korea
it will be august
august
destiny yes
yes
because um
nabi mama
yes i want to say nabi mama
[Music]
and she said after august musukashi
so we're gonna do it in
august
[Music]
yeah
oh i'm kind of nervous but i'm excited
oh yes yes yes
i wanna i want to
go to korea with an empty suitcase
and then go shopping shopping shopping
shopping shopping something something
something soft shopping something
and then go back with two full case
suitcases
i want to buy makeup and clothes
makeup and clothes makeup and clothes
makeup and clothes yeah
yes
i know i know
yeah we talked about that don't worry i
think we can still um
do
a collab
it should be fine
[Music]
yeah i like their fashion sense
i like ordered um stuff before from
korean fashion brands like there's a
brand called chu
c-h-u-b
i think two use
some cute stuff but my problem is
that um
the size i wasn't sure about the size
so some things
fit and some things don't
actually know i have one problem
with like high-waisted skirts
like when i buy like
uh
what's that s or m i don't know it
doesn't matter but when i buy
it around the hip
it's like super [\h__\h] tight but around
the waist
it's like still like so much space
and then the
the top of the skirt
like stands off quite a bit it looks
stupid
looks stupid
and that was i think s size
now if i buy hem size then at least my
hip won't be so uncomfortable
but then the waist will stand out even
more
i think it's because like generally the
cuts
and the cut is different
in like korean and japanese fashion
they cut it with less cur they cover
they cut it for less curvy uh bodies
and now you you know kiwa's hips don't
lie
[Music]
the best thing would be to buy m size
and then um
make the waist into like xs
if i could have a skirt that is both xs
and m at the same time
that would be amazing
kirby bonnie
nihontokan
foreign
my big purpose of dangerous size
could find a tailor yeah but i don't
want to bring every [\h__\h] piece of my
coffin to the tailor and be like fix
this for me
and with some clothes i feel like it
won't work that well anyway
because it will mess up the pattern or
so i don't know but i should try i've
never brought my clothes to a table
before
never tried it before did you guys do
that before
to change the size
it's not cheap fever is it i mean i i
i i i s
saw some suit solid
clothes
before
but i'm not like really that good i
would want someone professional to do it
i do it myself
not really
once or twice my tail was my godmother
ah
[Music]
and also i gave um my sewing machine
away
to my mom and then my second sewing
machine i gave to a friend
so now i don't even have my sewing
machines anymore
[Music]
i have to go for the tap to the table
for suits and it costs a lot
i hold on
pretty cheap and fast oh i guess it
depends on where which one you're going
to
[Music]
america's shop is four dollars to
shorten pants 12 the titan depends
but girls clothes is more expensive
really yeah
[Music]
that's not fair
why
oh well you bought it thank you for the
rest of the day
uh hi boss my hobby is growing plants so
i have to buy flowers but plant buy
money has already become a super chat
yeah you know what
your
super chat that you wanted to buy plants
with i use it to buy the plants on my
head
it was pretty flowers
[Music]
so thank you in the end
it's like you indirectly bought flowers
it's all good hentai
flowers on my head flower
flower
yes flower
[Music]
all according to plants
nice
thank you so much i'm known thanks for
the pinky thank you for another amazing
santa potential you and coyote sound
absolutely incredible i really love it
so much
i'll definitely be looping uh it along
with fever night and all the other songs
forever you're the best i love you so
much i know
thank you so much
i know you're so sweet
thank you
yeah for if anyone hasn't listened to
the coyote sound cover or fever night
yet
then what the [\h__\h]
what are you even doing here eh
hope you all did
um i'm currently working on the one with
reina
uh but i'm still waiting for the
translation so
uh
yeah the problem is i'm
not gonna be around all like the whole
month
so if it doesn't come like
this week then um
musukashi
but now i'm sick anyway
kind of sick anyway but i need to record
some other stuff too
[\h__\h]
reminder to kiwawa
reminder
right
[Music]
okay i wrote myself some reminders
on genma as if she was a posted
busy child
yeah
my my problem is also i am the
voice pack
recently i've been so busy i haven't
recorded it yet but like i really need
to
but i don't even know what to do
i still don't know what to do about the
wisdom
but it might just end up being a shorter
one
i still don't know what to do
i'm so sorry
jenna i'm so sorry
take care of six ten two points back
yes sick time to role play it won't
really be a role play for me maybe for
you
taking care of your sick boss oh
but that's
that's more of a pleasure for me than
for you guys like having someone well
then
now i would prefer you guys taking that
voice back
recording that voice back and sending me
your side of the role play
[Music]
yeah i feel like that that's more
something for me than for you
[Music]
take your pills shut up
speaking of take your pills
i called
one of my doctors
to send me a [\h__\h]
recipe because i'm sick
and i need a recipe and i can't go to
pick it up so she should send it via
email and she said ah we'll call you
back
and of course
she hasn't called me back
and i have not received an email
why are these people always so reliable
last time i had the same thing she said
oh yeah we'll send me an email next day
sorry you said you sent it via email
what happened with that oh okay i will
send it now one minute later it's there
like why couldn't you do that yesterday
huh
it was urgent
no
most of you in doctors i don't know
and this one's even a private doctor
sending me a private recipe
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i mean
prescription
and in german we say recipe
except
[Music]
also
and that's the last one from stanley's
parable we actually got something done
i am so proud
[Music]
incredible
so now
i will read german crash course
[Music]
right
i think
i think it's german crash course
[Music]
okay
no milestone no membership gift or no
membership okay
was it on purpose
i'm not sure if the complete was on
purpose because you have another typo
in your super chat and that doesn't look
like it's on purpose
instead of hiatus it says hi hi hats
you're still as cuddly as ever
i don't know if it's on purpose because
the curve is kind of a meme
an old meme
[Music]
i got you
too coffee julia are you right are you
writing it over c it's k
it's super ancient for the people who
don't get it it's okay it's a
old really
small hidden
meal within kfp
yeah yeah yeah yeah
it's just when someone type out love
instead of uh yeah and bro to come
how carrot will explain it
maybe yeah one day maybe
that one is oof how do you even get
the footage for that is that time
stamped anywhere
sounds tough to find
you look cuffly today
that's funny
it's funny because
you write it like
because i'm
sick
that is funny
oh
it's a preacher yeah but we did say it
on stream
right
[Music]
but yeah maybe maybe difficult one
all right uh feeling sad thank you for
the rest of the chat
thank you i hope you get plenty of rest
before and even after don't call me i
also just want to say sorry for not
being able to go once again this year i
watched the stream of course but i hope
that one day i'll be free to be there it
may take some time but i will be there
and i believe that i believe you
and i'll be waiting for you
[Music]
thank you
yeah
it's a heart for you
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat i'll be
waiting for you and all the other ones
who didn't make it to doko me this year
[Music]
i can't promise
so don't book anything yet
i can't promise that document will
happen next year
but
um at least something i want some kind
of gathering
somewhere
could be a different place
could be dokomi again i don't know
but yeah i want i want something
no don't book it you're stupid
do you even know the date yet for next
year has that been
set already because i haven't heard i
just heard it might be in summer
like more summer than this time
july
how do you know
that they say
sometime in 2023
[Music]
ah let's look at the tickets if you say
no don't worry now
it was my condition this year and it
would be my condition next year as well
to be announced before
tickets are sold out
and now this year there was some
complications
oh wait doctor's calling me one sec
[Music]
do
got it
i got it
[Music]
okay she's sending me the
recipe
[Music]
yeah yummy yummy recipe for a crispy
chicken burger
[Music]
crispy chicken
[Applause]
yummy
[Music]
i'm starting to feel
low energy but let's go i can do this
power fruit
[Music]
all right felix i'll see you soon
one day at a convention and a meet and
greet i would be very happy to see you
it's like
ah
finally having faces to some of you guys
just like last year as well
is such a
emotional and
intimate
thing
yeah i want that for all of you i want i
want
to see your faces and have a quick chit
chat one-on-one with all of you
so you better keep your eyes open for
any upcoming meet and greets in the
future okay
maybe maybe
maybe i want it so bad that i'm gonna do
um even without a convention and just do
like
zoom call meet and greets that we both
both parties will do from home
you know what in theory we could totally
do that
but no one's ever done that before
no one is so dead no one is so desperate
as i am
to see your face
but i mean you could still like
sell it as tickets
you know like um how about a birthday
meet and greet
uh 20 people can get a zoom call
with kiwawa 20 people randomly chosen
out of all of the ones who buy a full
merchandise set
[Music]
jedma you listening
how about we don't do the voice pack but
we do this one
[Music]
okay it could be more than 20 because
like i don't have to do them all in one
day
[Music]
i would kind of prefer this over a voice
back
[Music]
i'm in
yes i will save your faces
i kind of want to do
kind of an entrepreneur
yo
[Music]
i kind of want to do that
are you
are you listening
to my
ideas
[Music]
terabytes okay of people it's not a bad
idea
because i feel like especially for like
um the overseas
a whole life audience
voice packs are
i mean you guys will listen to it i
guess but definitely one thing i noticed
on my first birthday a lot of you guys
were like
what
what is this like what
what what is what is this anyway what is
this voice back thing i don't get it
she's talking to me
what is this
right so
like it's
yeah
in that case so meet and greet would be
more
way more interesting
but it's just not everyone can get it
[Music]
i'll discuss this and think about it
the frog
oh the frog is fine progress is fine
i love your two voice back really
[Music]
my two voice pack yeah that was for that
one at least i had an idea
and now i'm like what the [\h__\h] do i do
oh well
water the frog the what water frog is in
water
frog is in water already
look she's turning and turning as long
as she's turning she's fine
she stops turning then we should be
worried
gemma meet and greet
hey
no
hilar brings his beer at oktoberfest and
then scolds you for drinking alcohol in
the first place how about that
like here's your beer
but surprise surprise i made a
non-alcoholic you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
don't get drunk
i want you to be not drunk
welcome to oktoberfest have fun
without alcohol
don't you dare drink a sip of alcohol
i want
i want the
the clean and
say so
unchanged original you
i want the true
you
[Music]
no it's okay
whatever drink drink whatever it's not
like i care
nothing
[Music]
i don't need no drinks tonight give me
that big cat we don't sing feeling right
for me
[Music]
the way that you're moving you got me
shining glowing like a praise i'm not
discovering it makes me wow let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
okay don't shake my head too much
[Music]
thank you soon
i'm ready to be
fried you're you were born ready i know
are you already fried
are you fried
oh yeah i'm feeling exhausted a little
bit but i'm okay
i'm okay
[Music]
i'm missing from the [\h__\h]
it's almost over anyway but
um
[Music]
i always have trouble saying that one
out loud
thank you
almost almost
optimus prime dan kitchen
i love the order though
orphan of kamasum thank you thank you
thank you for your ransom chat red
apples let's go
thank you for the apples
i've been trying to eat some fruit i've
been eating kiwis
and i have some i have a lot of berries
for later
because uh
i read that kiwis and oranges and
berries and a lot of other stuff but
those are the three things that i
actually like
are good when you're sick because of the
vitamin c
because i've been drinking a lot of
freshly pressed orange juice
and
eating kiwis and berries
[Music]
too bad mommy couldn't make it for the
berries ah
the thing is
the berries
aren't ready
anyway
i've been um
looking at my berries
and you know the raspberries
they need a bit more time
they look like they need like like maybe
one or two more months
but the other ones that i had uh what
were they called in english
um
the small
red currant
um
i think
i might not really get anything out of
them this year
uh
they look like they didn't get enough
water to grow properly but
i'm still trying
i'm still trying we'll see we'll see
well
i'm gonna
try to revive them
and you know i thought i was giving them
too much water like a good amount
because my mom said you just have to
give them water once a week
so i gave them water
once two sometimes twice a week
and i thought i was even over watering
them maybe a little bit
but then my mom came by and checked them
and said
girl
what are you doing you need to water
them more and i'm like mom you said only
once per week is fine
but then she said yeah once per week but
then properly
apparently i won that one time per week
i just didn't give them enough
i gave them
i thought i gave them enough
i drowned them
but okay it wasn't enough maybe it
wasn't enough
no what does that mean probably
yeah very first berries
[Music]
we added some parsley and some fine
as well
and cherry tomatoes oh i hope the cherry
tomatoes work i love cherry tomatoes
[Music]
i'm done
this is next
this this is next
[Music]
this one is a little bit longer than the
others
[Music]
no i'm not stopping maybe after this one
i don't know
[Music]
thank you for the pinkie
welcome home kiwawa after 12 hour plus
travels what
after 12 plus hours of travel
starting at 3 am i was welcomed home by
my parents and dog he has gotten cuddles
of course dokomi was a treasure
experience for me
and all the other chickens here
there i'm so happy i got to cheer for
your life thank you
yeah it's
crazy
i didn't think you would come from so
far but you did it thank you so much
12 hours is a very very long time oh no
i mean
i've done 12 hours of travel many times
to japan
but no it's still still a long trip and
expensive i assume
thank you for coming from so far to
support me it really means a lot to me
and i'll remember that
[Music]
thank you very much
almost everyone else who was there of
course
[Music]
thanks for the red and the pinky
wait
it's hard time
yeah red and pinky
[Music]
purple says
i'm sorry for repeating myself but you
gave me the best weekend for real really
and i lost it when the dancers came on
stage that was really awesome my first
convention ever and thanks to it was a
really awesome experience for me i
wouldn't have thought that i would cheer
on
a concert ever because i'm really shy
but your show distract me to stand up
and which wish and towel yeah yeah
meet and greet was really special i was
so nervous but with your sweet and calm
talking way i felt comfortable right
away
thank you kiwawa okay if he loves you
thank you too
yeah um
first of all
there's so many people who said this was
their first convention
last year as well
but this year even more
yeah a lot of people told me they don't
go to conventions usually or it was
really the first one ever
so that was a big surprise for me i
thought because you guys you i think at
least we share the interest of like
anime
that kind of stuff
i would have thought that at least
you would go to conventions every now
and then
[Music]
because we share similar interests
oh
i was surprised just hear that from so
many of you going alone isn't very fun
ah
i guess
i think the
the key
anna
is to go to conventions when you're
younger
where you don't care yet about like
being alone
and then there you make friends when
you're alone that's how i my current
close knitted group of friends
we like it originated from conventions
literally like i didn't know many people
either but actually yeah
what's my first one i think so my first
now my first convention i went with with
like a school friend
and then uh after that my second
convention
i went to alone
from austria to germany
[Music]
and i took upon like a nine hour train
ride i think something like that many
years ago to leipzig book fair which i
told you before is more like an anime
convention partially
[Music]
and then i was
i
i might have had
um
how to say
uh
a bonus
that made it easier for me
um
because
let's say i was dressed up
and that you know gets so many people to
talk to you because like people are like
can i take a photo
and then there's other people maybe that
um
i don't know wear something from the
same anime or whatever
so that helps i guess
um but yeah i didn't i didn't really
unknow people but at that point i didn't
care so much yet about that nowadays i
would not go to a convention
i guess if i don't know anyone going
there
i don't think i would go alone
i think i would always want to go with
someone i need to drink my tea
[Music]
so yeah the key is to go early then make
friends when you're still like in your
teens
and then you
then you know people
yeah
but if you miss that time window i
understand
it might be difficult
yeah
it's easy if you're like if you go to an
anime convention
with
like a specific
uh
how to say
a specific
like like like as a photographer or as a
cosplayer or
or what else is there
i i really only know
those two things
uh
i guess you could go
ah what okay once i went to
japan expo
because
um my favorite aloe group was performing
there
and
yeah
i was mostly alone
but there at least during the concert
when i was also standing in line
um
i was chit-chatting with the people
there
with the people who are standing in line
because we had the same interest
but besides that was mostly alone but i
was still like somewhat somewhat
enjoying it
[Music]
in any case now you have a reason to go
to conventions
you're not alone because i'm sure you
can find people
within the community who go to the same
convention some kind of people
yeah you can go with them even when i'm
not there if you feel like oh i kind of
want to go to a convention again you
know what that was kind of fun
let me find out if other cave people are
going to this convention
maybe maybe i can hang out with them
i don't need to be there
you'll be fine on your own
but of course it's more fun with kiwawa
yeah
yeah so uh thank you very very much
forever
i'm so happy you made that step and i
totally understand what you mean with
like shy normally so don't want to go to
concerts and all that but then at an
idol concert
you know most people who go to idol
concerts in japan as well aren't
shy people not so outgoing people
kind of like otaku thai people
[Music]
i i've seen it many times
but then
once the music starts
everyone just melts into one
one entity and everyone has fun with the
chance and with the dances
it's
very different i think from like rock
concerts or whatever
[Music]
yeah
so let's do it again
miss this faction time donation for the
pinky
ah welcome back and thank you for
another amazing performance i was blown
away especially with the journey of
thousand years but
the entire show felt like you had uh you
like you at your best hope you had a
great weekend you certainly gave all of
us one
thank you kiwawa
thank you
[Music]
thank you very much
for the sweet words i'm glad you enjoyed
it yeah i sang a
journey of a thousand years alone
my
set list for this year just like last
year i felt like i want to mix original
songs with some
anime songs that everybody knows because
it is an anime convention
um
yeah yeah now i make a make a difference
in choosing what i would sing
and add my convention versus what i will
sing
at um
at my 3d
birthday i was so happy to start a song
oh yeah start a song was fun to sing and
fun to learn
i thought i should sing some new ones
that i haven't sang before
so i grinded learning that song
i heard viva happy for the first time
well viva happy i'm gonna be honest i
only really chose viva happy
um because of the
choreography i chose it with
the thought in mind that i'm gonna have
dancers
specifically two dancers
and the viva happy choreo
is made for two dancers
so normally if i didn't have dances i
probably wouldn't have chosen viva happy
but i like a song i like the song it's a
fun song
i know the dance too
it's a cute dance yeah
[Music]
that's what this song was called yeah
viva happy
birthday
[Music]
um
it was a bit difficult to sing this song
with the instrumental that i had
because uh it's difficult to sing it
alone
and there was no like background voices
in the instrumental
that could cover for that
and some lines have a really really
distinct timing
and no music like it's like there is
like no music it stops
and then you have to sing
[Music]
m
[Applause]
[\h__\h] frog
frog crazy frog
what's the crazy frog song like again
am a crazy friend
wow
[Music]
new sound cover
oh she's dying mamma mia
[Music]
lord evoke
um i really hope i'm not mixing up
people here but i'm pretty sure
i love your accent
this is also a great thing
some of the meet and greet people had
really nice accents
and now when i read your chat messages
in my mind i read it in your accent
it's
[Music]
[Laughter]
you really had that typical italian
accent it was so good
um it's so good
yes i recall your accents unless the
ones that stood out strongly um
you know the moment he
i think i remember this the moment he
like
walked in and then we started talking
and i heard his accent
um
i think he knew what was coming
and i i think for a moment i wanted to
hold it back because it's so typical
but i think
very quickly i let out mamma mia
[Music]
and i think in his mind he was like
mamma mia of course she was gonna say
this but i'm not even mad at this no no
no
i knew it was gonna happen
ah
of course
you cannot you
cannot come in here
with an italian accent
and not expect me to be like uh
like
italiano
[Music]
i love it
it's very very very very nice to hear
[Music]
nice tea
so okay where the hell am i solas kiwi
thank you
for the ransom check
here's a heart for you
wow doctor dot just wow dot i understand
a little bit of how dominic feels like
now dot helping to put together
something for kfp and see pictures of
people enjoying what you helped build
dota dot document this year was so
ambitious compared to last year dot
thank you for amazing time
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
glad you enjoyed it glad you came
to the convention to dukami once again
yeah
you say it was so ambitious compared to
last year
[Music]
yeah i definitely wanted it to be like
improved
at least for you guys i want i wanted it
to be a better
experience
because i knew so many of you were
coming from uh far away so i wanted it
to be worth it
[Music]
yeah um
so thank you very very much
it will only grow from here
your accent is our double excuse me
my accent what accent
you mean my italian accent all right
yes so soda i hope i hope uh it was
worth it for you i hope you made some
nice beautiful memories
had a great time i hope and maybe maybe
we can repeat it again another time
thank you so much
[Music]
you definitely have an accent boss says
the german one
funk
i think you have a stronger accent than
i do
[Music]
now i can roast you with my with my
knowledge with my dokomi knowledge
[Music]
yes guilty
at least you admit
[Music]
a chimken accent i can hear the verb
coming through what
i'm not with chimkin accidentally even i
have a phoenix accent
hello
[Music]
welcome back boss this weekend was a
blast what i experienced cheering and
dancing in your concert is something
that left a mark on me thanks for
listening to my nervous ramblings at the
meet and greet can't wait to meet you
again to a radiant future for you and
hear me i'm so sorry
i love you i'm sorry i love you thank
you so much
thank you
i wish we could have done the meet and
greet forever and ever yeah i'm sorry
that i also like had to cut everyone so
short
um i mean not short but like i always
have to tell you guys sorry it's
actually
actually time to go
but i hope you have no regrets and had a
good time
you know whatever
yeah
thank you so much for your love and your
support i hope also that you made some
friends and memories at the convention
it's so nice to have so many cave people
from all over the world come together
in germany
wow
i feel like we made the convention very
international more international unusual
because like usually dokomi already has
a lot of visitors from like
austria the netherlands
some from italy some from france
like the close by european countries
they do go to dokomi some of them
because it's very well known and very
big
um
but this time holy [\h__\h] we had so many
from out of outside of europe
wow
different continents
[Music]
meow
america
[Music]
wow
um
[Music]
there's a [\h__\h] frog
in my throat
[Music]
most men never get to meet their heroes
or tell them how much they mean to them
is this some
reference to the panel
about childhood heroes
i am beyond blessed to have been able to
this weekend thank you for listening to
me spill my heart out you a little
ah
i thought you what you missed the word
[\h__\h] and you were calling me a little
[\h__\h]
but i read it wrong thank you for
listening to me spill my heart to you
a little
[Music]
i was like oh this little [\h__\h] is
calling me a little [\h__\h] well you little
[\h__\h] better shut your little shitty
mouth
but no all good oh good oh good all good
we're good here no no fighting
[Music]
no one calls me
the little [\h__\h] master
a little [\h__\h]
i am the one who gives out the little
shits
[Music]
uh never forget this adventure it was
the best weekend of my life
thank you
it was a short one
but yeah it wasn't it was great for all
of you i think i also listened
uh you may have seen
i i didn't get bunked yet by the way i
don't know if gemma even knows
um
but when was it the day before yesterday
[Music]
i saw
that you guys were doing a big
kfb after document twitter space
[Music]
and i was like
i genuinely am interested in what you
guys say about it
but
kind of hard to enter without being
noticed
um
so i entered and i listened
and then i couldn't hold back and i
wanted to
say a word or two myself
yeah
but surprise i thought you guys would
freak out way more
yeah
um
maybe it was all because only like how
many like 10 people or so were able to
talk at once
but i was a little bit disappointed in
your excitement about me being there
excuse me
why
what was there no
cats
you guys were all surprisingly chill
about it
trying to act casual
yeah you tried to play it cool huh
yeah
wow impressive
and that was nice listening to your
thoughts about how dokomi was for you
not only for the ones who went to
it's in person but also for the ones who
went to
watch the twitch stream only
even those people had some nice things
to say like saying that
the
whole atmosphere came through
even when they were
looking at it from home
and like looking at the tweets and all
that
i got spooked when your voice came out
of my headphones
we screamed internally
yeah you better
you better
you make us feel very comfortable around
you yeah
oh come on
[Music]
okay they're cool yeah you did a good
job that one's not a microphone screen
yeah probably or they were just they
kept themselves muted
yeah
uh i keep on trying to like uh
swallow the frog but it just always
stays in the middle of my throat
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] frog
[Music]
hell mate
bloody
helmet
it's a persistent frog no if only it was
froggianna
brianna is still here right i didn't
swallow her look at her she's turning
i'm turning
is chew yes i have to chew them no
i didn't
i got frogged
[Music]
callie told me she's already feeling
better or like normal again good for her
she apologized a million times to me
because she got me sick
and you know
like
the on the first day where we hung out
she wasn't like sick yet
and then on the second day
i've noticed oh
now hold on
you have become become sick
but like at that point
you know i had the whole day planned out
uh like what to do with her i wasn't
gonna just leave her alone in the hotel
room just so that i wouldn't get sick
and we both actually were wearing our
masks a lot of the time anyway even
though people
literally everywhere
kept on telling us oh take off your mask
take off your mask because in austria
now you um don't have to wear your mask
anymore in most places
they lifted it pretty much everywhere
um except for like public transport
and um
yeah they kept on telling us they're
gonna take off your mask take up your
mask and we're like um
no so generally uh we like to wear our
masks just because
and then also
what i didn't say is that kelly was sick
yeah we had two good reasons number one
we wanted to wear them and number two
kelly was sick
well i still got sick and i think it
might have been
if it wasn't the whole day
before the karaoke then it was
definitely at the point of the karaoke
where she was singing her lungs out
right next to me
that was definitely
my
what's the
what's the word my my my
my
deaf judge thingy
come on in slam and welcome to the gym
my downfall yes
[Music]
my verdict yes
but oh yeah didn't really talk about
that
[Music]
i guess i could talk about it during
wind waker
um
but yeah overall
i mean originally more people were
supposed to come
um
but in the end the only one who came was
kelly
and i appreciate that
i appreciate that she came
and i tried my best to
you know make it interesting for her
and um
put together
you know it was right after me coming
back to dokomi and before dokomi i was
swamped too
so overall i didn't have much time to
prepare a lot of things but i still
managed to fill out the day
completely with activities
and
find nice restaurants
so
we did we didn't go the ferris wheel not
for dinner because i had some problems
booking that we just went to the ferris
wheel normally
and that was nice
and we did the
the horse ride horse carriage ride
we went to a nice cool museum
um
normally i'm not a museum type of person
but i enjoyed that very much it was
really cool
uh we got to eat so much good food i
showed her really beautiful
sights
[Music]
yeah
i was i think i did a great job filling
up the day
with things
that
she would hopefully enjoy
[Music]
what else to do i don't know what you
did so far
uh
if you're in
if you're in vienna
i don't know what you what did you do so
far pat
patsy
paxy is currently traveling for austria
how was how south spoke you went to
salzburg right
and you went to houston right
how was salzburg
well let me hear what's your what you
saw so far been visiting a lot of places
it doesn't help me
did you go to okay i'll give you two
things that you will have to go and see
if you haven't seen it yet
um the belvedere
and the gloriette
but definitely the glorious
um it's the gloriette is on top of a
hill
and it overlooks the whole city
it's amazing
you could even walk up all the way
or you can take a public transport or
uber
to go to the very top and then walk down
i recommend that one because that's more
comfortable
that's also where a zoo is but i don't
care about the zoo
i haven't seen the glory yet yet you
have to
yeah go all the way up there and then in
the gloriette there's a nice cafe
uh
the gloria inside is so beautiful like
it has a huge insane ceiling
with like wow beautiful like i don't
know stuff up there
and then you can all overlook the whole
city
from there you can sit outside and
on the grass
at the water and then you go down and
then you go uh through the schonbrunn
palace
and backseating he asked for it
he asked for it and then you go through
the for the palace and there's like a
rose garden and [\h__\h] it's beautiful
[Music]
yeah but definitely not gloriette go
there go go go go go go
okay i had a nice view
what
which one
what did you see in in salad's book
you you did uh
[Music]
you did the sound of music tour
i like i did that one before i wonder if
we did the same one
was there an enthusiastic guy singing
the whole time
[Music]
nice sound music tour is fun
it's so tacky but you get to see a lot
of things with the tour
while enjoying the sound of music um
music
enjoying the sound of music
[Music]
yeah of course there's a tour for that
because so many american tourists come
from america
to check out
where santa music was filmed
which was in salzburg
mostly
[Music]
with the sound of music
i am 16 going on 17 no no no no no no
no no no no no
[Music]
no
my favorite face i love that
um
favorite things ah
how's it go again
um my favorite things
those are my favorite things think of
ariana grande
ah because she did a like a cover kind
of
huh i forgot what's the words what was
the lyrics again
these are a few of my favorite things
yes
[Music]
rain drops
i feel like i have a fever but i
am decently fine so i'll tangent on
[Music]
okay i need to stop
my throat
[Music]
let me finish this these super chats
and then then we went
we went so far with the tangent where
are we where are we cuckoo
it's a dust and stuff
uh
oh thank you gerard
jim tries to dance for the pinkie one
full year in campaign what a year it's
been so much fun and so many memories
i'm so glad i decided to officially join
got to know so many cool people and
support the best bourbon in the world
much love and can't wait to see what the
next year holds thank you you're so
sweet too tracy thank you for
a full year oh my god you're still here
it's an honor thank you soon i
appreciate it
hopefully you can also be part of a
concert audience one day like the others
i want all of you to be there i'll try
to
have a concert at a convention in
america
one day
okay
enough and you all better move your
butts your lazy butts
i know america is big but i don't give a
[\h__\h] if i go so far to come to america
we don't know how often that's gonna
happen so you better come okay
doesn't matter if it's on the other
coast
[Music]
yeah
you gotta be there or be square
at least for the american ones no no no
no you germans don't need to go
you have dokomi or whatever convention
anyway i'm so close anyway
you'll get enough chances
you don't have to go unless you want to
[Music]
i don't want to be square right you
don't want to be square
almost like texas
don't want to look like that
[Music]
those hard rough edges
i'm canadian america is too far
well
i cannot
be at a convention in every single
country of the world unfortunately
but connect cat canada canada
canada still seems kind of
in the realm of possibilities
canada
[Music]
i can't
like
do much more for you guys than try to
come to your country
but then
you gotta help me out there i can't be
in every [\h__\h] city of the whole
[\h__\h] world
that's a little bit mutsukashi
not cantata
[Music]
i'm gonna pour my hot tea over you
oh man
don't look at me with that face
the innocent face
it's morbid time thank you so much
thank you for the two pinkies and thanks
for
coming to talk of me to see me it was a
pleasure
your concert was absolutely insane i
couldn't feel my arms at the end there
i'm glad you took it seriously though
because i know like most of the people
in the middle of the audience they were
using the arms and the ones on the sides
they were just like
mostly watching
calmly
so my favorite people are the ones in
the middle
[Music]
yes
i appreciate
the passion
of every single one of you guys who
raised their arms and stood up
for the concert
i'm so glad to have this document as my
first real convention thank you for your
patience during meet and greet and sorry
about the babbling my mind went blank
there several times about the unusual
gift i know it's a bit imperfect but i
will be crafting a better one once the
package from the uk ordered one month
ago we'll finally leave customs health
and bring it to nexcon as a gift 2.0
thank you
speaking of gifts um
dokomi
uh sent me the gift so they should
arrive sometime this week
[Music]
did you watch your performance on twitch
i've been trying not to watch the whole
thing um i watched some bits of the
parts of the dancers
but i've been trying to not watch much
more because i wanted to watch it
together with you guys but i don't know
when
[Music]
we might not have time for it until
after
or like right before my birthday
damn it
yeah
i've been trying to avoid it
but i want to see
so i definitely watched draenei
circulation because i uploaded it
uh
not according to
keikaku yeah i wanted to um upload the
other videos too yes yes yes did the the
ones with the dancers yes
uh
okay continuing thank you silly slappy
fellow and don't worry about it it was a
pleasure to talk to you you were a
little bit of a what do you call it
wary bug or what do you what do you call
that when people worry too much you
worry too much
is that it's all good
no need to worry about anything you said
i worry what ah there we go
[Music]
everything is okay
yeah
it was nice getting to know you yeah
hopefully it wasn't the last time thank
you so much
[Music]
thank you
mr big
no
[Music]
i'm so sorry
oh
[Music]
i want to repeat it because it seems
like that could make you sad again
but
feel feel hugged by all of kfp
okay
that sounds very very
rough i would be
i would be like
so so so
sad for
months
so take your time
it's okay to be sad
you mostly have been able to move on
all right then
but yeah still it's okay to be sad okay
[Music]
um
cat is hopefully now unhappy
cat heaven with lots of kibbles and
snacks
and burps to hunt
happy cat
that's the spirit yeah
let's be happy chin up
from how i read it it seems like you
still have
other cats so
i hope they're fine though because i've
heard like before
when
people have like more than one cat and
then one of them dies that the other cat
can get very depressed
and not handle it very well
maybe even handle it worse than a human
[Music]
so
i hope you give other cats much much
love i hope they're okay
[Music]
yeah
and if you only have one cat left then
you might want to get them a new body
so that they can
play with someone two more one of them
stopped eating as much as he used to but
he seems to have gotten better
okay but yeah
continue monitoring it
if they're doing okay
sad but at least they still have company
[Music]
that's so sad i don't want to think
about that man it's so sad
dragon birdie duncan thank you
oh i want to send a quick thank you for
the amazing salad uh dokomi i met and
talked to so many kind camping it was
seriously the best experience i've had
in a long while
i also think i'm addicted to otake now i
want more
oh i'm so happy to read that thank you
yeah i kept my
guides
um fairly simple
of course they can get way more
complicated
um
but yeah uh i think you guys said you
wanted to come up with uh something
maybe
you're welcome to do that
i just wanted to give you guys like a
push
to get into it
uh because you guys were all kind of
mostly first timers and i thought you
might need a push
[Music]
egg egg was a good meme you mean you
mistyped and you wanted to ride it was a
good help right
[Music]
need to get me some pen lights for
concert yes
if i ever have like a proper concert in
a venue
a kiwa only concert
i'll definitely sell pen lights as a
merchandise
along with some other things
captain meow
thank you so much for the pinkie and for
coming to dokomi
welcome back here look me is an amazing
experience
i was overwhelmed by everything that
happened i walked nearly 40 kilometers
and took me but i did not feel tired at
all
i'm so glad that i had a chance to talk
to you thank you attention care people
thank
ah it you nice to have you there thank
you for coming also from very very far
i really really really appreciate it
yeah powering through 40 kilometers well
the convention really was very big
a lot of walking especially like outside
on the way to the convention in the
lines yeah
[Music]
sorry my bro hurts
time to take one of these thingies one
second
[Music]
oh yeah right now studying in germany oh
yeah right that was true sorry
me stick
[Music]
yes still
still still
so thank you so much i hope you had fun
and
had a good time there
maybe you lost some weight with walking
so much
thank you so much
see you again another concert please uh
you're so sweet
[Music]
your voice sounds like a dream it feels
worse though and it feels like my throat
is on fire
scratch cut me off thank you shank
oh thank you
thank you thank you cow carrot duncan
roccatia
thank you for the pinkie
uh
what
it's never one of those
what if
yeah let's say you are sent to a world
where amma and bayer are living in the
basement
of linz international lisa what is that
would you take this as an opportunity to
spend time with them or would the fact
that they live in the school be too
off-plane
[Music]
that is such a weird
situation that you're creating
it's like in what world
okay and i say what what it literally
starts with let's say you're sent to a
world where this and that happens yeah
but in what world
[Music]
and what
of course i would spend the time with
them
of course i would
i don't even know that school why the
[\h__\h] do you know that school i don't
know that school
[Music]
yeah they're hypothetical
i don't know
well
thank you
thank you for the red subject
[Music]
went from korea
to dokomi in germany
to see me
and you were literally just there for
how many nights like three four five
nights
[Music]
incredible
thank you i i really didn't think
like anyone from korea would come for me
to germany and i don't want to make
anyone feel like bad that they didn't go
because i just didn't have that kind of
expectation
[Music]
wow i was so surprised
traveling from korea to my first anime
convention ever
it was a dream come true hopefully you
like my gift i forgot to tell you there
are so many korean viewers lurking
around we all support you and love you
really
[Music]
m
oh my god
[Music]
unbelievable
oh my god
[Music]
korean hearts for you
korean heights for you
you know with the hands um
i um
when i was like
uh telling
hook about that i wanted some hand
options
um i was like
i didn't want to do the exactly same
ones as as like amen did before
but i wanted some that are useful and
then i also had some before you know
like the simple fists
and the pointy finger
so it needed to be something different
that could still be useful and i didn't
really
i feel like there really weren't that
much more good options
[Music]
but then i went for
the cute
as hell heart pose
and the
these oops you know whoopsie got it this
one
[Music]
yeah
this one really works for a lot of
things that can be like no
no
you're sad don't look at me it's
embarrassing or like oh surprise wow
we're like happy
[Music]
yeah that one works pretty well
and the hard one now i can use during
superchat reading
and for cute thumbnails
[Music]
so very very very useful
i gave very exact
uh poses
pose references as to what i wanted and
what i needed looks like a yarn yeah it
can look like a yarn too
[Music]
like when i cough
i cough in my hand now guys please don't
do that
i hate it whenever i see people coughing
in their palm of their hand
please do not do that
please cough into your elbow
okay
i'm i'm a youtuber so i'm allowed to do
this
[Music]
just don't
don't cough into your hand and then
touch people
yeah damn
do the dab do them
all right all right i need to move on
thank you
really really really really it means so
much to me thank you so much i hope that
i can
return the favor
and come to korea um to an event in
korea
i know you've been like trying really
hard to get like events attention
and i'm sure it will work out eventually
thank you
one day yes
i'm excited i want to meet korean fans
korean mean and great
[Music]
i hope they speak english
thank
you for the pinky
i hope you had a best time i took me
enjoyed seeing everyone posting and
appreciated all the love given also
akira posted a beautiful artwork on the
27th
about the newsroom so can i be sent
there please
no
you know i don't do this on like
requests no
[Music]
you have to do something that gives me a
good reason to send you there no it's
not for pleasure no no
but thank you for watching the concert
thank you soon
[Music]
optimus prime done kitchen
thank you come sanita
dokami was just wonderful meeting you
and so many chimpkins and how much work
and love and passion you and everybody
everyone put into this event was just
truly astonishing i just felt joy and
love all around what a glorious happy
experience thank you
optimus another person never chicken
who i now no i mean i guess you had your
face on your profile picture since
before
but
but it was different now i was able to
see it move
so that was special
yeah handsome yeah
uh-huh
yeah it was nice talking to you very
very chill
thank you so much for being there
i hope you had a great time
um
[Music]
it's live today
indeed yeah
i miss it already i miss you and the
other is everybody
[Music]
ah
thank you another time we shall meet
again after miss prime
minister thank you for the pinkie
i'm so excited for this stream i always
sadly watched and never participated
this joke of me was overwhelmingly
amazing i missed out on such a great
community
thank you cathy thank you kiara i'm so
incredibly happy i met you see
you hear this guys
all the lurkers are you listening
a kfp
chicken
who was a lurker
met all the wonderful cave people at
dokomi
and is now like
out there
[Music]
trying to be part of the community
and regrets not doing it earlier
what do we learn from that huh
[Music]
you all shall take an example
by me lunenburg
stop learning
i drive a lot i'm here okay okay okay
okay okay
i'm feeling called out
[Music]
no but i'm honestly so proud
i'm so proud that you guys are
such a sweet community and people feel
so comfy
[Music]
you had so much fun like going to
karaoke and eating dinner together and
all that
and bonding
it's nice to see that
very proud i'm very proud
[Music]
it makes me happy to see you guys happy
see you guys finding like new friends
[Music]
i'm going to convince you for the first
time and then having such a great time
that you want to go again because of
you know kfp and kiwawa
yeah yeah it just feels too good to
learn
it feels better to come out
fb
you better be talking
i'm sick
i'm sick too right now you better be
nice to me i don't have the energy to
put you all into the usual room i don't
have i really don't have the energy
please
please be nice to me
i'm using up so much energy
and i don't have
my original sub channel okay that's okay
using the sick card yeah cause i am sick
[Music]
thank you for the soup
don't i look so cute
don't look at me
don't i look so cute in this new outfit
huh if it oh my god if it's just this
part it almost looks like a wedding
attire
[Music]
with the flowers and the updo
the choker
white lace
oh my god
yes i do yes i do
[Music]
i am yes i know
cute
cute wow
how are you know
[Music]
oh
first convention first time in germany
thank you
maybe i hope you have a good time
super snake mario dancing for
i saw your concert online since i
couldn't be there in person but you were
so good it was a lot of fun to watch
uh you're truly an amazing performer i
love you singing so much i can't stop
singing of your songs during my day
during my day today
oh thank you
yeah everybody who wants to twitch
stream as well thank you very much i
think
i think you know even uh watching it on
twitch it must have been pretty damn
good
yeah
i think i chose some good songs
[Music]
on and at that stage as well
the stage was made for dokomi and for
the outfit review
it's kind of german themed german
festival aka oktoberfest themed
carnival themed
[Music]
yeah put effort into it
i'm glad you guys enjoyed it all
even from a distance thank you thank you
thank you i love you too
[Music]
thank you you also came to the meet and
greet yeah
thank you so much thank you and leave a
closer
let's have you fine
thank you for the love
hopefully
we can do it again
thank you so much for coming
and you got your employee number now hey
nice uh didn't i give you the number at
the meet and greet
i feel like
i gave you the number at the meet and
greet right
yeah yeah
i think you were the only one who asked
me for a number at the meet and greet
and then i gave you the date of dokomi
as the as the um employee number
very special number you got there
um
ask something how did you survive those
idol concerts of your noodle arms
it was absolutely amazing to cheer you
on with the rest of kp but i was so
exhausted after your concert i gotta hit
the gym so next time i can up by
cheering yeah i heard a lot of
complaints from you guys about that
[Music]
i think
uh
for me at idle concerts it wasn't quite
so bad
because um
uh
it was more like a mix of
you know the pen night moves
and
um
choreography from
like
the songs that they would perform
so maybe my arm was in general
more
in movement
like in different positions
uh
but in any case
what i can say
to that
[Music]
y'all are weak as hell
so you better continue
lifting those weights
[Music]
ah
i'm not asking you to run a marathon
i'm asking you to
wave those pen lights
uh-huh
if you're a weed on your mum you [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah the rare time that i can call you
cheap
it's weak yes
[Music]
do you even lift bro
you don't live do you
[Music]
you just need more
i don't know more
[Music]
i have to say
you guys probably were so serious about
it
that your arms were like very tense
you need to be less tense
you need to have more
what's a rap word
swoosh
[Music]
and more
no that's not the word that i mean
[Music]
but i guess that works too
yeah you guys are probably just too
tense you need to be more relaxed
and just go with the flow
[Music]
[\h__\h] hot mate
oh
burnt my tongue mate oh my god
so anyway
it was absolutely mentioned here i don't
know your recipe but i was so exhausted
after your concert gotta hit the gym
next next time i can upload sharing
well then maybe in one year
you'll be like really really buff
and you'll be able to lift more than two
pen left you'll be able to lift 20 pin
lights at once oh that wait that wasn't
the problem
i'm looking forward to your
transformation
thank you
[Music]
glad that you participated though even
though it was exhausting it means a lot
to me
maybelline thank you for a red super
chat as well great to hear you again
boss glad to hear dokami was a good time
for you and everyone who attended but
there is one burning question that needs
answering when genma got her phoenix hug
payton pay pay 10 pending
how many ribs did you crush my money is
still on free
nah no ribs
what i can say is
this time
this time the farewell
was less painful
because i know i know
for a fact i'll meet her again this year
[Music]
so yeah
i'm excited for that that that lifted a
lot of the pain when leaving
and i didn't have to wait so long to see
her again
[Music]
yes yes yes
thank you maybe
[Music]
me this was the first time i traveled
out of my country alone i learned a lot
and also was the most outgoing i've ever
been wow
i might also have missed the side of the
concept because i got lost in the venue
oh no i hope it wasn't too much
now well i hope that a lot of you
learned from this year to be early next
year uh
it wasn't really your guys's fault
just uh actually you know what i won't i
won't accept such an early time slot
anymore
because it's really dangerous like what
if like even even if
the whole waiting line outside was
acceptable
even then
let's say for example that train
problems
people have
delays well it would be best if you
could be there one day before but if
you're actually you have to go on the
very day
then having the concert at 11 o'clock is
big
yeah
i know there were a lot of waiting
people who wanted to watch it but
couldn't get in because they were still
outside of the convention
in the line
moving slowly
and just couldn't make it
yeah
so i know i i i personally didn't want
to be
the first act of the day if i
could have chosen i would have been the
last one
[Music]
but at least this way
it was possible to do the meet and
greets until after the venue closed
because there was no concert that i had
to do
we could just go on and on and on and on
and on and on and on until we were
finally finished with the meet and
greets
woke up at 6 40 didn't get there till 9
30 because of buses
these two beings are early let's reserve
middle seats for cheering yes
[Music]
a forest fairy
messaged me
hey
[Music]
hey listen
okay i need to read some chats
while i'm waiting for her reply
yeah
thank you tonian really it was nice nice
to have you there next time you won't be
late i know
[Music]
okay
was all the people that were still there
past 8 p.m
and you are still doing fine i just
forgot almost everything i wanted to
tell
i can't believe
you know i was i was already like
exhausted during the meet and greets um
you know
backstage uh with no break
but
you guys were also the ones that were
like
in the later hours
you guys were also waiting for hours
right you didn't you had to stay there
in line right at the mean and great you
couldn't like go anywhere right
so the ones that were there at the very
end past 8 00 pm ooh that means that you
already waited for like three hours
in line
what did you guys do
what did you guys even do
did you
watch kiwawa archives or what did you
even do i was there for moral support
that's so sweet
i'm so swayed
we talked with one another we flirted
with each other
[Music]
and for free four actually was four
hours in total we had so much to talk
about for four hours
watching videos twitter
was there a whole life member streaming
during that time
[Music]
i wonder at that time
that's the time slot where usually only
kiwawa is streaming
most of the time
[Music]
no no it was not japanese prime time
during my meet and greet no no
eating bugs and seeds excuse me
i was there with everyone to give
support because everyone was there even
though i was the first session ah
[Music]
sweet we compared our gifts
ah
oh so this is what i got for kiwawa oh
and this is what i got for quinoa
cute
yeah
and usually only me sometimes uh fauna
starts a little bit early right and
sometimes
sometimes the others invade my territory
but not often
it doesn't happen very often
oh you know what then that member stream
i wanted it to be a member stream where
i watched um
the
the concert
we could combine it with an unpacking of
presents
with a camera
unpacking the presents because by then
they should be here
[Music]
i could do that
i just hope there's not like anyone who
doesn't want their gift to be seen
i'll just not show it immediately
maybe if there's a name on it i can be
like are you okay if i show it
and if the person is not there then
i'll show it anyway
unless it's something if it looks you
know i won't read out the letters
but if it looks like something that
could be shown
[Music]
if it looks like something that's not
too intimate
[Music]
okay
i won't show the letters
i'm okay with mine being shown not a
hodo
i don't know which one it is though
[Music]
i would be glad to have bonkers again
it's like literally everyone in the chat
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
nothing
i'm going to read my letters in german
anyway
no all good all good
sorry for that piece of paper in my gift
i don't even know what you mean yet
why do you write proper family after the
concert but 20 seconds
don't worry about it
all right all right all right
so thank you reckless serrano for
staying so long i hope it wasn't too
exhausting and tiring if if anything we
suffered together
gemma also suffered
henma also suffered we all suffered
together
that's the spirit of kfp
strong together
[Music]
don't worry bonkers want to eat and
bonkers is so picky
a 12 hour meet and greet session next
time so we can have 10 minutes each
and
no thank you but
if if i get that idea through i'll ask
for like at least five minutes
holding channel absolutely ready
thank you for the thank you for your
massage thank you
which massage you mean the one i got
with cali that one was really nice kelly
fell asleep like constantly
it was like a really long thing
starting with like a
jacuzzi
enter jacuzzi
and then uh
and then
and then appealing
full body peeling
and then
[Music]
yeah we got rid of the peeling
then they told us that the thing that we
were supposed to use them it was like a
like a warm
uh cabin
was broken exactly in that moment
so we just took a break to drink tea
[Music]
and then we went back and then we had uh
the proper massage which was like a
aroma oil massage
but yeah kelly fell asleep during the
peeling she fell asleep during the
massage
she
actually at the end of the massage she
was like asking me
it is over weren't they like supposed to
give us a facial and i'm like
kelly we got the facial
eh
you honestly sleep through the facial
how do you not
wake up during that and then she touches
her face and she's like oh
yes i guess i did get the facial because
it was like oily
i can't fall asleep during that
no matter how
tired i am it makes me it gets me close
to falling asleep but first of all i
want to stay awake to
experience everything
consciously
and second of all
uh
i just i don't know these things like
these situations they make me
i don't know i can't i can't shut up my
brain i'm like constantly thinking about
work and all that
yeah i can't sleep
during that
[Music]
yeah she did definitely sleep
did you say anything no no
no you didn't say anything
isn't it a bit of rude no i don't think
it's rude at all what the hell what can
you do about it if you're that tired and
it's that relaxing it's more of a
compliment to the massage therapist i
would say
i would say it's a kind of a compliment
it tells them it's that
that relaxing so yo budoki mucho
yeah it's just like it must be just a
little bit awkward to like keep on
waking them up when you're like can you
turn into the side or like can you
can you get into this position
uh
[Music]
how tired kelly is oh she actually got
good sleep during the trip she told me
like i always asked her did you sleep
did you sleep well
she slept in a hotel
a nice fancy hotel
and she said she got good sleep
good amount of hours
all good
yeah yeah she slept i know incredible
and then
you know what was good
you know cali is like you know a
workaholic
[Music]
we had the perfect situation going on
with vivrena in the maldives
she had uh data
everywhere and i mean hotel wi-fi
because we were like mostly just in the
resort
so dana was a lot on her phone
but kelly
did not get data for austria
therefore since we were walking around
the city the whole day she
was pretty much never on her phone
[Music]
just sometimes like in maybe in the uber
ride or so
i would give her my data share it with
her
and then we would quickly check our
what's going on
and then turn it off again
yeah it's really good like we i feel
like
that was definitely
necessary for both of us
[Music]
and since we ran around town the whole
day and went for a museum listening to
history and all that
social media detox exactly i think that
was good for her and for me
it wasn't raining only on the phone
because you were i'm gonna be very
honest to you here reyna was on the
phone
more than i was like
i'm i'm serious okay
i know you're not gonna believe it but
during dinner for example
i would like have my phone on the side
but not look at it and i would just like
you know
look into the air but during it would be
on her phone so at some point i would be
like oh i guess i look at my phone too
yeah yeah then it was more on the phone
than i was incredible i know
reigning betrayal
i'm sorry it's the truth
hmm you had her take your pictures uh no
no no
during dinner no no no no
we only took pictures of the food
end of a gecko
[Music]
ask glenn if it's true she probably
doesn't even realize it
it's okay though because then i would
just put out my phone too and be like
all right i guess it's phone time
ah yeah
it's okay
no problemo but because i said as i said
that like we
we may have still done a lot of social
media during the vacation but still the
vacation was so overwhelmingly
overwhelming
that
it balanced out the amount of social
media
that we were doing part that we were
partaking in
[Music]
where am i
ah
giant firing coal also massage found
thank you
[Music]
it was a little bit of an expensive
massage so thank you for that
yeah yeah me and callie like callie was
like i want to do like a
long massage like a spa
thingy and i'm like i don't really know
like here in austria i feel like
the spas are not so much
spasm not so good
but then she found something nice
and we booked like a whole package
that was like four hours
four hours
but my problem was even though i slept
quite a lot before that
the facial
made my
eyes so tired that after the massage for
the coming
three four hours i was just
always like this
so tired
yeah
[Music]
i don't know made me so tired not not my
body but just my face was so tired
sleepy chill
yeah that was tough
[Music]
i couldn't i couldn't wake up my eyes
anymore
anyway thank you john firing coal
fried skull duncan black kitchen
decoration for production mysteries
danish and dominican
[Music]
so did you guys not go to the
um the japanese hotel kayoke
the nickel one
when you guys say shady i'm guessing it
was a different one
because i know the nico one has a
has a
karaoke no okay
oh well
you were there in the big group so i'm
sure that overpowered the shadiness
nico one seemed run down
oh
well turns out both are [\h__\h]
one is run down the other one is shady
oh man
[Music]
it's just that kind of karaoke
it's not really common in germany
austria
like we maybe have karaoke bars but not
the japanese kind
of karaoke
i wish we had it you know the private
rooms
high-tech karaoke
with literally every [\h__\h] song in
there
don't
um
[Music]
foreign
marrying kiwawa
huh
[Music]
i'm too small
oh my fruit hurts
i'm almost done with this
thank you
next
time
[Music]
i didn't
we still have a lot to read from other
streams but
i am catching up
but
i should probably go and leave it here
and the takamali one and the outfit one
that's okay
[Music]
i'll get there
i'll get there my throat hurts i don't
wanna risk anymore
yeah thank you guys for coming
spending some time with sick joel
[Music]
my
it was nice talking to you guys again
i hope um
we can do it again soon
supposedly tomorrow
[Music]
um
yeah
supposedly
[Music]
supposedly tomorrow
slight chance that i switch tuesday and
wednesday
or
slight chance that i get rid of the lost
egg
slight chance that i get rid of one of
the wind wakers
if i feel even worse tomorrow
or if i feel like i need more time to
practice dancing
because so far
i don't have that much down i need like
two days
roughly
for one choreo
um
currently being slowed down by being
sick
uh
[Music]
yeah i have fever night like somewhat
okayish down
[Music]
there's gonna be some body waves
i hope they look smooth
some some sexy body waves
[Music]
i didn't see diablo 4 yet
didn't see it yet
don't wait looking forward to attention
thank you
i might die on the spot
yeah i got enough sleep i slept a lot
yesterday because i was thinking
i'm sick so
let's try to get a lot of sleep in
uh but enzo still did some dancing and
stuff yeah
yeah
chihuahua grove
i hope it's gonna turn out good
and like a proper
concert like the other
whole live japan members do
i think it's gonna be noticeably
different but
we'll see
why does this girl keep on putting the
fingers up like this
step
[Music]
what is it with this girl
oh okay
it was really nice talking to you
i hope everyone's doing fine
um don't catch my illness please
disinfect your hands when you leave the
room
with alcohol
a disinfectant thingy
[Music]
and i will now stop talking
thank you
tomorrow
stanley parable
continuation because you guys enjoyed it
so much last time
surprisingly
you know stanley parable and also um
what was it before like um
portal
and also
uh
[Music]
what's the one before that super liminal
all these streams while i was doing it
i felt
[Music]
i want to sneeze
i think it's gone
i even got out my hand
i felt so um self-conscious about
um
[Music]
about like whether or not it's
entertaining
like during the stream i would be like
ah [\h__\h] i'm gonna
get some comments about how this stream
was met afterwards
and every single time
afterwards i see you guys saying it's
one of my best streams all of these kind
of like narrator type streams
[Music]
uh
yeah i'm surprised
because i i feel like my performance
wasn't that good for any of those
streams
i try though i try
but it's hard to keep it up forever
with the narrators the banter
um
it seems like you guys are enjoying it
so it must have been doing something
right
but that also put so much pressure on me
you guys were also happy with my portal
playthroughs and now the stanley wants
them like [\h__\h] uh like after 0.1 i was
like how can i
how can i possibly
do the same thing for portal 2.
i don't i don't think i can
and then it was fine but now i feel the
same way for stanley oh another stream
of stanley parable
i don't think i can satisfy the viewers
again
[Music]
oh well we'll see i try my best tomorrow
or the day after tomorrow i might
i might move it um
[Music]
everybody thank you for being here
take care of yourself don't get sick
like me
take me as an example
okay
sexual
and in german we say
[Music]
oh said
bye bye my beloved chimpkins i love you
i'll be
i'll hopefully
be back healthy and
fully energized again
soon
soon hopefully
oh [\h__\h]
wrong no
there we go
my donuts and you can keep the
bye
bye love
you bye
[Music]
do
you