questions
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this is
thank you foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
hello hello hello hello hello hello
hello
[Music]
the monkey what's the monkey doing here
go away monkey
that's not that wasn't the monkey
where's the monkey
business
monkey
oh
oh you're so long
guys I'm kind of tired man
value
to give you energy
how you guys doing
again
what then why just I mean you know I'm
always tired
doesn't mean I didn't get enough sleep
I'm just always tired so
hahaha
I'm fine
I'm great now that I'm hearing your
stream thank you yes mostly hope you got
rest after cuddle okay yeah
how's our 1.5 million subscriber
attention
[Music]
well even watch a stream of me napping
oh man
wouldn't that be nice nap time ah
remember when you were a child
and nap time was a thing that was like
reasonable
and now
now as an adult
people don't believe in naps anymore
why why why why
guys I'm in my kimono outfit today
because I thought uh I want to wear
something that I don't wear often
today
[Music]
I should actually I guess I should be
like behind behind the table wink wink
now I'm behind the table
kind of big though
kind of big
oh yeah
yeah just imagine it's uh
I mean
most foreigners
think uh everything's a Yukata anyway I
don't know the difference between a
kimono Yukata
Nicole kimonos
I wouldn't say ignorance just lack of
knowledge but I have told you guys about
that several times so by now you should
know um
yeah yeah yeah okay music
um
oh
[Music]
nice
I really like this one
it hit
that's what ignorance means no I don't
think so
ignorance is when you know something but
you're choosing to ignore it
[Music]
uh-huh
you wanna get into a
disgusting with me
[Music]
again guys why why do we always gotta
start off negatively like this with a
fight
come on make me you're gonna make me
really angry
[Music]
foreign
I hate you guys I hate you guys
[Laughter]
I hate you guys I hate you guys I hate
you
[Music]
no I hate you shut up I hate you
makes no sense
[Music]
[Laughter]
well maybe I don't hate you that much
you you
[Music]
guys
I
oh I will I will I will read super chats
today more than I did last time
hopefully and there's no deadline really
either
for today but
as you know reading super jets for
longer than especially if they're like
you know all themed after anniversary or
birthday or something they get
repetitive so after a couple hours it's
like
yeah so it won't overdo it
but getting some done would be nice
maybe if we could read the full stream
that would be nice I I should show you
guys again Ryan you want to see it right
it makes it easier to follow
[Music]
right now it's TGs right
um
[Music]
I wonder what kind of things got
announced
[Music]
are they announcing anything there at
all like anything that wasn't announced
yet
[Music]
you know the stream super chats that I'm
reading today they became my number
fifth
most super chatted stream according to
hololizer
number fifth
no wonder guys no wonder you guys are
going crazy
on my countdown to birthday was number
six apparently
sheesh
the countdown not even the birthday
stream you guys you guys went all in
there
t
thank you thank you
[Music]
what was number one number one is uh the
Kiana pretty birthday that I did with uh
like at Emma's place
[Music]
uh in last year
last year last year last year
and the second most was first year
anniversary stream
the third most was the two-year
anniversary stream the fourth most was
the 3D showcase
and the fifth most is now for the
anniversary third anniversary I mean
thought it would be birthday or 3D live
well yeah the the first one is the 3D
live I did without them
which yeah that was 3D but not cover
Studio 3D
I'm Afridi
yeah
okay
I wanna go here
and then and then and then and then do
you guys remember the number
something like 86 was it like 86 could
it be could it be
no before 86
right
[Music]
I think it it was uh
50 yeah why you guys
yeah regano was the last ride why do you
guys have different information huh
[Music]
okay yeah after I gonna yeah yeah yeah
okay
[Music]
let's bring up a window capture
this one
oh
[Music]
so it has a filter on it
no don't look at me
don't look at them
[Music]
it's not important anyway it's just
basic [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh my God I'm gonna analyze her saved
thingies
can't believe I used Gmail
[Music]
okay
we've seen it before yeah yeah but I
cleaned it up a little bit since then at
least more on the right side
um
what the [\h__\h] is that though what's my
science project what's my Google Slides
and it's probably my 3D birthday Google
Slides
[Music]
can you guys read this on the phone I
guess not I'll try to make it
bigger man
[Music]
do you want to see the colors
it's readable
[Music]
oh
yeah only a little bit of color
[Music]
hi
yeah yeah you'll figure it out guys okay
[Music]
also let me check
I'm not down to 1.49 again right right
you should be fine now I think it's
stable
almost guys it's kind of close to going
down again don't do this to me
[Music]
it's like it keeps on getting up and
down and up and down
do not do not do this to me
[Music]
don't don't don't don't don't
yeah yeah I know so it's still 1.5 but
it's very close to not being that
[Music]
um
but it's okay then it will just go up
again
[Music]
we'll just we'll need to build a safety
pillow
[Music]
tequila
I can't do tequila in an archive stream
no
[Music]
where am I
here
okay
[Music]
I watched that video again because I
think somebody sent it to me
the video of that guy in school or
whatever some school talent competition
competition in a Spider-Man costume
and he just Waits and everybody's like
losing it mm-hmm
and then he's like tequila and people
people
absolutely lose it then
laughs
[Music]
oh this is a real talent Joe like not
just the school thing
[Music]
yeah it's called Talent
what oh oh yeah oh yeah it's called are
you making a joke
or did you forget some words
what is the bird consuming
what are you eating um
cookies chocolate cookies
[Music]
but they're not at their Prime anymore
makes me think that
yesterday I watched um
the newest video from that
um that girl
the the rotten mango girl
[Music]
I think it was the newest
where she talks about a certain talent
show
being absolutely rigged
and so rigged that well
hey Aura thank you
um
[Music]
not a Korean one
The Voice
but makes me wonder if it's because the
voice is in so many countries
it makes me wonder if it's like rigged
in other countries too
I don't think that's necessary
um
necessarily like a
a given
because
I feel like that was very
um
specific to that country
[Music]
but
um
who knows
[Music]
they're ready
but
makes me wonder like how many of these
talent shows that you watch
are actually rigged and how much of it
is real hmm
makes you doubt everything
[Music]
um
now I will not name it but I'm watching
another
um
[Music]
a certain Idol Survival show right now
and
I'm so angry about
the rigging no it's not Rigby
um
[Music]
it's not it's not rigged it's just
unfair
it's just really really unfair because
they
um praise and prioritize
girls that are not so skilled over the
skilled ones
yeah they have huge bias and then they
do this thing where I'm I'm I'm like so
sure they're gaslighting the audience
they're trying to guess at the audience
but it's not working when I'm reading
through the comments nobody like buys it
but throughout the show they praise this
girl who's like really cute
she's really cute okay
and and you need like one really cute
girl I guess in the group and that's
that's okay
but you know
they try to guess like the audience into
thinking that she's also good at
everything
yeah
yeah like a dancing and singing but you
can hear even with the auto tune that
they put on there that she's not good at
singing
at all
um
and then they praise her endlessly like
oh my God your singing is so good and
all your emotion and this oh you just
have so much emotion like whenever
they're like in doubt of what to praise
her about they just praise her emotions
because no one else can show any emotion
like her
and yeah sure she's she's cute and all
that and yeah her expressions are okay
um but her dancing and there's
especially her singing Isn't So Good
and now it looks like they're kicking
out someone who was loved by all the
contestants all the viewers
who was pretty good at uh ever
everything honestly
[Music]
and they're kicking her out and like
when they perform together in this
recent episode
like you could obviously everybody could
see how well she did that girl that
they're cooking out
yeah because you could really see like
whoa
she's like even getting better and she
did a great job and then they only
criticized her the judges
and uh
they only give her credit critique and
then for the others it's like it's
really obvious who they're they're
trying to
give a good reason they want to give the
audience probably a good reason as to
why they made it into the group and why
the others didn't make it into a group
but you can't just make up this [\h__\h] ton
of critique and the [\h__\h] ton of praise
when it's very obvious to the viewers
what's going on
[Music]
yeah
I've seen in other shows they did better
at like hiding their bias
but I don't even understand like for I
understand they want to like have
certain members to fill certain roles
probably but like this girl like I think
she really should be in the group
because she is pretty she's great at
dancing she's like super positive she
has like great Vibes she's improving she
could
um
possibly
um maybe be a rapper also I don't know
um but she's she's really great like I
don't see why they need to kick her out
no shoes she's I love her she was one of
my favorites because throughout the
whole show
you could always see she was always the
most like supportive of every other
contestant like they would always cut to
her to get a reaction because she's
always like so happily like clapping and
and smiling when when she's watching the
other contestants with her thing and so
everybody loves her there was even like
votes
um like the the members would vote every
week on like who they are thankful for
who they like the most and uh from the
other contestants who helped them and
and then she was one of the top
most appreciated
from the contestants really tells you
something right
um
like I don't have a problem with this
girl getting into the final lineup at
all like she's super cute but I just
don't think it's fair to praise her for
things she didn't do that everybody can
see
and then critique the other one who did
obviously better than her
I don't know man
it's made me really really upset this
one then he was Angels right my my
producer
um
Trio
they watch these kind of shows too
so I went to them and I I I've several
times by now and got really angry and
they agree with me and we talk about it
yeah
thank God thank God they get it
um
[Music]
their taste the line so well they really
do but hey did I tell you guys
what do you think of kg uh she's a great
singer but she's really bad at dancing
and
and then like in that Idol in that group
that Performance Group yuria I'm talking
like specifically to you now
in that group right they only praised
the 2ks right
and they criticized the other two who
were
really good I don't get it but it makes
me think like ah the other K that they
critiqued they were against free case
[Music]
um the other kid that they critique
they're obviously kicking out too
[Music]
and that one I kind of understand
because she's just too young
for for to to be in a group like that in
my opinion she looks too young like the
others are this g girl right Julia
the g girl who's the same age but she
looks way more mature so you know but
this K girl she's so young and she has
like this baby face
she has this absolute baby baby baby
baby face makes me feel
weird you know
yeah yeah what was I saying no
um yeah so it's very obvious in that
group depending on like if you look at
who they criticize and who they praised
to see who they're kicking out
and for the the K girl I get it but I
don't get it for the
um
the sea girl
yeah anyway anyway
uh yeah did I tell you so did my my
Chihuahuas angels
might produce a group day
like everything that I like right they
love charm for example so I thought they
must have seen uh Gilmore Girls and must
have liked Gilmore Girls
so a while ago
I I like tried to talk to them about
Gilmore Girls
and now the single one of them watched
it or even really knew what I was
talking about
and one of them I think it was Moni she
thought I was talking about
Trump bro Golden Girls
oh
what the [\h__\h] I'm like
yo you would totally love it like why is
why have you guys not tried watching
Gilmore Girls before this would
I think you would love it this would be
so your thing why what what's going on
with that eh you missed out
yeah I can't it gave me flashbacks
because Cali made the same mistake but
Cali not watching Gilmore Girls makes
sense to me
um Chihuahua's Angels not watching
Gilmore Girls makes no sense to me
[Music]
so I recommended it to them
um
and I hope they will eventually watch it
uh morning actually I gave her so many
show recommendations because she wanted
them
but those are more like um like about
fantasy shows
um
she's receptive to my recommendations
at least someone is
[Music]
yeah so okay okay
that's enough beginning
uh tangents
[Music]
um
enough for now
using a king cover to getting your I saw
yeah
what fantasy shows do you recommend well
I won't tell you
I'm gonna tell you well I just told her
about you know
I won't tell you
[Music]
judge me
because I gave I gave a very honest
recommendation I said you know other
people might not like it but if you
didn't read the books
[Music]
I said it like from a very objective
point of view okay
I just said this exists and you might
like it if you're not too critical oh
no not I mentioned rings of palette but
it was more about little real time
because I think Wheel of Time is
genuinely
pretty good if if yeah
if you didn't read the books I guess
um
my mom ended up watching one episode
with me
kind of
and then at the end like she had like a
really like critical face facial
expression that was like
don't ruin this for me mom
and I asked
was there anything like you look so
critical but was there anything that you
could tell was like absolutely wrong
compared to the books and she said no
but
I think she
I think she her biggest problem is like
the maybe the personalities or something
but hey at least in that episode The
like plot itself
wasn't like
off
so
it can't be that bad
and really I thought
I think the second season so far is
going better than the first season
um
[Music]
I'll add it to my list really I don't
know how many episodes it has but it's
currently in its second season
I remember you not loving season one see
I don't remember that really but I I I
think I wasn't as impressed as I am now
with the second season
so I think surprisingly it's actually
getting better
I will hold my tongue uh what's your
problem
I think it's like pretty uh riveting at
the moment
yeah I was all right but like you know
some parts are maybe kind of mad cheesy
or Tech tacky
but the second season I don't you tell
me that you still don't like it please
because I think it's pretty good pretty
good pretty good
[Music]
um
second book is seen as one of the best
so the season based on it should be
better
oh
oh so you think it's actually like cut
like the first season was really one
book and the second season is really one
you got a book
is it cuts so cleanly like that
[Music]
it does seem like it cut off at like a
good point
[Music]
um I think a unique taste is cute unique
and unique
you can say my taste is
generic
because it might be I wouldn't say
unique I'm sure many people watch the
same shows I do otherwise they wouldn't
have gotten the second season
we're fine
no oh
I'm not taking offense to it I just
don't think it's that unique it's I
think plenty of people will watch it
they may be basic [\h__\h] like me but
you know you watch Umbrella Academy
you're based in my book
but Umbrella Academy
I enjoyed it was high quality but there
were also
especially how many seasons were there I
just remember not liking it as much as
the first season anymore and yeah
it was a bit too much
yes free Seasons yeah okay and
especially the last season I think was
um
mm-hmm
season one was the best yeah
oh yeah so we agree on that
[Music]
um
so many things were just like what the
[\h__\h]
what what
the comics are better oh right there
that's also based on a comic then was it
um accurate to its original
thing that's what I wonder
now
Life's too short to complain about other
people's things
lives to show do not just watch every
[\h__\h] Series in existence yeah
and now it's showing my watches let's go
tattoo yeah to its source material
that's what I mean yeah
[Music]
it's better than the comics
you think so
[Music]
Girard
aha
helped with the show
I'm gonna watch my Phoenix girl and said
ah good choice good choice
very good choice
[Music]
once I finish the one piece anime in
five years
you're watching the one piece anime now
good luck
all right guys
here we go let's read some super chats
Uka
foreign
thank you for two pinkies
three years huh you know it's kind of
crazy to think that you've been a part
of my life for part of my life for a
seventh of my life
well now I need to know how old you are
so I can know how much time that well
well it might it might have been three
years right three years
seven
seven times
so young
[Music]
uh I would never want to forget oh
every moment spent with you on campaign
I wouldn't trade it for anything else
even at our lowest moments we're there
for each other a bond to never be broken
from now and forever I'll cherish it all
I hope you will too happy anniversary
Kiara much love to you too thank you see
you're talking about our lowest moments
I've been to yesterday was one of my
lowest moments in terms of sanity
for you guys too
but we had a mission
and we went through with it
if there was no going back at that point
when we were so close
yeah
tequila
no thoughts only tequila
I felt yeah
[Music]
I was praying for it to end
because you know I could have done a
non-cola
marathon that then it wouldn't have been
so exhausting but then I don't think it
would have
um gotten so many people
I don't know if it was just a normal
gaming stream I don't think it would
have been that special to like get
people to
you know I think somehow karaoke is good
for a special uh yeah special moments
and
I I could have probably also done
something like um ring fit Marathon but
that also that I I don't think I could
have done that for six uh hours
but that might have also been fitting
for a marathon if it was shorter
but yeah I was really happy that you
guys uh stayed with me through the end
even if that meant losing your sanity
thank you guys and thank you rad for now
always being there
spending a good chunk of your life with
me
[Music]
thank you so much rad
my My Fire Emblem consultant have
consultant for
everything
except for for tails off I don't need a
consultant but I had a hoodle consultant
[Music]
should be in his name yeah if you want
to have a title rad
you can name it Fe consultant
soda and shambles he tried but I'm an
independent girl when it comes to tales
off games
[Music]
yeah I'm My Own consultant
I really want to pick up another tails
off game to stream even if it's not so
good as a streaming game but we're
getting the DLC now anyway so let's wait
for the DLC yeah it's gonna like
you know be there really soon anyway did
you see big hoodle no what the [\h__\h]
shouldn't be big
[Music]
Symphonia Symphonia too someday yeah
symphonium
would be nice to like read
uh live it
I guess generally I don't like her
playing games
but Symphonia is very very special to me
so it could be it could happen
cool for smash
[Music]
yeah or take the chance and play
something I didn't play before
I always wanted to play like Fantasia
and uh uh what was that one re
[Music]
EF
but fantasium
I don't know how to play it yeah
hopefully a Reverb yeah hopefully they
bring out a remaster of Fantasia
[Music]
but tails off doesn't do many
remasters and stuff and remakes
I wish I did some more like especially
now so much time has passed they should
totally remake their old games
yeah Fantasia is 2D
they were talking about making New Ports
really I hope so I really hope so
[Music]
like Fantasia is one of their Classics
they have to make it more accessible
hmm now it's more popular maybe we'll
get those remakes I hope so
I hope they focus a little bit on that
like especially now that there's like
time they they just released the big one
right so they have time anyway to work
on something else
I don't know how long it takes to do a
remaster
doing a remaster can't take that long
right please give me a remaster yeah
just fill the Gap until the next release
with that that would be great thank you
a full-on remake for Symphonia would be
insane
ah Symphony I would prefer to remake
older ones because there's so much
potential there
like I'm I'm very biased towards him
towards Symphonia but I don't think it
needs a remake yet
they gotta give others remix first yeah
the older ones
[Music]
and yeah especially the ones that the
West didn't get mm-hmm
or they're really really really old
platform ones yeah
[Music]
oh
Tales of Tempest
sheesh yeah I like the main girl she's
cute
um
I like her
she I never played that one before
either it was on Nintendo DS
[Music]
oh
damn
hey wasn't that actually isn't that
Freddy
and that's Freddy actually wow
cute ps3d
[Music]
um
cute wait Tempest there's no is there
English Tempest
[Music]
was there ever an English Tempest
release let me check
no right uh
oh man that's that's what I need
[Music]
um
yeah but I don't see that happening
I don't think Tempest was as popular as
other
uh releases
I don't think they would choose that one
first
no oh well
Tempest
leverage your Ambassador Powers I don't
think they go that far unfortunately
but
but they've been really nice to me you
know
they've been really really nice
also I was like panicking when my
internet went down
um because it never [\h__\h] happens
right
and uh it happened with us with a
sponsorship that I really really like
appreciate a lot and I didn't want
anything to go wrong
and yeah I was like first I was waiting
a bit for it to come back naturally
because I didn't realize it was like a
longer one so I was just waiting for a
minute or two
um and then
I saw that um like jenma and the The
Producers Etc they were like in voice
chat mutants just you know like I guess
monitoring what was going on
uh and then when the internet went down
they were like talking to each other so
I went into voice with it I was like I'm
so sorry
what's going on
and I was restarting the router and I
was doing this and that it wasn't coming
back and I was like what the [\h__\h]
yeah so then I called
my provider and
those
suckers
we're doing a maintenance and I'm like
huh
is this like a regular thing because I
never had this before
and and it's It Feels So Random
Feels So Random and yeah lady didn't
have a good answer for me really but
yeah it was in the night time like but I
would have liked the warning like don't
they think like maybe some people need
the internet in the night as well like
couldn't you have
don't you give out warnings like that
it was uh like a planned maintenance but
I had no idea what's happening
yeah throughout the night like they said
like until 4 00 am
um but like you know
throughout Austria I guess and like like
if you're if yours started in your area
or so then it takes like so and so long
but generally it's until 4am
yeah they don't send warnings no no I'm
not saying they should send a warning at
12 at night they should send the money
like ahead of time a week ahead or so
and tell you hey we're doing uh
yeah but they don't do that like why
like people rely on it for work
make me so angry
I rely on it for work
[Music]
could have also happened for example for
for the Pokemon sponsorship
Pokemon Unite
that would have been [\h__\h] too but at
least for days off they were really like
nice and kind about it they were like oh
don't worry about it you can reschedule
like anytime from now on whenever you
want ideally in a prime time but
whatever you want it's okay I'm like
thankfully it came back
at the reasonable time and we could just
do it the moment it came back I was like
oh it's back
and I immediately left the conversation
because I just wanted to get right back
into it
[Music]
while we were still talking about
rescheduling yeah
but they're so nice
they're so nice and before the stream
when I had questions the producer the
producer
quickly replied to me about everything
even though it was like I think it was
like night time for him
[Music]
um
yeah but then they're like they also
prepared oh this is also a reason why I
like the sponsorship so much
um last year too they always prepare so
many things for me like
um documents and and script stuff like I
don't have to do much like some
sponsorships they're like pretty loose
and others are
pretty like strict
and and this one's not strict but like
they give me a lot of stuff to work with
um
[Music]
while still giving me Freedom you know
yeah
so
y'all and did you see swap
the artist for my newest outfit was
really happy to see me in action uh
promoting Tales of our eyes again
with my outfit from him
foreign
yeah
that was that was really nice awesome
I wonder if um the producers from Tales
of arise noticed what I did there
if they realized that I just got myself
an outfit to match roof tails off and
and and any RPGs really but I got the
artist that was involved in tails off
[Music]
I wonder tell them maybe I will next
time we get into a conversation
this is your Colony Sonic pretty much
but I did it
like out of my own
you know
they didn't ask for it I just I just
made it happen
[Music]
they know now since you mentioned it on
stream but I don't think I said it in
Japanese but they may have picked up on
it though
I wouldn't mind because like that shows
them even more how much I love
tails off
um yeah yeah so I really love that
sponsorship and I I I'm I'm just so
shocked that it was able to continue
because I honestly I thought well they
don't bring out so many new things all
the time so until the next sponsorship
from them it would take ages and then
they hit you with the unexpected DLC
oh
shocking
um
oh my God
[Music]
because
congratulations thank you
so okay we're gonna need more water
[Music]
you can't imagine them
download the content
foreign
[Music]
mainstream I'm so proud I'm so happy
they're going places I'm I'm glad they
just need to you know continue the way
they're doing things I think they're
doing really great
um they have great potential I was
always thinking like why is the tails
off not as popular as Final Fantasy like
man it's not fair
[Music]
he
yeah I'm getting uh number one RPG was
also great
Pride I was I was so proud
[Music]
yeah I mean I generally understand yeah
because like visually it's probably more
appealing to
the West
um
but in the end people who play Final
Fantasy are in the end there are people
who are very receptive of anime stuff
anyway
I ain't
in the end I think it's pretty much the
same audience but
so
I get it but at the same time I don't
[Music]
know well
it is what it is yeah
defined gaming Generations yeah yeah
yeah sure
[Music]
that's all seems more starring character
Focus to me yeah I don't know about that
I'm sure FF has a lot of story too
[Music]
yeah
oh wow
now I was saying I think both people who
play FF are receptive to anime not
everybody but I would say most
[Music]
anime Graphics or so
I only found out about tail series after
this area but you liked it right so
hmm
ah we're getting too deep into tangents
man stop stop stop stop stop stop
that good thanks for the pinky it's
saving for your anniversary merch
release ah so here's happy anniversary
one second we have thank you thank you I
hope this time the merchandise uh like
shipping Etc is not such a big issue
um from what I haven't really seen any
complaints I think so it's looking good
I think
but yeah I understand if you have to
like if you want to focus your money on
that that's totally fine thank you again
thank you Doug Hood
hmm
more reasonable good good good good
[Music]
shipping to EU is Hefty
bundling seems to still be preferred if
you can yeah yeah if you can bundle it
guys then do that
um
larger orders are pretty chunky but I
think even though four Waters it would
be expensive
yeah if anybody like you know is in
doubt maybe try pencil and see if it
helps you
[Music]
I have to pay for Judas and Tacos yeah I
saw some people get like extra charges
for taxes so that's weird but no
it is what it is
[Music]
jingle thanks for the pinky for two
pinkies
a lot of things can change in three
years but you know that what didn't
change in three years your tenacity to
try new things never running away from
challenges and always looking to
communicate
these factors always impress me and I'm
proud to have you as my Aussie probably
I won't be able to see all of third
anniversary stream today due to Korea
trip but happy fruit anniversary and
looking forward to what you have
prepared there is one last thing that I
have that hasn't changed since debut
it's my support for you thank you thank
you you're the best thank you that is
true that is very true
thank you I hope you enjoyed Korea
and
yeah thank you for the sweet words to
sweet message I'm glad you're always
around it's like I can always count on
you to be there especially for like
events
um even if it's like far away thank you
so much love for all the dedication
and all the love that you give to me and
kfp yeah
you guys
[Music]
are the best Korea Korea I want to go to
Korea again too but man I can't do too
many trips one after another now it's
Japan trip and then later another Japan
trip I don't think I'm gonna go on
yeah I don't think I'm gonna go anywhere
uh in between
I do still want to plan like that like
Maldives trip
I want to go to the Maldives again but
this time in the correct season
[Music]
um but we're still like figuring out
who we actually bring along if it should
just be uh like two people or maybe a
bit more this time
um
no no no
Wayne at this time
no no no no no it's not gonna be like
verbs
I'm I'm thinking you know I want to go
with someone who I haven't been to a
vacation before
to bond with others you know
I mean maybe maybe
it's going some with someone to another
vacation it's fine maybe I will
but I wanna I wanna
I wanna mix it up
maybe four people group we kind of like
are thinking about it yeah yeah maybe
[Music]
would be up
I don't know
[Music]
guys I have if I if I go to all these
places I won't be streaming anymore
[Music]
Wayne is uh Wayne is coming to see me
that is fixed
and because she is coming to see me
anyway
it's also a reason why I don't think we
need to go on another trip
[Music]
she's coming to see me in winter time
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
so
we can do off collab too probably
[Music]
I'm going to be a tour guide probably
yeah will you take her skiing no thank
you I don't want to get hurt again
skiing makes me so anxious but yeah I
think
um
[Music]
just gonna show her Christmas markets if
they're open at the time I don't know
they might not be I think it might be
after
um
we'll see we'll see
oh but I know what we can do ice skating
we have some really pretty ice skating
rings
[Music]
okay
has she ever seen snow
oh I mean she was even surprised by
seeing Stars
[Music]
but wait snow I want to say no but who
knows she travels a lot so maybe she did
I'm not sure
paragliding we could do better gliding
yeah
[Music]
mmm
that's actually like a good idea from
now on for like if someone comes to
visit and I want to show them
a nice scenery
[Music]
I think you can do it in the winter too
right
I'm pretty sure
and James Jackson thank you for the
pinky wow they're sure a lot of pinkies
and pre-chat thank you for being my oshu
you're saying that one also sending one
hmm what are you trying to do
what you trying to do 24 Karat magic in
the air
yeah I was told though by the
paragliding lady that uh the time when I
went paragliding is generally the best
time of the year
because of the Winds and all that
um
so I
coincidentally chose the perfect time
for it
hmm
kitchen Hollow members to fly in Austria
via paragraph
oh yeah if I do it again I can make
another video out of it oh
content anyway thank you James thanks
for watching me for choosing me
that is the best choice you could make
in life
with two Reds of attacks to our dearest
Chihuahua how time flies it's the third
year anniversary already as a camping
employee I thank you for delivering all
these great contents and songs even
brain what I mean convert me to love
pineapple on top I even speak such
affection during my sleep what
this feeling of Rush is real oh wait
wait wait
um this love is true retrospectively the
Sparks was already within my heart while
I wandered in the wild
and now I get this now I understand
uh I wanted in the wild alone my last
word is to all the Italian Nikki how you
like them pineapples anyway I gotta go I
need to get my holotalk cup back from my
girlfriend
what is she doing with it hopefully
treating it well
be careful with it Mrs girlfriend
there's this really difficult soup get a
new one
if something happens to it mm-hmm
that was like a word salad yeah yeah
[Music]
right that's what I told her good it
should be your cup only to use because
then it's only your
how to say
um
[Music]
what's the word
um
help English help
[Music]
no
something responsibility thank you
I think my mind responsibility yeah that
is only your responsibility if she
breaks it she's gonna like feel really
guilty
so she better not use it
anyway thank you donkey tongue for the
support and for the big red super chats
and for staying with me for such a long
time and also really appreciating my
album apparently
and yeah forgiving pineapple a chance so
many haters they just they hate on
pineapple and pizza and they don't even
give it a chance
and that's just not fair
[Music]
yeah while I'm brain tired in general
after breaking the cup she's gonna
listen to retrospective and be like
and regret everything
[Music]
I tried it and it was disaster Maybe
nah maybe maybe you didn't get a good
one
try it again until you like it
thank you
I'm perfect
time moved so quickly has already been
three years this year in particular has
been knots between the album and 3D
appearance thank you to you and kfb for
the wonderful times wouldn't trade my
time here for anything in the world
here's to another year thank you I'm
very happy to hear that
thank you so much it's been exciting um
throughout
the whole year so far
I wonder was it the same amount of
excitement last year
because it feels like a lot this year
but it probably was every year like this
it's just like always on the grind
last year was much combat are you sure
last year I went to America
wow that whole Arc damn
[Music]
sheesh
that was quite an intense time man
special
very special I hope we can do something
like that again where we're just
together for a good amount of time at
least a week yeah
I hope so
[Music]
you see it's been really back to back
action yeah and I don't know I think as
a viewer it's less definitely less
intense
than for the person who's experiencing
it me
um but yeah
it's it should be a good thing when
times are exciting that should be a good
thing so
gotta enjoy it while it's going on
[Music]
well I think now now
no for a while
you know we just reached 1.5 million we
had anniversary we had birthday what
else can possibly happen now I don't
think
I don't think
anything's gonna
yeah happen until like Christmas time
anything like big huge you know
[Music]
just normal
every day
stuff mostly
um member anniversary wow that one will
just be that's not that big I'm thinking
of bigger things like anniversary
and stuff Halloween I'm not doing
anything special for Halloween
[Music]
except maybe
um
well nothing huge like
don't you get it don't you get it
the way this summer was packed with huge
events and huge milestones and all that
it's not gonna be like that for a while
I'm pretty sure
[Music]
Fatal Frame we can make that happen yes
hmm
[Music]
glad you guys are happy anyway thank you
awesome
thank you so much I hope you'll continue
being part of kfb
C hours
[Music]
thank you
sneaky B2 B 50 thank you for the pinky
from Norway
happy third anniversary thank you thank
you so much thank you that's a cute
profile picture a cat with a sweater and
some cute cats gotta stay warm in Norway
I guess
thank you thank you thank you thank you
hope you're doing well thank you for the
support are you here to here too
hey no way
no way
I need to visit Norway
I want to do I want to do a Europe trip
next year how about that two to three
days in each City doesn't necessarily
have to be every city in Europe but I
want to go like to the north
to the West
to the South
hmm
[Music]
my city
wait what's your city again you gotta
help me
[Music]
go to Spain with Nina
honestly all of that that's really just
on the members who keep on talking about
I wanna go overseas but that then they
don't come
that's not on me
[Music]
nobody ever comes to Denver Denver
have you talked to another recently no
sadly no you know there's always times
where
you know certain people talk of certain
people more than and more than other
times and
you know Downs down time
you know I haven't haven't really done
anything with Nana team
[Music]
for a while
um
she might be getting serious about it
when did she ask about that
[Music]
most of them are a bit scared of
traveling alone to a foreign country she
'll I got her back
I'm right there Europe is small I can be
anywhere within maximum four hours
scared away man I did not
[Music]
that was banter
looking really hard at Germany and
Austria
any suggestions well Austria and I think
Vienna specifically
continuously gets like ranked number one
or really high
for being a good city to live in
especially for students
[Music]
so go for Austria
not Germany
[Music]
Germany
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes
happy third anniversary it's a long
journey but I don't feel that long
because you always bring fun streams and
great contents to US release
especially your songs which helped me a
lot from bad days thank you for making
every day wonderful thank you
for being such a bright and positive
energy in kfp helping with projects you
know I see you I see you thank you so
much
for everything for the support I
I'm very grateful
[Music]
you're so cute yeah thank you
I'll continue trying to give you guys
good content so I hope you can continue
watching it too
um
and not get sick of me hopefully
type and thank you very much it's hard
to believe how much you've done in three
years and all the joy you've brought
into so many lives you've proven that
you can change lives just by making
people smile thank you for three years
for more of more smiles and I can count
it's really the luckiest chicken thank
you typhoon oh I'm so happy that I can
bring happiness to you
and on on the on on on the topic of type
and
I'm getting a great shoots position
wrong let's go
my financial advisor and I had a meeting
today about
um
insurances
yeah
yeah he's making me get some really
basic ones
um
that one I just mentioned is like the
the the the the one for like if you need
a lawyer for something
um
why is it so long it's not that long
[Music]
um
no no life insurance [\h__\h] that
yeah uh that and the like the like a
home insurance thingy for like when
something breaks or when somebody breaks
in
uh stuff like that and then I think
[Music]
um
if I have a big accident
and you know
I think those free
[Music]
no I don't have any insurance besides
health insurance before
I never needed it and honestly in the
future as well I don't really think I
really need it except the the the the
the the lawyer one I think that could be
useful
um
but the other is I mean sure it makes
sense but did I ever need it until now
not really
not really but you know it's not that
expensive so it's like in total for free
insurances
I'm paying like 60 bucks per month so
I'm like okay whatever
[Music]
um
yeah yeah yeah like if something's on
fire you know how often I start a
kitchen fire I guess
no
it never went that bad
[Music]
did you buy buy extension no I didn't
okay I have everything under control
okay
[Music]
the other day I cooked so much oil
to make my schnitzel but everything went
okay
[Music]
yeah and blow it out again with my
insane lungs
ah nothing's ever been damaged except my
mental health because I was very very
paranoid
about fires
[Music]
of course every apartment needs a fire
alarm it's like a law so of course I
have one
[Music]
um but yeah so just so you know like I'm
I'm prepping myself up are you proud of
me Typhon I can so I can get like legal
advice every time and I can
um you know if something happens I can
sue people for free let's go
yeah so don't mess with me
don't mess with me I'll sue you I'll sue
your ass
serious
[Music]
yay free suits suits
I don't wear a suit foreign
[Music]
I'm surprised so many people threatened
with lawsuits when it's so expensive I
guess do all these people have that
insurance as well I wonder
what does it even called in English
I guess I'll Google
in English
legal protection insurance
[Music]
um
can still get a lawsuit and you'll get a
lawsuit and you're gonna do
which people in America was super
anything
yeah I don't even know how you can have
so much patience for that kind of [\h__\h]
like I don't want to bother with that
[\h__\h] generally
too much time and [\h__\h]
we basically Sue each other as a form of
greeting
uh they'll make money they make all the
money so they encourage it yeah of
course they do
foreign
[Music]
bother with it much once day once you
hand it over but
um
[Music]
yeah maybe it'll be my new hobby suing
people
[Music]
I'll sue DHL
[Laughter]
that's a big first opponent though man I
should start smaller Maybe
yeah let's go
[Music]
six shut up
they're Reds and so on they take time
okay
you type in mwah kiss for you you got
your Facebook happy fourth anniversary
I'm a quiet new kfb
or even then I recognize your name very
well but a lot happened after I joined I
feel you're really hard working and
always
all out there trying new things like
with POV oh for me it's more like but I
guess this was before the stream started
but for me that that applies very much
to my Vlogs yeah I admire you a lot
thank you for making every day much more
fun thank you I do try to within my like
limits and skills try new things like
you know one one can think of stuff like
the the snack boxes for example and all
my hand cam streams
um
yeah because I I I'm not like as like
technically skilled uh with things as
like Ahmed for example so there's things
that I want to try but I don't really
know how I would how I would go about it
but I try my best to do things
um you know within my limits of course I
canceled it I haven't received one in
ages
um
I would like to do it again but yeah
maybe I'll do it again it wasn't that
bad
yeah I I don't know
maybe next year I don't know
[Music]
foreign
but I already also I feel like I covered
a lot of countries already and
getting countries that I haven't covered
already when it's like a thing that they
decide and
they're like
sometimes they even with in one year
they're like doing Japan twice for
example
hmm
that's
unfortunate for me because like I'm
trying to get something new every month
um
the Guatemala one that ended up being a
Mexico one mm-hmm
that's that's where I started doubting
if I should really have the subscription
anyway thank you you Connie I'm so happy
you became part of KFC
you know we need some newcomers
to grow so I'm glad you have made your
way here
[Music]
maybe ask people for Taiwan well but
she's like not in Thailand right so I
don't know if she would have access
to
yeah
such snackles
[Music]
oh but her mom does oh
who I am hmm
whole her family could send it to me oh
I feel like if I make a request like
that her family is gonna go overboard
and send me a snack box as if they were
sending it to biboo and gonna send like
this huge
box with a million things inside
treating me as a daughter of Their Own
[Music]
but yeah they could send me one and I
could send people offer and one if she
wants hmm
in theory I like the idea
[Music]
before in Brazil
foreign
[Music]
like it comes from Chile
yeah I generally getting a snack box
from someone who put it together
personally for me is obviously the best
the most ideal thing
but yeah we don't we we have of course
we're scattered all over the place but
we don't have so many unique countries
like Austria
um
[Music]
have I had an Indonesian snack talks
before yeah I mean like for a stream
[Music]
oh no did I do Indonesia
I tried some snacks yeah but
it wasn't really a snack Box review
right
[Music]
yeah
I should still do that
[Music]
hmm
well I feel like the Indonesian members
already gave me like a bunch of snacks
so I'll see them again if I request a
snack box they'll probably send me some
of them the same ones again because they
seem to be popular choices oh
oh we're back oh we were gone for how
long
[Music]
huh
hi
um
[Music]
for eight seconds
oh my God
how dare they deprive you of me for
eight seconds
that's like
between life or death
I missed you too
[Music]
I'll sue that them
let's go
Um Papa thanks for the rainbow it
becomes a rainbow three years I'm glad I
can always be here also made some new
friends from camping oh happy
anniversary and thank you lava love you
and love POV album so much my head is
going to grow up pineapples let's go
pineapples thank you
you're so sweet sweet thank you so much
I love the pineapples all over
we need more pineapples at kfp K of
pineapple
yeah and I'm really happy to hear that
you know you're so sweet Papa so one
could only like you
can't imagine disliking you
you're the best thank you for the
beautiful rainbow and I hope you can
continue enjoying your time here
with me and all the other Jim Kings
[Music]
thank you for the recipe chat wow I
can't believe it's already been three
years happy anniversary
yeah three years man
it's crazy it feels like a big
accomplishment and I do
feel like
it's been less time than three years but
wow there it is the big free I feel like
you're free Heroes it's such a
important number two like two years and
four years man but free free such a
magical number right so
it was an important one
[Music]
now five will be special again but
honestly every year is special because
like every year you know we should
celebrate it it's just the number three
it's just extra special
[Music]
yeah I wonder how many of you guys will
still be there for the next one and the
next next one
I hope to see all of you there and even
give me a promise guys can you promise
me something even if you take some time
away from kfb because maybe you lost
interest
are you busy with other things
and then promise me that
for my anniversary you'll stop by again
and who knows maybe you you want to stay
for a while but
promise me to you know say hi and check
out what I'm up to how much I've grown
you know
you owe me that
[Music]
for for you know we've been here so long
why why what we have we have a special
bond okay
um
that you can promise nice
you promise thank you thank you thank
you
good very good
and same thing for birthday honestly
stop by at the big events at least that
would make me very happy if you couldn't
at least say hi at the big events and
who knows maybe that will make you feel
like you want to stay
for a while longer again
promise but I'm not going anywhere
that's fine too
that's okay Wayne promise yeah
thank you guys thank you you yeah you're
not really allowed to leave but it's not
like I can really like stop you
sadly
don't think I can get rid of you now
[Music]
uh
just like I'm like some freaking
uh what's it called
Kusa in your garden
[Music]
but you love me right
no the bad grass not the good grass the
bad bad grass evil grass
thank you Dr Diablo
the moment you hear you're a real kfb
member don't worry
oh yeah wait thank you I forgot the word
[Music]
I'm just a straight cat that moved in I
love Stray Cats I want stray cats to
move in
all thanks for the membership welcome
I am the Casper in your lives
you're not trying to Blind me with
poison right don't
please please
[Music]
this movie was a bit annoying day last
night like I gave her like dinner and I
gave her midnight mid-sleep breakfast
and then normally that was okay always
but now she wanted the second breakfast
once I actually got up
I was like okay well whatever
I just need you to shut up so I'll give
you something
yeah
now I wouldn't say she reverted just yet
this was just this night we'll see how
it goes tonight
she's like sometimes she's better
sometimes she's worse oh man
oh memo
[Music]
yeah still better than this will be at a
worst oh yeah oh yeah
[Music]
and I just gave up like
I just well when she starts meowing at
me I just pet her for a little while and
then she just doesn't stop so then I
just get up but I don't I don't like
close the door anymore because it makes
me feel so bad
[Music]
I couldn't
yeah we'll figure it out
you know at least now I get a little
break from her
I don't want to get a break from her but
her waking me up all the time I just
want a full night's sleep without having
to get up to give someone food I'm
thinking of moving the the food bowls to
next to my bed
to not have to move so much because like
the footballs are pretty far far away
from where I sleep
I'm honestly thinking to that'll make it
worse I think so
but I don't want to move so much it's
like waking me up you know the more I
move the more it wakes me up
[Music]
um
it's pretty stinky no not that bad
[Music]
she'll have more reason to come to you
you think so
yeah smoothie is in control but we've
crew we've like kind of we have a
routine now
we pretty much have a routine
now
um
[Music]
yeah
it's okay the electronic food dispenser
I tried it but I noticed that she lives
and she has more left over and I had a
feeling that the food starts to stink so
it's not well preserved I guess in there
um even though it kind of claimed that
it would be fine for wet food
seems like it wasn't as suitable for wet
food after all
and yeah
it's not that hot in my apartment though
it's I don't know
it's not that bad
but yeah she you know she left over way
more food than no and sometimes she
wouldn't touch it at all not even a bite
so I gave up on that but it might I
might still use it in the future maybe
when I'm like gone for
one night and I don't want to organize
any anyone to take care of the cats
maybe I'll use it again then
[Music]
but still then I wonder is it gonna be
preserved well
I I wonder if I can because it's like a
round shaped flat one
if if I put like it turns you know it
turns to the open slot
and I wonder if I put like a like a
cooling pad cooling thingy on top of the
feeder
if it's if the coolness can go through
the material and cool the food a little
bit
I wonder if that works
[Music]
it's just directly on top of the machine
maybe a little bit
[Music]
oh wow whatever I don't I don't know
might have been a a
um and fail calf uh
it's English for field code
is there a word for that
being cough
Miss purchase really
doesn't sound so smooth in English
[Music]
yeah for dry food I mean it's totally
fine but for dry food I don't even need
it because I just put like I just filled
a bowl completely
I don't really think I need an automatic
dispenser for dry food
[Music]
I feel it like
once every
day or sometimes even only every 1.5
days I feel the bowl and everybody's
happy
[Music]
yeah the German word is better somehow
anyway anyway I'm time to think
I read this one right so thank you Timmy
thank you
what's up
check right you're also from Europe nice
noise
GT
[Music]
D thank you for the red superchato yes
there I thought so yeah yeah
[Music]
happy third anniversary I've been an
eventful year for us and I'm honored to
witness that you what you have achieved
this year continue being true to
yourself you're making me laugh for
nearly a minute polka collab Club made
me follow you but you're genuineness
caring hard and passion are what made me
stay I'm proud of you my coming
thank you so much I didn't know I don't
think I knew that that's what made you
follow me
did you tell me before because I don't
think I remember that maybe I Hold On
[Music]
yeah it was
it was this
but I don't think I knew
I think I knew
nice you mentioned it and forgot I'm
sorry yeah but I like hearing your
guys's origin stories
was a good moment though good moments
with the poor girl collab yeah
yeah
I saw a clip recently of like recently
like two days ago or so of her talking
with flamoko
um polka is so sweet and genuine too
like she got two I think she got really
really really happy
um by being loved by some cool eyes
specifically it just feels special you
know when someone
chooses you specifically
it's it's just like it
wow
that's how I feel with never say you
know and polka really deserves it too
such love
and then coming from the dogs out of all
people wow I'm happy for her that was
really sweet she's she's so sweet oh
I hope that they will get to
you know do lots of things in the future
together Tete
titty
[Music]
the speech on the icebridge was what
made you my ocean ah that one you mean
the one that was kind of controversial
and made people hate on me a lot
actually
that one
thank you
[Music]
yeah I think it was uh controversial
yeah yeah the one million
see like yeah
I feel like it's uh difficult as a
streamer like me to say your feelings
because if it's negative feelings people
will often be like
um
picking it apart and yeah
[Music]
yeah
so
that was one of those moments
and I mean can't really help it to have
some brain worms in this industry you
know
so
I don't know I think it's a normal thing
and I'm sure that many many many many
other members
uh experience the same exact feelings
that I experienced
um I'm just the one of the few people
who don't hold back in expressing it
most of the time because I I just I
don't know
I just I just want to share my feelings
I want to have you guys know what what
kind of
you know mindset I have and you know why
I do the things that I do why I feel the
way that I feel stuff like that
um
I really don't get what the problem was
um yeah I mean
many people were upset about it you know
[Music]
so I'm glad that not everybody took it
like that
thank you thank you and GD thank you so
much
so much forever I feel like I can always
rely on YouTube thank you I'm I feel so
bad because you you're like one of those
people who have to always
sacrifice
their time because of the time zone
but I can feel
even more like determination and
loyalty
and love from you for doing that no
I wish we didn't have time zones man
[Music]
I really wish I could cater to everybody
in every time zone
[Music]
like you're constantly
Night Owl constantly
like turning your whole day and night
around for me
I don't know how you do it
I don't know why I do it
I just watch you in Hollow and then and
watch you and Holo anymore
[Music]
I don't know how you do it
this is normal time for me
you're being six hours ahead honestly
works better for me yeah yeah I think
for n a it's like still like more
manageable than for as my sea viewers
so that's
I wish I could like hmm
I wish I could do something about it but
I also I I know that I shouldn't like
completely scatter my streams throughout
the whole day I'm already scattering it
plenty and I know that that's already
not good for like keeping a big audience
if I knew that it would be like this
[Music]
like then I would have uh like if I
would have known how much more effective
it is to always start your streams at
the same time then I would have done
that from the beginning but I didn't
know it would be like this
and you know I just want to make sure
that everybody around the world has
some chance to like catch my streams
um
so I try to start a lot of my streams at
like 4 P.M my time because that's like
11 P.M jst
in the winter that's midnight
unfortunately and so
[Music]
um
but even then even then it's not ideal
and I'm so
sorry about that I I I wish I could make
it easier for all my viewers on that
side of the globe
it's always something I have in mind
every week when I make my schedule I
always like
struggle with that in my brain like what
do I do what about my Australian Villas
what about my my Asian viewers ah [\h__\h]
I always think about that and I'm always
trying to compromise but man
yeah and then one then if I if I if you
know European views will also complain
because I'm the only one they have
but honestly European viewers your
little shits you even complain sometimes
when I'm I'm like doing streams that are
like
[Music]
evening of EU and then it's still too
early or still too late and I'm like
what am I what this is like wow
huh what do you want
[Music]
ah
yeah 4pm is a little bit early for like
people who work but you know I I keep in
mind that I'm about to do a long stream
when I start my streams at 4pm I know
that I'm about to do a long stream
usually
that's why I started early
you know
I'm not gonna start a seven hour stream
at 8pm my time
you know that's that's just that doesn't
make sense to me either
yeah see I obviously I can't please
everybody and I know that but I'm trying
to find a good balance all the time
[Music]
um
yeah
so everybody
who's trying their best to keep up with
me
thank you you are all my MVPs thank you
[Music]
sometimes you can watch me at work
that's great like I know so many people
watch me while they're working
so weird like I don't think many others
have
I feel like I
[Music]
percent of my life audience watches me
at work
I don't think that's normal
[Music]
we should ask
should make a poll I mean there's not so
many people here now but
the people here are very dedicated kind
of people right let's do Paul do you
often or sometimes
watch my streams during work
[Music]
home
all questions started to you okay let's
see
[Music]
if you guys are multitaskers
yes oh
[Music]
I mean
I work from home does it count I would
say so yeah
I would say listening pounds
[Music]
my
guess was pretty good
did I say 60 or 70 percent
67 now
[Music]
I said 60 was even higher
at least with this audience
wow
see that's that's dedication though
that's how much you really want to watch
my streams that you risk getting in
trouble at work or you you risk not
getting done much work
it's a 69.
I used to because it was easier now they
care about rules that's too bad
[Music]
no yeah but like I
I remember watching some streams doing
my work because it was like really
really boring at times nothing was going
on
um
I'm glad some of you guys can spend your
time at work like that and it's not too
busy to you know
so you have to miss out on me
[Music]
thank you guys for trying your best to
keep up with me really really it means a
lot to me wherever you're at work doing
my streams whether you're you should be
sleeping during my streams or even if
it's at a normal time of the day thank
you for always trying to be there and be
be here
[Music]
um and watch me
anytime I love you guys
love you guys for that hmm
[Music]
thank you Janine
happy for your anniversary you will
always be my oh she let's keep Korean
memory of kfb let's go
thank you Skye also one of the oldies
but Goldies you guys are my Golden Girls
thank you oh Big Night Shift not worried
about anyways yeah night shift off the
night shift people are often alone or
almost alone in their job so
yeah now thank you Skye I'm so happy
you're part of kfp
yeah another very positive
ray of sunshine
almost like you're Phoenix
only almost
not quite there
because I'm the only one yeah
thank you Skye
thank you a restaurant for the rainbow
wow
I can't believe this journey with my
favorite Phoenix YouTuber is already
going imagine
the H tuber
tuba
still same pronunciation
Phoenix tuber is already ongoing for
three years and you always know how to
make a smile I've much experienced in
those three years but I still have
something to do one I can check off now
a red subject of emotion yes you and
even made it into a rainbow ah there you
go I've never been to check up a pinky
yes somehow never did that I follow and
support you since the beginning and I
will continue to do so I hope for many
more years to come I can enjoy your
streams and this fantastic Community I
hope so no
I want and while I'm at it making the
rainbow yeah many things happened but if
I had to name my highlight I say dokomi
2022 where I not only could watch a
concert and meet with many KFC but also
could meet you in the meet and greet
yeah I remember
thank you for all that thank you for
many hours of fun thank you for being
such a nice person thank you that you're
always so passionate and communicative
with your fans thank you for everything
[Music]
not to forget thank you for all your
hard work and novel Thanks goes to
Carefree the best community there is oh
you're all great people thanks Viva
lucky are announced forever to my
favorite chicken hey you started with
Phoenix what happened
yeah that was such a
thing down
all right
one of my German
German chickens
um
all the correct really
really I don't know if I can believe you
it doesn't really like how why would why
would it correct from Phoenix to chicken
makes no sense
but since you were so nice I'll give you
the benefit of the doubt
oh
thank you you didn't have to go so hard
checking up all those things off your
bucket list but wow
thanks for a beautiful rainbow for all
the support and yeah I hope we can you
know do stuff in Germany again in the
future
or anywhere really but
yeah those were good times I was really
happy to see you guys all of you in
person would be great if we can
make it happen again yeah but I can tell
you now
wow wow will not be uh next year I
highly doubt it no no no
no no no no
[Music]
so far actually I don't have any
knowledge of anything for next year yet
but it's still kind of early anyway very
early usually
it's like
um
six two
[Music]
three months maybe ahead of time
that I find out about being somewhere
[Music]
and in my NYC when is that no I don't
think I'll be there
my last one for this year
is uh the one in Texas
right yeah yeah
unfortunately no no anime NYC but isn't
there maybe somewhere else from home
alive I feel like
they probably have someone right
[Music]
Advent ah
well there you go
[Music]
oh and Susan oh that's interesting
oh
well you know I know I don't think it's
really normally with so many members in
whole life it doesn't really make sense
to bring anyone like a second year in a
row or so yeah
was I at NYC before then I don't think
it's gonna happen any again but
[Music]
um
don't we still have an unannounced one
no that one kind of
um got canceled
I think if we're talking about what I
think we're talking about
y'all I was looking really forward to
that one but
um
ah too bad
[Music]
anyway thank you so much restaurants
thank you sir
wow
[Music]
Indigo five Alpha thank you for the
recipe first Super Chat it says here wow
happy anniversary thank you this is my
first Super Chat and I want to thank you
for everything you've given us I tried
to watch the vods a two-time speech just
to catch up
you make us happy with every Stream So I
wish you great success
wait it's your first super chat but
you're already so you're really you've
been here for a while
you make us happy with every Stream So I
wish you great success in every aspect
of your life love you five five ever
thank you thank you thank you I wish you
great success in everything you want to
achieve as well of course
and thank you I'm glad you're you're
trying to catch up doing your best there
I I'm sorry I stream too much for people
who are too busy but still want to see
everything I'm sorry
um
okay gotta talk really slow yeah so when
you're watching
this Vlog unless you're here right now
then you can hear it properly in two
times speed
I hope you don't accidentally miss it
that would be such a waste wouldn't it
thank you for your
first ever Super Chat oh there you are I
didn't need to speak like that then God
damn it
there you are
[Music]
a little [\h__\h] made me do this
I'm glad you're here
seven people donations he is falling
even
it's love to be too bad
[Music]
happy first anniversary Dental that is
full of happiness you guys are in sync
here these two
whole [\h__\h] so in sync Days full of
Happiness of you go so fast thank you
for every one more time let's together
for more join us nkfp need more chicken
yes we do I mean we the good thing is we
gained a lot of new Champions yesterday
yeah that was honestly very strategic of
me I'll admit that
because
I know from past experiences that these
Milestones are a way of getting
subscribers faster
and you know
I felt like if I can get a push then I
should freaking take it
[Music]
um
so I thought even if it's not as
effective as it was in the past I will I
will
I will use this strategically
got some new people in
um
it was it was very effective though
I think if I wouldn't have done the
marathon it would have taken me weeks
with like natural growth
so for me it's like big success honestly
everything done correctly
business woman
genius y'all
[Music]
no
I stopped during one of your karaoke my
reference so the end they were like oh
wow and you're still here so I hope that
all the people who subscribed during the
marathon yesterday will also give me a
chance
speaking of
let me let me check something really
quick
ah
shy is that how you say it of 1.5
million again oh
[Music]
but that's okay it will go up again
Free People
[Music]
at the beginning of the stream it was
um 1.5
million and two
so that's why I knew oh oh oh oh
this is dangerous you'll stop with your
smart fridge can you really do that can
I tell you
tell your kitchens I had the biggest
[Music]
shocked today
in my kitchen
don't worry
nothing was on fire
oh
I was standing in my kitchen
and I was thinking about
sinks
and
because I was like watching uh some
random video on YouTube where there was
like a sink where you can pull the the
tap
and it's like a like you know you can
pull it out and then it's like a shower
head almost yeah the holes yeah and
I was like standing in front of my sink
and I'm like thinking to myself
imagine if mine had that option and I
never noticed that I don't know why and
then I'm like wait
shall I try
and then I pull it I tried pulling it
and it comes
[Music]
why did nobody tell me when I moved in
oh
that's my sink could do this
same thing happened to you really
what do you mean why does this always
happen to you
like I I didn't think this was such a
basic thing now in kitchens
might be more normal in America but I
don't think it's so normal
like nowadays like I think newer
kitchens maybe like to have this option
but I don't think it's like
that common
no but I was like
mind blown
I see it a lot in like an American like
sitcoms or whatever yeah I don't think
it's that common here they do it but
it's not that common okay so it's not a
given and it didn't look it just looked
like a normal tap
so
oh
I didn't expect it and nobody introduced
it to me when I was shown the apartment
I didn't expect it at all
also because I don't really need the
feature I don't need it I don't use it
now that I know I have it I also don't
think I'll use it much but good good to
have it I guess for certain times when I
need to fill like big containers or so
um
damn good for dishwashing I don't
dishwash I have a dishwasher
[Music]
you have no idea how mind-blown I was
because I was just like in my head I was
like I imagine
and then I wasn't even gonna try but for
a moment I was like
but what if
nah no way and while thinking nah no way
I'm just like you know this
pulling it as if I'm like
falling for a clowns trick that's how I
felt
I was like no way and then I'm like what
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my God
it's it's oh my God I I still can't
believe it it's crazy it's so crazy
[Music]
who knows what else I missed out on
like features
I wonder
yeah you learn something new every day
laughs
it's crazy
I have to pull it again
to make sure it was really real that it
really happened I'm not sure if it
really happened did it really happen was
that real
I have to pull it again
oh my God maybe it was a malfunctioning
maybe I was destroying my sink in that
moment maybe it wasn't intentional
maybe I broke it
maybe my arms became so strong my grip
strength became so strong recently from
swimming that when I pulled it it wasn't
a feature it was just me destroying it
[Music]
maybe my fridge has a secret Ice Cube
Department somewhere and I don't know
about it
nah I don't think it does have that Mo
like I think this is also very common in
American fridges
um but here
fridges don't have a ice cube or water
dispenser unless you buy a really really
expensive one
[Music]
that's like American style like there's
legit American style fridges
and then there's normal fridges
um
I didn't drink a Red Bull no I was
considering it though because I was kind
of tired
but no I didn't drink no I was just shy
how much is a normal fridge I don't know
I don't know
no idea
Maybe
Amazon
how much
cool
shrunk
question
[Music]
oh oh cheap
oh five cheap
like a typical oh one that looks like
mine
like same size
[Music]
on Ikea 500
yeah it really looks like mine no it's
not mine though but yeah
500 euro
[Music]
that's fine
with the full-size fridge here
[Music]
but the American ones those are more
expensive
here I see one from Samsung that looks
like you know the size of an American
one with a water dispenser with two
doors opening to the side yeah that one
is one thousand two hundred sheesh
that's a lot of money
it's not it's not um necessary guys to
spend so much money on the fridge
smart that's a smart fridge right
I will not
I would not buy a Smart Switch because
you know they are sentient and they take
over your home
and they will kill you
so I wouldn't really recommend it
smart fridge is a little bit too smart
for our Goods
yeah let's keep our appliances dumb yeah
with no brain cells please
[Music]
fridge uprising
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
terrifying
where was I
oh yeah thank you
that's what I read right yeah yeah thank
you see his Pony
[Music]
another one didn't you already send one
so proud of you for making it this far
and I'm so proud to be a chicken your
music streams and personality have made
my life so much more fun oh
I love you thank you for being so sweet
when you guys say things like that it's
like really really
hard to imagine but I am honored thank
you Jackson
[Music]
yeah
hmm
you guys
overwhelming me with love
Kitty
car 47 out thank you for the pinky
what's up
oh yeah it was about to begin let's go
let's go exciting I'm reaching the
beginning of my stream but the the
scroll bar is already like almost in the
middle
so no
it's good it's going good good
oh my voice is not hurting yet
I'll I'll read it normally congrats on
the three years you've achieved so much
and have brought so much happiness into
my life
it's hard to think what it would be like
without finding you I sometimes feel
like I'm repeating myself saying it but
your passion and kindness have always
inspired me to be a better chicken
thank you for making my days Amazing by
being the perfect honestly I love you
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
thank you soon
yeah
God
I don't know I don't know how I do it I
don't know how I do it
I just do it my my sheer existence is
just a blessing to all of you I suppose
now thank you one dog I think
even without me
you are a great chicken
you didn't need me but if I can help you
have confidence or or enjoy life a bit
more
than I am more than happy about that
thank you so much
[Music]
appropriate outfit really
I guess yeah this one was used for that
image where I'm like oh
[Music]
that was funny
thank you
I miss the times when you wear mooncat
[Music]
the Jesus while I am Jesus Wawa
takanasi Jesus takana Jesus
[Music]
life would be a lot more dull
no
[Music]
true my life would also be a lot more
dull
[Music]
and thank you Shawnee and Ian thank you
soon Randall sand thank you blue thank
you for the pinky oh
you baby
my baby
let me
let me hold you
and swing you
you just be sweetie I'll lead up a dad
happy for your anniversary I think I've
said this a lot but you truly are an
inspiration in a lot of ways and amazing
I don't I'm proud to be a member of kfb
for Life much love wow for life
I take this because you wrote it down
this is a written agreement
therefore it's a binding contract you
are aware of that right
hey
[Music]
I mean it's
it's written down
and
you know I would be careful now because
I'm I'm lawyering up so
yeah be careful be careful what you
write down towards me
[Music]
I will take a screenshot of this
do I need to sue you already
didn't you say for life did you alive
and where are you
I don't see you in chat
[Music]
surely you will watch the archive right
hopefully
to
to make sure
[Music]
that everything
is being
I lost my train of thought
[Music]
so the train is now canceled
it just ended just ended
[Music]
you mean father of train no I don't
right I don't mean that
you're always gaslighting me
for the train no no can't be that
[Music]
I'm not thinking of trains I mean now I
kind of am but
I'm canceling the train of thoughts
about thought of trains
[Music]
no more
there's no legal loophole
[Music]
I'm closing them off
no loopholes
no
loopholes would be dangerous because if
you fall into one by accident
then it's a work accident
and that's a problem
no no no no no no no
can't have that thank you Alita
I don't think I ever had brisket before
brisket
what is a brisket
[Music]
Deutsch
I always see it in shows
[Music]
I mean
it it looks like I could have had it
before because
although probably not like no
Wonder
I wonder
[Music]
seems to be a specific part of the call
but
hmm
[Music]
the the the the
outside of it always looks very very
dark huh like almost
burnt
are we sure that's not burnt
um
very tasty and fatty ones slow cook
brings it out
[Music]
it's the best part yeah
crispy and heavily spiced so kind of
like bark bark bark bark bark
that's bark
what tree bar
what
definitely looks like a tree bark
[Music]
brisket sandwiches oh oh
don't make me
huh why why
I have a banana and I'm not afraid to
eat it
I'm gonna eat it now in fact special
but that's not really
a good equivalent to brisket honestly
um
[Music]
oh my God
um
food yesterday arrived so late
[Music]
way too late
and the delivery person
didn't come up to me
asked me to come down and then I went
down
in my pajamas I went outside
I looked around for like
a whole minute
or two
and no one was there I couldn't see
anyone
yeah
nobody was there and I went back up
because I forgot my phone
should have called when I was down there
um
but uh yeah
then I called and like where the [\h__\h]
are you
can't even say it I didn't swear but I'm
like where were you I was down there
right now and you weren't there
hmm
and he's like oh I was there I was here
I'm like I was there too like
I'm gonna go down again okay
[Music]
now I got my order in the end but it was
unnecessarily complicated I don't think
he even tried to
figure out how to ring my doorbell or
anything
didn't even attempt it
[Music]
um
I didn't get pizza because
delivery pizza is [\h__\h] here
and I am spoiled by a real Italian pizza
so
I even eat real Italian pizza with a
frozen pizza because the frozen pizza
for me is a different dish
but deliberate Pizza is just like really
really really really bad Italian pizza
and I don't like that
so most of the time I try to not order
it every time I order it I'm so
disappointed
[Music]
frozen pizza it's different
and like just like
delivery here there's like a million
delivery places that make pizza
and I tried several but none of them
not surprisingly not a single one of
them
delivers real proper Italian pizza
they're all like shitty Pizza
I can tell you none of those pizzas are
made in the proper oven
oh [\h__\h]
tried so many
oh [\h__\h] why why why why why why
[Music]
and then they give their restaurants
like Italian names
but you know
it's just
all fake
they're all just pretending
[Music]
be okay yeah
but I don't know
um
when you tried the real deal
a few times in your life
then I'm I'm just so done with this fake
Pizza [\h__\h]
it doesn't Spike joy in me
well
um
[Music]
okay I finished my banana but now I
really need to go to the island meeting
wow wow
I am like
turning into liquid at this point
wow
I'll be right back
[Music]
and I found smoothie
over my shoulder now
[Music]
oh
you just woke up because I stood up
she heard me walking
[Music]
okay I let her go
he has no patience now I go
[Music]
foreign
TY but I did go to idle meeting I have
chunky ones in my position
[Music]
it's so cute she's so fat and big and
fluffy I'm gonna put on my headphones
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] my PlayStation controller
blah my my pink PlayStation control
yeah chunky monkey you know she's so
cute these days
um when I stream
she always sleeps
uh in the bathroom where
I have my clothing hamper
because I'm too lazy to take the clothes
off of it
[Music]
um
so she always sleeps under it under the
clothing hamper where the clothes are
still hanging
am I saying it wrong
yeah because I think she likes the
feeling of being hidden she thinks she's
hidden
underneath it
but I know she's there
and and also I guess it's more like
quiet in there so the cloves and
everything dampen the sounds
for you
thank you for saying hi
she's a baby
[Laughter]
she's such a baby I love how she smells
after she cleans herself you know what I
mean you don't know what I mean probably
but
I don't know smoothie doesn't smell the
same
but
it's like I don't know she smells
she has a nice odor
a nice body old
I like it
yeah
[Music]
she's not even damp anymore at that
point but you know
I don't know I I it's just like I come
on this is probably the same of humans
when you spend a lot of time with
someone you appreciate their body odor
unless it's like a really uh sweaty and
disgusting one
[Music]
ah baby
I can't let you go you're too soft I
need to cuddle you baby
I can't let you go unfortunately I know
you like being cuddled don't be like
this
if you could buy cat fragrances would
you
wow she's a baby she's such a floppy
chunky
wobbly baby
[Music]
okay let's see if I can read something
here while I pet my cat this is perfect
uh
McIntyre
[Music]
is okay if we time sure went by fast but
those were three amazing years filled
with emotions and I'm so happy to have
been proud to call you my Aussie I'm
your Aussie keep being awesome thank you
see it's not my not your first Super
Chat apparently but I don't see you uh
in my super jets that much so it feels
feels really fresh so I'm happy to hear
that I'm your Aussie thank you what does
chunky monkey say about that hmm
[Music]
laughs
she's a bit jealous
[Music]
yeah
oh no oh he wants to go but I but you're
So Soft why are you so strong did you
gain weight I don't think
[Music]
she is purring by the way it just
whenever I put her face to the
microphone she stops
he's being grumpy
oh
she always purrs when I touch her
[Music]
oh
anyway thank you McIntyre
you know I still I still feel
like I don't know what's the right word
um
[Music]
embarrassed no flatter
I never and anyone says uh You Are My OC
[Music]
that means I'm your number one
makes me very happy
[Music]
why would I feel constipated from that
hey
that makes no sense
it makes no sense
somebody said constipated no
no
[Music]
thank you McIntyre delvio thank you for
the pinky happy fourth anniversary
attention keep up the good work I'm
still here supporting even if it's not
that often congrats also on the new
album I'm looking forward to it thank
you thank you so much I'm glad you like
the album
you know what the the new girl should
play Don't Starve Together with our
character
I wish I could play Wawa
they should play it shouldn't they
I suggested them
where's my I made a group to communicate
with Advent directly
let me
let me suggest Club game to you girls
I don't know if you know but years ago
when myth was fresh
someone made a Don't Starve Together
uh mod
skin for the myth characters
and we used it
in our stream
maybe you girls can
dream it too and there is can use my
skin
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah when myth was still baby
[Music]
it's a fine game
it's fine
[Music]
chill and fun cute it's cute
I don't think it's that bad
haven't played it in a long time though
we had fun when we played it especially
you know with our own skins makes it
even more special
didn't we even play it twice
um
we just didn't get very far in terms of
frost progress so that's unfortunate
maybe they can get further
[Music]
too high as a collab game I don't know
they'll figure it out
they have bibu
apparently Bieber is considered a huge
gamer
[Music]
yeah one Swift and once without yeah
yeah exactly
so anyway here I'm promoting your work
to the girls
thank you so much for your support I'm
so happy you're still around even if
it's not that often that's fine that's
okay you're still thinking of me you
know it's like the promise we just made
that you guys show up at least for the
important times
yeah I'm still very happy about that
what do you mean long time no see you
still you still got the Wawa profile
picture you still love me right you're
not gonna leave me
right
[Music]
yes yay that's what I wanted to hear
yeah
[Music]
thank you thank you sir Nico no
I can't believe we are at third
anniversary yeah it's crazy thanks for
just doing what you always do which is
bring some fun and smiles to us all I'm
happy to have been a fan since the
beginning of myths debuts thank you for
being my oshikiana the beginning you
know that's quite the flex I would say
at this point
um
I think it's the flex
good Flex
thank you for being here since the
beginning for for never giving up on us
for never getting tired of us for over
supporting us especially me apparently
is that a strawberry that looks like a
strawberry what is that chicken holding
[Music]
I think it's a strawberry
I don't remember this chicken being
drawn
[Music]
no in in your size guys it looks maybe
like a heart but uh there's like dots on
it it is a strawberry
I don't remember the strawberry eating
chicken
[Music]
Debbie was such a long time ago I still
remember it
[Music]
W time was weird man
the heavier time was just weird
surreal to think about it now even
um
[Music]
weird weird weird weird
damn
crazy time man
[Music]
life-changing wild time
how small y'all made good a small in the
first collab she was like one inch tall
generally I think back then
um
we weren't
putting much
uh in priority on having our models be
like
equally sized the problem with good is
though that her face
to body ratio is so weird compared to
others
you know
so even when we wanna
like make her
face the same size as ours her body will
look so much smaller
[Music]
big hammerhead
yes she admits it
no no no it's a thing like we talk about
it
it's you know I'm not Bobby shaming her
though
[Music]
she's beautiful the way she is
it's just uh you know hard to balance
the sizes of us
[Music]
but yeah and then because well it was
just exaggerated everything like made
Cali too big to tall
uh and then yeah
good at way too small
and
I generally when I do collabs I like to
have everybody at the same height I
don't care about the character height
that much
just because I want it to look like
good on the screen like I want to have a
line
you know right I try to keep them the
same height no matter how big their or
how small they're supposed to be
[Music]
also if you if you really try to put
everyone at the same at the height that
they're supposed to be then people gonna
get like cut off and stuff and that's
just annoying when setting up the stream
so you know
yeah that's why I try to put people
around the same size roughly at least
maybe just a small difference like
um just slightly
not exaggerated
[Music]
sticker even nothing to read let's go
thank you for the support
yay
[Music]
Nathan thank you for the rest of the
chat congratulations on Freehold your
extension here's to many more now get
yourself a snack or does a snack like
you even need a snack oh oh
stop hey I already ate a banana just a
moment ago so I won't I won't get
another snack um for now I also ate
watermelons before the Stream
[Music]
small watermelons
I can read the stickers for us please
found reasons alt account number sizes
you
Larissa cotton
see you could it be Marissa by the way
was so sweet and supportive last night I
was like talking with her a little bit
after my stream was over not talking and
like voice just text
she's so sweet
she's always so supportive like I feel
like I have someone who I can go to to
like vent about anything and she also
vents to me about anything we're like
really really open with each other
like I I don't think I've ever felt this
this much of a freedom and welcomeness
to talk about anything at all
of someone
in hono
you know I just feel like you know
whatever I say she'll she'll listen to
it and she'll agree with it
um
I saw what she said about me in the
Louis collab yeah
hey
I mean I have some good conversations
with other members too you know but with
narissa it's just like on a whole nother
level
[Music]
um
you know so it's it's been great so far
[Music]
we don't talk like every day anymore
um but still plenty and I know she's
always there for me so
every every second or third day like
yesterday I had to tell her to calm her
tits
[Music]
yeah she said
she she I was like I'm gonna go now
she's like good go to sleep bye bye and
I'm like hey you and she's like I love
you Kiana you're my muse and I'm like
pien You Are My Hope and then she sends
me a kissy emoji and then I'm like thank
you for being the sweetest love and then
she's like in caps lock I literally love
you and I'm like okay okay
[Music]
um gift of me bonking a chicken with a
with the baseball bat
and and I said call me a titties
and I love you too though
[Music]
foreign
but then I ended up not going to sleep
we ended up tangenting a bit more
about this and that
and she calmed them no yeah she did she
did she did
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
what does that mean
[Music]
s
aren't you spanking the chicken with the
bat yeah yeah
oh she probably likes that
[Music]
yeah the way she's so passionate when
she says how much she loves me it's it's
wow so flattering
she's like so exaggerating
it's so funny to me anyway Thank you
Nathan you know what if I need a snack
maybe I'll nibble on you a little bit
[Music]
oh the skin on the chicken honestly yeah
it's great I agree
roasted chicken skin mmm marvelous
I agree
Daisy God
good taste Daisy seems hungry
thank you Daisy wow
[Music]
sounds like she loves you I think she
does
[Music]
a bit like Ollie yeah but but like I
don't think with only that she loves
anyone like as particularly much as
narissa does me you know
only only divides her love pretty
equally
I think
throughout everybody
[Music]
Thai tea
how you doing
hi tea I feel like I haven't seen you in
a while too
so happy to see you
every once in a while when you show up
thank you taichi for being there I hope
you're doing well I don't know if you're
watching now but thank you so much for
showing up at such an important stream
for me
um
means a lot to me I hope you will
continue
to be part of kfb don't don't go away
[Music]
thank you soon for celebrating with me
the silent hero
human expenses
[Music]
three years of myth is three years of
Yen yeah
true it wasn't only
three years of myth it was the end third
anniversary of whole have English too we
didn't even like
think about that
or talk about it
oh
that's a great point
any myth anniversary will be a Ian
anniversary
which is
actually huge
damn
whoa
why didn't I think about that
now I'm like even more proud
I'm so proud wow
wow
[Music]
yes
soda
is
[Music]
oh
I have to write to jenma about this
[Music]
whoa
did you realize
because I didn't and
it's special
myth anniversary
no third myth anniversary equal
anniversary
[Music]
and for free yes wow
wow
I'm gonna send the mind blown yeah the
GIF from the guy with the glasses and
the universe
good good good
[Music]
thank you for pointing this out this is
actually
not something I thought about
you ladies all carried hard to bring us
to this point and I credit you the most
from my initial lurking 2.5 years ago
you're by far the best boss here's to
many more great years to come wow
thank you
yeah I mean we had to carry Ian hard and
indeed for a long time because it took a
while
until we got the you know first couple
of new members
and then even from there on it took even
longer
for Advent Chief kids whatever
[Music]
but yeah yeah
so indeed the responsibility
was on only us for a long time
[Music]
yeah Advent took so long man
I really
wanted it like at least half a year
earlier but you know
can't
really influenced that
for something really good
[Music]
hi
big
sometimes I wanna be bigger music change
[Music]
even though I love that bgm I didn't
even get sick of it after
three hours
good bgm
okikunata
I took the Mario mushrooms
um surely also something to consider but
you know I just felt like
we needed it we needed it um
we I think we really needed it uh but
yeah
takes time
and they prepared well
so
all is good in the end
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah when Ian almost all
of Ian was sick or just not streaming
yeah yeah nah that winter the winter of
2022 will never be forgotten
it was a rough time for all whole life
English fans suffering from lack of
streams
so desperate to provide content
takanashikiala while being sick with
several
illnesses
God turned into a crazy state made sock
puppets to make up for the lack of
friends
and continue to stream with the sock
puppets
the flag of Arc
also known as the flag Embark yeah
maybe I don't know sock puppets this
year I mean I probably will make some
yeah yeah
because they were well received last
year and it was fun to make them maybe I
can improve them a little bit this year
thank you so much senior shitaka you
raised many great points I am once again
proud thank you mwah
thank you soon happy for your
anniversary thank you thank you so much
thank you for being there on my special
day
on a special occasion and also on many
other days thank you
[Music]
Ryan ains thank you soon
Crystal Clips tag soon Kiana's chicken
nuggets thank you for the pinky
congratulations on your third
anniversary the past three years have
been amazing I feel lucky to have been
here from the start looking back at how
much you've achieved is super impressive
and inspiring I can't wait for you
future streams and releases thank you so
much yum
yeah it's been a long long journey and
you're part of it thank you for not
leaving my side my cute chicken nugget
dude
thank you thank you thank you
Amber Man Down kitchen
soon
dragons
I can't believe how lucky we are to have
you in whole life you've brought so much
joy to people and they're just an
incredibly fun and loving person I can't
wait to see what the future holds and
I'll continue supporting you thank you
I'm
I'm really glad I could
um
find this place
and make make it my place you know
so much that you know even when in the
beginning there were doubts
of what makes me special
I think
I think many people would say
that
I I brought something special to me to
Whole Life English and to whole life
and and that I was an important link of
myth and still am so
yeah
I'm glad I could prove myself in that
regard I mean
thank you thank you thank you guys thank
you guys
yeah
yeah yeah yeah beginning was a bit tough
because of that like all the doubts I
had
because they were put into my brain I
was quite confident honestly before like
right before debuting and and at my
debut and then my confidence was quickly
destroyed but
um
tried my best to build it back up and
prove myself anyway regardless of all
the negativity negativity that was
surrounding me
and I'm I hope that
um even like non-regular Watchers of me
can say
with confidence that I deserve my spot
and that I am a necessary part
of this generation
I'm really really happy to have been
given the chance
[Music]
really really glad and honored
thank you guys
guys I'm so happy I could meet all of
you
I'm so happy
if I wasn't in whole life I wouldn't
have met all of you and you wouldn't
have met me
we would have never known of each
other's existence probably
I'm so glad it happened
I'm so glad you could find me
thank you for finding me
I love you guys
so also dragon's fire to you especially
thank you so much
I Can See For You
thank you soon
hope we can spend more time together
thank you thank you thank you thank you
yeah I was definitely vulnerable and
emotional and yeah
I definitely was I mean I still
am but I think I I I got stronger
I'm just glad that I could maybe change
some people's minds over the time
um
no if I could do that for some then in
theory I could do it for everybody but I
guess just some people are especially
stubborn
[Music]
and the game of Korean things on the
pinky happy third anniversary Kiana it
has been free fantastic years with you
and the rest of myth I've been here from
the beginning watching you and the
others grow and become such an
incredibly talented entertainers and I
couldn't be more proud of y'all
thank you
yeah we've all grown a lot all of us not
just me um
all grown together
and I'm proud of us
me and myth
um
thank you so much the game of creed for
looking over us
or looking up to us because you're small
small chicken smaller than gouda I guess
you're looking up to us not over us
thank you thank you for being here thank
you I keep on forgetting you're in
Norway what the hell
damn
I always think you're in America
happy first anniversary
[Music]
thank you so much thank you soon
nip
if it weren't for you I probably would
still be staring at a red knob on a
faucet
why what
does that mean
also what did I just drop what the [\h__\h]
friendship the chicken
that is such a thing to say oh my God
ah
chicken shaping
[Music]
no that's so sweet
and also sad at the same time
thank you for a triple red wow thank you
holy [\h__\h] happy third anniversary Kiana
it's wild that has been three years
already it honestly doesn't feel like
it's been that long they do say time
passes faster when you're having fun I
want to feel the reason for that anyway
thanks for all the great streams and
being amazing for a third year in a row
ever
oh thank you ever
you're the best thank you so much I'm so
happy you're still here
thank you for always supporting the Wawa
thank you
[Music]
such a Chad so much support what the
hell
thank you so much
I really really appreciate it that's
insane be careful with your savings
please
now they're my savings
thank you soon for contributing
to my life
yeah think about it think about it
I'm using this donation
for paying my rent
and buying food
and clothes
buying cat food it's like basically
are you ready I'm gonna say something
really parasocial
are you ready are you ready
it's like
it's like we're married
[Laughter]
oh
oh [\h__\h]
I oh
it does it like
like
I wanted the voice
is it like I didn't say it is
it like
[Laughter]
take your meds hey
everybody calm your titties
oh I got a DM
Ma
oh I wonder actually Jen mom
how long have you been
I don't know if I can say the answer to
the question but how long has she been
in
huh
do you work for
Japan the fireman before
when is janma's anniversary
where you hired for Ian oh
oh Gemma has same anniversary
so basically
hired for Ian
um
but you were so efficient and skillful
and professional and helpful
from the start
she didn't even need a warm-up phase
[Music]
anniversary to YouTube
hey
I feel like from the team that was there
in the beginning there's not that much
left over
I mean it wasn't the big team to begin
with you know but Gemma remained a
constant
in the team and I think that really gave
um a lot of the members a lot of
stability
um I don't know if she's listening right
now but
should I say it
you really give Hollow
and uh and I'm listening okay
um
yeah like honestly even members who
weren't managed by jenma when in doubt
would always rely on General everybody
always knew you could rely on General
your own manager isn't around rely on
General
she has an answer to everything she
knows what's up
she knows what to do
she will take care of it
janma has I think great reputation and
is very very beloved within the talents
I probably I mean I can't judge that
well but probably also between staff
yeah she's the MVP of Ian yeah
management she's like the A10 of Ian
yeah
[Music]
let's have dinner soon
hahaha
time she gets an avatar she already has
it just doesn't move
now you're sounding like you're married
to General cheater hey
cheated first
I think
I would just assume so
I love cartoon Don
what else do I want to eat I need to
make a list
of what I want to eat in my next trip
because it's not that long I have to
organize it well
I really hope we signed the Purina
I'm trying to prenup to to to to get all
my money after we divorce
no
won't happen
gonna sue you
because Seinfeld prenup episode I don't
remember that
it's gonna get a prenup
um George
who's George marrying
was he marrying the crazy lady
Susan Susan ah Susan
Susan
yeah yeah yeah
hmm
prenup is so you don't have to give away
your money oh
that hold it
oh
oh yeah right it's always like in TV
shows it's always like when the rich
husband mentions the prenup the lady
gets like really insulted yeah yeah yeah
and it doesn't want
especially especially if it's like a
gold digger type of character oh
it's like huh you don't trust me you
don't love me
I mix something up there my show
water
[Music]
no
no definitely not would have tried to be
a staff or a manager no no no I don't
think I would have even been eligible
for that
um and yeah no no because I was only
seeing home live from the POV of a fan
and I wouldn't have thought about
becoming a mentor I don't think I would
have had the skill set and I I it's not
really some job I would have wanted to
do anyway
um I wouldn't want to work in a
Japanese work environment as a as like a
anything besides what I am now
like what I'm doing now is okay because
I have a lot of freedom but I don't want
to be tied to Japanese work environment
like um like a like an office worker or
whatever
no
yeah I I know how
how rough how tough Japanese work
environments are
and how you know over hours and all that
it's just given and part of the culture
pretty much and I respect anybody who
can
survive that but I'm not the type of
person like if I work over hours I would
say that I work like a lot
um but that is like on my own accord I
choose that
and I you know I don't feel pressured to
do anything really
so that that feels completely different
and I have a different like motivation
source and all that
um and I what's the word incentive I
basically get an incentive for the more
I work the more I get
no not exactly like one-to-one but
you know
so it just makes sense
um
[Music]
yeah
I hope jennma
takes care of herself properly and goes
to sleep now because it's already very
late in Japan
[Music]
I don't know if she's still listening
but
you should go to sleep at
she heard
what are you working on Denmark go to
sleep
go go go
catch the Dead
please
Germany's arrest
every time I meet Jenna and I'm like did
you sleep she's always like no
it's always a no
but every time I meet her when I'm in
Japan it's always like a busy time so I
would hope that when I'm not in Japan
she catches more sleep than when I am in
Japan I hope so
of General typing
the reply I've never replied
ah there it says Don't Stop together is
fun no she played it before then
Maybe
now we have a chance to see Advent play
Don't Starve Together we'll sleep soon
good
you better
okay okay okay where are we where are we
where are we
foreign
oh I love sparazzo that's one of my
preferred
cakes actually
when I choose a cake
I genuinely love cakes the most that
have lots of cream and fruit
some kind of fruit and Schmucks for the
kitchen it has like I don't know if you
guys know that one but it has lots of
cream and like chocolate chips on the
side like really thin it's like
stratzatella type of really thin
chips and and and and the little
cherries yeah yeah it's a black forest
cake yeah yeah but I feel like the
American black forest cake and European
black forest cake or Austin black forest
cake and it's probably a little little
bit different in taste and all that so
if you guys ever come to Austria or
Germany please eat sweet stuff desserts
and all that Portal cake oh it's the
portal cake ah
um
yeah and and
and I don't like me some like simple
jelly jelly cakes like like creamy
on the bottom and jelly on the top you
know what I mean with some strawberries
or raspberries
and this and that just simple ones
and I love sakatoate the most out of
like chocolate cakes because the
sakatoada the chocolate flavor is so
intense and so good but it's like
there's a refreshing Jam layer really
thin one but it's like it it works
wonders
so
I love I love all of them
you need to get back into Pokemon unite
they finally added the chicken the
chicken what chicken
eh
do you wait wait what you mean you don't
mean Pokemon United right you're talking
about uh
uh the cult game that we played right
because
isn't that something we were waiting for
are you mixing up some crazy stuff now
bag now
you do mean Pokemon oh okay but they
also apparently added the chicken right
in Cult of the Lamb
I want I want Advent people to play Cult
of the lab
and Marissa should play it and then
Harbor chickens
let me tell her
play Cult of the lamp and then choose
the chicken followers thanks
I can do it because they didn't have
them back when I played
and I told them to add it and it took
them like a year to add them
now there is chickens right there's
chickens now right
[Music]
it's so good she says she loves Cult of
the Lamb so she probably played it
before
I love it
what do you mean they're deleting the
game what
what do you mean yudia what does that
mean
eh they're remote what what huh
what what if I already have a copy
it's because of unity what the [\h__\h] Cult
of the Lamb
remove
what does that mean
massive monster made the announcement
that I will be deleting Cult of the land
as of January 1 2024 this is because the
game is built on the unity engine which
will see the introduction of a new
install fee this was this fee will
require developers to pay unityfx okay
okay so
when I already have it it's fine right
and who knows maybe Unity will go back
on their weird ways
I was a joke but it could probably
happen
they were joking oh okay why does it
come up here like
as like the first result
like I don't even have to click any
article they should like say it's a joke
it's a joke
they wonder it was more a joke as a
threat
yeah honestly though totally
um
uh
[Music]
warranted thank you
totally warranted like my God justify
yes Justified
what's what's in their brains that made
them think to make such a decision that
impacts
hundreds and thousands of game creators
small and big
what's is there a mind flare in their
brain
my God
okay Jen might still listening I should
I should I should be careful what I say
she might still be listening
heads empty yeah because the mind flare
ate up everything all the brain matter
was consumed
so head empty
that's not something you do after you
already established your
like programs
whatever
for so many years like
that's like if you want to do that do it
from the beginning or do it with a new
software
but you know
not when already so many people are
relying on it and already are using it
yeah
but they didn't go back on it yet right
but I feel like I mean maybe they will
though because like with so much
backlash
[Music]
not yet
not fully not entirely um
good
they will
I'm sure they will soon
three years ago myth debuted and I feel
see I I just read that naturally like
that I I don't think I could even like
by Omi is a different story but debuted
I will stay with debuted
uh and I felt like I got an early
birthday gift months later I became
a part of kfb and every day became
Christmas Kiara oh wow I am Jesus after
all you're always working year-round
doing everything you can for us we love
you Kiara and you will always be my
number one and only
love love love love love love love love
love
is in the air
thank you so much
thank you Merry Christmas
Dougal Jones thank you Merry Christmas
Merry Christmas to you Merry Christmas
to you
Merry Christmas in your pants too Merry
Christmas in your shoe
thank you so much
[Music]
mm-hmm
The Germ donation you know what they
should be because I just read someone
say I am Jesus player went there should
be a Jesus simulator is there a Jesus
simulator
imagine you're like Jesus and then you
walk through the city in the in the
simulator and everybody is like reacting
to like oh my God
is that what happens in the game too I
wonder
they're just like amen when they see you
I think it's called I am Jesus Christ
it's called I'm Jesus oh so that game is
the
Jesus simulator
wait I want to look that up
good luck getting perms for that yeah I
mean
I don't think it's impossible
I am
I am Jesus
oh there's also I am Satan
I am Jesus Christ
what happens
walk in the footsteps of Jesus in this
incredible first person retelling of oh
it's not really I want a shitty
simulator you know
I want a shitty simulator like all those
other simulator games
this already seems too intricate
I just want to walk through a city a
modern city as Jesus
and everybody reacts to me
and then I do Jesus things
I'm pretty sure it's shitty no
how do you know
Goat Simulator would be super fun a goat
simulator but Jesus
Jesus
there's a GTA mod for that
why
why is there no Jesus simulator what the
hell
oh well um
lean thank you for the recipe Chad happy
third anniversary thanks for your hard
work you bring light in our darkest days
and happiness in our saddest moments for
more years to come we love you P.S your
album is amazing I love it currently at
work watching your stream
be careful be careful
when you hear footsteps
close the stream immediately
or just disconnect your monitor
or shut down your PC
I'm also watching during work now
it's actually like around the same time
the super chat came in like 8 P.M 20 and
that was almost 9pm
so possibly you're at work now too hi
Baba yes be careful thank you for
watching even during work and we were
talking about this just a little bit ago
I really appreciate it I hope you don't
get in trouble don't get in trouble and
if you get in trouble make sure to argue
that
I need you
tell them there's this orange no excuse
me I meant yellow
ostrich YouTuber
that really really desperately needs you
foreign
and she just told you
something along the lines of that you're
married
and you took it very seriously so you
must you must care for your wife
oh
okay continue
[Music]
oh
I've been a long distance delicious
[Music]
oh my God nah thank you lean Jeremy too
thank you soon eating my thousands and
thank you soon
happy fourth anniversary thank you
you're amazing talented and so
heartbreaking and though I haven't been
here since the beginning of the three
years I know know that I'll continue
supporting you for the rest of many
years more thank you it's a promise
it's a promise oh even from Europe all
right
if you're from Europe you know
if you if you don't keep your promise
it's very easy for me to find you so
just saying
plot Twisters well I am
huh
got a problem guys did I say something
weird I didn't right everything I say is
normal
but well I am what what
what
hmm
nah everything's normal here
everything's normal at kfp
not the worst thing I ever said true
get used to it
so thank you sir I'm so happy to have
you around
hopefully for a long long time
hopefully we can make many memories
[Music]
today marks the end of the third year
and also my fourth birthday review last
year was a banger so any surprises and
events it's also overwhelming in a good
way even ending it with a banger album
let's rock the fourth year too you yeah
I'm so glad I could put out an album and
have it as one of my accomplishments of
this year um
I'm very proud and I'm glad that with me
you can celebrate your birthday happily
every year
I'm always making a party just for you
for you hey
it's a party in the kfp
it's about the indicate everything
[Music]
no
I want
I want Burger I don't know what to eat
today because I should be cooking hello
fresh
but I also have leftovers from yesterday
which are mid
but I also want to take a burger oh and
get a burger
but I'll probably cook
[Music]
hello
but the recipe is lorenza beans
let's see one of my recipes I forgot
uh
no no
no no no what happened
didn't I change this so well
um
ah this one's this one's fine I think I
made this one before
some
some pork steak with the the self-made
Earth butter
but the other things are like meh
one even has
spinach and champignons two things that
I hate
in it
I wish there was a function in
hellofresh where you can say like in
your general settings like I don't like
this I don't like this
and this and then they will not put any
recipes in your automatic selection
if it includes that
that should be a easy enough feature
yeah they're trying to kill me
if it was just one ingredient I could I
could still cook it and and just get rid
of that one but without spinach and
without Champions there's not much left
of this dish
[Music]
I gotta buy some extra things to replace
it with
maybe just a cherry tomatoes
oh
no oh well
explains the noodle arms hey
my arms are not so noodly anymore I
think
trying to flex
[Music]
yeah
no it's not much shorter no no no no no
no
I wouldn't even put that many things in
it just just almost every Seafood
um anyway nah uh thank you Lord evoke
yeah grazia
thank you
for your support
I'm happy to have
some Italiano in my chat
I want to go to Italy
to a nice place not the overly touristy
ones I want to go to a pretty empty
Beach
Gotta Give me recommendations Lord evoke
about what
Beach is the prettiest but also one that
doesn't have many
um
tourists and hopefully somewhat
reachable with an airplane and then
whatever I am I'm willing to take a
train or something like that a bus
although buses buses always scare me
overseas because buses always kind of
work differently Wherever You Are
sometimes you can't buy a ticket when
you enter sometimes you can
and I don't know sometimes it's per
station how much it costs sometimes it's
just per enter the bus
difficult
your city doesn't appear on the maps
what
oh do you mean sardini Sardinian I've
heard of Sardinian
in German you say Sardinian
yeah
a lot of people yeah I imagine because
it's really well known I also know it
not avidazen yet uh nothingness makes
the pinky happy fourth anniversary Piano
thank you thank you soon I appreciate it
thank you for celebrating with me
thank you duck attack
for the rest of the chat happy
anniversary potential for years with our
beautiful goddess has gone by so quickly
and has been a wonderful experience I
look forward to everything you've got in
store for us and of course I keep your
music on Loop the new album is fire
everybody
thank you oh
thank you I saw somebody talking about I
think in my kfp hashtag or so maybe
about my monthly listeners on Spotify
thank you guys please continue listening
to my music digitally if you can if you
feel like listening to something maybe
maybe while you're walking outside or
while you're in the bathtub or something
like that um
she's going on a tangent every single
super yeah cause you guys deserve it
because I don't want to just go like
you know take everyone off like a check
box
but I know it's not very efficient
I listen to it all the time it's so good
thank you thank you
you know thank you Dr Tech I am so happy
that even after three years you're still
here with me thank you mwah from the
bottom of my heart
flaming pants
thank you for the pinky I'm glad this
year you got so many well-deserved
chances to perform in 4D not only your
showcase and forfeits but also being
selected for hallo 27 and station
archive and even getting an extra iron
concert with Ian it has been the best
year so far that is true
that is true
that is very true indeed I agree yeah we
got many opportunities this this year
and I hope it will continue next year
I hope I get to have
many chances and hopefully uh also like
Freddy birthday on time maybe for once
and pretty yeah an anniversary would be
nice
and all that kind of stuff
yeah and I think Ian our own Branch will
hopefully work
on you know
creating more stuff like the the 3D
moment Recreations like like stuff like
that like maybe we can make more
General content on our side
and not rely so much on the Japanese
Branch to
you know
include us
yeah
because
doesn't
seem
like
yeah
oh you know what I mean
so I'm excited for the future to see how
the next year plays out I hope we can
you know
have a similar level of excitement
um
for being here and supporting me
throughout all of it
hi thank you also for the pinky Wawa
Love Sai love thank you thank you soon
chocolate Insomniac thank you for two
random chats Mamma Mia
Mamma Mia
thank you
thank you I can't believe it's been
three years I've never been once
regretted stumbling upon your Mario Kart
rage Clips ah
which ultimately led me to use dream
you've been such an inspiration to me
that these past four years have been the
best years of my life from attending
multiple conventions to supporting you
at connect
I've never thought I would meet so many
amazing kfp and whole life fans thank
you Kiara for entertaining your
entertaining streams uh for the many
Great Moments and most of all for being
my honesty
every time I read that it's like an
arrow shoots from my heart
thank you so much that's so sweet
and the Mario Kart
are you just mentioning that makes me
feel like I want to play Mario Kart
again
um the new uh tracks the last ones
are they out now
because I know they in
showed them
but are they also out no
yeah yeah
oh then we should play Mario Kart
together
so we can try all the new tracks that we
haven't tried yet it's been a while
since my last
um Mario Kart outing
would be fun
[Music]
Ian tournament
yeah that could also be a thing
I think we were just talking about
a different game uh for like you know
and all all of Ian uh
stream
um
I do want to look into f-zero too
actually yeah because I watched uh some
content on it
and it looks kind of fun
personally not as fun as Mario Kart but
it could be fun for one stream
[Music]
hmm
who
don't ten who
I don't know such a person what what do
you mean what who's that
finally guys
he finally hundred percented everything
oh my God he did like several streams
where he was like grinding like killing
all the bosses on the map in the
overground and underground all of them
took him hours and hours and hours and
then he did a stream on grinding the the
sign guys but he didn't like the Sign
Guy so he just teased everyone with the
floating platform
good
I thought the Sign Guy was kind of fun
of course it's like annoying when you do
it all at once you have you should have
done it like
whenever you see one then it's kind of
fun I think the you know who I mean
the guy who stands with his sign
everywhere
I like that guy like I didn't also
always do it I didn't always feel like
doing his
um thing
but I I liked him
there's maybe a little bit too many of
him
but I think it's
um a fun little in-between thing to
figure out how to make that science
stand I enjoyed it
yeah
but I think his problem was when he
first did one he thought that was the
only one and that he's done with it and
then it's ah then he saw him
uh there was a misunderstanding he saw
the same NPC all over the world several
times and he just assumed that the quest
was already finished by doing it once
so he ran by them so many times that
eventually when he realized by the
comments and all that that uh it wasn't
done you have to do every single one of
them
um then he was like
fucktal that sucks
and yeah because we already missed so
many then he decided that's [\h__\h] and he
doesn't want to do them
well in the end he had to do them
because they count for the hundred
percent
yeah
if he would have understood from the
beginning then he might have just
enjoyed it more but I feel like he
ruined his own experience yeah yeah
he does generally talk to every NPC but
just this one he ignored because he
thought he was done with it
and
yeah yeah also I really liked it because
he gave good food sources I I just
wanted the food
hmm
no no oh well but he's finally reaching
the finale I need to watch the the
videos
I'm excited to see
his reaction
hmm
it's it's yeah it's a bit tiring
sometimes he can be very negative
yeah
um
no
German DSP I wouldn't say he's that bad
but every now and then he shows signs of
it
yeah because of his complaints but
gameplay wise he's definitely better
than him
[Music]
yeah yeah dsps on a whole nother level
yeah yeah yeah I I agree with that
mm-hmm
we both have the same sub count let's go
maybe no he will collab with me just
kidding and I wouldn't want that
[Music]
this is why I mostly stick to positive
people like you me positive
playing so much not about like not so
much about the games I play but just
like everyday things and just everything
[Laughter]
me positive I wish I could be more
positive
I wish I was more positive
I feel like I spread a little bit too
much negative energy
but I can't hold back
and it's relatable thank you
you are a very positive person what you
think so
you're the most positive person I know
really yes you're a positive a bucket
and TV shows
I praise everything
TV show
I enjoy
everything
you're a pessimistic optimist
um
[Music]
your negative isn't as bad as you think
it's not a level of instruments okay
okay if you think so
that's one thing I was a bit worried
about
[Music]
it
still very uplifting to be around thank
you
to pretty negative at time and yet you
love me raigana
you definitely had your moments when
you've needed our reassurance oh oh you
know because it's rough sometimes you
know
like putting yourself out there every
day almost
it's just like I'm sharing my whole life
too this is like big brother guys
beat tubing
Big Brother
you you'll hear and see me so much
every day I'm bound to share a lot of my
feelings with you and you see me being
vulnerable a lot
we're at the shower scenes ew
don't want to see that
fingers normal levels thank you
foreign
[Music]
ful for all the time we have spent
together and all the hilarious and
touching moments I hope you still love
doing this as much as we love watching
watching you thank you
I think I
how do I feel about it compared to the
beginning I wonder
I
I maybe
love it more than in the first year
because I just have had a really rough
time in the first year and I didn't get
to enjoy it much
um
yeah there was like a barrier
and now that everything has been
overcome and I'm just in a in a routine
um
I I still love doing it very much
there are some days where I feel
very down anyway still
and where I don't know
you know
can I really continue doing this and
this and that but don't worry guys I
push myself
because in the end it's worth it and I
still have
things I want to do and achieve
and it's still fun like there's there's
plenty of fun days that that balance out
the negative
days
[Music]
and I am good at
ignoring
the
like suffering so
um
I am having a good time
a good time
I want to continue doing this this is
this is my thing now it's my thing and
I feel like there couldn't be another
job where I could
Bloom this much the you know with a job
where I can use all my skills and be
free relatively
and
just
just yeah
fully use my talents and skills and
interests
in a in a very comfortable surrounding
AKA my home
like there is not really any any better
choice
in terms of job genre
um
so hell yeah
I'll continue it
for as long as I can thank you
panopticon
116710 Snoop Dogg DD thank you for the
rest of the chat in German oh let's go
to some drifting yeah
[Music]
respect love you
and yeah
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this whole time when I was like only
side eyeing
your profile picture I thought it was a
hair iron now I get a closer look at
it's a skeleton of some dinosaur or
something
I thought it was a hair iron
and I was like why does this guy have a
hair iron as their picture
so Random
happy anniversary
weeks ago when I was going for Hard
Times how are times watching you was the
only way I could Escape those feelings
oh really
thank you I'm glad thanks to you and kfb
whenever I'm feeling anxious and lonely
I know that there's a place I can go
where I feel safe and welcome
you'll always be my Oshi and I'll
support you until my last breath wow we
love you Wawa until
already
so your icon a skeleton are you even
breathing
maybe you should check that get that
checked out
there's not much skin and meat on you
left
[Music]
ah but thank you I'm I'm so happy I can
help you it's always crazy hearing what
effect I have on people and I'm glad
this is my place but it's also your
place it's our place kfp is for us
[Music]
um
so
thank you so much I love you too wait
wait a [\h__\h] second that was a 500 I
didn't even see that
five
hundred
are you okay
are you okay Dante
Dante are you okay
are you okay
be careful Dante
there won't be much left over to check
out that condition of lacking skin and
meat at the doctor anymore
if you spend so much on my
streams
[Laughter]
let me know if you if you need to borrow
some money
thank you so much holy moly that is a
lot of a lot of cutting thank you so
much for the support that's insane
um
wow
crazy crazy crazy crazy you know what's
your favorite little Pinky
happy 30th Anniversary I was around for
more than two years but that was a
hardcore looker whoa hardcore so
hardcore you were actually the one who
dragged me out with your friendly and
kind and find personality
thanks for all the laughs you gave us
you're truly the best boss ah
I'm so glad yeah cause like there were
always so many lurkers I'm like why
don't you just say something
say something I'm giving up on you
any lurkos here right now then say say
say say something
don't lurk
oh
hey some of you are not lurkers
how dare you take that special Spotlight
away from my lurkers
lurking egg
hi lurkers thank you for chilling and
hanging out here feel free to type in
the chat every now and then more often
foreign
I have a DM oh I didn't
oh my God I think huawa might be real
because she she answered me
I think she's real
hey yo
nonsense
what'd you guys think she was just a
reflection of mokoko or what
oh
Bubba Sim
[Music]
yeah I can assure you both are very real
where are we Diego
genoves or genoves
again what could it be
[Music]
both are you here both but if even you
say it then I guess you don't mind
thank you for the rest of the chat oh
boy
oh my God oh my God maybe also both
very very
what's the word I forgot ah
first time
happy for years kiwawa from day one for
every new face you remain my absolute
all
the arrow hits me
help
though I'm often silent in chat no I've
been here from Star cheering watching
and always supporting oh man
I look forward for more precious moments
of you and all on this Cafe oh man
oh man are you Cupid because you shot me
right in the heart
is broken
thank you I'm glad you don't have to
lurk so much show yourself you sweet
potato
how can you be so sweet and not share
that kindness with me more often in the
chat
I demand
you to unlock yourself
at least sometimes
thank you
For Your Love mwah
love you forever my cute thank you happy
birthday debut anniversary
yay
it's our anniversary too happy
anniversary I didn't forget about your
anniversary with me
since day one well then it's definitely
I was just gonna say maybe it's not
exactly our third anniversary of what
apparently it is
thank you thank you thank you wow three
years man that's honestly that's such a
long time to spend with people
right
[Music]
it's like where besties
sorry I downgraded you did I just friend
zone you guys because first I said it's
like we're married now I say we're like
Besties
[Music]
yeah for questions
ouch
I know my best friend for 24 years holy
wow
I
know my best friend not that long
by far not that long
but
um
what was I gonna say I know but
feather you want to be fooled
you're too good to be food ahead
I don't think I have a best friend are
you sure
are you sure
[Music]
don't do you not prefer one friend over
the other
think of everybody equally maybe you
have more than one best friend it's okay
to have more than one best friend
um
[Music]
eat with our friends
oh she friend
your friends
not not one with which I'm very very
close
um
it's
it definitely helps to have someone that
you're really really close with so I
hope you can find someone or get closer
to one of the existing ones
[Music]
Comey friend
or she friend don't Oshie friend change
me
17 years wow probably my cat
you know how much of a cat person I am
but I would never say that my cats are
my best friends
because my cats are my babies but
[Music]
your cats cannot count as your best
friend I know about dogs I know people
always say a dog is a human's best
friend and all that and they definitely
have best friend potential but I don't
know if if I think I need to have a dog
to be able to say if I would with my
full sanity consider a dog my best
friend
hmm
and not just my baby
I don't know about that there's
definitely like potential
but is it reasonable to say such a thing
to seriously
previously not jokingly consider your
dog your best friend
my cat is my best like like a friend she
mostly ignores me and only shows up for
food wait yeah no that's not like a
friend
oh
that's just a child I think actually
really children are a good equivalent
for
cats
cause like
maybe not in every family but I think in
a lot of family especially the the
puberty kids
they will ignore your view AKA parent
and just
when there's like four you're like okay
and you take your food and maybe you
don't even eat it together maybe you
just eat it in your own room so that's
um yeah
cats are teenagers
thinking they don't need their parents
but still rely on them and take all
their resources and food and money
but act like they could totally survive
without them and are independent wow
oh
[Music]
ah they are polish it they are such
teenagers
but I handle my cats very well does that
mean I could handle teenagers very well
um
yeah I would I would probably spoil my
kids huh
if I had kids
I would probably spoil them
would I and I would go insane I would
probably go insane
nah nah
you handle Kobo very well
that is true
I didn't spawn Club yeah I didn't buy
her anything yet
[Laughter]
and I still got
her love
uh funny now thank you Dusty
[Music]
for the rest of the child happy third
anniversary and time flies by when
you're having fun I'm looking forward to
many many more years of your
entertaining streams great songs and
fantastic performances thank you I'll do
my best I'll try to keep it up
I'll I'll try to continue
entertaining you
and hopefully make you proud thank you
so much
for the support wow
okay it's been four hours
my face is starting to hurt
don't know why
I think the screen is like tiring me out
and the talking
I want to do a bit more though
what are we doing at tomorrow's Friday
the day that I kind of kept open right
like if depending on what I how what I
feel like
[Music]
oh you guys thought I would take today
off right because of how much I sang
Yesterday
but I recovered
decently
yeah I'm surprised I still had a voice
honestly
um
I was surprised too
I'm very surprised
yeah I might take it off
I mean the day
[Music]
0.99 tomorrow how much screaming
compared true that's the one thing that
you know I love Hotline Miami it's so
much fun but the one thing that bothers
me about it is that I cannot stop myself
from
screaming so much and it hurts my throat
and it uses a lot of energy it's just
always like
ugh
ugh you know
no it's not every game I play Hotline
Miami is especially bad at this
yeah my adrenaline
um
I'll see I mean I think it's good for my
channel also to like not spam everything
something you know
um
I'll think about it hey
you would be a riot to startle as a
friend with how much you scream all the
time
my friends never startled me though they
don't try and they also don't
accidentally do it though I can I think
in real life I struggle less
maybe because I'm more aware of my
surroundings I don't know
it's just not much going on I guess
yeah
no I'm not jumping IRL
but maybe I'm just not giving I'm not
given enough reasons to be jumpy
hmm
yeah I'm pretty chill
I would say around I like save a lot of
my energy like it's not like I'm faking
anything but I think I save a lot of my
energy for the moments where I really
need it
um
however when I meet Holo members for
example IRL I that's also a moment where
I try to let my energy out
I get energetic at those times unless
it's like someone like Cali for example
with Cali I'm just calm and chill
hmm we talk a lot though
and Kelly
never mind we're together IRL but we're
calm still like
like you know we chill we just hang we
just hang
so yeah I'm I'm more on the calm side
with my friends too
need to preserve energy I am old
and you're cool you're cool thank you
for the pinky that question cute emojis
cute cute I wish I could add more power
Gundam thank you for the red super chat
wow three years of ten to already three
years since I found a certain oh you too
you're the second one who's mentioning
Mario Kart wow
it's three years since I found a certain
Mario Kart clip and fell down the
objectively best Rabbit Hole the
internet has to offer and how lucky I
was to somehow exist in the timeline
where all this happens yeah okay if it's
truly blessed love you Mama love you too
thank you
buy a card seems to have gotten a lot of
like early kfps
um
yeah the banana clip
[Laughter]
[Music]
Mario Kart was always fun
yeah
yeah that one showed my my fun crazy
side and then there was the other clip
that got a lot of people that was that
showed my emotionals
sweet side
[Music]
the Super Chat one
the sim Sims Club where I told Iris to
light the Christmas tree oh I don't even
remember that
spending two hours
four levels [\h__\h] that
Sue that level
oh
um
thinking about it
gives me migraines
does somebody trash can
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
that's also like one of my favorite
legendary moments
but I don't like what it implies
I'm not that heavy
her trash can thing was [\h__\h] you can't
even call that a trash can
it's just a trash
Clipper because it Clips the
bag onto its
whatever it's not a container
it's only like 10 percent of a container
it's weak it's plastic it's weak
it's not stable
[\h__\h] it's trash it's really trash
I'm hungry
why'd you sit up so why did you sit
because she offered
and barely had
it
[Laughter]
she had one chair and that was her PC
chair
she had not a single other chair
hmm
that was my designated chair
set on Subaru
oh man
the question would have done but then I
would have sat really low on the floor
and couldn't have really seen anything
yeah yeah yeah I I I I went to uh off
collab with her again right this year
and I was sitting on a chair
a
proper I think it was a property I don't
remember anymore
I did say yeah true
character development no trash can
development
anyway thank you so much Sarah
I'm happy you fell into the rabbit hole
the the Phoenix hole
glad you're here
fantastic dungeon ateza29 thanks for the
pinky happy anniversary kiwawa you
became my ocean after watching you on
third Hall of Fest oh
and I've loved my time here with you and
kfp I know I'm not always around due to
work but I'm always supporting you
congrats on your album I can't wait to
hear more music thank you
so I mean
somewhat reason
huh
nice
so
wait before that you had a different
Ocean or what
and you watched Food Fest and it made
you think damn this girl
how could I how could ignore her until
now
is that what happened
[Music]
because
I know fruit Fest is like you have to
pay to watch it so you must have already
been in the whole life rabbit hole
at least
but it seems like you're not here to
give me a live answer that's okay
thank you so much for
yeah finding me and then deciding to
support me I'm really really really glad
thank you
oh my God
very nice incredible views happy third
anniversary oh this must have been
during the paragliding
yeah I
was quite something
I I
overcame one of like you know normally I
don't really like to do crazy stuff like
that
that was like my limit anyway because I
don't think I would ever want to do
bungee jumping or anything like that
this was for me
um overcoming like a certain
limit of what I accept to do
without like
pushing myself to do something that
freaks me out so much that I want to die
yeah yeah I'm not a frill Seeker mm-hmm
I
I am I'm I'm I'm planning you
entertained with the simple things in
life
AKA food and Netflix
yeah I hate roller coasters
I hate them
I mean I still go on them always in the
hopes that I would enjoy them
and I I only enjoy them when they're
like baby level
yeah
I just don't like the feeling in my
stomach at all and it just terrifies me
all the time
lucky we had amazing weather yeah it was
generally good weather around the time
always
oh
you never rolled one oh my God
climb Mount Fuji next year
hole climbing a mountain could be yeah I
could do that maybe
could be a mission a challenge
yeah
but not too high
have to do a lot of cutting though
probably
there's not much
probably same content a lot
yeah hello our hello welcome I'm
probably not gonna do much longer but
welcome
[Music]
considered an Enthusiast oh
mountain climbing needs a lot of
preparation including physical yeah yeah
I don't I don't underestimate it don't
worry
approach starting to yeah my throat
hurts you know I can say that my throat
and my face hurts
so anyway thank you senior you're the
best thank you wow oh membership gift
sweet
Ness
cute name thanks for the pinky the
challenge videos were a lot of fun happy
anniversary yeah thank you for watching
now I'm so glad that you enjoyed them
because I put a lot of lot of time and
effort into it
thank you so much
[Music]
Brooke 6 000. for the pinky these videos
are amazing great job thank you and
editor's Son yes
yeah the editing Top Notch even though
there was so little time I am so happy
with it
like I didn't even ask for having the
hand when I reach out for something in
3D I didn't ask for that sheesh
that's like
extra efforts nobody asked for it but it
it made the video so much greater I saw
you guys reacting like oh my God can't
believe it immersion is there
everything was so smooth I like to over
complicate my life
uh it was so good everything's so good
did you see a little detail that was my
idea though but did you see the detail
when I took off
uh at the park lighting video when it
took off
I asked calcare to add a detail that my
hats would fly off
he did that too but not it's kind of
difficult to see because they're really
tiny but I saw you guys noticing
not so many people noticed in the live
version but a lot of you guys probably
noticed at least afterwards
mm-hmm
[Music]
when I was watching my footage after I
took it I was like really surprised by
how much my screams were echoing through
the mountains even when I was really far
away
I was genuinely terrified the moment I
took off man
[Applause]
I was terrified
I was embarrassed for screaming so much
but I couldn't hold back
the hills are alive of the streams of
wow
the running in the air after you took
off was funny no but she told me to do
that she she said
um because there might be times
where you
like
I kind of want to draw this but like
where you start taking off but then you
like bounce back onto the ground you
know
so just in case you need to continue
running until she tells you to stop
running
um
yeah in case you take off a little bit
and then lower again and then up and
lower because I guess sometimes that
happens
I know it looked like the dog paddling
moment
yeah that was great it was fun what an
experience man
so thank you Brock and I'll see thank
you for the rest of the chat thank you
that trip to the Austrian Wilderness was
amazing your bravery is outstanding as
expected of lady takanashi
thank you so much hey I'm glad you
enjoyed that which which Vlog did you
guys enjoy it more in terms of content
the paragliding or the
the camping because the camping is like
was ended up being quite
like mostly a joke
[Laughter]
yeah you like that one it was really
funny the paragliding was like really
nice to see I think because I challenged
myself and it showed a really beautiful
um scenery
okay
actually I see everything now
I with the camping one I felt a bit more
comfortable like talking and vlogging
uh because well I was most it was alone
or my mom was there
yeah so you know for the paragliding I
still felt a bit embarrassed because I
mean I told them
I told them you know that I'm making
Vlog and all that and they were very
like understanding of it they had no
issue with it they didn't think it was
weird or anything people have done it
before when they went paragliding there
they told me
um but it still makes me feel awkward to
Vlog in front of people who I don't know
and they don't know me
um
so I felt a bit Yeah weird about that
the forest water stream
yeah yeah
I asked my mom if she has anything that
I can
you know any any natural water stream
but
you know I just wanted at that point I
was already fine with the whole video
being more of a joke than anything else
so I just asked for a tap like an
outside tap
and then she just used the the hose the
garden hose
[Music]
my pants
and everything I was my my gloves were
absolutely soaked
after that incident she purposefully
sprayed a lot of water on me
yeah I was attacked by the water wobbly
aggressive water
[Music]
no no it was natural River excuse me I
misspoke
any way to do more camping in the future
yeah my brother also actually asked me
we can go camping together I'm like yeah
yeah and my best friend too
um
but I don't know
I think oh Autumn is still fine for
camping right but I don't know if I have
time really anyway thank you
Pebble leadership
thank you
[Music]
they did
[Laughter]
thank you for the pinky dear tanaki
Shakira Shakira
I just wanted to say that for those
three years you have been a shiny bacon
I say bacon in my life
bacon I really appreciate your work the
effort to always be entertaining you're
the best dancer we could possibly have
oh
thank you
I'm Tana Tana
Kira Shakira yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
Shakira
Autumn is great for camping
sounds fun
[Music]
thank you
my shy night thank you soon I am glad to
be your bacon for four years I hope you
don't cook me into your breakfast
keep me
keep me keep me forever
even when I get moldy
thank you Kiana fried Pebble thank you
for the recipe
for the year anniversary I've been here
since the beginning and I love you so
much
thank you for all the hard work you've
done POV is amazing and my new favorite
is the great Wanderer I'm streaming the
album for many hours every day really
oh
perfect example of uh
perfect employee of kfp
it's just a single pebble
streaming my album
hours and hours on end
thank you I really appreciate it when
you think you think you think you
everybody don't forget about streaming
POV please thank you so much
Pebble with huge Ambitions yeah
you have that name even before Bijou
debuted right so this doesn't like we
didn't like change it right this was
your name before was it was it
are you here
[Music]
is my Pebble here
no pebble
no Pebble right now no Pebble maybe you
can tell me at some point
I am cave pebble
eh
you're not the same person right
ah
see I think I thought when I first saw
your name though that I was like um
this name seems fresh to me
but your icon says you've been around
for a long time now you're rainbow why
do you change your name like this do you
not want to be remembered by me do you
want me to forget about you like who who
are which which identities are all your
identities don't you think that like
maybe I'm like
like I remember you as one name and then
you you change your name and I'm like
where the [\h__\h] did that person go
where did he go did he lose interest in
me
don't change your name I have too many
which ones name them name your names now
so I know that they're all you
and I don't have to worry about
them disappearing
I'm waiting
I'm Christy shaver
and
are you hiding any more of those names
in your pockets
[Music]
what about your
your pants Pockets your inner pockets of
your jacket where are they just let them
all out
um
empty the pockets
hands up in the air
get on the ground
no I'll stay over okay you stay rainbow
for me okay no changing names no more
you are putting me through a mental
roller coaster if you change your name
in a way that I wouldn't recognize it
like if you change your name and you
keep the same profile picture I still
recognize you
but not like this
actually I see uh your profile picture
is broken anyway like I can't even see
it
anyway thank you if that's really you
thank you thank you thank you
for the support
keep on streaming POV
I am a team
um
thank you for the pinky nice testicles
ma'am XXX what
I come here come here
smacked you
[Music]
how's that sound
I wanted to have it half a slapping
sound but it didn't sound like a slap
[Music]
like a bonk um
I came with the shot clock
Turtle cubes language
four for One Direction
dios Mayo
welcome
[Music]
[Laughter]
don't say that to me
happy first anniversary thank you for
being such an inspiration to us all free
space for boys first oh
[Music]
I don't have time for it
thank you though thank you for thinking
of my
urges
thank you very sweet of you
um so thoughtful but for Jim King who is
already got so many wonderful messages
thank you I mean yeah that's very very
sweet wait even those freeze free snack
and
get ready to get set and go go to where
am I going
wait it's a rainbow
go okay I'll go
kind of lean that really quickly
[Music]
foreign
wow
I just went straight to the one cat that
I know
where she will be
still under the clothing hamper
she was so happy to see me I swear
she went like
and then she flopped over to the side
and let me
like take in all her fluffiness
and she still smelled so
good
ah
the one that couldn't save herself on
time it's not about saving themselves no
no I was just happy to be cuddled and I
was happy too
a moment of bliss
[Music]
thank you
that made me very happy mwah Slavic
fellow thank you you're the best
blind spell thank you soon Captain jerk
pants thank you for the pinky happy
third anniversary to my Kami OSI when I
came across her life I was in a very bad
place mentally and emotionally started
with clips and then came across you it's
been over two years since I became a
full-time campaign I'm not leaving ever
[Music]
oh
he's so much I love the determination I
can feel it I can sense it
I'm honored to have you
forever hopefully thank you soon I hope
you feel overall better these days than
back then
and even on there sometimes where you
feel low and down again I'm sure
you will get back on track you can do it
um
yes you can
I believe in you
foreign
[Music]
happy for your anniversary it's been
amazing for years thank you
love you love you too
also be some Diet eating spicy noodles
yeah um spicy noodles can I just say
something
I would say I played it up about five
percent
five percent only five percent
they were
like not enjoyable to eat
and
definitely the more time passed the more
latest everything was like tingling
uncomfortably
I tried and it's actually spicy it is
spicy if you don't trust me try it but
yeah
what I noticed that it wasn't so bad so
I was like
oh it
but I guess I mean I wouldn't eat it on
my own I would never choose to eat that
um
no it didn't taste like carbonara no no
not at all
I tried the black bulldog and it wasn't
really bad and no then you have high
tolerance because I heard the black
Bulldog is definitely very spicy
yeah
should have gone for the really spicy
ones well I didn't know really like what
how spicy each of them really are I just
knew I I don't think I would be able to
take the the most spicy ones
so I wasn't sure like what was a good
level for me
um I could have probably gone up one
more level
but then yeah
this was like manageable but painful
sufficiently suffering
basically
which was good for the challenge I would
say yeah maybe next year we can try
again with like one or two levels higher
maybe maybe
oh she flopped over she's asking for
cuddles
[Music]
I think I've been I think
she does this she knows I'm still
streaming
when she comes to my room to say hi at
times like this it's always after she
just went to the toilet
laughs
that was smooth van
[Music]
plants just like
nibbling on a box
hey hey
[Applause]
yeah she's doing it on purpose now it's
like after toilet she's like ah what do
I do now walks around finds me it's like
all right let's get my
she has like a routine you know
she has a routine
there's a pattern in her behavior
darn teenagers exactly
she must announce she has done yeah
the one without me having to wipe her
but
that's I mean expected of a teenager
though
anyway thank you Miyako
thank you thank you thank you thank you
for supporting me with my spicy noodle
challenge too
I
I think at least like
next time I'm in like Korea or so for
example I'll try some of the spicy
dishes Maybe
just because there's not much else to
eat
and yeah I'll try maybe they're not
so
difficult to eat
but it's just like
not that fun to consume you know Korean
Fried Chicken is damn good and me and
Navi we had Korean fried chicken I
remember us sitting together
eating Korean fried chicken that was a
lot
was there that much spicy food
ingredient I feel like everything was
like that we thought about like Nabi had
issues finding non-spicy food for me
basically
hmm
I know so many places without spicy food
really
pong tell me next time tell me tell me
tell me tell me
tell me where is the non-spicy food I
need some good food tell me Well you
made a map for me oh my God you're so
sweet
a food map all right that's that will
come in handy next time
tell me
[Music]
oh
okay I want to try to book it actually
you know what I I I I I
have an idea
there was this like Korean restaurant
that my Korean teacher recommended to me
and I still didn't go to it but I told
my bestie that we should go there uh
sometime
and it's like a it's like a buffet
all you can eat I think it was
um so there the good thing is it's
genius because I can only because it's a
all you can eat buffet I can like take
only little little bits and pieces from
each dish try everything
I don't have to order one big dish and
then leave it because I didn't like it
or so
yeah they surely have topoki I have to
try it
and everything else I can sample perfect
so I was planning to do that
make myself a sample platter and find
out what I really like
um I should do that soon soon oh
thank you
sorry ah
whoa
did you hear that
ouch
did you not hear it
oh I laid I laid my phone on my XLR
cable
and it
barked like it felt in my headphones
like a spark sparking zappy sound yeah
I didn't hear it oh wow
[Music]
no oh
pull
[Music]
okay
I'll try everything they probably have
all of that
no get XLR doesn't mean XLR the
microphones need an XLR cable
yo audio Noobs
the cables that connect the microphones
are called XLR cables
probably one of the reasons why they
named It Go XLR because you connected
also with an XLR cable
all right I'm hearing something weird
I guess you guys you guys don't hear it
huh
what if I put the phone on my on the
cable again
it really spy put the phone on the cable
but now the weird sound is gone that I
heard
you heard that right okay
uh yeah the I had I heard like a
buzzing sound
now it's just a normal buzzing sound
yay okay
yeah the bus is just always there I
still have to try that uh yeah I want to
borrow my friend's microphone to see if
I still have the uh buzzing with with
her microphone because I already tried
everything else
I tried a different power outlet I tried
the XLR cable changing I tried the whole
mixer changing
[Music]
um
tried a lot of different things
same shirt yeah she has the same so
should be a good comparison
yes I changed the XLR cable yeah you
don't know about it but I did
and UPS what was that
whatever let me raise up a chance
um
the green bikini looking like not even
love this hey happy three years
anniversary and looking forward to for
more QR in the future thank you I am
looking forward to more quinoa in the
future too what will she bring what will
she look like what will she say what
will she sing
hmm we will see but only if you stay
with Wawa
thank you for the support no no no Nami
tangent she's cute but she ignored me
she hates me
non-square pixels
thank you soon thank you triple tripod
tripod tripod
[Music]
Kiana fried Pebble thank you for the
recipe you can stop eating the spicy
noodles great job Kayla I don't wanna I
don't want you to suffer anymore thank
you you're so sweet you're so kind
thank you
yeah I
yeah yeah people told me that it might
be because of that but um I don't know
she could still just answer and say
thank you no I don't know so she hates
me
anyway thank you thank you thank you for
the support
and
I should try the the least spicy version
maybe I could really enjoy it because
the flavor generally wasn't bad
this is how kfb sounds when Kiana
doesn't like their comments
um guys yesterday I liked like literally
everything but let me just tell you one
thing if you want kiwawa likes
I normally don't like anything that's
just like one line sentence or so
I generally just like things that are
like a paragraph you know
because then you put an effort into uh
the reply to me
if it's like a at least like a free line
paragraph
your chances are high very high
very high
to get a like it's that easy
only full five paragraph essays get
graded yeah but even the non-paragraphs
I still read them you know
I still read them
I just don't feel like liking them
sometimes
I always take 10 minutes damn
now don't Lord me the text of the
[Music]
[Laughter]
where are you listening guys did you
catch it
the Lord read a text
[Music]
speaker moment
ah good one good one
oh man today's first day that means it's
almost Friday so past midnight I
episode from The Wheel of Time
I was waiting so long for Friday ah
I'm really really really curious right
about it it's it's not like there's
anywhere the full season already out
right I have to wait a week on Amazon
Prime each each time right I have to
thank God it's almost Friday yay yeah
also a2k last episode but I don't
I don't even wanna
I don't want to see the moment when
Christina gets eliminated you know it's
just
nah
[\h__\h] that
wait we love time is on Amazon Prime
yeah yeah
[Laughter]
when it first night of September hey
[Music]
yeah we are done trying to hide the
thing
[Music]
Christina Manzanita
do you remember
the 21st night of December when you were
watching the wow we're reading super
change
too
hey
I've been thinking about the 21st night
of September man
I'm so close to the end can I do it
I shall do it even though I'm I don't
wanna anymore but I'll do it I'll finish
this I'll finish this mofo
[Music]
's elimination
yes
no tensions allowed I don't know
well you get another kiss I think you
are afraid
at least there's not so many Reds and
things anymore golden
um
ah thank you man space wonderful thank
you
[Music]
I hate tomato juice
is a fried egg good addition to any
instant
fried noodles the instant noodles yeah
Ice Cream Sandwich I love ice cream
sandwich
thanks for the pinky
oh yeah there was a second page but it's
not so much right yeah thank God the
challenge videos are so good the scenery
is amazing I'd love to visit those two
Lakes at least once there's actually a
third one if you remember the the map
from the beginning that I showed
uh there's like it's like free Lakes
kind of like right next to each other
and they're all all beautiful great
editing two I couldn't stop smiling the
spicy noodle dough as a fellow no spicy
guy it pains me to hear yourself oh
thank you but about the about anybody
who felt like the scenery was beautiful
let me tell you that sooner that area is
apparently the most popular for
paragliding in Austria anyway I didn't
even really know that but I just assumed
it would be a great place to paraglide
also because it's familiar to me
um and uh the lakes are beautiful it's
like a really well-known area in Austria
because it's just a you know a really
really chill pretty area everybody goes
to the lakes for swimming mm-hmm
so if you happen to be in Austria at
some point I recommend you checking
those Lakes out if you want to go swim
swim in the in the summer
a little bit refreshment
I mean we surely have many similar
places in Austria like that
but I think that that area specifically
it's just the best hack
and astrotactical danger and Cloud
Invader Duncan I'll go
I'll go ah thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you
and nothing to read for me marvelous
you are a gift from Heaven thank you
thank you soon
thanks chief chief oh she sheesh chief
thank you soon thank you so much
[Music]
everyone five free garlics thank you for
the pinky happy fourth anniversary yeah
you are truly a legendary YouTuber you
think so
surreal to think of myself as
you know like an outsider like a non-me
non-me person an outsider of my body
yeah
[Music]
biggest pizza in Europe
well I'm proud of myself
thank you for making me who I am today
guys
Flappy boy thank you for the recipe
this time you really went all out to
bring us unwary for Champions as crazy
as bang over shell hey hey you're
welcome I wanted you guys to have
something special
um even after three years of nearly near
uninterrupted content correct creation
you still have so much fire and creative
potential inside of you to keep reaching
New Heights
I I'm glad you enjoyed it so much made
it really worth it I'm I was so happy
with the feedback
thank you everybody
I saw many of you in my mom's Garden
there were so many Flappy boys
Flappy boys like you and also other
Flappy boys like and there were lots of
bees many bees
fascinating beasts zombies I've never
seen before
um
many Flappy boys many slugs too yeah
[\h__\h] them
must bear thank you for the pinky away
Flappy boy now Mama's bear
and it comes Anita
wow wow third anniversary
congratulations
changed me a lot one day I'll be the
person who makes people smile just like
you thanks for your passion you already
make me smile right now you do
um I am smiling at this very moment oh
[Music]
oh
okay I gave you accident kiss
ah
freebie
discounted two two
[Music]
hope you're happy
you deserve it thank you
midnight reader oh friend size or fun
season live
taxable another one you
as many and incredible as your
achievements have been this year you'll
find a way to tap all of that and we'll
celebrate you for it on your fourth
anniversary don't
don't raise the bar like that let's go
for one more year of labs tears Wows and
Smit of Madness
thank you too
the bar has been raised
but yeah I really liked making this kind
of content so
maybe next year I can do it but with the
support of cover because like they have
done this kind of content before as well
right for anniversary or birthday I'm
not sure what it was but they have done
it before so maybe I can do something
like that in Japan
with their editing and all that
um yeah
do something special in Japan
maybe especially for something like a
climbing Mount Fuji hmm
[Music]
and
oh I could do like maybe like
um
other experiences should only work in
Japan I don't know like
learn how to make oh I want to do oh I
want to do I already had this idea with
like other restaurants in general just
but I want to do like a day in a
restaurant like you know working there
as a Apprentice or trainee or whatever
so I could do it like in a Ramen Shop
maybe in a small Ramen Shop with
coverage help I think it would be easy
to get like permission and get into that
and then I can do my my cap camera again
that point of view and just wear the
gloves and you can see I think that
works really well do you know those
short videos like YouTube shorts and I
guess tick tocks maybe probably too
where this like these people like
usually like McDonald's or Burger King
whatever they make their orders like
they have the camera like a GoPro or
whatever on their head yeah or Subway
yeah there's like several of them and
it's just like really like nice to see
them put together the order is really
professionally routined
um
so with a POV like that me learning how
to make ramen or sushi or something I
don't know
from a professional uh cook
that's one thing I would like to do yeah
yeah
possibly before restaurant opening hours
who doesn't like sushi I guess that's
okay
aggressive Supply doesn't like sushi I
guess that's okay
the flow
I love that song
oh really it's funny yeah I haven't
heard it in a while
uh what was it oh yeah thank you
hi also watching over me while I was
making the Vlog you were everywhere
around me
David is cute action golden boomy thank
you for the pinky once again happy third
anniversary thank you thank you thank
you thank you
thank you soon thank you for being part
of kfp I hope we can also celebrate
together and anniversary
Unwritten direction
thank you foreign
or just got in did you have any
Daydreams about collabing of your future
senpas did any of those Daydreams come
true
um
I think I definitely had a lot of
moments where I just like
talk to myself
uh
in in like like kind of like acting out
things I would say on stream
as if I was streaming
um yeah but Daydream is about collabing
with someone I probably did I can't
really remember but I probably probably
did
like maybe not full-on Daydreams but
definitely like
you know hopes and dreams
thoughts
yeah you think that's normal really yeah
I did dream of suicide
hmm
actually sometimes I won't even say that
because you guys freak out again
thank you thank you thank you thank you
I thought you were gonna go on like you
know this whole thing where you put all
my album songs into your super chats but
you didn't
so was it not even on purpose
I wonder Tobias
uh space wonderful things to the pinky
happy for your anniversary this was a
cute amazing spicy and hype stream these
four years were were great fans since
day one as you might know so many
memories I look back fondly to the
moments with you and kfb love you love
you
love you
day one KF people
absolute MVP
Seas
MB chickens
I'm not traveling
the other people did it too though
Day Zero chickens you mean like since
the Twitter days
are there some people who would say that
or claim that they already felt like I
was their Oshi before my debut stream
like
during the Twitter days yes
took you about a week
you hate me
yes we forget the artist a little I'm
sure some people will claim them
two weeks
seems weird I choose the Phoenix
I am Timeless
I am timeless
I am I am
I am indeed timeless
spider when you put a pinky and thanks
for all the fun time Santa thank you oh
my God what a cute spiders are the
Christmas hat a Santa hat
oh it definitely is
that makes you a little bit more
bearable
thank you thank you for being around
when I need you
first and thanks
for the big three oh my God calm your
titties
time really flies when you're having
we're having a good time so proud of all
you've accomplished and I don't take a
single day we have together for granted
my neighbor love you Wawa and hopefully
we'll all continue celebrating more and
more anniversaries hopefully yeah
I hope so too very much thank you so
much WoW
why are you saying that so much I don't
know it just came back to me
I don't know
and it was in me before but I just
didn't come out much
we'll get to that five year mark I hope
so it would be nice would be would be
great if we can go that long
yeah
oh my God wait
that's what you meant with free free in
one super chat I was like where's the
rest of them
there's only one
you crazy
that's absurd
thank you sir for your insane support
and your love and your dedication
so happy
happy to have you as part of kfp yeah
let's do more fun stuff together okay
I'll be around I just need you to be
there too
chat
[Music]
you don't even see that anymore
this is the end of the page
and happy first anniversary thank you
your true inspiration to us oh hi I'm
here by the way uh
I wish that Your Flames will burn
brightly forever yay
uh I hope so too
I hope so too thank you thank you ah I'm
glad I can inspire you
what am I inspiring YouTube
whatever it is
I hope you can achieve what you're
dreaming of
much love to you mwah
imagination
mode
TDP thank you for the pinky thanks for
an absolutely wonderful stream happy for
years it makes me happy to see you
thrive this year all the performances
streams and the special of the album
keep on soaring yeah let's go don't stop
don't stop just go the wow away
oh
thank you soon
for following my journey it's been a
blast this year hey
cow can reduction for your help are you
the best thank you for letting me do
this job
before thank you for suffering through
my orders Robin Hood face of the pinky
thank you for free amazing wonderful
life-changing years it's been amazing
watching you grow experiment in flourish
love you always Kiana careful forever
yes careful oh
thank you
hopefully we can last very very long
I still want to see us
collab with KFC
or Burger King or McDonald's or Wendy's
or
scissors
or any of those really
that would be so dope
why not see this just because
anything
anything any food restaurant
[Music]
I'm switching a page now guys let's go
let's go oh
JD Duncan r9000 thank you
sit please
reserved for wholesome congratulatory
message in the future aha you mean
you're gonna send another one like later
when I'm done with these super chats
that is also a way to go
thank you I'm waiting for the message
I'm almost done
thanks for the pinky happy oh actually
two Piggies happy third anniversary
here's so many more I love these Vlogs
they're so funny I would love to see
more
let's see those two and God bless you oh
also have a friend who would love to see
if you could use your pacifier with your
blouse off oh I did yesterday you know
for science maybe zoom in a little bit
[Music]
you're a little [\h__\h]
every time she goes behind the
supercharge I don't know where Bob was
that why are you satisfied by yesterday
[Music]
you better
say yes
it was glorious
ah
he's chickens I can't take him anymore
oh hi I can be here too
[Music]
yeah it's an archives I gotta do it no
don't worry I'll rebroadcast it yeah
yeah I'm looking forward to artwork I
just want people to draw me in the
swimsuit not necessarily with the
pacifier no thank you
most of kfb is down bad too the same
well yeah yeah he's like the scapegoat
for all of your horniness guys say thank
you to navida Medi
[Music]
there's old
whoa
do you think he grew out of his interest
for me is he too old for me now does he
maybe think like I'm too old for this
[\h__\h]
what do you think
am I not cool enough anymore
[Music]
could be
what do you mean is an island baby now
did you see him in the Advent dreams
the hell
that would be Unforgivable
it's my baby
baby is gone
and they were two babies
they were
two babies at kfb and both babies are
gone
where did my dead baby go
where did
they call it
what a question
I got
[Music]
so cool now I am the crying baby
it was all just a plot for me to become
the crying baby
I miss you baby
I miss you
anyway thank you
um
[Music]
part of me was doubting if I could read
it all today but I did
didn't
yummy hey
nice
my mouth hurts I
hope
[Music]
oh
look into my eyes guys
look into them
I love you
now that we had that
clarified
thank you for watching today
I'm probably gonna cook some food now
or after I take a little break
then I'm gonna watch
A Wheel of Time
possibly finale of that stupid idle
Survival show that is biased as [\h__\h]
and yeah Twin Falls cute right
and yeah uh tomorrow I guess I'll take
the date
sorry I'm unreliable
but the marathon
I I expect that to take a while but I
didn't expect it to be that long and and
then and then take that lunch
energy
I mean I'm fine but yeah
yeah
[Music]
because I didn't really have a day off
this week
turns out
I've gotta work deadline oh good luck
with that say no more take all the time
you need you guys are so sweet
you schedule things
yeah
thank you you should take two days off
that's what I was telling myself but
then again and again I just feel bad
especially because I'm going to Japan
very soon so I thought
um maximum one day off because
I don't know how much I will actually
really stream
but I'll definitely stream here and
there probably you know the Aki Senpai
one will be on akisenberg's channel the
annoyed one
I'm not sure on which channel that will
be mine or hers I'm not sure what we're
intending
but those two things are definitely
happening
um
I want to organize uh ID
of collab
I'll definitely do at least one or two
solo streams hopefully
but once I arrive I also also have to go
to dance lessons
um
that will be fun though I think
yay yay
for the first couple of days
first couple days I'll be
dancing dancing dancing dancing
[Music]
and the last couple days of the trip
I'll be
at a wedding so I won't stream for those
I will I will upload some videos yeah
I'll see what I can prepare
hmm
dance dance
Twitter spaces
yeah I could even do Twitter space maybe
while I'm like not at the wedding but
like
around the wedding
ah dance dance dance with my hands yeah
the anniversary doesn't but I'm already
planning to put them up here and there
and also there will be a love rash
um
simple music video really simple
mm-hmm
so yeah we got some things and then I I
still have like a few cheggy videos that
I could put up
okay
oh you brought this
but it's a big six hours that will take
a while to download from for for me from
YouTube
[Music]
rebroadcast
what are you going to do for Memo's
anniversary
what day is it
[Music]
Ah that's really bad
that's that's sad I'm not streaming on
the 27th
we'll have to move that
we'll have to move our anniversary
[Music]
to after the trip
she hates us
hmm
yeah sorry sorry
that is unfortunate timing
Mama thank you thank you
yeah okay
just after the badge
okay
[Music]
I have to make a decision
ah
I probably forget about it
and then I'll just update it when I'm
actually doing the anniversary stream
it's not like you will fade to exist
just because I didn't add a new badge
oh hello
timing
now you will not fail to exist
you'll just keep the same emote
same badge so don't worry you'll be fine
you got that
can we exist to faint
that is a myth speaker moment that
you're having right there
[Music]
oh yeah Ryan
there's one thing I was hoping to
maybe change about the badges
[Music]
okay
I shall
leave now
you gotta go to physical favorite oh
well that's chill good luck
Andrew when we say
[Music]
Alvin
oh yes hi
[Music]
have a nice day night whatever
oh
bye bye
finally I did it High Five Guys
[Applause]
good stretch yeah
that was a lot of cracks no it was just
free
[Music]
next time I ask for what movie to watch
and movie watch along tell me that we
should watch that one yeah
but we also need to watch Pitch Perfect
God damn it
Indiana Jones yeah
[Music]
why did we forget about that last time
I didn't see a single Indiana Jones in
the suggestions when I was scrolling
through
[Music]
tell me really really
but first we have to finish Pitch
Perfect
or I'll watch it on my own
maybe
maybe I'll watch it on my plane ride
perfect
Watch Andy on your own
watch a long picture okay okay oh yeah
okay okay I I shall not watch it alone
yeah it was fun together okay okay okay
[Music]
all right