[Music]
n
oh
[Music]
love
m he
[Music]
l
K doesn't this look cute with with
glasses
[Music]
on I'm like a book nerd elf don't we
love that
Trope yay cute I look
intellectual
intellectual yay
hello I can't
believe the day has come
we gonna have a party tonight yeah let's
go
um catching it in candy wrap
paper I am not
sure
um I'm
that's the only thing I have here I'm
not sure uh if I'm GNA don't look at me
like that chunky wonky she's like why
the are you talking I was sleeping
why are you waking me up I'm not sure if
I going to or if I should or if I want
to stream really until the
very
[Music]
end um not sure what the best thing to
do is
because like first of all I mean I think
I prepared everything uh even in OBS
everything is set up like the loading
screen and the intro screen and the main
screen everything is set
up but I don't know I might need to take
a little break too so to eat and I don't
know if I can go all the way to 2 a.m.
yeah you also want to break okay I don't
think we necessarily need to you know
raid I mean I would raid into it anyway
but I don't think it has to be like
exactly before right before um so okay
if you guys
agree then yeah we won't force it
yeah yeah yeah you want a nap please
allow us Europe to nap well I'm not
napping
either no but sure
um surely that's fine so maybe by the
latest maybe two hours
before I'll give you guys a break and
myself a break that' be
good yeah
well but I'm not going to sleep because
I shouldn't sleep I'll be too excited
anyway even early we'll see how far we
get um I do hope to make more progress
today if possible
because maybe then we can read some
super chats I don't know um we'll see
hopefully we'll be a little bit more
efficient today I mean we weren't that
unefficient last time we did two
dungeons but we were already right in
front of the dungeon when we started so
today also considering we want to
probably do some side
quest
yeah cuz now I'm not right in front of a
[Music]
dungeon Super Chat ring stre this week
no not really I think if anything next
week also I have to put out one more
guest announcement before so it's good
if we end a little bit before so that I
can put out the last
tweet um the last tweet will be
announcing two guests at the same
time actually three but one of those
threee has already been announced but
the picture shows Free
People excluding me so uh somehow we
don't have a better
picture so it will be like two people
actually three people announced but one
of them has already been announced so
you actually only getting two people
announced but the picture shows four
including me no I am in the
performance yeah the last the last
remaining two and then when that happens
I'm going to change the fum
nail uh I think I mean the Silhouettes
look cool too but I think I'll change
the thumbnail already already to the
ones with the cleared up silhouettes
I'm mean I'm I'm in it too thank you for
inviting me takasi
Kiana yeah so far what do you think
about the guests who have been announced
I I will say like as I said this life
was really cursed I had to cancel songs
I had to change members cuz like when I
plan a song um I decide the
members uh by like trying
to uh fit the vibe of the song like I'm
not going to just mix any member into
any song you know I'm pretty picky when
it comes to that like getting the right
voices and the right visuals too like I
don't
want uh like too many like extreme size
differences like like all kinds of weird
uh things that I'm
considering
um Ida was a surprise yeah um Ida Ida
originally well the song I'm doing with
Ida originally wasn't supposed to be a
duet but again things were cursed and
things went wrong and then it became a
duet but it's fine as a duet too um but
yeah uh so because I had to change a lot
of
songs uh I had to change a lot of
members too so maybe some things you
were expecting aren't there and some
things you were not expecting are there
like yeah Iris I think is a surprise for
you
guys more or
[Music]
less
yeah and originally like you know I was
also going to have like cobal but kobal
kobal got really
[Music]
sick so I had to switch out Cobalt like
okay so so many people that I had to
switch out
yeah
[Music]
yeah one you have a guess for one more
Ian member there is no more Ian members
the last two are Japanese
members the last two are Japanese
members so so far we have um uh waya
announced Nissa announced Iris Ena
announced um MAA announced
uh lisu announced and Ida
announced I think
so two
more yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah only you would bring so many an
speaking member to gu really I don't
know about that but I I definitely tried
um to you
know Implement a lot of Ian and ID
members also because I love ID and they
have great singers and there's a lot of
songs where I felt like o I need strong
vocals strong vocalists is what I need
so I considered that a lot but then I
was like oh damn I need more vocalists
for this song too but I feel like I
already like
chose all of those that have time and
are available and who
else was it was really
difficult I appreciate lineup so far
thank you thank you thank you I'm really
curious what song you did with MAA Anda
why are you making that face as if you
as if you have a an idea but I don't
think you have an idea why would you
have an
idea well you'll see I'm getting excited
holy I can't believe it's so
soon and then uh there's a premiere
which if you watch my streams every day
you will be able to assume what that is
but just let it happen it's still like a
question what question what
[Music]
question I still want to like keep it
kind of I wanted to still keep it kind
of vague so that there's an element of
surprise but
yeah new item on the kfp
menu non kfp and preat are surprised by
right I know I've seen already like you
know people are like huh what is
this can you really not tell well that's
fine my third my fourth hat what do you
mean for hat but I do you like the
thumbnail guys that was my
idea you it's a meme you bite into lemon
and
then your face sucks it itself inside I
don't know now you might wonder what
what's what's the next
step it depends I I got one super cute
um fan art of me in this like Zelda
attire
uh yeah never mind um and maybe I'll
will use that van ARD for the last
thumbnail or I have another idea if if
it looks like we need another part
before the finale then I have an idea of
what to do but yeah I tried my best to
make that look like the meme but it
doesn't look as cute it looks more
cursed why does it look so cursed
I hope there's few more left I don't
know like apparently we're like this is
the oh is this the fourth one oh okay so
it took us free streams to get to like
halfway through the game okay maybe we
do need three more parts including this
one
it looked real off oh come on I tried my
best I don't know what's wrong with
it that's
[Music]
loud how about
now ponytailed
Zelda feel like I'm in
Mirage H what does mirage
mean but you know I uh I saw that
members have been like giving their 3D
lives like some kind of
title these past one two years maybe
even more so in the last
year um like baz was like called dream
catcher right like so there's there's
titles now so I was like oh I have to
title my life now I mean I don't have to
but maybe it was would be interesting
rather than just calling it takanasi
2024 anniversary live
yeah so it's good to have a title I
guess I don't know I don't know we're
trying it out with this
one yeah it's what the cool kids do
these days I got a chicken ketchup I got
to catch up with the
times you
know um yeah I've been spoiled by the
way
that there's a cat on the roof I've been
spoilered spoiled
spoilered
[Music]
um Dad there is a certain costume that
has to do with
cats spoiled by someone's
thumbnail godamn thumbnails I'm I'm
avoiding to watch all of those that I
don't uh understand yet that I where I
haven't been to yet then I still get
spoiled but uh I don't know how to get
it at least but I'm assuming maybe you
got to talk to a lot of cats and then
eventually maybe it's interesting how
you can't oh you can you can't talk to
the dogs this one's kind of
cute oh why is it following me now it's
never mind it's it's following me come
back I kind of liked that you followed
me that was
cute cute oh he follows me
[Music]
but yeah that's that's too far
huh I know the feeling of being spoiled
by
thumbnails yeah I try not to I don't
think I do like I usually keep the same
artwork from the game and then I just
put a different picture of myself
there maybe I have to collect cats I
don't know I mean the only thing you can
do with them is talk to them so far so
and like just have one word
Exchange oh there's a quest here all
right let's get into it
[Music]
guys
wait hi Miss princess lady I got a
question have you ever seen a door oh is
that the
candle the candle was it the candle one
or or the non candle one there's small
little monsters you can find all around
here I saw a picture in the encyclopedia
Wikipedia from my dad Z are round and
Wiggly and so super cute isn't it kind
of weird that monsters can be cute well
I've only seen them in pictures so
please show me
one wonder if he wants to see all of
them well doll is an easy one
anyway everybody has a doll
wa what's the F excuse me don't you know
the lemon meme
it's sour so my face went inside of
itself hello an how
you wow that looks exactly like the doll
the wiggly body those big round eyes
it's so adorable I just knew it would be
cute thank you do you know there's
different ones the candles
mhm my eyes they hurt when I
S bro it's like they're like like
they're going to my eyes are going to
like you
[Music]
know you laughed at my f yippe very good
very
[Music]
good s becoming a black hole
okay plus menu might help no yeah oh my
God it's on fire igny to it's totally
different from the green tow looks like
a candle well it's really hot do we have
the blue one
[Music]
too see I knew it but that's that's the
last one I
think unless there will be more
it hurts my eyes ah
[Music]
looks like the rear end of a chicken
okay I
mean come on don't you know whole life
real are
sour I'm just trying to be funny and I
drew I cut the lemon open and I drew
like the inside of the lemon it's not
really a lemon but it became a lemon
it's a lemon now for sure is the quest
over
a huge eh he want he want wait I have an
idea how we can do it but uh
huh how
huge so um I realized
those Hydra
dools does it have how close does it
have to be they become big in
water so if we make water blocks
here and then put a hydro gel
in oh it's already big um but yeah
[Music]
go yeah okay there we go well I think
that was because he was at the water
right but maybe he didn't have to be in
the
water you like using hydrol for what so
far I haven't really felt any good need
for them oh my God it's huge huge it's
bigger than my bed you know there's so
many kind of Dos and they also different
some light up like candles some more
like water what I want to know is how
did the same thing become so many
different things oh I know they're
monsters but they're really interesting
and fascinating cool and thank you Miss
princess idea looks like I like do even
more now here's a good thing my papa
gave me oh
thanks
[Music]
yeah if you if I think of enough ah okay
there might be progress in this quest in
the future and there might be more dolls
in this game g
h okay is
there there's a side quest here but let
me check the guda place if there's
anything new there first let's go let's
go City by
[Music]
City what if I put my finger to into
what into my
face my lemon face
don't you
dare you don't have fingers
anyway
you're the one who got rid of the in the
dessert oh I've got a favor to ask it's
something I can't really ask anyone else
to help me
with
what showing you how to use a
pad but I don't want anyone out there to
over here so let's step
inside cats so you haven't run into any
beetles have you the gross little bugs
that crawl perpetually out of the beetle
moons until you destroys the nest those
are beetles I thought those were spiders
I think usually I am busy with Soldier
duties but right now I am tasked with
eliminating Beetle mounts moons MS
I just can't
stand well what's wrong with the British
guys they sing great have you ever heard
like I don't know lemon tree is that
from The Beetles oh it's from The
Beetles right oh the the Yellow
Submarine why are you such a beetles
hater is it because they're
British wait let me move my
microphone okay oh surprised that didn't
make any sounds
oh the nasty little legs and the V is
move I'd been warning about this to my
friends but they can't be bothered to
help
them so could you deal with the B Moons
for me I'll give you something
good the N I'm supposed to deal with are
in a cave Northeast of here say swarming
in there
though let me know once you've gotten
rid of all of them and be careful of the
borins in the
area
Northeast your F thank you finally
someone who can appreciate real effort
and and passion for graphic design and
all that kind of
stuff someone who
understands
Northeast a cave Northeast have I been
in that cave NE it's like maybe
Northeast I don't
know is is it out in the open or is it
against that big wall I wonder oh yeah
right wait oh do we want to do
this we can do this now although is
there a quest for that I wonder
[Music]
wait actually
maybe whatever let's do these two okay
uh how did I do this
again what was I mean now I can stand in
here so I don't have to be so extra
careful
[Music]
but I will bring out my PE hat fly leaf
let's
go uh yeah I've seen a glitch
deploy the oct armor yeah I don't know
if I want to repeat that let's see uh oh
wait no uh wait
ah ah but that was how you were
supposed to do it right um pull it
out with the ultra
hand my fly leaf has nothing to
do okay and then we hit
it oh just
anywhere Hey Hey Hey cap
here we are so much stronger than
compared to back then so this should be
good
not let's go
fly that's
it pleas literally only two
times oh but they dropped a good amount
of
money two times remember how much how
hard I tried did I get this one yet okay
how hard I tried back then Mama
Mia oh was that fly leaf is this the nor
face cave
that feels like it
is the bug that she means oh my yeah but
I've cleared this before wait I got to
go around the
corner oh okay it
acknowledged what I have
done want to kill all of those while
we're at it
Yeah clean it up clean it up
nicely I tried so hard but got so
far
oh
yeah lwn mowing not
quite oh a fly has died in my home
tonight once again oh let me clear this
so I can get the treasure chest
ow okay come down thank
you
yippee getting stuff done here in the
desert before we never come
[Music]
again yes something got
zapped the cats get the fly no no I have
this like tennis racket it looks like a
tennis racket but it's a
electric fly water and I just have it on
constantly standing uh on in on the
kitchen counter and so it's just doing
its thing every once in a while some fly
flies in and dies
automatically is there another Quest
here by a
chance no no no
okay sorry I need to get a feeling again
for everything
even though it's just been a day uh
there it is there it is there it
is automatic fly Farm yeah oh before by
the way before the there's a G outfit
what the before um today's stream I
was like prepping everything for today's
3D live and also we had a little test
for 7 days to die and also they came up
with a schedule that is a little a
little bit better for me a little bit
more bearable so that it's not like
starting at 4:00 a.m. each day my time I
think it's more like starting at 2: a.m.
and then also there's a different slot
for like 10 10: p.m. my time or so
something like that or or was it I don't
know but um they've made it a little bit
better for the Europeans
so um and I don't have to participate in
every time slot but I'll probably be
generally aiming for
the uh not in the middle of the
nighttime slots except for the F the the
first stream I think I W to be there and
my sleep schedule is still kind of
right now anyway so why not make
use of it but then I'll gradually
probably turn towards the more European
friendly times slash it's g no actually
it's I I think okay so uh it must be
like 300 p.m. or so my time European
friendly time slot because uh I think it
was like 1 p.m.
jst is one slot where people are
expected to start and then that's like
300 p.m. is for
me sometime around that and and then the
other one is like morning slash early
noon pre noon jst which is na prime time
which is for me
so right was it like that yeah yeah yeah
yeah but it's not a as it was
originally going to be anymore so both
slots are okay I'll show up here and
there yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah she said she'll be in the
evening slots too but she won't stream
yeah
yeah but I think yeah the European girls
and I don't know who else maybe um um
some others too will join the late uh
evening jst time
[Music]
slot but European girls but herb is not
participating so it's really just me and
CeCe but I think others will join too
like I saw already some comments that
some uh prefer the evening jst time from
the girls because of their schedule and
stuff so yeah
yeah I think even Ena will join on one
of the later time SLS late for me no
late for late for jst not late for me
anyway yeah I did it yipp oh a
ribon heart
baret huh makes Hearts appear more often
don't I already have an item like that
oh we're going to pretend that she took
care of the beetles
or apologies for bothering you when
you're off duty but I wanted to speak to
you about the N oh yes I just finished
dealing with them I was about to come to
tell you I knew it I just received a
report that they have been eliminated
I'm so impressed you strength for
so wait let me recalibrate am I looking
straight I don't know kind of why am I
so why am I
so do I look straight right now guys
can't
see
no wait really wait
okay I
mean no I look pretty straight looks
okay looks okay you guys are just
bullshitting me
[Music]
oh another Quest security looks good oh
Zelda I'm happy to see you is your
journey going well since he left I've
been hard hard at work as captain of the
Guard just the other day Chief s ordered
tighter Security on the treasury which
I've improved I placed some of my best
and most trusted soldiers as guards
there but I feel like I could test
things to see how well they'll do
SOA do you want to test out the security
I've put into place if you can steal the
contents of the treasure chest in the
deepest area of the treasury you in
uh the
treasury where second floor of the
palace on the west side that place you
open it up
now the place that was always
closed I knew it I knew that was a
treasury
I had a feeling before very sus we can
finally jump onto this platform without
turning into link isn't that
wonderful ooh wow oh oh it's stealth
again this layout feels extremely
familiar did they don't tell me they
reused the
layout I okay so we did hyru uh Castle
last time right and
[Music]
and the stealth part I struggled a
little bit with it right I got caught a
few
times and I watched I watched a certain
German YouTuber go through it and he
cheesed it so hard by going
through everything so fast with the
flying
tile can you believe
it I was like what
no wait am I supposed to take something
out of
that uh thing right there
too or is it at the very
end is this just for show no make it to
end okay well then let's try this I
rarely use the tile but let's cheese it
a little bit too but got to be careful
cuz yeah
it they can jump up okay that's yeah
well that's relatively low oh okay maybe
you know not the easiest way out but I'm
I'm going to try one more
time I think if it's uh two blocks high
then they can't get me that was one
block High I got to jump off like
earlier maybe I don't
know like let's stop here for
now and then ooh ah they want me to get
that Treasure Chest she jumps up looks
oh my
God but okay just that Treasure Chest
over
there I could try cutting off their
paths they go they don't go to the
treasure chest oh but will they see me
the moment I stand up there let's see no
oh yes
[Laughter]
ah okay then I will just become a pot at
at that
point that that should definitely
work getting off there and then huh we
have to go get down here maybe
safely ooh and then become a pot just a
pot a pretty one
even here we
go nice move thank you at that point
just run for it maybe when I'm like
past this whole
[Music]
section this is pretty easy what's up
there is there another chest over
there please don't look at me I'm just
that's a
pot
[Music]
po sneaky sneaky sneaky saky oh what's
she going to
do oh please choose a different path
because what are we going to do about
this situation
huh if I move she will
know if I move she 100% knows I
shouldn't have stood in her path
oh yeah yeah she definitely
knows that was a wrong
[Music]
choice I
understand but why is she so dumb why
did she have to just stay there
forever ah
just a
pot I'm just going to walk straight
through the
middle seeing more and more Japanese
yeah they started a little bit late huh
I saw W Senpai and someone else I think
please make way for your
princess no what you
s Mama Mia oh yeah
[Music]
mhm why why why do why
what went
wrong what went
[Music]
wrong it was just like
the I couldn't get
in no I don't think the middle is bad it
was just like gidy gidy it was it was so
close for her not to see
me really
close yeah she saw me hopping in uh
oopsie
which didn't have to happen I think I
can avoid
that please get
in can't just fly to the other shelves
well the length is limited of how far I
can fly and uh the height of those
shelves is too low they
would uh see me when I land and they
would be able to uh jump up
so see the left shelf that's high enough
but these ones although the green ones
actually are they they might be high
enough it it's hard to tell yeah they
actually they might be higher
than one block yeah but oh
well
oh she's going around this time
[Music]
okay W that was so loud what's wrong did
you hear that
she's been so cute yesterday I had to
cut a little bit of her butt fur because
there was some poop stuck it doesn't
happen to her that often these days it's
been a long time it's been like a year
since the last time I had to do that but
she was so stinky because of that poop
stuck to her butt and then she was
like making it really difficult for me
to get it off to cut it off you know she
like panics when I try to get close to
her
butthole no don't panic chunky
o Don't Panic chunky wonky I'm just
trying to
help but I want to
see is that
really is the left really low and than
the right let's test it out if they can
see me
there well first of all there's
distracted that's good I can send
another one like uh over there maybe
that maybe they hear that too no what
about one more over
there and then I just go get
it is that all I need to
get oh is there
more maybe there is
more
okay something up there huh okay
can she see me up there no
right okay no
problem so far so
good can I walk
up in a
pot
no well then
uhoh
[Music]
okay my cat's more affectionate than
your dog I don't know about
that but they're pretty affectionate
they're cute oh she's sitting on the
floor being a cute blob
ponytail Zelda it's so cute right and
what not no not
again no no no no do I have to redo the
whole thing then probably not I can just
skip that area cuz the chest is already
open
right oh please change your
path damn it so
over so I I stood in their way again I
did it
[Music]
again I'll figure it out it's good that
it's not too
easy get off
here wait a little bit I think it's
better before flying over
them uh I I want to get off
here m actually guys go there can you go
there they don't hear
it
okay oh
um okay so what now she walks on
the edge of this
parameter but she doesn't go around here
so we definitely safe here
now if I just make a water
block and go up I don't think she sees
me and then I just fly over
there oh wait there's another guard
there though so for now let's just go to
the next Green
area but it's so fin oh
God and then the next Green area okay
okay okay yeah I feel like you without
the tile honestly this this this
challenge is
rough she was already going for me oh I
got silk pajamas
cute please let me keep
them do you think that was a treasure uh
I'd hope so let's take it and get thank
you lemon oh she got me out of
trouble you
you're welcome I can keep the SI
pajamas y we we're matching she has the
same
set let me see but um they don't have
any like it's just just a visual
right oh wait my hair my hair is
open but still like there's literally
nothing like pulling my hair back like
at any tie or so but it's still like so
slicked
back oh Hearts recover B faster and bad
a okay but there's no downside to it
right ah there it says Okay Okay so this
doesn't have anything special so I can
just wear
that yeah there's like a lot of hair gel
on
her hair or it's like helmet hair but
for her it's like a tiara hair
thing where her hair is just like
forever
stuck okay just checking if there's any
more side quests or if that was it but a
look at me I wish I could get a closer
look what first time I'm in
here also wait can I go in there
normally now outside of the side quest
and or are the guards always
[Music]
there oh they're always
there okay but I'm guessing I found
[Music]
everything any more
stuff if I forgot something let me know
we'll move on to the water
[Music]
place the dirt patch you think I can dig
into it I wasn't
sure I can try though maybe that's the
real
treasury I always wanted to
try mangle placed by The
Oasis ah right she did say she might
make something even more difficult right
uh
what is it
starting
okay it doesn't 100% look like such a
dirt space to me but we can
try it is it was sus oh it's a
shortcut that's a nice shortcut you can
just go to the both Treasures from there
quite
easily well now you
know but I think it was fun to figure it
out wait do they care about me
now
okay you
guys you guys seem to have something in
your eyes cuz it took you well to see
me
okay
mangoes they need glasses like
me drinking orange Peach
Capron
Capron yummy they've got tomatoes on
their ass
yeah all right this crazy lady is this
what I look like with glasses and my red
orange hair is this what it look like
especially when I put my white hair band
on I wonder
yeah oh you've been waiting for me uh
the great grand is work
oo okay we'll see we'll see I don't
think I can first try it but ultimate
seeds
I didn't pick a proper item yet though I
do have the water block now but I feel
like the trampoline might still be
better cuz you can kind of get stuck in
the
water we'll grow forns and bomb flowers
but I'm sure you'll do great bombs yipp
60 or more
mangoes let me change an item
[Music]
though I wonder I also wonder
only I can collect it right my mobs
can't collect it I
[Music]
assume oh I'm already like ah what
is this what is
this let me okay we're just going to
figure out uh oh where everything is now
and what's a safe place to put a
trampoline so far that's that's a decent
place it seems oh my God this is fast
[Music]
uhhuh oh wait why did I do
that it's been a while we're not in the
groove
okay uh I think it should oh that's a
heart it should be in the middle like
the left
one she doesn't know
what the frog ring oh I have it on
though wait can I jump up there now
normally do I not need my
trampoline oops
no oh
Tornado works for harvesting stuff
oh I want to try that but that sounds
chaotic it like it probably Harvest it
but it drops it on the floor
no
we I'll
try you know I'll just you know I can
get up there for real
no how many can I summon how many do
they cost one
oh
oh are they harvesting it can you guys
tell can you guys keep an eye
out
[Music]
I feel like I'm harvesting less
than before wa I need to I need to ah ah
ah maybe I should like respawn them
sometimes you know to get them you know
where I need them to be
doesn't seem like there it doesn't look
like it you keep missing when you shoot
them maybe yeah maybe I have to like aim
them
properly but I'll
I'll I also try to just like be faster
is there any uh smoothie that makes your
walking speed or your running speed
[Music]
faster
h
no it's possible to do with summons I
believe I honestly can't tell if I got
that
or no please wait
shouldn't that explosion have
harvested some
mango this is difficult oh it's does
harvest no it does but ah
[Music]
Ah
Ahh oh but they have to okay cuz they
don't see the mango as
enemies
so I have to send them out like that so
that they actually spin I
think I'm better without summons maybe
they're confusing me maybe
okay would some armor would the armor
dles work better H
interesting
maybe I don't know if they would Harvest
it either cuz like they're just rolling
around I understand that the wind you
know the wind kind of makes
sense just focus on spinning just focus
on spinning
focus on spinning and then you know
getting to know the patterns
too oh let's go feel like that
was not a good direction to
take
[Music]
ah
ouch should have known
[Music]
okay we got
65 70 is
close yeah P hats also don't activate
until they see an
enemy oh what for for like a millisec I
thought it was a Santa Claus
outfit EAS to move in this Oh you mean
on
Sand
mango now I can get the 70 for sure
[Music]
let's
see it's easier to move and increases
your spin area easier to
[Music]
move I don't know I think it's it
doesn't make me faster it just increases
my spin yeah wow oh
oh mhm where else do I ever need to
spin I mean maybe on the field when I'm
just running around when I'm like lawn
mowing it would be nice to have a bigger
spin yeah for
[Music]
traveling and it looks cute and I got
ponytail again cute
there's a ring that makes your spin have
a knockback effect
wow
oh wow wow the spin is
[Music]
big no the
no can I redo
wait did that explode because I
spined into it I don't remember but
probably spin into it spinning into it
is bad I
assume
ah
yum what do I get at 70 it must be a
hard container at that point right
okay
okay we're next here okay EAS easyas
EAS
okay I saved I saved my
ass my ass is saved
guys
ah thank you for the raid oh the heart
is in a different position is it I don't
know I did it oh my God even Jo I got
bumped
[Music]
yippe yay y y yay Exquisite Divine you
harvested everything you vast exceeded
my expectations Yi I got let's go
finally
finally hi
you use the monster to spin through to
to get the
really it's quite difficult to be
honest okay um wonder if we should make
anything do we have anything new no ah
the
pumpkin pumpkin GRS faster key winding
key excuse me what is key winding
is that
spinning what's key
winding is that supposed to
mean I something I don't have
yet oh no wonder I don't
know wow twisty's
movie
cute um somebody said mango and salt
sure I think there's a lot of um very
similar
recipes
so just got to do the most obvious
things have I done mango and butter yet
no but see I don't know I feel like I
tried that before and failed no I just
mixed two fruits together and that
failed but I wonder if you can mix the
butter and the mango
I don't know N I don't want to risk it
but if you can mix the fruits with the
salt then you can probably also mix the
pepper with the salt
right um I wouldn't be too sure about
that but the pepper with the milk
maybe P Peppa with the milk spicy milk
makes sense
right spicy milk makes sense
not for me but okay good good
good spicy milk hot ass milk
oopsie did I make salty milk before yeah
what about honey
milk oh definitely first of all the the
what the effects of the honey don't
really seem to negate anything so
second of all that just makes sense IRL
too
yeah wait that's so
cute I love the stir thing and it's
wooden which I wonder if they made it
wooden because they understand the thing
that I just found out recently that
apparently if you put a metallic spoon
into your Honey Jar it will ruin all of
the good things of the honey and that's
why wooden honey spoons are a thing I
need to buy
one I've been using my wooden uh
Chopsticks now I think they know yeah
yeah I've been doing that my whole
life I don't know if that's a
lie I think it's partially true I would
say like it doesn't obviously it doesn't
get rid of the honey being
honey but um yeah wait what did it say m
honey
metallic metal metal spoon oh it says
it's a
myth a
really no but the enzymes some experts
believe that honey when that when Honey
comes in contact with metals like copper
or
iron these metals are capable of Destro
destroying what destroying beneficial
enzymes metals like copper and iron
react with the acids in the honey
to produce salts this process kills off
useful enzymes copper is known to react
with acids in honey it can produce toxic
compounds too iron can also react with
honey it doesn't produce any toxins but
over time can change the taste of honey
stainless steel is considered safe to
use of Honey ah and considered
non-reactive silver is non-reactive as
well and considered safe scientifically
speaking the effect of Honey interacting
with metal is not fully understood
studies offer a mixed bag of reviews
which is probably why we see warning
articles floating
around why I care about it because
enzymes are a very important part of
honey they include
diast Inver glucose
oxidase
M catalase and proteases these enzymes
help break down complex molecules making
it easier for our bodies to digest and
absorb so I honestly believe this I
believe this this sounds like it makes a
lot of
sense and wooden honey spoons are cute
so why not buy
one I choose to believe it because
there's no harm in me getting a a honey
spoon for my honey
specifically what about honey with Apple
oh my
God she or
[Music]
no okay it doesn't look like what I was
having in my mind I wanted like a
honeyed apple on top of this movie as a
topping
[Music]
sad have you mixed any T go again no
because I don't need such extreme
effects yet
really I don't feel like I need
it but um I I might sell some of them
cuz they they make good
money maybe when I have more Hearts it
makes more sense you
know mix drink of glow restore some of
the drinkers energy is that the blue
energy that they mean probably
right I don't know what else to
do let's leave it at that for
now
okay um then we go
to ah actually
here the first
Village maybe it has something
bonus accessor SL no uh wait that was at
the
ferry was that at the fery place yeah I
can go to the ferry again I wouldn't
mind spending some money
there chilly fluffy and totally white
that's what Snow's like you want snow I
don't I yeah we're probably going to get
a snow block but I don't have one yet
okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
M should we go to the I wonder what's
the recommended place to go to Snowy
Mountain
or the rock
people what would you say
[Music]
guys link is a local here yeah that's
cute
I feel
faster Rock people okay then the snow
has to wait a little bit did I go in
here
[Music]
before oh yeah yeah it
did okay
okay radlands rock snow volcano swamps
okay depends on the person
[Music]
huh um I think I'll go to Volcan first
because you
know oh
do there's also apparently and don't
worry I have not spoiled it myself I uh
purposefully skipped it um there's let's
see apparently there's like extra
dungeons too here and
there um I don't know where exactly uh
but maybe we'll come across them and if
we come across them then we'll do them
and
are you kidding
me that looks like I can go
there volcano unlock some stuff okay you
did volcano last
[Music]
huh should be able to upgrade some
things again now that we have progress
in the
story Rift here yeah the rift is old
we've been in there don't think
anything's changed if it did then let me
[Applause]
[Music]
know
okay by the way seven days to die when I
played a little bit today it felt oh my
God you kidding me expensive it felt
like
rust I mean we didn't have a zombie rush
yet there were some zombies around
I guess it's just rust plus the element
of zombie rushes at specific times
coming to
you yeah with rust you
like you go out of your way to find
[Music]
trouble uh have I done something here
before
[Music]
probably yeah
okay yeah it feels very similar
thank you
discy
welcome wow yeah this is really Greatful
lawn
[Music]
mowing thanks for the membership starf
Bobcat you think it's a little bit more
interesting going into places for L and
having to find zombies I I think um
possibly I mean rust was kind of
interesting too but know we'll see it
has potential to be more interesting for
sure oh let's get up there it's
time how far up this is go go away what
what happen with
[Music]
it should open lawn mowing business yeah
I should Zelda should open a YouTube
channel for mowing people lawn who don't
take care of their lawn anymore for
whatever
reason Zelda should open a business for
that not a business but YouTube channel
she get so many Subs it's so
satisfying I mean I don't know about you
guys but it's satisfying to me
[Music]
welcome back to my YouTube channel today
I will once again ignore that link is in
trouble and mome LS because that's more
important that's people are in real need
of having their M
Lawn mode lawn's
mode I was lowkey hoping that I was
going to make that mistake one day
because it was always like it was always
there's so much potential there
for me to say that I always think about
it where am I I'm just like aimlessly
mowing
lawns I can't help myself this was a
mistake yeah I was hoping for it I was
always questioning myself did I say it
correctly for
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's go only one for now I don't think
I have enough money for the next
one can I eat some chocolate yes yes
takasi please go ahead and eat some
chocolate thank you
[Music]
by
call
mhm I'm still eating the chocolate
kinder Kinder chocolate Bon
boms
why are you talk talking to
me that's not
normal now
they it didn't always these cats don't
always have a speed
bubble I don't think
so is my ship your ship you mean you big
ass ship is that your ship the big one
why are you so scared
oh damn
it here now you should be good come on
calm down tell me about your
quest see have a big ship out there
there one in the southwest
Waters well that's my sh I've fallen on
Hard Times a real wreck now too when I
was a young sailor I once to rule the
hyan Seas a dream that takes zip but
when I got my ship out there I ran right
into rocks oh the hole got gashed open I
swam back to the store kind of feeling
suck myself but I haven't given up on
the dream I've been making repairs ever
since don't work but I'm getting there
now my ship's been claimed by a monster
that I can't get near it's ABS up jobs
oh sounds like electric
jellyfish a big one maybe this rain my
ship's going to be sunk then I'll be STK
my dream gone I don't stand a chance
against that monster take someone with
real zip to defeat the monster I'm
Zippy hi Tippy H hi Tippy that joke
sorry I know the look in your eye same
look I used to see in mine now listen up
I shut the ship's hatch nice and tight
to keep people safe from the
monster you've got to use lot of force
to pry that thing off then you can get
inside Force m i
[Music]
see see this one doesn't have a speech
bubble so is that a little dungeon
or a big
dungeon let's go check it out um
[Music]
mhm mini D and really oh
M I don't know if that's the one that I
was thinking
about honestly it might not
be I just saw something on a thumbnail
with a green
blob that doesn't seem like something
that would appear in this ship
there's two of them near here
okay
[Music]
sh
ow thank
you T oh good boy
good boy okay so ah we enter from
there was that available to enter
before like from here maybe I just never
[Music]
tried no
okay let's see ship was always
s what is this
room it reminds me of a room in the
Super Mario RPG that we
[Music]
played yeah you know you know which
one just also because of its size
fitting into one screen
oh I didn't even think of destroying all
of that thanks peut what what is your
name PE
hat fly leaf ah there's a
hole
okay let's go
lawn mowan well I don't need him to mow
my Lawns anymore I can mow my own lawn
[Music]
now by the way I want to on Monday I
want to do a
stream where I talk about certain things
like the live concert
hope you guys are up for that so it's
like a satuan
stream I know we have a members only
stream like on for me on the day of
[Music]
the oh now you're running away from
me you I hate these these might be
my most hated enemies um in the member
stream we we're not going to even talk
about any 3D life related things if I
can hold back because I want to keep
those discussions for
um for
the public
stream you know if
possible no I have to hold back wow two
hearts at a time
sweet nice bed nice bed nice
B don't you
kill it kill it
please
ah no I will have to hold back you you
guys will have to hold me back worst
case
ow did you do it good
job maybe don't try to yeah you're just
going to die ah
need something better ow you can see me
from
there it's so over for
you
okay oh you didn't have to do that but
thanks danger water is dangerous for
[Music]
you
okay now we're just going to watch anime
May and the only topic we're allowed to
talk about will be
monoar we're not going to talk
about my Frey life or any other topics
that might be interesting to talk about
because that will be for the public
stream I now we have to we have to
resist I don't want to repeat
myself you hear me
cat tangents cat tangents are
always always allowed if not even
encouraged you know what we're never
going to use it otherwise so I'm going
to drink um wait we don't have a glowy
drink we actually don't H okay
I was just thinking of not being a
hoarder but I guess I'll continue
hoarding by the way I think I
successfully placed a brain rot brain
warm into gig's
brain I remember her not being as
excited about World of Warcraft but I
first mentioned it but now she dm' me
and she's like when can we when do you
want to start uh playing where the
warcraft uh with me I'm like
oh okay she seems to be into
it she wants to play World of
Warcraft oh there's is there no oh cuz I
don't have a dungeon
map
ow Dead
End come with me
Shar yeah I mean honestly I'd prefer to
play mm RPG but they all don't give me
freaking pums they all ignore their
freaking
emails oh yeah go for it now go for
it bubble bubble bubble
c one time was serious I don't know
depends on how we're feeling about it I
just I don't know like I really like uh
grinding in MMO RPGs but on the stream
grinding can get
really not like not maybe not boring but
it will just not be as like it will be
more of a chill
stream at that point I think a chill
series which is fine but um
well I don't know for long term if
that's really a good idea
H can I uh I guess that's a ceiling I
can't go up there
okay good for
jatsu
yeah come
[Music]
on
wait huh what
why
bro Kiki just finally wants to collab
with me I I get it me too me too man at
least I got my oneon-one collab without
I done
now
Italiano nice to flex my Italiano
yesterday did you guys watch On's
Channel she's so
cute for once I'm not the one teaching a
language that's a rare
thing so I was excited about that
Prospect oh only one
so watch The Vault after work thank
you I think we have a few only a few but
we have some Italian viewers so they
must have been very happy our first
golden
rupy y let's go good
money you're Sound Italian oh my God
there's a lot of
mobs when in doubt uh fly
leaf or so I thought yeah yeah um yeah
well okay the blocks are gone oh this
one he can he can tell P little bastard
do we have
something maybe I
can bring out an octar Rock I
guess we can stun him um
but maximum is four right
okay ah what I thought you died ah
ow what if we s the same
one why he's not even acknowledging him
I don't even care
man man
please I finally had some link
energy just grab
him he
oh oh oh
bro you for
real I guess I'll drink the milk sovie
and just kill
him that's so
[Music]
much wow that takes a lot
what are you
[Music]
doing targeting before grabbing makes it
easier
H me wearing this dress makes me feel
like I'm like I just started this game
and this is like the first outfit you
start off with it just feels so like the
beginning like I'm this innocent lost
reborn
Priestess the plain starter
linen
clothes oh sh nothing in this room
[Music]
really oh okay because it was a pre-
boss room to maybe find some hearts in
there oh God oh God that's crazy that's
crazy what am I supposed to
do I would say shark but he'll hurt
himself a lot with the
electricity but I
guess can you swim like that yeah okay
oh wait that actually worked for
him well and then
um do I ever get some link energy
here wait the the the outside jellyfish
they don't oh that must have hurt
h no yeah that will hurt but there's one
that's not electric
buddy here that one that one that one go
for that one
specifically or not like now
yeah oh she gets it now Taki ah yeah
good job takanasi
Kiana she gets it
now waiting for them to be open
again is is now is now does not
work they're flying though no come on
come
on
oh no no no
a wait wait that that that
one thanks for
nothing come on yeah one and two you can
get more if you want to I guess you
didn't want to
they fly now is that a meme
too please you can do it you you little
now you got another we have to
probably get him down to zero
huh come on come you can why are you so
stupid
[Music]
I link energy
doco ow oh that's not really it's it's
too tight over here BR
okay turn
ow
ow what's what's oh he was still
stunned wait
no ah no he's too fat he gets into the
electricity so easy
yeah I'm just going to drink this
but wait
let's I could already
but
okay ah
[Music]
ah
H yo okay yeah really without link I was
trying to brute force it with link but
without link
it's mukashi
but he doesn't give me I mean I was I
was thinking maybe the pots have link
energy but I was kind of doubting it I
was thinking they probably have hearts
yeah that's rough without link
energy nah I feel like I can't really
trust my summons who have ranged attacks
they suck they all suck I just got to do
it myself you know in some some
cases but yeah it seems like we gained
the
heart let's
go yeah the tacos are just too weak
maybe when we get an upgraded version of
them but even then like you know
everything was spinning and moving so
fast you really have
to um be like Dynamic and
variety Boomerang
moblins okay oh well
yeah it's EAS with link
honestly so that's fine I would
say is there an easier way to get up
there can I
just oh okay
nice are you going to reward me
too maybe now that yeah he saved the
ship maybe he'll set up some shop or so
there that would be
[Music]
nice probably not a second
bottle they're not us okay Tetra was a
more badass Zelda yeah but this Zelda is
pretty badass too not going to lie Tetra
watch
out second bottle is kind of crazy we
could we can go pick up a another fairy
but let me let me see if there's really
no other Quest here before we go
oh is that a quest there was a boy who
head out to the scene a hurry haven't
seen him since he was all fired up eager
to be a big shot as he kept saying so L
him my boat
[Music]
okay you want me to look for him huh all
right I'll do that and then we'll go to
the ferry
again ah there it is that was easy just
swim straight maybe make a few energy
yeah that would be good I'll make some
more when I get to
it I oh my God that's a lot of
sharks and bomb fish yeah that would be
very
scary very scary
indeed
ow ow pleas why are you so strong
[Music]
yeah he will take care of himself oh did
we have to I wonder if we had to clear
all the enemies
anyway so that he can go home
wait no how do I jump
[Music]
and when jumping is on a
wait it's on B was jumping always on
B I'm having a hard time getting up
there
yeah
there we go save
me I'm not tasting I swear
he's we he wears a scarf like the tunic
boy huh the monster So
Gone TAA did you deal with all those
monsters surrounding the boat thank you
you saved me let's go inside I've got
something for you inside the tiniest
boat that'll be cramped what that's way
less CRA when we're inside huh it's like
a magical inventory
way bigger than you think it
is that's
nice that's cute is that a big ass
toilet or a bathtub
[Music]
ah
okay like thanks I
guess are you bringing me back is he
bringing me
back where's the boat manual for real so
we're
staying no he did bring me
[Music]
back I appreciate that
okay
um wait what's this place
though
sauce chocolate is so
good
heyo
[Music]
Nan now wait that's not close enough mhm
yeah thank God I need more of
[Music]
them oh and it recharges hello thank you
I appreciate that thank you for thinking
of me what
17 didn't I already have
17 be griefed
there treasure chest
hey can I not open it
[Music]
wait
y
smart I guess I could have yeah I I can
just move them with my ultra
hands but you know we got a rupe oh
have you been here
[Music]
yeah I want to check out that tiny
little
island maybe I've seen it before but hey
look we find
another another
crack guys do you believe in the Denver
air report oh being weird cuz I watched
the conspiracy theory about it yesterday
and I thought that's not as weird as you
guys make it out to be and all these
explanations sound fine to
[Music]
me no like I don't know there's
something about Denver Airport
apparently like it's weird apparently
people say so Denver Airport
International Airport like there's
tunnels and people are like sussing out
the purpose of the tunnels
like maybe they were sold to
Illuminati did I get the stamp now or
not okay I'm
stupid and like the art in the airport
is apparently
weird and and controversial and I mean
and then there's this horse which in the
process of the creation there's this big
ass horse statue right right with
glowing eyes glowing red eyes and it's
placed outside of the airport somewhere
but in the Pro process of creating the
horse the guy who was sculpting it he
was crushed by the horse when a part of
the sculpture fell down and he died and
that's why they say it's cursed they
like the children finished the horse but
they were kind of forced to finish it by
the airport people I guess who
commissioned it
um but they say yeah the horse is
cursed I mean it's definitely a like
really unfortunate accident uh do you
have to read so much into
[Music]
everything I don't know
man oh and yeah there were a couple of
things that they brought up but
I've heard worse like better conspiracy
theories than
that you know how there's like these
Chuck-E-Cheese conspiracy theories and
stuff someone should just make a joke
video about kfp conspiracy theories kind
of trying to resemble
that like oh my god did you know at
kfp the conspir conspiracy is that all
the chickens that work there also end up
being fried and eaten and the um the
workers lunch and
dinner
is they're
co-workers no way and did you know
apparently there's a usual room when
people try to bring out the truth or
Escape they're being sent to the usual
room sounds crazy
right what is the usual
[Music]
room when they come out of the usual
room they all seem to be
very I don't know weird they just not
the same
[Music]
anymore seems like I need to charge my
controller
I have a cable over there I
[Music]
think but that's just a theory a
conspiracy
[Music]
theory
um excuse me switch ch
please let me insert the USB cable into
you thank
you is
it is it connected
now I can't tell shouldn't there be a
sign
[Music]
okay so is there any Quest
here I've come all the way to check with
you
guys reveal yourselves if you have a
quest for
me that's
sus I feel like you know we can do a lot
of side stuff today but then probably
just one dungeon which I think is
fine
considering the next stream won't
seems like we won't be the last
[Music]
one the map North of you too what's with
the north
[Music]
what's play too much Zelda but not yet
not enough Never Enough not even close
to being enough
[Music]
I'm just going to swim
around
[Music]
aimlessly
we ooh we should clear the
monsters
oopsie that was
easy just those two that's barely a
challenge
[Music]
I want more heart containers
please please bless me with more heart
containers ow please be nice
mosquitoes active all of player I hope
you do stream it again oh thank
you yeah I sometimes you know I do feel
the urge for it so
oh I'm excited last time you know I was
playing it alone with you guys which was
fun too but it might be even more fun
with another member
[Music]
together and then you guys can try to
find us again it's kind of inevitable
for you guys to find us so maybe I'll
just share from the GetGo oh not
share n i i shouldn't notri share the
server that's going to be chaotic that's
like I'm asking for you guys to um you
know get in our
way is there something up here
too yeah we were discovered I was
discovered anyway uh back then no matter
what
did I just go
here I think I
[Music]
did oh
okay I can't tell I don't want to I
don't want to miss
anything but I'm confused I don't
know okay looks like bonus Rift up north
from there ah that one you think is
bonus
Rift is
it I wouldn't mind doing a bonus Rift if
it's
bonus if it's bonus I'll do it heart
container at the very top of the
waterfalls m maybe we'll get there
anyway if I try to get to the North
[Music]
oops wait oh we we we've been there
before right behind the
waterfall we walk through
[Music]
here love these
platforms yippe yippe
maybe oh oh I see it maybe I should test
more often if I could walk through the
waterfalls if there's a a hidden oh
fairy ah guess I don't have to catch the
one in in the
fairy
house yeah maybe there's hidden caves
more often than not not here at least
[Music]
okay it ends
here and
then can use the rift
but that's not what the entrance would
be I guess from the bottom Maybe
oh from there ah oh
no oh fast
fruit okay lemon Chan if you don't want
to be fully eaten then behave well and
bring me into this Rift and also bring
me back there was a bumb wall really oh
why am I so
blind I'll go back there first otherwise
I might
forget no
where where where where where did I miss
it a here that's so obvious I was just
looking to the to the right
side you're in the
way money
money it's like two chests in the ocean
H
how oh well as as long as I'm not
missing heart containers I can kind of
forget about it although I would like to
have the blue stones at least cuz a lot
of them are
necessary Pudo on my eyes I
can't believe
it
P don't you also sometimes have
Pudo p on your eyes eh when you guys was
impressed with how much I already knew
honestly all that me Pia stuff also I
already knew but I just had to be
reminded of
so I have some
Basics somehow I feel like I almost
remember more Italian than I remember
Korean but I took way more Korean
lessons than I did for Italian and they
were oneon-one
what's wrong with me I guess like
European language is easier
for me to pick
up there are more blue stone than reard
yeah I would assume so but still I'd
like
to get more cuz right now I feel like I
barely have
any is this a dungeon
too or just a
[Music]
rift was I in here before
no just a
rift you just need a cute girl that can
teach you
Korean
H man but you
know honestly like asking just like a
random person who is not a certified
teacher wait this is oh this is
funny I I thought I had the upside the
the the birp puie
on but it's not it's just just like how
these things are placed very very
purposefully but I was going to say I I
think nobody should expect from like a
normal person who's not a certified
teacher to teach you a fullon
language like any more than just like
the easiest
[Music]
words and so with Raa too like she seems
very open to doing this like more
and regularly but I don't
really I don't know maybe we'll do one
more and then call it a day because I
can't say yeah I don't think and I don't
want
to
um I don't I don't think she it's easy
to you know you would have to at some
point have this whole system of what you
going to teach them how you going to
teach
them is there anything in there no
right that's just too much to ask of
someone and uh even if she's
like like open to doing it I don't think
we really have to go that
far even though I'd love to become
fluent in
Italian it's just not really feasible
[Music]
I wasn't sure what I was falling into oh
okay okay
okay we go back here okay was I here
before no the fish the fish are
[Music]
new oh interesting it's stopping my
arrows even though in water I can oh I
cannot shoot arrows in water Oh I
thought I
[Music]
could but yeah I don't think this is a
dungeon because uh there's free things
to
collect that's usually just a closure of
a rift but maybe after closing it maybe
there will be a dungeon who
knows I'll be happy with anything you
two do I think for sure we'll be
doing quite a few things in the future
together
[Music]
mhm one
more
oh
no I want it that way yeah
that way please and that way
please speaking of that wait that was a
One Direction no not One Direction take
that right what were they called n but
that reminds me of One Direction I saw
like the craziest like One
Direction fandom drama stuff tell me why
where am I why am I here I think this
part is
done that was backstage boys okay but I
was thinking of One Direction because
they're disbanded now right which is not
active anymore
but I never listen to them I don't
really know their names or anything
except for this hairy guy he's so
hairy
um
but there's this guy
Liam who's been doing some crazy
which is so weird do you want to
hear the tea the drama
the the Liam guy so apparently Harry or
some other One Direction member he was
going to do a
concert and Liam knew where he stays in
which
hotel and Liam was just like going there
maybe as a guest or so like not he was
not performing there or
anything but he goes to the hotel where
he knows the guy is staying in and
there's a there's a lot of fans outside
they no they know him from One Direction
for sure but they're not directly his
fans right they're I mean these girls
will go crazy over any One Direction guy
I suppose but he's he goes there and
takes a million selfies with all the fan
girles are standing out there of the
hotel not for him in particular but for
The Other One Direction guy but isn't
that so weird like I thought that was
weird he's like taking pictures with
fans of the are not directly his fans
he's just like soaking in all that
attention because they're going like
yeah oh my God okay I'm actually here to
wait for Harry Styles or so I guess but
you're fine
too and then he's just like soaking all
of that
in like go and a a really famous
celebrity going out of the way to go to
someone else's
fans cuz he knows that's where they're
getting to together to take a and
the pictures with the the fans that're
not really your fans it's it's weird
it's just I don't know if I'm explaining
it properly but it's weird
[Music]
yeah yeah apparently he wasn't so
popular when he was in the group I don't
know
why but then he did something weird at
the concert
too so he had like what a seat at the
concert just like like a VIP seat I
guess still kind of
accessible um for the fans to see where
you
sit so but it was kind of well cut off
you don't if you don't want to be
bothered by fans it was a seat where you
wouldn't be bothered by fans it was like
you know a level higher
in ter in terms of height
so but then he like leans over the
fence during the concert or so uh or
like maybe during the waiting time when
everybody's getting seated he leans over
the fence and all the girls that are
close by see him and like turned around
to him and started screaming and you see
in the video that he's just
like his expression he's just so
I don't know into it
like they're all like starting to film
him and scream for him and wave at him
and and he's just like smirking at them
leaning over giving them a little
like and then he turns around and goes
away after like a minute or so feeling
so uh yeah like
accomplished I mean if I was a fan of
this group grou One Direction I Would
probably be happy to see anybody from
that group up close so I understand the
fans reaction totally but it's like
him going out of his way to
like claim this like fan
interaction for himself you know what I
mean yeah it's fan service and the the
fans are excited about it but there's
just there just seems to be something
with this Liam guy
that
is
[Music]
interesting oh Liams GF found out he was
cheating on her via fans Instagram post
oh oh no he's just a really interesting
kind of person yeah so I didn't even
know about this GF thing but see if you
consider stuff like that too he's just
um yeah
yeah it's not my world either I don't
listen to boy bands I only listen to
girl
groups that's tiny I can't even go like
ooh because it stops immediately two M
crystals two are you for real for such a
intricate Rift I mean was a bit
difficult to move around you
know High School a Wawa no she wasn't
like that no no no
what are you talking
about if anything I was always more on
the quiet
side uh wait the rift is
gone but
what it didn't really block
anything important huh
[Music]
J J cave ah you mean down
here princess dius
what princess theis
oh I was like what what is that oh
hard
container wait did I watch the other
movies I don't
remember Disney movie with an
hadway she'll have it that way
H certainly not the first time she heard
that right tell her
why okay I don't know did we get what we
wanted here do I still have
a I should pick up the
[Music]
horse cuz I don't know if I got anything
left here I I feel like I don't I feel
like I'm
[Music]
done ah although I didn't check in here
in the seora village yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah so there's an
a I wonder if the horse if if they let
me summon it or if I also have to like
pick it up and bring it
everywhere I hope they let me summon it
[Music]
Quest Monsters around to seea the people
of seaside village with real difficulty
is wait what you heard all that did you
I'm trying to work on a solution for
something I may as well fill you in I
want destroy my treasure for Safety and
Security this just a collection of
shells and rocks I found while swimming
but it's a treasure to me and I'm quite
proud of my collection but I don't have
room for it all so I need to find
something I can store it
in Nar
[Music]
uh
underwater
so I
don't I feel like a pot wouldn't work
because it's
open but we can
try uh wor about a LD that it wouldn't
work on the water s
[Music]
um this kind of looks like a container
but I'm guessing not well this doesn't
look nice I don't think he like the
wooden box
[Music]
right he brought me something uh but at
least it doesn't look suspicious I feel
that I'm I'm being fussy but it doesn't
feel special enough for my but then
other people maybe won't think like oh
this looks fancy so there must be
something fancy
inside you know
yeah I don't have anything
closed is there I mean i' uh I remember
those pots that had the wooden lid on it
but I couldn't learn
[Music]
those I don't know how to summon a
chest I don't know how to I I don't
think I can learn how to summon a chest
there's one
[Music]
around and then bring it to him I guess
well that oh wait oh wa wait it's I
didn't I didn't even open
[Music]
it
okay all right good to know that works
as well
really need to think more about moving
things around with the Master Hand the
ultra hand you like that certainly looks
fancy well he likes it I
think
okay unusual Stones ah okay why thank
you I still don't know how to use these
but I appreciate
them one day
we will make use of them right one
[Music]
day okay let's move over
here uh
here now we can do the mini game there
there's another Quest there at the seor
US oh
[Music]
okay
wait who may I talk to about my horse
inside
[Music]
maybe on one of the outside Islands
huh
okay wait
[Music]
huh wh where is
everybody are
you no
but where's my white horse it was here
before maybe it also got stuck they
should have come back by now I wonder if
something's happened did somebody take
on my white horse how dare you put it in
danger lady imp to is to expect you I'm
afraid we don't have your horse what the
you had one job my brother took her
out for some exercise but not too worry
they should be back soon uhhuh I would
hope
[Music]
so well well
welli goodness what are you shouting so
loudly for you afid the princess's
nerves disas
we were at the carrot patch no voice of
hyru Castle and the rift opened up and
my horse fell
in you had one job guys what the
now my horse when I bring it back out of
the rift will be
forever
damaged what if it's mute and won't be
able to speak my language anymore cuz I
assure you that horse was a talking
horse before it fell into the rift I
will sue you if it's not able to speak
anymore afterwards
I will sue
you where the hell is it there that's so
far I will sue them I will sue
them I'll put them into the usual room
hi fly leaf that is not my fly leaf
[Music]
my American side we will be pursuing
legal
action huh I will
[Music]
be
ow that's a little bit too
far but it
works
okay a side quest
Rift but kind of one you're probably not
going to miss carrots can I take no
okay cuz you will want to get your horse
this is basically a main
quest lemon
time oh a the horse wanted a carrot a
yeah that's why the carrots are there
that's
cute let's give it as many carrots as we
can four areas
okay is maybe one of them in one of
these chests uh
boxes
oh no can you please make them on top of
them
no yeah get under
them yeah
ow but it's okay I don't get damaged by
it haven't done that in a while it's
very satisfying guys I recommend
it oh hey my buddy is here
ow huh I think I have to open that up
first and that body is actually there to
remind you to use him oh you don't have
to remind me ah twice about
[Music]
that okay you do go higher I was hoping
so it I don't fit oh now I do
[Music]
a damn it a damn it
a difficult
[Music]
Birth please thank you number one un
ech
ech num how do I say here is number one
when can I
Italiano
please doesn't need an article it feels
weird to give it an article because of
the
Uno but I see
Dam it all right all right all right all
right all right let's let's let's do it
the proper
way
oh ha Get
Wrecked Uno would be male yeah I
know carrots there's even so many
carrots down here
you got what I need spit it out
now spit it into my hand if you
must by the way I did not watch the last
uh rings of Power episode yet I wanted
to the last two days but then I don't
know I didn't have enough time and then
I was tired and stuff hoping to watch it
maybe tomorrow cuz toight I'll also be
kind of up late I don't
know I don't know
I wonder if it was
good no I don't think I'll be running
into any thumbnails I haven't had
anything related to that on my
feet on my feet speaking of feet did you
see what the hell
good she dropped her fourth year
anniversary uh solo merch just like that
on
Twitter uh which is also I think
first haven't seen that been done
before but she has freaking like feet
keychain or something like that and like
it's just the
feet it's literally just the
feet
ah I found that to be very
amusing as many of you probably found it
too
[Music]
oh this is a
puzzle you don't understand I think I do
[Music]
understand what this however I don't
understand what maybe I can just wait I
can just
jump get rid of them
completely into the void you go oh
[Music]
yep what what's wrong with the feet guys
maybe I should also do feet
merch otherwise I'll be defeated
haha but there's oh there's no
winning when it comes to G's feet I
cannot win against her I will always be
defeated and then the other thing is
also kind of amusing the shark
tail I guess you just stick it to some
window or so and then you can make it
wobble I mean why not it's
cute I find the feet more to be
something to poke at
very interesting merch Choice
gura very
interesting as your gmate I would like
to have a talk with you about
feet can't believe she released feet
merch but never built the like a a a
foot imprint on the ground like I
suggested her to do back in the day in
Minecraft what is this place
did I already get what was in there and
I just I'm just not registering anything
right
now you remember that I was asking her
to make like a Bigfoot print on the
[Music]
ground I'm too focus on feet yeah always
review feet with her like
oh you're right they did that did
they wait did they reveiew legs or
feet a
horsey oh that was B she should build
that willingly voluntarily when I look
at her merchandise I don't understand
why she
wouldn't feet and greet oh my
God they both legs and feet
I forgot about that um
maybe maybe I wanted to forget
about feet feet feet she likes feet feet
feet feet feet feet feet feet feet feet
are
[Music]
great oh oh
oh let's go lemon what you're
finally gaining another one at level six
did he did she did did yeah you did
right yeah
o I thought it would never happen at
this
point let's
go two fly leaves can
we now we got five now and horse where
is
[Music]
horse it's hiding
somewhere
okay maybe we need a flute
guys do you have a flute the
carrots fresh smell of a
carrot cute it looks like it's
wooden isn't this made out of wood there
it is
why does it have this kind of
texture Play aona song yeah right give
me a
flute flute is
[Music]
good what should I have for
dinner
chicken I'd actually love to have like
freaking McDonald's burger or something
like something just sometimes you really
just want to like a cheap ass low
quality okay not that low quality it I
just mean like not a restaurant quality
Burger not like a non fast food
restaurant quality Burger not chicken
food what the hell right I just want
like oh I just want those
fries the craving is
real it's too real
[Music]
I got my hell fresh order by the way a
day
late
um and I was
worried about the ice in there that's
like cooling the
meat that it would be completely melted
but I was wondering if they put the hell
fresh order the the the boxes into a
fridge when they're storing them to
deliver it the next day cuz they
attempted delivery but apparently failed
even though I was at
home which when it comes to Hell fresh
packages I don't take that
lightly there's food in
there but yeah
um the ice was not completely melted but
I'm still kind of iffy about it there
was some chicken meat in there and I I
don't know
[Music]
man okay
so I don't
I can't learn it so I guess I'll still
always have to like take care where I
leave
it and if it gets completely lost I
guess
I get off I can get it back from the
farm
huh it feel warm when you took it out
not warm but also not as chilly as I
feel like it should
be it was never Frozen to begin with
they're not frozen usually
anyway we wanted to make some more
energy with the salt I guess is that the
only thing that gives you
energy uh
okay I'll make one of
these but then can I do salt and an egg
for example just to make
the or just salt I don't I just want the
energy I don't care much about anything
else but okay I'll make more of these
cuz I have so many mangoes I guess it's
fine you can rip the carrots
out learn the carrot is a if I spawn the
carrot the horse will come
[Music]
hey I have over a
thousand rupees um but not anymore now
it's
[Music]
999 oopsie yeah I don't know what to do
about it the chicken that was at least
the only meat I had in my hell fresh box
this
time but I'm just is not in the mood for
cooking today especially cuz I don't
have time to cook today but if I
want like McDonald's or anything like
that I'll have to end you know early
enough to get some to get
[Music]
some not even to deliver it
I think they don't I don't I don't
think there's nothing until midnight
sorry we
are we suck in
Austria okay but what if I do it like
really far away let me test
this uh
uh how about how about
[Music]
here not every D stre needs to be 7
hours
you're wrong it has to
[Music]
be I my
Mo where did you come
from you're like a
cat
cute all right that works
nice I'm guessing not in a dungeon
though and what about in the
ocean what if I'm like here since we
still have to go here anyway
apparently wait also have you noticed it
doesn't speak it doesn't speak my
language anymore it's just doing horse
noises I'm going to sue their
asses okay this doesn't
work it's not coming
okay one of the islands you
said ah that one
[Music]
okay oh
RMA
RMA yeah your predicament Chief kajara
has been acting strange
[Music]
oh chief chief Kara has been Consulting
chief drad on some matter this isn't
unusual given they were friends long
before they were our Chiefs but we're
used to her relying on all of us seeds
are our too so this makes me feel quite
uneasy lady Zelda can I trouble you to
ask Chief dreat about this mysterious
matter what is going
on is she like in love and she doesn't
understand her feelings so she's like oh
what is this feeling in my
stomach I don't understand it
it's making me
nervous and
anxious Rock
muts oh my God not drama it's
love I'll bring I'll bring all the drama
M Mama all the drama mama with my girls
and my and my back girls in my back
drama M drama m
no the
[Music]
drama it's an espa
song Kpop
gr I'll bring I'll bring I'll bring all
the
Dr the Dr with my girls on my backs my
back the
[Music]
no bation for a few weeks we were
together all the time but now at is I
can't take it avoiding me Whispering
with Kara seriously what is this
about I'm new I'm learning so I can't
that he can't tell me everything still
it's going on all the time
now I'm way fast I'm boiling
over oh D they've got something going on
huh I you want to know where the boss is
I don't know I other River Zora in the
village he's been talking to some of
them maybe they know
something the other River Zora in the
village what do you mean aren't they all
rivor you mean this
[Music]
one you want to know where boss R's gone
to uh only thing I know is that he got a
letter and then ran off in a hurry a
love
letter tellum tellum is going to tell me
huh where the is tellum
he says he ran off what is it what
they're all they're all yapping about
this T might know more about what T went
fishing east of the village thank you
for the
pinky chicken class ticket chicken class
ticket that sounds very economy to me me
own the East fishing in the
East fishing in the East to say
where
here
oh this one's got Drool on their mouth
what's it a teeth tooth never mind it's
a
tooth oh found
him cargo
C
A now you get first first roll tickets
of
[Music]
course you want to know where the boss
has gone off to I don't know he Chief
Kar it's a wild guest but maybe he's
going to the cave in zerov
great for swimming races swimming races
are we going to do a swimming race how
can I win against them what did he say
here okay
okay this is quite the quest way longer
than the other
one your little chicken heart no don't
cheer him out you'll
die don't do it
do I have the swimming things
on I
do I
do go back in here again I'm probably
going to get some swimming cloves or
something right oh they all give me
cloves it's so nice so many cloves
available what are they doing
she and I are going to ask the Chiefs
what's been going on but our timing is
off no no no that was not your accent
what are you
doing is he
proposing yeaha
what brings you
here what you know what said we've been
acting
different no because we're pregant aun
what no you're being weird are you being
are you you are being
weird you know you know please we
shouldn't I want answers now F what's a
big idea avoiding me having secret
messages with K sure I'm new to the job
but it's my job and I want to do the
right for not at
all yeah feels just the same perhaps
some M matters are for Chiefs only but
we are here to be of
assistance
sorry
oh oh this piano music stop it's going
to make me
cry so here's the truth the two of us
have a baby no uh we want to thank the
two of you
not sure how yet but it's our fault you
two were put In Harm's Way during the
crisis we thought it best to put our
heads together just Kara and Dread no
formalities we want their thans to be
personal though we're still trying to
figure out what's
best looks like we bungled it though
didn't mean to make it too worry it's
hard to just be ourselves in matters
where we should speak from the
heart so
ragma thank thank you for saving me I'm
not perfect but I hope I can keep asking
for your
[Music]
support of course nothing would make me
happier thanks to you too you know what
you know me I charge right in and I
don't even see the small stuff so yeah
thanks for keeping me out of message
before I make him Bo never knew you felt
that way H but maybe you could charge in
a little less and look around a little
more
oh my God that's right still I'm a happy
door I'll work twice as hard to keep
things on an even
que blah blah
blah you again you're so cool oh my
God lemon I'm not a lemon at some point
I'd like to meet this round thing you
keep talking about well then come with
me to my next Rift if you want to I'll
throw you right in there I'll dip you in
like your strawberry that I'm dipping
into my chocolate
fountain
spicy a
br a br but I wanted a smooch
misunderstanding that was a
misunderstanding my friend that's not
what I
wanted okay more Ries I see I
see yeah that can be good can be good
can be good
and now that we have done I think all
the available side quests
mostly we shall
buy one upgrade at least probably can
only afford
one chocolate dipped fish sounds
conflicting yeah
ew that doesn't sound good
[Music]
doesn't make sense for them to give
clothes as rewards yeah but they could
have made me a
swimsuit I'll do my sword even though I
kind of want the
[Music]
energy one more
month let's
[Music]
go thank you for being a member for so
long okay that's it these crystals are
hard to come
by let's go to the
volcano
from I wonder if it's from
here oh wait there's a oh wait what is
this what is this this a
farm but should we explore
this can I even no that that was cut off
right kind
of wait no but I feel like I can get
there but is there a point let's
see
kakar
kak oh maybe there's a dungeon
there involved into gold Sean I let's
go man I'm so happy you guys
think I'm worthy of your support for
like four
years thank you not just your support
but like your money thank you
crazy crazy
Lads there it
is thank you and I mean I know there's
certainly a lot of people who wish they
could be in my membership for so long
but it's just not possible financially
honestly it's like a lot to ask 4 years
how much is it I still don't really know
five bucks or 2.5 bucks I don't know but
asking for that each month can really
add up so doing that for 4 years it's
not it's not something that should be
just assumed five okay that's yeah
that's
crazy that's
crazy so I don't expect you guys to ooh
just to support me you know
just every freaking month is
um a lot of course so I understand if
you can't at all even that's fine
too it's not a given is what I'm trying
to
say thank you should join faster it's
fine anytime he keeps on jumping over
his
axe so useless
now we're too low uh too
[Music]
high these pigs look crazy they're so
glowy
too come
on I don't know they're too slow in
their attacks thanks for the membership
gift
I get more from you than from Netflix oh
they raised the Netflix prices
again can't believe
it did it
again don't run away but good Dodge good
Dodge oh there's a there's a camp here
too
oh I can have both out that's
crazy give me attention I'm flying
you're golden too oh my
God can't be memester also thank you
guys yeah fourth anniversary
live
soon ah
soon I can't believe it's like after
this stream oh my god I've been like
prepping so hard so many things for this
moment for this
day
oh finally one's dead there we go ooh
wait there's two camps next to each
[Music]
other be a banger fin the Japan Arc will
pay off well it's been paying off you
know are there two different ones oh
seems like it it's been paying off here
and there already you know but this is
the last thing I
think that I did oh energy
gloves increases the likelihood that
more energy will appear ah okay I was I
was going to hope that it will like
drain my energy slower but this is fine
[Music]
too yeah one has Boomerang mhm exent
gloves
M oh yeah they they messaged they sent
me um an email cuz I guess they saw my
tweet or so days later they were like oh
how can we help you
I don't know man I can't be
[Music]
helped I can't dig when you're
there
ah there's certainly something
there oh let's go good job
just one but that's
[Music]
fine I was about to sing my
song
to stamp to the
right wait I want to check here too
[Music]
a game that lives up to its name that
true but as I said last time I don't
even think that it doesn't make
sense uh just because you play link
doesn't mean it can't be the Legend of
Zelda but if you think about who's more
legendary link or Zelda I think it's
link so he should should be in the title
if you play as
him foreview of the first song on The
Mirage that was no no
no that's not what I'm going to be
performing well by the way I'm going to
start like probably 5 minutes
[Music]
early and then have like one minute
loading
screen and then there's um
the intro is 6
minutes the intro is 6 minutes and 16
seconds that's why I'm going to start 5
minutes
early but then the live is like 57
minutes so it will end before the full
hour it's a long intro it's don't worry
it's not just a video uh of like you
know music playing and pictures flying
in and the name being written there no
no no no I had a very special idea that
I'm quite proud of it's very
special very
special you were trying to make me think
that there's nothing
there w
3D
hey
no
nothing now the intro will be fun it's a
very special one I had this like genius
idea as I always do miners always have
these genius Strokes that comeback from
La was so funny yesterday good job La
that's that's a good
comeback I'm getting a heart
stroke are you okay lder
ah I'm not
okay okay now we go in unless is there
something on the left what do you think
there could be ah yeah there probably
is her heart was challenged she streamed
heart Challenger a little bit too much
it
seems not my fault I appreciate the
streams though
[Music]
no that's
it stop messing around with me I am the
hero the legendary hero of all times
Zelda lemons more lemon juice
yummy okay wait should we go over there
too I still haven't checked out out that
freaking hole in the spawn
area I should have just gone for it I
should have committed never mind we're
fine flying Ty and
prey yeah I'm I'm using it more now cuz
it does seem to be very
useful now we return hopefully we will
arrive ah
ah we
did
[Music]
no ah no don't
scream why would you do
[Music]
that obliterated
it's like I'm playing Oblivion or
something nothing beat the ground
pound that's it what about the holes I
want to check out the holes is there
nothing
there just teleported me
out usually there's nothing like that
there though so I guess we can
go we're doing so much extra
stuff today
wow I have so many mentions let me check
Discord right now oh my
[Music]
God
a
ky you are so
sweet she says she's planning to raid
into my stream cuz she's starting a
stream like three hours before my life
starts
and she told me she's planning to raid
into my um fry live stream she's going
to play until
then
yeah so
[Music]
KN she's a keeper yeah hell yeah she
is I knew it
I knew it from the getg
go thanks for the membership
welcome
uh uh yeah um I asked my director to put
some stuff together for NG outakes but
yeah I got something but it wasn't as
much as I would have hoped and
apparently there was just not that much
recorded behind the scenes this time I
still upload what I have for members
only but it's not going to be as
much I
[Music]
think but at least the opening is sick
hello n guy
hey you want to play again huh all right
then let's do it I can jump high now so
not many obstacles that you can give me
I would say mm
nuts
nuts nuts nuts yeah yeah yeah I think I
can reach all of that nuts nuts oh that
one will need my
platform but that's okay what oh I see
okay thank you 16 acorns yeah that's a
lot in 1
minute should be fine
[Music]
with my froggy ring I can do
anything oh almost missed that
[Music]
one oh I see I see there's one down
there so the last
one wait I didn't even I didn't even
think about turning
but I could have spined spun I think
he's happy with my time is
he one Ruby anything
else Lightning Fast yeah one time bonus
oh n this broken trap still has sharp
pointy teeth it's too dangerous to use
in the state
hey
what oh it's one of those
items wait horse I forgot we'll do it
another time
and I don't want to unless
it's I forgot about the horse game we
have the horse
now I guess I'll
go we still have something to do here oh
also I hope that area just now I hope
that was just a mini game and nothing
else to explore cuz I didn't really look
around
circles yeah yeah our good old boy
circles but this is not
circles I know it's probably confusing
but it's a
pona hello Tim King so
cute you're so cute let me Grill you let
me Grill you
you're so chunky you need to be grilled
it would be a waste if I wouldn't
[Music]
o uh no what about the mini
game what
[Music]
H I guess it's just
outside
hey where is this
[Music]
game were you able to Dash with a
different horse I think you could only
Dash with this horse
huh hello somebody go outside talk while
on horse okay
okay Princess Zelda you decided to stop
by you can take part in the flag races
if you want we're try on horses with
these FL would you like to take
[Music]
part okay this is your first flag race
so let's start off with the short course
by the way if you feel like you have a
lot of eyes on you that's probably
because there's these H life girls that
bet on horses and they watch you know
these horse races with their viewers
together ever so don't feel pressured at
all there's like thousands of people
betting on you and watching you like
some vtubers or something I'm not sure
what that means but yeah they're really
into
horses so yeah just just uh watch the
course you know you can do
it
oh
okay I think the horse jumps
automatically over obstacles I don't
know if it can jump over
the trees I would say no but the chests
[Music]
maybe
yeah
no it's hard to
control okay at least wein the time
doing the extra time on these is such a
pain oh God I can
[Music]
imagine does she want under 20 that
would still be realistic under 18 or so
might be
rough under
[Music]
17 this course under 7
but I am 16 going on
17y the bonus objective is only on the
first one
difficult well yeah don't hit the trees
mhm well I was worried that I'll you
know have troubles with the mangoes too
but it became really easy really fast so
I wonder if I should try to not jump
over the boxes and just dodge them
wonder if it slows me down at
[Music]
all can I go through here no I
can't CLA CL enough but not quite but I
see the
possibility don't forget the ability
what
ability what about what the abil what
what what the ability do I push the vase
while I'm on the horse I didn't even try
doing that
before you mean the tree right grabbing
the
trees it's a good idea
but then I'll have to drop them I
guess won't I have to turn a little bit
to then drop them off not right in front
of my
face let's
try difficult
[Music]
[Applause]
I
want but I somehow I still managed to be
relatively fast
uh what I don't know what I was
doing like it was confusing
me it was getting in the
way don't Dash into turns
yeah that's just something someone would
know who's race
sir we got butter oh
thanks we're close to the
time I'll try one more time without
grabbing
maybe and I'll try to not be Speedy on
the curves except for this first one uh
I I I I'll I'll speed up right
before do the flags load up my Dash or
am I just imagining that sensation
[Music]
um one
second one
second I feel yeah I mean I wasn't I
didn't make any real mistake but I guess
it could have been a little bit better
in how I took the curves and
stuff after you touch each flag but for
the last flash flag Dash as early as you
can before touching it so you can have
one more Dash right
before touching
it at each flag but then before the last
flag after each flag but then before the
last flag you mean but then what about
but yeah that yeah okay dash at the
beginning then dash at each flag and
then Dash before the last flag well
okay so that I can dash one more
time at the end
a see that curve it doesn't seem perfect
I'm like
unsure that was a
mistake that was a mistake I got too
excited I thought I could do it but no I
shouldn't have dashed
there but you sh at each
flag but not there because it's at the
Curve
[Music]
M would do this immediately with no
problems right she would first try
this I wish I was a horse
girl I wish I was a horse
girl don't listen to us we're only
chickens no you do sometimes sometimes
you have good advice
too okay that already felt
better now I wait with this one until I
have the curve then I go diagonally and
then not sure what I that
[Music]
sorry that's a weird timing what do you
mean okay okay okay got another 15
milliseconds I think the the beginning
of the course I did quite well
optimizing it Min maxing
it you dragged the last vase what do you
mean
vase you mean the tree right a the
because they're in a vase that's what
you mean dragging it yeah maybe the last
one let me
see those yeah but I feel like it will
just stop me in my tracks
again but I'll see what I can
[Music]
do damn it but oh my God Mom my time was
what how how did I get so slow again at
the end thought I almost had it no no no
no okay okay okay I
try but I feel like it's possible
without Ultra
handing it should be it's got to
be you I have to
[Music]
okay you stop dashing after jumping do
you
really the dash is just really short I
think
I need one more
Dash but I can't dash at the curve so
it's something about the timing at the
very end about I'm not really I I
literally just come out of a dash I
don't think I can Dash earlier at the
end unless I figure out how to dash over
the
[Music]
curve but I don't think I need to do
that
wait I got I don't know how I fumbled
and I still kind of did my best
time
[Music]
what I missed the
tree do we need on the
[Music]
tree I drifted I don't think I drifted
with my
horse that would be sick
though turn on some Europe be remix of
this song
[Music]
oh this time is good
no oh oh I can I
can I got better
again 12
milliseconds 12 milliseconds
bro this one's so tight
[Music]
getting a lot of butter
though horse stops when you make the
last
jump it does why does it do
that should I move the crate instead ah
should I move the crate
all right all right okay okay then that
one will be easy because I can just move
straight I don't think that it'll be in
my way you know that was my worry when
we're still in front of a curve and
taking the tree with
us here we go horse race a takanasi
Kiana is in it once again the whole life
girls have her back they believe in her
she can do it for sure she got carrots
in her pocket that ah motivating her
horse but she kind of got over
again oh no we all believed in there but
now we're losing all our bets but she's
using this as a practice run now it
seems and she up even
more all the supporters of tak's horse
circles have been disappointed today but
maybe next time circles can get back the
hearts of the viewers the hearts of the
lovers of the
horses what happened we need to analyze
the situation what went
wrong was it her nerves that got to her
or did the nerves get to the horse
H you know usually the the heart of the
Rider and the horse connect when they
are in a Race So their nerves influence
each other's nerves it is quite
common so they both have to be as
relaxed as
possible to make this race a perfect
one can she do it this time can she or
will she waste more money of the whole
life rubbers
from cak
Corp the investors are crying already at
the
prospect but it seems like perhaps she
can do it this time
a what happened there what is happening
cuz she ah she grabs it too early that's
when the horse is thinking it's still
supposed to jump over it and then there
this big BM boole happens
seems like she has reached Enlightenment
now and
[Music]
understands she needs to grab it earlier
and then Dash
[Music]
okay is there your repeat version of
like a different other
song wait I can just say no thanks each
time why am I always asking for
explanation
I'm losing my investors my STS no
[Music]
I waited for the dash because you
somebody said I think to wait but I I I
need to dash I think
earlier I don't know know then I'm too
fast to really grab it I don't
know try the last try so you don't have
to do that curve
what what
[Music]
the last
tree
[Music]
tree oh that was a bad
Dash ah
know what the I don't
know I don't know what I'm supposed to
do I'll still have to jump over the
Box what I don't really understand this
sucks lady this absolutely sucks your
flag rate sucks
[Music]
jumping box is
fine
okay
[Music]
okay let me just I wish there was a redo
button I don't want to talk to you he's
freaking
[Music]
time stop why is she nodding so
much 17 12
man don't say this is the Run don't
say
no why do I spam the B button hm why do
I do it there's nothing I can do about
this
[Music]
I don't
know I don't
know I forgot about the tree I got un
sure it was a good time though
still have you tried restarting your
horse off and on
[Music]
again you did it without tree
[Applause]
here we go here we go no more Hing
around that was a good
curve wait for
it go for it
[Music]
I've been doing this all day
until my Frey life it
seems
what what
[Music]
that was not my best time no no it was
32 I
did 12
before 17:32 what's just
now I did better
before meow meow me meow me meow meow
[Music]
why did I do that why did I do that I
hate
myself I wanted to try I wanted to
[Music]
experiment I'll try like two more
times and if I still can't make it I'll
try off off stream
no no
no
go horse horse horse horse horse horse
horse horse horse horse horse horse
horse horse what the are you seeing
ghosts or something why did I do that
why I don't know why I do that so don't
count this
[Music]
one why did it jump
though I was did just jumped over air it
got me out of it I was
[Music]
like don't quit you can practice the end
I know but I feel so
stupid horse horse horse horse horse
horse horse horse horse horse horse
horse horse horse horse
horse it did the trees intimidate
me the trees intimidate me I'm so scared
of
them wasting my time going around the
box but I thought it stops the dash
and I should try and avoid
[Music]
them what last jump I'm always dashing
when I
can
no okay let's try again to jump over the
boxes then
okay even the first one
[Music]
yeah I guess it stops the
dash it didn't make me faster that's for
sure it certainly did not not make me
faster do I need this much butter lady
what do you think give me some milk
instead for once you're milking my
wallet after
[Music]
all save your last dedge for after the
jump okay but
[Music]
horse what horse horse horse horse horse
I'm going around so that I can not stop
dashing
[Music]
I'm going
to try something like
[Music]
that this run will be
bother they did it by hugging the inner
walls well I like to hug them too you no
but they hate me
ah also there's obstacles there I'd have
to move like all the
trees is that what they
[Music]
do why did I
what's wrong
with bye
you five five five five five
[Music]
why is she so
annoying yeah I'll try to pick up the
tree I'll try to pick up the tree pick
up the tree
no I know the course I Know
It Go
[Music]
hor I don't know sometimes you just like
hold your hand just like get stuck and
you're like not sure what to do where to
drop
[Music]
I'm becoming a horse girl slowly I
think falling into the horse
hole What will what will happen to
me I don't know
[Music]
I
what what what
[Music]
why do you hate
me give me some
like oh two Mill oh I'm so sorry of
course 0.1 no
this is the strictest mini game in this
game should have dashed
what I hate my life this game hates
[Music]
[Laughter]
me well if I never pick up the flag I
can forever practice here
[Music]
oh nice music never heard it that
much the good thing is that the
trees she won't even attempt to jump
over them because they're too tall so I
can't fumble like I can with the like
you know jumping even though I'm picking
it up with the
chests new
[Music]
record yeah sure at least you won't get
better are we happy about that okay here
we go here we
go what am I going to do I'm nervous
what do I
[Music]
what what a you
ston Rising
again I am one with the horse I am a
horse girl
wow I took two trees baby I'm ripping
out those trees you can blame me for
deforestation yeah baby oh my God
free free M
crystals that was worth a heart
container by far oh it's not over yet
guys it's not over two it took me 200
rupes I didn't even want to look at that
why did you tell me such a devastating
fact 25 seconds okay well I have a lot
more experience
[Music]
Now show me the course oh my oh my God
oh God 25 seconds for
that what is wrong with
you is there a
hack um
[Music]
like how can I move it to the
sign well you know oh hey I made it
before 25
seconds
okay should I
should I try
without what's the time you want
eh what I get this okay heart container
is the last
thing 20 seconds that's
manageable that was the first time I
wrote that course so I still very
uncertain wait there's a long course
what what
what what do I get in the long course
what do I get here do I just get blue
crystals
again oh okay well those trees that are
right in the middle I feel like I should
move them but maybe just the last one
[Music]
yo I was logged in in the horse Zone I
was horsed in I was a
horse baby yeah yeah yeah can you
believe that this one's so easy oh and
then the other one what
what
what this needs to be patched in tendo
that needs to be
patched you say there's a long
race the first one outside the rench and
then the truck oh do I go from outside
to inside why do you hate
me why do you hate me
will they combine the 17 seconds with
the 20 seconds oh my God
what what what that's very
confusing
okay eight
Flags oh I shouldn't have dashed in the
very
beginning oh ah right okay uh well you
know what maybe that was fine
[Music]
okay well that won't
work wait there's 50 seconds for this
[Music]
wow I still need to get the Nord of
course so excuse me for not dashing
ideally what what what who w w
[Music]
well I made the 50
seconds I made the 50
seconds so at least we're not losing
anything cuz we're getting some reward
right what are we
getting okay we getting some
money she has the audacity to only give
me 50 after she took over 300 or so
wait what did she say something about
record time or is there no more for the
long one I would I mean what else would
we get when we already got a heart
container 40 seconds oh okay but maybe
we just we'll get like a golden rupee or
so because we already got a heart
[Music]
container so we just
had something like 43 or so that's very
very do
able right not Dash in the beginning I
think Dash
now maybe
[Music]
move that one's a bit
rough nice the way I went in there that
was a hor horsing
professional ain't no horsing oh
horsing around
here ah close close close close oh wait
we can do it oh my
God the first course was just absolute
troll they were trying to scare me off
of the other
courses
what what do I get money
a charging horn we this charm made of
strong horn while riding horses to power
up their
charges what you mean my
dashes
oh H what where is
it ah here
[Music]
no no no no no never again
no I was going to test who the hell are
you I'm testing my
horse you what is he why is he carrying
a a wrench you got is really important
to me now be a good little bir wait is
he the guy who wants the monster or Stu
you you me the crow I promise I won't be
mad if you give it back
now wa you little I know you can hear me
you're ignoring me the great Dum
damp like my pants the most genius
inventor in all of viru stop being a p
and give me my
key don't for nothing if I don't get the
key
B the key why do you need the key if you
have
K hey oh
oh you're coming down I didn't expect
that
[Music]
somehow was he trying to destroy my
ground pound
machine cute attempt
B you were on his back and just decided
to not go for it what's wrong with Y all
these birds see this is why I
hate the birds they suck they're just
not doing anything
[Music]
oh is that a
gravekeeper thank you defeating that
wildy Crow and getting me my KY I was so
busy being angry with that crow that I
forgot about introductions I damn the
most genius inventor in all I already
know an inventor and I don't know if I
need any of your inventions
but we'll see what do you
have I suppose being the only automaton
engineer also makes me the best are you
the creator of CeCe anyway you seem
pretty tough good much uh experience
defeating monsters maybe lady is the one
who really make
the you are the one who needs those
stones
right my house is real funky okay yeah
you are yeah you are that's the guy
that's definitely the guy now let me see
my
Dash oh that's probably at least longer
than before if not faster I don't
[Music]
know o is it that automat engineer dump
damp graveyard what the
hell all right then we shall finally
proceed to somewhere else
Dash damages enemy more did it ever
damage enemies I don't think it ever did
before wow it damages me too okay maybe
just because it was
[Music]
jumping left have I been in here
before I I don't I don't got time to
check I'm sorry
what's up in
here oh princess hello I'm here under
King's orders to help look into the
Ro sorry I looked at their faces they
look
[Music]
funny digging spot I missed one oh well
another
time yeah that one did damage when I was
riding into it um the Villers say that
roofs have appeared in Elden volcano and
up in gor City apparently the Gorn
haven't been spared and all this either
the gns have always been good neighbors
we're pretty worried about them they got
a new leader recently but that's all
I've heard we don't know how to help
them we love to help them with the r but
we're not cut out for the terrain and
monsters up there that does appear to be
all we know
[Music]
yourness
SK cool
[Music]
thanks let me place my fancy ass bat
here to make
everybody uh Jealous by the way I
switched
um pillows again and I think
it's not a new pillow but the pillow I'm
using now it's it's it's a bit better on
my neck I think I still have like weird
issues I should I think if I stretch a
little bit more again in combination
with that pillow I think I I'll I'll get
better
again yeah but it's been it's been a
little bit more comfortable with that
pillow so I've cycled through all of
them again to find one that kind of fits
[Music]
chy and they're growing grapes here how
nice
wow W what's this
[Music]
place wait maybe he needs the de the the
monster Stones I don't
know oh yeah oh yeah this gives me Wind
Waker vibes
[Music]
Hy you seem to like circles just like
me
do don't answer voice put on your
listening ears I can't do this voice
forever I mean read
normally the only don't Where You Train
Dreams this is reading normal by the way
I know I know training makes it sound
like a spiritual joury or whatever but
it's real simple first I show you a
dream an astounding dream based on your
life then within the dream you defeat
all the FES trying to get
[Music]
you cuz I'm fine I'm all right
me my life boy I'll get get
get get down my life boy get out my life
boy Bam Bam get out my life boy oops
deleted your
[Music]
number yeah um
sorry each training session has a go
time beat that go and I'll have a
special no not more Min
[Music]
games join up now and no all your
training sessions are free of charge oh
my God what do this
deal but there's even more oh my God if
you keep on your training there will be
an astounding reward as proof of your
skill all right are you ready to do some
training yeah am I supposed to do that
as Link
[Music]
Link you're will then you're Now
official student of the Slumber doj can
we sleep is that the training no okay
cuz we do it in our dreams oh ooh go
gold okay there's gold
times I'm not doing all of that now I'll
do that another time or maybe even off
screen honestly oh but you get the sword
huh but it's not usable probably so what
the
hell I was just making his
laugh are you looking for a
chicken H she is I know the face of
Terra when one of your chickens is Apes
I just recognized that so
easily all I saw was her face and that
she's looking for something I knew it
was a
chicken forget horse girl I'm back to
chicken
Lady B BG please come
back oh you could you let me a hand for
some reason my dear sweet cucko cucko
decided to escape all on the fence this
morning they're running away from me the
little Rebels I should put them in the
usual room what do you mean you have a
usual room too if you manag to get a
hold of my cus what can you put them
back into this
pen there are five cus total C is that
their word for
chicken okay cute we do one of them
right the other
back in there you Gober safe for you we
just want you to be safe are they also
outside of this or are they all inside
the city
still maybe they're also in
houses no carrot cake M looks
good the only city
okay a species in here okay oh
chicken good chicken don't go away
he's like oh no not her that's my
nightmare that's my biggest nightmare
that
[Music]
lady I'm guessing they're not in houses
are what a cute cat that's a fluffy
[Music]
one it's got some nice pretty eyes too
and who are you
[Music]
Grandma refreshing grapes would really
hit the spot have I can give you some
but you're not asking me for any also
that oven looked crazy in there
[Music]
damn had a feeling you would be up there
uh being sad about all the chickens you
have lost in your life so far chickens
who have been killed before you is this
still the city I don't think so
[Music]
yeah but I got to go up again I'm sure
upright is probably the last
one chicken crying at the cemetery
chickens you're not supposed to get
sentimental when you cry you're going to
lose all your
[Music]
juiciness chicken
last
chicken I'm guessing it's over here this
is not the city anymore no let me go
back you interrupted my quest
lemon no
no reminds me
of the
horrors of the volcano area and Skyward
[Music]
Sword wow that's a big mountain but
there should be somewhere I can make a
rift entrance up there I wonder where we
can find the
gor uh yeah but what about the
chicken cute a should leave it there it
just wants to go k Kitt in the
morning I'll rescue you though maybe
it's scared up there maybe it didn't
want to be up
there no no you're going to get crushed
quick get out
of my presentence saved you don't worry
about it don't wor Don't
Panic it's oh it's going to be all right
isn't that relaxing flop flop flop flop
that's so relaxing we should do more of
that anyway maybe now we'll learn how to
make a chicken after this
Quest it defeated the masch no no it was
my present I saved you yeah Eternal
sa you still missing
one did one leave
again what is there another one on the
roof
me still missing one oh maybe up here
too that's a cat can I'll talk to this
cat
to
hi
no I got stuck I
[Music]
think is that your cat BL hard enough to
make the windmill spin
uh no I don't think that's you
can I do more
speed no
okay H where is this
chicken it can't be
there we need to look at
it from a chicken point of you
[Music]
ah I didn't consider this
area
oopsy don't tell W I'm hiding it's over
for you back into the fryer you go yipp
I'm so grateful please come this
[Music]
way she going to give me a chicken
burger or what
hello I am so glad my C are all back as
for why they ran away in the first place
I think they were looking for a place
called kfp I don't
know grapes can I summon them with
grapes
now
what a third fairy
bottle okay did you know if you live a
CUO over your head and jump from a high
place you Glide from the air really I
suppose you could do that with any wi
creature don't try it with the cat
though got you
thanks is the Ocarina
refence just like an Ocarina of Time you
get a bottle
mm what can we buy here is there
something specific
here a a belt or a bracelet
Leever
B we don't we already have something for
climb I don't really need anything to
climb faster I have potions
too I don't think I'll need that I don't
know if I want to waste my money on that
ever we'll see how it
faes when we're climbing up the stairs
H yeah uh St oh God I'll do the other
Quest later I want to do some dungeon
now because I feel
like we've been definitely doing a lot
but so much side stuff we got to do some
main stuff
[Music]
now hey
you why the long face huh do you say
that in
English it's a stupid saying huh
do you say that at
all
yeah so such a weird say isn't
it are these new ones not that I want
them to be
honest the Strat is so op can't tell me
nothing it's a new one
[Music]
okay don't really want to learn it but
okay just going to spam my um monster
[Music]
inventory we are officially on the Elden
volcano Trail let's go I feel like this
is the wrong path but I still want to
check it out because my RPG senses are
tingling like tingle tangle bul what
tingle tangle that's
Simpsons
interesting there's nothing here
huh I think what I was really trying to
say is Tingle oh wait there's something
here from uh different Zelda
game oh wait he's got a different name
in
in English on Simpsons
huh yeah it's the crazy
guy some kind of crazy guy this was not
quite worth it cuz I've never used a
monster Fang
before but yeah of course my senses
work uh
oh what do I spy oh nothing in
particular okay
all right then let's go to the main
path wasn't necessary
okay tingle tangle
B okay at least I can be somewhat
ignored is it going to be
hot in
here ah
[Music]
um I don't
know eh Get Wrecked oh they're kind of
cute with their question marks not
knowing what's going
on and I like how they jump oh there's
one more
here no more speed no more speeda bugs
you're
terrifying apparently some ladies are
terrified of you me too I saw you I Ally
would be
terrified
okay got nothing for that though no
reward to be
[Music]
seen can I go up there no
such Destruction has never been seen
before perhaps she's not a hero after
all
but
evil
s she must be
sour even the last tiniest innocent bug
squashed by her magical hands with no
mercy even if there is nothing to be
gained
[Music]
flamethrower
fun H
climbing all righty
[Music]
how do we go about that it's burning
Well for now PE
hat do
[Music]
something wait I need to wait for it to
come
closer yeah the potatoes aren't worth it
but the feeling of having done evil is
so worth it let me tell
you feels
good feels good to be bad
sometimes squashing the
bugs bullying things that are smaller
than
me what are you you look like you're
from Metroid
Prime what
H leave him no chance leave him no
opening
[Music]
ow
thos they look like from Metroid Prime
in this game is it just me
[Music]
ooh there we
go yeah the space pirates
mhm you get it you get
me you just get
MEP why I love you
I have this feeling it will still take a
while until we are allowed to enter the
rift but what can I do but make my way
towards it in a hurry
not too long compared to previous
CHS greetings from
[Music]
grat what's good
ah wonderful what a flower
flower
flowery wearing one makes fairies appear
occasionally when you cut grass and not
plants sheh but honestly with Free
bottles and the opportunity to always
fill them
up m
M I think we don't need
it but it's pretty nice to have an extra
accessory isn't it
lovely what is that can I learn that
doesn't seem like
it foda yeah
Fi not Fiora
hot hot hot hot hot hot hot
hot it goes higher
oh who there we go that's what I like to
see Stones falling down in gonia or not
really gonia yet I
guess well that's a lot of St ow owow
there's a cave down there have about
been in it when I see the cave sign does
that mean I've been in it would it
otherwise not be there I haven't paid
attention to
that oh what the hell are
you tee wasth a mistake it's a new wind
monster no careful
I can't I can't learn it I can't there
we
go the sign doesn't change so so are
they
always ah you promised me I could get
over there maybe if I jump as well
what what is this
[Music]
illusion don't trust those
add the wings as she wants me to carry
something with wings
well I feel like I'm going to get turned
into fried Phoenix if I walk over there
maybe I need some I know exactly what I
need never mind don't worry
B I would
say honestly the thing we just learned
is fine too but I think my wind machine
is more useful for that where's my wind
machine
ah but what about
me I
forgot does it go on again no
then D it don't matter but now I can get
rid of it can I get rid of it while I oh
she can climb with one
hand
sheesh oh you use water block
my my thing is better wow thank you what
does it say com the head oh really this
is a really um hard to access
City harder than if you think about it
this feels harder than in other Zelda
games where they it's like they don't
want to be
accessed by other people
access did you miss the chest no I saw
it but yeah I wasn't sure which
direction to go all right I'll go there
first before I
be ah
no a
f although we'll have to do this again
it seems
but I can't control
them that
[Music]
oh oh wait maybe from
here
no maybe I should put myself a wind
machine there
too or just anything I guess I don't
want to let go of him though I like how
they're all following me okay
um one of you come here
now yeah you yeah oh
you
hey come back to me I had you in my
hands
ah
no
okay yay I don't know how you guys did
this if you did but my solution is nice
just going to say my solution is
superior come on
pick me
[Music]
up y'all fired y'all are
fired I don't want to do this again
nice I can just toss
it
perfect can't trust BBS yeah I don't
know really I'm really
trustworthy except the chickens chickens
are
trustworthy no you can't change the
tiles Direction midair as far as I know
[Music]
okay good clear ooh the chest was here
should I have gone left for the city or
is this the right
way oh yeah yeah we're there we're
basically there
can I do this while no okay I can't
shoot while climbing Zelda can make
magic while she's climbing
so she seems to be more capable wait but
he can use his sword while fighting okay
okay I'll take it back I was going to
say Zelda is more talented with one
hand
[Music]
ah I okay
I'll send my
own probably at the
end maybe I'll use my torch
slug oh how do I make it go on the
wall oh there it is it's on the Hello
look
up oh well these are just you're
distracting it thanks yippe we reached
it stamp
time we filled it
[Music]
up do I got to reward
again how did I do his
voice hi and howy St guy here uh I've L
St since I was an inting guy now's
greatest expert you fil up another card
she your next reward is promise you've
got a KN for two stamps four stamps who
knew You' you do so
well really
xeg hey what a time really moved I feel
like I should SP all the secrets of my
past what not interest oh sorry in
for next Co shock that legit look look
like something good I would
draw but honestly her Doodles are so
cute just roasting her but the Doodles
are so
cute I love goba
[Music]
Doodles all right let's get the
teleportation let me check out this
corner over here ah
ah I could have gone up here but I
wasn't really missing out on
anything okay
something's throwing bombs oh these
flying thingies are from oh no get me
oh okay danger zone volcano spring a I
want to go to hot spring again
maybe if I get to Japan in the winter
this time maybe I'll take a quick trip
to hokido or so
again honestly you know I I I talk about
not liking onen because I'm embarrassed
but I I really like the vibe of onson
with the
snow
no it's just
so soothing and
like you
know
mythical but at this point I honestly
don't know when I'll be back I have some
plans but it looks like my plans are
falling apart which is
great so I'm not sure right
[Music]
now do I have anything
new
no then I don't know what to make
oh they had the same guys in Link to the
Past of course he's one of the
gorens it's no time for
h no no a Roi sprung up and a bunch of
my friends fell in and on top of that D
fell in after he shouted that he'd save
for friends but he got too close and the
rift swallowed him up ah oh D and you
just became the
chief let's get to work out oh she's
stressing me out this lemon why you can
fix Rift oh yeah right I'm not I'm not
hiding my identity anymore at all I
guess cuz hyro doesn't give a
anymore I don't need to hide myself from
these people either huh so we can be
honest from the
GetGo my thoughts of immediately going a
different
direction those were in breath of the
wild
yeah thank you so much for helping us
this is the ri that's to all Chief Dar
and our
friends all right okay let me go
straight in stop crying what the h
oh he he looks like I don't know how to
describe that like he's into leather and
studs like maybe a biker Goron but not
quite where's the biker jacket my man oh
there's a cave there or a
house okay I I'll go to the rift first
let's just do the ri
[Music]
first he's the boss of this G is a gym
is a gym
what is it really a
gym Pokemon gym yeah it's the rock
gym time for a cracker
cracking some
rocks
what
what ah
[Music]
okay let's try to deal with
them good thing is their bombs will
always thanks to
um the the thing that keeps things on
the
ground thanks to that it will always
fall down so it can't hit my fly
leaf we're still taking a while to kill
it gravity yeah oh no we didn't even get
to kill it I went in too
early
oh this looks kind of like some mini
game or so
[Music]
oh I can do only one at a time otherwise
I could spam them a little bit like time
them it's kind of a cute
idea the way they I said it lose why
didn't I said it
lose do
something bomb ability this time yeah it
feels like it's leading up to it
but it was kind of weird that link
didn't show up in the last dungeon
really cuz like you started to think
that he'd show up in every single one
but then you would think okay but
there's probably more Dungeons and
abilities that link can give you so they
just skipped it once and now I guess
they'll go back to it
they just interrupted the rivm a little
bit to bambooz
us
oh
no that's what I'm trying to do no stay
there please I'll hold you
[Music]
I should just do it from above
huh oh is that just a
pun just a
jelly okay uh just because I'm worried
that I'm missing some treasure let me
get rid of these two or like a hole in
the wall secret
hole hidden
okay we're probably
fine wait I feel like I should have
gotten something in here
though
H or was that the first one I got I'm
just I just my memory is like so
bad maybe I did get
something I'm just not realizing
I did I did get lemons in there how am I
forgetting
this takanashi
[Music]
Grandma brain empty no thoughts that
describes my vibe today
perfectly seems I have given up on using
water blocks
completely we're back to ground pound
machines
lemons ooh cam nle M with hot vanilla
sauce that's also one of those
typical um o h food Foods Foods on the
on the Alpine
Huts one of the foods I couldn't think
of in the moment but uh is one of the
foods I mean when I'm talking about
going skiing I'm having a
nice hot dessert on the mountains that
was it
[Music]
h no I prefer the hot vanilla sauce I
like hot vanilla sauce unlike
everything
everything kaisman yeah I think kaisman
is
still my preferred
dessert but I eat it way more than gamol
because gamol is not as as common as
kaash I think depends on where you go I
[Music]
guess just a little little tiny oo
I don't want to leave yet I want to see
is did I no wa I already climbed in
there never mind I was going to say let
me climb into this pot gon pot next to
me but I think I've been in there in the
beginning
[Music]
mhm those are some nice eyebrows you got
wow so Square they look like key Caps or
I don't know something something a
button that I can push like I can push
his eyebrows
in FAA sending a season desist wait I
got five DMS
again what's up ah oh my
God thank you
pasal here we go here we go here we go
here we
go B and the RO orang
sight but they all look C fun that one's
got red hair and like clown hair on the
sides of his
head she she really did
it let's
go what happened I remember there was a
r for when I want to check it
out oh you made it back
too yeah the rift's gone and everyone's
back home
so and she's the one that saved
[Music]
you you
did I hate their belly buttons
sorry thank you thank you so much what
your
name what see they do the other kingdoms
arew of Zelda I just said that Zelda and
he immediately gets
it those freaking ladies in the desert
they didn't get
it they had no respect they they were
not educated in the royal families of
this
land it isn't their belly button
really I think it is
though it's a pleasure to meet you
well Dar you recently appointed chief of
the
GS and who's your floaty friend oh you
see him oh yeah right Tre oh nice to
meet
you his cheeks where
purle wait a sec I don't see El fever
what I can't make so many different of
these voices ma m Mia
The Rock roast once again comes into
play
huh Chef told me something Shed off at
the's B so he went to
check CH what do we do we got to find
him give me a second to
think I can't just search randomly got
to do something though better check the
Slate again the manual of How To Be Boss
oh I know I know listen everyone I'm
going to find our friends myself so you
all should wait here look it's of wisdom
number 42 don't stop when it's school
time I sound like
[Music]
shinan of wisdom nuggets of
chicken D Sho seems different from the
leaders of the gudo Andora huh I wonder
where he
went he's new to this give him a
[Music]
break I want to try to take off the lid
I don't think I
can I got to check out these
rooms
noise hot spring bathtub continuously
hot
[Music]
this doesn't seem like a gym to me isn't
this just like maybe the place for
the closest to the boss like the Elders
or whatever of
gonal this quite
messy I like I like the vibe in here oh
you sell Rock potatoes and rock salt who
would have
thought but you got no special other
item cu the climbing item is in the in
kak
let go time where do I
go
a I got to find everyone who's missing
but how maybe I should consult this L
again think Dar the
think let this beautiful Maiden assist
you and do everything for
you oh is the golden CH 56 nuggets that
k eats every day uh there 56 motos that
Ki eats every
day wow
56 yeah it's a lot but she um is hungry
you know without those nuggets she would
starve so maybe there's more to it than
just those nuggets maybe there's some
real wisdom behind them now my father
was a previous Chief he's not here
anymore is there anything else you'd
like to know about my slate
no I really don't care about you
slate we've been going around mending
the rips we're looking for a big one
nearby do you know where it might
be the biggest RI is at the crater but
you can't get close cuz of all the
poison gas in the
wa wait I once heard there's a shortcut
to the crater
somewhere I don't know the details but
the ERS call and might proba is they're
both missing oh what do we
do hang on a
sec could you to maybe help me look for
everyone who's still missing I know I'm
Che for I don't know what the hell I
should do so the elders were supposed to
headed to the rock rock rose quy on the
northwest and the
okay poison G it's realistic now
huh you should hand
first yeah let's just do it and surprise
him with the result afterwards
guessing something's over here so let's
go I'm just going to maybe just walk by
these not going to waste my time with
them oh yeah I do I have to fight those
no right I don't think so what are
those fire Octor Roo do they shoot
fire or fire
Stones okay about to tell you you're
amazing well it seems like I don't need
to convince you with my amazingness
anymore but if you want to see more of
that then please watch my frd live in uh
soon time how does this work not at all
okay how does this work ow that's so
rud ah ah
[Music]
ah Mama mia how do I get
them how do I get over there tell me
maybe oh I need to grab them though
they're too
low I guess I should kill one that's
outside here
[Music]
no no no no
no how am I going to grab them do I have
wind would bind work yep
[Music]
maybe
no okay first see that was a that's a
good reaction of
me
quickly getting a cool head again really
quickly otherwise I would have died
probably what small rock
enemy I already tried water in the lava
but
didn't
work oh wait um you mean an actual rock
can I can they sink a little bit
oh m
oh oh you come back oh that was a
surprise okay but
now um
oopsie oh but they do s they do
sink a I don't like this volcano area I
need to figure out a bit way to Traverse
these areas cuz otherwise how am I going
to get through the
dungeon
what everything for stamp
man no
see
nothing but yeah tiles maybe are the way
to go but I wouldn't have been able to
pick up the octorok with that either so
a combination of stone and tiles
hopefully will do the
trick oh well look at
that we learned something
new lava rock Echo all right it's just a
platform I
guess so those two people he's looking
for I guess are in the
rib so
is that in
here oh I think it's too
hot what are you
go
hungry oh Dar I thought you wouldn't
show
up I got
up what's going on over
here is that
you I go glad to see you here after all
I was here right I was about to snack on
some rock roast deep in the Quarry when
o Open we got to out we got to get out
of here as you know fast as we could but
now we're too tuer to move and I didn't
even get any roast I'm
starving in the CL so it's not safe here
either no what if it starts spreading
would we be able to escape in
time yeah you just do it
think let me do it let me figure it
out okay can I make it for this heat
though it looks very
hot the hot springs restore Hearts o oh
yeah right like in every Zelda game
huh kind the heat ah still seems
[Music]
fine I don't think it's a ground pound
right so
aha wait I can just move
them away with
you can't jump huh but are you just
going to stay there
forever have you accepted your
destiny yes stay down
there yeah put him in a
Timeout m
[Music]
M
bro okay twers oh they don't sound that
name sounds different from what they
were before or is that the English name
it always
was this is too similar to prep of the
Wild
it's the same kind of meat but I guess
they all have been eating that for
Generations this is Rock roast one of my
favorite
foods going to deliver to the El
okay of course I'll carry it of
course I'm a princess I'm made to carry
things
right no
respect oh I can learn a yeah but this
is the same thing as with the side quest
that we had that um it needs to be one
of these right cuz they did say
something about like I don't see a
difference has to be carried I assume
can I jump no oh God
ow so
rude I forgot to jump it seems my
button didn't work it's the Ping it's
the Ping I'm telling you
no this is
fine how cute he's got a pot on his
head cooking pot oh one for you
what you really asking me to let's make
a shortcut maybe but that's four it's
four okay I can't make a shortcut with
four do I really have to carry all four
of these or three
maybe H or I should have maybe tried to
spawn one of these in front of them
maybe it would have worked who knows
oopsie almost dropped
it just two total oh okay it's fine it's
fine bounce bounce
o is that the guy whose hair is normally
pink it just looks different here
the clown hair
guy
oh Tip
Tap shortcut tell me please no I can't
remember for the life of
[Music]
me fine I wasn't too sure about the
leadership sh but you're doing
great but I still won't tell you the
shortcut but Sil might know about it
should have really gone there first
but if I went there first would they say
the same
thing I'm
okay my father was great at this but
since I've been a chief I been nothing
but chaos I'm a war reward and I've only
ever been good at studying I've been
usess without my slate I never be good
you will be take some time you got to
learn all of those things first and
especially learning by doing is the best
way so this is a good learning
experience don't
worry don't you worry about a
[Music]
thing yeah this part is
complete I'm guessing they don't want me
to walk on that heart container Spott
it
easy I got too excited
let me check
[Music]
something h h
okay thanks for the
heal where was the other
one oh over
there ooh looks very hot and
spicy if I fall into that lava I'll turn
into some spicy chicken wings oh
no I don't want to deal with you wao
fast waa
reaction what a pro am I even supposed
to go
here oh my God it's a chaotic
Place very chaotic
um no no don't get don't get
ah okay
whatever missed the way point oh yeah I
guess
so but what comes around come back
around or
so
danger ah is it the thing down there no
that's a
city oh there it
is what goes around comes around
thanks that looks
funny why does this look
so pasted to me like
inserted like it's not really blending
in the other things look like that to me
too not really but it looks kind of
funny when you look at it
closely looks like a piece of dung kind
of yeah no it looks out of place a
little
bit I guess it was difficult to make
that um oh what I need to go there but
it's so hot
there Zelda can't take it Phoenix can
take it of course but for me it is
questionable what is it this time
your ELD what are you doing I we've been
so
worried there were just new dark first
of us so we came to have a look but we
had to retreat was so scary this is a
defensive position maybe you should have
just headed back though I've never heard
of Dr off oh the yeah okay they're the
tainted once
what I'm a phoenix but I'm saying I'm
playing Zelda she can't take it
guys do you want her to become a crispy
human
leg unknown dark creatures are you
thinking what I'm thinking
fell
hell those are not
[Music]
dark
y do it again do it again
ow am stupid
no no no
no oh I wanted to bring out a lalos
while while I'm sleeping but yeah that
won't work out
[Music]
anyway
okay thank you guys you're so nice
H okay oh we're ready to
go it really supports this nap culture
doesn't it these are
new I'm terrifying these only cost two
let's see how they do against the LI
Alphas oh pretty good they're relatively
fast okay but these are strong
wa maybe got to help
[Music]
oh oh my God
I'm
died um is it worth
[Music]
now oh but this one
died the hearts probably I get damage
just going there don't leave me Lo stop
do something oh thank God
[Music]
princess you took care of them already I
got a strange feeling there's more ahead
it might be dangerous but I can't keep
relying on other
people's you want to go first oh you're
going to get sucked
in I've seen this before PTSD
don't worry we get our
[Music]
Echo hey let
go eat the
go oh no oh no do I have to fight you or
can I just walk around you I feel like I
can just walk around you
maybe I will oh he didn't even see
me goodness Trident is there broken you
broke it what's wrong with you she's
going to
quiet I'm going to I got to fix it I'm
got to repair
it I was supposed to take care of
it look
up no
B on the cave structure my weight and
speed if I just okay I got this
what wa no no no no
no okay you got rid of one
two do it
again do it again AR any more rocks
where I could use that so now it's your
turn you little ass you little ass
um threee versus one is just not fair oh
but good
kill good kill good kill oh there's more
broken Trident so maybe that wasn't good
as Trident
then
ow okay okay
okay
yeah
beautiful almost as if she was a warrior
maybe a part-time Warrior I think you
could call Zelda a part-time Warrior now
couldn't you or a part-time hero
maybe but for some reason I just feel
like part-time Warrior rings a bell with
me
shortcut do you know yeah you forgot too
oh my God he
forgot okay so that was all for nothing
I should have just let you R to
die what the did you just say I'm
really impressed with how you're doing
so far though I had some concerns about
how you take to being Chief but you
proving me
wrong go might remember the crater
shortcut you off go I already talked to
him can you guys put your two brain
cells together and
remember blink twice no no no but I will
make my last announcement
soon I really want he now but maybe I'm
not cut out for this like that shut
up what do you
mean well I my father was strong
Dependable everyone respected him but
Daron you helped de feat those m
mon why is she mommying him now only
because I had my dad sleep I can make
calculations but I don't have the skills
to really unite people like he could I
told him I could do this but I'm scared
I was lying to his
Bo don't worry so much you're going to
turn into
Walmart but I don't want to give up I'm
going not going to be the kind of Chief
my father was and that's okay because
I'm not I'm me and I will do everything
I can to help everybody yeah that's what
that's what that's the
spirit hello there thank you are you
ready are you ready for a 3d concert
tonight
[Music]
tonight let's go
I wonder if I can do the dungeon
today how long do you think the dungeon
will
take where did he tell us to
go
there I'm going to
jump there's a heart piece up there
didn't I already get
it should found a shorter and more
simple than the
others maybe not
okay hopefully it starts soon like
now yeah surprise now put your brain
cells together come on put your little
fingers together maybe do that pose to
con connect your brain cells
pose really what you would remember you
know
what if I don't remember I don't
remember what else you want is
say El go El there's something else I'd
like to ask you Mo what exactly is to
shortcut to the
crater b b cheese back in the
day thank you I wish you gunite as
well may gunite be with
you on the trying
paths custom faded long before
it find himself to take one tile of CH
short is Rel to the Chie but that's me
now isn't it
D understand your father that's it I
remember now your father once said
something about blocking off the path in
my room is it the big statue right
behind us or behind you in front of
me oh you're going somewhere else else
okay I thought I just have to move that
statue
no
ah is kind
of thank you
[Music]
the smile the smirk she behind me it's a
portra my dad doesn't he look so cool
smirk but that made me promise I'd
change this portrait one day you'll have
to hang one of yourself when you achieve
so proud I'm so sure I'd grow up like
him I've left his up but I did promise
so I have to do it
anyway now we got to
fight
hi oh wait huh
no I thought so I thought
so was the
[Music]
angle
okay why do people type that jibber bush
with a te when people sneeze you don't
know yet that is German for bless you
like that's what we say when somebody
sneezes and it's our culture to say that
here yeah but he wanted it was it's the
it's their tradition to break the
portrait and make a new portrait
guys his dad seems to be his dad seems
to be dead so seems to be okay to move
on whoa what the hell I just broke
something in my game capture
card what the hell
me reopen
it
[Music]
yippe do you want to come over here too
or can I hold enemy bats probably not
right um but do I need to bring him or
can I just fly over with my
dial
bye
Del that was so cool don't think I can
use that trick but I find a way to catch
out with you
bye thought
so oh yeah I could have bound enemies
but I don't know like ah controlling
them is kind of rough you know what no
no stop I didn't want
to ow what is it higher I guess it
is all right let me get a
bird come here come here come here come
here come
here literally why do they make it so
difficult am I doing something
wrong there we go
okay but I'm curious what's over
here okay look at all my birds following
me all my birds in my back birds in my
back oh
I thought we could jump together and I
forgot we
can't birds of a feather flock together
yeah
okay wait but that doesn't work huh
unless I make myself a platform and
because they're so cheap it should work
but actually I could just fly over with
a tile in this case
s
ow it feels like it's made for me you
think so what makes you think so I do
really enjoy it that is for sure thank
you so much
endless I guess for New Zealand like
okay it kind of sucks if you are
watching this whole
stream then you'd be pretty tired for
the 3D life but if you're just waking up
for the 3D life
Dam it's not too bad
right that thing is higher is it
not guess I'll try and guess I'll die
yep guess I'll
die maybe with a wind machine
again
combination not tired who is tired
anybody tired
you can make it guys believe in
[Music]
yourself what was
that okay that's a pretty good position
no no no no no no
no okay maybe I should follow the bir I
don't know man I'm not good with
this water
blocks okay in this economy
not up I kind of want you to go straight
but
okay oh now we can summon even more
blocks
because I have more
trees are we in the dungeon right
now sometimes I lose track of what I'm
doing is this a dungeon is this a is
this a a
butterfly no not
yet
oh well
okay she never
learns uh-oh
what
no
W that might not work here
unless
go ow
wait for
me
that's
um
what help
me I what no I don't
need wait I I know how to do it he yeah
I'm good um I know I know
I had
it I had it guys had it up to
here I know I don't have to do it like
this
but look I'm going through it with
style when it works it works and then it
works smoothly so what is what else is
what what what is this room what what ah
they want me to go
up uh does this
work I'm scared I was so
scared come down
okay away the
away here we go going up
again up against
what Dar you
again I finally managed to C J wo
there's a giant rock in the way this
path hasn't been used for a while so it
probably fell at some point how
convenient for
you I leave this to me going to roll
into it Show Me What You Got make me
proud make mommy
proud Oh I thought this would be an
embarrassing situation just do it again
punch
[Music]
again you're not going to do it you're
not going to freaking do it there's
times when carvings on the Rock Aren't
Enough um I think you prob me finger
thingss out the words are valuable but I
can't be a great Chief when I'm striving
at this slate so I'm going to quit do
you want to be Chief no okay I guess
I'll have to do it I have to keep my
eyes up to see what works best for me so
let's try something different oh
[Music]
what G's Chief notet so fre number
what did he punch the slate and like
that like it's like you put something in
there to wiggle it kind of but like I
feel like he just needed to punch it one
or two more times on its own okay look
creative of what you got believe me this
was the only way to do
it you're
slight wasn't it really important to you
no haven't you listened tree it doesn't
give a anymore about because it's
not been giving him any good advice
really he need to learn on his own I can
still use the Nugget of wisdom my V left
to help me do things my way
then besides I've got all my father's
Mars memorized
now sorry to keep you waiting on my big
inside the CR ahead such as the
dungeon it seems stars's really made a
breakthrough it's nice to see him more
confident half confidence
all right is this a
dungeon is this a dungeon is this a
dungeon oh there's a rift that's the
dungeon let's speedrun it guys
please is this a
dungeon is this a muscle
dungeon
yeah why speed run because
food because
food understandable right we all love
food food's good what are those it's
like almost as if I can walk on it
because it's not
moving never mind it's like it's
like hardened candy you know oh never
mind I don't need
it wait maybe this is like a ground P
platform is it I guess no maybe yeah if
you drop it but it won't go back up so a
bit similar
[Music]
ilar sure I'll jump from up
there h
ah you know there's one thing I really
hate and it's those
I don't even have anything good
to counter them I think okay
wait first of
[Music]
all I'll just have to resort to my most
Desperate
Measures booming mbls
ah let's try where are they ah this
strong
one help do
[Music]
something he's
literally static
static can't be that
hard there we go
okay um left or right
H it's going to be kind of difficult to
reach there maybe there's a better way
from over
here you do
you do it do
you static also works but what did I say
potato
uh-oh holy he's still alive how is
he still alive
wow now how is he going to reach
that oh he's still
alive he's in the zone
sorry I don't know how you deserved that
you honestly didn't but that was
impressive maybe I'll use you I'll hire
you a few more times
then did I miss something good
there I hope not otherwise I'll come
back
uh
oh can I fly myself over there
to then
climb immediately oo
smoo difficult very difficult
oh
whatever
Smo smoo
[Music]
poof okay nice way
point way to go Point ah
ah I don't know what got into
me Echo a wall Master you mean one of
those I I think I got one but um you
mean when I'm going to make one
never the fire ones I've summoned a few
times but I don't like them that much
either
I think I understand now how to
effectively pick them up at
least oh
shoot okay where do we go though
uh W the burst
said the shock the shock of it it was
too much for
me if they burn then I
burn where am I
going oh okay I see
now oh oh God I'm scared okay let go no
I keep on hearing these birds
dying but I'm not really seeing it so
it's maybe it's not real there is not
really happening dungeon time
baby
m
[Music]
w
ooh that's a nice soundtrack
let's get
tracking do it do it do it do it do it
do it do
it
wow I don't even think we have to kill
them but let's just do it don't step on
the burning Stones no he's streaming hot
hey we learned one
H guys have you spoiled yourself yet
with looking at the
screenshots and getting a Vibe for the
stage don't look at it too
closely I don't I I don't want you to
look at it yet oh
look I accidentally didn't crop one of
them so it was more visible than I
wanted it to
be but it's okay you're already going to
see it
today key already I try not to spoil
myself well I I worry about that but I
probably shouldn't care too much it's
just a stage it's just a
stage H when is the last announcement
going life after the stream maybe after
I get uh some food into my
system yeah
[Music]
yeah okay well what about this door
though that was
[Music]
open did you see it yes he sees it
before they see what and you still
[Music]
missed oh well thanks for opening that I
guess
ooh hidden
treasure
hey what do you think you're
doing I would say that's probably all in
this room eight Twisted pumpkins that's
not too
bad
okay r
[Music]
such as the
consequences of picking on
me allo got a tweet about your live
right oh have they
not maybe they'll wake up for it and do
it
soon oh why is this
moving oh does it go up and down oh
dear how frequently oh God oh God oh
God I see though I understand my mind is
so
clear do you do those guys want to be
killed because how else is that door
going to open
huh I'll just shoot him
[Music]
didn't open the door maybe I'm supposed
to stop it from doing this I don't
know there was a treasure chest
is there a lever I don't see one but
maybe if I fill up the main hole if
there's
one
um
yo there's not enough time to pull it
out and then open
it
o golden egg golden egg um what is going
maybe I
no no I have to proceed from here that's
the only
way I have an
idea didn't think it would go up that
high ah I knew it cuz that one was
already there had a
feeling is it still going to go
[Music]
up yes
has a little bit of a grace period mhm
great Zone ah they posted it on Hol
plast oh yeah uh when when I first
posted a tweet
huh yeah yeah yeah indeed I think they
did well so far so good
um
yeah oh
perfect but how do I get there it's too
far
[Music]
yeah why don't I
just
oh oh oh yeah I can summon it while I'm
climbing thank
God but that jump is also very fu
looking
High that's
four I could try to put a water block on
top of it I
[Music]
can't maybe one bed built on
top or trampoline that's also just one
I'll try over the bed
first oh thank
God really that's how we're going to do
it what is
this chest up ahead something or nothing
down
[Music]
oh a different room here oh I'll go up
first I don't
know seems like an a special kind of
solution oh invincibility frames we love
them
um I mean
nothing beat the ground pant but I'm
going to get hurt by the last
[Music]
one I don't know man I don't
know it's okay it's okay it's okay it's
okay ow
water
blocks maybe would they have stopped
that so down or up ah maybe down because
that seems to be a dead end with the
treasure
chest so we'll have to pass by here
again some time
low heart hey yeah wait why didn't I
sleep more oh I didn't sleep at all did
I I use the rabal loock like in the yeah
right you can just lift it oh I was
thinking about lifting it but somehow my
brain was like a that's going to be too
heavy but nothing's too heavy for this
lady is
it is it well I can't test it now I
guess
okay what's going on in here I see I see
is there a point in going to the
left oh there he
[Music]
is
nice always check the map and make a
plan guys
you always forget you can do that do
what oh carry things you forget a lot of
things in this game I think oh my god oh
thanks it's inevitable I'm not the only
one feel like everybody like is kind of
overwhelmed but even if you forget
things you usually figure out a
different way
o please don't hurt
me key for above okay wow I feel like I
am speedrunning this right
[Music]
now
help wait let me just place that thank
you
okay how long am I
climbing
smovies if I have
one I don't
[Music]
okay I know like honestly I don't I
don't feel like climbing is so slow here
anyway but if you can make it faster
then why not I guess I wonder if the uh
maybe the boss fight has a has a
climbing
element oh it might be and it might be
one of those like fiery uh on the--all
slugs or something like that but in big
or so maybe
and then you have to dodge cuz you're
also climbing on the wall and then the
lava goes up and down probably too and
you have to dodge
and I could see that oh yeah oh
yeah oh yeah oh
yeah oh also we didn't see link running
okay there we go I was going to say we
didn't see him running into the dungeon
this time but he's here oh my God that's
fun that's so fun
ha what am I looking for link do I want
him to
die
oh ah wait are you going to go away
don't go
away why would you do that was that
timing a matter of timing or because I
got too close hey don't suck up my
energy where are you going will you
always go away if I'm to
close oh well I got got two hits and
then that was
enough oh wait what more
what am I getting sword lasers because
I'm full health I normally never get to
experience
[Music]
that
shees round two yeah yeah more stand
back link is moring oh is he oh he's
just he he just became a bomb I thought
that was
more I was good I was locked
in but I wish he could have exploded
more for us but I guess now we can do it
on our
own yipp yippe pressing a while in Sword
fighter form
[Music]
let's get rid of everything then and see
if there's something
hidden so much
energy maybe there's nothing hidden here
at
[Music]
all so
sure something give me something
[Music]
no check map true yeah there's
nothing okay well it was fun destroying
things like that but that's also just an
airflow okay but the fight was fast huh
I just went for it I was like I ain't
got no time for this give me your bums
Now or Never
oh please
you're doomed aren't
[Music]
you do they hurt me too though or is it
like my echo where they don't hurt
me
what mhm probably got to go
around I like that there's so much
climbing here it's um you know oops see
in the water dungeon we had a lot of
[Music]
swimming I want to
just um
okay there we
go how did you guys do that of course
I'm still add it I'm always
[Music]
added do
something throwing him in there to die
fight for his life on fire
even wow good job
actually good job damn this guy's
[Music]
good I don't have so much
energy how's the game I love the game
especially when it gives me
money but today we were just horsing
around a lot and it was um
fun it was fun wa what did they call
again
um come come
come what you're not even reacting to
him do
[Music]
something
great I'm out of
energy do you think he's can he's to do
something
no whz robes oh yeah maybe I'll fill up
my
energy should I I have a
[Music]
couple why why does why does it not hit
him so often like these followup arrows
what's what's wrong invincibility frame
insane
unfair hello he's there lock on him this
is why I hate that you can't like lock
onto specific things
[Music]
really wack it with your
stuff y thank you wait are you not going
to be watching are going to be sleeping
well I hope
you don't let me land please thank you
yeah are you going to watch the archive
targeting is awkward as hell it's like
my one of my least favorite things about
it but generally I'm very very happy
with this game I just wish it was longer
already 2 a.m. but it's I I I thought
well at least you know I put it on a
weekend and not on like a Sunday night
but a Monday night is a little bit
better I
[Music]
thought can you do something no oh wait
maybe if maybe if he goes up and then
down no okay just wanted to
try no no no I was going to I was going
to purposefully not waste my energy
about use a bomb
fish stay
[Music]
there to for me too but I'm going to
watch snuggle and bed with my tea and my
C dad
is there's I don't think there's any
better
way to watch my 3D Live than
that it's the Wow
way maybe it's how I'm going to watch no
I'm going to be no I I have to be on my
PC I got to change OBS scenes between
opening and introduction and stuff yeah
I hope my internet will behave so far
today it's been behaving I think
yesterday with r it was just weird
because of Discord like when I'm when
I um when I try to stream my screen to
someone on
Discord uh it lags a lot I guess it also
lags a little bit when somebody streams
it to me in too high quality but it's
weird it's not like my internet is bad
it's just like
Discord
somehow is very problematic in that
sense more than any anything
else so yeah this this is what makes me
so nervous when I have to stream such an
important stream on my
own and like if I'm doing like an outfit
reveal I can kind of wait for if if if
there's like a a little bit of stutter I
can wait for that and just say what I
said again but it's a pre-recorded VOD
of a Frey life
[Music]
so bye
but usually for those if they're
stuttering then the archive is fine
usually right
so hoping for the
[Music]
best there you go I'm finally summoning
one of
these that one's really in the
way no the set well I've noticed that if
I make a really low quality ooh stream
then it's it stops lagging when I do it
like 15
ah I just looked for a shortcut so so so
sorry oh I have to pick it up again well
then let's sleep
[Music]
first I need to
pee will be fun to get to the boss with
a full
bladder no I don't want to go I want to
feel this like intense pressure that I
would feel even with an empty bladder
are you kidding me the thing's back what
what am I is it because I died once or
what will make the boss battle even more
intense and Nerf
rank no not the
bed uh-oh it's going to get stuck oh no
okay all right I made it it's not going
to continue
right okay
stop you got me for a
second
it's the I really need to ooh ah my
bladder but we already got the boss key
wait do we yeah we have the tiny key for
up there okay okay okay
[Music]
okay this is uh
no I don't
know do I have to do this
link
wait
off how do I how do I what
[Music]
I wish my
face expression would be captured when I
make this expression that's
like it's
it's it's one of the few Expressions
that it it really can't
capture it just seems incapable of
it yeah kind of like that but nah it's
more like raised eyebrows
and kind of a pouty mouth that's also
frowning it's like really
like really
now what are we doing here
[Music]
no that's not the button I pressed don't
waste my
energy
wait okay I guess I'll
fly I feel like I could have tiled my
way through
it maybe I yeah I was going to say maybe
I got to wait for the lava
[Music]
and they're starting to
burn I See Fire F fire inside the
mountain and on the bird
swings oh what a fairy oh look like a
bottle with a fairy Now fairy in a
bottle no fairy into a bottle Farewell
My Fair Lady fairy friend oh no that's
not good oh I didn't see you there
hello oh no
oh yes here we go oh I've reached
it yay how many birds have been
sacrificed for me to come here all this
way it doesn't matter because the birds
love to sacrifice themselves for
me it's their Destiny they feel
fulfilled I would love to have some link
energy inste of Hearts but okay I'm
going to go pee can I get a go piss girl
too
be right
back is it going to be can you oh you
can write that it's not going to get
banned nice
okay wait I don't want to end it with my
hair in my face here
[Music]
okay thanks for the super chats I
guess uh okay
well that was a short
dungeon didn't miss anything
right don't think I
did let's
see how difficult the boss
is should I get I I'll see if I can get
some link energy easily in the beginning
otherwise I'll charge it
up maybe I could have uh
ooh so it's not in the POV that I F but
this is kind of yeah kind of what I oh
but a dragon I didn't expect a dragon I
expected a
long what
a long long a long thing for
sure is that a thing that existed before
Oh my God Dragon Balls Dragon these
balls
n how do you fight this
thing do I just get to it and then it's
going to go somewhere else
right oh oh
ow oh I fell in
I fell into his
hole ow that was a great
start damage
[Music]
reduction all
right I got a million fairies so bring
it
on oh okay we'll wait for that yeah and
then
[Music]
this time I'm not falling in not falling
for you stupid little
tricks but so far it's pretty easy like
there's no nothing difficult to figure
out
yet where you going to
[Music]
go see okay that's going to be difficult
for me to reach I'd prefer you to be on
a
platform you
know oh oh ah
oh did you do that because I because I
made a
[Music]
platform well would I have a bow my
friend I can do this
forever I guess it doesn't do too much
damage ow
I'm going to heal
anyway I'm not sure like how what what
how would a normal person do
it where are we ah ow
ah oh okay that's better but uh kind of
hot I can't step on that really I
think put something down but he seems to
like get rid of it
immediately should I just should I just
keep on trying to do it from a
[Music]
distance ow wo
wo
what if I sleep a
BL my fire out thank
you
no holy
y'all chill the
out
uh-oh oh
yeah uh what should I do it hurts it
hurts
okay sleeping on the job actually I
could
now there so much
time all right
uh let me place this guy here uh-oh oh
oh it's is going to get
sacrificed ow no oopsie ow oh
oh
no uh-oh
[Music]
um
uh-oh ah
well I'm making full use of all my
smoovies at least no more
hoarding got shoot it over here maybe
get rid of the pot no
okay no
[Applause]
[Music]
I think I can't really throw bombs when
he's in the lava right cuz they'll just
stin or maybe they blow up
[Music]
immediately oh they kind of
do just need some
space and more link energy
[Music]
ah
stop I will give you that I haven't
taken so many healing items before I
think in a boss fight but it's very to
simple boss
[Music]
fight could sleep again now
oh well is he going to the middle
no ah
[Music]
okay yeah once he's in a good spot then
you can spam them and it's pretty
easy when he was in the lava I don't
know about that space man not my
favorite
place I did it in under an
hour
yippe
lemons vaj is down and out in what other
game was he a
boss what
other Zelda game or should I say link
[Music]
game oh car of
time there
ooh and now turn all the lava into onen
water no
okay would have been a bit more pleasant
but all
right boss beaten Rift Clos that was a
quick ass dungeon
she that was crazy short
you can do even more oh more
discounts okay oh my fly Lea got a
discount and the Wolf okay okay oh and
the boomerang
guy five let's go how many do I have now
you know what maybe the Monday stream
where I talk about the life and
everything that that's a stream that can
be a Super Chat reading stream as well
hey
y' oh yeah cuz they talked about the the
the the goddesses or so being over there
in those free the the Triforce goddesses
right
Priestess pre
[Music]
PR
Priestess
Priestess PR Priestess
Priestess Priestess no
Priestess oh really your power has freed
this land which was swallowed by
nothingness I am the goddess
din one of the free who created your
world you have demonstrated your true
power
thus I grant my sanction unto
you
wow it's like a Dragon
Ball Dragon
[Music]
de will she say
more this sanction extols your
Deeds the path to the Prime energy will
open for the one who dance before each
of the three two
remain remember this your power will one
day be your
salvation
H surely that has a deep meaning that
we'll understand
later or maybe not that deep who
knows the path to the Prime energy will
open for the one one who stands before
each of free so we won't get near to
Prime energy before demonstrating our
abilities to the goddesses this probably
also means our enemy hasn't gotten near
the Prime energy yet
either makes sense why the enemy
imprisoned the goddesses in the Rifts to
hinder us they must be afraid of someone
getting the Prime energy I wonder what
this energy even
is there's not really anything else to
do in the still world now so let's go
back
halt I need my heart container oo there
it
is another beautiful heart let's
go
yippee okay we only got one dungeon done
today but we got a lot of side stuff
done and the the dungeon was really
short so we could do a lot of side stuff
in stupid ass mini games a lot of horse
riding so
oh good stuff I suppose that we did
cursed from excuse
me did you never try to bite into a
lemon and this happened to you have some
compassion
okay it took a while for my face to go
back to
normal it
hurts when your head is trying to eat
your own
face limited edition merch uh
no there shouldn't
be let me double check but
uh there will be
merch
announced
but
[Music]
um where
is where is it uh here
I mean there's a bonus but it's not like
signed not
limited
yeah I think I think I can
confirm yeah yeah yeah yeah
but you should still get the full set
because it's cool stuff to extend
something
[Music]
maybe the Giant Wave is gone o hopefully
everyone's back now to now he found his
way to catch up with me he didn't really
catch up at
all it's more than one thing well I mean
of course um it's more than one
item uh several items
oh my God a
a yippe yippe yippe hooray
yippe
yippee and no one picks us up and we
fall on the ground and I break my back
and I
die well the first time I've been the
guy TOS in the air I'm just so GL that
everyone's Back and You're back is
broken sorry um anyway before I met you
I actually regreted becoming Chief it
been like a mistake but I don't think it
was I'm just finding my own way of doing
things I know you'll have to go in more
W soon so I'm going to keep leading my
people yeah thank you so much for your
help come over here will you sounds like
I'm needed
[Music]
coming come back anytime
we have saved gonia
[Music]
y d changed a lot from when we met him
he had so much trouble deciding things
before now he's confident and his
friends are smiling I guess he's happy
to be relied
on I'm so glad we managed to meant the
Elden volcano Rift and now we have the
sanction we received from the goddess
there that leaves the holy Mount Manu
and the faren wetlands Rifts let's get
going
Zelda yeah I would say those two
dungeons we can do the next uh Zelda
stream next week in one
stream and then some more side stuff and
the finale maybe in the final stream if
that's really how it goes and there's
not much more but what do I
know what do I know
there might be
more that will stop me in my tracks in
my running
tracks sounds great look at him he looks
he looks like you
Noble it's it's a
scarf I thanks for saving me I'm going
miserable miserable missable oh that's
also sad a lot of times people don't
notice me at all I noticed you
immediately if you hadn't shown up I
might have been stuck in the rift
forever you think I'm about to give me
the Shivers maybe I should go on a nice
long run to warm up you
know go on
race are horses involved in it probably
not ready set go
run
okay oh no oh no oh no oh
no oh how what horse is it horse I have
a feeling it's with a
horse what are you
insane one flag
only is it one flag
only horse or not wait
he's
oh I think not horse but can I take
[Music]
shortcuts oh he's fast
oh you can roll over the hot
stuff I definitely have to use shortcuts
but damn I'm already H yeah that H that
won't
work
wow can we yeah can
we can
we no surely we
can't
but I wonder if there is an obvious
shortcut that makes
everything so much
easier
you wait wait for me no okay but pretty
close I
mean that was pretty close it seems like
I cannot put anything in his way cuz
he's going to get rid of it
flying TI the end oh yeah
okay let's go let's go let's
go
you abstraction of Justice
[Music]
haha oh but I was cheating so hard I
feel a feel bad for him like I was using
magic he's just
himself what you got to do what you got
to do you lost Fair Square I I wouldn't
say so but sure no I don't think you
lost fair and
square but we finished the side quest
yeah
a seems like there's no extra levels of
that my brother said hit to the glider
glideride glideride and never ride oh my
God these people love races and
stuff I'll show you I guess is it do I
just use my uh bird is that what you
want oh oh I see
chest
okay so to
the West you kind to Glide without
touching the ground all the way from
here to the flag
okay first let me get the boot is there
a
timer I don't think there
is oh
oh well ah what he let
go wait I press B I think
no we do it again yeah did the bird get
tired was it was it my depth perception
did I fly into
something I yes I did did I fly against
the wall is that can you not touch the
wall at all the wall at all where is
it
there yeah yeah the G I wanted to touch
the wind but it was difficult
this time I'll try my
best and I'll probably be the last Quest
we're doing today and then I'll leave
you guys for a nap if you really want a
nap no I'm doing it what do you
mean thought I was running off huh just
because I was going
diagonally but it seems like like you
can't like go somewhere else and
cheat this is actually
easier cuz the they're so close to the
walls you don't want to accidentally
land on
something
yay that might have been the best view
of this POV in this
game are you going to
nap are you guys going to nap
guys going to
sweep what what you have something
else your brother wants to meet me
m okay going to make food drinks get
coffee M me too but actually I already
lost the appetite for burgar so maybe
I'll just eat pizza
oh more gliding
okay let's do it show me can't be that
bad no Burger
Pizza yeah
probably nap for 1 hour then get Brey oh
thank you guys
for what is this
track what the hell oh is that can I
choose choose your
adventure well yeah um thank you so
much for
suffering through the night for
me
[Music]
ah
interesting maybe there's a specific
combination of up down up down or do you
have to take all of them
well that's just rude can someone be
more careful up
there I'm doing a
[Music]
challenge it's going to be worth it guys
I can tell you
[Music]
that I'll try taking this path and then
oh no y that was so close to the ground
found maybe I wait I can just wait I
don't have to go fast uhoh a bird is
that my bird yeah it's my bird I thought
he would kill
me all right what do you mean I didn't I
latched onto the wall
huh don't put a climbing ball there I
was going to
land
she
rude rations you
fa oh that part is so close what the
[Music]
hell okay nice nice nice nice nice
today's only race suffering really was
that first horse
race what did I
get
[Music]
okay two of them
oh all right all right all
right
what okay I wonder no no
more
fine I would have gladly done another
one cuz I like flying but sure let's
check one more time uh what I can
upgrade St to the
right oh
man too late mafin too
late you have to have a third eye in the
future to see when I'm going where
anticipate it
more
okay bomb
upgrade we can do two or no probably
just
one I want to upgrade my bow though
it's weak too weak for my
taste is the look going to
[Music]
change it did oo
cool you got to pay attention guys yeah
the bow definitely needs more damage
oopsie yeah okay then we'll work on
these ones 30 so many I need to go find
out where I can where in the areas where
I've already been where I might have
missed
any of these
stones but I mean the way I'm playing
the game surely isn't like that
carelessly I I don't think I'm missing
that many of these Stones so maybe it's
just normal to be around this level at
this time
right now there's more optional Rifts
that we could do I guess
also
yeah can go back to the great fair to
help help of M what what can she do what
can the Great Fairy do to me for
me she going to sell me
some you don't need all the upgrades to
finish the game but I want to I want to
feel stronger I feel too
weak oh a quest maybe quest to find the
other fairy
[Music]
[Applause]
time for the last update I guess 500
rupees bye
[Music]
lost oh
there's B it okay but that's the last
time
wow girl you
greedy you can't make Princess Zelda
your sugar
[Music]
Mommy that's just not right just feels
so
[Music]
wrong cuz that honestly Zelda gets all
her money from her daddy so then the
king will be your sugar daddy no we
can't have that no
no
so okay I'm going to while I'm
here let's make the announce more
wow while you're
[Music]
here
oopsie have your eyes on
Twitter if you want to
be um witnessing
this glorious announce some
more guest announcement
number eight
and I can't typ eight and
[Music]
nine
Pi which one
[Music]
H yeah I don't really have a good
picture for this
group they all like spread
apart
unless wait I could cut it no but then
we're not get
[Music]
wait
maybe let me try to cut this one like
this
ha then you won't know cuz I did tell
you that they're part of a four member
unit right but the other member is
already announced from a different
picture but you won't know if I cut it
like this you won't know who is the
fourth member of this
unit ooh still some mystery to
be uh kept
yeah didn't have a much better picture
for this group
[Music]
but let me get the orhi
marks yeah for free hours you'll get
more mystery
mystery and
then the other one the other Senai
oh what's her ocean Mark that
thing is that the oce Mark I guess
samai find out
in three hours
approximately let's put a link
um this time I'll put a link cuz now we
have a
link a link and a
Zelda
b b wait that's me stop
that okay
are you ready going to post
[Music]
it okay here we go three uh two uh one
uh go
which means now I can
change the thumbnail I
could last is rpai and auki Senpai more
amazing vocalists again this group was
one of the groups where I needed really
good
vocalists so yes yes yes yes that's why
right did I save of course I did but
look save again
yeah now you wonder who who will they be
comboed with COA
combo yeah I love I love their voices
and Luka's voice is so special with her
whispery
tone so it's going to be very
interesting how it's going to
sound and what song we're going to sing
are you curious yet M what do SAS is
going to be like um I will say I've kind
of tried to have a theme but it kind of
ended up being like two themes
maybe like I feel like there's a part
one of the live and a part two and you
might notice where where the vibe kind
of changes from like in terms of music
style halfway through it will kind of
change I would say but then it's going
to go back again I
guess to I don't know it will be a mix
yeah but there's some kind of vision I
had but hard to say it's all just a
mirage it will feel like a mirage
probably honestly yeah Mirage might fit
quite
[Music]
well okay so the ones who want to sleep
a little bit I'll give you time to sleep
now um then uh Sunday we have um Members
Only Watch along for more monani and
then Monday uh I'll have a stream a data
stream where I talk about everything
that's going to happen now
and read super
chats enjoyed my stay I'm happy to hear
that good good good then but your stay
is not over you're going to come back
right in 3 hours approximately make sure
to come a little bit early um I mean
even if you come on time you're only
only going to miss the intro but the
intro is fun so come early like 5
minutes yeah cuz I'm going to start 5
minutes
early I'll see you
there let me show you the final
thumbnail It's the final
[Music]
thil see second row they're sitting some
people recognize ena's shoes this is a
little bit repositioned though but yeah
some people recognize ena's shoes and
were like M might be Ena I was like
most others did not understand who it is
and not just her shoes a little bit
maybe of the Ring Around raina's hand
may have given it
away yeah oh actually ah wait that's the
PO where I didn't adjust the height that
much yet oopsie well whatever it's fine
in this case it's fine cuz I put the
logo but I'm left it was a little bit
difficult yeah cuz there's such
different heights here going on
sassy
way I might still switch this out but
it's mostly
fine
so see you there I finally put a ring on
waya you are funny ID came to sing and
Rick Havoc for real like they is so
powerful let me tell
you they are going to make a huge impact
in terms of voice voice power horse
power horse power there's a lot of good
singers here anyway like look oh my God
like look who look at look at this line
up so much vocal
power
crazy but um well I mean there will be
some
special reveal or so I should have put
that on the thumbnail I
realized during the live some special
surprise so uh make sure to watch it
from beginning to the end I'm excited
I'll see you there in J when we say V
let's party in 2 and a half hours yipp I
wonder want
me yeah you guys kind of get
it bye
bye I hope you will like it oh man I
really hope you you like it I put so
much blood and tears and sweat into this
bye-bye oh
[Music]
n