[Music]
you
so
[Music]
okay
hello
yes i was still doing some stuff um
there you are chat you look so invisible
what the hell
did you drink an invisible potion or
something
hi
cheeky chickens trying to fool me
trying to fool me and be like boo
probably right you wanted to surprise me
i know i know i know you're not a ghost
chicken
no no no no
you're hiding behind me good
cute
just thinking of that looks cute in my
mind
boo with confetti oh i wonder if there's
gonna be more confetti today
uh welcome back to portal 2
uh we're going to finish the game today
um
we we're we were pretty much halfway
through
uh oh cave johnson oh no on you
why is cave johnson in the chat he's a
scary scary old man that doesn't live
anymore i wonder how he died if he was
killed or something maybe interesting
i'm interested we don't know how he died
right maybe
hmm maybe he was assassinated for
being such a piece of [\h__\h]
my voice sounds weird it why now you
make me feel self-conscious
it why why why why
but is this more like it is this more
like it is this my is this is this this
keanu voice
more like this
[Laughter]
weird
hey dude
how you doing
as joey likes to say and friends how are
you doing
okay
uh
one thing though
um
i hope we finish the game within like
maximum five hours or so
i want to be done at 11 pm so i can do
some cooking
uh
so probably no super chat reading um but
let's do it
let's go
i really hope my brain works better
again yesterday my brain
was i don't know if if it was the
puzzles that were just too difficult at
the end
or if it was my brain
that was
just too stupid at the end
[Music]
you guys gonna help me right worst case
because
i wait i didn't tweet i forgot i forgot
to tweet
starting
did you like my little twitter video
message an important message is up on
twitter in case you missed it
just in case you missed it
yeah maybe i was overthinking at the end
let's just say that's what it was
starting
um
we have started ages ago where are you
at
uh
nihongo nihongo inputs here
hi
actually important of course important
everything i post on twitter is
important
oh
yeah oh
okay
oh an important message
that is anything you say is important to
me is my stream okay though by the way
because youtube tells me
that
it says my mainstream and my backup
stream
should be set up correctly i know i
didn't change anything youtube is giving
me some some warning message but it
seems to work fine right
i didn't change anything i don't know
what they mean
let me actually refresh youtube anyway
cause [\h__\h] youtube always
always
always goes like
don't know how to load i don't know how
how to
how to be a website
maybe you need to uh bought
be bought by a billionaire too huh
youtube
youtuber
okay
um
let's go
continue
okay
okay let's do this
i need to drink more water i've barely
drank water today i think
oh
oh i mean at the game are you there you
go
uh
to repeat
um
last time
let's let's revisit what happened last
time
i
was uh important one i was at the end
dragged back into
um the facility
and then years later many many many many
many many years later i woke up again in
a little bit of a different room
not the game's allowed okay
a little bit of a different room that
was more it looked more like a hotel
room and then uh someone greeted us
called wheatley which is a robot in the
shape of an eye
is that better maybe that's still that's
too quiet maybe i don't know um
that's where he did we came from there i
know we probably gotta go there uh
and um
and yeah he's uh he's british
and from the moment from the very
beginning i said uh pretty early on i
said that guy is says
he looks like he could be one of uh
gladys's eyes so
you know that looks says to me and then
and then
we did some puzzles again
because glad this was pissed gladys was
like [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h] you're terrible you're
really bad being um you disappoint me
let's do some more riddles cause that's
my fetish um
and then eventually we managed to escape
kind of
we were about to escape because we got
wheatley to take control over gladys for
them wheatley was so s um
overcome with the power that he had like
he was like oh my god this is amazing
you know what i will be evil now which i
said it would happen
so he got yeah um
full with power and decided he will be
glad this now uh throw gladys
away basically glad it's turned into
potato
um
and we were now escaping from wheatley
not from gladys
yeah
they they went mad with power they all
seemed to go mad with power it seems
because and now we are here in this
old facility old factory
um that was
the original
factory that they started up originally
and with from that guy um wait [\h__\h] i
forgot his name i just said it a moment
ago
that guy what's what's his name again
uh the old facility guy
uh
uh who's a really really rich cave
johnson right right who's a really
really rich dude who got uh really rich
by selling um shower curtains to the
military did i get that right you're
surprised you're surprised i got that
detail aren't you
and uh yeah he got rich with that and
then
he made this factory but he started out
with these gels he produced gels there
are more gels than one
and that we will learn about later i
think i've heard you guys told me
there's uh more than one gel which i am
not looking forward to i can't handle
even more things in my brain
ah
and uh but yeah he seems to be insane
too because they started out you know
all these
he's basically the one who started
everything these whole you know
um
tests you know but the original subjects
were smart subjects like smarter than me
you know uh military people no military
people like uh astronauts and um olympic
people
and one more thing yeah yeah an aperture
they were using those people first for
their experiments in his basement yeah
oh yeah veterans i guess as well was it
or not and or was it people who were not
veterans yet who were already who were
working in the military at that time i
don't know
um
but yeah uh
he was using them and performing some
really really really
tests on them
and now
for some reason i i landed here so i
gotta go for the same tests partially
because part of this factory is broken
anyway
yeah
so
uh additional two ah wow i'm blue dub
and d double die
additionally to
oh
uh is that one of the extra gels of the
see-through
additionally to the portal gun we now
have these
these well
then these bowling bling jelly things
that's water
oh wow shower
yeah
so we have even more
things that we need to
uh consider
when
uh
yeah doing stuff okay so
why is there water now
okay let's see okay we have we have blue
jelly
uh
we want to get up there i suppose
let's do this
uh
well wouldn't it be nice
to have it somewhere so we can boing and
jump over there
us
i don't know it shouldn't be too
difficult can we like make it go further
no because then it will go for the water
what about here
ah
it only sticks to surface like this huh
is that
ah it feels like it could be almost
enough momentum
no
no so close
then
uh
can i
what
oh
[\h__\h] oh that bounces off
that bounces off there
oh
well we don't want it up there um
do i have to like
oh god oh god here we go
hint is in your title
yeah yeah yeah yeah thank you portals
yeah yeah yeah yeah
i'm trying okay i'm thinking of portals
and blue jelly
no not
well okay
i would say
can we
be shot through
with the jelly
ah what about
what the [\h__\h]
my foot jump
out
what's this and let me try
uh wait no no no i wanted i want to ah
damn it
that door is too close to that place
oh sure oh [\h__\h] no i want more wow
wow
okay okay uh no no no no no no no no no
no oh yeah yeah yeah i know i can stop
i'll just stop just stop stop
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
a brown color
can i
if i fall down from there bounce up one
more time here and then jump over there
i wonder if that's enough
oh god oh god oh god what oh god oh you
know what uh
how about
here nah
not here
i kind of want to be closer but here i
feel like a bunk against that thing
oh wait what the [\h__\h] there's a button
wait what
there's a oh
i didn't even see that button there
huh
there you go
oh okay
uh wait how do i activate things again
uh
uh which button was it again
what button
did it work
ah that makes the water stop
um
why did i need the water to start is it
gonna come back
i hear a timer
the water is not really like in the way
for me right now but
maybe it
[Music]
ah yeah okay okay okay yeah it is it is
an oil okay okay
hi hi
here we go
okay
[Music]
i i for some reason did not see that
button at all
i need to investigate more keep your
pants on hi
this next test may involve pants are not
banned yet so word of advice if you meet
yourself on the testing track don't make
eye contact lab boys tell me that'll
wipe out time entirely
forward and backward so do both of
yourselves a favor and just let that
handsome devil go about his business
time
traveling a future you try it
if a future you tries to warn you about
this test don't listen
ah well yeah unfortunately no one is
warning me about this uh i wish someone
would warn me about it oh i have to go
up here
that that seems manageable
okay we have small amounts
of the bouncy liquid
uh
coming from the top um
what do i get up there
ah
i can just probably play
here where does that go
now
[Music]
i don't even want that there don't
really care uh what if i
look at ah
now if i if i fall out of there i will
bounce off maybe like the jelly and then
bounce over there does that work perhaps
so there's already jelly there no need
for
any more
testing
yeah baby
okay okay okay okay that was the first
one
you can see kanji
uh um
up up
up question mark
that's where we came from
no
i guess i'll go this way
right
can i just fall
i can just fall there's no fall damage
am i okay to go
it must be that way
next year it took me so long on y'all
okay
well uh i don't know let's go over there
i can go back
what
now i think i'm wrong here
oh ah
do i need to bring some jelly with me
out here
nah
out here no jelly right
yeah really yeah
[Music]
oh yeah
it was indeed yeah it wasn't it outside
of that thing so i guess it would work
but
where is it where does that blue one go
here this stuff i'm supposed to take
this with me
so audio balance okay by the way
oh oh now it oh it's falling into the
water where do we want it to go
where
this one goes here probably
this one will land here
uh-huh
and then i'll fall for the same one and
bounce hopefully up there
[Music]
doubtful but
okay i hope we don't need any more of
that stuff
with enough momentum
oh
okay okay we reached the top
do i need to go even further
i need to go even further do i need some
blue ah do i need some blue stuff here
oh [\h__\h] but where would that bring
me why would they even bring me
let's say i land here and then go zoom
well i will
go back to the bottom for now
owl
does not hurt
does not hurt uh
i guess i'll go back up
no was that okay
oh
i missed the wall
oh okay hey i really don't need any more
blue okay okay
okay i mean i wasn't sure where we would
go with that anyway
um
uh
okay
maybe a bit more in the middle
i'm ready to play some super mario
now i think
huh
[Music]
can i make a jump like that
perhaps
you should maybe connect the pabst
who wouldn't recognize the thrill of
that sounds like danger
they didn't fly into space storm on the
beach or bring back the gold no sir we
did it's you and me against the world
son i like your grip hustle confusion
now let's solve this thing okay
okay
oh no
the cube is in cube jail someone saved
the cube from the cube channel that
reminds me of the handmaid's tale
um if whoever watched the handmaid's
tale will probably know what i
am talking about holy [\h__\h] that is
that was so painful yeah bad bras
they're mentioning pants and bras so
they know what i react to and what you
guys react to when cube is in cube jail
does anyone know what i mean
i'm gonna need the cube first to put
that on there
okay where are we putting this stuff
this time
here
is there is it open at the top
let's see
oh
it is it is open oh [\h__\h] what what what
what what what what what oh my god
oh [\h__\h] oh oh oh [\h__\h] what what oh [\h__\h]
now it's bouncing around everywhere
oh there's water how do i get the water
on the cube when it's like [\h__\h]
everywhere
chill
can i pick you up wait wait wait oh i
got it this is like a basketball now
basket cube
the cube is free we breathe
does this work
it's clean again oh that that jelly is
pretty easy to get off of
you huh i thought it would be like
pretty difficult to get off not the case
okay well sorry for breaking
this
surprising that there is no glass shards
on the ground
uh
okay now i need to go up there so we're
not done um what about
here
that should be enough
okay can we go up oh
a cube
oh
we need to move it while we're um
while we're up here
what if we drop the
jelly on it no not quite
oh no
oh yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
which box is he talking about or oh no
oh
he's not firing a box is he telling them
to pack them with their stuff in the box
that i was worried about the our cube
the cube did nothing wrong okay
now who is he firing
the glass cube or the cube inside or
well what are we firing
poor box
hmm
some some
people who were on here previously the
simple fact that you're standing here
listening to me means you've made a
glorious contribution to science
ceo of aperture science i thank you for
your participation are we done we can
count on you for another round of tests
we're not going to release this stuff
into the wild until it's good and damn
ready so as long as you keep yourself in
top physical form there will always be a
limo waiting for you
picked up by a limo
goodbye carolyn
why is carolyn saying goodbye carolyn
he says say goodbye carolyn
goodbye carolyn it's like a dad joke
okay open up please
hello
let me go
what
i'm not supposed to exit through there
i guess i'm not supposed to exit through
there okay
[Music]
all right all right
we're going to
pump station veda
yeah i think we were an alpha before
oh
but now i actually understand
that um
that one room that we went through
before the blue gel
uh before we met that for the first time
uh when we activated something like that
now i understand what we were pumping we
were pumping the blue uh gel through
nano hodo
uh what what what um
what what why are these things here
though
i to go up here
this is oh god
[Music]
okay
door open dot open
door open not open
oh yeah
oreo oh yeah
why is this
why is there
um
won't i bounce
or like against something here if i jump
up here oh no i could i could probably
maybe reach that part
it goes out guys
nope that was not enough i think i don't
know
eh can we get some
blue gel in here friends
the leap of faith didn't quite work
uh even though i believed sometimes even
believing will not be
enough maybe i can just teleport up
there no
i believe i can fly
so close
no it won't be enough
yeah
can i like get some gel in here
i wonder
none of these work they're all just
decoration
what did i miss
what am i missing
wait there's one more
wait a minute
we go up here for ah
but then then i can't make the port
there here it is then i can't make the
portal over there
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
uh
oh dear
oh there
oh hey wait uh
if i fall through here
and then come out of here and then make
a blue one over there oh my god i don't
know if this works
liberal fave number two where are we
where [\h__\h] is this is this right oh my
god oh my god
i think i'm ready to become a basketball
player
oh
there's some nice letters an orange one
orange one brain big yeah holy [\h__\h] and
first try
i'm getting better with these like kind
of
falls
oh that that was like scary what
the texture looking weird
what does that do
did we
did we turn it on wasn't it already on
but i guess maybe not not in this part
of the factory i don't know
now we turned on an orange one as well
oh no
all right
okay
next
next room
next testing room please
no testing room
oh
scary music
moving platform
greetings friend i'm cave johnson ceo of
aperture science i know you might know
us as a vital participant in the 1968
senate hearings on missing astronauts
and you've most likely used one of the
many products we invented
[Music]
am i in danger
who wants to make 60
cash you can also feel free to relax for
up to 20 minutes in the waiting room
which is a damn sight more comfortable
than the park benches most of you were
sleeping on when we found you
so welcome to aputure you're here
because we want the best and you're it
nope
couldn't keep a straight face anyway
don't smudge up the glass down there in
fact why don't you just go ahead and not
touch anything unless it's test related
um
i think i understand missing astronauts
so the test subjects died
and
he's using
homeless people
now
because
he [\h__\h] up
oh
she
well
yeah
i guess
they
and he's like kind of like
uh
not teasing
that's all right he's just making them
join by offering some money
um
okay but how did the astronauts die does
everybody
die
cave johnson you look funny with those
sideburns
it doesn't look so evil though
i've seen more evil looking people wait
where do i continue in here please take
a number oh
they have a number ticketing machine not
a hotel and they sit in here and then
they wait
that's in subject waiting area
remember alert your supervisor if you
see
osha inspector
laptop energies mcgraw accountant
undercover police officer nuclear
regulatory commissioner female accordion
journalist public works inspector okay
so oh fbi too anybody who who could
possibly
figure out that what he is doing in here
is yabe and shouldn't be done
i don't think we can continue in there
maybe that's just a lower room
oh we have another one of those oh
locos big ass logos
oh
[Music]
okay we have to do this without gel
right here
let's first try this come on
but what about these ones maybe do i
need to use these ones too
wait is that
isn't that where it came from no wait no
wait no no no no no no no
that did not work at all
that did not work at all what about here
i was just like while i was falling i
was thinking wait a second what about on
the left side
okay
[Laughter]
no it's just another
little room
oh [\h__\h] what
oh [\h__\h]
this is where we continue
if you're allergic to peanuts you might
want to tell somebody
you may turn your blood into peanut
water for a few minutes peanut butter
make this happen they're going to have
to have a new type of nobel prize to
give us so
hang in there no i'm not a big fan of
peanut butter
i mean if it's if it's maybe like a
peanut butter cookie or something oh
then an achievement ship overboard
ship
this is secret
easter egg room what's the easter egg
borealis i've heard about that before
the borealis is inside the ship
and was this like
was this where the ship would uh chill
the ship parking lot
half-life 2
another game i haven't played
but i can't continue here can i
[Music]
it doesn't open
this is not it
all right we're working on a little
teleportation experiment now this
doesn't work with all skin types so try
to remember which skin is yours and if
it doesn't teleport along with you
remember which skin is yours
i guess this was uh also that was a huge
lower room like why is that one so big
oh my god
damn
if you see an orange jumpsuit hit the
red button wait what why why why wait
i'm wearing a red jumpsuit what do you
mean isn't every test subject supposed
to wear those why are you supposed to
hit the red button
why are they wearing something like
carrying some little
little uh
thing on the on the stick
you mean because they escaped
if they see them like out here i guess
so yeah yeah okay well but uh
this wasn't
this was this didn't but i gotta go over
there i gotta go for that blue portal
okay hmm
why did that jump not work
that i went as high no i mean i guess i
can go a little bit higher
we've been in here right
what
oh wait it doesn't that doesn't work
[Music]
we have
we haven't we've been on the first floor
maybe
[Music]
oh hi
say you're good at murder
what
evil bird bad birds
[Music]
it's a crowd
oh
is this trying to eat the potato
[Laughter]
well i will have fun watching that while
you're getting eaten
no
no i will not
you
you wouldn't have helped me either if i
if i was in this situation
i'll just be watching come on should i
get some ketchup for you crown miss mrs
mr crow
i'll get some ketchup or mayo whatever
you like to eat with the potato
i'm glad there's anything to say
all right i'll help you why is this
shattered
oh thanks
where's it going
he doesn't know what he's
doing this whole place is going to
explode in a few hours
[Music]
no i don't think that makes sense i
don't think i need you to stop him
you look fine to me this is like this is
like when you're like
you're not really sick but you feel like
a little bit of a sniffle and you're
like oh i'm so sick please
treat me nicely and give me some soup
and all that
you look fine gladys
berg is coming back come back bird come
back gladys wants to get kisses from
here
even now the game is telling me to pick
up gladys
hey
are you really gonna be a good potato
who's a good potato who is a good potato
gladys what's the good potato potatoes
huh i got you oh my
is god with it
where's that
button nevermind
[Music]
no screaming aloud don't know
did something move out there
to burn miracles in the atomic fireball
that little idiot is going
don't get so angry gladys it's not good
for you okay just calm down chill for a
moment what is this button
whatever jump on you
the potato was on the button so that now
that we lifted that it changed something
but i can't push it again
was was the potato necessary for me to
go over there
what changed
ah
did this thing
uh
change
the lift
the elevator
oh oh oh
but this thing went up
like that so it's closer now so i can
make the jump maybe
why do i have a [\h__\h] potato with me
now
i guess it's um gladys doesn't know this
is now my emergency in
food
emergency nutrition emergency oration
what's the right word in any case it's
you gladys thank you
i
i would love to make some fried uh
french fries out of you
i keep on dreaming about french fries
glasses you really chose the wrong
person
i love french fries can we go can we go
let's
okay let's go it was normal that we
couldn't reach it was supposed to be
like that
okay
i had chimken nuggets today by the way i
was thinking of you guys when i was
eating them isn't that romantic
reunion
is just up ahead the quicker you get
through the quicker you'll get your 60
bucks this was happening carolyn are the
compensation vouchers ready
gladys is caroline
but was carolina human because it was it
was weird how caroline would say um
goodbye caroline even though she is
caroline so was she even a human to
begin with i thought originally i
thought or caroline was like a a person
working there
but
mm-hmm maybe she was maybe she was
always like a little robot assistant
she was just quirky and making jokes oh
she did a dad joke when i i i perceived
it as a dad joke but i didn't think she
did it on purpose oh
oh it was a dad joke a purpose oh okay
well then okay she was a
person she was she was made into a
computer
okay
it doesn't say thank you for a help for
keeping our enrichment spheres clean
you're welcome
what does this do
oh
no no
wait orange jail this time
oh no i don't even know what that does
uh so we're gonna i guess go here
press that button
orange gel
what does that do
jumping is normal oh [\h__\h] what
is it slippery
feels very slippery
like like i'm on ice
a speed ah
ah but it doesn't go on forever we need
more of that
i suppose
oh is this like a ramp like zoo
so we would want it to
[Music]
i need to go up again first
let me go up first
and then we'll make a portal here and
just try to get that orange [\h__\h] all
over there
yeah
wow that spread nicely like the nutella
on my morning toast
good stuff okay okay
but since that button does something i
suppose
we need that do we
but where's the where's the cube
where's the cube
oh okay we can make it with without the
ramp
that's weird
that is weird
what everyone's telling me to go there
and then left
oh [\h__\h]
it
[Music]
how do i go with it
i need jumpy gel
oh there's a portal
thing here
there's someone there
i don't have jumpy gel
do i need to think with a non-jumpy gel
mater
can i go back
uh
orange remember orange
oh wait i'm going
yeah
wait
wait wait
wait no
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
otherwise the other one will will
disappear
we have to go here
and i use blue
let this go through
i see it i see yeah yeah it's working
over there we go through here too
okay smart
we i you know orange is my color i
understand this color perfectly
oh
[\h__\h] oh my god oh there's a cube
come through
oh
yeah oh [\h__\h] i hope i
okay i use the red color uh what
i can i can go back i can make a portal
there again
wait what what am i doing
wait what i know i just gotta go into
inside the room
and get this
now
we can go back there
now we have the cube
to put
on that button
uh
i guess let's just make one here
i'm so fast oh my god
gas gas gas verb
gas gas gas
alright now it's higher ah there was
like two levels okay okay okay
then let's go up to the second level
way
nicer
isn't open yet oh god it's not over yet
do not leave it
on touch the glass wear shirt and shoes
at all times move quickly what about
pants
do wear shirt and shoes at all times
what about pants what about underpants
and pants and everything else what about
socks huh
do people really only run around in
certain shoes here
that's weird that looks weird
maybe they finally understood bad too
bad pants yeah
bra is optional yeah bam brows too
please move quickly through your test
track not forget to not do not forget to
not touch the glass
do not touch the glass which glass
which glass
there's a control room over there again
ah
what
there's a button up there
i'm going
oh i just fall i can just fall maybe
fall
through
oh
there's nothing
can i fall for
here
no wait wait that makes no sense does it
okay
makes no sense
how do i get back first of all i'm just
okay
um
blue blue is here
we wanna
we want to fall
wait did i i placed it on the ground huh
run through
went through
oh
orange gel kind of
very powerful
speed very powerful
more than 1.6 volts
now we know that
we just need to relax
yeah relax glad i feel like this is
therapy
potato therapy
it's it's time for you to just
go back to the simple times you know
when things were simpler and easier
gladys don't think too much thinking is
not recommended in aperture laboratory
that sounds like something they would
tell you
okay
oh now we have both of them oh there oh
there can we just maybe maybe only deal
with one of them please
huh
that only
it's unreachable for me though i can't
even make a portal there oh no i can
i'll never mind i thought that
that would pro uh
uh not let me do it noodle i can make
one there
yeah and where do we want that to go
um and we want to go to the other side i
suppose we need to use the speed again
can we
like it would be perfect if we had it
straight here but it
can only really go
for example
what does that do
that's
let's use this
comes out of there will it reach over
here no way
what that reaches oh [\h__\h] it flies so
so like
huge distances
no no no
god damn it it accelerates itself
that's a smart gel oh no they reset my
gel no
clown back orange gel paint everything
orange
yes
base color
okay um
did i jump weirdly or
wait wait wait well i mean there's a
reason why there's blue right
if we combine it with blue then i can
because i was there like the distance
was enough but i just there was a fence
in the way so maybe if i get a little
bit of height
with the blue one
uh wait one second wait a second wait
wait wait
oh yeah there we go but though
everything's blue
oh everything's blue
is it really mixed properly now well i'm
not i'm not speeding up anymore
oh
ah okay let's make it orange first
uh
orange first
first layer orange second we're making a
cake
so much for the cake is like
we're making one right now
uh
one here
okay wow look at your surroundings for
god's sake
that's exactly what i wanted yes
just a little bit of blue after speeding
up and
oh shoot whoa whoa whoa
nice
pretty everything's so colorful now i
like that because this old ass factory
looks really
run down anyway
that beautiful bright color really adds
something here
yes
oh
there's isn't that fence in the way
though if i
let's say
i
jump over here
how high did i reach when i came here
did i
bonk against this platform
if that is so
could i like make one here
make one there come out of here but
i mean we gotta try
what else can we do
voices just for going back
because i need something on my height
let's see
yeah okay okay okay
okay i mean
it doesn't hurt to try
let's go
oh that doesn't work
i thought so the fence is
jama
jamal
oh
there's another one over there
ah i don't know you guys keep on telling
me to look up man
uh
ah no it's okay it's okay i can oh get
back while i'm up here and leave that
portal there
okay okay okay okay
and now
blue one here and
let go
that was that should have worked
ah damn it damn it damn it that should
have worked normally
[Laughter]
well we'll make it work i just need to
keep control over my body you know what
froze me up is the potato you know i got
really used to how my body works with
the way it is the way it was and now i
have this little bit of extra weight on
my portal gun and it just froze me off
it's the shitty potato we need to throw
it away or eat it fast lettuce i'm sorry
but i can't work with you like this
yummy
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] i'm letting it go
with your help
i'm a hero i'm a hero
that's what
yeah because you're probably caroline
um
really interesting though
was she like she wasn't in love with him
though right but
i wonder
was she always so
mean as she is now or did he make her
mean
um
[Music]
did he
did did he maybe lose all his test
subjects and the only person was left
was her his assistant maybe so he
tortured her instead and that made her
go insane if you're interested in an
additional 60
flag down a test associate and let them
know you could walk out of here with 120
weighing down your bindle if you let us
take you apart put some science stuff in
you then put you back together good as
new
oh you get some extra money if you
get someone else to join us
oh my god 120 i mean not bad but depends
on how many
tests they make you go through like
if it's worth the time well i would say
generally yes
what are we dealing with here let me
pour some more water
what the 20 what a deal yeah
you can buy two games yeah
or a game and a nintendo switch pro
controller
oh
okay
okay uh what do we have we have this
stuff
where do we want it and when do we want
it now
where where do we want it that's more
important answer that question here
where is here
ah wait over there
there's arrows on the ground
but which one does it matter
let's start with uh
or oopsie orange
wait i just noticed
it's orange and blue points and it's
orange and blue gel wow
they like those colors don't they
that's nice i like those colors too it's
the colors of uh
gouda and kiara
so stream ico
[Laughter]
our song cover from ages ago
yeah galaxy brain big brain
[Music]
and kiwawa is literally the story of us
and kibaba forever together
uh
let me take a look over there let me go
over there
will you enjoy not so fast not so fast
you
oh we can go over there too
where i don't know where the [\h__\h] do we
go there's something over there as well
and over there
oh there's a cube look
a cube chan
i didn't see a button though
one
[Music]
man this is too big
it's too big i don't know where it would
go well let me take a look over here
oh
we might want either some orange or some
blue here oh there's the button
and we can jump over there to push the
button but that would mean we first want
the cube
the cube is over there but that's so far
away i don't think i can reach that
[Music]
wait where exactly is it over there
i want to land
where the cube is on that plot how do
you think it's it is on the same
like line you know what i mean so that's
kind of sus if it's on the same height
not on the same height but like you know
what i mean
it's kind of sad so it's probably like
oh
can i go like
i don't know
i gotta test it out but what about this
is this helpful this this stuff i don't
know
um
i will
we'll test it out
so ah i run in there
and then
i come out of here
but
do i only need the orange or would some
blue be helpful let's test it out first
how far we get
oh oh wait
can we get some blue on there
that that thing there well i want some
blue there because we bounced off there
get a bit more bounciness and then we'll
get where the cube is holy [\h__\h] i'm on
fire today
uh
um so it's pulls
here look at the blue yes yes yes
i've successfully charged my brain you
know
okay uh
all right all right this should be fun
now this should be fine let's go
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] what
game i'm not that heavy okay
uh
let's just go back this way
but wait
but it was over there right we can't go
straight over there
i would
say
what
i thought the button was here
it's over there
it is right there
okay
okay okay one
one important step is done not although
this just
flipped over
probably so i can land on
it i don't know when i need to go there
but uh
is that on the same height
no it doesn't look like it
no no no no i know i think we
hmm
oh wait from here to here
maybe maybe maybe it is to there
i need to get a better look
ah it is on the same line again
it is on the same line yeah yeah of
course i need some stuff there i missed
a step
really
uh
can i not get some
blue on there when it's like this
but how was it how was it positioned
before
uh
if i like have this one here and then i
got damn it
um
if i go over there
put like
an orange one okay okay i'll check my
dad
i put an
orange one there
uh
yeah yeah yeah that's okay i'll go back
through here
not like i wanted there but i wanted
it
no that doesn't that doesn't work
no no no no no
no no can i
[Music]
uh can um cheese this no no that doesn't
work
[Music]
oh wait that's so i'm just that's this
is what i had in mind originally anyway
but i forgot while i was coming back
here i forgot
okay okay now we have it on the platform
i hope i land on the blues though
okay okay oh
okay
uh let's go
nice
let's go
here oh
oh
oh that just happened in in like the the
mini amount of time where i
didn't place both portals but only one
because i don't remember putting blue on
here
i think i want orange though ah no i
want i don't want blue ah
no no no no no no i don't want blue i
don't want blue let me uh this is orange
this is blue
i don't want blue um no no i don't want
or yeah i want blue there yeah yeah yeah
yeah
i don't know what you're saying chad but
i know that i know it so don't tell me
anything
it's okay i'm going through this um
so now i will uh
put oh [\h__\h] i want all right i can
probably
i can probably
reach that to make a portal yeah yeah
yeah uh
orange
okay okay okay
oh god is this gonna work
we have blue on both of the platforms
it should work
[Music]
so that's a complete reassembly
if that actually works
then that does
sound like one way to get rid of a tumor
so
i mean
i don't know if you still
i
i suppose back then
um what year was that
whatever year they probably didn't have
much uh any other ways to get rid of a
tumor maybe i don't know how far they
were back then
but
so that means that
um you have two options you have uh the
chance of dying because of the tumor
um or the other option is you have a
chance of maybe dying because of you
know having your body being taken apart
but there's also a chance that you'll
survive and be tumor free after that
so
there's higher chances of being tumor
free and alive
if you go with aperture sciences
aperture laboratory laboratories
whatever yeah
it could go wrong but
it's more likely
to go wrong
if you just don't do it so you should do
it
i mean
i mean you're just gonna believe
plus 120 yeah and now 60. only only 120
of you get someone else to join the test
well
i don't know if anyone really took them
up for that but
for staggering your way through aperture
sciences
you've made some real contributions to
society
and for that humanity is grateful if you
had any belongings please pick them up
now we don't want old newspapers and
sticks cluttering up the building for
many of you i realized
that's it that's all he sees them for as
test subjects
we're not
loitering longer than when
oh nice nice floor
all forms must be fell down the ledge
legibly and completely before eligible
to receive a payment of success
can i have my 60 dollars please hello
hello hey no one there
that's [\h__\h] i did all the tests
where's my sixty dollars oh
oh and we need to cancel apertures
laboratories oh my god that's dark
is there a secret here
this reminds me of um
you know when we went for the dark in in
super liminal
and found some stuff
but i don't know if that was supposed to
be like that or
is there something there i want to find
something secret
there's nothing in this dark space is so
sus
there's like i see something there
see weasley at least could have lit that
up by shitty glasses potato can't even
light up that little space
oh i got my 60 from the super chat is
that aperture
holy [\h__\h] they're still they still exist
oh [\h__\h] them can someone ban that super
chat i'm just kidding
that's a short trip there was no
nothing in here
okay gamma
pump station gamma
what
this way i mean this one oh
station gamma let's go
alpha beta gamma this
is
can you really think that hard with what
was it 1.1 volt
that that seems like something you would
have to think pretty hard for to figure
out at least for potato like you if
you're smart as me and you figure it out
immediately but you're a potato right
now gladys do you remember i can't say
it often enough
i really need to point out your [\h__\h]
potato right now gladys and that makes
you that puts you way lower on you know
the
scale of smartness than me like by by
kilometers by
way more than kilometers
a million [\h__\h] billion kilometers
oh in the scale you know you understand
holy [\h__\h] there's a bird [\h__\h] gel i
thought the water was the third thing
oh no
what is the last one if we had
jumping and running
what is the last one sticking but we can
that's that doesn't make sense
or maybe it does make sense
so that for example if you put it to
like a wall
instead of bouncing off you want to be
you want to stay at that wall maybe i
don't know oh dear we start we um
we started something else there too okay
yeah i don't know what it is but we'll
find out yes yes
wait is that already the gel
white wait it's
like everywhere now
this is leaking too
oh
there's a
portal wall here
wait can i if it's a sticky gel then i
can literally walk on walls
like spiderman
that would be too
wait i mean what does it do
what is it leaking from somewhere only
the blue one is leaking can i let the
white one link
did i turn on everything
i did turn on everything right
oh
it makes everything portable
what's the right word for that
portable
poor poor
poor portable port
[Music]
portal
okay
so
cool i don't know where to go we need to
go up here
um
okay well i can't make one here because
the
blue is covering the white one so
now hold on
i want
i suppose we want to go up here but
that's not porterable maybe we can make
it porterable
uh there's also this wall there which
makes me feel
like something needs to go here too but
no maybe not no no no it's just
continuing maybe from here i don't know
uh
feels like um
now with a third gel
i think my brain is slowly logging out
oh
no
those those kind of walls are always
like superstars they it's such a
giveaway
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] yeah and you're right i never i
never look up and i never look down
[Music]
okay
ah can i get some blue here oh yeah i
can i can totally get some blue here um
blue portal orange portal oh [\h__\h] all
right that doesn't work
i cannot get some glow here okay
why not
i want some blue here
oh oh you never mind
okay because one thing i've learned that
i didn't understand
during the last episode yesterday one
thing i've learned is that
there's actually like
if i jump from this height and land on
the blue [\h__\h]
i will also jump the same amount of
height you know what i mean i thought it
was just like
i don't know
maybe not the exact
same but yeah it is the exact same yeah
i didn't realize that
that's good to know holy [\h__\h] there's a
lot of orange hair whoa
oh it's okay i can go
as long as i'm just fast let's go
carla the complainer says is that
another version of a karen my new boss
is the robot
yeah it is because i mean complainer
what did you know roberts are smarter
than you robots work harder than you
robots are better than you
volunteer for testing today
wait how does that come
how does that work with the other one
how does that like
connect
wait [\h__\h] he's a road look at his eyes
yeah
kawaii
she has been replaced but but we're
testing with humans
but they say robert's so better why
don't you test with robots then huh why
don't you test with your super awesome
robots then huh at least okay i'll agree
that robots are great because robots are
probably at least also made in a way or
at least you can like program that in a
way that they would not
feel pain either you know
isn't that great you could have test
subjects
that
don't feel pain wouldn't that be amazing
no no no we kill no birds here
i am
all right
yeah go back to thinking
okay
yeah i signed co-op uh i saw i saw in
co-op that you play robots i saw that
um cute cute little robots i want to be
territon can i be turrican
i want to be i want to be the very best
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
all right
we fell down well can we not just make
it like i don't know here
i kind of want to go higher
okay
i'm just testing
wow
open
cloud i'm so sorry to put you through
this deja vu oh my god
[Music]
oh i'm here now
i'm here now
you didn't think i could make it did you
want to go higher
oh [\h__\h] that's not it that's a sign
oh i cannot go higher
i mean i don't think it says that that
wall wait what oh no
we came from here
didn't we
no did we come from the room above god
wait from which one did it came from
because there was uh there was a
it came from here
i just saw no now i see the room below
hello
open
that's weird no i came from
oh came from above
i came from above i'll get [\h__\h] today
what's down there
what if i go down there
ah wait i remember this place
[Music]
we were here before
i'm going back what do you mean i'm
going back
am i going back
no no no i'm not going back
wait
wait no we're not going back because
that thing with glados here was was uh
was new
but indeed we've seen we've been there
we've been over there before
yeah i fought so till the angle is a
hint like as if they want me to go like
and land right over there ah
i need i need to make this portable
or i know we need to make this portable
let's let's go oh [\h__\h]
i was too eager or ride or ride or
rattle run all right and ride all right
all right
hey but you need to understand that um
you know
the fact that
there's like so many walls over there
to portal to
and like
pretty close to this room too
wouldn't that make you want to
go over there with portals i was just
thinking with portals the problem was i
was not thinking of gel
[Laughter]
i'm trying i'm trying to watch my step
really i'm really trying it's really
dangerous here welcome to the enrichment
center
is he sick participation
what's sounds against the results
though the bean counter told me we
literally could not afford to buy seven
dollars worth much less 70 million
bottom anyway
[Music]
poison out of a man's bloodstream unlike
gives you lemons make lemonade
let's all stay positive and do some
science get here
did the moon [\h__\h] poison him and that's
what he said just as fast as possible
oh no he's wait and i shouldn't be
feeling for him he's suffering that's
good
oh it made him sick well good great
great great
and now only now that he's sick he
thinks oh maybe i shouldn't be testing
with human subjects
duh
now that he feels some of the effects
from it now he's like
maybe i but but no it's probably not
even that it's just he can't use humans
anymore because
yeah all the everyone's finding out and
nobody's probably volunteering anymore
so
probably it wasn't even that yeah anyway
uh what
which
where did that come from i came from
here right
yeah okay
secret room
we need a special code
okay
that's in subject waiting area you guys
have a lot of waiting areas oh oh now
he's looking more even he got an old and
got rid of the sideburns you can like
see him changing this portraits in these
portraits
i see my portals through
all of the walls
rabbits don't sleep they can test and do
your job wow volunteer for testing today
are you telling are you telling robots
to volunteer for testing
oh i thought they were speaking to
humans with this poster
it's confusing what does that do
opens the door does it stay open it
better stay open
i see the subject waiting area
oh i had something like i was put in a
room like this exactly like this
sideways with the windows and all that
and the projector here and when i made
it through the auditions the the
audition in progress of not whole life
but the airline that i
the big big ass airline that i um
signed up for
um to work at and they were like yes
we will take you please now follow us to
watch this super inspiring
video
of uh our airline that you're going to
be working at you're right no i didn't
work for aperture
every time no no no no no no no no no no
no no but it was i remember that that
was nice it was like only me in the room
because everyone else already um it was
like literally at the end of the
audition day
everyone else was gone
i was the last one to make it in i was
sitting there and i was so happy
yeah a certain a certain big ass german
airline
i was like so proud of myself
after that whole auditioning progress
where where honestly i didn't even do
that well
uh
surprisingly they took me anyway
and yeah i was so excited and so happy
i was looking forward to move to germany
and then work as a steward is
from there for this cool airline do some
long distance flights to to japan so i
could visit japan anytime
for work but still that's cool yeah they
saw my potential
[Music]
foreign really inspiring
beautiful
okay what does this say here's not
testif you're allergic to lunar sediment
and or starch
oh i don't think anyone would know that
they are
allergic to lunar sediment
that's not really something you usually
get exposed to you have fulfilled a
monthly test self-election
quota uh-huh if you're confident enough
in your work performance to unvolunteer
from the test self-election project wait
what does that mean i don't understand
i'm not even going to take the time to
try to understand let's go is this open
yay
did we finish a chapter
a reunion chapter no not yet
ah
huh
the women's day will fire me if i don't
test that oh it's okay i don't need to
be fired because i don't even work here
i don't even work here
i don't remember signing anything
ooh
where is this gonna go
now where is this gonna go
hello new huge [\h__\h] room where are we
going
oh wait well
me i mean i need i know i can create new
surfaces with this but
first of all it looks like milk
first of all though
oh wait can it please go the other way
oh [\h__\h] you know like should i cover
everything here
what if i cover the whole room here
splatoon
monochrome splatoon
why is this not working
i cover everything maybe that helps
i don't know it probably won't help am i
wasting my time
[Music]
wait i mean
i i i i made a i made a portable surface
over there isn't that good
isn't that good
i think that's pretty cute
passion i can't reach baby
let me go
am i supposed to be here
did i cheat
i feel like i cheated i feel like that
was not how you're supposed to do it
um
where is it is it maybe it is who knows
can i put it over there no i'm not you
know what yes you know what we're just
gonna
go with the flow yeah spread it
everywhere the more the merrier
how did you guys
that was the attend really
that was okay good good good good good i
felt a little bit stupid hey there's
something landing on here nice
more like on that side please
spread it everywhere
let's go
spread it like
move it
why should where do i want it where do i
want to end up at anyway
where do i want to end them
up here
there's a door
become as milk oh god everything's black
and white
yeah hope crony gets better soon
everyone wish cronie
uh a get well thing
yeah yeah wish her to get well
yay it looks so clean
now
they needed a new coat of color anyway
you're welcome
aperture
not even getting paid for this
once we have filled everything with this
white liquid
we can start thinking about what to do
with it
nice it's fun this is splatoon right
this is how splatoon works
[Music]
time to play some splatoon
okay
did i get the white color everywhere
where i need it to be oh let's go up
here by the way
oh
this room is very big too but i suppose
we gotta go here there's also another
extra room probably just a lower room
over there
well
[Music]
this this seems of course very sus
there we go
what if what if what
[Music]
that doesn't get me very far
uh
i'm gonna get up there
um
i'm stuck
there was a portal there i forgot
what do we have over here
what do we have yeah and that's where i
came from right
elevator
um
[Music]
not even been two hours and my brain
already stopped working
and i can do stuff like falling down
from here and i don't know but
how does that help me and i think in
lines again
i want to get up there maybe i don't
know
but what is this for where would that
bring me to let me let me look at it
from this perspective oh that would get
me up here
but i need to fall from pretty up high
so first i need to
land somewhere i need that i need that
juice
to
go somewhere high
the hand is literally feeding it back oh
dear
i don't see anything up there to put a
portal on either
[Music]
i'm very close
am i
i need to
um
[Music]
um um
this is this is
these walls are stars
[Music]
oh maybe not maybe they're not sus
maybe i'm sells
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
ah
no
good try though
try
ah
oh
this literally ball jump uh strategy
again but no we're not like we're
jumping but we're just this way we can
get higher and higher oh my god
okay
uh
there we go so that's how what color was
that blue on that side
[Music]
now we have
momentum right
so
if i fall through there
i will play
oh dear there's not much on the floor
here
if i were to place something there i
would need some more white color there
now
on the floor please
this way
i might be completely wrong though
i might be completely wrong oh oh yeah i
was uh there was a platform well
whatever just just
just trust believe in cuava okay
uh okay
big brain
okay
okay okay
uh
blue is there
orange is there
it goes off
yes oh wow
that was a nice jump would look like it
could be too long ago don't make
lemonade why not life take the lemons
back get mad i don't want your damn
lemons what am i supposed to do with
these
the man to see life sweaters make life
rule the day and thought it could give
cave johnson lemons do you know who i am
what's your problem i'm the man who's
gonna burn your house down
[Music]
the point is
if we can store music on a compact disc
why can't we store a man's intelligence
and personality on one so i have the
engineers figuring that out now brain
mapping artificial intelligence we
should have been working on it 30 years
ago
i will say this
and i'm gonna say it on tape so
everybody hears it a hundred times a day
if i die before you people can pour me
into a computer i want carolyn to run
this place
now she'll argue
she'll say she can't she's modest like
that but you make her
now put her in my computer i don't care
all right test's over
you can head on back to your desk
too many thoughts now i have too many
thoughts
she reacted to
him being very aggressive
way more than when he was normal even
normal whatever is normal with him
that's so that's a weird point
um
and yeah okay so carolyn was a human
before and and now yeah because he wants
this place to be run
by someone else because he's dying he
wants it to be run by carolyn uh
he did not quite um no why are we
putting her already in a in a computer
though just to make sure she never dies
oh
um
oh dear carolyn didn't apparently maybe
didn't want it though in the beginning
as he says she might not
not be um
volunteering for it
but she seems in his opportunity to have
potential potential and would be the
best person to go with
thank you for volunteering please return
to your desk and wait for the
opportunities
poor carol and yeah she was turned into
a computer
i wonder how young she was before they
turned her into a computer zoom view why
why
because it's so far away
oh dear there's a lot of portable
surfaces
eh
i suppose we need to fall
higher and higher and higher or
but there's nothing on the ground
what can i for example go up there
there seems to be something to stand on
nice a room
doesn't seem to have anything
special in it though
well we have a room there at least we're
already up pretty high at this point
okay
hmm
she's in her 20s 40s and 40s what does
that mean once in so many different
years
she went to fame until she was 30.
um
oh i guess we just keep on going
higher like this we don't really need to
think much
um is there something to stand on yes
what's what do we have here a
window uh we're almost at three thousand
meters we gotta go even higher
all right this is but this is too simple
there must be more behind this
i didn't look into that room but it
looks like the same kind of room
[Music]
oh
is that a stuck elevator
and probably uh go there
and
land a little bit below
okay
what's it this one am i supposed to
enter that
i suppose so
the ground of the elevator is a portable
surface
what does that tell you guys did i tell
you guys
this here
as well
[Music]
so here we have some a way to make
momentum
the ceiling is not
there there's no ceiling so we can fall
pretty
high
i don't know if that's enough for
whatever but let's try
it
i made it here
now oh i can have can i have even more
is this this is about the same height
though
[Music]
that doesn't look like
anything
where do we want to go up here
or up there
right but we can
can i fall
can i
like
if i fall
through here and i will just
try
[Music]
uh
i don't know
[Music]
can i reach that no
i'm gonna get dizzy
i'm overthinking
ah
[Music]
why am i overthinking what's there
what's there to
think
wow my game really lagged oh god oh god
my game had a huge lag just now did you
guys see that on stream
did the whole stream lag
[Music]
stream lag two
sorry about that
i know i'm
yeah
okay
[Music]
i don't know if this is correct though
oh [\h__\h]
where where no no that's not
[Music]
that's not it
can i like i don't know fall
here
that that's such a weird spot nah no way
[Music]
i know
i know i don't know i don't know
um
[Music]
oh wait i think thank you
stop fooling with me and playing around
with me okay okay uh
[Music]
i forgot what i just which one i placed
before
[Music]
uh which color i saw something over
there where was it where was it here
which color um
uh we are
[\h__\h]
orange
okay
um
yeah
no comment
on that one that was a little bit
unnecessary
yeah did you guys get motion sick too
that would made me feel a little bit
dizzy too
that would have been horrible in vr i
would have probably thrown up
um
[Music]
wow
i'm not going to lie to you the odds are
a million to one and that's with some
generous rounding
still though let's get mad if we're
going to explode let's get mad let's get
mad
let's explode with some dignity i like
that
oh there's more falling there there's a
hole there oh yeah
what
all right
all right naruto i'm on my way naruto
that's okay i'll be okay
ah nope that was um
that's not it there's nothing here but
there's this here
maybe that's for later but that you know
all the angled ones are always sus
uh
that's not one of them
but okay well all of these ones are
portable so maybe i need to fall from
one of them and try my best to fall into
a hole down there
then beyond and then
make a portal there and beyond i don't
know that's
that's that's wishful thinking
but
you can try
yeah
[Music]
you gotta like try to
move while i'm falling
and i would place
an orange one down there and one um and
let's try
no [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] okay
i'll get i'll get better at this
that is not enough
momentum probably
[Music]
[Laughter]
what is going on
is it okay to just fall from here i
wonder
let's say we'll fall from here
and then we'll do this
yeah okay
okay
oh look what's drooping out of here
oh
what a perfect placement that is
oh how wonderful
oh oh i can from here i can get even
more momentum
all right
uh
like this
do i really want this much momentum holy
[\h__\h] let's go
yeah yeah hello everybody
how's it going we're going higher and
higher to put gladys back into her body
i wish i could put her back into a human
body though
oh what's this
over what's this
huh
what's this
hmm i don't wanna
caution hole
i don't wanna go down again can i
why already seen the next room over
there
this looks
complicated
need i need more
blue probably but
no
i need to get up there
how do i get up there
are these fences
um
if i let some blue stuff go uh through
this portal
yeah
wouldn't that just land like somewhere
here or or here oh depends on
the angle
if it were to go through here
eh
does it even land on surfaces like that
ever
then then i would go there too and then
build like that no that that doesn't
work no no no no
no no no
it also doesn't land on on surfaces like
this because it has holes
so
would be too good to be true
try it
okay
i don't want to bounce off of it right
now
where where was the blue stuff
again where was it
oh
i don't remember
wasn't it
where did i get that from
no more it stopped what
what what
what do you mean it stopped why did it
stop i didn't turn anything off
no
need more of that please uh all right
but i think this hole is obviously sus
or maybe it's just for me to get up here
to begin with
booing
i already solved it
why did i solve it
[Music]
where does that go to
what then we'll figure it out just give
me a
give me a second
wait a second did i did i
yeah i was i was there before no worries
no no no that's not
[Music]
what did i just spy with my little eye
oh
it's not that i can jump up here
it's just when you jump you see
something where you can put a a portal
at
a
hello hello
many liquids
oh this will be fun
i can make this
go
to all kinds of places again but
we're gonna make them cool here but no
oh oh yeah right it doesn't go anywhere
else no a little bit but it mostly stays
in this perfect square that's that's
too good to be true come on
come on spread it a little bit
a little bit be so kind
maybe i don't even need it
hold on
[Music]
there's there's
something here
is there even
space between the wall and the
uh the
i can't speak english anymore
oh wait
that's blue
it will go through there yeah yeah oh
it's an angled one
wow
that's a nice color um
so much color it looks so fresh i'm
gonna get sick by the fumes of the paint
though i'm breathing in a lot of paint
films
okay
ah
we um
well now we can make a
portal
perhaps here if we wanted to and do
stuff like this like spread the blue one
around
or where is that going
no the blue one is extremely bouncy and
just goes to the other side of the room
and just disappears okay what about this
one
this one
[Music]
at least lands over here but that
doesn't help me either
okay now we're just gonna spread
some of the white one how about that
wait we did that already the white one
lunch
partially on top of the platform
ah
we can put it here
[Music]
but but that we might want the orange
one
we might want the orange one for that
so we have some
oh wait what the [\h__\h] happened what the
[\h__\h] just happened what the [\h__\h] just
happened what the [\h__\h] is that
yeah wait no no don't delete my portals
oh
i bounced off that blue
square
i'm not accidentally solving this online
[Music]
i bounced off and landed exactly
in my portal
i want to try it again
what is that telling me we need to get
up pretty high here maybe
i would say that the orange hair is
correct
and the blue here is correct too
what the orange portal up
oh oh yeah oh you guys are helping me
too much today
now oh
oh i want blue here
i want some blue
right there
you guys are helping me too much though
please don't help me so much i i want to
solve it myself oh wait that doesn't
work i want white i want white up there
um
i don't need i need to go down
i again i want white there so i can make
a portal up there and then make the blue
go to the bottom
complicated but yes
is did it do what i wanted it to do
yeah now we have a white wall up here
and we can make
um the blue stuff go for there
yeah yeah well i will ask you guys i
guess if i really desperately need some
help but see this one if i get out
myself
this one i figured out myself yeah i'm
really scared to look at the chat
because i i saw that there's always so
many backseating comments but it's not
really what i'm looking for
maybe you guys can um turn it down a
little bit okay
okay
i'm i'm i've proven already or that i'm
smart oh why is there one is there some
blue here oil oil
i gotta color it orange again
i'm gonna color it orange yeah yeah yeah
yeah
that's how i like it
and
[Music]
we made it
oh there's more white stuff here
uh
why is it blinking
theory i can already go there eh
what
okay
why
what's this
and this why why can i
am i suppose not supposed to bring some
color with me
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
oh no i'm just this this is this is
supposed to be used i feel like every
every wall
where you can make a portal
is supposed to be
used for something
but
this one
not so much like how how can i use it
it's angled but there's a
the skate in front of it so
so
oh
no never mind
i might need it
where am i
maybe
it is useful after all because if we can
can you just
can you just not
bounce for a minute okay can we
um
what was that that we just saw uh we
have
uh orange right we need orange
to go through here
see i'm telling you i'm telling you
they're always they always need to be
used
mess yeah but no they're just getting a
fresh coat of paint
nothing wrong with that they should be
thanking me should i go all the way up
there
shouldn't i oh
this is really trippy right now okay
okay okay
wait this looks so trippy for me
do you understand why this is only me or
also you guys
oh you should what
whoa
is it like this
oh my god oh my god this is up i think
this is up
i think this is up
wait how do i
i'm stuck
what
what what what oh
even the game is telling me this way up
but it's so confusing if this is up why
can't i just walk up if that's um
oh my god i can't look at this
i can't look at this
where are we going though
oh god can i go here oh hallelujah
[Music]
thank god that's over
it was like an optical illusion it was
[\h__\h] with my mind
i wasn't the only one right
gosh
oh my god oh look at that big big door
i'm starting to feel oh
sick
[Music]
okay that gave me motion sickness
okay where are we going are we going up
there
uh
no
is this maybe this over here no that's
too easy
oh that's so easy to reach that's not
where i need to go everything that's
easy to reach is not where i need to go
see it doesn't open
but we can go
up here but that's also probably an
insignificant door
yeah
but we can fall down from here
nice and
uh
no
here
let's try
easy
i've got an idea okay easy lemon squeeze
i know i don't like lemons but yes
look at it okay
oh
is that so know your paradise and even
the rogue ai stance still remain calm
scream this statement is false new
mission refuses mission does the set of
all sets contain itself
we need to scream at really this is
false
you're fake or what yeah is that what
you're saying
just yell some words at him
the [\h__\h]
i pressed it twice now it's [\h__\h]
opening
is it just gonna be a tiny ass door
again
no
oh it's connecting some more pumps for
more gel wow
and then we'll go into the other
upcoming rooms i guess
oh look at that
is that from me
oh it's gonna connect down there
and open not a huddle okay let's go down
and see if we can
work with that i guess
uh
for a little while
i guess i'll just jump
yeah oh
okay
when we have a new platform here
let's look at it from this new
perspective
for once i don't have to eat myself eh
oh it goes up on its own i was just
about like to say oh do i have to press
the button and then quickly go down
i really don't have to eat myself it's
happening what i'm saying i should be
okay you're doing it for me
you'll be fine gladys you're you you
seem to have had really that redemption
art that i was hoping for
i hope you don't
undo it again
but right now
you seem like you have redeemed yourself
or about to redeem yourself you're
trying to redeem yourself i'm just
checking if there's anything to see over
here
what is this like what is this is this
holding up all the testing rooms and
stuff like all kinds of
factory
buildings
she just doesn't want to be a potato
what but i also was a potato before i
don't i don't think potatoes being a
potato is that bad
i think
we shouldn't be that negative about you
know being a potato oh look at that
we're like really back inside oh dear
are we going uh straight to wheatley
oh chapter done i think
chapter
oh was that was all of that that one
chapter the
you reunion chapter that was a long one
the itch chapter eight how many are
there guys
please tell me
is the potato gonna have an inch do i
have to scratch the potato
nine
oh wait i'm so close but i they told me
that these last chapters are really long
for god's sake your boxes with legs
it's literally your only purpose walking
onto buttons how can you not do the one
thing you're designed for
wait a second
i don't want him
to notice us
[Laughter]
just had to
grab that one really quickly
continue
very very very cold look just
[Music]
can get over that little
step you can do it
give me more
okay
wheatley is trying to
create new kinds of robots so he has
more
more new things to attack me with
guys we're back in the in the new
factory aren't we
yeah we're done with the old one
and in with the new
[Music]
should i rescue them
is this a rescue mission
oh yeah he'll probably come back to
check up if it's uh so
you'll hit him with a pair of dogs
guys you hit me with a paradox what tell
me a good paradox hi
oh it's two turrets and one isn't it oh
it's crammed up in there
captain give me a give me a paradox
this statement is a lie
oh look at this one
yeah that is literally a paradox isn't
it no it's not it's actually not
you could think it is but
it isn't really which one was first
there's actually an answer to the
question people act as if there is no
answer to those questions
[Music]
the good thing is she can't even
think that far anyway as a potato
uh
false look at the
[Music]
up it falls great seeing you guys again
don't just turn your mom it turns out
i'm a little bit short on test subjects
right now so is that perfect uh he seems
calm again though
maybe we can just talk with him uh off
we go
oh you just want me to walk further now
to do some more tests really oh my god
[Music]
priorities set straight you have no idea
what it's like in this body
i have to test all the time while i get
this this itch you know it must be
hardwired into the system
and gladys knows a thing or two about
that i do test oh
man alive nothing feels better it's just
so you're gonna test and i'm gonna watch
and everything is gonna be just well at
least testing is the priority and not
killing nuclear meltdown came out
you shouldn't ignore that one um but
okay
priorities priorities priorities
priorities guys testing we'll be happy
if we test just everything will be fine
as long as we test test
wow yay we're back to the cool rooms
area nothing deadly
okay you're not done with it huh uh okay
well impossible um as it is to imagine
there actually is a solution devilishly
hidden
shouldn't be so hard
well as long as that feels good to you
we can do it over and over again
as long as you don't kill me i don't uh
are we good
let's just continue we have easy rooms
yeah it makes me feel better too the
door there
i love to make him wait
uh oh
is so difficult why don't you just keep
solving
this test
say what and i can just like watch you
solve it
yeah that sounds much easier this is
this is this this this feels right
can i not i want to go from here
oh
this is weird this back door is weird
i don't want to go from the back door
[Music]
i was the same one
yeah i was thinking
over and over again do it again do it
again again
dude that's okay with me here there we
go
new
oh there we go
good for you
good good good for you
all right so my paradox idea didn't work
yeah
i'm not surprised not much of a
[\h__\h] potato can think of
luckily by the looks of things he knows
as much about test building as he does
about logical contradictions
shouldn't have left it till potato will
think up a solution
um
now you heard you he's not smart enough
with paradox to work
that is hey come on wait lee was
somewhat smart smarter than the potato
at least
so we we should be able to outsmart
gladys in potato state all right
everything's good i just invented
something
this is one of my tests
not entirely look at the word test there
on the wall i mean your test this looks
new
this doesn't look familiar to me
what the [\h__\h] is happening
did noises make me
worry a little bit
it's like water in here
oh
it's like water
the sound is like damned and everything
when i'm in there oh i want to go pick
up the the parrot cube
[Music]
what whoa whoa whoa
whoa
another new thing to
to work with ugh
wasn't it already enough
they're torturing me so how do we go
down
no i want to go down
ah portals
excuse me
now stand still just be a cube okay
don't do anything else just be a cube
oh
okay and then make the cube hit this oh
i thought the jails would be the last
thing
i'm impressed lately but apparently glad
it's part of this not you
what you're gonna catch up with me
okay should i go up
going up
going up bye bye bye bye
next room
can you maybe while he's using your
tests
reprogram them
into something
that we can use to kill him
well probably you can't do it as a
potato
yeah and at least like she knows what
they
are and how they work so
i mean that should be of some use
i can't why not
you're on your own
what what's the reason for that
why can't you not is that against your
morals or something yeah
out of smaller tests that i found lying
around jammed them all together buttons
it's got funnels
yeah these pips are involved it's got it
all it's got it all absolute dynamite
are we only doing 19 more like okay not
19 um
17 more tests really really oh [\h__\h] no
look at these new things too
[Music]
oh man
all right
all right we'll probably redirect this
uh stream again
maybe through here let's fall into it
okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] uh wait
that's gonna happen a lot if all these
tests are like this then
yeah that might happen a lot
it's got funnels
it was just the wrong color
although
[Music]
there must be a way to do it without
dying myself
now let me look at it again
let me look at it again
oh wait
[Music]
there
can we can we um
go one more time
uh which color would i put there oh
orange
orange yeah wow
a bit no that's actually this is taking
too long okay i'll just tell you how to
solve it really
over
there will hurt you okay oh wait no no
that was fine no one's fine that was
fine
i had the right idea that was okay
i don't need your help wheatley
i'm smart
um
oh i don't need to catch it we need to
catch it with the flow
um
i need to catch it with the flow
and i got you i got you
i got you
and now
like this and i'll catch you on the flip
side come here
now i have you just stand still let me
do some more thinking where was the
button
where is the button i saw a button
somewhere
i hear oh
this is easy okay
oh yeah
don't be so satisfied
crips me
[Music]
well i'm out for you gladys good for you
but yeah wheatley is making me feel a
bit awkward about solving these puzzles
right now maybe i should stop maybe i
should stop solving them
and cut hair on my
snacks eventually yeah
so 19 yeah coming don't start yet don't
start yet
you are not going to believe this i
found a sealed off wing hundreds
hundreds of perfectly good test chambers
just sitting there filled with skeletons
what
this is exactly how we're supposed to be
i see absolutely no problem here
mm-hmm good job good job you wheatley
okay so we have an airflow or water flow
whatever it is
um
we wanted to carry us over there
i suppose to push the button and then
drop a cube and then catch it again with
the air
same principle
there we go we're going to the other
side pretty simple
thank god the riddles are more simple
again just for a little while
okay
i'm eating those
those white peanut snacks by the way
um
white chocolate peanut snacks from the
spanish
snack box huh
wait did that fall in front of it or
behind it
i can't quite see where where is it
falling uh uh let's look
at it like this
should it be here
no no more in the front
there we go okay
um
now we get this one again
so i can pick it up here
you know what i was complaining about
this new element but it's not so bad
it moves and it's on when you let it go
don't move
it's don't
so bad this new element i like it okay
we want to use this jumpy platform but
it will make me
let me test it you stay here okay
this feels dangerous
get it help me help me
i should have gone with you after all
um
damn it
let me go back
help
okay i'm going back i'm not going to
jump down into the void and die down
there this is how we're going back
oh you were in the perfect position
there all right
um
[Music]
wait
um
nice safe right i know parkour
i was born for this so i suppose
oh i can make it i'm not sure i don't
have a full plan but this is somewhat
part of a plan
uh okay
[\h__\h] oh you just stay there
ah
[\h__\h]
repeat
okay i should go the other way
messed up
i messed up
wait i can just walk oh
oh
oh overthinking again
but
i have to redo the whole thing
please don't say i have to redo it
give me my cube please
ah
um
just have to get the cube back
oh [\h__\h] that was too early sorry
i'm getting impatient
by the way a little update about my
workout since i've been very busy with
physical therapy i'm doing it the whole
week
um
and and we've been doing some low-key
workouts in the physical therapy
i actually haven't gotten to work on
i've been very busy so i just see
physical therapy as my workout until i'm
done with it and then i'll go back to my
normal workout again
yeah don't worry i'm not i'm not gonna
quit yet
not yet
it's just uh
i am very busy right now
oh it's so cute why is it so cute
can we just
can we just walk over here
come on
i can't i can't jump while i'm in here
can you just
this was not how i'm supposed to do it i
think
uh but okay it works
now
for here i should butt up
the wig how do i get
the cube there
oh i know
wait
keep jumping
come with me
we go here and then we
yeah
[Music]
here we go
where am i here finally
whoa
not so bad i feel
like i actually prefer these over the
jelly
are you happy lately
are you happy
eh what what
when to redo no
[\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h]
yeah
[Music]
why did i jump down i don't know what
what did i do wrong
he was already
like preparing to
moan again
he doesn't need me so i just yeah yeah
what what happened what did i do wrong
this hurts to watch then you're welcome
to leave if it hurts you i'm sure we'll
be fine
or you're welcome to play the game
yourself if it hurts you
i'm not trying to hurt you i'm not
aperture laboratories
i'm just trying to get through it you
know it's probably nothing
keep testing while i look for a way out
yeah welcome to leave so that last test
was seriously disappointing oh laser
apparently being civil isn't motivating
you so let's try her away all right
fatty adopted
fatigue no parents okay wheatley you can
leave my chat too
oh yeah explain what is wrong with it
thank you gladys let's fight this
together
[Music]
um
do we need do we need you or do i just
kill you
i think i just kill you
uh
how about
first of all what does what happens if
ah you get hit by
a little bit of this air other
[Music]
behind it
backwards walking not my strength
need to learn how to moonwalk
successfully
why would it hurt me i've been so nice
to your character's test was seriously
disappointing apparently being civil
isn't motivating you yeah okay i already
heard that all right
i'm just gonna try this again does it
not work on the turrets
what exactly is wrong with being adopted
it doesn't work on them
okay oh um now just drop it
there we go no no no no no no not me not
mean what's what's down there by the way
i am not
okay i don't want to fall down there
just do the test
wait did i need the turret for this no i
have a cube over there
okay
um
what's down here is there
anything
it's falling apart
please don't fall apart i need to finish
this game before it falls apart
[Music]
oh it reverses
but only for the moment it's reversing
right
no
wait a second
that means
well it changes so fast that i i can't
use it to suck me all over to that side
ah i can i can suck the cube
fun
come to me
um and yeah but when it said oh
oh oh no
uh
um
yeah yeah it will come over here if i do
it this way
it will just take a little while
and we'll just take a moment
there you are
here
this is nice and comfy
don't you want to stay on there
watch some netflix while you're on that
comfy button
i feel you i feel you
holy [\h__\h] i can't believe we're so late
in the game and they're still adding
uh
some kind of gimmicks here
impressive
i don't know where where where where are
we going um
is there
i wanna say it from the above
perspective not a hotel
i move that again now it's reversed now
i can go up but maybe a bit closer
enough if i'm such a moral why can't you
solve a simple test i mean i solved it
what
big brand yeah i don't know i have an
easier time comprehending this thing
than other things in the game like the
jellies or portals in general
that wasn't so bad
yeah
that wasn't so bad i think
[Music]
why'd you change the name whitley
and the music he likes classic music or
what are you trying to be
fancy sophisticated
oh oh sorry sorry sorry i hope that hope
that didn't disturb you too much then it
was the same books pages being turned so
that's what i was doing just reading
books
are you studying something just know the
hardest one machiavelli do not know what
all the fuss was about understood it
perfectly have you read that one yeah
yeah thanked it well on the test
there's more books not
ah
okay
oh god i didn't really want to jump
already but
not a little we have another flow here
where is the end goal
where is it
am i blind
[Music]
where would we be going
maybe up there somehow
huh
i don't know i don't know where we we
would be going so i don't know where to
aim for but oh wait up there there's a
button there so for now oh
uh for now
now
i'll do my get up there first
[Music]
i want to go up
oh wait this one this one i can put a
portal there right yo oh
easy easy there's a cube hello cube
um now
i am up high and that is cool where do
we go next
like
need a moment
i want
to fall maybe but not too far
[Music]
or am i we need to go far down and then
up again
we could let's say let's say i make one
here
and i fall down
around to that height and let myself be
carried like somewhere over there
or maybe like somewhere here
and then
ah no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
no that wasn't that
wait if i make one here it will catch me
there
i will go over to that side
[Music]
and i
if i'm there
i want to go higher again
or
[Music]
[\h__\h]
where do i need to i need to go here
it's the button to drop a cube
down here
all right let's just let's just try some
things
let's say
ah
oh wait no ah
[Music]
i don't know i'm just gonna go on a trip
i guess
um
[Music]
no no no no no no
oh but wait hey wait a second i can kind
of [\h__\h] wait
i can kind of lift myself like that i
just noticed if i place it just a little
bit higher but not too high
[Music]
i can kind of lift myself but i don't
think that they want me to lift myself
like one by one centimeter
do you need help um
do not know what all the fuss is about
understood it perfectly have you read
that one here again
we're here again
this one goes like that
let's go
let's go down again
for example
we can do
we can just make portals while we're in
the middle
of going somewhere
[Music]
no
huh
hey
i can get myself a little bit higher
ah
that's pretty close
no we need we need to go like over to
that
side um
you need to listen to them again
cheese cheese alert i don't think it
would have even worked all the way
through anyway
welcome back to weekly laboratories
[Music]
welcome back
hope that didn't disturb you too much
then it was the side of books pages
being turned so that's what i was doing
here we are again back in the middle
people say i'm overthinking it so i
would like to think simpler but it's not
it doesn't seem to be
the chaotic
um
uh stupid try
[\h__\h] what
oh wait oh my god
okay someone in the chat said momentum
and that made me think i need to fall
but where can i fall
if i can't make a portal above me then i
might want to make it you know anyway
okay
finally
oh there it is
oh
oh okay okay we need to catch it um we
can bring it here kind of the same way
right um
uh we will do that
catch it
nice catch
now we're gonna do the same thing which
will be even easier if i'm not the one
who's falling
there we go oh yeah oh i almost fell
down
what was that there was nothing that was
nothing there we go chill chill i did it
lately
eventually you build up a resistance to
it
unless you have the mental capacity to
push past it
it didn't matter to me oh yeah you
weren't that quite quite that euphoric
when i finished my tests that is true
so you already built up a resistance to
it why why not be happy
yeah
he's
he's just happy
guys he's just happy okay nothing else
oh blue screen
press any key to vent
radiological emissions into atmosphere
consult reactor cord
well that's a
blue screen is never good
um
but we're gonna continue testing are you
sure lately you're just moving closer to
me um i thought maybe proximity to the
test solving
give us all the results
well i guess that's good
let's get closer to wheatley
our best friend our best buddy
ah we're doing bridges again
building bridges
takanashikiwawa always builds bridges
so inspiring
we eventually want uh
to go over there okay
uh well first of all we have a button
right in reachable distance
oh i can stop that one
with
oh maybe here
nice
yeah
however if i want to pick that one up
there's turrets but that is also
in theory not a problem that one would
have landed a little bit better than
that i feel like
i feel like we might be able to make a
land
farther beyond further behind you know
not really really really really
oh
[Music]
come on
why must you land there
no no please don't deploy
no um
i will just quickly um get rid of the
wall grab it and quickly make a wall
um
oh wait i can crouch
come here oh good baby i'm so proud of
you but no not through here but that's
interesting cause like
there's
there's a wall that destroys the cubes
oh well
where are we gonna go huh
wait we're gonna go here
we're gonna walk through
i'm gonna drop you there
good luck buddy
what
no no no no
i'm not there let me i don't know
let me go somewhere else
[Music]
where's my cube
there it is i probably lost you
i finally lost you forever baby
oh it's my two favorite things together
turrets and cubes
okay
uh
let's try this by the way
monitors i was actually thinking earlier
today i wish i had fewer monitors that
were working so you're just helping me
really question them
did i just smash your screen oh you can
still see me find all right everything's
okay
oh i need to bring the cube over here
that's how i get around
that whoa no i do do
then let's jump together sorry i'm not
paying for that screen by the way you're
already breaking a million things what
difference does it make
oh
at least i knew the right color
[Music]
wait a second
oh that doesn't catch it does it that's
too high
is that too high
okay how about here
sorry guys a little
needs a little bit of work oh well hello
that's how i wanted you to land
originally why couldn't you do that
earlier
not deploying no deploying allowed here
um
chill chill chill cube oh can you uh
please go through
how did we do that before there we go
you stay there and wait for me i'm gonna
come and rescue you
oh [\h__\h]
there we go okay
oh try number two
now let's be more careful
shall we
no more breaking of these cubes on
amazon these little cute plushies i i
can't imagine they do
but the thing is i don't want uh
generally i don't really want any more
plushies in my
apartment i used to have like so many on
my bed my whole bed would be filled with
oh [\h__\h]
yeah you wait there my whole bed would
be filled with them
this is a safe way to get down wow
impressive
oh
if only i had my shield wait wait you
wait there i'll get the shield
i'll get the barrier uh
it will just be a little bit of a
roundabout way
uh
yeah what was i saying oh yeah i had
like
a million cute plushies like
you guys
it's like a relaxed bear
uh from
japanese
company
and
let me do
i'll wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
there we go
yeah and alpacas and all that kind of
stuff but at one point when i moved uh
again for the millionth time
oh [\h__\h] they see me
no we're good um
i figured you know what i'm gonna be an
adult now
no more plushies on my bed
no mom are you absolutely sure you're
solving these correctly i mean
you solved it but i'm wondering if maybe
there's a number of ways to solve them
and you're picking all the worst ways
no no that was the solution it really
sounds like my chat
it's part of my chat not all of them i
solved it what's the problem with me you
tried to show me how else to solve it
you know what you could totally
make yourself happy
if you
test your own
testing rooms
and absorb them you see where i'm going
with this
why do you need me to do it you can just
just just go and make yourself happy
you can't oh but these rooms are not his
own anyone these rooms are glasses room
so he doesn't even know
really you know or someone else could
make the room for him he could
commission glasses to make some more
rooms this is not good
yeah no it's not good
but what what are we gonna do gladys
think potato think
um
uh
yeah let's go
the game is falling apart
and then watch 10 at once get
[Laughter]
oh i understand yeah yeah yeah it's like
yeah when you when you want to watch
your whole season at once you don't want
to watch you don't want to wait to
uh you want to wait until
um you want to wait until one whole
season is out right you don't want to
watch one episode and wait one week
and then
watch the second one and all that
because that just takes too much time
yeah yeah i get too weirdly i'll get you
weekly
headaches days really
um
how so we'll find out does this uh move
the okay no it doesn't
what's over here vanilla
a cube
a reflection cube
which means i want to go
there somehow which means i would have
to
bring the
eventually bring the airflow through
here to get me up there or i'll just get
kind of pulled over there
not sure
which one it's gonna gonna be but um
wait uh what
i need to
i need to get back
uh
where does this go
oh
okay
my first
idea is going to be this
let's test it
um
[Music]
that doesn't quite get me to the cube
doesn't quite do the trick
right
should i even start with that
i think i think yes
what about these platforms that's how i
get uh out of here
i see i see um something similar to what
we had before right i need to fall again
and then fall out of here
so
which color i always need to make sure i
use the red color i'm scared of using
the wrong color orange here
no blue here
and then i'll fall over there i think
okay
okay okay okay okay first
first step is okay
we got a cube now we make it go
up there tori is the coco
okay
[Music]
what actually ah this one lifted
wasn't this one the front before
is that the only thing that happened
that was a really old sugar vape song by
the way
that you and takes me back all right
man i was so young when i'm still young
obviously but i was so young when that
song was uh when when it came out and
when it was popular
when i thought um holy [\h__\h] those ladies
no you know what no we talked about this
before i couldn't even i couldn't even
comprehend
the the sexiness and all that
those sugar babes
couldn't even comprehend it uh i didn't
even see it as sexy because i didn't
understand what was sexy
okay
uh
let's focus
um we have
we have lived to the platform
doesn't do anything for me is that
really the only thing that happened that
happened okay
what else changed
i want the reflection cube now i need it
to make the laser
go here somehow eventually
i get there
[Music]
i know i'm gonna forget i'm gonna forget
what i just wanted to do
um
uh what was i doing okay uh
here
and then
what was i doing
i think i think i think i think i think
no is that even gonna work though
no no no no never mind never mind never
mind never mind never mind
wait what oh
well we don't need you there right now
do we
don't we only need the cube at the very
end to be placed there
we don't need him to be there right
at the moment at least
right yeah okay okay i think so too
so we can't just
can we not just do the same thing but
just brian over there
but the problem is
problem is
that if i fly up there
how am i gonna make the portal there
whatever we don't need the wind
that's too easy
oh
they're playing with me wait wait look
i'm getting closer right
i feel like i'm in space right now
with the music as well
it's very spacey it's very relaxing
gravity loop
do i get it do i understand
if i
the moment no
um
do i understand it
i
think
i don't know
yeah the laser
the laser
i know i want to block the lace ah
wait a second
do
these cubes they they they block the
laser right we haven't used one in one
like this but
they do block the laser
[Music]
wait what
let me go there please
uh
where was the wind
oh
it's the laser
the wind disappears okay
okay
now it won't stop us from flying through
here anymore
oh
that took me
too long once again
uh
but anyway we'll be redirecting this
right
now
see i needed you for something else
first
here we go
but um
what does that
does
oh
well you know what never mind let's just
uh send it through cube you stay here
for now
let me go through here first okay
so the chest that i won't get hit by the
laser now we want the laser to go
through there
to activate the other thing
oopsie wrong thing there we go
and there we go i think now we have
solved the puzzle we just need this cube
to go back with us
uh
but for that we will momentarily have to
get rid of the portal
ah but we need to
airflow again
we need the airflow ah it's okay it's
okay i think i can deal with that uh
in a moment
so we'll just place you here for now
that you're ready to be beamed up again
like scotty no not like scotty scotty is
the one who is going to be myself um
okay now we place this one here again
this platform is being lifted
uh
we might already want to stand on it
maybe i don't know uh wait wait wait
wait give me some time i needed to do it
in some steps
uh
[Music]
i know i'm not sure if i can
stand on it but my idea would be
placing a portal under this cube
throwing it out of there i guess
then this will go up again though
but then we get the airflow to make this
cube go up there how do we do everything
at the same time
[Music]
ah
i don't want to do something wrong now
[Laughter]
[Music]
can you go for here
go for a be a good cube
and be a good boy
[Laughter]
don't hurt me
ah wait stop looking at me
stop looking
you go here
i basically already solved it okay
i'm standing on it now uh
yeah
um
[Music]
i want this
that's okay it will stay here right it
will stay
oh it will go higher that's okay
there we go there we go
there we go here we go okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
maximum focus achieved
[Laughter]
ah
and then and then and then we let this
one go oh you just saw that
i told you
to tell me before
you're making this so hard for me oh i
need to focus don't blame me
[Music]
it seems so yes beat me up scotty
scotty
this is the hardest map i've played no
it wasn't even that
difficult i'm just stupid
is that all
you let him keep his job that is so nice
of you
okay we have another big room but we're
at 12 guys we're 12.
we are looking at
the last
couple of rooms here
uh all right let's see if we need the
lasers to go through all these
all these
it's not holes not sure what it is
so first of all we'll start with a
portal here
and then we'll put a portal here
and then all the platforms will start to
move
and they go all the way to that side
don't know who the i place one
here
that makes them stop
oh
the low one makes a move
the upper one makes them stop
uh wait wasn't there another one
there here what does this one do oh i
can't
you can't activate it from here
not quite laser grid look again what do
you mean look at where the lines lead
which lines
ah
and now the lasers are gone
ah that's what you mean
but but
but
well ideally i would want both of them
to be active
to move and to
[Music]
have the no i'm not necessary if it's
like at the point where like the
platform is in the middle of the lasers
i can turn the lasers
no i don't know never mind we'll get
there
don't think about it oh do i have to
drop a cube on the platform though
that's for later too
[Music]
how do i get over there ah there's a
portal there
a portable wall
if i
do this
it's still standing still
okay
we want the upper one right
but we also want to move
um
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
yeah i am okay we got that
can i get off now nice
now we will catch the cube on the
platform
and probably bring it over
here okay
now
stop
somewhere there let's see if we can
catch it
oh it's a reflection that landed kind of
bad i hope that's not gonna drop but
it's a reflection cube okay
that's good
uh
let's
get going
okay okay i don't need to stop it
wait but i need to pick it up from there
so i will have to pick it up from the
other side ah
okay you have to go back
um
i think if i'm not wrong oopsy
once it's all the way over there we'll
make a blue portal
[Music]
that should be enough
yeah
okay okay okay so far so good
uh
i would have taken me a lot longer you
think so yeah as we once again see some
some riddles are easier some are
more difficult for me
and we put a blue portal there again
and now we start
uh moving again only
until
a good point to stop and number four
okay oh no a bit more a bit more let's
go to the edge
that's a good point
and we move on
and we perhaps stop for now
uh bring the cube
down here
then bring it to the other side of a
portal
i guess
but
uh
correctly though
not it right
that's too crazy
but that's too big brain
no way
[Music]
see there there
yeah
[Music]
it's not the same height but that would
be i i have yet to see them doing
that like sending it for the same portal
back where it came from originally i
don't think they've done that yet
um we've sent it for other portals sure
but i don't think this was a thing
before
um
ah
it is
yeah okay
um
which means we'll go to the platform
again kind it's kind of far right now i
think i need to reposition it
will you stand here for a moment
i took the toy in there now
and okay
that's that's okay it can stand there
and we will go through
with
the cube so we need you up here
no
no way
no we don't need it up here
no we do maybe i don't know we'll test
it out we'll put one here
we'll put one
no that's
not
it's not the right height either
that's not the right height um
but there's one in the
middle
here that's probably the right height
okay we're moving again guys we're
moving
uh this one's the moving one
that one's the right height so we're
just gonna go to the other side
okay moving a bit more
there
[Music]
we have them activated where we were
muggling this
the door is open
how do i get there without closing the
door again
uh
i should just place uh either a blue or
orange one
um
blue
[Music]
are we just chilling here now
wow that's a great explanation you sound
like me when i would do a tour
just something oh
can you not
right if i kill uh yes i guess so
i mean
i'll low-key miss him maybe a little bit
thank you for opening the door
ah this is the last last chapter oh my
god we're in the last chapter guys
oh no we're not this was not a new
chapter never mind
great yeah just uh
uh test ready not quite for you
obviously who else would i be doing it
for no one so let's see here next to
exit all right who else would it be
doing
can you move it closer
someone's running through
didn't someone just run through turn
that beam off i thought i had austin
when poking around for other test
subjects
oh i did find something though reminds
me i've got a big surprise for you too
seriously
it's a confetti again
[Music]
not all those
oh well we'll need the cube first where
is look cube
oh it landed up there
okay
okay guys
put your thinking caps on once again
ah
i
have some ideas but i just need to think
a bit harder about them
momentum
what am i doing that porto what was i
doing that for us
what is that over there
what does that do
orange color
but i can't
i needed to ah with maybe with the
airflow
we can
eventually
get it to go straight over there
not a hotel
but for now
i think it's of no use
um
i still think
that i need
some kind of
momentum
but i lost track
of my thoughts so
yeah i know i need that cube so i can
have the airflow go through constantly
if i just
if i lay here
if i just lay here would you play the
game with me and backseat me all the
time
uh
but no no it's okay
it's okay
i want to fall out of there
uh
what if i
when i when i fall through here
wait no what was i thinking
no no no no
[Music]
see that's where i want to go to um
that's another option
i don't know and i just need to test out
things
yeah i want to use the airflow but
but i need to stand on it in order to
keep it
i know i never mind
what
ah
oh
okay
catch it
it's just so obvious isn't it ah
my pretty cube
my precious little cube
but do we want you
here first right not over there
can we get another cube this one
disappears right if we create another
one
we don't want that to happen
yeah
yeah okay
that's what i thought
this is also my precious one
you're just as precious look at you you
precious little thing you're looking
so cute
i made a little sweater for you i needed
a little cute sweater for you i'll put
it on you later my precious
only the best of the best for my
precious
okay
that means there must be another cube
somewhere
or
they don't want us to use two at a time
but just uh
use it for like
a moment
to
would that even
work no
wait what if
wait we want the air
to help us spread
this [\h__\h] so
uh the air would be
ideally going through there
right
um
now i need to go in here
[Music]
and activate it
but
i can't get rid of that because when i'm
in here
i can't make that portal i could
probably make this one
maybe
or does the cube go in this room and i
go over there
stand
okay still try it the other way around
yeah that that might work easier
that might make more sense cause yeah
okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah and we just can we
can drop it and then we can make it
go all the way
over here and then we
know we drop it here
and our ramp has been successfully built
sorry my voice just done my road time
and this is what we like to call science
my little children welcome back to
kibaba stream
where does this go oh shh no no no no
no
wait what are we doing
[Laughter]
is too old for this [\h__\h] wait what
oh i have my cube wonderful
wait well we need to build it again come
with me
i missed one more thing apparently
one one step
one more step
so close to achieving greatness
all right orange
here we go
no problem no problem no problem
what did i miss though
momentum perhaps um
need more of it no i don't know ah
airflow we would oh [\h__\h] uh
we would want more
we we want the air flow
ah we would take the cube back
because we don't need the color anymore
leave it here so so that the airflow
continues
right yes yes yes yes i think so
yes yes
so
uh
and then um we will maybe put it through
oh
i'm wondering
i think
it could
go here
does that catch me
i don't want to fall down again and redo
the color thing
is this okay
okay
let's go please catch me please catch me
please
you're going to love it
to death to death
i love it
until you did
all right i don't know whether
you're uh you're picking up for what i'm
saying you're saying that the next one
will kill me but like who are you gonna
test with if you kill me
you have one problem with logic there
you're never gonna find happiness if you
kill me
but that feels like a
new chapter
next room
um
yeah so that's fine i guess
oh
so much for tuscarora
isn't this what you wanted clear happy
end for wheatley question mark
i was gonna pick up the cube
i think i could rescue the cube from
falling down maybe i get achievement
from that
oh that's sad
sorry i tried is it possible
did anyone ever manage to do that three
more chambers to your big surprise
rip killed
i fell for it
oh
what are you guys doing there why would
you try to hurt me
there's a button here too
but first we want to get rid of them
um there's a button over there as well
and an airflow
first step is also always redirecting
the airflow oh and seeing what this one
does
redirecting it
not a
do i want that already
there's also blue color over there
blue okay
don't go there
okay
in order to
uh get the color i first need to get
over to that side
let's do that
for turrets first is it turrets first
is it you guys first
there's some walls there
i could perhaps
not yet
best room you like this room
but like if i move around here they're
gonna try to attack me
don't know how um feel about that
so there's nothing
in this
area
to send my air through
this room made me feel dumb
oh every room makes me feel dumb
wait if it makes you feel dumb then
maybe the solution is actually pretty
simple you just need a
a while to grasp it and then you feel
dumb that's that's what you're saying
right
okay
i'll test something out here though
no no no no no no no
no no no
if i could redirect it
i'm in the flow i'm in the flow
[Music]
no i don't know i don't know what i'm
doing
[Music]
overthinking of course i'm overthinking
yeah no that that seemed like a big
stretch to me too
um
it must be something with this what
would i be
what do i want to
suck into the airflow
while i'm here
what
what how did that what okay if that's
what made you feel dumb then that's also
what makes me feel dumb
um
oh well wait how long is that time
limited does that only go for a certain
amount of time okay we might just want
to bring a certain amount of it over
there
yeah
for now
let's just bring it over there
uh and uh
drop it
oh no oh
ah
did that even like help at all
also
how how am i getting back
am i
am i getting back
oh
what
okay okay
okay hallelujah i found the way back
okay
now
oh no
now that we have that
i'm like i'm like yeah only one tiny
baby step closer
gosh i'm so dumb
i didn't change much at all
i
[Music]
i want to know what this one does
oh does it like open this window up or
something
ah come on pink
pink
do i wanna go over there again what can
i even do over there i can just
get some more color
and the color here
won't land anywhere
oh
no
i was thinking
get the color ah
i know let's let's go let's go back
there
for inspection purpose
how about
we make um
just go to the side
don't know why but why not you know
[Music]
well that doesn't do anything does it
i'm getting desperate
[Music]
that was probably not it
can i deal with the turrets now
i don't know how
hi there
what's up
ah
can
i
[Music]
drop the color on them
now don't look for me don't look for me
so for example
um
but can i place that portal
while i'm yeah i can place it while i'm
here okay okay okay
so the airflow is going through there
again
does
this make it possible to drop
oh wait no wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
drop
and then and then and then and then and
then
ah
oh one more
no
no that makes no sense
[Music]
you guys know what i want to do right
ah
um
[Music]
is the time thing
when it's going for the orange
no ah before it goes to the orange ah
before before before before before i can
send it back i can send it back
it's in the backs and the box and the
blacks and the blacks and back no but
wait are no no no no no no no no if i
change the orange one now
ah
send it back
make it go for the orange one
then make the blue one here and then
send it back again
or so i thought
wait
um wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait
go here
blue one here
now it will go through there and then i
drop it
like it's hot
i need to do it one more time
okay then we're we finally figured out a
way to get rid of them
hallelujah
uh
airflow
now
hey what
oh there it is
i was like where is it [\h__\h]
can i go faster
it's okay let's just reverse it we'll
just reverse it okay
reversing and we're gonna do the same
thing
we're gonna let it go for the orange one
and just drop it a little bit faster
come on come on come on come on come on
beautiful
[Applause]
[Music]
hi hi i thought you were gonna kill me
bye bye
okay
it opens up this
which
means
nothing and everything at the same time
why kill her because
i felt like i was in danger okay okay
do we
need more by the way we're going over
there right we're going all the way over
there
ah
we want to
for example
uh
uh with the airflow
go through here and then get rid of the
airflow maybe no
maybe we just want some blue color on
here is that possible
can we like bring the color over here
the same way again like make it go
through here
and then have it
no it won't go all the way over here
uh
and i think i just need to fly through
there
what's the best way to do that
well i've done this before yes i have
i'm just looking for
where to jump through
ah
[Music]
thinking thinking thinking thinking
thinking
oh
um
[Music]
what
oh i made me bounce up with that while i
was wondering why i did that
[Music]
no i know you have to use the momentum
let's go over here
and then
let's
[Music]
have a weird idea
but that's probably not it then it's way
too complicated
[Music]
but i can't reach
even if i create one here now
can't reach that
i think i
i i'm not capable of
using my brain anymore
[Music]
uh
what now
no no no no no no
no
no no no no no no no no
can i please land on it again i don't
know
probably not
[\h__\h]
let me land on you
no please
oh there you go
i'll give it another try
i can't land through i don't care
i can
[Music]
how can i under think
how can i under things
you say yes but i don't understand
what's happening
[Music]
i hate everybody
oh
you sold it good good one good for you
so he's inexplicably happy all of a
sudden even though he should be going
out of his mind with test withdrawal and
he's got a surprise for us what did he
find
not feeling smart anymore
but someone else in the beginning in the
chat said this one made them feel
stumped and yeah i understand you i feel
very dumb too
i'll bet you're both dying tonight i'm
so stupid
well
only how is that one of the hardest
rooms that wasn't very so simple
we're running out of time
yeah i'm running out of time i need to
cook dinner
nice surprise
oh that's fun
that was fun thank you for cheering me
up lately
i found two little robots back here
built specifically for testing
wow then don't use me
you didn't kill me
you think robots wouldn't kill you
but here you are a robot trying to kill
another robot hello why would i kill you
oh they're buying it they killed me
there i was smashing some steel plates
together and i thought to myself yeah
it's deadly horseman
it's still a work in progress don't
judge me yet um but you know eventually
i'd like to get them to sort of shoot
fire at you
um moments before crushing them that's
true
[Music]
i'm out of
the old days or we were friends good old
friends i like this can we just continue
running it's like a marathon
no problem can you come back
tuesdays because the game gave me
another choice oh my god did i really
just jump down there i'm on i'm i'm i am
insane
what
we got there it doesn't seem to be
a time
limit why can't i make them
on here
[Music]
right direction is that where it came
from
this is where it came from i just fell
down there on purpose though what the
hell
what
we need to go over there
oh
[Music]
i hesitated no [\h__\h]
i think i could have made that jump if i
just jumped right
uh okay
okay okay we don't need to start from
the very beginning
let's start at the very beginning
[Music]
can we
a little bit higher
i have to take it again somehow
i can do that jump
[Music]
oh
yeah i gotta commit to the joke
wow
little
uh
anti-climactic break both guys you're
gonna crash the bridge again aren't you
oh don't mind me continue escaping
continue
you can stop emma there we go i bought
so this is a portal wall if i've ever
seen one there we go
this one
oh no are you [\h__\h] kidding me are
they killing you they are killing you
aren't they no they're actually not
[Music]
that would explain the extremely quiet
real i was so scared for a moment
it's a broken one
fly out of the room
[Music]
i was about to panic
blackjack i know blackjack
i need to put my foolish ambitions to
rest
that was so foolish of me
well no matter because i'm still holding
all the cards and guess what they're all
full houses
new turrets not defective extra fours
the best hand are the beatles i would
imagine
[Music]
just notice now
oh there goes one
there goes another one oh my god don't
hit me don't hit me with that
there you are i think i got them all
nice
what about me though
oh should i go there too i can
is this going to kill me
experiment foolish
[Laughter]
quick
thinking
yes
holmes versus moriarty holy [\h__\h] this
place is insanely huge
i was supposed to drop i think i think
oh my god
[Music]
it felt like a horror game for a moment
interesting
i think i need to drop
uh
hundreds versus moriarty
aristotle versus matches oh yes yes yes
uh uh uh
stay still
end up all right please moving
[Music]
i'm hiding come try and find me we're
playing games
just like back in kindergarten
lately don't you don't you
want to go back to something right there
did it kill you that would be amazing if
it killed you simpler times hello
oh oh oh oh oh oh yes just on a freight
way i'll be back if you're still alive
i'm gonna be back don't die until i get
back
easy
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
okay okay
okay
that was not the solution in case you
haven't noticed
i will find it though oh oh
did something bright back there can i
oh oh did it kill you that would be
amazing if it killed you
hello
oh
explore it no just have a brain wave
i'll be back if you're still alive i'm
going to be back
but
not that i can pick it up though
unfortunately
um
well i
do i not have to go over there
yeah
i could maybe go
here but
[Music]
i want to drop the color on them
oh oh
[Music]
can i go here
and then
oh i just positioned a little bit
badly maybe over on this side
what no
huh
i don't know
oh no we're good we're good we're good
okay
nice
the blob of color that we wanted
oh
come on
[Music]
oh
i am just giving them a nice fresh look
you know
blue is a color that makes you
feel calm and free right
i'll set you free
there we go
[Music]
it's like one of those bouncy castles
and they're the children playing in it
ain't no problem with that
do we need to
bring it over there too
i see that there's that jumpy platform
so they want us to
oh their name well you know what i'll
just go here
stop stop stop stop
i
[Music]
i don't know if i should test that right
now do you think that's enough
it must be
oh
there we go
open up fbi is something that aputure
must have heard many times oh by the way
it went back to aperture logo what
happened with the wheatley logo when it
well i know there it is
it came back
and came back
okay okay
okay my dear sadistic
yes friend
what does this button
do what
is so what are we dropping red
what the [\h__\h] is that
bombs
what
what am i gonna do with that i want them
to
shoot
a hole in the wall maybe
but it always goes down there no
can i like make a portal right there
from
yeah but it's gonna be deleted if i
go for there
i need to
i need a way to
look through
what i feel like i tried it already and
it didn't work but it did work all right
never mind then we will shoot
i guess right there why not
go exponential
that's it that's all no more
okay
we have
the floor as an option now
okay okay okay do i go here
yes
okay
hello computers oh they're still working
like loki
maybe i can
hack them huh
potato does potatoes
would be your job to do that well i
guess you're absolutely useless right
now can we bomb some more stuff
that's the first time we see bombs in
this game can we
bump the whole factory
[Music]
maybe
the death traps have been a bit of a
failure
can i shoot the screen
that would be nice that would be fun
later
we're in that first one today why is
this going to be ridiculous
and uh i just wanted to give you the
chance to
kill yourself now wow
uh you just jump into that masher just
like that i'm not listening
[Music]
in a very very crucial way so but better
offer here
just kill yourself
we can run against this
hopefully yeah
that wasn't a no
at least we speak the same language
what has he done
i don't know gladys was this not what
you intended that's
not my problem man you guys are all
[\h__\h] up
uh
oh can i get some more of that
orange stuff
or do i not need it or maybe i don't
need it
do i need it
i feel like
we would want this as a runway run run
run and run then we can uh
basically jump into that or do i not
need that
i think i need it
yeah
i'll get some more of that orange stuff
and with an uh blue portal please uh
yeah that's what i'm talking about
all right almost picked me up by the way
my chat broke let me fix it really
quickly
there we go welcome back
let me show you my parkour skills again
a little bit more over there then it
should work
i i fixed you yes
live again yeah yeah you worked on the
obs screen but not on my side
oh dangerous music
i realize you don't want to put me back
in charge
you think i'll betray you and on any
other day
i believe you what else can i do i have
no choice
for the first time you have a
consciousness
as we like to say in german
uh
translated to
wait what uh what's einstein in
english and preserving is the first step
to getting better improving yourself
in insight yeah
inside that sounds weird in english you
guys don't say it i feel like you would
have a saying like that
awareness
awareness or admitting is the first step
would probably be
a non-direct translation but one way to
say it
what
we're in like
is already corrupt as [\h__\h] we don't need
those but okay let's try that
sounds like a plan
[Music]
enemies
yeah revenge is pretty nice oh
[\h__\h] i'm
ready up according to the control panel
let me just not
light up there the entire building is
going to self-destruct white color what
color are you making sure it's a problem
with the light i think the lights
but just in case it isn't i am actually
gonna have to kill you um as discussed
earlier so let's call that
and i'm not going to make the same
mistakes four-part plan is this we need
some bombs to make this blow up
two start the neurotoxin no no that's
not fair no
i'm going to give you a foreign chance
and turn off the neurotoxin
can you also make me
some portal
places portable five minutes
here i am i'm here
oh my god
[Music]
oh it's over there too
what are we gonna do with that
what are we gonna do with that oh
um
okay do i need to do that from like
every angle
i'm delivering the first car
near the catwalk
okay
here
this is perfect i already have my portal
there i'm on my way
i'm doing already boy
i'm already doing better than in the
first boss fight i've been in portal one
space
you space yes
it's not enough blue
okay warning core corruption at 50
bed system compromised neurotoxin
offline reactor explosion near toxins
normal when you kill people
there we go
remember
lower body parts buddy
what's the situation
wait wait wait wait
grab you from here
just like you're doing
[Music]
from the catwalk
where am i attaching it taekwondo
i am a cold spring right
here there you go there we go there you
go that's 75
reactor explosion timer destroy reactor
explosion uncertainty emergency
[Music]
where do i shoot you from now
i don't think this is gonna work you're
protecting yourself there how about
you're changing it
a couple of hundred times
for a few years
i hit him i hit him
what
i don't know what exact position it was
but okay uh oh do you have another
thingy for me
where where is that
as thought
if you have trouble with simple counting
use the following demonic points
what
where is it
i don't
they created orange [\h__\h]
i'm gonna fade
the automobile break was not invented
until 1895. before this someone had to
remain in the car and
the entire way
[Music]
oh gonna fail
what's up
oh but where are we restarting at the
two-minute countdown or from the ver no
it must be the two minute countdown they
didn't put us all the way back
uh i just kept on switching the portals
eventually it reached
for a few years
[Music]
this is gonna be the pink one or which
one
it's the pink one right
is it somewhere
here
we have enough time don't panic stop
panic it can't
be curious in the theory of
radioactivity
[Music]
oh
extinguishing
[Music]
please press the stalemate resolution
button
come
back
no
do not press that button
ah
let's see
there's no timer anymore right
what what are you still alive
oh my god i have hands oh my god i saw
my body for the first time like
this place
[Music]
what
let go we're in space
and you are not coming back
[Music]
no
holding hands i'm glad this is much more
fun
[Music]
is that the ending
you're gonna leave me
like that no no no no yeah yeah okay
okay okay okay okay
i was gonna say
oh you're
from the co-op
are you nice now mommy yes honey taught
me a valuable lesson sorry mommy i
thought you were my greatest enemy
when all along you were my best friend
a
[Music]
deleting carolyn just now taught me a
valuable lesson
the best solution to a problem is
usually the easiest one
and i'll be honest
killing you is hard
you know what my days used to be like
i just tested
nobody murdered me or put me in a potato
or fed me to birds
i had a pretty good life i saved you
[\h__\h] when you showed up you dangerous
mute lunatic so you know what
you win
just
go
you're letting me go yes no way don't
come back no way
hey
what kind of breakup is that
mommy
nah she's just just no she won't let me
go
no hey hey hey can we just talk a little
bit don't you want me to test some
things they're on my side now are they
they're like harmonicas
[Music]
oh god
i'm i wanna hear my
oh that's scary that's so scary that's
so scary please please don't kill me
please don't kill me please don't kill
me
[Music]
i'm sorry that i dropped all of you
oh is that your overlord turret
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] leopard skin
other instruments who would have known
they have such a talent they don't need
to kill people they can make the most
beautiful moving emotional music ever
they can become a core
i can perform all over the world i don't
need to hurt people why not just heal
people
with the power of amusing
[Music]
was it actual a real language or
gibberish by the way
oh my god i'm outside did she no [\h__\h]
i can't believe it she actually let me
go
but in the middle of [\h__\h] nowhere
i'm gonna die here anyway
well here we are again
[Music]
when you tried to kill me twice i don't
i don't remember
[Music]
i i'm taking it my freedom it's mine
you don't want to see me anymore you
[\h__\h] sunday come on
[Music]
a phoenix i live forever she doesn't
know she's still lacking critical
information thanks for not following her
[Music]
[Applause]
her to write a full song from me she
loves me my only friend you only do that
for people you love do you think i meant
you
that would be funny if it weren't so sad
yeah i'm your only friend think about
that i don't need anyone you don't want
anyone
you'll feel lonely down
[Music]
problems
oh
that's so beautiful
wow
i'll miss her so
it all much
i honestly do i honestly do wish i could
take it all back
and not just because i'm stranded in
space you look like a stardust no you
are mate maybe some
light reflects on you you look like a
star from earth isn't that nice you know
if i was ever to see her again do you
know what i'd say
you'd say i'm sorry
sincerely
i am sorry i was bossy no one needs your
shitty stories
and i am genuinely sorry put them in
your the end non-existent
[\h__\h]
oh my god she did not pull me back i am
surprised
i am
but i i can see how
you could still twist it if they wanted
to make a portal free and i have heard
that uh they have a problem with making
third games they always just do one and
two right
but if they wanted to they could
probably just twist it somehow maybe
just like the outside was a simulation
bamboozled surprise
it was not
the real outside haha funny isn't it
that was just another level welcome to
the fake world that was not the real
world
yeah they can't count to three
i've heard i've heard people want um for
half-life for example two right you guys
want to
uh half-life free but they never make it
they just never make it
sorry that you guys have to suffer like
that
but
if you want the colors and all that you
can find that in splatoon
maybe maybe that's
something that can cheer you up
oh
half life oh yeah there's a vr portal
right yeah yeah yeah yeah
vr portal that who knows maybe we might
want to check it out oh the community
test challenge that's what someone told
me about um someone said i should like
uh test out chambers that you guys made
um maybe we can do that
sometime in the future if you really
want to
uh
if you guys want to make some rooms i
don't know how that works but apparently
it's a thing
or not even yours i guess it could be
anyone's really like i guess there's
probably like an online
uh library to choose from maybe
how do i rate the game uh
portal 2 only or portal 1 including
um
i was very bad at many riddles but
that has nothing to do with the game
being bad just me being bad
so
portal 2 only
what would i rate it i think
it's not the kind of game i usually play
but for what it is it's definitely a 10
out of 10.
for the for the genre that it is i think
it's it's pretty much a 10 out of 10.
i think i don't know what would um
what reason there would be
to give it any less points like i don't
i don't recall anything negative
it's just okay it was a bit difficult
but that doesn't make it any bad and it
was not like absolutely unsolvable
so
yeah
um
[Music]
um gave us a deep deep
insight into
gladys how she became gladys
um and what what the what aperture was
like before gladys and all that
uh
leaves me curious curious as to how it's
gonna be afterwards though that's that's
a big question mark in my brain like
she's gonna stay there right and she
seems to still
wants to experiment but just not on not
on me
[Laughter]
which kind of makes you wonder are they
we're gonna make a portal friend
i wanna know what is she doing what is
she gonna do
co what happens after the singer oh i'll
see some stuff in the co-op oh yeah
right because you guys told me that the
story is different but i didn't know
that it kind of uh
uh continues kind of
oh
nice
yeah next week actually on tuesday
me and kovo are gonna play the co-op
version of this so make sure to catch it
um we're gonna
probably have to do two parts because i
don't think we can go longer than three
hours and i've heard it's like six hours
roughly
um so it will be a two-part um
campaign collaboration uh but not to say
in the same week probably one in the
next week and one in the following week
yeah kobo from her life indonesia third
generation are you her first senpai
collab i'm not sure
her um
collab band ends on like i don't know
tomorrow or the day after tomorrow so i
don't know if she planned anything
before
me
she might maybe have something planned
with indonesian senpai's also i don't
know but i i don't think she has
anything planned with yen senpai's
before me
um
or japan senpai's for that matter i
don't know i don't know but it could be
it could be
um
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
do you feel confident about carrying her
um well i'll definitely i definitely
will know way more than she knows i told
her that i recommend her to play portal
beforehand if she has time on stream
even maybe
i don't think she did it i don't think
she's uh
gonna do it in the next couple of days
um
when i recommended that to her i i was
myself not quite sure how important it
would be i just said you should maybe
maybe try
i'm gonna do it too
um but she'll be fine if she has me
as long as there's one person who
understands it
um i will do my best to explain it to
her
i can already hear kiara mommy yeah like
oh my god even in
even in dms she always calls me phoenix
mommy phoenix mommy now though right not
chicken mommy thank god that little brat
and she calls me a phoenix mommy so
she really is um
even in dms she is like that all the
time
which
gives me weird weird fuzzy feelings in
my
mind in my brain
no no if she calls me chicken mommy i'm
gonna give her butt spanx
oh no neco
it's question marks that's for sure
um wish i could understand indonesia
yeah kobu speaks a lot of indonesian in
her streams doesn't she which is i think
it's good for the you know indonesian
fans after all she's from whole life
indonesia so it's just sad that you know
i know a lot of us are curious a lot of
us who don't speak indonesian are surely
very curious but
um she's idea we have to accept that
i'll i'll get her to speak a lot of
english though because i don't
understand indonesian she will have to
speak english with me
yeah
yeah i am
i don't know if she wants to be spanked
by me but the truth is i don't want to
spank anyone i i wouldn't spank
uh if i had children i would never spank
them um so that was it was just a joke i
wouldn't i wouldn't spank her in reality
that's just weird to me
um she still sounds nice yes even if we
can't understand that is true she's she
sounds super super sweet and cute
mommy is your mom no no no she has two
moms i'm one of them
i mean
i would be fine just being
her big sister for example
i don't know being called mommy
confuses me a little bit
maybe i would be more comfortable if she
called me
something like big sister but
we'll have to talk about that i'm not
sure if i'm ready to be someone's mother
it already happened but maybe we can say
okay that means your mommy i'm your big
sister or something or your or your aunt
no not your grandfather no no no no not
that old bgm doco sorry no busy i'm
actually ending in here i'd love to read
super chats but it's pretty late and i
gotta still cook i gotta use up my hello
fresh ingredients that i got yesterday i
need to cook before before it's too late
yeah
uh i have like three different dishes i
think i'm gonna
hmm
i have some kind of chicken penny that
uh one of one of them is a chicken
penny with broccoli so i think i'm gonna
make that one
wish me luck
before the fresh is goodbye exactly it's
still fresh
not sponsored no no not sponsored
but
hell fresh what's up
feel free to
hit me up
i can do cooking streams
yeah we haven't done a cooking stream in
a while
um
yeah and they have a lot of nice recipes
it would be a good idea i think yeah
can i use coke chia to get 10 on my
first box
um currently no
currently no maybe sometime in the
future
make the cake from portal 1.
i think did we talk about that last time
but i i never made a cake before so i'm
not sure i should probably start with a
small cake to practice and then make
that big cake hmm
i love black forest cake though i
absolutely love it
there's a recipe online yeah that isn't
the problem but i wanna i don't know i
just i don't wanna immediately jump into
such a huge
endeavor you know
make it in a cupcake form yeah if it's
just a basic uh black forest cake
recipe then i'm sure there's like
a way to put it into cupcakes and make
it smaller
yeah oh probably
probably probably
i am actually
already very hungry
and uh i will read super chats
another time if that's okay for you guys
um i'm not sure if that will be a stream
tomorrow that might be a short one
maybe but
uh i'll keep you guys updated
uh as as if i can
it might be very gorilla if i do one it
might be it might be very gorilla
i don't know i'll see what i can do
i'll go cooking now
and then
i'll decide after that maybe okay thank
you guys for watching my journey for
portal 1 and portal 2. it was uh
fun also a little bit um made me made me
feel stupid but but i hope you guys
enjoyed it
um i tried to
um
do my best today even though
you might not believe it
the first part was okay again i would
say i would say the first couple of
riddles puzzles i solved pretty well
just fine
you can feel smart next week yeah
hopefully i won't feel i won't feel too
stupid when i teach kobo how to play the
game
thank you guys thank you thank you
it was nice to experience such a
well-known legendary game together with
you guys on my channel for the first
time ever it was my first time playing
portal 1 and portal 2
um it was quite the experience i love
the banter
um
the the level designs were smart and
interesting
there was some some passages there that
were more difficult but then we had some
more easy ones following up with that
again and all that relatively easy so at
least it was not
like there was some time for my brain to
chill for a little bit i guess
and the story was interesting and and
yeah the characters are really cute even
the little objects in yum
you like gladys or wheatley better
it depends in what state of mind they
are at the moment
when they're both nice
then
i like wheatley better because gladys
when she's nice the thing about gladys
is she's way more interesting when she's
evil
when she's nice then she's just nice
she's just like a sweet
sweet somewhat sweet nice person but
yeah whitley's much more interesting
when he's nice
uh when when wheatley is evil
then actually i prefer gladys because
wheatley as being evil was just um
yeah
he was
he was trying to be evil but it was like
a tryhard
well cave johnson cave johnson
let's just say i'm glad he's dead
yeah um
yes
may he not rest in peace may he rest in
hell
okay i'm gonna go now and i need some
time for cooking okay thank you guys
everybody for watching hope you enjoyed
it and the german was selfie that said
sorry i need to go
so
quickly today
sorry
but thank you
thank you thank you everybody
it was
great thank you
don't miss the collab next week okay if
you want to see more of this even better
co-op will probably be even more fun
yeah we can use both of our brains let's
see how smart kobo is um
love you guys thank you
thanks for the super chats too
appreciate it i'll read them next time i
promise
next time when i got done
[Music]
do
you