[Music]
I'm tired of the same song
every take me away like just two us
you feel music
[Music]
baby don't need no drink tonight give me
that me daning
[Music]
feel come on and slam and welcome to the
gym come on and slam and welcome to the
[Music]
gym so robotic so
emotionless across the
Dan Honey follow me
[Music]
[Applause]
up I don't need no drinks tonight give
me that get me Dan
[Music]
I'm in way that you're moving you got
shining glowing like a PR that this
makes me wild
[Music]
Shin Like
A makes me
[Music]
Al I don't need no drinks tonight give
me that feet get me
dancing I Don't Need No drinks tonight
give me that get me daning
[Music]
on and slam and welcome to the
gym come on and slam and welcome to the
gym come on and
slam come on and slam and welcome to the
gym come on and slam and n o a oo
okay
[Music]
stop come on in Minecraft and welcome to
the server come come on and mine and
welcome to the blog come on and mine and
and hey
yo yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
nobody here for now
but GAA will most likely join and I'mma
give me a maybe so uh yeah chat on
stream there's no space that
yo there's no
space no not this not this time
this time we're doing no chat no chat a
maybe yeah Amy gave me a May
a
I'm
oh maybe Kazuki Kazuki the am Clipper is
like his ears are like oh hey yo hey yo
did I just hear an AM
reference use Callie oh I
mean I I can put you there but
like I mean if you
insist if you
insist s this how big how
big you insist you do man
okay but I kind of the way I layered
like I layered it in Photoshop it and I
saved it so I can't really put you
behind Cy there unfortunately it's not
as nice it's not as pretty as it could
be
oh there just sense a disturbance in The
Matrix
no I just felt
something I just felt
something okay so yeah GAA told me that
she can uh show up like before her own
stream and she did give me a like yeah
maybe I can be there from the beginning
so we'll see maybe she'll like stumble
in in a bit Yeah and then I I don't know
and then tomorrow I might join like K's
session I might have two sessions
tomorrow
tph
mhm okay well you tell me if you see the
the shark you know in 2D I can't look
behind me so if you see something you
got to tell me well maybe I'll hear her
first before I see her but that was my
favorite joke I've ever made I think
yesterday and I I feel like because of
you know all the yapping it kind of got
lost but it's just I think it was a
really funny joke when the big shark was
behind me and I was like ah is there
something behind me and you guys are
like don't look behind you or look
behind you and I'm like I can't I'm too
see I literally I can't this is this is
as far as I can
go no that was so funny I was actually
one of my best jokes ever to this
date okay so yeah I'll go in then
um let's join the
server wait today we might need bgm
because at least for now wait let me out
let me
out at least for
now oh see Hol Ian can't resolve host
name um I think
they took it down or is
it they did say something like they're
taking it down forever and I was like a
yo what
no
no I cried what do you mean can't
connect okay shut The Mother We we'll
get there I'm looking for some
bgm here let me put in a couple and we
can like look through them it's history
exactly whoa
jungle jungle's kind of cool
whoa this is so cool this is a good
bgm it's
cute but that will be very
[Music]
repetitive
ah good old everyday
[Music]
bgm could also be very repetitive
yeah that was something Pokemon is I
know oh oh I think this one kind of this
Loops this Loop isn't so good this
[Music]
one and it's too
chill cute well let me skip a bit
H very
[Music]
wholesome I like this
one it's
funny maybe for now for a little bit for
the
beginning I want this for the beginning
now what what what what the [\h__\h]
happened
here there we
go
okay did something change I wonder a
it's time to read
Diaries Niki
y okay give me this is uh goba Goa you
guys don't know yet what they wrote in
there because they didn't stream it how
do you read this a there let's go day
one Batman I I I caught
a I caught a little dolphin ah do you
want to know what I caught what did you
cat GA I call a dolphin k i callau a
dolphin oh no GAA
don't I'm giving you an F on your
homework it's funny but you're got to
tell me okay maybe in this case it
doesn't matter actually the first day it
didn't matter but the next day better
actually tell me what you
did and I I I I understand now I
understand fully now that it was a meme
okay next one is Ena uh oh oh new start
many books my parent was murdered hey I
mean it was an accident and that in that
case isn't it called manslaughter or
pirate
Slaughter and and I mean mine was also
killed so I lost many things but we get
stuff
back okay yeah first day I will accept
this for the first
day oh
day one I'm the [\h__\h]
organizer that you are kaop be that is
true honestly without her this place
would be such a mess especially the
chests that that would be the biggest
mess of all I'm
me uh today we play one block I can't
believe it this girl these girls did not
take the assignment
seriously they did not take you Simon
seriously I will give them the benefit
of the doubt because this was day one
okay and because I was there for all of
it because the the general reason for
this is because what if for example
today I play some stuff I do some stuff
I get some stuff done and then somebody
picks up from there when I'm not there
and they might want to know what did she
do what did she do what did I miss is
there something new that I should know
you know and then they got to come in
here and read you know you know to find
out what they should
[Music]
know yeah where's your book well I
didn't we didn't have another book w w
no book maybe today we can find another
book you
[Music]
know overall we will decide first of all
what to
do we'll decide what to do and I don't
know if we should put this here maybe
not but Calli will take care of
it sorting Callie please sort this
Callie okay why H if I get what was it
two more two more pieces of paper I
think
then yeah how can you make pumpkin pot I
think we can't yet maybe oh bum boo no
we need it's like a pumpkin cake
right well
don't think I can do that
[Music]
now oh my God the donkey
scream scares
me a
berries ah no wait that was right that
was
ah y y y y no good no good no good oh go
oh no good no good no good no good no
good no good no good come here come here
yeah go around the
corner I'm I'm not going to have
anything be destroyed now is he
following me still ah he ah he's staying
there like I would lead
him let's let's just try to keep him
there for now because now he'll L up on
me maybe
though I'm scared creepers are really
scary I would bring him over there but
that also is kind of difficult what if I
die on my own that's kind of
sad hit it off the ledge
true
true oh do he see me oh he's he's he's
kind of coming for me
okay okay I mean the things I the things
I have with me right now aren't too
important anyway okay [\h__\h] y y come with
me
y okay come come over
[Music]
here attempt failed attempt
failed
well please do not Escape animals can
they go through I probably let me just
put this
here to be
fixed damn it can I go over that
too can they let me try to fix this
properly yeah they can jump on it ah God
damn it freaking Creepers we need to
have like more torches I guess what was
like uh
wood uh top wooden okay we've got some
fence gates and some Oak fence
okay axe no axe
H make axe
[Music]
maybe let's make an
axe always put things back when you can
so that you don't lose it right okay so
far why are they staying maybe they
don't want to be rained on so they're
trying to stay as close as possible to
the oh don't don't even don't think
about
it okay this works as close as possible
to the house because totally that
protects you from the rain
right rip free diamonds what do you mean
what happened with free
diamonds feel fill hole
yeah let's see what do we have to
fill I'm going to put this
back could
fail ah oh wait what what is that Coral
block do we have some normal
Stone bottom
dirt oh
there's stone stone
okay okay so stone equals
dirt yesterday you fell into the vo yeah
that was yesterday today is today we
don't live in the past guys we don't
live in the past we don't think about
the
past okay now
uh I think we're going to start with a
particular
Mission will that be enough
[Music]
can I how do you how do you cut
these surely we don't need
Sandstone do we have a stone cutter or
how were they were they just cutting
them in
here I don't remember that we had a
stone cutter okay wait ah you need free
Block block to make six
slabs interesting why not just put one
in there and give me what I
want not a
[Music]
h not a hood okay so what do you think
I'm going to do with that I think you
know you
know so I want to start by building the
basement I suppose because I'm not very
good at like creating anything useful
[Music]
wow what a what a comment to write
Crush of course it had a massive
viewership drop you don't have to write
it so directly but even then this is not
bad right
now yesterday was a full myth collab so
anyway
okay don't rob it in my
face not that I careed like why why do
you write
that why do I read it because of it was
a huge [\h__\h]
paragraph and I want to give you know
everybody a chance to be read if you
write a whole [\h__\h] paragraph you know
you you might think oh they have
something to say that might you know
ban in German we
Sayan the
stream all right now keep in mind I
might drown right so we don't want to
drown wait let me try to get on that
platform that already exists okay
okay now I don't think I have to build a
whole platform underneath that whole
path right for now we just maybe want to
haveit I want a chance to
be a
funny cute random collusion I hope I
randomly Collide into GAA and Amy
today but I think it's good to have the
basement just like here right like under
this main
area now just don't stop maybe I should
put it on toggle I normally don't but I
really should in this
case
uh was it
here
no what is this sound where is the
toggle thing
again maybe
[Music]
accessibility what the [\h__\h]
crazy sounds okay ah this is so weird
now I feel like because it's on toggle
and I'm not used to it now I feel like
I'm accidentally going to press toggle
again to un toogle accidentally even
though all I want to do is oh God keep
my pinky away from that torches ah I
should should I get torches before
continuing this I might be greeted by an
enemy next time I come down here
[Music]
yeah okay I'll try to I'll try to make
torches okay torches we need coal and
wood right coal was it
coal let's
see coal and stick m
[Music]
yum please help
me y yum
[Music]
Y no no no no no no no no no no no I
mean in this one at least there was only
CD right oh thank God oh yeah there was
only CDs in that one and I think I
picked some of them up bro
[Music]
bro
bro I can't I can't be doing this alone
I I I I need mental support and somebody
who watches my back torches yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah I'm trying to make them
no oh no oh no why is there so many
[Music]
enemies donkey do something donkey oh
there's one in there too does it kill
the oh no it
won't wait wait wait I need to heal up
first I need to heal why is there so
many spawning in the first place like
this shouldn't be
happening oh I should sleep for the
night if only I had a oh there's a
creeper in the skeleton if only I had a
bed if only I had a bed I shouldn't
should okay I think he lost track of me
for now there's enemies everywhere okay
torches Tor Tor Tor I need a I
need I need I need I need I need I need
a
workbench stop hitting me I'm here to
hit you
die ah do we have any extra workbench or
do I need to build one oh
God wait I'm dying wait I'm
dying jump and hit
no
to is there there's an Enderman in there
oh cute he will protect me
[Music]
right the sound of the parrots sounds
like a
creeper otherwise is open oh did you
take the block oh he totally took the
block oh my God
[Music]
man this is this is not good to play
Alone come on heal up come
on come
[Music]
on can you make one bed I'm not sure I
oh God the
creeper right outside the window as soon
as
I can get you know oh
no why are roaming around like
that if he sees me through the window
can they see me for the window no what
[Music]
right they smell fear they totally do no
okay um oh still I'm scared
[Music]
hi we're up to a great start yep
oh Enderman is protecting me don't worry
about it right
yeah so I will go outside try to make
torch to I have wood with me not
really I could make a workbench I we
should put a workbench in here for safe
working without being ambushed
[Music]
Camp there waiting for G G please C
please you don't need a crafting table
for to all yeah but like um I don't have
enough things
anyway I need more things okay it's
getting daytime at least one good
thing
but two Creepers right outside my
doorstep
[Music]
one here one here I a
spider
[Music]
um okay wait okay one on the left
where's the other one one over there
okay
okay spider right there okay M no that's
that's not good that's not good okay I'm
going to go I'm going to go we're going
to go and we're going to run
towards right side
maybe if anything like over
here maybe I should fight with the iron
axe catch him in the boat
what which one you can't catch a creeper
or a spider
right oh you mean him well the boat is
occupied H
hi
hi you can creepers and spiders you can
catch them in a
boat really I've never seen anyone do
that I
think oh come
on oh come on
[Music]
please
G
help go out the back make back
door oh
good yeah good will be my master
bait
[Music]
I'm I
can't help
help help me help me help
[Music]
okay I'm going to go through but what if
there's something there to there's a
high chance that there's something there
oh that leads to okay the Red
[Music]
House bit oh
oh okay wait that's that's can I if I
touch
him oh no oh no oh
[Music]
no please please no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
[Music]
me
me okay well
wait what's that chest doing
there
[Music]
okay let's bait him who bait bait bait
bait bait bait bait bait bait bait bait
oh God oh God oh God oh God okay ah ah
ah ah ah ah is he
coming hey hey
[Music]
I'm here I'm
here no not go don't go up there
hey although maybe I should have put a
block there so he can't go
down I'm never going to I'm no no no no
no
I'm just destroying
everything I'm just destroying
everything ah no no no stop
stop I'm just is there another one as
far as I remember I think there may have
oh or or maybe not now oh God oh God oh
God oh
God
um oh man I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm
so
sorry run for it animals no please no oh
my I should have brought oh well
whatever no no no no no no well we don't
need you guys any anyway not like we
need you guys we need the cows yeah you
you understood that we don't need the
llamas but you can go back in go back no
stop cow stop it C no no no no no no no
no you like the only one we really need
you stop it stop it stop stop stop stop
stop stop stop stop stop no no no no no
there's a block there I just put it
there okay
whatever what are you doing out
there okay whatever free roaming cows I
support that it's a good thing
so
um for
now fixing it up like that okay back to
making
torches as long as it's daytime we got a
Galu
uh didn't I wasn't there more
coal how did the girls get coal so far
just like uh like
burning wood
[Music]
burn wood with wood
H oh I want to put
this
actually in
here so that I can safely make things in
there is there any torches that I didn't
see chest by the water has coal oh
this one oh yeah 64 okay okay okay okay
then we're good we're kind of good we're
kind of
[Music]
good okay that's a good amount for now
although I'm probably still need
more probably still need
more sorry guys I'm like I keep on
opening the same chests over and over
and over and over again I know I know is
that all the wood no
[Music]
wood had one more of these
nice I'm going to I'm going to put
another one here cuz it's going to be
useful you think I got enough but I'm
going to make this whole area actually
we first of all we need apparently we
need more up here right
so ah maybe cuz this is an older version
of Minecraft that means that they're not
as like loose anymore with how little
light there has to be or how much light
right cuz they changed it so that you
don't need as many torches anymore but
we definitely need more torches
now cuz this is the like an old pretty
old version
so yeah makes
sense M should I make some up there too
oh there's a few maybe one two more
there's some up
there some here is there some behind oh
hello yeah you're welcome to stay there
stay
just I know this looks nicer without
torches but we need
them
[Music]
okay a light level viewer not sure how
to even look at
that
okay how what do you think is this
decent do we need a lot more so that the
mobs don't spawn
F yeah where's the server light there's
server light 15 Sky 11 block
no not sure where you can see it oh that
was
it does that mean every 11 blocks or
so 4080 nice yay
[Music]
you want eight plus block okay I don't
really know does that mean I have to
make more or is that the goal or what
whatever whatever
whatever here
m
m here
M
here maybe it's too much maybe it's it's
fine just place them all but they also
need to go below oh the creeper is gone
where did it
go where did the creeper
go let me put him here so no more
creepers spawn behind that where did he
go for real could he ah there he
is
M too bad you can't reach me hm how do
you hit him again without them exploding
I I I used to be somewhat able to do
it yeah yeah go here let's try this oh
mom maybe I can push you off kind of
[Music]
diagonally H A I did do the
hit you almost fell
off no come come here
there he goes all right all right oh God
it's turning night
again
[Music]
um yeah
yeah
yep at least there's a fence here but
still okay
this is why cats are needed instead of
killing there are cats but they're
chilling true we should set those cats
free what the hell I mean they they put
themselves in there honestly but they
would be really helpful for the creepers
yeah okay how to not kill the
cat did the
zombie kill the Villager is that uh
possible I think cuz I saw the Villager
in there and I saw the zombie in there
and I was like oh can they really
coexist yes okay that is not good that
that
happened but it's okay we can get
everything
back for
sure oh my God
hello g g
boo I've been for some crazy stuff
already did you survive did you die
barely barely survived um all of our
villagers are dead
um oh what happened oop sorry cat um
well I was like overwhelmed by
enemies a and had to run around and I
that was really a lot and then there
were some sorry cat zombies in the some
zombies in the in the room that we made
for the
villagers oh and I I couldn't save them
I
couldn't they are so dead did you
try I tried to deal with the creepers
first that were following me everywhere
and exploding some
things did you try to save the villagers
h no no there was no no I couldn't I
couldn't I probably would have died
myself first
[Music]
watch the stream play back and see what
happened okay well I also have been
putting um torches everywhere because of
all the spawning I realized we don't
have enough torches everywhere cuz the
enemies were spawning
everywhere so yeah now it looks a little
bit
better yeah and now I'm going to build
the
underground floor I suppose and put
torches there too
building a
basement a basement to put you in when
you're naughty what have I
done you your homework was not
satisfactory what homework we didn't do
we have homework the the Diaries but
everybody just wrote like one sentence I
mean you you made a meme which was funny
why I'll forgive you for the first day
because the first day the purpose was
really just not really the same um it's
it's like if I'm streaming and you pick
off of where I'm streaming then you got
to read my diary to figure out what I
did you
know we were all together so it didn't
matter fair fair fair you read my diary
though yeah of course did it make you
blush M it was funny it was certainly
fun you like it you need you blush I I I
liked it because I learned something
from it but I still gave you you an F
because in terms of diary and being like
a good a good followup of what you have
done it was not it was not good that's
subjective that is entirely
subjective people are saying you're too
loud but like I I
mean I do hear um you're like when
you're louder it's like uh breaking what
do you what do you call it again peing
yeah I updated my go XLR and all the
settings are borked my
bad sorry sorry sorry I I I like Peak
good Peak
Performance funny microphone
goes Xbox microphone let's
go
likey never had an Xbox did you ever
have an
Xbox
uh I've only re received an Xbox through
my time at Hol
label
[Music]
nice the Xbox was never on my
radar
Xboxes
uh Xbox nice I like how easily they
connect to the
PC okay another cat has died I don't
know why it preferred to jump off the
cliff rather than live with us but you
stinky
oh boy yeah Xbox to be cool I since even
to this day I've never touched one ever
before are you coming online or what
yeah I'm working on it take time I
thought maybe you just joined me to chat
and give me oh shark behind
me sh shall I adjust you
yeah yes please you want to be in the
Yukata yeah okay you got
your faor night outfit yeah yeah that's
what I was going to say it's the the BBA
for the gooa you got the waas out man
almost almost almost I got to bring
something I have nothing to offer I have
I got the W out you should bring the
goas out I don't have any goas to bring
goomas are whatever you say they are
they don't have to be the equivalent of
my
waas could be something else what are
the
goo what is my equivalent
maybe maybe just you're going to say
your tail yeah or the stinky
um my smelly Aura stiny
hoodie H shame if they say tail they
don't even want to look me in in the
eyes you just want to see my
backside for
shame I I need more coal that would be
nice so I'll make more uh
coal I'm so happy you're here now hello
let's go you can help me you can help me
be
productive yes oh why is it not burning
I thought you can burn wood with
wood uh it you
die it has to be logs no no no no no no
no no no no okay let's do something
about these trees here then we can just
regrow
them what do we have them
for damn one block Minecraft is really
difficult
yes what about this one is this okay
should be
okay do you have bgm I do have something
on right now good I'll maybe change it
later people get very sick of
it should so so this a oh oh
oh I thought it would have to be both
logs okay never mind just one plank here
and some logs
here
interesting doing a k later
huh and you're announcing
something yeah oh I have a feeling I
know what it is wait that's charcoal
does charcoal
work
maybe what
[Music]
yes it works okay thank god oh no more
sticks I mean you have not told me what
you're announcing but I still have a
feeling so it's not like I'm spoilering
anything I really don't know but I have
a
feeling what could it
me gooa gooa of the
boa goba of the Noba what is your wisd
oh she's here let's
[Music]
go it has been so peaceful for the past
20 minutes which is incredible
considering how it was before those 20
minutes Takashi K are the bringer of
chaos
so
basically um yeah it would be nice if we
could get sheep
again but you can help me build the
basement first maybe you place the
Torches and I place the blocks
yeah that works I think a was doing the
Sheep I don't know where she left off so
maybe we should letor some torches ah
damn
it
there nice my ping
hurts and wait we're making a few more
torches I'm not sure if oh maybe it's
enough maybe it
is yeah I'll have 16 16 more
take them take them
Tores okay
now I already started a little bit down
there I hope you are good with uh diving
through
water H well I am I happen to be a shark
ma'am true I forgot that how could you
how could you How Could You Forget well
you haven't really been very Sharky
recently
oh hi Takira oh my God I forgot you were
orange you scared me for a
second you hear that how that sounds
where is this
going uh follow follow follow go down a
little bit through the water wait wait
yeah come back oh you went way too
low oh
God don't
die oh my God what if I did that would
be like so funny that would be so funny
I hope we don't
be a shame if I pushed you right now
o do you have anything valuable in your
inventory
um
uh
food okay that's that's not I mean I
would value some food right now but uh
that's not that bad I have how do I
split a stack wait never mind I fig no
no no let's not do it now or
here yeah it's fine it's
fine actually maybe we're faster if
you're also putting down some
blocks give me give me some okay wait
safety here are some Sandstone
slabs ooh well there's a lot you've been
busy wait should I go on the opposite
side like this side
wherever
teamwork wow in the dream work just
always press
shift what if I don't want
to that's not a smart decision but I'm
not going to and then I'm going to blame
you when I fall why didn't you tell me
oo it's kind of like we're in the end
making paths in the end or in the
never it's about as dangerous
oh oh oh oh W I thought I bumped into
you no I want to bump into
you bump into me what did I say I was
hoping to collide with you I said I said
something like that before you came is
that weird to say that no no I don't
think
so why were the kfp like that's weird
dude I'm not sure I'm it's hard to
really take anything in
currently the
chaos ah oh because yeah I read a ah I
read a a a Super Chat and their their
name was random collusion and I said I
hope I'll be randomly colliding with am
Ora today oo and then the chaos was
happening and I said I need some bait
because I was like stuck in a house with
two creepers and a spider surrounding
the house and said I'm not going to go
go out I need I need bait I need I hope
GAA will be my master bait is what I
said uhhuh I've said worse though I've
said before that I'm the master Bor and
I was quite proud of
that of course only in situations where
it really fits where it's very
[Music]
suitable I wouldn't say it
lightly no only in the most serious of
times
no why I always make sure that context
is
provided always
yeah context is important I've learned
the Foreigner thing by the way I think
you were also confused yesterday about
it right yeah you guys started calling
us you start Foreigner
Foreigner for what reason what do mean I
think so originally I think the example
would be P
Senai uh like her image being men ulated
by foreigners to make a reaction image
so that would be one example but then
later on they've started doing that with
um what who was the next one not M moku
was like the result of what that person
said
uh you know how you a yeah yeah somebody
then went on to uh like enl Arch I think
the mouth of Ida and make that into a
reaction Meme and then a Japanese bro
saw that and was
like like explaining that to the
Japanese nikkes the other ones like oh
yeah so foreigners they like to
manipulate
images and then the is it new to them to
them it was like like oh again huh like
after P now you're doing it with Ida I
guess that was like how they saw it and
they're like these foreigners seem to
like manipulating images dude Mario
party is from Japan that's like a main a
mini game is distorting Bowser's face
that one you started it JP friends you
started it that one is not even you know
what that one is referencing though the
Mario Party game Bower stret you one
what isn't that referencing Nintendo
64 the loading still Nintendo isn't it
yeah yeah yeah yeah but I think that has
its origin too yeah Super Mario 64 the
loading screen is the reference I love
that the one where he laughs he's like
Super Mario yeah
64 64 and then because of that I didn't
know that I didn't know this was the
reason why then they went crazy with
like Moko
images um but the foreigners found that
comment so funny they were like oh okay
let's do more and then they started
doing a million of mos
specifically now they're all over I I
learned something new damn didn't know
that was the the motivation behind it m
m
j Mo
Coco oh my God Mo Coco my favorite twins
Mo
Coco MO Coco moo Jan and huaa it's fre
people it is three people yeah they're
triplets what wait wait I'm not up to
date on
this I I just updated you now you know I
need more
blocks why am I teos on your side what
is that what I look like oh you oh that
oh that you didn't fix it and it was not
on purpose oh no
I think yeah you maybe you like reopen
your phone thingy try that or a
reenter I thought that you were aware of
it can we not mix 3D with 2D maybe
that's what it is I think we can but
probably better not to I've seen it
happen before
though what should we split man what do
we have a lot like gr Granite Granite
Granite gr Granite Granite Granite damn
it granny wait I got to leave the room
cuz I uh wait wait wait wait wait
wait no problem I got to change my
outfit and the the the names of these
outfits is a mess mhm mhm I don't know
which is witch I always tell them please
delete this and this and this and this
and this please delete it so so I don't
get so confused anymore let me go into
to what is it called when you go into
Dev mode and let me change it I can do
it mode what you can do
that well can't you and you know when
you do slash god mode and then next
thing you know you can like go into
walls and stuff or
whatever I mean if that works for our
app let me
know damn
not in this app though wait wait which
one am I doing this
one you're still T posing in the yokata
for me I will fix don't worry
okay honestly all I need is your
voice but this is cute aren't you in
Lu okay I'm coming back wait
what's it going to be what's the out
going to be place your bets now
chat what what the that big face jump
scared
me iwi I particle eyes that
hurt oh cute I like those braids they're
so
[Music]
cute thank you I'm also really really
proud of you that you feel brave enough
to show you your
forehead cuz it's
cute wait why are you proud of me should
I not be should I wait is it bad no it's
just because I personally have like a
forehead um what's the word your self
conscious forhead and then also there
there's ena's case who had the forehead
thingy but then she stopped using it
because people were playing games on her
forehead I see I feel bad but I get it I
get it I get it but uh it didn't bother
me too much do you need help to be put
into your baby
seat wait wait I got
it can she do it I mean that's pretty
good they can use my forehead as a game
Bo cuz it it's it's a it's a
thought-provoking exercise it's good for
their brains give some exercise guys a
that
right you so right they need the
extracurricular
activity you have more blocks can I have
some I just ran out again of half blocks
I feel like maybe for now this is like
okayish and we should mine some more
blocks wa let me check cuz like turning
things into half blocks there's some
more prismarine
[Music]
it's just
all so little maybe these ones would you
break I don't know which is the oh okay
it's that one okay okay okay oh
wait now the best thing would
be uh to get some
sheep and some other cool
stuff sheep yeah but I think the Sheep
will have to spawn I we wanted more gr
wait why we have grass now why are they
not was it always this green this ground
I don't know I don't know what Amy did
Amy was watching the grass grow after
the stream chat um I guess she watched
it for really long because this wasn't
all green before I think I think I think
she was online for a while damn I
remember coming back and seeing her
still damn in M but didn't we think that
the Sheep would uh spawn on the
grass ah and I don't see any sheep
spawning there well no don't they have
to be pooped out of the The Source thing
again pooped out of the yeah I guess I
guess that's how it works I guess it
doesn't work any other
way I'm going to plant some trees here
why are these not growing maybe I mean
space issues here here
maybe is this not enough space for get
in the house no right right in the
middle right in the middle why you got
to be here yeah I'll go
into
[Music]
y finding or making an arrow and bow
would be really good too oh can do that
I think wait I forgot how to make one
Arrow wait we have arrows
[Music]
bow is he gone is he
gone I hear him well see now it's good
if even if it would have fallen down
there would already be floor down here
amazing let me pick those up blocks are
precious right
now who decided to make the gas sound
like a little
baby the developer I
suppose you you don't like it I don't
like
it let's send a
complaint dear
mooji wait how do you make a bow can you
not make a bow have I forgotten all of
my Minecraft abilities I feel like you
should be able to you want to go down
again we have a few more blocks to
Place actually maybe try to um find
something in the chest that you can turn
into
slabs and bring some
more okay okay nice nice nice nice I
don't like it it's like growling
ew it's Ching it will fly away and
despawn spawn
yourself you like you like like the lord
of the rain
stuff already right I like the Lord of
the Rings yes so I'm wondering did I
ever ask you if you like Game of Thrones
and
stuff I have never touched Game of
Thrones oh my
God oh my God you should no I've heard
it's really intense and I really don't
like intense shows they scary the Rings
is intense too no Lord of the Rings is
kind of not like not like Game of
Thrones I don't person personally I
don't think okay cuz the new season of
the prequel is coming out like I think
next week Game of Thrones so excited no
well Game of Thrones is over they're the
new like the prequel that they started
last year is called House of the
Dragon o
yeah no I I don't know anything about
but House of the Dragon I feel like so
far it has been I mean you could say I'm
wrong but I feel like it has been less
intense than how Game of Thrones was
going oh but it's good it's
good
uh sorry I'm crafting bre Breaking Bad I
still need to watch that's a good show
you like it if you like it's also I
watch it it's also I would say breaking
beds in pens in its own
way okay okay I extended a bit more but
but but I also just I like old men
characters doing cool
stuff is there any other example for
that besides the breaking bad dude uh
Devil May Cry is an example of old guys
being cool really yeah okay well I guess
actually that applies to gandal as
well yes and he gets bonus points cuz
he's a wizard yay just like you he's old
and he's cool and he's a wizard but in
The Hobbit you barely tell he's barely
there he's like hello hello boys here oh
I got to go bye yeah and then ra is
before everybody's going to die oh
suddenly out of nowhere here comes the
old wizard man busting through the trees
like I will save the day and then he
goes oh goodbye you don't think think
that's
cool I think it's cool
but I don't know I kind of
wanted I I wanted I wanted the the star
of the show to get a little bit more
more you know
true so why way these trees not growing
let me try a bone meal I don't know oh
okay I think it might have been these
things stopping it from growing but over
there I don't know is Metal Gear Solid
an old man
M gear solid uh the snake guy you mean
yeah is snake old is snake old yeah yeah
he seems old how
old is there an official age but if if
you can't go by age because what are you
over
9,000 they need to have white hair like
I do you need to be graying and then
then I'm interested oh okay so you're
are you old
then yes
oh old and wise old and wise not very
wise but very
old these things grow so slowly I don't
know if it's a placement
or
something
but I think at least we got some tree
stuff going here let me mine this one
already is a placement yeah I think so
too like right next to a fence I guess
it doesn't want to grow I
guess I need to look up a
list cool
old old a list for that there is a list
for that there is
yes are wait who made this that's so
pretty me that's my cocoa bean tree oh
damn yeah wait so can I cut this down
and replace it again with another
tree probably it looks like it has
lanterns on
it
nice old man deer list
when give me sapling come
on did you list funny old
men M Santa
Claus see another cool old guy yeah
totally
uh you don't sound as interested in this
as I would
hope yeah that's that's a difficult one
that's a tough
one k you oh yeah like K well he doesn't
start off old but he's definitely old by
the game that I
played yeah which one did you play well
several ones but like in the most recent
Yakuza that they released K is like
really old at that point I mean his skin
is still Flawless but he's like 50 or
something okay that's not really old
let's just say that 50 but like he's got
white hair already like he's he's aged a
lot throughout the games that is like
really impressive I like to see that in
a game like a game that actually
shows growth as in like
age that's so cool I love that it's like
Red Dead they did that and in a
significant way too
uh wait do you plant that Cocoa Tree
with cocoa
beans it's a jungle tree and then once
the jungle tree grows and you just put
the beans on the side oh okay yeah I
found the
tree
nice uh how did we make um what's it
called again the the the the the the
stuff to grow things how did we make
that
again the wait what the make the stuff
to grow things
yeah what was that called again bone
meal okay bone meal with bones I suppose
the magic
dust
bones but I don't know why I'm even
trying so hard to make these trees grow
right now it's not that
important let
me uh I think the basement how's it
looking down there maybe we're done cool
old men in video
games ah how's the basement looking
big big
okay sounds
promising then maybe maybe I'm going to
put the coal here top five old guys in
gaming oh have you played The Last of Us
no would it no would you
count I don't
know gal geralt from The
Witcher cool very cool he his voice
bothers me but yeah he's cool he gets
cool points oh my God you mean the voice
in the show yes it it bothers me too no
the voice in the game I've never seen
the show oh oh interesting so we're like
the other way around I was going to play
it though um a I I was like watching the
show and I was like okay I got to play
this game but yeah I'm going to play it
at some point this
year you played the game how far did you
play it did you stream it I I am playing
vicariously through sir funnel
ah you're not playing then but uh no
yeah you've been a lot in FAS and also
in my streams thank you for showing up
my bias is showing oh no my favorite
streams to watch oh
no wait I'm flattered right
now I was watching uh your boxing stream
also the other day oh God I was watching
it live and I was kind of like I was
vibing in my kitchen while watching you
on my iPad I was cooking and then you
were punching c yeah you it you were
punching and I was punching along with
you in
Rhythm why can I not what were you
making do you remember M don't know but
could probably check my Twitter on that
date and find out what I cooked kiwa's
kitchen yeah kiwa's kitchen what do you
think about ki's kitchen I like it I saw
your peanut Curry recently yeah yeah
yeah have you ever had chicken sa sa I
think so it's that chicken skewer with
peanut like dip I
guess chicken SK sounds yummy I I must
have eaten it before you it's so good to
put peanut butter dips or whatever on
chicken it's incredible I learned this
this year I wish I would have known
earlier peanut butter man do you like
peanut butter like on its own do you
like to put it on
bread with G I am not a consumer of the
peanut butter no okay me neither me
neither but it's amaz with with
[Music]
chicken it's also good if you do uh are
they called summer rolls you know when
you take rice paper and you roll fresh
veggies in them spring rolls summer
rolls it's summer rolls spring rolls is
when you fry
it yeah
really am I right guys wait wait wait
fact check fact check kfp it changes to
to summer
rolls because you don't fry it wait I
mean I'm wait hold up objection hold up
PA you got to look that one
up H un not fried spring rolls not fried
spring roll
no fry
fresh spring rolls is there no
difference wait what is a summer roll
heard of summer rolls too the more I
hear it now I feel like it sounds
familiar but is that really the
difference between
them I have no spring rolls spring rolls
are wrapped in Dough made of flour and
water and then fried while summer rolls
are wrapped in translucent rice wrapper
and served cold yeah those dip them
makes sense in peanut sauce oh so
good I can imagine that sounds good yeah
Yum Yum Yum Yum okay I'm going to mine a
little bit when what phase are we
currently in it must be the same one we
were in at the end of last
stream yes so what is
that um six seven
no six it was already seven
if G say six I guess it was six I never
oh yeah oh yeah never was seven okay
seven
GAA oh jeez
seven oh is the blaze down there with
you huh what did it go is it he's dead
okay he fell
down he fell down what a
loser what yeah he fell down down here
with me what then he died oh I mean he
fell down to you yeah okay okay okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah no did he drop
something
no
lame
he I was watching some footage of other
players play people playing one block a
and oh they did not put like blocks
above their like spawner thingy I
wonder is it really
necessary they seem very professional
about
it are we professional enough for
[Music]
that no we can keep it like
this what are you doing I you can try it
I see your name not moving oh you just
open did you
just you can't just do do this from
below you got to come up
LED I was wondering what you're doing
there right
underneath just waiting to pick up items
I don't have any more blocks I got to
get more blocks get get up you don't
have to do it anymore I'm sure it's fine
oh okay for now for now who put this
bamboo here I
did oh yeah that's it it felt it feels
like it might have saved me before I
don't know
it's a good security
measure that's what I was thinking it
would be like
okay cute the panda eat the
bamboo meum meow where are you oh
there
look oh
I'm yeah let's
go
Smitty oh
[Laughter]
how do I turn
off what she has Minecraft
[Music]
TTS look mhm look here follow follow
oh
stop what is she are the messages being
read out for her for real
[Music]
I'm a look I'm a look I'm a look I'm a
look I'm a look I'm a look look I'm a
look I'm a look I'm a look here
[Music]
unfortunately I'm sorry Amy this is part
of the explosions that happened when I
was alone for 30 minutes
is she even listening to the stream cuz
she's not in the
VC she just joined I hear her yeah oh
she joined yeah wait say
something oh she's muted she's
muted come here
P Mike is moving because I'm eating and
okay okay okay fortnite wow yeah we got
a number one I'm going to mute the BJ um
maybe if he doesn't get number one
Victory kick him
out tell him it's Minecraft time get out
out n how do I get this Panda to follow
me come here you Big O he's slow you got
to give him time or you put him in a
boat and you get in the boat too he must
come make panda
baby come is putting herself into
position let
me
help follow me come come
come you boy or whatever you are
come Army SM SM Army a it's pretty
cute what's wrong with her mouth but you
know it's kind of ridiculous that all
they eat is bamboo and they can't even
digest it
properly what how did they they digest
it they they're trying to but they
barely digest
it but they I think what was it some
percentage they only digest like 10% or
so or 30 or so like properly are you
saying pandas have permanent tummy egg M
possibly that's terrible yeah I think
the I think eating all the bamboo also
has that kind of like slowing effect on
them or something like
that that's so sad it does give them
yeah the nutrition yeah that's what I
mean they don't get like you know
they're malnourished their diet is
pretty [\h__\h] for them but they refuse to
eat anything else so it's their own
fault oh my God they're just like
me in in go in look look o pretty panda
wow wow wow good job pushing that big
butt yeah big fluffy butt am has an x on
her mouth
cute eating spicy noodles wait Amma you
look like a San Rio character with your
x-shaped mouth is that what it is no
myy I'm a myy but even without that now
that you say it even without the ex oh
cute oh God cute wait I'm me why does
she have smile and that sad face is that
her
smile that's amazing she's broken I'm
sorry panda
okay um sheep we got to get sheep do we
just mine and wait for sheep we got to
mine back to like phase one or so I
guess or phase two that's when all the
animals came to
us anyy M I'm making a panda baby hold
on whoa drop us a Wither head come on
that oh and I got a golden sword
whoa why are these pandas so
stubborn ignore them they're not worth
our time no they you're supposed to have
hearts and then
you I think you have to make pumpkin
cake um
man pumpkin cake or is pumpkin soup a
thing but in any case I don't think you
can eat it on its own yeah pumpkin pump
pumpkin
pie bless you than
you how do you say bless you in German
Gaz I'm sure you've heard it before Oh I
know that gazon TI yeah
D oh my God how blessed I
am what's I going to do oh am pickaxe
[Music]
oh another Wither
Skeleton
ow I'm
cursed it's okay greens you I I won't be
CED for too
long GAA has a panda Obsession now I
want them to make a baby so bad oh yeah
it by the way there's like so much
green thanks for for watching the grass
grow I had to like reposition some of
the trees because they were not growing
though going to get this one yeah need
more dirt more more okay we oh we got to
get back to phase like one or
two for that kind of
stuff I love how you girls are just
ignoring my fight here leaving me to die
H you got it you're wearing full clad
armor you're fine that's just you're
fine that's just my
skin close enough yeah food is
something we need to yeah there's no
food what do you make with these hay
bales what about
bread
oh are you making babies over there
[Music]
maybe they don't guys do these guys make
babies look look wait I'm trying to make
bread I don't remember how to make bread
yeah I'm looking a what the hell it did
drop a skull he to the
Y spooky
Waton yeah two more and we can get the
Wither to destroy our whole base
how do there we there we
go these pandas are going to eat me all
out of
bamboo oh it's pretty cute ah it's
pretty cute okay I made some bread I put
some of it into the chest the food
chest Yum Yum Yum Yum
Yum yeah I think we got to mine a lot
today so that we can go back to the
beginning get dirt oh no
ah hi take
cover it's not worth it to fight him oh
one is
gone
[Music]
no I you make a
baby are you asking that
like I mean I don't think you can
bamboo makes a
baby I mean you can try I can leave you
there and you you can go ahead and give
it a try I I don't know to enter love
mode there must be at least eight bamboo
blocks within a five block radius of
both pandas are you kidding
me damn so dramatic
is it is he gone yeah yeah yeah okay
okay are we safe seems like
it the air is clear as we like to say oh
we got some feathers a a carrot on a
stick wait oh so you can ride a
pig yeah can you fish with the carrot on
the steak just I guess you take off the
carrot goldfish
goldfish I think you picked it up
nice
to pandas are hard to breede IRL ah did
you know that I didn't fishing means
we'll get a lot of fish to eat then our
food problem may be
solved that's good I thought we were
eating mushroom soup forever and ever
you can guide pigs oh that might only be
to guide pigs
am they
say I guess you cannot take off the
carrot yeah maybe we can make our own
fishing
rod I
support all of your dreams am all of you
what's that oh no not
again stop please stop watch and
run man in this phas there's always
gests spawn it's the worst we got to get
out of this
phase I can be oh wait I have the carrot
on a stick wait want this do you want it
well it's only useful for the pigs it
seems wait that's mine
oh see you but yeah I don't know what to
do with this we don't really have a good
use for
it a see how useful this floor is
uh except there the one place said there
was no block placed don't fall in that
hole we need to replace the wood floor
by the
chests oh so that it doesn't burn
true that is
smart that would be smart
oh oh what's in
there BL powder but I have no space you
take it
me
okay okay gas is very far
gone we good we good good riddens
that gu
stinks where is
here
Birch we can make a brewing station the
blaze
powder Brewing Station yeah that will be
useful for when we're actually going to
the Nether and the the end yeah what do
we Brewing
fellas M like fire resistance potions
and stuffff like that maybe could be
[Music]
good it's so far I can't see
him
o he sounds like an old
man but not a cool
one go I've had so much flag them in my
throat recently what should I
do you've had what in your
throat FL them
huh yeah FL them flum ah FL FL ow FL FL
FL okay fum I will also call it fum now
you oh kid today you are supportive of
my
mispronunciations did yes you're feeling
more mind flum you like it okay nice
yeah like just one people liked it so
I'm glad you agree with it an Eye of
Ender that's very good that's very good
um can you take the
rest oh yeah how do you have a full oh
wait so do I never mind I'll put this
somewhere else over over here it's too
too too
precious it's going to explode I'm just
kidding we're
upgrading phase eight way wa wa way
[Music]
way in
here put this
here got to keep stuff organized while C
is not here didn't we have string M I
never saw but we might from the spiders
yeah ah there's some six string in the
top chest here behind you
Amy processing processing
processing and this maybe and this here
car you don't drink soda do you I've
never seen you drink soda before H
interesting that you say that every time
we've been out to eat k always gets like
orange juice H do I know do I yes I feel
like you always get orange juice yeah
melon soda really yeah for example and I
also would order like Coca-Cola for
example
H I've only ever seen you do orange
juice I like orange juice but it really
depends on the
occasion what are these blocks blocks of
quart
warts
jeart oh we're getting the chiseled one
W like
F Well that
so it's funny that you said you don't
think I drink soda because CI like three
two or three years ago she made this
comment that my favorite drink must be
um orange
soda and I'm like what do you mean like
that's not true I I don't drink like she
means Fanta I guess but I don't drink
that at all I never drink Fanta actually
oh oh never ever but melon soda
yeah goodbye oh wait how do we keep the
bee I don't know if we
can diamonds but yeah she was so
convinced cuz I'm orange isn't it yeah
but I actually my favorite drink would
usually be iced tea like sweetened ice
tea
interesting yeah like from uh Lipton or
nesty anything like
[Music]
that what's this oh is that honey
block yeah it's honeycomb block and a
little jelly how you doing cutie oh so
cute what you doing
girls oh she's fishing for real she made
a fishing
rod a wait go what get caught in
4k well I C A A A A Wild gooy
B whoever gets struck by lightning first
is a big stinky smelly
nail well then it's got
to I watching got stuck my
lightning
what big stinky smell the camera
please it happened immediately after you
said
it w it's like you were summoning it to
happen I'm telling you she's a wizard
I'm I know you can hear me anyway but
I'm telling you
that was funny I hope you fish some good
stuff wizard of the sky smite me
so
coward that's
incredible can we eat the honey blocks
what do we do with this honey uh-oh
sorry sorry sorry
whoops don't break her fishing
pond strike me down Zeus hey fishing
here
hey not Watson no you already did it
once do it to
me make beehive are bees useful really
wait we got a new cat a cute one oh my
God oh my God oh my God oh my God Zeus
is uh not very powerful Zeus is a
weakling I don't like Zeus very much
which cat is that it's so pretty
[Music]
M someone befriend this cat I'll try
right we have some
fish do does it eat puffer
fish puffer fish puffer fish is probably
not a good idea to oh thank you to feed
a cat
right no those are poisonous yeah that's
not a good
idea
um I need I need cie to sort our things
[Music]
goodies that's pretty light blue
terracotta I mean go if you're bored you
could sort these
things okay that I put in these
chests okay let's find this cat you got
it
boss I'm the seemingly the only one who
has a POV so I got to do something more
interesting than
sorting no
pressure where did the cat go don't tell
me it jumped off the cliff like the
other
one
please okay don't scare the cat don't
scare the cat get out the
fish I think last time it jumped because
I got too close
right I'm holding is that what it did
maybe it's got to be raw salmon
yeah h
it's got to eat the raw salmon I just
got to make it notice oh there we go
Zeus Zeus oh my God what a baby what
about this fish what about the tropical
fish oh God does it not eat the tropical
fish I don't want to am do you have more
Salon oh God we
place yeah yeah the good thing is we
have a a whole uh floor
underneath that's a good thing
okay wa let's let's work on let's work
on
the oh thank you for the
C wait this doesn't work what the
hell oh my God
[Music]
ooh what about terracotta terra cotta
doesn't burn
right n can't have slabs man and that is
so
lame oh what well that doesn't work
either
okay
wait yeah our Minecraft version is
really old we don't have
[Music]
um
what no oh thanks for the shoes
why is this cat
so yes yes
yes sweet baby what about what about the
tropical tropical fisho yes are you
interested want and give me
shoes okay it doesn't eat tropical fish
I
think what in the heck are we going to
do
with a coral oh wait
sponge I'm going to replace this
floor what is it about us always like oh
thank you trying to replace floors right
where people are
[Music]
standing why are you digging up the
floor I'm just kidding I know
why I don't even remember who did it I
don't I don't remember was it
you or did you were you the one who fell
no oh not me not
I
know why don't you give me the boots by
the way to get extra
points I'm going give me boots too okay
let's go a boot get dressed up I love
boot you're spling what does that mean
oh wait I know what that
means
neurons no don't you
dare spff isn't that a Minecraft mini
game when you knock the floor out from
people what it's like
yeah sping it's like a mini game it's
kind of like yeah oh no what happened
here you run around and you take
people's knees out oh wow wow that went
far Deep In My Memory
Bank very empty do you remember
Minecraft Hunger Games why haven't we
done that have we done that in Holo live
why haven't we done
that Minecraft Holo Games Hunger Games
when we team up and then we go off and
then we and we and we die or we eat each
other or something oh yeah and we have
have to like start working on getting
stuff to be able to hurt each other yeah
and then the Cannons fire and it's says
like 12 teams
Remain the Cornucopia in the in the in
the center and all
that I am certainly a Hunger Games uh
fan so doesn't sound bad to me Kara
Hunger Games Minecraft
event I'll take it under
consideration that would be cool
[Music]
what you
looking is there any good fish in there
no I mean you have another good
fish wait do JP friends know what that
means what Hunger
Games do they know what Minecraft Hunger
Games
are
uh uh no but we can explain it to them
and I think the cat ises
gone cat dead
no fish
wasted fish
wasted for real if you guys see a lost
Straight Cat let me
know Minecraft Battle
Royale meow meow
meow okay
[Music]
um I had an iron helmet where did it
go I didn't die I ate it
h I can almost believe
that I oh I did die with it damn it I
thought I got the helmet after I died
then back then Dam make a baby what was
that
parrots and you made a baby let's go a
baby panda pandas a he's got boogers in
his nose holy
moly yeah cuz they different patterns
right face pattern he's literally a
slobbering booger brain that's awesome
oh y good job you're a mommy
partially I'm a what would that make
me well I feel like without you there
would be no baby so you're I think
you're part of the parent system I'm the
Fairy
Godmother yeah I'm the god
parent I want to see the baby before it
gets big come
here oh it looked at
you he's got Pian eyes do you see
that very cute stop covering up the baby
let me see the baby come here you Big O
they're so
protected oh he's got a booger nose no
just like
you
no what was this oh empty the
baby I'm going to open this I don't how
do I make him not grow up
ever can you is that possible maybe if
you don't feed us
I'm going to starve
it but if you make it grow up maybe you
can just make more
babies make a panda farm and then when
the Ender Dragon is upon us we'll attack
him with our
pandas than you
C he
[Music]
sneezed wait is he sick is he going to
die those are
beehives hey
yo
beeh I need y y
y
donkey oh I was organizing right my bed
oh you were sorry sorry sorry keep on
organizing but I found uh I never saw
this item before we have beehive so I
guess we can get be bees if you were
done with the pandas you could try to do
something with the bees but the bee
already flew away I don't know if we
should have captured
it a
okay uh well now we know take your time
this is so fancy the quartz pillar
damn a it
nice I love quartz maybe that's my
favorite gem at least in
Minecraft qu
that's it for you this is the biggest
goall booger booger gops I want to eat
them all right oops I destroyed
something
here ooh wait we should
take
these we got a freaking Diamond D let's
go yeah
diamond diamond
diamond oh oh beehive oh beehive isn't
that
interesting yeah we should put it up
maybe it'll attract a b
yes next time when we will find a bee
that doesn't fly away immediately
okay oh oh wow I got an achievement for
that wow I'm so honored was that a
terrible Austin Powers
reference me no the a cityi place
no what did do no no I said something
and my eyes caught something in chat so
I made
fun who is Austin
Powers huh heard the name before I heard
it before I just don't really know who
it
is how would one describe that I don't
know comedy movie character Oh I thought
it was an
actor what no isn't it I should do a
watch I'm already very very busy with
watch alongs right now doing a full full
Bak monar All Seasons watch along along
currently
yeah because there's finally New Seasons
coming out like next month Y for the
first time in
years I'm so
[Music]
excited a fur I'm going to plant it oh
yeah
mhm wait the fern does it turn into
something
bigger uh bigger
Fern ah yeah okay well I guess I'll need
them I made so many pickaxes just
now find way Army I need you to
write a better like more detailed diary
today your
turn it was just one
oh was that cat cat it was just one
sentence your turn to be scolded by the
teacher
mhm wasn't there some cods in here oh
wait how much did I M
rate can I cheat I'm going to look would
they only eat raw how much did you write
one
sentence can they be
cooked probably not right
yeah who's a baby you're such a baby do
you like this too
no
okay where's the other
fish Gone Gone Gone
[Music]
Gone somehow these raw fish keep on
popping up out of nowhere I wonder where
they're coming
from and another one why you still not
like me oh yeah maybe I'm unit five or
so should you guys be ding I've been
digging and then we need to like stor
things back shouldn't you be not
fishing no the the fishing is useful
right now cuz I need the fish for the
cat we have we have mushroom soup it
hates Cod I
think eat your soup it doesn't like
C oh it's cooked damn it I didn't read
that damn
it and there's more raw salmon
oh oh I think the one you mean I already
took there only cooked salmon left in
the
chest and the cats don't eat the cooked
uh cooked one
apparently ra let's go ra
ra ra
oh oh yeah it's it's going crazy about
that
one go back to
safety look at Watson and her ass still
don't like me
okay Watson's
ass
look it's very
flat no the
donkey oh
the donkey what the heck what you called
it
ass yeah that's a nickname for a donkey
oh oh it's kind of mad at
me they're very smart but you know what
you were doing you
youing wow honey come w we don't need so
much honey
[Music]
oh I love
honey I love honey and
tea I like eating a by a spoonful oh
really also I I have realized honey
honey based
um uh dressings salad dressings are one
of the best ones like honey mustard M
honey mustard
baby good salad dressing
honey butter yes honey honey butter for
what do I hear a bee wait bee be how do
we get the Beehive away how do wait who
has a flower over there flow FL flower I
have Rose
B Rose B oh I think it's it went to the
lower
level
ah is it
there we need to be ready for the Beast
we need to already have like something
in place for them I have a hive ready
you to stop leaving maybe it's there
it's there there where go I guess this
is not the right flower oh you have a
good
flower maybe the hive should be right
where like the blocks are so it
immediately finds
it he's gone he's sinking he's going
down no put put a hive on tree like
closer to the closer to the block mining
thingy cuz they fly off
immediately
okay yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes
yes keeping oh wait and add flowers
okay this will attract him for
sure there's so many emeralds down there
oh I heard it sneeze cute
cute oh there they are
okay Dam it
oh cat is this the cat you looking for
oh which one where you at it's yellow oh
no that's a different one ah okay is
there more
fish sorry donkey Rock Let's
Go mysterious fish has appeared again
cat you shall be ours please be our
friend oopsie
oh baby come on no you still don't how
much fish does it
eat he's very hungry oh my God grass
where did all this grass come from she
oh I cast a spell my
bad bab Bob
booby yes grass is here and grass is
the in Austrian Austrian German we say d
for
dare for yeah D is grass D is grass that
is grass whoa oh thought it was diamond
block
damn yeah there
grass oh grass that's grass oh gorie ow
ow ow why do you think it's always going
after you hm oh my
god oh Mama Mia oh Mama Mia no don't
attack
no why don't why don't they go for the
one who killed their mother or their big
version your items are there although
maybe I picked up one or two seeing you
all good in the
neighborhood bless you bless Ash
boy okay I put some more things to sort
heyo why does this break you got a
boss I'll take
it in terms of
things we want to do
today a just another
reminder if someone could build I think
a stone generator is really
easy that could be
possible and M yeah any of these Farms
would be amazing but I know it's kind of
difficult so no
pressure Minecraft stone generator
I think that's one of the easiest
generators you can build just need uh
like a some
lava lava water we definitely have some
more buckets of lava stone we have a
funnel bottle of enchanting and a sadle
we got a saddle and another a music disc
and a golden carrot
shees wait do we have
a how you make a
funnel why is this Quartz in here I
guess it's
yeah see more as a building
block this goes
here where is the you have a music box
we don't have music
box it would be funny if this Minecraft
session like this uh oh what is it
called one block Minecraft if this is
the first time where I end up listening
to Minecraft
CDs o
never done it before you've never heard
Minecraft music I don't think I've ever
like listened to these CDs
before where should I put the another be
okay here wait if I build a Rock Maker
uh this one says it's for 1.16 and 1.17
that will not work on this one yeah no
that will not work I think
okay H don't
M something wow cobblestone
generator this video has 50 views let's
go oh that's why never
mind hello guys welcome back to my
YouTube channel trying to say something
me oh wait
oh
oh oh where should I put it here bless
[Music]
you are these just animal noises
you hear that
goog yeah who's playing the old fart
music
here music boxma gave us the music
box she's fishing for Treasure
good it's quite a
jam might leave it
on
nice it's like I'm playing Las Vegas and
New Vegas
guess oh yeah Amy I wanted to ask you
Amelia
Watson in your playthrough of New Vegas
which which fraction did you go
for cuz I have to decide and I don't
know who to go for I'm kind of between
the NCR and Mr
House oh oh yeah fraction let me know
what you think
typing I think N I would in my first one
M yeah I've been like trying to side
with NCR so far but I thought maybe it's
more interesting to go with Mr house
actually this is so loud can I turn it
down there we go it was yes
man oh
it's so
[Music]
loud
okay that's
[Music]
better Miss is an uncommon Choice really
I feel like it's very in like in front
of my
nose it wants me
to choose it it's calling for me no one
likes him
well he's definitely like obviously very
sus but I thought like generally his
idea is not too bad not too
bad not too bad I
think the so the am way the first out my
way was NCR maybe I should also do NCR
what happened yeah well so when I logged
in I was like attacked by all kinds of
enemies and then one zombie went into
the Villager
house and the villagers and animals were
like stuck in the boats so they couldn't
like run away run away and so the
zombie ate the
villagers while I was being attacked by
the creepers and stuff so I wish I could
have saved them but yeah thanks for the
name tag I'll I'll put it into the
special things chest for
now
oh start again or put different one
in how about this
one it's called wait
sounds like early Animal Crossing music
it's
beautiful
[Music]
wow wait if I make a stone maker I need
a lava thing we only have three lava
buckets is that that's fine we'll get
more anyway also cuz we're circling
through the
phases I think it's okay okay
M all the
donkeys save him
nah oh
obsidian that means we're at the end of
the face right
Sor I wasn't trying to do
that any dripstone yet no oh I guess we
need dripstone also for the generator
possibly depends on the version though
no it's kind of I mean just searching on
YouTube finding one that's for our
version is yeah it's pretty outdated I
guess people just make more newer ones
and then you can't find the older ones
anymore on
Google
H man Cobblestone generators work on
every
version are you sure about
that h
H oh you could give it a try with one of
the ones that you find the the
recipes maybe it
works okay it scared me with the
versions though
yeah just have a nonsource block touch a
nonsource
block lava plus water it's just lava and
water touching on the edges yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah I feel like it should
work I remember like there's one in the
server like behind ena's house remember
that one no but if you build it like
that one I think it should work it
should work material Okay lava bucket
water
bucket
M me time to hydrate
[Music]
need need two chest water is so nice man
water is not appreciated enough thanks
for the membership boo thank
you am I loud 150% volume am I loud yeah
I don't think so I mean I can't compare
you with armor because Armor's not
talking is that grass oh my God it's a
grass block
I am loud oh I'm
sorry I don't think so is she loud
now is it better I guess
so K's
Discord too low now
ah how about
that oh
no he what is
this testing ooh
ooh okay why switching the whole time
stop switching stop switching the blocks
I will speak
quietly we need a lot of chest
so e there's a I think always more and
more
chests in in the Sorting
chests that's sure
chest oh well not not anymore but wait I
have one more here and another
one can someone gooa can you replace the
CD yeah what do you want can I pick
anything ooh anything that sounds good
to
you oh uh happy
birthday maybe I can free you oh you
freed yourself smart one one donkey
that's not so stupid that it
stays in there nice oh wow
threatening this one's scary never mind
I don't like it I feel like we changed
phases cuz the blocks are so different
and I just didn't notice that we changed
phases go DJ
strad Str there we
go
o it gives me Zelda Vibes oh yeah it
does say in the chat
true maybe I missed something nah I
should have seen
it
oh oh this one's
good beauti
[Music]
oh too many
blocks too
many goba there's new stuff for you to
sort
have
fun am you still
fishing my rod broke I'm done for now
okay
cool but if you need inspiration on what
to do let me know but I think you can
come up with something yourself too
there's lots to do like mining
yeah we need stair
okay God damn it I
swear get him can they give us a warning
when enemies are
spawning that would be
nice like a heads
up my heart is very weak I've got a weak
heart hello
kid of water why
she'll build a house around the
block what nah no we don't need
that where am I putting a stone
generator lame and anywhere put it
maybe where where we have some
space Maybe here next to the quest board
diary board here that's a good spot
okay she's doing it she's going to
try gooa is going to do a smart thing
the smartest
thing she going to prove us
all off to a great
start it's going to go terribly wrong
you have no faith in me
what can go wrong with a bucket of lava
H well spit on
me
honey
Poney another chest damn inventory gets
filled up so fast
I've come for your
inventory what you looking
for your
chest I think there was one in
there I took it okay
[Music]
oh it's like a mix of everything right
now it feels like snow gravel prismarine
or whatever no that was some other
block am has made an iron pick Let's Go
no more iron now oh I still have free
iron pickaxes let me actually put them
into the tool
box
before well I haven't died today yet
even when I was alone
so I thought you did die almost almost
very close dangerous situation I found
myself in
she put the music back
[Music]
in oh thanks for the
memberships thank
you oh another name tag what are we
going to do with all these name
tags name the Ender Dragon and make him
our pet
name a pig comeon comeon
comeon
H Havier
H
okay oh oh oh what a
Bop H the bee there's a bee there's a be
oh you're right at the honeycomb nice is
this your
honeycomb am be Amy
be and a be and and a
be oh where' it Go did it go inside can
I
see you ate
no is that how am becomes
am is that just how life
goes but I guess it went in inside I
never saw that
before
cute am be is dead don't say that froggy
Wawa will be oh froggy Wawa will be so
[Music]
sad how's it going [\h__\h] ball
work let me
see
[Music]
oh this looks
good this looks like it could
work well jeez I hope so I really
do
nice nice nice nice hi hopes
fix it
iic are my stairs
backwards oh
yes
yeah is it two by one on purpose yes cuz
we don't have enough
material okay
okay wait which is the block that would
be mine this one in the middle wait
don't ask me questions I don't
know chat what do you think does this
look correct has anybody ever built this
before
Oh you doubting me I'm not done
yet I'm I'm I'm not ding this looks
really
professional this is sourc to you well
I'm not surprised gooa is a
wizard all
right we're getting so many dark blocks
now
[Music]
[Applause]
H yep oh animal was that a pig we killed
it we need to oh cat okay we need to be
careful with
the animals when we see a sheep or
so spectral
Arrow fancy all we need is a bow all we
need is a
bow upgrade
W okay 70
seconds that is nice
wait what was I going to do I was going
to oh she changed
again playing the wait CD while we're
waiting amazing
oh DJ Watson
DJ
[Music]
no DJ watching on the mic uh yeah we we
that's new
am instead of a
Tami all the spicy noodles you brought
it upon
[Music]
yourself okay I have some dirt blocks I
will extend this a little bit oh wow
desolate land wee oh phase nine okay
that means one more fa actually I guess
we got to complete two more phases hello
cat oh I found the cat again does
anybody have a diamond pickaxe or do our
are they on our players who are not
logged in he I have one can I have it
yeah put it back into the chest oh at
this very moment I see thank you
this is the cat that I originally was
trying to befriend right what what why
are you
scared who who wait why is it zooming
it's got the Zoomies don't get hurt in
the berry
bush no what what's
wrong yay finally oh I got a okay I I
will name this cat yes what do we got
these for
ah wa I have to name the name tag first
though right damn
it now we don't have an Amo yet guess
that doesn't work yet I will name it at
some
point nice happy cat we'll keep the
creepers
away a cat a day keeps the creeper
away oh but I was going to do something
else
I hear different
cut is it the other
one doesn't it sound
close ena's the only one in myth with no
pet cat I told her so many times should
get a
cat cute she should oh my God what is
these what is
this silverfish or what what's it called
kill it what's what's what are you
called silverfish yeah oh do we want
this no right cuz it's very
annoying nice
it's kind of cute though it looks like
um looks like from the front it looks
like a
hedgehog jungle
[Music]
sapling hedgehog
cute y oh well it is what it is
what kind of blocks are we getting here
stone stone
and O dirt and stone and
iron oh
oh
mhm and
Speeders I thought there would be more
like fancy materials at this point but
okay no problemm holy [\h__\h] dude why
didn't this option come up first oh an
easier version of why was I getting all
of the the gigar craft versions it's
it's a freaking hole in the ground G
brain
GA we don't have the resources for me to
try that what the heck is that bone oh
it's bone
blocks
dude I'm so sorry for the freaking
materials I wasted this is a bad thing I
think I'm going to
cry oh oh oh oh oh okay okay okay okay
where'd it go
dead dead
maybe oh no still
there that tiny little angel with a
sword it looks it looks funny what do
you want what you want to fight or
what hey oh oh no
what it's a Vex this is how a noob makes
a
a I saved her am I saved her oh you
deleted all of
it I know she's starting from scratch
okay
okay this how to just called me a noob
cuz I made obsidian whatever man
whatever dude whatever I see yeah you
poured water
over no yeah water over lava whatever
whatever NOP whatever hey at least I'm
doing it what are you doing well Mining
and stuff oh SK wait the
[Music]
skeletons uh wait oh you want apples
first
1 no
two three four wait this isn't going to
work there's nothing down
there yeah skeleton horse I know I have
a saddle but I
think I just
I gooa
hole goba made hole no saddle needed oh
shift click
oh oh
oh do I need to un
toogle at first you climb on him and
then you put it
on I'll make a raised one oh now you're
thinking empty
[Music]
hand uh
huh yeah maybe not in this version it's
not
working can't get oh can't get on can't
ride this skeleton
Pony no ride for you
no what about you
is is that yeah I I thought so I looked
at the sky but there was nothing
there a
ghost there we go there we
go I will destroy you before you destroy
us still not dead resilient
[Music]
yeah that's what I
thought your hand has to be empty to
tame it well I
mean I had empty hands but don't I need
like an apple or so I mean I don't know
how it would eat the apple as a skeleton
horse but wait do I have to make this
Stone generator out of dirt if it
touches uh Cobblestone will it turn into
obsidian
uh generally I would say
yeah but they say
no
ah any
blog
[Music]
okay oh so this should
work it's water touching the L lava
source that turns it into
obsidian wait can you Minecraft dorks
check my work please before I waste
another lava
block wait yeah I was showing them but I
can show again okay wait wait wait wait
cuz we don't have resources to burn
through here if I put this lava block
here I'm on my way I'm on my way show us
the L shut
up show me you want to put it
where here on the quartz block yeah
instead of the quartz block no no no
next to the quartz
block so that it kisses in the
middle they say
yes
okay oh yeah
who it's kind of slow but it works oh
there we go oh there we go amazing you
made
it Mark it off the list you I get a a
sticker on your homework for that I can
write about it in my diary today I built
I finally built a a thing employee of
the
day you're G your face I'm going to put
a portrait of your face on the the
wall
yeah damn she did it I can't believe she
did
it now we can't we have endless Stone to
replace like flooring and stuff like
that do anything with
it
[Music]
amazing let's
go there's this chest with like all
kinds of stones in it it's full
now gura the keeper of stone hey when
did we get the Bony
Pony I've been trying to put the saddle
on it but I don't get it you got a new
disc y bump the jams up
Waton mhm pump up the
jam Pump Up the
Jam oh oh it's for monologuing uh uh uh
an old timey detective show
kill the
rain oh nice
nice that does sound very very beautiful
Casablanca
[Music]
es how much does it want a
you h
[Music]
oh Goa have you noticed your your Panda
grew up and it still has the PN eyes and
the snot he does it does oh bless his
soul he's a little booger boy for
Life rare pool for real yeah it is I
think I remember when when pandas first
came out in the Minecraft server that we
have in Holo I think some Japanese
members they were going crazy over
getting the pen
Panda
pen it is R look come long enough to
make a panda yeah here eat more eat more
get
fatter no they're going to
explode my
children I need more
[Music]
AAA here one more yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah you like it I know you like it
yeah oh yeah good stuff good stuff okay
no more oh oh baby wait another baby ah
it's already flipping us off let's go
but no no special eyes I think show us
your face what's he doing to us flipping
us
off oh my very I mean fitting with you
know the fact that it's been made by me
it's got to be a rude one
okay it looks pretty normal yours was
yours was a better baby goba I give it
to you booger
boy Amy who you
fighting she be
fighting let's get out of this phase
we're almost back to phase one let's go
let's
go one more
face face
ah not another one of these
vexes where'd it go so
small curse you
vexi vexi hexy where are
[Music]
you did I imagine it you guys saw it
right
oh oh you didn't see it
Chad saw it right I saw it
100% oh maybe can it even show up in his
face hey yo what's with this
horse why is it
green Zombie horse there's zombie
horses a Zombie horse
what wait Chad is also impressed why
I how come I've never seen that before
Oh you nether it's been a thing for
years how does that happen does it have
to be I've never seen it is in the over
here in the corner the green
horse
e yeah they're very rare they don't
spawn naturally oh so do they have to be
made by a zombie we have to treasure
this one he's an undead first time I've
seen one okay so I'm not the only one oh
they don't spawn in vanilla wow creative
mode creative mode only oh so it's like
even if we have a horse and a zombie it
doesn't happen that easily
huh I can't catch
him chat give us give us the knowledge
of how to capture Zombie
horse yeah maybe he does like zombie
FL try
love it and compliment
it is that how you capture
auba uh
maybe that's har made the skull like me
do we have any apples for the
horse give them a care what you the
skull you were like throwing him around
yeah but then I kissed him and he he
came he came around came to the yeah
that's yeah s
okay what's I carrot carrots I guess it
also
eats oh yeah that's a sick
horse it's it's wearing a green screen
full
bodysuit yeah we need
[Music]
Anvil Anvil I think for anal we need
iron or iron iron
or was it just Stone I don't
remember 31 iron for
Anvil oo I wait we got another of the
green
horses let's let it out come on get out
of there before you hurt
yourself
damn what kind of luck is this I guess
they're just normal in this
phase to Common like the donkeys I
suppose gooda you're mining now
yeah take a step back for a
moment there you
go you think now that you've built the
generator you're free from my
control is there more you want me to do
well do you want more to
do oh I'm as okay okay okay
whatever stand there and look stupid oh
good
job expand the dirt tou okay does uh who
has the diamond
pickaxe got it mine this some oh wait I
have it here wait take this wait what
are you eating
nothing how do you
know share with the you're eating
something is it that obvious
yeah oh
no what is it is it snacks
yeah y yum y it's dark chocolate oh dark
you're I don't never a green horse
you're a dark chocolate kind of person
oh yes only only
ew damn I didn't
know it's not ew it is the best
chocolate my mom would agree with
you it's the
best I m I like milk chocolate and white
chocolate but dark chocolate is if it's
like really low on the percentage then I
guess I might still like it
yeah yeah of course she had to say
that my chocolate isn't real chocolate
it's literally not it's just sweetened
milk yeah but like they sell it in the
chocolate section and so I take it as
for milk drinkers like you I don't drink
milk oh I only eat milk chocolate but I
don't drink milk on its own oh green
horse we're going to have a whole Army
of green horses stop hurting
yourself wait Watson you only like milk
chocolate
then I don't like dark oo white
chocolate is not real
[Music]
chocolate dark chocolate is okay in
teeny tiny
[Music]
quantities okay teeny tiny I might have
gifted you girls like chocolate
before and it was probably not dark
chocolate although did I baby but I
could slam a whole bar by
[Music]
myself all right dirt
gone dirt gone I have two blocks of dirt
two whole blocks
e I'm going to try to sort a little bit
actually I think since that chest is
full I'm going to make another chest a
stone only chest cuz we don't have a
stone particular Stone
chest dark
chocolate we play the Jukebox only
because you act so nicely yeah it's so
quiet I have so many tabs open with
sound I'm a bit overwhelmed but it's
fine here comes the bride this is the
one you're going to play ready to die
this
is super
chest I got several streams open that's
right ow they don't combine
[Music]
huh okay this wait I need another
task another one well there are a few
ones on the
board oh okay maybe you can find
something that tickles your
fancy what tickles your fancy me
[Music]
lady is it in there where is it where's
the monster oh it's in the sky we need
beds God damn
it get sheep it will fly away right um
now we can fight this
one she's trying she's
trying we just got to get back to phase
like one or two or something like that
soon soon soon come down come
down come
down this thing is not good at this job
the cat is scaring it good kitty really
I didn't know cats work on these things
too
really oh damn I I thought it only works
against creepers okay now we got to
listen to those screams for a while
now until it
despawns
m water pop water pop what a pop what a
truly pop pop what a pop what a pop
the beautiful
pop pop the
[\h__\h] SK pop the
W sorting things is really difficult
when you only have one brain cell
man just got to rub them together more
see
see would it be a ways to turn all those
bone blocks into
bone
meal Chad is it I don't know put
everything in the right
box the Box on the right or the correct
box what is
that wait it's a a dead never
mind go for it wouldn't burn them all
but it's fine okay how do you rub one
brain cell together you fold it in half
a bunch of times and then uh rub it the
two halves
together you you sound like you have
experience I do ma'am yes I
do I mean you just have proven us of
your skills of rubbing brain cells
together I can never deny but can you do
like uh are you smarted than a fifth
grader stream again please like I want
to participate
which one didn't you do a are You
Smarter Than A Fifth Grader stream
before the Big Brain Game a
yeah yeah do it
again
okay yay it's that easy it's that
easy the berries the evil berries we
could play like big brain games to make
it faster wait no what's that game Big
Brain Academy big
I am did you play that no I don't think
so oh
fun I am not
knowledgeable the bra Academy is is fun
and they and they give you like a
personality chart for your smarts m i an
empty blank sheet of
paper why does this one not
grow am I wasting the bone meal
does it need more space is it a big
tree I asked for uh perms for the are
you smarter than a fifth grader games
but ah I don't think that'll ever
happen so Big Brain Academy is as close
as we're going to
[Music]
get is this not 2 by2 goba help me with
the maath nope nope no I mean what I'm
doing not what you doing nope oh you
don't want to noep oh the sapling ah so
2 by two does that mean like this
or not so easy is it
[Laughter]
huh does it have to be like like all
around it like like
[Music]
like a NY think moment that was one by
two okay well this is 2 by two then I'm
don't hurt the cats though this got to
be 2 by two what's happening oh there we
go wa W that's a fake
tree and I'm going to destroy it right
away I have learned but you know I'm not
the only one who didn't know apparently
cuz those trees were placed
incorrectly no don't kill him
CHP the stairway
up M no I can reach I think hooray which
one is
it another one
meoi
oh that's
okay repeats are fine too because if we
get attacked maybe we'll lose some
and then it's good to have
Backup
backup these chests are not
organized
yeah well I just made a a a stone only
chest so that at least that is like
separated it's on the B left wait where
over
here
ow okay what should we you know what I'm
going to put a Cobblestone chest over by
the Cobblestone cooker mhm mhm
mhm hey aren't there chests already
there
no okay
no it's so
peaceful why is it so peaceful feels
wrong oh it doesn't want to grow
what is your
problem is it these
[Music]
leaves uh it's the little cats and all
the Torches that have been placed for
sure wait where is the
uh yeah there we
go what you looking
for wood oh I have some wood do you need
the wood
no no thank you I put more wood into the
wood chest
wood wo oh he's wait waiton
horse you don't need that many horses
what are we going to do with them right
I thought he was I thought he was black
he was like cool different color and
yeah was only because he was taking
damage sadly oh that
[Music]
sucks I'm going to mine mine mine
mine
what okay wood will not be a problem
anymore I think
wood is
app yes let's go apples pick it up why
you not picking it up why is it
[Music]
bugging I want those
apples somehow this is not the first
time that something dropped here and I
couldn't pick it
up maybe it's the area server lag is
killing me man oh yeah
to be
lagging is it HED in JP I think so
yeah
okay scoozy but I I think you know the
only one who's really suffering for from
it is you seemingly it was
lagging not as bad as you yesterday yeah
that was bad
[Music]
H I'm making so much Cobblestone right
now oh I'm made 20 never mind
uh stop hissing at the
tree it's your new cat
tree
what
what take these seeds dangerous
oh the Phantom sounds like it's Hing up
the
tree D I know exactly what you're going
to tell me to do on it
boss need more I have two blocks oh no
never mind I
don't I'm going to eat
dirt I I'm
consuming just because Amy is telling
you to eat dirt doesn't mean you have to
do
it but how am I going to be a potato if
I can't consume thy soil become potato
you can't be a potato am am is the only
one who can be a
potato we are not worthy of potato
ISM all you got to do is eat
dirt
no no no no
do I have to go over there and feed you
proper
food
no I will feed you that broccoli and
that
asparagus oh I tried eating vegetables
today but I just couldn't do it not
today today was not a vegetable
DayDay was not today I just couldn't do
it like
[Music]
oh did you want to eat it just like on
its own just vegetables or with a proper
dish it was proper but I couldn't do it
not today I eat vegetables like actually
every
day and it's always in my a part of my
dinners actually I'm so healthy
wow I'm like so
healthy maybe we should where do I put
this Jacko Lantern where do I put this
on your head no it will abstract my
beautiful eyes I'll wear it I
can't oh can you even wear it somehow I
can't put it on my head I think it's
just
decoration oh that's a shame why why
it's not working or is it the
lag it's a light source oh okay nice
I'll put it
somewhere maybe
here how's the digging
going I shall provide
assistance
assistance I saw there is pink Mercy
now she will provide assistance to
OverWatch
players skeleton is sniping me while I'm
digging my my stone that's not
cool oh wait that was you no that was
yeah over there over there somebody kill
him he's sniping me
oh why is that hole
there
huh I am a dwarf and I'm digging a
hole
oh DIY DIY hole
oh oh
upgrade so people said we only have 10
phases so it better be going back to
phase one
now
yeah let's go back to the
beginning back to the start of
it yay yay oh oh there's the white cat
oh that one is
different oh oh oh 61
seconds raw fishy fish no no more raw
fishy fish raw fish ah a little bit
let's try continue feeding the
cat he
brought wah I wonder if you would like
that game which one oh man I played it
it's called Deep Rock Galactic and you I
want to play it I bought it like round
Christmas you did I did it like I was
hoping to play it with
someone holy cow it's a four player game
we could get a fourth and then we could
stack they just released a brand new the
new season is out we do it again we
do me some else yeah four Stack Rock yes
please yes
please okay we have many Lobby duby cats
let's go
[Music]
why oh yes the cat got out actually
that's good the end okay now it's Phase
10 all right get out cats you can get
out you
can come out come
out wait what kind of enemies does the
end spawn I think it uh spawns Ender and
so on no not the Ender
Dragon wor Dragon it it will not spawn
the Ender Dragon but I did look up
yesterday like how do you even get to
the end and I think end pearls yeah but
like where do you get the the portal
where do you find the Portal you can't
just like ender pearl you way into the
sky right there's no portal anywhere
here
right and then I saw in a video that the
portal just like spawns around yeah
underneath your your mining area the
block mining
area uh who had a brown cat uh I I have
did you kill it I think I killed it no
there's one over
here it's probably oh that's where he
went yeah oh c don't worry you killed no
cat it already likes me I don't think
it's new they're both sitting down for
me
[Music]
cute you cute
I wonder what breed that is maybe it's
just a normal house
[Music]
cat no cats were harmed in this room oh
yeah yeah I think the one that I F
jumped off the cliff one one I
definitely perceived I watched it as it
fell down but the other one came back I
think put a cat by the pandas okay I'll
try follow me but you don't follow me
right you just unless I have
[Music]
fish no maybe
little Maybe
[Music]
now we're getting even more blocks
man where do we put all these
blocks Stone goes
here I have an
idea I'll put one
chest here for tree St although there's
already one where that stuff is inside
but I think it's good to have it here
[Music]
yeah why is that Phantom still
there wait if we no what how dare you
hurt my cat you
bastard give me that bow drop the bow so
I can shoot the stupid Phantom my
God it's so annoying get down
here yeah yeah yeah get closer what if I
can
[Music]
I where did you come
from where did you
[Music]
go oh oh
no that's not good touch me
immedately this is this is oh no no no
no oh Mama Mia oh he
stopped what where are they are the
zombies coming from the
spawner there's no way they're all
spawning when there's so many torches
around they must come from the
I just want to go over there so the so
that the Phantom follows me and then I
can take it
[Music]
down oh oh about the cats the cats they
okay behind the house which one oh you
think there's a dark spot there I think
I
already put torches
everywhere oh yeah this place is
fun I got to pee real bad W oh y y y oh
no
[Music]
what chance of me dying ooh was not
zero the dirt area that G Built a new
one no I built off of the other one
right oh wait yeah ah over there over
there yeah cuz I extended it did I know
you like a pink oh God there's so many
[Music]
enemies P cushion goopa do something
don't run to me do
something I have a half heart
oh eat something I'm eating I'm eating
it's
slow nice dead nice
nice my ping is not I am not the one for
this oh dear okay
no you're who no I I I I my
pumy let it yumy a no no no no
no no no
no
uh-oh little help
here okay I picked up my
things how that you foul green
creature okay uh do we have some torches
left over somewhere
that area over there be behind the
bamboo is really
bad if nobody has torches I'll make
some uh I have six oh oh you have some I
okay together with good six torches
maybe oh
ow hey I'm talking
here I'm gameing
here okay don't go over there don't go
over there D go over there wow don't go
over there no the
trees Oh my days
C no I missed the donkey whoops y y y y
y come
onon wait we should go inside until
daylight yeah I need to heal oh God okay
run run run run run
but when we wake when when it's
daytime the skeletons will still be
around I
think
okay I have hidden in the
shed where are you girls over there ah
over
there
oh I'll be right back I'm going to do a
synchronized pee with fun I'll be back
with
fauna
what is fauna streaming and also went on
the toilet right now and she's watching
that on the side what
she's she's watching fa's stream
while playing Minecraft with
us oh my god oh is she playing Witcher
and that's
why damn girl she really likes The
Witcher huh she's really kind of living
vicariously through
her play
through
[Music]
damn if fauna knew that GDA is watching
while collabing here she would be happy
[Music]
Amy looks
sad it's a cute
face cute Amy face oh she went back
out Brave
Amy and it sounds
safer
uh-oh give me give me wait I can't eat
the tropical
fish let me please take
else oh I miss taking care of it I
think
[Music]
I'm no
if it says cat was blown up doesn't mean
it was a tamed
one no oh well oh actually good that we
have a bottom floor I can pick up oh was
that spider that was SPID the daylight
has to there's a bee down there uh good
I found it really funny I had to put one
and one together to understand but you
you're watching faa's stream while
yes while collabing with us I have Yoshi
music I have our stream open and I have
the Fest stream open damn is that not
like too much input in your brain you
feel not overwhelmed I need it D
exactly I need the
stimuli she you are dedicated to The
Witcher to Gerald
uh show to the green lady
[Music]
yeah but you did say you like The
Witcher like the game cuz you yeah from
what I've seen from watching yeah
yeah um dirt block so dirt block no more
I have one
oh yeah we'll we'll have to work on
fixing that tree
area is it bed it's a I already put a
few ones back the ones that survived but
there was not many
blocks holy holy
moly
what at least one cat survived okay okay
oh it comes
back it's good I'll put some torches
down just in case oh yes yes many muchos
torches muchos
torches this is like Mafia music so I
was tell joined the
game is
she
hi by I'm taking a break from homework
oh let's
go seems to be a lot of fans of that
yeah but the thing is they're not coming
down for us to kill them because of the
cats which is good I guess but at the
same time now we have to live with them
Farm the membranes like this is good
well but they don't come down far enough
for us to hit them oh no but when they
die they still drop stuff on the
platform sometimes no I haven't seen
anything they're just always
around and so loud wow we have so many
horses they they all kind of
UNL have you seen the have you seen the
green horses
they don't look very uh they're zombie
horses do they not die uh if they're
zombies no no they're super special and
apparently you can only get them in
creative mode even though this is in
creative mode but yeah say super
rare wow oh so grassy now yeah and then
yeah just before you came all of that
over there exploded
soan a big area exploded here just down
oh my goodness yeah right before you
AR a a combination of all kinds of
things
yeah it was
rough but we end yeah we're like I think
we started spawning more Enderman now
because we're in the last phase should
we start farming the ender pearl skin I
don't I think we're far from ready but
we I mean it's good to have so don't
know just put them in bools or keep them
there some
had where did it go ah I put it
somewhere else yeah we have one ender
pearl
already and I think by the end of this
phase the portal might spawn right under
our uh block our one
block yeah there's some Echo coming from
Ena I think oh can hear my sound my bant
I have my speakers
on at the blast some what's
it uh blast some Speedy music to get my
homework done
faster you're a
beach yeah you're
be know do you want me to put up a PNG
or do you want to join
the I can
okay Ina of the
[Music]
homework oh yeaha another thing we have
a uh thanks to Goa we have a cobblestone
generator
now such generator much
wow much
Rock uh let me take this away I got to
make sure join the right room ah uhoh oh
yeah it's it's the it's yeah you know it
you know the password she knows
it it's not the usual but still the
usual same as
yesterday what who is this I
cannot I cannot see are you an intruder
I can't be sure I'm intruding into the
strength cute
hoodie than you Ena the Intruder and
Wawa The Foreigner
Intruder what am I doing what am I doing
oh we have a Wither Rose
yeah what
hit should I what what should I should
should I do something I I don't know
what to do uh if you oh you could I feel
like you have the potential to build one
of the Farms or you just dig farms uh do
we have enough sheep or we we have Sheep
No we''ve been diing uh from phase seven
to phase 10 now to hopefully get back to
phase one and two I think that's when we
should get sheep again okay get dirt
yeah dirt more
dirt collect
dirt damn so much
obsidian okay I feel like I feel like we
can only get the iron farm started if we
have pets for like
the yeah food
farm so for now I guess just like
digging until we get the the phases with
the Sheep again and then we really have
to protect those sheep at all
cost yeah build a nice
little Barn that's the
word
Ena that hoodie looks so funny man it's
right I don't want to talk to people
mode
[Music]
okay now maybe I can kill the Ender
while I'm at it you want to go for
it be careful though I probably need to
make
a an
[Music]
ax yeah I can't believe we're four
people right now I didn't expect us to
be almost a full set of myth damn I was
going to take a nap then I was like ah
we need your helpa we need your
[Music]
help who keeps putting their cat on top
of the
chest well let me unit
yeah oh wait is it because I have the
all right okay yeah go somewhere else
cat you're not
welcome oh yeah and we uh we found or
made no am made a fishing rod and then
she made a pond so there's fishing
possibilities now I know you're you're
an avid Fisher youa so o I do love me
fish don't take the cat flly don't set
the cat flly no no help somebody kill
that thing please no
oh uhoh BL on the tree let me go oh God
my cat good why are you flying
too no no no no no no no no no I land in
the water land in the water land land in
the water land in the water no is Just
Fishing is Just Fishing what is it's the
from the end ah sorry it's from the end
have you never been oh I Mo I just Sher
oh God I need where did it
go um yeah wait it's still around
somewhere yeah where did that thing
go dead no it it teleported somewhere I
can't find it I hear it always sounds
mad it's always
mad in there where is it
hm well that was
fun maybe from here little bit
spice ah maybe it's under in the bottom
FL oh it's up in the basement yeah
that's also a thing oh it's down here
yeah oh it can't send me flying here can
it are you going to kill it I'll try
yeah I don't really have weapons oh okay
I might die I might die don't die
there it
is oh ped
again wake
up okay get the sh thing no
no that would have been so
good how do we get up make sure we have
enough torches to put down yeah yeah
wherever you extend stand make sure we
have
torches how do we how do I get out of
the basement just swim up the water with
space Oh any of the one um no the one
wait I'm coming this one ah that one
okay Ina of the
water
dony a should we have caught it in a
rail car what would have what would that
have done for us
you that I've been better I don't
know how about making some stairs no no
no no no no we like
these
oh rail
cart I'm rail return I like the sound of
that it should be easy to make stairs I
know but
I like the water we need a shower every
every now and
then we'll take
it I need a shower actually
IRL you guys ever like not want to
shower cuz water the sound of getting
wet just feels so unappealing M no
that's not it but I I get the feeling of
not wanting to
shower
oh no really nobody nobody you know
no I like the sound of water yeah but
rather than getting like wet in
particular I I wouldn't like uh getting
my hair wet all the time cuz it's
annoying to get it
dry what is like I think what is this is
not the Hedgehog what is this I think
like that only applies if two swimming
pools and not showers cuz swimming pools
are a little annoying
but like when you get wet then you have
to get out and then you're going to be
damp and
cold yes not after a
shower yeah you get I'm warm
after this
sounds goba showers after after I swim
in the swimming pool I agree cuz it's
very cold and Soggy and then you smell
like chlorine and it's gross but enchant
the B but it has zero HP no oh if we
make a if we can make a Whatchamacallit
uh Anvil can probably fix it I have like
a I have a bow we
need IR or so for wait you guys don't
air dry
after no but which part hair or the
body the body I don't dare dry hair
something
sometimes what was that what was that
end end sorry I'm so sorry I didn't is
it going to be mad I didn't want to oh
god oh oh oh oh oh what's happening with
it see
see wa what's what's happening with this
one
guys Zeus
cowardly the first one
we don't have any copper do we no
there's no copper in this version uh oh
yeah it's not that yet okay hope nothing
sets on fire get zaed first you or me oh
that already happened Ena you missed a
good moment GAA was like
de what were you saying I said the first
one to get zap by lightning is a big
stinky toenail and then watch some good
zap by lightning immediately after she
said
it that was so good
I have to go in five minutes oh yeah
right you
[Music]
haveu what you going to
sing I have a couple ideas but that's it
you know I want to do like a vocaloid
kind collab stream with you one day cuz
I feel like you know a lot of the old
ones yeah like
me I always love your
choices is hard to sing though no no
it's fun chill no although it's true
like some some of the vocal producers
just because they're not working with a
human they really go all out in like
Speedy lyrics and high
lyrics yeah they don't think about
little crazy yeah they're rain
it's zoom in it does not like the
Wayne I can never
understand classic Vocaloid yeah The
Disappearance of
hat the
goose okay let me put some things on W a
goose I'm a goose no no no the song a
Goose Mother
Goose goose song oh No Mother Goose ah
yes
ah yes oh
diamond
diamond diamond diamond ooh Diamond
obsidian oh wait
I'll just push push her down she she
we're missing a
panda over they kill my boy no way
turn
around okay
good oh oh it came down now would have
been a good time to hit
it what the Phantom came down for a
[Music]
moment oh I love the sound of bamboo in
this
game
yes yes yes yes
all right we're going to make another
snot panda
m you think you can get the gacha gods
to bless you
again make a baby make a baby do it do
it where should I put the obsidian w w
w I'll put it wait didn't I put it
somewhere
else oh
here yum yum yum yum yum
is that a new
cat think that's a new cat which one we
don't have so much raw fish sadly maybe
you'll go fishing or I'mma maybe she got
some more she's been
fishing oh Thunder it scares me
[Music]
yeah maybe the hoodie can protect you
from the Thunder
I so oh oh oh
end do
it dragon's breath wait what was oh what
does that do need
a oh you can make like you can make
different stuff with it like some of
like
uh I know I can make some different
potions and arrows and stuff like that
but get
bottle of
enchant
yeah Panda
yeah yes T what's with you hi booger
Baby
Bo is that a rare
Panda it it do be rare yeah look it now
there's
two need to blow the nose
Jesus too can't believe their snar is
green and
CH hi booger
baby I feel like we're almost at the end
of the
SP the end yeah the end of the
end where where do these lies normally
spawn I've never seen them before in the
end aren aren't they like the end end
endermite whatever they're
called I've never seen
them they're pretty rare in the actual
World Ender
might when you eat CH
fruit
ow Spa rarely when you ah they rarely
spawn when you throw an ender
pearl that must
be remember cuz like I was looking at
guys to make like the end
exp farm and they're like you need an
Ender Mite and stuff like
that wait are they useful for
anything
uh don't think they're
entirely useful they just
exist but do we need a purpose to exist
no why is our mushroom cow brown did
I suck all his soup out
oh maybe it needs to did it evolve oh no
there is that type of uh mushroom cow
too I think well he
was I think it evolved I can't drink his
soup anymore yeah I thought this was
normal oh wait I'm full never
mind he got hit by lightning wow no
way now he's cooked
mushrooms that's pretty cool you got
zeed get zeed get Zeus
nerd so close I Feel It In My
Bones test I'm talk hello hello let's go
I'm floting she
speaks ow no The Phantom after
me oh fight
me like wait what if we used the the
Sher to fight off the
Phantom can they do
that no like like we can
fly yeah and then we have
a but I don't I think we need to have
rails to put it down like I can't just
put it
down
[Music]
Fally right chat right chat chat knows
bad right right right right
right where' the Shel
go I think bottom floor again again M I
saw it disappear
[Applause]
okay a there it is s makes is
good where they go is it up there
again yes it is oh no it's okay it's
dead now okay didn't drop anything cool
nope oh the the yeah our animals are
flying fall
damage
chaos go k and announcement in 30
minutes well the announcement probably
not in 30 minutes but
no my formula how do you
know is it 1 hour in is it 1 hour no how
do you know the secret formula who's the
time traveler
now it's the Hol life formula oh again I
will keep you for 1
hour why does this one make me dig
down oh I ran away again okay I got to
go
okay thank you so much for
your yes hello goodbye goodbye good luck
with your
stream I'll probably end it soon
anyway
byebye
bye There She Goes eventually you're
already water here right right guys
guys
no no [\h__\h]
ball maybe [\h__\h] B you can just stay in
the live Tod room oh is she already out
of the voice chat she can just stay in
the in the
room I wouldn't
mind bless us with her cute
face oh she knows she knows what she's
doing
no she's gone
no
no yeah it's fine it's
[Music]
fine damn so it's been 3 and a half
hours we got stuff done right yeah I
mean I think I'll at least go another
half an hour I don't know I don't know
all maybe if we just get to the the next
um yeah we got to get the Sheep at least
otherwise rip
rip rip we got to get to
that what is oh that another one of
those guys yeah all right fight me okay
to the water fight you at the water
Phantom oh he can't hit me right
here I shouldn't go here this is a
different chest all I have is a iron
pickaxe oh you need oh oh I went R let
me check downstairs he got scared
coward up there I can't hit you
there well can I maybe I
can another
one don't tell me it just
dropped what did that look like Chad
what did that look like did it drop we
killed him y we got a Sher shell sh
shell was there another one cuz I killed
one downstairs and it also dropped the
something don't I only got one okay cool
cool cool cool how many did you need two
for a box oh another one okay let's kill
this one I'm floating
[Music]
bye-bye I found the cheese spot oh he
teleported they sneeze
yeah he's so cute
God damn it so much stuff C
doco wait wonder if someone flies away
if you could catch them with a fishing
rod i' that must be tried for
science
okay o a new
disc playing music what do the ne roses
do again
uh okay look
gu they did damage I think if you go
near it
though they hurt flying donkey that
that's seems like something that would
happen in a Shrek
movie oh yeah it did didn't it it wait
are you flying are you flying horse is
flying I'm near the water though I got
you it works it
works it's okay okay give me give me
give me give me give me I have a balloon
I yeah I never eat a balloon
takoi let's
go does it even stop you from like
floating away really or no uh I don't
think so it keeps going unless you pull
me in I guess oh
okay
next M catch me I'll cat you
balloon W oh this is the happiest moment
of my
life I Sav you okay
yay oh my God she caught me ah so
romantic I'mma catch
me oh my fishing rod broke no no fishing
rod you're too heavy that was not worth
it I'll make it
okay we need need them
fish come on oh Another
one not
again I'm moving
around Amma is practicing her aim no oh
oh yby oh yby Health very yubby health
yubby oh no oh no oh no oh no a oh
another Shel
tether me to the
ground oh oh come here come here damn
that leash extends
jeez not a leash yeah I
guess close enough some people use it as
a leash I feel
like got the fish on the leash
e another
[Music]
one nice
save stop using your teleportation
skills it's too
[Music]
open oh so peaceful oh the Phantom's so
close come just
well this is actually makes sense
now
food okay
come on give me some sheep come on did
we get to the next upgrade place not yet
not yet but working on it I smell
it it's a lot of blocks sweet Ender
[Music]
charm I just noticed Ena yeah she's here
hi
here for a short bit taking a break from
homework
land she's
blending in or she's blending out
actually
bone I need to do that Ina is in Ina
Cognito
yeah incognito
get out of
here
no looks like a little croissant like a
purple croissant purple
Quant
aant you guys know I made I made JMA um
freeze quasons for me because there's
like in my favorite Bakery in Japan Sanu
St Mark um they have like always they
always have limited time quasons there
and the current one I really wanted to
eat it but it ends before I get to Japan
again and so I told jenma to go grab it
and put it in her
freezer and then there was something
else that I wanted some time limited ice
cream from bask and Robins so I want to
get that too cuz it also ends before I
get to Japan now she has two different
things in her freezer for me
freezer burn No No E no no no cuz the
the quasa will just bake it in the oven
[Music]
again and the ice the ice belongs into
the freezer anyway yeah Baskin Robins
they have a kit cat
collaboration cat
OHS yeah
Kito did it go down let me check
of course it went down oh wait no oh
there I hear it all this St there's like
an infestation of them here oh they're
like terites we got to get rid of them
before they take down the entire
building this is a good Gap here say oh
no oh
no wait I have the course for I have the
course for
oh no please leave me alone leave me
alone I need to get back up oh was
that how do I get back
up maybe here oh
oh good that's that's safe
dangerous I'm
back I'm
back oh yeah Sher
shell yay oh I made I made a Sher box
well we can make
several ah there's a mine cart you know
what it's purple so I'll put purple
stuff in there
go oh
oh thank
you oh maybe I'll make my own yeah yeah
yeah I think I know how it
works W remembers
Callie's going to have a blast cleaning
this
up but I'm trying I'm
[Music]
trying stone
bottle oh another Sher
shell girl is a
M oh whoops I don't even know where that
came
[Music]
from she will enjoy it okay then I don't
feel so
bad nice fruit safe yeah for real those
are precious but I think now we don't
have
[Music]
anymore m
M cool stuff cool
stuff this is so many blocks oh my God
we've been mining forever we're almost
there yes BBE yes yes we are
wait n Another River Rose
beautiful we're going to put it on the
grave of the Ender
Dragon what what happens
oh
what does she look like ran away
coward does do Enderman always look like
this like with a
pattern pattern he has a
pattern is
that I think so probably just never
noticed before yeah it didn't
there's another one in here no
way no way I never noticed that the one
inside looked normal to me yeah this one
oh no never mind never mind oh I've
never
noticed okay uh let see how was the last
time you went to the eye doctor
uh I think the last time my eyesight got
checked is when I um
um did the health test for my lft H
cabin attendant
audition he has a random crazy
lore I was before h i I told the story
before but before H I was supposed to
work for
Lanza as a cabin
attendant I made the audition they were
going to take me but I failed the health
test
you but it it's kind of like uh I I
shouldn't have failed it there was no
reason for me to fail
it but yeah they checked my eyesight
there but my eyesight was
fine my eyes were
good not color BL but also I I think I
need to you know defend um
maybe you know cuz we were talking about
it yesterday and she was trying to
defend herself I will try to defend
herself her
too maybe her
monitor uh color settings are just
really off oh maybe does she have a a
gaming monitor maybe maybe something
like
that uh so yeah sorry
n oh now she's going to be remembered
just for
that oh no not the
mean to live them years later like yeah
oh the color blind yeah we all have
something like that we all have
something like that don't we
all it's like for me for the longest
time it was being bottom
left Yoo it's so dark oh wait look at
that yeah
now we have the portal there wait oh my
God how many 1 2 3 4 5 there's only this
is pretty good there's 1 2 3 four only
four ender pearls
missing okay we got some Blaze R and
stuff or enough yeah oh oh also we
should probably get rid of the
infestation down below yeah I that the
one that's left over is like really far
from going to die like the platform
ah shoot no
I'm oh hi oh nice you picked up the
items that bothered me this whole
time oh my XP I was like 25
no we need Arrow W stuck wow we're stuck
please teleport me shulker
chn please teleport to me
yay come on come on come on
okay oh is this Amy stuff this looks
like Amy stuff in the vision B yeah yeah
I don't have space for
it
[Music]
NE I want to go oh I keep floing is it
you need help down there it's the one
that's like really far out
yeah
could oh parrying that's like next
level ena's on the next level I'm
getting hit from
like okay okay I'm out almost died
you're out but it's not dead is it out
no it's like way too far out ah
man get your dang cat off of here
what your cat oh sorry always it keeps
on going back there I don't know what it
is I I even put a block for like to sit
on but it doesn't want
to just wants to get in the way like a
real
cat Okay so if we get rid of this chest
then perhaps we will go back to phase
one for now I guess yeah we'll just
build the uh back around so we filled a
hole and when we need is there a portal
under there well we need four only four
ender pearls to activate it but yeah
there's a portal yeah I I have one I
think we have enough in total yeah we
can just we just keep it for now you
know yeah look how convenient that
there's a Enderman here m
oh oh No Mercy Enderman in the boat Ena
the
goat no ender pearl
darn it's okay we have so much
time if this will be
what I will be happy about it bye
oh oh it dropped the Pearl I got another
one M let's
go put it in the precious
chest oh good I thought Ena would be the
cat collector but so far it's
me I would collect it but I have no
fish I have a fishing
rod didn't it broke you made a new one
she made a new one let's go
oh yeah we should start putting things
in
here
okay oh thr off it shackles and pulsates
with energy you have reached the after
phase what do you mean what's that mean
we're going back to phase one
right we're we're we're mining something
maybe the after phace is like everything
com
probably combined cuz the one one you
link Kara was a different
versiones okay that looks very combined
Goa
mhm cuz I got a head loock and an
endstone I don't think those were
together no let's there a flower
pot can totally decorate this this place
right yeah if you want to go for it
pretty there's a single flower on there
now o be seed I wonder if we should make
a bigger Farm area yeah I tried that and
then it blew up oh it blew but you can
try again I guess we have more dirt now
yeah both um food like a plant farm and
Animal Farm both very very valid choices
I mean I wonder if we can just make a
dedicated monster spawning area like
just like have a branch out and there's
like a platform where it's not late and
then we can can use that as like a
monster M material farm with like get
lots of bone meal from there and like
string I'm losing my voice oh my
goodness spawner oh yeah PPP or TT would
be good but I single platform cuz
they're it's going to burn like when the
Sun rises right
so M so get a lot of like bone and stuff
for more food
mhm heck
yeah all right this is more
stone m
M I need more torches I have 64
actually go go
okay my inventory is a mess cuz it's
every block
now oh yeah we need our residence
order tomorrow I think she'll be
around I I yeah
more dirt blocks
please uh I put one in the
chest let's wait a little bit until we
have
more and I shall make an an axe
[Music]
again ah I can't believe it's so hard to
get sheep again once you lose them you
never know until it's well I'm sure
we'll get one I bet we'll get one it's
still going to spawn random stuff
right uh yeah I think
so so far I didn't see any animals
[Music]
though maybe it's over we lost our CH no
it can't be what is
this ah dirt block okay who whoa whoa w
w
difficult oh yeah we could put a mine
cart with a hopper under the block so it
collects the blocks and put it in a
chest by putting another Hopper under
the M mine cart yeah for any
like blocks oh hello me a slime
okay
true yeah I maybe it's
good I need to turn down the freaking
hostile creatures to
zero think I've been listening to that
for like 2 hours or
so
no what's if all these blocks damn
damn yeah um this phase it might be
smart to put a chest down there to pick
the things up we do have a lot of chest
I I can make I think I can make a rail o
I'm the railways is
real that is so
nostalgic I'm going to
cry I love when like you made the
extension for the for the original
railway and I was staying on it and then
it started going like beyond the station
I was like wait a minute get me off
[Laughter]
oh it's nice
[Music]
though maybe this can go here
busy bees aren't we some busy
bees such busy
bees okay the cats are pretty annoying
too to be honest all the
hissing cats are never annoying W well
my cat's IRL don't
his it's just the hissing that's kind of
annoying in the game if they were
meowing I'd be happy meow it's because
there's so many there too many monsters
right that's why they're hissing me it's
just a phantom up there is there stuff
underneath underneath what under the
platform no currently there shouldn't be
anything there's a Sher box still oh oh
that one okay yeah kind of far I will
should I risk it for the
biscuit maybe maybe maybe although would
be better with fruit no actually
no I just need to build a path
there I'm going to get the biscuit time
to make a bow can we make a
bow uh we have a bow we have a bow oh my
God what we do yeah yeah and Seven
Arrows I think we can make more though
cuz we actually got full of this
time he where's the
bow oh the bows in the the cat chest
that's
blocking okay oh
wow okay I'm going to try my hand at
this
now uh oh oh that's uh oh 22
[Music]
arrows it shouldn't be too difficult if
I have an
arrow and a
bow okay just got to stay here ah easy
all right nice
y wait so uh how do I do this again I
put a something in a thingy in the chest
and then I put a chest underneath or uh
put thingy in the you're asking the chat
right not me or not
Ena maybe Ena knows I don't know
huh do do you know how this works when
you want to put like a a chest under
something to collect things
automatically
like a hopper uh I think you put the
hopper and then you
put the box
underneath it's been a while
H you put a hopper and a chest onne yep
chest says the
same box under hopper Hopper directly on
top of
chest chest Hopper rail Hopper mine cart
in that order
not pointy uh okay you can do it am if
good I was capable of building something
like that today you can too uh there's a
Shuler right beside the water
entrance you you can get him okay I'm
stuck on the ceiling love me down
okay oh I dropped the shulker sh but
fell no
unfortunate we'll get
more okay well then um that's
[Music]
good it's almost like the the Phantom
isn't here anymore I can just ignore its
existence
ah so
relaxing the sound of nothing oh reminds
me music on
Music why does always go
here incredible cat if I break the End
Portal can I put it
back uh I mean it's not even on now so
it should be Oh you mean which
part like that I need to get in there
can you even get rid of
that I don't think you can mind that all
right well I guess I'll
just yeah
[Music]
okay I'm going to head out for
today but thanks for uh showing up Ina
if that was really you I can't be sure
no that was my doble
G okay bye-bye
[Music]
byebye see you maybe tomorrow
maybe tomorrow
tomorrow okay only am and me left but
we're going to try to be a little bit
more productive and
make this
oh make it
work I think the power rail came back up
to me that's so
weird uh stop grabbing
them and like lands on top of the the
farming
block oh oh now it's there for
you oh no no it keeps on coming up to
me okay
H stuck
stuck I don't want the power
rails
Works uh yeah but that doesn't go
anywhere I got to put something
underneath it I
think underneath the
rail I don't know you don't know you're
the rail construction
boss I I believed in you I put all my
bets on you we probably don't even need
it to be a rail carart to be honest
right probably not
no
well oh you'll get a chest in the
middle that's not going to doesn't it
need to be inserted into the chest
though with like
a I don't
know I've made this kind of thing once I
think for my chickens like three and a
half years ago but I didn't I don't even
think I did it right hey yo what the
hell random a chest in the middle maybe
that'll poppet and check is good enough
whoa whoa whoa whoa what the hell pu
fish
stop fuku fuku
Chan [\h__\h] you
can I get
a [\h__\h] you from
am oh oh hello
hello I'm going to be like hey I'm
building here stop closing the
path okay let's see if it
works um but for now I think I'm still
picking up the items am
I yeah you stand back a little bit but
my inventory is full now so maybe now
things will fall
in is it falling the block stops it from
going in I yeah it's on top of
it yeah it starts falling down but it
goes back up because it spawns so
fast what do we do damn it I think the
mo plac
um a piston push the blocks
piston oh yeah does that oh interesting
interesting
thought but then it would be a constant
like or is the hopper full now no right
no nothing in there
no man I keep trying to tell him okay
I'm looking at the chat what is it P
Water they said I I don't think water
will do anything if we put put like a
block of water onp poer cart needs to be
directly under spaw a
block is it not here look at look at it
from here so that they can see
it ah it needs to connect to the block
am it's connected disconnected yeah
damn
done question mark question mark I'll
get a bucket of water just to test yeah
wa oh it went some it went it it went
somewhere but not to the
chest wait
uh oh wait did it get rid of your rails
oh it did an idea the water got your
rails oh that's okay can pick them
up full inventory
to I'll try something else
see
Sorita where I
put
here oh looking good
oh oh
interesting
science Minecraft
science
[Music]
yeah the
way uh now if I put a
hopper sideways maybe it should col it
from the water hopefully place a hopper
cart on top of the rail with a hopper
under it says
somebody I'm going to do it my way yes
my own
thing the am way is the only
way you should know by
[Music]
now hold that
to put this a little bit
further bre why would the
baker puffer fish it's not edible why do
we have it in the in the food chest if
it's not
edible questions over
questions oh let me move this
away I'm getting tired why am I so
tired sleepy
baby did you say sleepy
baby
yeah yeah two but I stayed up like super
late and I woke up super
[Music]
late but I had some cool dreams and for
once I was able to use my magic in my
dreams when I needed it yes like a wand
no not not a wand I was like fire and
then the person was set on fire whoa
yeah cuz they were they were threatening
me maybe that was like another universe
and then you killed them
M and another person is actually maybe
because I because it happened in
Minecraft that I was dreaming of this
but I I uh let someone like float and
blow up like I guess I was thinking of
the expendi of
gura and the person in my dream was like
floating and and and blowing up and then
exploded and you know that was fun oh my
God
what is your subconscious trying to tell
us H that expendi is real and we should
not ignore it because that's sad we
should J about it it's serious yeah it's
serious so we have to educate people
about the the the things that comes with
it it's real it's a real
problem I actually don't know here try
this if gooda called it expendi but I
don't remember the real word well I'm
coming I'm coming I'm coming you doesn't
work no man maybe CU oh maybe cuz I'm
going straight down maybe if it came
from a different block oh wow this is
looking
[Music]
sciency
H hold on hold on I'm improving hold on
[Music]
mhm i pen the sidus
what a
Amy oh the
lag think that was my whole PC
lagging
oh cool stuff then cool
[Music]
stuff oops
what is it with these cats HH sit down
there stay
there I love you D I love you sorry for
sounding
aggressive messed up you messed up it's
okay all all
mistakes are a learning experience and
will lead eventually to
success okay without failure there is no
success after
all well wise # philosophical
Phoenix a hashtag that has been unused
for a long
time I need to be more
philosophical if you need some rails I
still have them I I used to use that a
few times yeah if you need rails let me
know I'm safekeeping them
okay h m is it
working
no
um come on am use your brain use your
brain cells all right I'm going to put
the water block uh maybe it's just not
possible I don't know I'm I will make it
possible just need more blocks mhm like
a little uh Contraption I'll make it
look nice you'll get one block because
this is one block
Minecraft no more than
one flag them in my FR let's go
they don't know that this mod forces the
drops to the
[Music]
spawn it might be like that
yeah but do we want to say that to Amy
and and destroy the moment she's
having what is it um apparently the mod
forces the blocks to always go back to
but that's not necessarily true because
one when you the one time when you
poured the water I saw the things go
quite far away from where they were
originally and they didn't go back to
the
block
so I mean if we can defy gravity like
that one way or another maybe we can
make it
work but the Redstone rail went back up
oh when you were dropping the rail and
it teleported to the block a yeah that
isn't that different because the rail
didn't even Spawn from the Block isn't
that
different just
um why is she using water just a hopper
cart and it will be fine
because I think because we want to move
it where would you put the hopper cot
Hopper cot Hopper C working oh it's
working it's
working no way I just need to fix these
blocks to make them look nicer cuz
they're kind of in the way they never
doubt that
way oh
no no
way no way okay now check it I'll check
it out okay uh it was was it this block
let me fix these got to get rid of this
oh yeah it looks like it's going in
there but that means we always have
[Music]
to can you make it a double chest
somehow uh yeah you probably need to
combine it with another Super chest
there's there's one here I think this is
there one there yeah I think this is a
super chest yeah it is I picked one
specifically oh
okay oh CH oh we got to put the Torches
back cuz I took some
mm yeah I'll I'll I'll put
[Music]
them oh I'll fix this up I think I think
it's working
though yeah it's going in okay but that
it seems like to like prioritize going
into the chest rather than to our
inventory
so we'll have to like empty it regularly
huh yeah but that I mean that's fine
right I can't open can you access it no
it's cuz I put a block on top of it
water
okay
not done it again hold on I'm going to
make it look nice though cuz it looks
crazy yeah it's again
Patchwork yeah yeah yeah maybe use some
of the purple blocks or so I'm just
going to put more signs to make it yeah
I I'll uh purple blocks into the purple
sheler if you're looking for
some materials that are the same
color okay
yeah nice
H and out of these things we didn't make
much but we can do this tomorrow too we
built the basement and we made a stone
generator and this wasn't on it but we
made something fancy here
so
yeah yay stone
stone [\h__\h] bar
creation you can expand the basement
more
yeah a little bit perhaps
I think these can be turned into slabs
[Music]
so but like how long does the waa want
to go you
know we already
had several
visitations so I feel like it's not
going to not much is going to happen I
think
from now on
onwards what do you mean I don't know
feel like the most of the progress has
been made for today unless I'm I don't
know do you want to play
longer uh no I'm just going to fix this
up and then I don't cuz I don't want to
leave you alone you
[Music]
know okay we'll fix that well you you
finish that and we we can like
find a good way to end
[Music]
it
okay making a
mess where's all this water coming from
okay
MH you followed me even though you're
sitting you're sitting I told you to sit
how are you moving huh kitty
cat oh you teleported to me didn't
you she loves me I love cats I love
cats
oh a few more
Amma do you think you can build a t TT
kind of thing
eventually
uh sure I mean do we really need it
[Music]
though I mean if you want to end up
enchanting some things and uh maybe
otherwise I guess
not but if anyone is capable of making
it it's you
Amy and you know how much I love tit you
know yeah maybe I'll do it properly this
time no uh wait I said t i mean PPP I
love T
PPP
oh my my PPP yeah your PPP is the best
thing I've ever seen the best
construction I've ever seen the most
beautiful the most Soulful the most
elegant and the most helpful to me
personally so if I get another chance at
seeing a PPP too wow sequel to
PPP I'm going to
cry uh uh I'll make it better yeah okay
okay you could yeah I think we already
said we can build it at the end of the
path that you built the armit path
yeah uh
yeah if you can ever get past that
creeper I can shoot him
actually let's shoot him and then I'll
put some more torches there even though
that area is currently
unused there he
goes nice dang
it no I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry y y
[Music]
y bring him over here oh that was so
clutch that was so clutch just
now holy
moly I literally touched him he could
have blown up Atlantis it would have
been my
fault
damn okay didn't see them here bro
okay that makes sense that makes sense
that you're here
uh I'll take you down now I'll take you
down it's over cats cannot protect me
anymore oh nice shot whoa hey come
here far very far all right come check
out the new system it's uh
it's not perfect mm but uh you know it's
it's it's uh it's something okay
actually maybe I can use a trapo here
instead of
this this this one block I don't like
this one block yeah cup
test yeah I mean it looks a bit
confusing
but is the arrow supposed to show where
the block is yeah I think maybe if I put
dye I don't wait how do you do uh I
guess the glow apply dye to it hold on I
have I have dye oh
oh maybe I shouldn't have thrown away
that one di that I had oh you can't
really see
it I don't know how there's a way to
like put an outline on it
yeah maybe it's like in like one of
those ink sacks or so the the ones
aren't those
glowy oh yeah I don't think we have one
hold on maybe I'll put a glowstone block
on the
floor as the floor not in this version
oh yeah that might have been a new
version thing that it glows with
dye oh I think I'm out of
arrows okay yeah nice oh ah it did
become pink
yeah H it's a little bit less visible
than before now
yeah yeah I me look there's a red there
that's like oh this is where I said
perfect maybe if put a a lantern hold on
I think I can make a lantern really
quick
oo what yeah then I hope if animals
spawn they won't drown
right oh I mean not right away I got to
test that there I hope an animal animal
shows up got some light got like a up
there m M cuz I feel like that might get
them stuck even more if it's an animal
that we
want let's wait and see how the water
makes them I haven't I mean we haven't
seen any animals spawn so they don't
even spawn what the
hell wait for it oh okay there's a a
wizard and he got
oh you got moved by the water
got him
yeah uh uh oh ah stop burning
me okay I'm going to die uh oh oh so
close with half a
heart uh uh I'm Legit hungry uh what do
I
eat we need more food oh bread
okay so enemies still spawn so I would I
would hope what why am I right I'm going
to change the purple blocks other block
oh it can't kill me the poison can't
kill me
okay I think we can spawn
animals
yeah
oh water
do what' you do to my water I didn't do
anything where'd it go I just mined my
own
[Music]
business but good question where did it
go I Contraption I thought you removed
it to fix
something oh okay I can put it back I
just uh just replacing some of the
blocks anyways make it look nicer H the
spae oh because a sponge blob SpongeBob
SpongeBob sponge Spong
spawns that's funny so whenever
SpongeBob spawns we need to put the
water
back that probably won't happen that
often right yeah I mean there's many
blocks so the possibility is low is that
obsidian oh okay all right water's going
to come out right now I
think there's water
already there my more
got to move the water further up maybe
start the water
higher could that fix the
SP all right hold on Min
maxing
wao oh I think the chest is full no it's
not why did the things end up over here
maybe wait
nice nice nice nice nice
nice yeah now I should empty it just
want to pick everything up I just be
like one person's
job
yeah yeah we don't have to do it like
this we could just remove it
no no no it's fine like this you went
out of your way to build it and I think
it's helpful we just got to keep on
checking the
chest okay congratulation am you are so
back in business it's like you never
left construction
work I was made for
this it was made for you this business
was made for you
you all right uh yeah it is a little
confusing but uh could tell what it is
right yeah I might just have
to I'll take a screenshot and I put it
I'll send it into the Discord
fored both Ena and GAA didn't write
their
Diaries I think this will not be the
trend that I wanted it to be
H oh Trader
hello oh I have like it feels like I
have this huge chunk of fum in my
pho
fum
FL gross yeah but I can't get it
out it's just
occupying
everything yikes oh my God this chest
[Music]
you you're still working on it or uh
just cleaning it
up me too me
too yeah I think Callie will do a
relatively early stream tomorrow earlier
than this one so she'll have so much
time to
sort yeah the
OCD will hit harder than
ever all these blocks are so pretty
wow I want you think it still looks
[Music]
confusing let me let me Let me refresh
my eyes you know you stand right by the
red block and then you
yeah yeah I
think I think they might mistake this
one stone block here for it at
[Music]
first but I think then after that no no
once they mine that and realize it's
wrong they should get to the solution
maybe I should make it like a glow stone
or something M maybe I'll make another
red block that way oh yeah yeah yeah if
you make that one also red block
yeah yeah now it
looks oh purposefully put
there you know what shaders just
probably looks so pretty the water
Reflections and like the Lantern and it
already looks so pretty because you are
standing right there ah hey a mer mhm he
doesn't have anything interesting there
flowers flower okay
okay nice work I'll
um Place some blocks
here okay oh wait I got a lead for free
what the hell
why let me put it in here yeah good job
M thanks for showing up m yum yum
tomorrow I'll stream again guys I'll
stream M Minecraft
gun oh but the one with cie I'll
probably not have a slot up so check out
Callie's stream
yeah
and
very productive even though we didn't
get this very far but we're getting
there we already got the portal so we
could go anytime now so we just have to
prepare to fight and then that's it um I
guess so but the interesting thing I
thought I was
informed that before the end of portal
spawns you'll get like a like a portal
to the no I guess you have to make your
own nether
portal yeah I thought it spawns uh for
some reason but so before we go to the
end maybe tomorrow or so we might want
to go to the never I'm not really sure
what would what we would be looking for
already okay now what would we what what
do we need from the never anyway oh is
it just the
experience
uh I don't know never
right oh no I'm not going to go for
never right during one block no no no
never right that's a bit overkilled
baby
especially with chances of us just
randomly falling off or dying somewhere
imagine losing your never right armor
I'm going to
cry but we should go there anyway
whatever it doesn't matter if we don't
need anything just for the
experience
okay so if you're around am tomorrow
we need your power you your your
knowledge your
skill gamer skill of Amilia Watson
shouldn't we all be there though or yeah
I don't know if I'll write a message and
see if everybody can be there otherwise
I think we can stall one more day or so
for sure with like getting sheep and
stuff and make the never the day after
tomorrow oh okay I should be fine and is
this water going to stay there no I'm
going to fix it I'm just trying to get
up
there
okay get some food iron yeah food we
don't even we don't even have full iron
armor yet
so and I already put get diamond armor
on the board that is not realistic it
seems
um and yeah food is surprisingly scars
uh I mean we have this stuff but this is
difficult because the pumpkins you have
to make into soup at least the
Watermelons you can just Farm like
[Music]
this but yeah we should actively mine
these as well because we're running out
of
food oh oh there's be fruits beetroots
beetroots is it ready to eat I can't
tell oh
yes yeah bigger field would be nice here
bigger field do we have the the hole
somewhere oh my God okay I will stop
placing torches until you log off and
then I will place torches because then I
know then I know
[Music]
okay Amilia floods
in I'll try to fix this she's
swiming wait I hope our bees are okay
are they in there these can survive in
water for a little bit maybe m
oh they're
bonding all right I'll I'll stop messing
with the
water okay
[Music]
torches there you go all right
nice then maybe it's time for
us to say goodbye
time to exactly oh my God can you speak
German you never told me that you could
speak German wait so the water's going
to come out for just one second I'm
sorry f
i
mama it's fine okay okay I won't mess
with it right that's probably plenty of
torches anyway
M do we have some dirt blocks really
quick I just want to fix that we have
seven dirt blocks seven no way there
must be more there's some here maybe oh
yeah 19 dirt blocks
okay it's
another happy Trier chest for cie to
sort
out ooh the grass grows
fast ah it is so difficult in in one
block to find a a point to stop because
you can like go forever and ever and
ever
yeah but I will stop I will stop should
I read some super chats I probably
should o you said you would stop messing
with the water o oh I lied AIA
licon I made more trap doors
oh that looks like chocolate bar
oh y that looks good damn it today might
might just be a little cheat day after
dinner maybe some
chocolate I put the water this makes it
look a little bit better red it looks
amazing
actually I really like
it thank you
four cheat days a week let's
go no it's not that many you guys don't
understand I don't even eat that much
food although sometimes on on those
cheat days where I ate chocolate that
one day where I ate chocolate where I
wrote about it in Twitter that day I
didn't have lunch you know and I only
had small breakfast and dinner was
healthy so no lunch means I can eat
chocolate in my
opinion
yeah right I'm not done messing with the
water I'm
sorry you will never be
done I me you to watch me though yeah I
I'm almost done I want
[Music]
to put the music back now yes I will
music DJ W M
DJ uh
okay please hold the
line H is
fixing things that don't didn't need to
be
fixed wasting bone meal let's go hey y
wait who stopped who stopped working on
this axe
doco maybe it was
me maybe it was
me where we ending the stream yeah but
it's so hard to end and I want to show
you the final version of whatever am is
building here
the final
form okay there almost
ready nice
nice ah don't
shoot okay it's
working oh wo I like the look look at
this
oh okay that is that is easy to
understand the chocolate look is really
really yummy makes me
hungry very tempting to bite into
it oh but it's made out of wood so I
hope it doesn't catch on fire or
something a we'll be fine because
there's water
yeah all right good job am you're
getting a a sticker on your homework for
that one yay I already got employee of
the day yeah you'll be employee of the
night
ah green horse oh it
survived
oh actually now that it's like pretty
open over here I wonder if enemies spawn
I guess they'll be able to roam around
pretty
freely I'll put a I'll put a slab to
stop them maybe the slab will stop them
but not uh kill
them in any case if they want to roam
around that's fine
too yeah use
glass a if there was glass around I
guess they wouldn't see us that could
also be good but
nah
[Music]
nah no need
give me one slab over please oh it's
obsidian okay
oh okay wa I'm going to get the diamond
pickaxe but why why am I still mining I
think I want to see an enemy spawn and
see what happens but they don't spawn as
often anymore it feels
like oh why am I jumping
boy oh maybe cuz it's a trap door I
don't know
M enemy
come oh glass uh I see chat says glass
that doesn't suffocate them
oh you want to do it maybe the Lantern
and the slab will stop them mhm also I
put a
trap oh there we go something
mhm oh no you can still access the chest
like this
nice come on come on come on give me
something give me an enemy a tall one
ideally a zombie or a wizard
[Music]
sorcerer something interesting not a
small lice thingy Ender M no thank you
is a chest
full uh
yeah oh all right uh okay it just flies
out okay yeah yeah all right goodbye
I'll put another slab I mean for that
one I think it's fine if it can just fly
out that's
fine
there cuz I I feel like you know when we
make it too low then maybe uh the
animals that we want to survive will
have troubles Staying Alive we just need
sheep right sheep are pretty short yeah
true cow in the background what what
about
us Chad can help her connect to multiple
chests only
one good
question chat answer
do one
Apparently
one all right well we' finished yeah we
we should help me help me end this I'm
help
me take Minecraft away from me
please all right I'll give you the cheat
code
C alt
f4 oh let me
[Music]
try oh no damn it
works Hall left game what I'm a cheater
now I feel like I shouldn't be playing
the game anymore I've cheated it's over
I'm
disqualified now thank you am for
helping
tasar it's so nice to see you doing like
technical science construction stuff
again shows your
talents oh yeah maybe I'll see you
tomorrow maybe no pressure
though okay
yeah just uh I'm waiting for a custom
installation it's like a custom thing
that I'm waiting for and then I'll be
back to streaming uh people that are
wondering okay okay you got to get your
stuff done that's okay it's before it's
before the end of the month ever should
be we will wait for
Army thank you do your thing yeah okay
uh I think I'll read a few Super Chat so
I'll just say goodbye to you now and in
German we stay have
am I'm going to go yeah yeah
byebye have a nice evening no more tummy
hord
please oh I just didn't hear
that oh my God I got like a million DMS
oh but actually not surprised because I
sent out a million
DMs I just got a million replies
[Music]
what okay uh Discord DM jump scare yeah
that was legit terrifying
actually okay yeah sorry uh maybe today
was kind of low energy because we were
just you know doing Minecraft things you
know but I'm so happy so many of the
girls showed up I didn't expect Ena to
show up she said she couldn't there she
was she couldn't she couldn't miss out
on some
action very chill very calm yeah the
highest energy was maybe when I was
alone and was panicking the whole time
yeah I'm kind of hungry and tired but uh
I don't know I shouldn't be tired it's
too early uh actually so I'll read some
super chats so that we don't fall too
far
[Music]
behind hello the wahas the waas there
they are
too early too early because yeah it's
almost 3:00 a.m. but I adjusted my sleep
schedule for this yeah but then I
thought I'd have to stream like even
even later but the girls joined me quite
early in in the evening so that's nice
of
them oh thank you thank you for the
Super Chat no no big deal no
biggie no biggie to throw this together
at
[Music]
all Super Chat at 3 a.m. just a little
bit we need to we need to make some
progress just like half an hour
maybe half an hour of super chats uh do
you guys know where oh yeah from outfit
for I think I wanted to read the ones
that are not like pinks and reds but
I'll skim over over those as well to see
if there's any
thing uh
important you don't believe in me doing
it in half an hour well it's not like
I'm going to finish
them not
tangents it's not a lot if you filter
out the pinks yeah that's what I thought
that's what I
[Music]
thought okay but I hope you guys had fun
today in this m Minecraft stream if
you're leaving to do other things then
goodbye thank you for showing up maybe
maybe show me your face again tomorrow I
would be
delighted who knows what will happen
tomorrow I think it's still too early
for the never like for real considering
how little food we have how little
iron we just got to I mean there's a lot
of blocks where the iron or the diamond
or whatever several gems are in the
Stone we have to mine that to get the
actual iron then maybe if we do that
then maybe we don't have that little
iron
actually maybe maybe there's a lot of
iron that's just not
ironed and iron farm iron farm but for
an iron farm we need beds right is that
oh and more Villages and now now that
the that all the phases are mixed it's
going to get uh be really hard to get
what we need it's going to take a long
time to get one
villager
[\h__\h] we need free
villagers yeah so I don't think I need
to stall
anymore it's stalling on its
own tting already well just talking
about the game still I'm still in game
mode so H but I do think I think we need
more iron and it doesn't seem like we're
getting that much on its
own so it's definitely worth looking
into if we get three
villagers then we got to make a farm got
to make that
[Music]
farm but can we make out of out of two
villages we can make the third one right
yeah just got to make just got to get
two villagers and give them bread and
then they make baby
that's not so bad two villagers I'm more
hopeful about two villagers than
three all right H Cho chto Super Chat
reading time um so as you guys remember
I did a outfit reveal and then and in
that outfit reveal I did the Polaroid
thingy for any
pinks uh the reds are getting them too I
suppose um now let me first get rid of
all the pinks and reds oh does no that
makes no no I'll just I'll just go
through it like this oh but we need some
bgm we need some
[Music]
bgm but I have a bunch of tracks
here these are also similar but they're
all different this one this one this
one and this one fascinating
okay I'll keep this
one what what make a mob farm for spider
silk to make beds beds with spider silk
spider webs you
mean what you can do that too I never
heard of that I guess that nobody does
that because sheeps are normally
easier W Wool with four
strings oh
damn I didn't know I didn't know okay
that's an option but I don't know how to
make a spider
farm I'd have to look that up is that
easy is that
[Music]
manageable we tried to tell you sorry I
was like more focused on like talking to
the girls and and being efficient in the
game than looking at chat
sorry yeah we have a lot of cobwebs
M and
strings dark room to start off
with maybe just a general mob like PPP
I'm is going to make the PPP then we can
have all kinds of things from there see
okay there's there's quite some use from
PPP I need armor to make
PPP okay let me read
the chats I'll just put up the thumbnail
to
where is it which one is
[Music]
it
ah
wait open image in new tab save
[Music]
image
okay okay here we go d
d for several super
chats oh Gilma girls for your birthday
I'm giving you my Gilma Girls season
free thoughts let's go you left oh yeah
you finished at season two Rec like
before that oh long season so need to
spread them out that's okay take your
[Music]
time season 3 episode 1 opening has Lor
light dreaming of having twins of Luke
but they don't tell you it's a dream I
was Bamboozled I don't remember that
damn I need to rewatch Kim my girls and
thought I was in the wrong season just
with new girl already mhm more the
womanizer Luke gives laurelai a donut to
make up over Christopher cute laurelai
can be so easily suede with
donuts for me I guess that could work
too yeah okay first episode done thank
you for sending your thoughts again I'm
happy to to read
them you don't have a preference in the
polar okay okay okay okay okay h py
d Studio Rob sends a pinky but doesn't
ask for any polar ride what the hell oh
no it says a post postcard you mean
polar ride right give the PO to someone
else and you don't know how to access
the are you sure Studio Rob I think when
you sent it there were no no examples
yet so you didn't know what to ask for I
I'll check if there's another Super Chat
from you where you where you gave your
wish to
[Music]
me okay humic also my choice this is
confusing this is confusing because the
first couple of pigs they don't say any
numbers or
so my eyes are confused at what's what
to look at let me read the non pinks
Honolulu
also
Honolulu where is your Polaroid wish
this is just a normal
pinky a do I read this or
not
confused I just wanted to give you guys
more time and I I thought that I would
show the Polaroids earlier but then I
decided to just show them on
stream okay I'll just I I'll move
on Jess b d k d np15 fre D hyper Epsilon
D Roose toar sends a red Super Chat that
says send
tweet no polaro wish either but here is
where it starts with the Polaroid wishes
okay thank you
roar and then spanking time you get a
little kiss for that
one many many Polaroids many many
Polaroids mp15 free garlics M red Super
Chat is
Pinky and wow that's a lot of pink that
is just pure
pink whoa in between Danon red Super
Chat thank you dun
[Music]
and a lot of pink again muchos
binkos every another C thanks for the
red super
J has a pink wall shees oh shees oh my
oh
my okay now I'm like visualizing
this uh One X One D
and
7 Jack Red Wing thank you for the red
super
chat you'll get that polar right just
got to be a little bit
patient Big
Papa thank
you K Lo wonderful D Baby
D D D my own D fancy D Electric D mod
arcade d trimo d candy stamps
D wik Tunes
danash for the pinky that doesn't seem
to be asking a for a Polaroid cuz I
guess you already did kid Loco
danash dwark Warf also not asking for a
polar as far as I can tell thank you for
the
pinky distracted Crow d Sean Aon
D oh it was a hard Choice honestly there
were so many good but that's I tried my
best to combine two outfits into one you
will see eventually that be Dan
D
P na cotton thanks for the red super
chat signing up for the aerobics
class I pronounce it like that it is
more like aerobics but when you say it
fast it turns into aerobics don't get it
thank you
Nathan I think you can have your own
aerobics at
home aerobics at
home aerobics R it's more like R
aerobics
nah I don't know you you all of you guys
seem to write it in a different
way that's it
aerobics there's no W there why would it
be pronounced like
that aerobics that's just because
English is not um what's the
word it's not always the same you guys
are
weird yeah consist
that's the word you guys are not
consistent enough not my
fault
Kim d j d Nathan did I give you a
kiss lover d thank
you I feel like I might be missing some
like to read and pinkies that aren't
even Polaroid wishes I'm sorry if that's
the case it's just confusing ch
this guy says he wants to visit Austria
and then says what's your recommendation
and then says the
kfp uh workers have been telling me that
inbrook is recommendable is a good place
are you trolling or are you genuinely
[Music]
confused who told him that eh who told
that chto um chicken
that he they got to go to
inbrook Bonk
Bonk AC thanks for the pinky this Al St
saying to bless you and the
artist the ah bless you want the artist
H you look so adorable and jiggly yeah I
think I suddenly need to double up your
AR aerobics class also I'll take the
laser suit one good God ah why you got
to say say it like that that is a
Polaroid request I I saw no number which
one is the laser suit the one that looks
like a suit where I was like what is
this and you guys told me it's AIT I
think I know next time you got to put a
number
there confuse
me disco disco disco party
party Ro milk
[Music]
Ean gavette D ad business regulation
Director
D D Max with first D steal D 73
d f d MC C DT k
[Music]
d h n is asking for a Polaroid for his
friend Hugh
Jaz are you serious do you want me to
sign it for huge huge ass hug ass you
really want me to do
that I'll do
it tell me tell me if you're
[Music]
serious it's my body from elementary
[\h__\h] you shut up no he's
not no
you don't have to lie to me like that I
already see through all of
your
pranks cute jazz is a cool
guy all right H Jazz you
know he really likes your new
outfit just be honestly it's
you nothing to hide maybe you just want
a second one that's okay wait can I get
a number four we have four do we have
four yeah we do for a moment I thought
it was a like that we don't even have
number four so it should have been
obvious to me that it was a prank no we
do have
four but I dou Jones
[Music]
D whoa solar Punk
dreamer sent two Reds to get a Polaroid
even though you only needed a pinky I'm
I'm I'm going to read it out loud okay I
don't know if you're here right now but
feel like you you overpaid by far
so hi k I love the new outfit looking
respectfully uh f is my favorite song of
yours for real are you here by the way I
can't see you and I thought this
matching upha reveal would be a great
opportunity to show my appreciation a I
guess so yeah makes sense I really love
what you do love the I know wait uh
thank you for all the hard work and the
many hour hours of fun
gameplay amazing dance and music as well
as many fascinating tangents you're
always giving us much love for me just
another Euro
kfp oh also number one for thank you
Euro kfp why it's my pleasure that's
right it's in Euro I didn't realize oh I
am
honored thank you so
much Fever Night appreciation month
is what it is it seems
like we all appreciate fever night this
month baby I even switched back to an
old version of the loading screen the
fever Knight version as you may have
noticed if you're here from the
beginning of the
stream I was like Hey I was like
cleaning out my openings and then I
found that one I was like hey yo wait I
could use this when I put out my fever
night outfit
H thanks for the
rid yeah now I've been playing fever
Knight remixes although yesterday it was
a fever Knight instrumental not the
remix it's actually my K instrumental
with my backing
vocals that's why it sounded a bit funny
maybe thank you so much solo Punk
dreamer m m m m
to wherever in Europe you are I would be
curious if you can tell me
sometime cuz if you're like in Germany
or so and we can talk in German that' be
nice
too thank you for your support it's nice
to have European viewers because at
least for you guys I don't have to feel
so bad about my streaming times except
for now but that's a different story
[Music]
andreos dangun big papa Blake again
dangun Rowan Hood
[Music]
dangun ah oh okay here Honolulu sent me
what they wanted that's
good Marco
har thank you
s i missed reading your
name s it's like uu speak
Marco
har thank you okay I
think I think this is okay so the pinks
that didn't read they will get those
polar words at least if you put down a
number you'll get them as soon as I have
time oh the chat is about ah ai ai yeah
I saw that in a in a m
uh in the mumi clip where where is this
AI
thing where do you guys get that
[Music]
from I don't seem to have that option to
to let AI tell me what the chat is it's
mobile
only turn off hyper chat it's not on
right
[Music]
now
weird maybe they did didn't give me the
feature
yet got to figure it out one of those
days I want to see what it
says I have the chat in a separate tab
open
yeah start without premium on desktop
but only once is it like random because
it's just testing still
Maybe funny hey help us tell me tell me
what my chat is talking about I I I
don't understand what they're trying to
tell me I need your
[Music]
help finally I'll be able to understand
you guys when that AI comes to help me
and save
me okay guys I think I can quickly read
The Fallout super chats how about
that yeah can I I can and I
cooked the curry yesterday so I can just
eat the curry today I don't have to cook
so we're fine on that regard but tell me
one thing guys do you think I'll be okay
I have one piece of salmon the problem
is both my chicken uh Curry the chicken
of it and the salmon both expired on the
15th now it is now the 16th because it's
past midnight but in Fury I think I
could still cook the salmon
but do you think I can just cook it
tomorrow evening because even if I cook
it now I won't eat it and it won't be
fresh because I still need to eat my
second servant of the chicken I don't
understand why they sent me stuff that's
like uh that goes off so early like both
dishes you think it's fine I think so
too like I I have free dishes right free
and they're all with some kind of meat
so fish and chicken and one more is like
sausage
stuff sometimes it's so stupid they like
2 days after you get the box it already
expires okay so you cook that first but
what if the other thing also expires 2
days after it
arrives so
dumb and I can't freeze it because the
fish that they sent it says on the
package that it's uh de de Frozen like
it was frozen before and it's been deep
Frozen to like get to me and it says
don't freeze it
again
so yeah defrosted yeah I don't want to
like spend time now to cook that just to
not even eat it fresh I I think I also
think like one day should be fine yeah
okay I'll I'll cook it tomorrow it's a
premium meal I paid extra for it so I
hope I hope it will be
H have you have you checked the
1.21 change you mean in Minecraft no we
don't have that update yet speaking of
okay I I know I said you know reading
super chats butut speaking of I uh I saw
Callie's revealing her 2.0
I actually also have my 2.0 but I I uh
need some fixes
done
um but even then even when they fix
those things I'm not sure if I want
to do an actual reveal or so for 2.0 I
don't know if it's worth it um I saw
Callie's 2.0 she showed us
yesterday it looked uh quite nice now my
two .
[Music]
Z I think there's definitely some
changes but I don't think it's like that
big that I would want to make a big deal
out of
[Music]
it yeah so personally I'm thinking I
might just hold off until
3.0 or just start using
2.0 without doing a
reveal without like advertising it as a
big
reveal we'll see
but you know there was one thing that I
was kind of
like you know how default
Wawa has
actually quite long
hair remember that I don't use the
default outfit much and and even when I
use it it's not always that visible but
remember how it has quite long
hair it actually yeah goes down to like
my shoulder blades
[Music]
and but it's it's weird because that
part of the hair down there isn't like
shaded like the rest of the
hair
M and then in the
3D version of Wawa my hair was cut short
so that shoulder blade length hair was
gone and but honestly I think we all
kind of saw it
as like it shouldn't be there fan art
was usually also drawing me with shorter
hair the sh the hair that the hair
length that you think I have unless you
pay really really hard attention and see
how long it is like between the arms you
can like see it flowing
sometimes no no no so for 3D I saw it
was cut but I was like okay yeah
whatever it's not that noticeable in the
2D um and I don't think they can change
it
anyway uh and originally I would have
liked to have longer hair you know but
then in 3D they cut it and I was like
okay I guess that's how it is that's how
short my hair is supposed to be now it's
weird
because like hook Papa Drew
it hook papa is the one who drew it in
both ways like I don't know what
happened
there um but then now in the 2.0 it's
still there and the thing is because the
rigging is so to say better the hair
moves even more and now I feel like that
shoulder length hair is more visible
than before and like shows up way more
like it's more noticeable you know what
I mean so I'm wondering is that going to
confuse people maybe now is the time to
remove it if possible uh and I asked and
I said no because it's not like a
ringing thing the the main art would
have to be changed I thought that maybe
you know all these things they're like
Single part right separate
parts so I think you could remove it but
it's like whatever right it's not that
important but it's something I noticed
where I was
like this has always been a thing
but cuz normally they do everything they
can to make the 3D accurate matching
accurately matching to to the 2D and
then for me for some reason that didn't
happen now I thought you you might want
it to match I was like well you guys do
you maybe want to match it up now
because we have a chance here and
they're like no we will not do it I'm
like okay
[Music]
okay no it's it's a bit weird it just
confuses me
it just flows so much more so it bothers
me but yeah I don't think I will I don't
think I'll do a re I'll wait one more
time until they fixed the issues that I
brought up and now I'll decide them but
there's a chance I won't do a reveal for
it I'll just bring it out randomly
maybe lowkey reveal or maybe a member's
only
reveal h
H nice
[Music]
yo yum but yeah finally it's moving on
finally we we got 2.0 and and then it
means from there on they can start
working on the
3.0 cuz they they couldn't just skip 2.0
they
said that's why we got to wait for that
one
first
okay uh fallout is it the third fourth
fourth stream
right the thumbnails are so similar it's
hard to
tell we had your 3D update and new
outfit so we ate already yeah well the
3D update was
yeah um initiated by me
the hair doesn't look that long in the
concept is illustration which one do you
mean but yeah it's it's I think it's
really supposed to end up there I don't
I don't know what what that long part
there is doing it doesn't even have the
same kind of outline that the rest of my
hair has in my default outfit I'm
looking at it right now
actually um even though you guys see
something else
but it doesn't even have the same
outline so it's really confusing
no sneaky
[Music]
hair in the reference sheet your hair is
about collor bone hide H you mean yeah
yeah yeah yeah so that's what I would
see as the official
version anyway and do Hood D and do Hood
again thanks for two pinkies with Gilma
girls review okay two
episodes uh episode two glad L reli let
Kirk down gently L is the chosen one
Chosen One For What but Chris showing up
at Emily's dinner was
tense I feel like my memory is even
worse now than when you were reviewing
season 2 but I think I remember
something he that's happening
there happy Emily defended laureline
despite liking Chris oh let's go
that J Rory kiss from season 2 is
messing up my perfect Rory deanship
waa I don't like either of those couples
to be honest I feel like Dean is
too like BL like he's too much of a
goodie boy and then his hair is so
slippery and he's too tall makes me mad
how tall he
is and he's just like he's trying too
much to be Prince
Charming and and Jess obviously he's you
know he can
be a troublemaker quite a lot so that's
also not
[Music]
good I do
like the Blondie boy that she gets later
in fur but in reality it's not it's not
a very
realistic uh get together
[Music]
anyway uh his hair is really greasy
uh uh okay season 3 episode 3 Rory
freaking out thinking she's unqualified
for Harvard but she's super qualified
yeah I wonder if W doubted herself when
she applied to whole life you're such a
perfect fit created funny the f voice W
I know W where she belongs honestly I
did not doubt myself I was very
convinced of myself and I would say that
probably helped
me like make a good impression like you
always want to seem confident I
think I think that is good for stuff
like this I mean maybe my confidence
level here and
there like had times where it lowered
itself after joining but at the time of
applying I thought I was the perfect fit
the perfect
match and that I can make it in easily
well I thought so I definitely was
thinking positively and I mean they they
sent me back uh an email
immediately thank you
danela they sent me back an email
immediately I I was so lucky honestly I
feel like realistically maybe if I would
have uh although no I think even if I
would
have uh auditioned for later gens I
think even though there were more
auditions
auditioners I think I would have still
had very high Chances with my skill
set I think I still could have made it
in yeah I made my submission in a really
short amount of time cuz I I was so
motivated you think
thank you Chad yeah I'm pretty sure I
mean I think I have the right skill set
and even if it wouldn't have worked out
for like second gen maybe it would have
worked out for third gen or So
eventually I would have made it in you
cannot have whole life English without
waa I am destined to be here whether you
like it or
not but I am extremely lucky to have
made it into the the first
generation very lucky very privileged
D
yeah so I'm very proud very honored and
very gra gra gra gracious
gra
thankful you know what I mean grateful
grateful yeah grateful damn it it was
right there it was right there so
easy thank you Doug
Hood Che
forro py py py oh yeah I finally reached
1.52 million subs and then I
wondered I wondered wa where did that
come from so suddenly was I always so
close these days cuz growth is so
slow I think it happened on the on the
yeah on the
3D reveal YouTube short stream
thingy did the vertical thing actually
have I don't know if it's the vertical
thing or if it's just because I did a
funny 3D reveal
stream I don't know maybe I have to test
it out for science guys maybe it was
both yeah a combination of both
[Music]
it works ask narissa I I have been
seeing her growth
yeah I don't know I don't really want to
rely to much on it like I think for like
kok streams or even outfit reveals or
stuff like that I think it's um fine for
that and for the soccer football uh WFA
European Championship uh watch alongs
that I said in the preat that I want to
do them I think we can do you YouTube
short for that too YouTube short
stream for people who missed it there's
currently the European championship of
football going on and Austria has some
matches and I know Austra sucks at
soccer and that's exactly why I want to
watch some some Austrian
matches the upcoming one I don't think I
can make it that one's on Monday because
I think we'll still be busy with
Minecraft um but there's like two more
after that for now maybe more after if
Austria manages to get to the next round
so to say uh a not so bad you think
so I don't
know aren't you bad lately really did
things change have times changed well I
would like to see it I will cheer for
them if they do well and if they do
badly I will laugh at my uh Austrian
fellows yeah I don't know I really want
to watch it because I don't know much
about soccer football
but I don't know stuff like European
Championship I'm excited to watch stuff
like that I'm actually like kind of
excited it does interest me when it
comes to bigger things like that when
it's a world champion ship or european
Championship I am genuinely interested
and I remember when I was really really
really really young and I was really
really small I uh there was a European
Championship going on and there was I
think a finale of Greece versus some
other
country and my whole family and family
friends that were there in front of the
TV they were all thinking that the other
country would win yeah Portugal yeah it
was more likely anyway cuz Greece did
not have a good reputation in terms of
football skills um and not like I like
had any idea or like
any like anything to base it off on but
I think small waa just wanted to go for
the
underdog yeah
2004 20 years 20 years
ago well I a phoenix
um
damn
she 20 years I was very very small I was
practically a baby um so yeah I didn't
have anything to base it on but I was
like I will support Greece I think
mostly because um Underdog and also
because the flag was pretty
and so I I put like A4 uh pieces of
paper pieces several pieces of A4 paper
I I drew the uh Greek flag on it and I
put it all over my body I made myself a
paper
helmet and I think I made myself a paper
shirt or something like that out of A4
pieces of paper where I drew the Greek
flag on
it and then I was just crawling around
in the living room hoping for Greek
Greece to win and they [\h__\h] did and
everybody was like what the [\h__\h] and I
was like Yay I knew it I didn't know it
I did not know it in fact but I was so
excited that I actually cheered for the
right
team
[Music]
yay so because of those memories and me
just generally being kind of interested
in how austar will do and me thinking it
will be kind of fun to do a little bit
of uh yapping zsan chatting stream while
watching soccer I I want to try doing
that maybe not for every match but we'll
try to do uh some Austrian matches
there's Netherlands and there's uh
France and there's
Poland I
think which one was the Monday one not
sure I forgot but
yeah my 30 minutes are long up whatever
whatever
whatever I'm having fun Monday one is
France okay yeah I don't think we can
watch that I'll I'm excited to hear the
result while I'm streaming Minecraft
probably uh or yeah it might just be
before I start streaming Minecraft I'm
not
sure uh what was I going to say oh yeah
uh you guys if you're not in Europe
you'll have to figure out a way to watch
it I'm sure there's some way there I'm
sure there's some streams where you can
watch
it for Europeans there's like a
different provider for every single
country % there will be a
way yeah worst case use a VPN I don't
know probably on ESPN in the US maybe I
saw uh it's on I think it's on Fox
Sports or whatever some some kind of
sports channel from
Fox you just described the match I
cannot how do you call it scream shout
shout scream shout
uh cast scream cast shoutcast shoutcast
that's it is
[Music]
it commentate cast shoutcast Shout cast
okay I'll try I'll
practice we'll practice our shout
casting in English skills I think in
German you have higher chances of me
being able to do
that and it will be around usual Wawa
streaming time so that's
nice no no no no no no uh the yeah the
France one starts at 9:00 p.m. and the
other start at 600
p.m. yeah German Channel content h
no I don't
know no no no no no I want to commentate
in
English just say messy messy messy when
he's not even
around twitch stream I feel like on
Twitch people would expect me to show
the match on the
screen so even if I get randos coming
into the stream they're gonna be
like what the [\h__\h] this a watch long and
there's nothing to watch what do you
mean you're watching soccer I don't get
it because that like normally on Twitch
everybody just shows whatever they want
right not not even only on Twitch on
YouTube too as long as you're not part
of whole
life so I feel like that's not a good
moment to go onto twitch no
I'll just do it as a YouTube short
though anyway
continuing
hro wait I feel like I read that didn't
I read this oh yeah here py D James
Jackson D logical Paradox
[Music]
daneses I don't know how to say that Me
Fallout dun not a good username dun no
no not Caesar Kaiser
the
Ste happy
birthday congratulations Tassimo Tassimo
again thanks for the red of chat I'm
Tassimo and I'm here to ask a question
is why not entitled to the sweat of her
bro
brow no says the N the NCR it belongs to
the Republic no says New Vegas it
belongs to house no says the legion it
belongs to Caesar I reject those answers
I show new Wawa so you're saying I
should go
independent the sweat of my
bro it's a book reference
uhhuh I don't know man I really can't
decide ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
man I can't
decide I don't know what's like the most
interesting what do you think is the
most interesting
for the sake of the
[Music]
stream I'm between independent house and
NCR NCR
oh oh a lot of NCR
supporters oh
okay are you sure that's the most
interesting I feel like it might be the
most boring cuz it's so obvious like
right in front of your
face has a lot of quest well great I
don't want to do them
all not like I want to do them
all you make the most allies okay
[Music]
okay okay NCR is going up higher in my
list
then okay I still think about
it thank you
[Music]
Tassimo but yeah new Wawa would be best
soy killer Productions
d uh yes I think I did the steel D Lee
Edward D
Yi d i wonder did it come back to me
because it somehow watched the VA and
heard me talk about me missing it and
being really like the one time I missed
I didn't see the Super Chat that it sent
and I was like okay I I'll give her
more I really wonder if only it could
talk then it could tell me what it's
thinking man I wish it would just tell
me I think akaan can have a character
development by now and learn to talk in
baby
speak it's been
years I think four-year-old
baby can
speak quite a bit
no yeah evolve to toddler ch
they talk a
lot you never taught it how to speak
it's supposed to learn on its own for
chat maybe AI it should have ai and like
teach itself words through super chats
and
jets no He's Alive it doesn't say that
it's dead
anymore it used to be dead now it's
alive
maybe it's all separate entities who
knows the Ste
D thank
you the Ste say make
fall
oh you you pretty much wrote the same
Super Chat twice okay you're an NCR
supporter nice Garden Park D the steel d
hey Veronica's dress that was so random
man her reaction was so delayed what the
[\h__\h] you
have
lunch Omar Simpson space
wonderful estan Gonzalez dun the steel
dun the Mad kitten
dun oh thank you for watching my outfit
reveal yeah I think you have no choice
but have it live rentree in your head
especially if you're on Twitter and see
all my retweets that are
amazing he really liked what I drank
from the toilet
yeah that's very
attractive M she likes maybe she likes
dogs and she thought oh that's such a
dog like feature
[Music]
Ste UF mod panopticon pinky awesome new
outfit k I love the Retro aesthetic and
the hair is incredible also boobs I hope
you don't mind the Avalanche of thirsty
comments but it's great to see you get
so much attention for the new outfit
everyone seems to have loved it thank
you I haven't even seen as many first
comments as I have seen thirsty fan art
and it's making me quite
happy actually like a lot of the fan out
that I'm seeing is like kind of loot but
not too loot that I wouldn't retweet it
and that's a really awesome balance like
you struck gold of
that it's so close to me not being able
to retweet it I mean I could but I don't
want to if it goes too too horny too
naked or so
but like it hits right the spot on the
edge to NG to now being okay
anymore especially those those those
ones that from the same person that are
untagged that I
retweeted
yo yo as if my boobs didn't already go
through inflation by this outfit they
inflated my boobs even more
[Music]
more looks so
good looks so
good
yeah absolute
blessed space waterful Jack
FB flight fancy D unon viewer D Ste d
space wonderful d i
clay clay d clay Kai D np5 fre G SP for
the pinky you did care you saved bis B
with your
love I did
it I am a hero
[Music]
oh oh let's go good for you let's go
sounds good good luck with the new job
ixus is red
d d naan thanks for the pinky cute
moments doesn't do you J is more like
perpetually cute
existence
R thank you oh my God stop oh endless
thank you so much oh my God New Zealand
what time is it like 10: or so no
probably
not that's like Japanese time
difference what time is this but
something like that
right roughly yeah maybe
11 torturing my EU fans nah they have
enough of prime time streams 12:00 noon
oh
after 12 oh
1:45 oh good time damn good morning
sunshine I hope it's
Sunshine where was I Nathan thank you so
much Sensei thanks to the pinky as well
thank you for being there all my
afternoons while I work computer
programmer oh you're
welcome you're are very welcome thank
you for being here too Cody props D Duck
Hood
[Music]
D hey I did it I read two
streams
okay I'll have more of my um
[Music]
Curry I'm tired wow I'm
tired so Callie moved her
stream to be like 400 p.m. tomorrow my
time
I'll try to
um be with her for a
bit she kept on moving it like like
first she put something in the calendar
and then I saw okay she's doing
Minecraft there then I put mine on top
of it and put mine there too like my my
Google Calendar
thingy and then she moves it a few hours
and I I I'm like oh okay I make my thing
follow hers I adjust it to hers and she
did it again and she did it again I'm
like kie then she even switched the
freaking day and I'm like girl
decide it's like keeps on running away
from me do you not want to play with me
I'm just kidding I'm sure she just you
know has been
realizing like honestly from what I can
see in her schedule
she has too much Minecraft in there
anyway actually no she changed things
again who think she changed things again
oh my God
[Music]
girl yeah it's it's just I shouldn't
even look at
it
okay next week is going to be an
exciting week but no schedule but it
will be exciting anyway okay even if
there's no
schedule so just you know I always like
seeing your reactions to my
schedule so it's kind of sad when I
don't have one but just go like who
imaginary schedule let's
go I got to put which spring R somewhere
cuz I feel bad for not playing it this
week so if there's no Fallout I might
replace it with you know I might I might
put witch spring r
instead but in anyway it's gorilla so
we'll just see when Minecraft
[Music]
ends okay I'm going to go damn potion
craft potion craft also have to wait
until I have
time and time is of the essence
currently
not much not much's
time
okay suddenly so [\h__\h] tired man we at
a few super chats got awake by them and
now I'm tired again
nice but I got to eat which will make
wake me up
again thank you guys I love
you tomorrow's Sunday right yeah
Sunday
Sunday oh yeah now it's Sunday too yeah
oh [\h__\h] tired bye byee bye bye bye bye
bye my eyes are falling
[Music]