go with
me
[Music]
once once upon a time there
was an owl a chicken and a
raven right and it it was uh it was the
night of Christmas Eve
[Music]
oh all the little birdies were tucked
into their little nests when
suddenly when
suddenly outside their window a huge
duck
appeared with an insane face picking
pecking at the window PE PE PE PE PE PE
PE
carrying the duck oddly like a bunch of
balloons were a few other birds a
peacock and and a hawk carrying it very
oddly in the
[Music]
sky a little ow shot up from her bed and
exclaimed oh my gosh my dreams they're
coming
true uh the the other two words that
were stuck in the bed also jump up and
uh ask the owl what do you know each
other then the the duck breaks through
the window and starts rushing the room
with the other two
[Music]
birds all of the little birds huddled
into a corner hugging each other
tightly oh
oh the the the uh free uh Str stranger
or not stranger Birds um uh Corner the
cornered birds
and uh uh with a loud scary threatening
voice they
exclaim that's a word
yes what do they exclaim
hark I have come with gifts for the
three English members of hot to and hot
toi tooran
[Laughter]
turn all the
birds we're so
happy The Little
Owl asked oh great big ones what is my
gift the ow ask that first the ow okay
theas thank you for the
confirmation um uh the the huge
duck uh gives the present into the 's
little BB
hands and does the bird the owl bird
opens it and is surprised and floored by
the insides which
are which
are oh God
uh pretty gems that they had collected
from lands
afar
H the little ow stared blankly then
looked up and said what the heck am I
supposed to do with
these oh oh the the duck says you
ignorant foul fool fool owl
these gems are for you to
give never mind I am the foul because I
actually gave you the wrong present this
this was for the The Raven
girl cuz I'm sure raven like shiny
things so never mind sorry give that to
the Raven girl the intern girl
okay I don't don't make me pick presents
um M with a little owl but owls like oh
no I'm sorry I'm a bird I just like
shiny
things wait who's talking right
now I don't know the the big duck okay
that was still from the big
duck I was going to give the little owl
something something she wants
right she racks her brain the duck
thinking about thinking about what a
good gift for The Little Owl might be
and then Eureka she pulls out a present
and inside of
it oh is another gift that the owl
doesn't want she looks back up at the
duck and says what the heck am I
supposed to do with these newspaper
articles newspaper articles oh oh okay
well well well says the huge duck by the
way the other birds are still there also
in the same room they just they just
don't talk um the duck
says in this in this newspaper
article is uh there's a there's an
important um news in there written that
is specific to you m and and that is an
interview with with that paper bag that
you like to ignore your supposed friend
who has uh in the interview exposed you
of the bad bad treatment they have
received from
you so it's an
expose happy Merry
Christmas okay next moving on to uh my
present I
guess pulling out the last present for
the little Phoenix the duck from her
mouth pulls a present box out her
mouth yeah and and presents it before
the little Phoenix m M oh not chicken
okay the duck was blind the duck was
blind and thought it was a phoenix but
it was really a little chicken
hey your turn
oh but then I can't
okay uh the the F
phix takes the gift opens it and
within is an egg a golden
[Music]
egg she asks the duck what egg is this
the duck
replies Hatchet and you'll find out but
it will bring to you great wealth little
Phoenix okay I think I
won best K okay is that the end
[Music]
they should leave shouldn't they how do
they leave the room and then okay and so
and so the little birds gathered around
looking at their presence as the bigger
Birds the big duck left feeling like
they didn't accomplish what they set out
to
accomplish and so uh the present the
gifted Birds happily go back to bed and
then in M's no no wait and
then in M's
dreams
she uh meets The Paper Bag
friend that was spoken about in the
newspaper
article haunting her even in her dreams
asking her why would you do this to me
why why
why when M when wakes up after this
incident she decided to or decides to um
reconcile and unite again with her
paperback friend and thus happily ever
after work together in cooperation Merry
Christmas M merry really really really
want me to be friends with friend
yeah why don't you want to be friends of
friend oh if only you knew Kara if only
you
knew so but no in this story you
reconcile and you you live happily ever
after and and narissa is happy with her
gems and I will hatch my golden egg
that's me so the whole time the whole
time we were the little birds yeah yeah
M yes wow what what a Twist surprised I
mean I totally didn't say m several
times throughout the story I know that's
where I was starting to question
everything like well this is deeper than
I thought it is all very deep so thank
you for listening to our ad love
Christmas
Story a very holot toy Christmas yes yes
goodbye Merry Christmas thank you for
opening this door happy
holidays
bye-bye