[Music]
oh honey
feel it R
[Music]
meting DJ keep playing
em
[Music]
feel it r
me
[Music]
feel it
R feel it like me
[Music]
d
oh honey
[Music]
feel it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
oops
Kik
hello
K you like the BDM it's cute right I
brought uh some new TR tracks some new
tracks I I I have brought to you hope
you like the
music don't worry you don't have to
listen to it the whole time I got a
second one it's silly right I
know well well well uh welcome everybody
I'm surprised there's so many people
here um makes me feel kind of pressured
wait let me adjust this
differently cuz I don't know it's not
like you know it's not crazy like you
know I don't like I mean I I don't
know
e what do you mean t are you sure they
actually gave you a 2.0 and didn't just
changed the label I'm not sure I'm
improving up on you as POS
oh
oh oh
[\h__\h]
okay oh well um wait I for got to get
water fresh water I only have like old
water let me just get fresh water and
then we can
[Music]
start
okay yeah I'm a raed me but I'm
surprised people stayed for so
long cuz she raided me like way before
the stream start
right why are you naked where are the
two hat shut
up maybe the two hats will come back
with 2.0 who
knows okay I'm not sure how to do this
like if I should do the charts first or
the reveal first or
the re yeah or like a mix like I I have
two charts like ID and Ian uh what are
you guys actually here for for the
reveal or for the charts let me make a
poll what are what are you I mean you're
obviously here for both but what are you
most excited for poll uh the poll yeah
the poll charts or reveal oh
sure did I say by the way
charts there charts
yes oh reveal 63% actually charts is not
doing so badly 40% for the charts oh wow
W it's rising a little
bit oh chart
enjoyers free
[Music]
food not sure about that possibly
uh okay 40 W WAOW it's like 50/50 okay
then you know what I will kind of do it
50/50 and then everybody's happy because
I wasn't sure what to do first anyway so
we're going to do the ID charts first
because a little bit less it's just uh
you know nine girls and then we're going
to do the reveal and then we're going to
go back to the charts we're going to do
Ian at that point and now I'm not doing
it like uh a lot of people are thinking
uh because of Ian Reco recently
uh you guys are thinking I'm going to do
like this crazy uh subway
map with like all kinds of arrows and
stuff no no no I'm doing it like the way
that the Japanese members usually do
it
uh uh with a table table no what's table
oh thanks for the Super Chat oh my God
why Ian Reco chart is going to be insane
no I'm not doing an Ian Reco chart
that's the thing so
uh where I made charts myself I took the
time to like make a graphic wait I'm
probably going to make this bigger
anyway uh
here um and I probably should put a text
somewhere that says we haven't revealed
it yet
CH I should probably do that where is
the
[Music]
chair I want to move
myself chair and Wawa go over oh
nice wow
wow wonderful
okay okay okay
okay oh yeah and then let's put put the
put the text
somewhere not Super Chat rating don't
worry uh
reveal didn't reveal
yet please
wait
okay here's
fine okay Pama baill out okay good go go
we're switching now
anyway this reminds me a little bit
of but it's not it's not it's different
just reminds of something else though
too now that this part
[Music]
starts okay
um so what I'm going to do is like in oh
in the oh the screens are kind of
whatever uh in a in a relatively simple
way like not too many words I'm going to
uh try to sum up my thoughts and
relationship or so or secret hidden
desires with them so this looks good
right by the way I was doing Polaroids
before the stream I only have like one
more number left like I did them like
all threee first all all ones and then
all twos and now missing all the fours
so all the fours from the second half so
uh please wait for the pulls I'm almost
done eh since when has there been
anything secret or hidden about your
desires well yeah you might think that
they are pretty obvious but maybe not
well about ID I think generally you guys
know how much I love ID members because
they're so lovable now let me choose a
font and a size because I have done that
yet maybe like got to be pretty
[Music]
small maybe white is fine and then yeah
caps look is fine too
[Music]
but okay wait uh like
this even on Anya I
hate okay I well how much can be right
oh oh yeah that's not good what the hell
we need to fix that too
Photoshop let's improve this situation
to like there we go wow graphic design
is my passion what do you think about my
graphic I I tried my best to make it you
know
organized okay okay but we start off
with Ru I'm going to be honest uh
unfortunately I um Lisa is one of the
people in ID that I have like the least
like collabs and interactions with but I
know she's still super cute and super
sweet and super fun and and just
adorable and an amazing singer
obviously so should we right like my
relationship to her huh and what I want
to
do if you guys remember we like our last
clab was so long ago if we ignore like
Minecraft cuz that was just all of ID uh
but like actually long long long time
ago we did this like Japanese Monopoly
collab or so with her didn't
we so H I'm not sure I have never done
this before like that did I what what
how do I start what do I write what do
people write
here uh uh
should maybe
smaller should collab again
[Music]
M right what you just said what did I
say where how do I put it into
words first impression curent versus
current impression oh that's also
interesting but then then there's
probably no space to write much well
okay okay that's actually actually
interesting okay like we write a little
like one two sentences about first then
about SEC like now impression and then
something like that I hope for and wish
for okay okay okay we're getting we're
getting organized
now uh my first
impression
huh
honestly I don't know if I had much of
an impression that's four years
ago because they were already there when
I was there when I joined they were
already there they were like a a little
bit before
us h
my
first original
impression I don't remember it's too
long
ago
uh
huh different
branch
[Music]
uh M that I have yet to connect with
that's might be kind of the same for all
of them
but this now it's interesting because
like at this point right I have like no
connection with ID but like the other
girls once the other girls are joining
I'm already like kind of connected with
ID and I I pretty quickly connect with
them let's make this a little bit
smaller after all and then the now
[Music]
impression is like
huh one of best singers in
h h
[Music]
h has
no shame in
promoting these nuts
[Music]
respect I respect that it's fun
and then
uh we should collab
again I want to sing
[Music]
together something like this is that
okay is this how we should get going how
we should do
[Music]
it oopsie oh what did I just
do what the freak did I just
push h Huh
oh oh well okay is that good that works
okay that's going to be everything no no
no okay no no no no no no it won't it
won't it won't okay for others I will
say I don't want to collab with them
okay original
impression here like kind of similar but
if we go a little bit
further how soon after I
joined did
she bond with p
how soon after was
that hey ma hey
[Music]
Ma maybe pretty soon same time really
bow that like because it's not like they
were uh like bonding before I joined I
think it really just started when I
joined
[Music]
uh so
I wish I could bond with P
[Music]
to that was my original
impression and then now
impression H chill
Senai who did my hair
before who did my hair styling IA she
did that
[Music]
before
reliable and
cool
[Music]
experienced
woman she is a
woman and then for the future I also
want to sing with her
why did we miss the
eclipse
Let's uh connect let's overlap again
let's let's overlap soon
okay
[Music]
okay cuz this year there was a nice
Eclipse that would have been a like in
America that would have been a good
opportunity because it was a big Topic
at the time would been a good
opportunity to make a joke stream out of
it and we missed our chance which you
know sucks uh now we have to wait a
million years yeah let's overlap you
know our bodies at some point
[Music]
anyway there's one in Spain in a couple
of years yeah I think I that's the one I
looked up for like oh which one's next
then which when when I when can I pull
this joke
next yeah okay original impression
speaks
German
apparently let's do German collab we
never did we never [\h__\h]
did never did German
collab why
[Music]
uh uh cute
creative girl who did my hair in a
different way cuz like did she Drew my
hair right I'm not like just imagining
this in her hair
salon uh what First Column is off what
are you talking about I'm still writing
this oh you're not seeing it oh that's
what you
mean there you
go what was I going to say oh yeah
because MAA um did my hair IRL and eii
did my hair like in a drawing stream
isn't that funny oh wait there's some
kind of green screen on
here oopsie I have some green screen
filter let me turn it
[Music]
off oops sorry a little bit little bit
messy
so
okay wait do I have what's my I have to
think hard like I need to focus okay is
do I have any
other impression
now my my brain is so empty what I want
to do with her like what I want to say
or what anything random
here I should draw her her back because
she drew me I don't mean I should draw
her like behind but I should draw her
back like cuz she drew me before right
so I should draw her
too German artstream
collab draw me like one of your German
girls
[Music]
oh why heard dumpy so famous and mine
not real talk it's not
fair not
fair I want my dumpy to become a Hot
Topic as
[Music]
well okay let's go down
here okay ol's turn oh I'm sure she's
curious what I was going to what would
write about
her I'm sure she's
curious copy
paste all these de oh yeah so this is
the time where I watched uh everybody's
debut so I have an actual impression
from the debut as well I
guess um okay my original impression was
like oh my God I don't know if I can
handle this
energy cuz her debut stream she would do
you remember she was
talking like a charge rifle as she likes
to
say she was trying to squeeze in English
Indonesian and
Japanese uh and had so much to say in
her uh debut like she was talking so
fast but she was also very interesting
in terms of personality and design I
feel like her design was
very
[Music]
Innovative and
personality okay we'll probably have to
adjust this
[Music]
again no want to say I was a I was a
little bit
[Music]
intimidated so energetic like people say
I'm energetic but like Ollie Ollie is on
a whole another level now
[Music]
impression um sweetest
supportive
girl who deserves so much
more M need more
uh
Positive Vibes like
[Music]
hers uh and then the comment would
be uh currently in
sync but
probably going to change
[Music]
soon don't like get excited ol like it's
a absolute
coincidence because I normally skip it a
lot on purpose cuz like a lot of people
a lot of girls get so confused uh like
surprised when I tell them this
but you you don't have to you know you
can just skip it if you you know and so
I just skip it a lot because I'm like I
don't I don't want to have Tommy
Hort a lot of people people who are not
on Twitter and who didn't see ol's tweet
have no idea what I'm talking
about are you starting to understand you
can what that's wild yeah okay you're
saying that maybe because you you don't
you know you're not probably not a girl
but even a lot of girls get so surprised
when I tell them
[Music]
that how does that work um okay let's do
do you want some girls talk right now
all right um so there's um this thing
called the pill of birth control and
um oh boy I I I honestly really have
been taking it for a long time for my
acne acne
uh it helped me a lot like there's
different types uh different ways uh of
like whatever's inside there it can
handle different
things and yeah sit down and listen now
uh normally you take it like I don't
know how long do you two three three
weeks or so like there's one like strip
and you take the whole thing and when
it's over you're supposed to take a one
week break
um but you can just not take the break
if you take the one we break you will
then start to have the
flaw um and also it also like makes it
less
painful uh and less tummy hor less and
and maybe less you know whatever um it
just controls things better but anyway
if you don't take the break it will not
initiate the thing but that's okay it's
not like everything things
like um like stacking up in there no no
no uh it will just not explode hi
[Music]
Ollie only perfect
timing yeah yeah I didn't want to tell
you cuz I didn't want you to get too
cocky or so because I'm I'm going to go
off syn again very soon so when you when
you do don't take it you you H when you
don't take the break you just
continuously take it and you know for
example in summer I like to do it so
that I can go swimming
anytime uh and and then I never have
tummy hord you know while I'm traveling
and so on you know so I'm so happy yeah
okay I just just uh know it's been a few
months so I decided okay I'm going to
let it happen I'm going to explode I'm
going to morb and it just so happened to
start on the day as yours Ollie I'm glad
you're happy I thought you would be but
it's just this once just this once is it
health it's there's no health problems
um talk to your to your uh female not Fe
probably not I don't know doesn't have
to be female but talk to your uh woman's
doctor if you want to know more about it
um they often don't say
it uh but if you ask about
it
gynecologist yeah yeah oh
God I
feel weird talking about
this when probably 80% here are
um don't deal with that kind of stuff
[Music]
great reveal so far boss thank you I've
revealed some things about
[Music]
[Laughter]
women oh man well olly um how's it going
huh my tummy Hort was really strong
these past two
days was really strong like big tummy
H but it's it's supposedly getting less
now H anyway okay that's freaking
okay uh original impression of
Ana voice is so uh cute and I
think did second ID gen debut before or
after
Iris you guys remember can you look it
up before right
yeah oh my God she's better in Japanese
than
[Music]
me what I I'm just like it's just a
observation it's not me like being
jealous or anything but I was pretty
impressed like wo and I love the way she
talks it's so cute she's just so so
pleasant to listen to and funny and the
way she the way she talks in Japanese is
also I don't know I really like
it uh wait we should put this together
again otherwise I don't have any space
now impression oh my God I hate
[Music]
her
um but actually okay but
actually let's be honest okay let's not
be so dramatic let's be honest for a
moment
um she's so
chill I didn't expect to like get uh
like close to her in the
beginning um I didn't expect it but I
feel like you know I'm close with like
pretty much everybody in ID
um no I hate her uh actually she's so
chill and I really ooh re oops
really like her music
releases Please Release
more um
comment oh also wait another original
impression was art style is so
unique that was that was really shocking
this whole generation was really
shocking to me
[Music]
M Everlasting
KN let's collab one time on now so for
people who don't know me and Ana
uh we for the longest time our only
interactions would be through Callin
like when she had a Callin stream or
when I had a call in stream she would
call in I would call in we would talk a
bit and we would promise each other like
oh my God we still haven't collabed yet
we should collab soon and then next time
we hear each other it's just another one
of the call-in streams and it just
continued and continued and eventually
we came to the conclusion or you guys
came to the conclusion it must be
because we hate each
[Music]
other and I thought that was funny so I
was like Ana I hate you and now we're
just going with
that love hate all the same if you know
play the game
is something a wise woman once said oh
shut up Windows
shut something
a what I'm not doing any
hello something a
w do you hear
this I'm
not what oh God let me save this before
I get a [\h__\h] blue screen again what
is going on
[Music]
what Ana stop cursing
me calm down PC okay I think it's calm
down
okay what was my what was my first imp
ah oh my God bird I think at this point
I already
established um like my bird bond with
Subaru did I because then I must have
been like oh it's kind okay okay oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oopsie did I okay cuz then pretty sure I
was like
H did I already call it holon though I
don't think I called it holon first I
think I only called it holon when there
was the third bird lady I
think but then first I called it tur
duckin and then the Japanese word for
tur duckin we called it hotori because
tur duckin in Japanese well you know was
it was just nicer to call it
hot I think something like that uh must
make
bird unit cuz actually if we ignore subu
because I mean come on uh after me even
though there were already so many whole
life Japan members
Arena was the uh second bird the first
after me to uh be a bird in whole
life so nowadays there's so many
birds but somehow we started a bird
Trend whole life was like oh okay let's
make more Birds because they're so
versatile which is
true [\h__\h] the USB device I don't know
which one it
is must make bird unit oh great she even
sings I want to say well but I don't
want to use another line oh my God
there's so many oh my
gods uh now
impression
[Music]
is one of my favorite people in Holo
um deepest Bond went on the
K she's so so so
dorky she's so
dorky yeah and then comment
[Music]
don't thanks for inviting me to your
freie
maybe Pretty
P pavi again
[Music]
soon okay we're going down
to the newest gen which at this point
isn't really very new anymore they've
been around for a
[Music]
while original
impression she looks like straight out
of Ark
Knights sweet
voice and cool
design oh off [\h__\h] okay sorry sorry sor
sorry sorry sorry sorry I'm so useless
Yahoo pello I was watching a little bit
of your Super Chat reading
stream
[Music]
hello what did she say I'm going to I'm
going to write something about you but
much later because you're like on theend
chart and that's that's going to be like
pretty much at the end cuz also you're
at the bottom of it with with Justice
it's going to take a
while okay uh
uh uh now
[Music]
impression surprisingly
dorky uh
always sends funny
submissions to
things
so uh good comedian because not only for
my Frey not Frey uh for my K like the
what was it the birthday K but also for
like Callie I saw she's like quite
the like comedian like trolling around
in fredie and her posing and stuff she's
very
chaotic I love
it I love it
H we played Grand blue together recently
uh but besides that I don't think we've
collabed
much
um maybe we should also she's so
fashionable let's go shopping
[Music]
IRL she's one of the most
like fashionable cute see people I would
say in
h she said happy birthday kie I wonder
if she really uh did that by accident or
if that was one of her troll
moments everyone always says vetta well
it's
true okay
K my original impression is W
she's so tall
and
long
uh super deep voice and
calm what like I really did not I did I
did not have any kind of idea what
kind of like streamer she would be
become h
I wouldn't say calm no well that was my
first
impression now
impression
gamer and
endurance
[Laughter]
beu it's so cute to see their bond it's
it was like so unexpected and I love to
see it I love to see it
[Music]
um now random
comment wonder what there is what's
what's there to say
[Music]
h i can't think of
anything be be
what that's a new name for
her
sleep get some help I mean that's
[Music]
honestly I don't think she needs help
she's got things under
control
[Music]
and let's play
Minecraft like I really liked our
interactions before um
um very
[Music]
helpful yeah like when we when I was I
think I was looking for the Sakura biomi
the cherry blesss biomi and I was so
nervous when I was like talking to her
cuz that was kind of the first time we
properly
talked and we were like oneon-one in a
call it just made me so nervous
[Laughter]
[Music]
makes me a bit
nervous nervous okay okay I'm not going
to mess it up now you're going to see
you're going to see you're going to see
what I'm going to write
here just this one I didn't mess it up
she's here oh my God why are so many
people showing up I got all of the help
I need and yeah let's play more games
together not only mine yeah please
please please please please
please and maybe dance together
sometime I want to I want to dance with
Kawa I hope we get an opportunity at
some
point some it's a summoning ritual
yeah that's fun I'm glad people are here
to see what I say about them pressure so
pressure so much pressure okay R what
was
my I I was
immediately like interested in her uh
right like I was I I was just shook by
her
singing and
energy immediately adopt
oops I I really immediately adopted her
but then immediately I regretted
[Music]
it don't cheat on your
mommy I'm I'm the number one mommy
remember that Cobo boo
[Music]
boo we got to do so much together
already Sweet Memories like we hung out
IRL in Indonesia but also in Japan and
you know we did the the the song
together yeah so we already had a lot of
great
opportunities M but I hope it's it's not
going to you know end I hope it will
will
[Music]
last Kobo show up where are you
Kobo
[Music]
bu her fans are so passionate and keep
on calling me
[Music]
mommy
like it's just so funny like other uh
girls that I'm close with their fans
they're they kind of you know stay on
the down low or something I don't know
maybe they're around but like kobo's
fans they're always asking me to collab
with Kobo again and they always call me
mom like you guys don't call me Mommy
nobody else really calls me mommy except
for Kobo and her fans like to them I'm
[Music]
Mommy so it's a really interesting
Dynamic there really funny to
me it's like I I adopted all of her
viewers as well they're all my kids what
how did this happen I didn't plan for
this I cannot afford so many
children no I don't want you guys to
call me Mommy no don't I'm your boss I'm
your
tal you can call me your oi your
boss something like that
H Auntie no don't call me
[Music]
auntie boss mommy
no no that just sounds
wrong Jai already do that with L calling
her
mommy Yeah well yeah she's like the the
she's like the Italian Mommy that's like
it's kind of different
okay we're already finished with the ID
chart let me show
[Music]
you
nice so Lisa Lisa we should collab again
I want to sing together MAA why did we
miss the eclipse let's overlap soon
okay y I should draw her back why her
dump be so famous and mine not what the
hell
Ollie we're currently in syn but
probably going to change
soon Ana love hate all the same if you
know play the game waiton do thanks for
inviting me to your fre maybe freie Pabi
again
[Music]
soon uh Zetta she's so fashionable let's
go shopping IRL Kaa let's play Minecraft
very helpful and reliable makes me a bit
nervous and B her friends are so
passionate and keep calling me Mom
yippe you know what this
means I perhaps could show you my 2.0
now but I don't know I don't like get
like I it's not like that crazy
different I mean besides my Expressions
I would say there's like not
really much
different oh there's not much you can do
any anyway like you know I don't have
like uh props that you can make jiggle
because why would you make my shield and
my sword
jiggle four hats extra hats would be
nice all right then uh I'm
thinking um going to well green screen
never
works except for maybe a darker green
screen nothing ever Works honestly um
but I just want you know
clean clean
background so first you look
at my
1.0 J
jfyi myth were the last ones to get 2.0
While others were getting
3.0 so it's pretty pretty late for this
uh 3.0 will be surely like an even more
interesting grander upgrade uh two 2.0
we were already pretty like like how to
say flexible with 1.0 already when we
first came out people I remember people
were looking at me and saying oh my God
she looks like 3D who Su because at the
time you know I got KY Papa and KY
Papa's rigging was very different from
the other rigging others
rigging uh like it was like known to be
extremely flexible big movement range
and all that within
Hollow
yeah yeah yeah yeah so there were a few
other examples on the Japanese side but
everybody who got key Papa were being
told like oh my God you look like you're
[Music]
3D so I was quite excited about that
back then I was quite happy with it now
4 years in we're getting our 2.0
finally uh so let me show you just like
generally I don't know why I have my
arms crossed right now actually I know
why because I wanted to show you one
thing that I never noticed I wonder if
you guys noticed this um but when I
crossed my arms there was something here
here uh no here see wait do you see
this on the where the like the arms like
they cut into my body can you
tell here do you see
yeah so I got that
fixed I didn't notice that until now
when I was like asked okay anything we
can fix
mhm it's hard now that I want to show it
I I find it hard to trigger it but yeah
yeah oh there you yeah yeah oh there you
see yeah so that got
fixed uh you'll see but generally okay
so we have but just you know normal
shoes this is two this 1.0 okay just uh
original a little bit of a little bit of
Shadow when I bend my
knees this is as much as I can bend
them I don't know if I can bend them
more actually uh in the 2.0 I didn't
try then we
have you
know little bit little bit of movement
movement on the Belt
here I didn't really check if the belt
looks
like different much I mostly looked at
the face we'll see register all of this
information you can probably also tell
when I look
down something some angle changes here
with the legs like yeah you know they
get a little bit thicker
somehow and yeah um this is this is uh I
well I never got 2.0 but after our
reveal they asked us if there's anything
about about the riging generally that
they want we want to adjust and I said
make my boobs less jiggly because they
were so like fluffy jiggly I didn't like
that I wanted a more realistic
bounce so that did I don't think they
changed anything about that in the 2.0
this is still 1.0 okay still
1.0 and then here we have me so as I
said I already had quite a range
originally but I guess like one thing
you could say is when I look up to the
side like this
up there's some improvements that could
be made in terms of the flatness of the
face I guess oh thanks for the
raid um yeah I don't know what else what
else you know I'm already so
beautiful and of course do you remember
I haven't used my I haven't shown my
turkey in like maybe 3 years
I have this turkey the turkey legs but I
don't think anything was adjusted or
changed there to be honest we'll see
we'll see we'll see and we have The
Sword and the shield the sword
oh well you know it's you see some kind
of perspective going on
there this
is this is as far as it goes I don't
know if that range is going to be
extended and we see a little bit of a
glow on the shield The Shield is pretty
dope and okay wait I think there's one
thing that I noticed uh let's look at
the
sleeves let's take in the sleeves maybe
that's going to look a little bit nicer
in the 2.0 I'm not sure I'm not sure
about
anything
uh ah oh and when I when I take out the
sword and shield look at my chest
just this once you have permission
thanks for the
memberships so right you know huh see
what happens there look at my chest who
and just recently I
realized
that well you know I knew that this was
happening and I I knew that the badge
was you know kind of you know it looks
like the shield and
everything uh the shield and the sword
combined but I I didn't realize that you
could do the same with the big version
of
it didn't realize that you could in
theory put the sword into the shield
there just like with the badge I thought
that was just like a way to combine it
nicely into a
badge here didn't realize that you would
be able to do that in the like real
versions
too like there's literally a slot right
there that's why there's the ups and
[Music]
downs on the
shield I I guess it has the perfect
shape to put that sword in that's why
the sword is so small guys that's why
the sword is so
small
unbelievable it all makes sense now well
and of course you know I have hats this
hat yeah and this
hat is quite wobbly this
[Music]
hat looks pretty big when I look over
here and then both
hats yeah two hats a Mana
hey yeah they still
exist okay all right I will now reveal
my
2.0 are you ready
oh wait no wait no not yet let me I just
want to want to remind you okay so when
I this is my normal expression hi waa
this is my normal expression right in
1.0 we're still in
1.0
um well my eyebrows are fixed they can't
like be anything else than this angle
they can move up and down but they can't
change angle keep that in mind
and my nose might look a bit different
too
later now this is my happy we have five
Expressions there's normal happy sad
angry and surprised
and my happy expression is a bit
difficult it locks me into this happy
mouth and my eyes
see normal happy they kind of go down a
little bit but it just it doesn't look
too different so I uh in the future for
like uh future outfits I sometimes asked
or I always asked them to add a blush to
the Happy expression at least to
differentiate it a little bit um but I
always had to use like points for that
and then it takes away possibilities to
do uh to use points for other things
like hairstyle and so on uh even even if
it was implemented once I had to for
every other outfit I had to use points
to get my blush again so now perhaps the
default will have the blush by default
in the happy expression and then I don't
have to pay for it
anymore yeah so happy expression no
blush now but perhaps blush later and
let's see how locked in we will be
this's a sad
expression I don't
think there'll be much of a change here
this angry
[Music]
expression don't think there will be
much of a change here either and this is
surprise expression now here I'm also I
my eyebrows are locked into being like
happy my mouth isn't locked into a shape
but you
know yeah
H also no wink cannot blink in this
expression gy money okay now that we
know this have you written everything
down to compare I wish I could put like
both 1.0 and 2.0 on the screen at the
same time but I can't so uh you have to
remember all of
this all right let me reveal to you my
2.0
[Music]
please wait please hold the line are you
ready yay
[Music]
[Applause]
perfect I
know
yay I was just I was just
kidding I was just kidding I'm
sorry I'm
sorry do you want to see the real
one
okay but
to I don't know if it's see even like
worth it to reveal it like that but
we're going to reveal like from the from
the
feet wait which
one oopsie this
one
okay T wow so go same
feet uh yeah looks like I can't bend
more this seems to be
same same here same I think no same same
same this all seems to be the same I
think this same
same
same same kind of like movement I
think
but I didn't ask for this and I don't
know if we'll ever like really need this
but
wow I can take the the thing off let's
wobble in the B oh yeah maybe
wow which implies that now because the
we always had this lore thing it says
don't use belt if I take it off does
that mean I I'm ready to unlock and lock
in and Hench
in I don't know you see an improvement
yeah yeah I think maybe like the way the
Bel moves is less wobbly which in this
case cuz it's a like um you know it's
not a soft fabric or anything the the
the thing the badge uh it's probably a
good
thing
yeah but yeah we can remove it so let's
remove
it uh yeah here uh we
fixed uh this
problem now I'm too I can't trigger it
well it's fixed anyway
[Music]
no
and we still got sword and
shield H I
think is there more movement and I think
the sleeves kind of look different a
little
bit but I could be
wrong I feel like the
way the poofy arms the sleeves they look
more like I don't know 3D less flat
maybe
maybe and the movement of the shield I
feel like it's different too I don't
know it's hard to tell when it's not
side by
side um oh just up and
down I don't know if there's more
movement there the the way the booies
jle or should be
same but also
I can take this badge off now
too I mean
cool uh okay I
mean that will change my
life uh yeah more toggles why not why
not why not why not guys now I don't
look like I show up to henin anymore
maybe now without all the stuff maybe I
just look like a normal totally normal
fast food
[Music]
worker a little a bit little bit more
casual the hair looks more fluid um I
think the hair there shouldn't be much
more difference but we'll see we'll see
okay okay you know there not much
difference there in general oh here we
go the face is really like the
most different
part are you ready hi oh my god there
she is okay I'm I'm staying quite kind
of
expressionless are you
oh so this is my default face and now my
eyebrows are not locked in
anymore so I can do funny things like
this and I don't have to push the
buttons to be sad
anymore but I feel like you know I have
to like be really frowning but I can
also like have sad eyebrows and
laugh which is kind of
cute sad
sad happy sad I'm doing face gymnastics
here yeah I've I've been after four
years I've been getting so lazy in terms
of pushing
buttons um so I'm glad I can now change
my expressions with the eyebrows to a
certain degree on my own without yeah
pushing
buttons it's really good I think
and wait I don't know how I can wait
wait how do I
do but not happy mouth
um that's hard to do my my face
gymnastics are not working
working but I like that I can do Angry
Eyebrows with happy
[Music]
mouth Gremlin it's kind of hard I have
to raise them really high so we're still
working on this behind the scenes um cuz
when I actually look angry often it will
give me sad eyebrows
instead um so it's not 100% accurate yet
um but if I want to do Angry Eyebrows I
have to like raise them really high and
kind of raise the outer edges IRL which
is not how I would normally do
it but for now it's funny and cute yeah
so and then you can see I have more of a
nose now and the shape of my head is
more um
round look
can you
tell my cheeks are I think a little bit
a little bit rounder a little
bit H when I look down the nose is also
I I wasn't sure if I if this looks weird
or
not my nose is very apparent when I look
down too
[Music]
yay and now my happy expression finally
has blush and you know what's really
cute these eyebrows are also not locked
in anymore and my mouth is not locked in
anymore either before it was just
constant capital D and my eyebrows were
constant happy
too um but we have blush and so now with
the uh versatile eyebrows I can
do this is like when I'm I don't know
happy and sad I don't know something
like a you guys are so
sweet this hits hard I think and
[Music]
then you know what I mean
I don't know how to uh describe
it w my eyebrows are so
exhausted so in case I get too exhausted
to force my eyebrows so high up I can
still you know toggle to
angry and toggle too sad without having
to do face gymnastics thank God wo no I
can't raise one eyebrow M I feel
like I was thinking about it
but I wasn't sure if it's if it might
not actually look too
funky maybe in the future and then my
crazy
expression the eyebrows aren't locked in
anymore even so I can look really
crazy or
capture
[Music]
this I think that's really
good because before my eyebrows in the
crazy expression were always happy
[Music]
it's so
funny oh okay really exhausting for my
eyebrows still can't blink no I kept it
like
this C can't blink even
in her crazy expression some people can
some people can't I'm just built like
that
yay I hope you like this because that's
pretty much all there is to it I
think uh I mean I still have the T oh uh
still have the
turkey I don't think the turkey changed
uh ah my hats I don't think the hats uh
changed it all in terms of how they move
or so no they're the
same they look the
same no I don't have more hats I
[Music]
wish so originally when they first
handed me over the 2.0 and we're like
hey how is this I was like M it barely
looks different from the 1.0 and you
know why because the eyebrows didn't
move uh differently like it was all the
same and then I looked at Callie's
reveal and she had movable eyebrows I
was like
oh if I had
that H that would be bigger impact so
they were like okay are you sure
because wait
H can
I can I move my eyebrows into no it's
just because I closed my eye
right yeah I don't think no I can't move
them individually it's just what I close
my
[Music]
eye and what was I saying oh yeah so
then they started working on the eyebrow
thing and you know a lot of adjustments
are necessary because of how my face
Works um but now it's you know I think
it's pretty good pretty useful to be
able to move my eyebrows like that but
that's the I would say the the biggest
and most significant thing about 2.0 3.0
you know uh now we can start working on
it and all future outfits will be on 2.0
the previous outfits I don't think
there's a plan so far to turn them into
2.0 they will stay like that most likely
but future outfits will be made with 2.0
and then once I have 3.0 they will be
made with 3.0 I think No Maybe not maybe
not because
3.0 I don't know doesn't that also
include like the keyboard and stuff I
don't know we'll see we'll see no but
that doesn't mean that I don't I will
not use my outfits anymore I will 100%
still use them I think they are amazing
anyway your mouth checking is a lot
better I did ask them to make it more
sensitive but when I compare it to to my
I don't know cuz on my phone in front of
me I have my 1.0 and somehow it looks
the same to me but at the same time time
I'm I'm I'm agreeing with you I'm not
sure 3D 2.0 when well I made my own 3D
2.0 before and revealed it not so long
ago uh on my channel uh it's my own so
it has blend shapes 51 blend shapes so
if you're interested in that it looked
really cute it looked really
cute so now we can return to well our
our little Mission
yeah let me put away
the the oily chicken
turkey do you like the new Wawa is it uh
uncanny is it
weird my side profile is definitely
different so you might want to get used
to
[Music]
it now I can do this like Derpy face
that Kelly does with her 2.0
now like she has the sad eyebrows so
much while she's
[Laughter]
laughing oh yeah I did reveal it
now
yippee can't wait for 2.0 S changes yeah
now now you maybe know why I originally
said I don't want to reveal it because
at that point the eyebrows were like
were just the same so I was like
H not sure if there's like oopsie that
much difference you guys might be
like
what you
know so once I got those changes I was
like okay okay okay this is this this
just is
interesting yeah my nose my nose has
grown oh oh it's so pointy invisible
now it's it definitely felt uncanny to
me like I don't know do I like it do I
don't not like it this nose looks
[Music]
funny oh you're making Pinocchio jokes
uh-huh funny well well well now
ta I made an y chart as well of
course and we're going to fill it out
now just like the ID chart let me switch
over and like copy paste this because
it's very
[Music]
useful Amy yeah we start with
amyyy sure
[Music]
okay let's go I came in a great time
yeah you did you skipped the whole intro
we skipped the ID chart too though
that's sad you shouldn't have skipped
the ID
chart
okay I don't
know what was my original impression of
Amen oh so TCH Savvy savvy is that how
you write that or is it double v think
one that's definitely one fault I
[Music]
had cute
design cute gramlin
voice I don't remember it's four years
ago
a
flat I I thought she was
[Music]
flat she was hiding her
assets
ah no definitely like helpful since the
beginning um and she was very
knowledgeable about everything cuz I was
I was uh you know like not so
knowledgeable and like she gave me
advice and helped me uh for like uh like
you know how to do things like
uh cuz I wanted to make
a uh streaming
layout um because I don't know at the
time I didn't have money and uh we could
have like kind of
like commissioned and then like so to
say borrowed money from the company but
I didn't want to because I didn't think
I would make much
money and so I'mma kind of help
me uh making the streaming layout as in
like she told me where to get assets
from and she provided me with vectors
like there's this like website where she
told me oh use this website I can
download the vectors for you and I'm
like oh let's go I don't even know how
vectors work and she was like okay I'll
I'll uh turn them into like pngs for
you mhm so that was really helpful my
first my first stream layout was uh put
together by me with uh you know she
downloaded the things that I chose for
me and I put it together and she also
made the Stinger for me pretty early on
she made this like Stinger I I drew
fried chicken and stuff and then she
made this like uh Stinger OBS stinger
when you change scenes you know the
chicken was flying around nowadays I
don't have a stinger anymore what
happened I I used to have a stinger even
after that when I changed it but then I
I think when I switched to a new PC or
so when
I installed OBS a new or so somewhere I
must have gotten rid of it or I lost it
actually
[Music]
H yeah oh well cuz at some point some
fan made one for me free to use and I
used it because it looked really
nice but yeah I don't I don't know where
that one is
either well now
[Music]
impression what's my impression Now what
is my impression now I don't
know um what's my
[Music]
impression I can't think
anymore um well she's obviously still
tech
savvy um she's still cute and everything
but she's not
flat but I'm not going to write that
down
text I chok takes up too much space to
write
that so
[Music]
Innovative
Innovative wait my brain really isn't
working ah
likes moms well not particularly I
wouldn't really say that she just
because you know that's more like an old
thing an old
[Music]
meme but you know I might uh continue
her mom Legacy because I I I've been
known as well for being very popular
with the moms
they really like me recently in Italy
too I I was like a mom was clinging on
to me a lot a mom that I didn't know
before I met someone's mom and don't
it's not L's
Mom it's just a mom and she was like
so
so she loved me
[Music]
and then she she was like so excited to
talk to me kept on talking to me she was
cute she was really really
[Music]
hyper was this mom drunk no I don't
think she was drunk
no no no no no not not Mama Lisa no no
no
no just like a you know some Mom some
random
[Music]
mom nothing be Brown Pound no not
crony's Mom no just a random mom not
whole life
mom yeah I just walk around in Italy on
the streets and a random
mom decided to make me her new child no
it wasn't like that but you know it was
a pretty random mom like I didn't know
her
before just let's just say it was a
random Italian mom
anyway I'm it uh oh God I can't think ah
well okay okay okay okay I think
[Music]
like I I feel like we've Bond it so much
over the years but I still get nervous
about um like what she thinks of
me I want her to like me you know so I
still get really conscious nervous about
it
and you
know the OSI
nerves ah well okay she became my
OSI like seeing what she
does like right next to her you know
um metaphorically and in reality uh it's
just really impressive and and I I love
her creativity and
her innovativeness obviously so yeah she
became my oce I've been saying this for
a while I'm number one Amit
[Music]
Gosling
um she's she's um she's
caring cared for
me when I stayed over and she cooked for
me
yeah and she did so much for me she she
uh because of her I was able to have a
3D music video you know and the 3D Live
she organized my first fry life my
birthday life in what was it
202 one or two I don't know um that
wouldn't have been possible without her
it was really w
we worked so hard on that we worked so
tirelessly for hours and hours uh on
that like because we had to take a
million takes and we had to take
separate takes and combine them because
uh at the time her Studio was still new
and um recording motion it it was still
kind of janky here and
there so yeah we worked so hard on that
and the result was so great and I'm so
I'm so glad I'm so I'm so
thankful for what she did for
me 3D MV and
concert yeah uh I love her own
Fredy content like when she just messes
around with Fredy she's always so funny
she's so cute and all her different
amerse characters and so
on yeah she's just like this whole this
whole I don't know she's like her whole
[Music]
circus
and the comment you know well basically
now it will be I guess related to her
leaving h
M thank you
[Music]
for helping
us out
and grinding with
us for four
years I love you
forever
I'm oh
[Music]
I'm going to miss her so
much legit I'm
just it's going to be so sad I'm going
to miss her I know I can talk to her you
know and this and that but it's just
going to feel different you know it
doesn't matter if I can talk to her like
off screen off stream and all that
doesn't matter it's still different
still sad
me but it's okay I will support her in
her Endeavors
and it really makes sense for her in my
opinion and I wish the best for her and
I'm going to be observing
her
closely I'll be right behind her
watching her every
step
yeah and she really has been
playing such an important role in myth
and Yan and Holo as a whole left such a
big
Mark and I don't think anybody will ever
forget her and nobody will ever replace
her many many things I could say and
write about her but only so little
space
yeah I'm going to miss
her oh I don't want to cry let's write
something about GAA [\h__\h] um GAA original
impression
H quiet very quiet I we barely talked in
the beginning also because of time zones
uh
quiet
um
well it was It was kind of difficult to
get an impression of
her
[Music]
yeah still quiet a little bit a little
bit
shy maybe uh but very very very
mysterious to
[Music]
me hard to read yeah that's that's also
true let me cut this off a little bit
oops
[Music]
ah the ah was also like oh oh that's H
genius interesting that's how you go
about it I see I have fought so hard
about my first tweet and she just writes
ah it's that
simple ah
[Music]
and now uh what did I write now
impression now
impression
sister I feel like when we spend time
together in Japan like I see her being a
little bit
loner so so I try
to What's The Word
stick with
her
[Music]
and be her
Rock I don't know if she noticed or if
she feels like that too but
yeah um I see her being a little bit
anxious or so here and there so I try to
just be around especially when there's
like a lot of other girls from different
Generations or even branches then I'm
like oh you know she seems very quiet
not so talkative at the moment so let me
let me just you know make sure she has
me so I try to put all my attention onto
her so that she doesn't feel like I
don't know bored or I don't think she
would feel bored but I just wanted to
know that I'm I'm here for her
maybe like this is a lot of IRL talk but
um I think there's like a good example
from one of the the Christmas VR chat
stream where you can see in my POV cuz
GAA didn't have a POV um but in my POV
you can see like I noticed that she
separated herself from the group so I
found her and then I was like okay I'm
going to go over to her spend time with
her keep her company M check in with her
see what she's
doing
yeah so I always try to keep an eye on
her but I feel like it's still a little
bit hard to get a hold of her um so I I
worry a lot about
[Music]
her Gooby DEA talk to
me more
[Music]
yeah what's up gooda tell me talk to
me which I guess could just be the
comments too but uh it's also my
impression oopsie oh also
like why should I write
this lovely voice
and
uh h
natural no I don't know what to
say like her singing really it has a
really special
charm which her whole personality has a
special charm let's write that
[Music]
down I want to hang out with her again
let's do
something let's game let's go go go
gaming oh uh what's that game
[Music]
Outlast let's play games that aren't
horror
please
um like it's for her I I would like
literally accept anything you know
um but ideally ideally I would like to
play something that wasn't
horror yeah she's so she's so brave I
guess I feel like she seemed pretty
brave when we were playing it together
when she was like observing me play it
but she on her own it's not like she's
that strong when it comes to horror
games
I don't think she is that's not my
impression of
[Music]
her she just like
screaming I like her I like her rambling
noises
SK
originally I it we can put this into
original impression to be honest because
uh originally I asked her like my I
thought she was um she had a lot of
knowledge in
memes teach me so I asked her to teach
me like I I I kind of like pitched a
collab
idea to have her teach me memes cuz I
she I thought you knew a lot about
them um nowadays I feel think I'm I'm
I'm somewhat informed on the memes but
this collab never happened I feel like
it would have been difficult anyway to
put it into a proper
stream she knows old memes what about
new memes I feel like maybe for new
memes bioo is number one but those are
just Tik Tok memes and honestly I I'm
like face palming whenever I hear about
Tik Tok
memes Goa knows beyond the Tik Tok memes
I think it's more than just
[Music]
that okay so if
Ena what was my original
impression so artist probably yeah she
showed us her art pretty early like
right away I
[Music]
think yeah and very calming voice of
course
so she's my impression was you know just
like oh calm calm
[Music]
character what else I wonder I should go
back in our chat
[Music]
logs I don't think I had like a that
much of an impression did I I don't
know but then now it's like Tako toi
sales team we do so much promotion
together
I I literally just oh cut off oopsie I
literally just got
another like sponsorship offer for the
future quite far in the future but it's
again takoor and I'm like what
again you guys keep on asking
specifically takori what's going
on I mean you guys say we're such a
great sales I feel like I could do a
great job with other girls too but sure
okay takoor it is uh I
I um wait as a comment I want to write
sorry for
stealing stealing your
CSS uh off
collab
continue how do you write that
continuation continue
when we ended up not having time at all
for it H in Japan we were going to do it
she I was surprised that she wanted to
continue it and then it well
unfortunately no
time please take
time to rest you know she always tired
she always busy
yeah uh now I'm
also I am happy to see her uh dance
Journey you know what I
mean she's been really excited about
dancing and I've been watching her and
she's you know picking up coros quite
fast doing a good job when she's not
super sleepy and sleep deprived at
[Music]
least
um
yeah what's a CSS it's like a a code
uh for like all kinds of things I stole
her chat box CSS for uh OBS not this one
right now
but yeah watching myth in General Grow
you know while I'm next to them it's
very has been very excited
exciting what else we still have some
space
[Music]
h h
M
tomorrow uh
also uh not not really the dumpy for her
it's more like the back but people were
impressed by the dumpy too but that was
like you know the shape of the skirt but
like why why everybody get famous with
their
dumpy that was more the back
was just going to bring it up because I
brought it up with Yi but not quite the
same
[Music]
here
uh gamer she's she's uh surprisingly a
gamer I didn't expect that in the
beginning actually like you know when I
saw her game interests I was like oh we
have some similarities in
like similar game interest to a certain
extent in
certain
ways um yeah but now like seeing her
play like El ring and stuff she gets
locked in kind
of yeah and I'm sure she's like super
good in like you
know ff14 didn't she play
that mm RPGs I don't know how she's
doing in GTA but uh I think I think
think that's not like quite real uh GTA
so you can't really tell if she would be
good in a real GTA game
but generally yeah I've I've come to
realize she's quite the gamer
H okay original
impression Midway impression we're going
to add one here because original
impression
is
like
oh
we
should do stuff
together because we were in Japan at the
time yeah and I was really like anxious
about just like I don't know everything
so I was hoping that we could bond and
you know Takami it just made sense to me
and she she also said yeah makes
sense it was in the middle of Corona so
we couldn't
travel so you know we were kind of like
the only ones who could meet and I
really wanted to take advantage of that
now mid my impression the reason why I'm
adding that is because like now
impression is also very different from
Midway and beginning
um Midway impression you know we had
some ups and downs and I would say there
was some downs but those were necessary
perhaps for the
UPS um so I was like I think around the
time when I left
Japan I was like
H not sure how she
feels about me uh I I I feel like we
didn't
really H vibe that well at the time but
now we are in sync and I don't mean in a
period S period
sense but just like our work ethic
and um just way of thinking so that
makes it really nice to just be with her
and it made
takoni better than
ever and I
hope and I I know that we will stick
through
together as far as we can fight we stay
strong we'll be there together Takami
forever
H we can rely on each other
and just you
know we know we can count on each other
I know we can count on each
[Music]
other yeah
takam he y y y
yay oops what the there you go I I will
I will move it don't worry don't worry I
will move it I will move it I will move
it we have finished off myth now we're
going to do a
I so she was our first Kai in the Ian
which was super
exciting but uh yeah now
impression but I I don't think
we um like interacted much because she
was like
managed kind of like it felt like so
separate and uh because she was a v
singer so felt kind of
separated and therefore there were like
little interactions and she's she's
never even now she's never been much
active in the
Discord
uh so
I don't know like when you interact it's
like either IRL or on stream but or
maybe in DMS
recently wait I will write this down now
recently we've been talking a lot more
and getting a lot closer getting much
closer
finally it like it it took a long time
to really
um you know get to know each other more
that was really recently like this
year cuz I invited her to you know the
collab with Quon and la and we talked a
lot there and we talk a lot about like
music production right now and how
things are behind the scenes for both of
us uh in in terms of like you know
everything you know complicated yeah the
nails collab too the nails it it started
with the nails collab I guess
M but then there was a big break again
because you know just wasn't in Japan
and so
on but from there on basically for the
nails collab I I think I knew okay Cali
was going to be in the collab who else
do I call uh cuz I kind of wanted a
third person and so because it had to be
someone in Japan I was like you know
what
waa got to you know try to
bond with people you don't have much of
a bond with yet let's just do it and
then I invited Iris and uh no regrets
really it was a really pleasant
experience and from then
on especially recently we've been doing
a lot more together and I think it's a
mutual uh
[Music]
agreement um she's funny and so
energetic uh it's like I think a huge
gap more for
her I didn't expect that in the
beginning at all that she would be
so so wobbly bouncy and you know
especially in 3D she's just so funny
like IRL so you can now see it in in
Fredy mhm
drun drun
this is like even more even more
so she's maybe maybe the only drunk
person I will
tolerate wait I really don't have much
because like she I should write
something else but we just didn't like
talk ah I really liked her design you
know her artist
I was like
damn
beautiful beautiful design I mean it
changed but I liked it since the
[Music]
beginning yeah red juice Papa so good so
freaking
good and then comment
um h
[Music]
H collab when uh yeah I guess we never h
ah we did have a one-on-one collab right
where I taught her uh
German use Discord more use Discord
more no no generally I I just want
to hope we can continue our um building
our
[Music]
bond let's sing together
soon yeah that makes sense to
[Music]
me okay moving on to the green one the
green one
oo let's go wait what was my first
impression I feel
like I must have been
like
um probably like excited about her being
a cat lady fellow cat
lady sweet voice so sweet so soft spoken
yeah
ooh I love
green I I was just excited you know but
someone green
[Music]
and maybe teach ASMR to me please but so
far nothing yet I I was hoping like
maybe off collapse sometime but it's
difficult I guess I got to go visit her
[Music]
so okay now impress uh I feel like with
FAA too because H yeah so at the time it
was Council and when
Council came out you know I again had
the time zone
problem I really
couldn't Bond much with
them uh at least not like it just didn't
happen naturally I would have to like
go out of my way and ask for collapse
and I mean I could only do so many at a
time
um and yeah so it was really difficult
it it takes a while you know because
like we wouldn't like spontaneously meet
anywhere in like Minecraft or so either
because of the time
zones yeah and right it twice uh but I
would say
h let me
write
um what should we
ah
fils
uh FS
[Music]
AI healing
type
uh space to get slot I don't know roll
inan which I think you know she has her
Niche it's perfect for her and she's
doing it really well
mhm comfy Vibes so true so
true a really
cute and
dress fashion
sense reminds me of my old
self yeah I think the first time I met
her I was
like is that me from the
past like the way she styled her hair as
well it's like oh my God that's how I
used to style my
hair so
cute so freaking
[Music]
cute and then uh it's a
comment I
secretly
always um
think
about joining and helping her in
MC but well she's been doing it alone
for so long that I feel like now it's
like
weird
like but I watch her sometimes and I'm
like ah she's still still on it I wish I
could help I want to help but I I don't
really have like a Kake like
[Music]
but uh I don't want to
[Laughter]
bother like really i' I've been thinking
about it so much like oh oh she's
working on it again ah you know I like
Minecraft and I want to help him she
probably doesn't need my help anymore at
this point she's so
far you guys say she wants
help well I've made my intentions or my
my thoughts clear now um f you need help
hit me up I am willing to work with
[Music]
you yeah I'd love to help
her yeah and I'm also thinking like she
might just enjoy some company right I I
love Minecraft I'm also kind of sad that
it died off so her like still sticking
with it I really respect that and I wish
I could support her in that but it's
hard when nobody else plays you
know okay moving
over I'm awaiting your DM
FAA let's move to quason who was on the
thumbnail did you read what I wrote uh
woman of the year but it it was cut off
there it could have also been and this
makes even more sense woman ner of the
Year such a womanizer womanizer oh woman
woman B you you you are you you you
are my original impression of her ah I
was um you know uh love the artist holy
[\h__\h] I was like Wow Holo Ian is bringing
out the most insane
artist Love The
Voice debut
stream big
concern I remember watching her Dem
stream and I'm like oh my God
she ended so early she seemed to not
have much to talk about uh y like I was
so
worried yeah but you know she's gotten
into her element and she she is doing so
well now um yeah she speedran the debut
i and she stalled yeah that was her
stalling and I what was it like 40
minutes or so
like nowadays like shorter debut is
becoming more and more normal and a
thing and somehow
popular um but at the time like I was
like yab how can I keep it under an hour
like or like exactly an hour I think a
lot of us were struggling also to fit
everything into an hour people like
Ollie as well you know who like talk so
much Yap so
[Music]
much I I don't know I feel like 1 hour
is still fine um I like it like on the
long side not longer than 1 hour just
you know exactly 1 hour because you know
I think there's a good amount of things
you can share that uh especially like
nowadays that debuts have become so much
more creative uh with like people always
coming up with funny interesting ideas
in little games and so on which I think
is also difficult for newer me newer
Generations because now they feel like
oh they have to come up with
something um for myth it wasn't quite
yet like
that um but with Council I think that
kind of started because uh I think
before Council there was also maybe was
there cuz I yeah id id second gen
debuted before Council right so yeah
more and more girls were coming in doing
really interesting things in their debut
so if I were to debut like now I would
be so pressured to have to come up with
something that hasn't been done before
and is really
interesting okay I did like this little
thing with the book that I drew the lore
book um I tried we we already tried to
be a little bit creative like not super
basic debut a little bit but like
nowadays it's
crazy
H yeah
so uh I'm sure they were all really
nervous obviously but she's doing so
well now my impression now is oh my
God makes me
[Music]
nervous just like with Amy like okay not
it has changed a little bit
um ever since New York I feel a a little
bit more confident in the fact that she
might
just uh tolerate me enough to like
me but
until before that I was more like oh man
I want her to like me and sometimes I
think she likes me but I'm not sure I
want her to like me more because I like
her she's so
[Music]
cool she's so cool
she's so
cool she's so
cool
and she makes me
swoon She's So Perfect uh love her role
playing and her like in games like Ian
Reco but also in general like her whole
um perfect
stick um her
attitude love her
sassiness I love the way she talks to
her
fans love the way she yaps I love I love
her so
much she's kind of kind of an oi of
[Music]
mine hold my ores not going to
lie and and now
comment let's honestly go to the
males to the
males I think she's really considering
[Music]
it
um let's massage each other
more
H
um I love talking to
her she's so
cool um can you tell I'm kind of
swooning over
her why do
she why does she always go to EU but
never hits me up
[Music]
what the hell
crony
oh
qule I love her I love
her so funny okay sorry sorry I need to
calm down uh crony makes me so
nervous H what was my impression of M
well another bird oh my God
honi is
growing and then I was like kind of like
panicking like oh we were tur ducking
what
now like I I I had like no like honestly
I'm so happy that she is uh you know in
h now but at the time I was like wait
they added another bird how many more
birds are they going to add is is
because like now fans are expecting me
to add every bird into hotori
but like how when is that going to end
how many birds are there going to be how
big is this group going to be and this
like you know like so far I've been like
really lucky I like all the birds that
they've been bringing out like I've been
kind of vibing with them but you know
you can't always expect that that might
not always be the case so but then like
if they naturally get like forced into
honi just by being a bird I like you
know worrying about it like ah business
business decisions but birds of f flock
together you
know so I really I really loved her
singing and her
creativity and I thought
uh I thought like oh she's like perfect
perfect for holon actually cuz she can
sing so
well and she's kind of a
freak kind of a crazy girl I like
it it's SP CAU up oh
there you
[Music]
go yeah my now impression I didn't
really I think for the longest time I
thought she was so like sweet and say so
um but my God she's
terrifying is that how you write it
Terri terrifying
is that how you read
it nightmare fuel
yes she scares me no she doesn't really
scare me but um that's what makes her so
interesting right like that Gap Gap is
so
[Music]
interesting and she's always up for
like anything
any kind of collab or uh whether it's
like watching [\h__\h]
Twilight or doing girls talk with me
like anything she's up for anything
she's so
fun yeah so I don't know I'm so excited
to have her in
h let's do new H song
soon hopefully and um BD Bond must grow
stronger
glad that you happened to be a bird fate
it's fate it must be
[Music]
fate I feel like she also really like
all these girls all these girls you know
fill some role and and have a
a big part in
Ian I love the world that Mum feels like
she's you you get to know her and you
feel like oh she's such a sweet singer
she's so talented holy [\h__\h] but then
she's so cursed so
funny it's just so
funny oh where are we here all right all
right all
right it's Bay time all right I remember
my original impression for BA quite well
cuz again holy [\h__\h] another insane
artist Choice uh but also
Australia made me immediately feel like
a connection even though I'm not
Australian but at the time I was still
calling myself Australian every once in
a while
Australian
Bond and I really liked her uh energy
and
uh character so I thought immediately I
was like
huh I want to be the first Senai she
collabs with if she will have
me want to be first
collab cuz I I really believed in her
success and I thought like oh my God
she's going to do so
[Music]
great and I wanted to support her in
that
[Music]
so I don't know if you guys remember but
I was her first Senai collab we did uh
the I think the BMB diffusal game and
then after that you know I continued to
try to you know build upon that and did
the snackbox reveiew which ended up you
know with
s that was
uh funny because like uh ba like I sent
Bae a snackbox I think did I did I no I
think was I going to no because I was
doing generally like snackbox reviews
from all kinds of countries and I was
like oh she can send me an Australian
snackbox did I send her one of mine I'm
not sure I think did I yeah but after
yeah she sent me the Australian snackbox
first but then I don't know why anymore
but she just couldn't be there for the
review with me
and so I had
S stand in and she um explained all the
snacks to me it was quite
funny yeah we had a Golden Gate time oh
that's a good time good
memory yeah yeah yeah yeah cuz we had we
had two
Australians right oh my God that's so
crazy nowadays they don't seem to bring
out the Australians
anymore
H damn what happened with those
[Music]
Australians well well well now
impression is uh like oh my God
she's the most insane dancer
ever crazy like the the body
control is so so
Top
Notch I want to be like
that yeah we haven't been doing that
much but I feel like you
know we have like a lot of similarities
and stuff you know also game interest
like she's she's gotten so deep into
Yakuza which I've been playing for a
while too so we can connect over Yakuza
and stuff
and
K-pop yeah now we're doing World Tour
together
so we're going to be doing a bunch more
stuff together in World Tour World Tour
gang it is
all do you do you was
legendary wasn't
it yeah sore sore sore
sore sore sore
[Music]
sore also I love her F like man why why
does she have such sick F can I get
those FES too what kind of workout does
she do I mean I like I I really you know
what I
mean those f are so defined in her free
model freed Model F fight F such a
difficult word okay we have reached
Advent and
ooh original
impression
H
mysterium
and like
oh oh she's
like super
creative and like kind of reminds me in
like how she does things uh of am
[Music]
sh and I love her
design oh and the artist like Oh The
Moment I Saw the design uh I was like ho
holy
[\h__\h] I've been following her artist for
a
while oh God the art so
gorgeous Peak absolute
Peak what did she do for her
de we stream again I don't remember what
did she
do what did she do it's not even that
long
ago what is
[Music]
it she yapped she scared
people talked about bugs H rob the bank
what did she
[Music]
but yeah I think I think um we had a
little bit of a a slow start for our
friendship and she
uh wait actually that goes into this now
impression um I've noticed she's kind of
like a
loner but she enjoys it and she's she
feels like very comfortable with that
and uh I don't know I kind of admire
that
H in a good
[Music]
way I admire
that yeah she she likes the isolation
but she's also really good with people
anyway like she's so funny
um really funny
and good for collabs because she just
yaps so well I love people who Yap so
that I can like lean back a little bit
with my
yapping really good for collabs yep yep
yep yep
yep and I
think I think um you know am is
irreplaceable but I hope that her shies
skills and ideas and
creativity
[Music]
will like I feel she's a loner you know
and she doesn't really organized
collapse but I feel like she should she
should how what not not really like fill
the void I just hope that she will kind
of
[Music]
like Take the Lead skills and ideas and
does this is this a sentence I
hope I hope
that her skills
and ideas and creativity will take the
Le
Pro projects let's do projects maybe
together even
projects also she's easy to talk to
actually
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes yes yes
yes complicated in a complicated
situation there
[Music]
mhm all right all
right here we
[Music]
go okay where am I
be
boo what was my first
impression oh my God she's so
[Music]
squeaky uh
cute
um she looks like a f emblem
character maybe that's my Fire Emblem
brain rot
at the time I didn't quite know about
her like memess and Tik Tok addiction
yet which I would put in here Tik Tok
brain
rot can be a bit much but uh it's cute
she started a lot of like good um memes
and like viral clips and all that so you
go girl you go
girl ski
yeah she's she's I think she's the
reason why I say skine like that's on
her blame
her um so
small uh cute fashion cute fashion
fashion
creative as heck because I really liked
her frw and her ideas gamer she's such a
gamer so much endurance she's a perfect
parir with
Kaa I'm so glad that you know she's so
into it so motivated I as a senpai and
as you know the first generation of the
branch I like to just see someone who's
absolutely thriving love to see her
thve and um make the most of it is small
like oh my
God she is
motivated I wanted to write caps but
it's already caps by default so there's
not much of an of a impact
[Music]
here
um uh want to see her dance uh
[Music]
journey
and dance
together yeah it's really really nice to
see how you know motivated she is for
streaming but also for like the idol
aspects as well it's really lovely as a
standby I'm so proud I'm so
proud cuz like she had no experience I
think either when it comes to dancing
but she's been doing so well she has a
talent for
[Music]
it so next is noisa
original impression
oh another
bird but oh my God someone who likes
me I was so
happy savior she's my she was my
savior cuz she came at like a really
good time for me I really needed her h
[Music]
she's so dorky she's so dorky there you
still
here [\h__\h] as heck so
sweet she's so sweet she's such an angel
[Music]
and ah I don't know I could say so many
things about her a like she oh
[Music]
well we don't do it as much anymore
maybe we should write after this stream
we so like before the whole Japan
Arc we called like so much on Discord I
never did that before with any other uh
coworker like I mean every once like
rarely like sometimes maybe but like I
never did it the way I did with her like
just after my stream she would usually
be up
so and she would maybe have watched a
little bit of it towards the end and and
then we just like talk and I'm like ah I
need to I need to vent and then she
vents back and it's just it's always
been so nice we should get back into it
with
uh now that we're both you know back
[Music]
home
yeah yeah yeah I I also love to see
her
journey and she's been doing so well I
feel like she's integrated herself so
well and she's she's
like she's
definitely like kind of the glue of
Advent she's she feel to me it feels
like she's in the middle of it like cuz
she's connected so well of all of them
and she's so loving so loving and caring
glue of Advent probably not the best
word to say get well she's sick oh
[Music]
man oh but also can I add one roast
she's uh wait here let's let's get rid
of
that dorky she's so dramatic like I love
her American dram
dramaticness cuz she will be like oh my
God like I'm dying I'm going to die like
so often it left such a huge impression
on me
[Music]
she like I'm literally
dying she's so
dramatic sorry R I love it
though jirds I'm
[Music]
sick it's so over
for musical brain
rot I'll make this a bit
smaller musical brain raw I'm I'm sorry
sorry I can't keep up with
it I'm so sorry
[Music]
W
but
anyway
um without her I
would be so [\h__\h] dumb
at this point
[Music]
probably
H thanks for
being my rock
and loving me so much I love you too
let's
marry forget about
SHI I'm your true love am I right
hey hey call me wi I miss
you why haven't to we
called recently oh you can't see that
[Music]
part Italy wasn't enough
let's meet
again come move to Europe
okay
[Music]
okay yeah no we just met but I really
enjoyed our time together let's cut it
off um
like
here I went on a tangent there I like
how you
know like all she all she reflects the
kai no no AI reflects the person oing or
something like that
because like isn't it so funny how she's
like one of the yappers and isn't she
kind of similar to me in some
ways not many ways but some
[Music]
ways it's
like it's like she um I she imprinted I
imprinted on her she imprinted on me I'm
not
sure oopsy what the hell ah
I
imprinted okay okay okay I get
[Music]
it he slapped in the same bed yeah
several times
now in the Mal Dives and in Italy like
the moment the moment like I I pretty
soon I was like uh let's go to males and
she's like
okay let's
go uh
[Music]
impression I
had many impressions for
Fu so many that I
cannot uh even put them into words but
also
uh these girls
will leave the biggest
that's word
impa how do I put this like I knew these
girls
will do so well
twins
will make people go
crazy wait who's
talking I had a hard time
differentiating their voices in the
beginning which now I feel like it's so
obvious in the beginning I was like what
wait who's talking right now cuz they
were using the same account too on
Discord and voice calls I'm like what
who's oh [\h__\h] it's embarrassing to admit
that I don't know who's talking right
[Laughter]
now yeah now it's so obvious so weird
how I mean maybe I heard a difference
but I wasn't sure who's who like I heard
a difference in oh this sounds different
but I I couldn't like um attach it
to like one of them you know what I mean
like which is
[Music]
which now you mess up in a free well
that's a different thing that's not
about the voice that's just because
they're freaking twins of course I'm
going to mix them up when they're you
[Music]
know dressed the same
way anyway they look nothing like I
mean it the it
looks on YouTube there's like color
filters and stuff I don't know uh IRL
is different maybe I wasn't wearing my
glasses they're twins
okay now
impression go
go more gole more gole please take
[Music]
care of your throat and your voice
please
[Music]
H so
funny
b um
I want to dance with the
[Music]
twins also I don't know I guess this
will end up in me writing the same thing
for both of them but I'll try to write
something else for f but um this sound
this is like more the
generic I guess the generic one uh that
kind of applies to both H
um the the wrestling
was
insane I love p LS
[Music]
too I really like that was pondering was
already my go-to uh
donut and honestly the only donut I ever
get um at Mr Donuts all the donuts are
nice too but that one is just so good I
love the the the
chewi and the sugar I just I I think I I
used to when I was like kind of younger
I used to like
things um
like donuts pastries more overloaded
with things but now I appreciate the
simple sugar
glaze just a simple sugar glaze it's
just perfect okay now uh huh how am I
going to what should
[Music]
I how do I do
this
ah now I'm impressing
um
[Laughter]
backseater um I love seeing them fight
[Music]
jokingly I love it I love the twin
banter I love the um I love The Sibling
banter
energy m
whatever I'm not going to write another
impression um except for for but I just
want to generally
say great addition to Holo
Yen
um great work epic and
drive although take
breaks well they're doing it now they're
they're more careful now somewhat
yeah um but uh I
think I think I
think I'm just like as I said like with
all of these girls like they're they're
so great they're all they all fill a
role uh fle fills a role that you know I
didn't even consider needed
filling but you know it's cut off oh God
damn it
there you go triplets
wi
um
please how to
[Music]
stay just continue doing what you
do
you you you're oh wow apost apostrophe
you're doing so great girls
[Music]
yeah thanks for hard
work
yeah okay another generation oh my God
we're almost done yay yay yay yay y uh
like writing these things down makes me
so proud like oh my God it's
like this is giving me such a strong
feeling of oh my God I'm a mother I am
mothering these
children like it's like eh it's it's
becoming so clear like all these
girls
joined like watching
maybe not necessarily actively watching
us some of them yes some of them no but
like they they stepped in our foot
prints
shoes
and like you know one day when you know
when when we might be gone they'll
continue our Legacy uh I hope and I
think these are all great girls to
continue our
Legacy well I'm hoping to stay you know
super long and all that but I'm just
saying I'm just say just don't
panic I'm just saying like if if anyone
I can like leave it to these girls I'm
just like
[Music]
glad that I have such great Co High stop
this is wholesome this is
wholesome
guys
guys stop
[Music]
no stop
panicking Mama Mia Mama
Mia okay um
Cecilia
ooh German
speaker yeah I did not expect like I I
feel like I've been asking for European
fellows for a long time um I didn't
expect them to bring out someone German
speaking I thought they would maybe
bring someone like
Spanish from Spain or someone from
France or I don't
[Music]
know I guess she speaks some French but
I thought they would bring someone who's
like is from France or from Spain or so
that's what I expected yeah or some
maybe maybe yeah I don't
know
yeah but German you know that's uh funny
that that that immediately like opens up
uh like talking topics and
stuff
violin
oh this girl is talented that was my
impression yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
extreme
violence uh now impression well okay it
really hasn't been so long
[Music]
so
H hasn't been so long I I I guess I
could say like
uh I've observed
and like yeah she's creative very
creative and
[Music]
like I I see her like socializing really
well so she's doing really well very
very
social good for her very
good yeah she can do like
anything it's like she can do
anything like apparently programming too
[Music]
crazy uh what else
we haven't really talked that much
yet and the few times we talked we just
like joked a little bit in
German potato PC oh really well I
haven't noticed
that German efficiency at its finest
what people say that about Germany but
at the same time you guys know right
that German train for example they're
always late nothing's efficient about
that Germany is not that
efficient their trains [\h__\h] up the whole
European train
Network some German trains they go
through like the top of Germany then
through Austria and then through like
Switzerland and Italy and so on and like
they'll be so [\h__\h] late just because
they started in
Germany train
slander no D Jaan is [\h__\h] D toan is so
[\h__\h] let uh oh this is already like well
yeah uh let's do German collab slash
talk about
culture because you guys are so
fascinated with that
apparently on the German
Channel what German
Channel I don't know what you mean
German
[Music]
Channel if only I had a second German
Channel no I would feel bad to like do a
like force her to go on to my German
Channel which you know it's it's so
small I I would feel
bad but maybe I can maybe she can pay
the Senai
tax
H maybe could because I am big Senai I
could you know she could not complain
about
it
[Music]
M yeah chance to revive the German
Channel
H off
collab when
meet like yeah uh I already already met
an in Japan so I'm excited like these
girls I haven't met them
yet I hope I will cuz like meeting them
IRL oops adds a lot to the
impression
and to my image of them and it really
just changes
everything there's so much more you
learn about people when you meet them
IRL cut off yeah okay chill chill chill
chill chill I'm still adjusting
[Music]
okay original impression
H
Italian
[Music]
exciting I want to
flex my skills teach
me and oh my God art so good draw
me now impression
[Music]
uh get along way better than I
thought
sweet
AF wait my let's put uh this is like
already when I met her but it was my
original impression when I saw her is
like looks
Rich smells rich is Rich I don't
[Music]
know uh
as f
[Music]
um I'm running out of space
love
how she loves Holo I love people who
[Music]
Holo it just a nice perfume will do
honestly uh uh what's the word uh um
not ad dict is is do you say what was
what do people say uh when someone
laughs and it's like her her laughter is
dot dot
dot her laughter
[Music]
is addicting yeah infect contagious
that's the word
contagious
laugh uh
[Music]
it's just so fun to listen to
her and I I love to see her grow because
first of all she's growing as in she's
still learning English and it's so cute
it's like watching a baby but she she's
so smart because she learned English so
fast she told me she told me what what
did she say like how how long ago in one
year or so selftaught yeah she learned
English in like one year recently or two
years
mhm and yeah so that
growth obviously but now in the future I
I want to see her growth as an idol of
course and as a streamer but she's
already a great streamer she really
funny just naturally funny because of
her just
italianness that's all it takes
yeah I already talked I think the most
of her so far and we already met IRL so
I have a lot of thoughts about her you
know already had an off collab of
her in
Japan so
[Music]
G original impression was like I think I
think she pretty much immediately
was
like I want to
[Music]
adopt because I really like
her
uh like
everything I like her voice I like her
character I like her design I like uh
her like interests in games and her
style of
streaming H or orange finally an orange
[Music]
friend yeah I like Gremlins I like
Gremlins like
her I like gramlin but it's not only
Gremlin just you know I mean you know we
have quason okay she's cut off there but
quason is not really a gremlin she's
like
hot yeah but like she's yeah g g kind of
reminds me a little bit of uh
Kobo in like her
energy love her energy and uh charact
personality it's too
[Music]
long energy and
personality
uh yeah I I'm like honestly I love her
so much it makes makes me sad that she's
not
[Music]
European why
notan because if she was a European or
like at least like I guess she doesn't
have to be European she just has to live
here like I'm sad she doesn't live
here I'm just saying that because that
then we could do off collabs all the
time I would just fly over the whole
time
yeah what the [\h__\h] is the
kilometer why
why why don't you why don't you just
move to Europe gigy why don't you move
to
[Music]
Europe yeah we wanted to collab but I
was so busy and I was like [\h__\h] I really
want to collab
but so Now's the Time I'm finally
freeing up so uh here uh let's collab
soon I'm
[Music]
free
g
wait see now impression honestly
same has not changed at all feel like my
my original impression is just for her
like I immediately read her like
perfectly you know what I
mean like she was such an open book and
so it was so clear what kind of person
she is from the
get-go and I mean I I the first day I
already me like spammed DMS with her
so giggy is just
giggy giggy is gigy
gy is
gy it only only gets
[Music]
better uh yeah
like can't that's you
know let's [\h__\h] play some games
[Music]
Girl original okay I thought I wrote
that wrong for a
moment
okay uh
uh ho if her voice is
crazy like even before debut in her
first in our first conversations you
know usually when a new Jen gets
introduced just they get introduced like
honestly pretty late like pretty close
to their debut they want to keep
everything like top secret and uh you
know get the girls to prepare and focus
on their debut so they take so much time
to let us get to know them so we
honestly don't know anything about
them uh like until so late and it's
usually like Cali and some other girls
mostly C is like always like hey hey hey
hey when are you guys when are you guys
finally introducing us to the new girls
hey can you introduce us to the new
girls yet hey I I really want to get to
know them I want to you know be there
for them to give them advice and stuff
hey it's not much time left can you like
when when are you when are you finally
showing them to
us yeah Kelly is still on top of
it let them into our server when are you
letting them into a server I just I just
want to you know make sure that they can
they have some senis to rely on and ask
[Music]
questions yeah but then they finally get
introduced to us and um first they like
bring the the the management they like
show a PowerPoint and they introduce to
us the generation and the concept and
everything and then they're like okay
now girls you can introduce yourselves
and they introduce themselves and they
speak and we hear them for the first
time and and then after all that they're
like okay now you can do whatever the
hell you want they're in the server now
and then we like move over to the to
just a Channel with only the girls and
then we talk and then I I'm at this
point I'm honestly asking so many
questions I'm always asking I think the
most questions I have like this whole
list of questions so sorry for
interrogating uh you justice and Advent
for Council I think I didn't was I even
there I don't know if I was there time
zone might have been an issue but I feel
like I was there I must have been there
yeah I must have been there but
especially if Advent and Justice I've
been inter interrogating them so
hard asking a million questions
[Music]
and um yeah anyway after all those
questions like you know we we were in
the voice chat already so long and then
herb offered to sing for us cuz we were
like so she was like people were saying
oh she's such a great singer like the
other girls were saying that Justice
members so we're like oh we got to here
and so she gave us a
pre-debut uh Taste of her singing
and she sang one of those
like you know one of those
[Music]
songs and we were all like holy
[\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h] what is
[Music]
happening so that was my impression like
oh my
God this strength in her voice is
something else so wow that'll be
interesting not gamer was also an
impression I think cuz I think she said
that she doesn't really play games much
so I think that would be like really
interesting watching her play more games
and it you know it would be like
remember when I played Minecraft I'm I
was already like well versed in games
but I played Minecraft for the first
time on stream in my first year uh like
early on right and and isn't it so fun
to watch someone be absolutely Noob at a
game like Minecraft like something you
expect everybody to have experience with
but I never had experience with it and
watching those baby steps watching
someone insist on playing Minecraft in
the third person
view aka
me yeah stuff like that uh so I'm I'm
looking forward to
her gamer gamer
[Music]
Arc um well also uh now
impression um
oh love accent now impression I I've
noticed she
she's actually like so caring
like she'll randomly messaged me like
yesterday too I don't know why I think I
know why but I don't know why um she
just randomly sent me a hug emoji
yesterday which I think is probably
because she saw me
crying um after the
I'm a
thing
yeah yeah and and like oh she will
that's not the F that's not the first
time why why did she send me a hug GIF
[Music]
GIF on the
13th of August what happened
then she's just like randomly like
there's no like conversation she just
like randomly you know some something
something happens and then
she she knows I need a
[Music]
hug
yeah oh I I I'm so excited for her uh
old anime song knowledge I
say
H like in my birthday K I did not think
anybody would choose an icho
song but she did I'm like whoa let's
[\h__\h] go I didn't think I would get to
sing
zuka she she seems to know a lot of
those songs so I think maybe some of our
anime interests overlap like I don't
watch anime anymore but like back except
for B
H and so caring sudden
Hogs I'm excited to meet her IRL because
I wonder if she'll give me son and hugs
and and if her caring nature will be
very apparent IRL as well I I assume
so yeah
[Music]
yeah and I also like her role playing in
Ian REO like she she was I was so glad
that I stumbled into a group of her
because she really made me
feel appreciated and like like she just
visible you know what I mean she saw me
you know what I
mean thanks for seeing me like genuinely
not not only in but like she sees me be
sad and she just randomly sends
me these like
messages why is she why is she so
[Music]
nice camera arc
when singing is sick let's
dance like I know she can sing now I'm
so excited to dance with her combine
those elements
and see where that goes also I really
love how to
me in terms of design there's so much
Synergy with narissa both tall both
powerful the colors are just so
complimentary it just makes me feel
so it's just
[Music]
ah feels good man all right oh my God we
finished
it that took me way longer than I
thought okay just in case people came
late let me show you quickly the ID
chart in case you missed it here let's
go over it you can read it while
I'm should I read it for you you can
read it yourself
here wall of text what's your impression
of
Ki
me like sometimes sometimes I I see
random old clips of me and I'm like
cringe cringe
cringe I'm sorry I was so cringe back in
the day I was like just really trying my
best to fit into this body and um well
now you're going to be like oh don't
hate on Old
[Music]
Wawa but no I I always I since the very
beginning I was very committed to this
job
and I try to make the most of it
and um yeah make my dreams come true my
impression my my my impression of me in
the past is oh my God she's stressed out
uh she's pressured
she's anxious she's um a mess
mentally uh but like so glad that she
got this opportunity
[Music]
to be in a place where she has a lot of
um tools and
opportunities to thve and make the most
of
it and use her
skills and now now it's
like I'm proud of how far I've
come very much I'm glad I endur
even very rough
times
and I'm so happy about the bond that
I've created with other girls that
I you know explained to you uh today
here and I'm also so glad about the bond
that I've built with you guys
especially I'm really glad that you guys
are p and that you guys are here for me
and so
supportive without you I would be so
[Music]
lost yeah and random comment I don't
know uh I don't know it's weird to to do
this about
myself
well I don't know I don't know what
there's to say uh there's some exciting
things
upcoming um that I will announce soon
and I hope you guys will uh all support
me and watch mhm now wait let me put
this aside uh I have important notice
not an important
notification that well you should
already know don't worry it's nothing
new
but tomorrow
stream whole talk with Amilia Watson we
are beginning the ends I've been been
wanting to do this for a long
time U I've been saying it for a while I
want to do ID and
interviews
um I'm probably just going to like do
the live translation but like in a more
compact vague way hopefully Japanese
people will show up the thing is it'll
be really late for
them uh so I wonder if they'll be
watching at all but maybe they can watch
the VOD you know we've been doing this
the other way the whole time so I I I I
I asked jenma and HMA and they were like
you should either uh just not do any
translation or you should still do the
translation but they didn't seem very um
fond of the idea of doing it in text I
don't know if it's because they just
didn't want to do it or because they
thought it was a bad
idea uh but they said just either like
do it or don't I'm like okay now I don't
know
[Music]
man no no no it's more like they were
saying oh you you know it always worked
now let's do it for the Japanese Bros
let's let's translate you know for them
to Japanese uh you know or and and Gemma
was like ah you know what I think it
would be fine if you don't leave it out
too that's fine too well well well I
guess I'll decide tomorrow
spontaneously um but yeah this is
happening tomorrow if you're wondering
about the time uh it will be today's
time plus one more hour I'm sorry
sea um but I thought because it's like
an
interview and the an a audience will be
the main audience doing it at the usual
holot talk time which is early morning
na would be pretty
bad um but I don't want to do it around
my morning time
either cuz [\h__\h] that eyebrows let's
go
um yeah a good Japanese practice I don't
need
practice so yeah
that's the best way of doing it for me
is doing it at my late
[Music]
evening yeah uh no not Prime Time na
it's going to be okay well let me look
it up
properly I'm going to put up the
reservation after this stream
[Music]
anyway okay it's going to
be 10 p.m. wa Time 5 a.m. jst I'm so
sorry uh EST 4:00 p.m. p.m. PST 1
[Music]
p.m. yes so I hope you guys can come uh
there's a community post up with
questions uh you can ask questions still
but uh I think we already have enough
probably it's all kind of spontaneous so
I'm going to uh grind
tomorrow like finish up collect and
finish the questions translate them put
them into graphics
uh prep work is going to be a little bit
rough don't have much time left because
I had to wait to announce
this
yeah yeah the Amelia Watson
announcer
of
paladins
the okay I was hoping that that this
would be like relatively short actually
that I could read super chats but it's
already midnight I got to I got to go
cook and then wake up at a reasonable
time so that I can prepare this whole
stream so
yeah but I hope you had fun I hope you
liked the the idea with the
charts thank you so much for watching
today and for looking over my new 2 zero
hope you like my eyebrows on fleek
than thank you so
[Music]
much and German M
of yipp
thank you for watching wait I totally
forgot oh my God I had a big
surprise H well whatever the big
surprise uh okay it's not that big for
me it's big um cuz I haven't
commissioned something like this in a
while um a new Opening screen animated
by matu uh I'll use it as my ending
screen now
so from now on it will be an opening
screen so you're going to get to look at
that now it's so cute it's so cute it's
so
cute here we go the
[Music]
n
m
[Music]
oh