[Music]
OG
Hey, I'm here. I'm here.
Ki
[Music]
Soooo, sooooo, I'm looking at you, sooooooooo,
wait a minute, Minecraft crashed,
but that's why it's Raden-chan's voice.  Asai, I'm
Rade-chan, I'm sorry, Usa, Kara,
oh my, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, Libby Boi, big voice, big
voice,
big voice, cube, thank you for big voice, you said
yes, so the white group gathered together.
Oh, I'm doing it right. I'm talking to the book that's there. It's so much fun, so much fun. [Music] It's too loud. I'm quiet. Please be kind. [Laughter] [Music] Please.
Okay, okay, you're awake, okay.
Well then, I missed the team division, so I
thought I'd make a quick announcement. Yes, I think so, but do you think it's okay?
Please, I, please, don't fight for me. Stop fighting for me. Is
it real? Don't get
in the middle. I'm sorry, but I'm sorry. I've
been beaten up so much. Thank you. I
'm fine. I'm a junior.  It
seems like there's a lot of energy when O's juniors are in good spirits.That's amazing.It's good to see them in good spirits.That's a good thing.Emae of the white team.I'd like to announce each competition.Yes,
but first of all, I would like to announce the flow up floor.  up  It's a
competition where you climb higher and higher.
Yes, it's a game where points are determined by how far you can go within the time limit.
Oh
flow up, Roboko-senpai and
[Music]
Kiaraki book, Chiara, do your best, bird.
Yes, you can go to the top with just one blow.
What do you think
? I don't include it, but the next step
is Princess Lese. Yes, this game
is a game where a knight protects the princess.  It
's quite a difficult game as there's a lot of things for Princess Tehaidone to do, but Azuki-
chan does her best in this game, Masuhide Kanatan, and me. Next up is
Iroha,
and then there's
Igozaru, and then there's the fourth person.  But,
Mme, I'll ask
these four seniors to do their voices.Yes,
yes, I'll do my best.If I listen to Sairoha-chan's English, I
think we don't have to support her.Little
Igri Little Fashion
English Good English is more lively than Japanese It
's not like that. It
's
not like that. It's not like that. It's not like that.
As expected, it's the next obstacle.
Physics. Yes, Azuki-chan.  Yes, there will be two events Yes,
and
then Amecha, then and then Yuzuki Choco-sensei.  The
next one is Mume,
Hime Hime Chim, even though there are three other people besides me,
and Kaera Kakara,
that's the last of the seniors.
Nerisa,
Neri,
onee-san, and the last Holo Men Hunter. The first
one is Holo Horo Home Hunting.
Leader Shirokane Noel,
Aro.  The second one is Chiara.
[Music] The second one is Chiara. The second one is Chiara. The second one is Chiara. The second one is Chiara. [Music]
Ki is
onee-chan.
And then there is A-chan.
Big sister, then Neri, Sayai, and last is Raden.Ra
I'm more than ``Yes'', it's controlled in such a way that it appears once or twice.
Yeah, it seems like there's a lot of people there, so yeah, yeah, let's go around the venue and try out some competitions.Let's do this as a favor, let's do this team.Rade is like that.It's like I'm letting myself use up all the calories I spent today.Have fun, have fun, have good energy.  Stroke
Okay, I'm happy. Let's go. It's easy. Well, let's start
with the first holo-up. Oh, I
'll go from here. It's a bit dark. It's
difficult to go full-up. It looks like it's going to be difficult. It
's quite high. It seems like it goes all the way to the top.
It's dark all the way to the roof. Is it okay to use the fire regulations? Turn it off.
Yes, I'm
here at the venue. I'll
be participating in that follow-up, but I've
never done that only-up before. I think so.  It's
rare because everyone is doing it, sure.Everyone
was doing it.Yeah, yeah, even if it's
okay, it's okay.Okay, first of all, here
on the left, it says Noe debug item.
Please light light
click click click then follow up Eh
trident yup
Weak and strong will come out Weak and strong That's true Right
left is right is strong or let's
light strong yeah weak yes light
Look strong, I'm climbing something. I'm
flying. I'm
flying. Right-click where you want to go and you can fly. If you right-click, it's fun. You can
hold it with the right button and release it. You can press it.
Release it.
Jump
There are strong jumps and weak jumps, right?
No, when should I use the weak jumps? When
is the distance short? Ok, here, here,
Oishio Glaister, Unro-chan, Light.
Click Oh, hey, nice,
nice
red
Ahahahahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Lee
Accident
Act
No Accident No Life Lee Can you
erase the clouds of books in the sky? They're a little
crowded. They're real clouds.  I do
n't think there are any real clouds right now. I can see them. I can see them in the book. I don't have them.
Why are there clouds? Why are there clouds
? Are they in the way? Why are they there? I want the sky to be beautiful.
Settings Settings Is this a setting
? There was something like, ``There are clouds or not?
'' I'm sure it's somewhere, somewhere, oh, it's in the video settings.
Oh, it's gone, it's gone, it's gone, it's gone, it's gone, it's gone, it's gone, it's gone, it's
gone, Roro, it's gone. Oh, it's gone, it's gone, it's gone, it's
gone. Oh, in real life, if you fall, your HP will be wiped out. Well, in real life, if you fall, you might die, so check it out.  Go back to the point
Yes,
go back to the checkpoint, and there's a bed in the middle where there's dirt,
so click on the bed,
click on it, and from there you
'll get a
response.
Oh,
this is difficult. I need a lot of practice. It
feels like that. I'll practice. Nice.
Okay, let's go watch the next competition.
Next NEXT. I'm on top of this on the left, but I wonder if I'll die.
Click on the debug item on the left.  Right-click on it
Okay, I wonder if it won't die? It won't die now.
No, it won't die if I enter debug mode.
Good luck. Good luck, good luck,
everyone.
This is it, I'm going home from here on this side. I'm
going home. Oh,
please turn on the lights. It's dark.
It's dark. It's really dark
.
This is the next step. It's an obstacle course. Haha, it
's this way. It's this way. It's this way. It's this way.
Okay,
this is the place.
This is where we start.
Well, on the day of the event, we'll open a gate here. We'll
start from here.
Well, it's not one lap per person, it's
half a lap per person.
One person
runs from here and goes to the other side.
There's also a line over here, but it
seems like you'll be separated from the people who run this far.  So,
from here on out, we'll run half a mile and then come back to the other line.We'll
have two teams, or rather, we'll have them split into two.How
many laps will it be?
2Well, that's eight people running.  I wonder if I'll do 4 laps.
Well, for now, let's run through all of them. Let's all
look for our strengths and weaknesses, and we can
talk about which one is better. If we can talk about what's good, then it'll turn out to be a buff. If you
touch it, you'll get a buff. This
hurdle seems like a big deal, too. If you touch it, you'll get
a buff.  Oh, it's true, I guess it's
slow. Well then, let's run a little.
Let's take a quick run.
Or go to the Starbucks and get ready.
Start, go go go, it
hurts, it hurts, right? My
pants are blown up, and the right clip is on.  I
can't take it. I can't take it. I can't take
it. I can't take it. I can't take it. I can't take it. I ca
n't take it. I can't take it.  I
can't get the light right right click I can't
get the left click It seems like it's only the left and right I wonder what happened.  I'm
passing here, I want to pass here, knock me down, you're
doing something, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it
hurts, it
hurts, it hurts, something's happening, what's going on? Are you hurt? Are you
hurt? Are you okay?
What are you
doing, Senpai?  That
's okay. I was hit. Maybe I didn't get hit. I
shouldn't have been
hit by Ra-chan or Raden-chan. I see, that's
okay, I hit her.
Okay, it's okay here, let's move on here.
Go oh wow, oh wow,
oh, run, run, here. Hey, oh, oh, it's difficult here.
At least there's some relief here, so it's okay to
move through the water.  My
way, yay, my
way, yay, Ade
Kokoha, that's what happened yesterday, isn't it? It's amazing, isn't it?
Genius Genius Genius Laden Genius
Raden Genius Raden Genius
Don't Do Nono Genius This is amazing
Raden-chan, turn around and see
where he is Raden Look Genius He's
almost there He can't climb he ca
n't climb he can't jump he can
jump he ca
n't climb he's
nice his
senior
was this.
Hololive is Hololive This is Hololive
or this is Hololive.
Wannais Genius? At the bread place, I
have to get some bread. It
seems like the bread place is set so that when I get to the bread place, I'll be really hungry.
Ah, that means I'm eating.  It's right,
it's right, it's right, it's right, it's right, it's right,
it's like that, my
listening power is
increasing, it's
left and right.
Oh, that's not Wright, Lee Wright. I don't know left or right. I have to
eat. It feels like I'm eating while running. I wonder
if I should eat. If I
don't eat, the next stage is going to be tough.
Here, too, I'm
going to eat while I'm eating.I can
run fast in places where it's not deep.I can
run.I can run.It's a concave place.It's so concave that it
doesn't look like it's powder snow.  I
see, that's why it's powdery snow ahead, so run as fast as you can and jump. If you keep jumping, you can
run faster. So here on the ice,
keep jumping, it's true, it's a jump, so it
's the last jump.  Now, if you step in, you'll see, I see, it's like
this,
and somehow the
timing is perfect. Oh
yeah, yeah, yeah, if you prepare like this, you'll probably be able to
get there without stepping on the snow. That's right,
Daifu. I see.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, I said yes, so I was like, Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
that's the obstacle.
Thank you, thank you.
I, I, I, I, I, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But it smells like cigarettes.My
gym uniform stinks.No, I don't want to
smoke.I don't like Yanicus Princess.I
don't smoke today.I
smoke today.I don't smoke today.I don't smoke today.
Well, I don't smoke.
That's right. The princess has a bit of a cigarette smell.
Yes, that's why we're a team of four people.
Well, first of all, we've
decided on one princess, so we'll have three knights.  become  I
wonder if Akara is missing or not.
Senpai,
look for the princess. Where have you been? Ka-san,
where
have you been?
[Music]
Oh, then it's just 4  There's a lot of people, so
let's have a little experience with the four of us.
[Music]
Io Yoshi
1234 I see, the
real team is all here today.
This is the actual team and the
members who are not on the actual team will try it out. Let's try it
. The
team team is here. Which one is more difficult, the princess or the knight?
Well, the princess might be
more difficult.  No, that's right. Well, the
princess has to explain various things to the other members,
but I
think you'll understand once you try it, so I'll
explain a little while doing it.
I know English and Japanese, so I'm sure I did
it the other day, and I'm
a bit of an experienced samurai, so I'm a bit of a Kama Samurai, but I can't help you, Hime Hime, At
Hime,
do your best.Thank you in advance.  I completely understand. The
princess is the best.
Other than this, I'm a knight knight and I'm the best knight.
Please right click on this one.
Click here, oh princess, oh princess. So
cute.  That
's nice. What's this really cool?
What's this? Let's
do this with the other cute members too. Let's do this with Kohime in the middle. Ok,
Kakae Kiara. Who should we call Princess here? Princess Kiara. So,
A-senpai, yes, yes, yes,
Oma,
Princess Magical Princess.  I'm Gozaru. I
'm asking for a magical princess. Then I'm going to play.
Yes, I'm going to start the game. Where
do I enter? This is here.
Gate gate o gate open I'll do my best Get open
and ready go do do do go
go go first I want you to use this as a foothold
So yeah
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
nice Where are you now Oh yes this
moves in order This is bad or mixes up.  Hey,
ha, where are you? I'm going to ride in the eyes of my senior Opieka right now.
Hey, that's what it
feels like. Nice, nice, nice, now I'm
riding in my senior's eyes.
Akiko.
Ooh, Nex, hop down,
press the button, press the button, oh, I'm stuck,
Imaichi.
This dream guy here is going to climb up again, so he,
senpai, please move. He, senpai, he, senpai,
please move. Hey, stop. Come on, move, move.  Oh yeah,
let's do it again lister male top
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah like this nice oh
yeah that's right here here oh oh oh
senpai stop zuki stopka senpai suo now  I'm
on top of Cato-senpai, so move on, move on, oney nice, osupum stop. It might be easier to understand if I say there's a puu.  Top Ostop Stop
Everyone is stop stop Ooonananao Oooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo Restart
Restarting Architecture Architectural Architectural
Architectural Architecture Hey,
press the E button to take the event
Toga's creative mode-like moves
Oh, I see, I see the theme, so I can see it.
Bifu, bifu, everyone is the same, same, yes, yes,
sem, oh,
nice. Oh, wait a minute, oh, oh, oh. Nice, but I don't know what that is. I don't know.
What, what, what is this?
Nice, I'll
make it and teach it to O.Make-up
Aaah, I already know what to make.Yes
yes, from among those.The
princess has a list book, so from among those.
So this is the list
Press that button Press that button That's nice Yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah this is here Momo
[Music]
No, wait, I'll do my best Oh
no, this is it
Nice, nice, my
Princess What I want to eat right now  I'm going to teach you
steak and elite pancakes.The
steak is a
pancake.The
steak is made by adding raw beef to it.Okay,
so I guess just one piece of beef is enough.
Oh, I wonder if this is the English version
Elite Elite Pan Elite
Pancake What is Pankay Pancake Pancake
How do I make it? I see. I see. I
need wheat, egg, sweet berry, wheat, egg
or egg. Where's the egg? Here's the egg.  1 egg, 1 egg, 1
egg, 1 egg, 1 wheat, 5 eggs, wheat,
on a cutting board.
How do I cut this? How do I find the ingredients
? Right-click on the mana board,
place something, press the mark that looks like an ax to place the ingredients, and
it's
on the left.  Well, I guess there
was an ax mark in the back, so I guess
it's wheat flour that you get when you press it.I
shouldn't have drawn it because I don't know.Maybe I don't understand it.
Bake flour and eggs together on a griddle.Bake flour and eggs together on a
griddle.Give me some flour.Let's
move.
That's
right, I'm sorry. I can't hear anything.
That's right. I can come, Kanamu-senpai. Asokamu-
chan, wait a minute, come on number 3. Is that what you
said?
Yume-senpai, I'll call you too.Are you
okay?Are you
okay?Ah, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come!  I'm going to cut it on a cutting board.Wheat
and sweet berries.
Sweet berries. Sweet berries.
Shop Yeah Shop Aki has
cut off the sweet berry now,
yeah,
put in hate belli, and it's so amazingly
amazing that you
can bake Comnico and eggs on the next iron plate,
but I wonder if you can say an iron plate.
Teppanyaki hot play ah grill grill yeah hot
play grill grill grill ah
where do you put the wheat flower azaza hole uh hey eggs I
think there's a part of the egg that's turning white.  I
have something like a griddle here. I'm
probably making flour. This is a hot pot. Egg
. U. Put the egg in here. Yes, please. I
have somewhere. Okay, uh, please.
Hot play, please click.  Hot
play Hot play Okken
pull Put it in and put
it in and it's gone It's gone It's gone The egg I was throwing earlier
Nice nice nice nice nice pitcher nice
egg pitcher woof woof woof woof
woof woof woof woof
waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaru air hot ply light click light click please okay yup yeah now egg
yup here ah nai nice nice nice That's
it I've made it near I've made it that far I've made it O I've
made the pancakes  Pancakes, ah,
don't serve them with pancakes, uhm, do
n't serve them with this, this cat, this, uh,
sweet berries and sliced ​​sweet berries.
Well, I lined up this and
arranged it like that.
Elite pancake, oh, how about this
? I can see it. Wow, something is done.
It's so nice. It looks delicious. It's so
cute. Please give me that.
Wasteak
[Music]
Tete-
tete-ba oh, nice, nice, nice,
perfect
When you're like that, you need coal. Yeah,
grill it, grill it, it's really good.
Only the steak is okay,
okay. Only really, really, really. Oh
, okay, this is okay. Nice, okay. Nice.
Ah, is this okay?
Okay, so I guess there's
only one spot where I don't understand the color, and that's
probably what's in this color right in front of you.  It's the
one that you can see in the box,
right? Yes, it's four, it's four, it's four, it's four, it's
four colors, it's four out of these, uh,
four blocks, four blocks, four blocks.  Look at it and
look for what's missing. Let's
try it out. Let's try it out. Let's
explain it in a difficult way. The left arm is in Japanese.
First, the left arm is the upper left, the orange is the
upper right, the red is the red, and the lower left is.  is red
Red right here means right here right here
wrong top left is orange orange
orange orange light up is light above light up
yeah red light down that's wrong
Soli left left down yeah red red
red
yeah right right pink bottom right right yeah  It
might be faster if you just put a number on the 4 blocks that you don't know about and specify it on the day of the day.It's true that one, two, and
four are okay, but that's not it.  I'm sure you'll
come up with a strategy a little later,
otherwise you might not be able to tell Mu-chan.
That's certainly smart.
Genius, Genius.
Senpai, what color did you just find? What color was this queue?  I
can't win. I'm a genius. I
saw something completely different. What color is it? I
wonder what color the answer is.
Oren's top left is orange. Top right is red. Bottom left.
It's red and I don't know the bottom right, so I can figure out the color.Bapi
pink pink oh ok
ok Nice nice That's what I mean It's a little
difficult to find.
Thank
you, thank you, I
will defeat the monster.
Hey, it seems like your allies won't take advantage of your
allies. Listen, your allies won't take advantage of you. No matter what this is,
it's PPVP, isn't it? PVP, oh PVP, yes,
pie. Bye, I can hear the sound, yeah, yeah
, yeah, I'm here. Oh no, no kiss.  Let
's go one more time.
Is it better to go to the other side? That's right. Yeah, that's right. It's
better to protect the princess one by one.
Yeah yeah
Piseo Ah, I see.
[Music]
Ooh
oh
Filhill Monsters,
Fight Fai Fai Fai Fai Ino Nice,
next level 2 Ah, Ah, Ah, oh,
oh, oh, oh, ochi, and I
protect the princess may be stronger.  Yeah,
Ah-chan, what is this? What is this
? There's no such thing as a dangerous life.
Ah, who's this?
Run away, run away, you're running away.
Nice, okay, okay, trust me, I'm an
old man, so strong, so strong. This guy, this guy, is strong. Where is he? If he falls down, call me and I'll come help you. Ah, okay, I died.
Thank you, okay, okay. Where's the rest?
Above.  There's a magic person on top of me, and there's a
magic guy who says, "Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa"
That's right, and it came out really strong. Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's
it. Nice, oh, oh, nice. Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice. Nice. Are you going back? Should I go back now?
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's go back, let's go back to the other side. Yes, that's
us. It's been about 5 weeks, 5 weeks,
5 laps. We're on our 5th lap. It's
us. Lie, true, true. I'm true, yes.  It
was difficult to explain, yeah, it's difficult to explain,
right?
Click on the right button to interrupt this game.
Yes, yes, it's open.
This is the
start of the
game.  Reset Eto
Entry List O
All you have to do is press Edo. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Clear.
So number 4, okay, thank you
. Thank you, okay. I'm
sorry. I'm sorry. I'll let you know. I'll let you know.
Thank you. I need a little strategy. I
needed some practice. This is probably Kazeno Gahime.  It
may not be necessary to explain the
rules, but if you
can understand the rules, you'll probably be fine.
Regarding communication, I think I'll be
able to look up some English that I need.And I'll
try my hand at it.Maybe I'm the
type who would be better off fighting hard.I'm
good at it, Mike.  The enemy
Minecraft is scary, so if there's a sense of humanity, I
might try playing Princess with everyone.Also,
I'm going to have a little practice with Minecraft, so I'd like to go to the next line of
Holomen.
Hunting hastily Holomen
Hunting seems like it's still being adjusted,
so I get it.Yes, I
don't need much practice in Holmen hunting.I don't need practice.I just want to
make it clear.How much do you know about the Hololive members?
Even if I'm a
newcomer, I won't give up.Even if I'm a newcomer, I wo
n't give up.What do you know about me?I'm
sorry, but I'm going to
apologize.
Yes, I lost, so no.
Well, Mokubasen is a game where two people fight in pairs,
so yes, yes, we
have to decide which two people will be in one group by the day of the game. I
see. I see. Yes, I see.
Everyone might be traumatized by a group of two or something. I don't like it,
but it's
not trauma at all for two people who have already been in that even numbered state. The
one when they were empty was traumatized.
Yes, in a group of two.  It would be nice if you could do that.
Well, is that okay?
Hey, I'm not going to participate, so I'll
leave it to everyone. Come on, everyone will participate. I'm
sure this wasn't all participation, right? Yes,
everyone will participate. Everyone will
participate. We'll do it.  Kaedan, uh, we're going to
be participating, too. That
's right. Well, today is the time. Now, for
now, I'm
going to press that button. I need someone to help me out. So, let's take an
example, but how do you feel about it?  I'd
like you to try using that example to see if it will
work,
so I'd like you to
try it in rehearsal.
Then, I
got that riding club.Yes, that's right.If
you want to ride it, you
can right-click and try it out.Let's
ride it.
Wow, what's going on with this? It's a strong color. It's
riding on its head, and it's got
legs underneath. It looks like it's running around.
Na-chan is attacking, yes, it's attacking. Yes, I see.
Person ATTB.
person
runsB WeAllhave
play yeah
yeah yeah
yeah isotherGAME
apparently
allp
ridsee yeah yeah
each other yeah
yeah let's beat each other and
compete for the number of kills oh
kills even if you count just one hit you won't die  Well, I'm pretty sure there are
only 3 hearts attached. 3 That
's what happens when you start the game. It's probably true, but
there's only one group, so it probably can't be done.
Yeah, yeah, there's another group, too. Well, it's
yellow or something.  Let's try it as a group,
senpai, please use me as a horse,
but I can't help it,
okay, let's go and
ride.  I'm
sorry, but I'll have to wait for a while.Oh,
that's
awesome.I have a book that lets you ride by right-clicking on this.
There's a place where if you right-click on a book and right-click on it while holding the book, it becomes a target.Ah,
when I open the book,
what should I press?
Oh,
wait,
wait, just open it, open it, uhm,
click, yeah,
click on the block in the middle of the white, Okay, yes
[Applause]
Scary, wait, it's
crackling, it's dangerous.
Strong,
strong,
dangerous, strong, strong, strong, isn't it?
We're so nice. It's a game we're playing. We're all playing this game, and we're
all playing this game.
Everyone will do this. Everyone will be there. Everyone will
be fighting on the same field. It's
going to be amazing and at the same time.
Wow,
yes, so there are 21 teams.
2121 teams are yes. If we
divide them up, how will the battle be? Yes, I see.  It's
like if you defeat a general, you get a little bit of a good score,
so maybe the general is going to be the boss of each of you.I'm going to
protect you, Senpai, and Unja a little bit.  It's
good to keep this in mind.It's true that one
side is fighting with the other.Sometimes the
white group is already fighting both sides.It seems
like they are going on a fishing trip.Focus,
focus,
everyone.  So I'm going to try to become an octopus,
and it's become a competition where I have to crawl and crawl,
and I'm thinking that I have to
decide on a pair of people by tonight.
Gogohogoho
Yes, it's okay, it's okay. We're here as gorillas. It's okay,
gorillas. We're not going to be defeated, so we're going to be gorillas. It's okay, gorillas, gorillas. Let's team
up
with gorillas. Are we going to make a gorilla team? We've decided on a
team.  I'm not happy with the regular gorillas anymore. I'm
going to stick with them.
Yes, yes, yes. Well, I'm
going to go see Holomen hunting, too. I
feel like I can't do it yet. I can't do it yet.  Is
n't that right?
[Music]
Kakoko Yeah, let's
get along, get along, get along
Friendly Friendly Friendly
Park Friend Ripa That nipple is showing, but it's
okay on YouTube I
think it was a bad thing Gozaru
Yomi-senpai This is  It's all about the color,
but it's okay, it's okay, it's pink and it
's barely safe. By the way, those nipples in English
are
``naes''.
There are two of them, so it's a diagram, is
n't it? If we put them together, we'll become Japan, right?
That's not what we're
talking about.  For the
actual Naru game, let's
take an example.
Three members of the red team's representative, the catcher and the hunter,
come out, but when the red team comes out and the
hunter comes out, the entire red team takes a
break.
All members of the white team and yellow team will participate. There will
be only one Unaha
. There will be 3 Hunters, 3 people, and 1 person from each team. There
will be 6 people per Red team,
but 2.  I'll divide it into 33 times, uh, oh, uh,
Hunter PERTeambok,
uh, uh, the red team, the hunter comes out, and
sometimes the yellow team and the white team run away,
uh, the three red, uh, all the other white, yellow.
OksayhuntersfromRed
TeamTheOtherwhite
andYELLteamswillAll
bepresentandOnlyThe
HUNTERwillbehunOh,
thank you,
as expected.
If you're an animal inside, you should catch people.  You
can use it by right-clicking, right-clicking, or something. An
item will appear. Yeah, what is that? It's
not a rope thing, it's a rope thing, and you can catch it. If you right-
click, say lead, lead, lead, kana-tan, etc.
Yeah, I'm tied up with a leash and I'm being taken
away. I'm being taken away
and I can't run away anymore. I can't run away.
Right-click on this hunting.
person Ah,
yes, I'm going to go inside, I'm
going to go inside, I'm going
to go inside.  An
expert was doing the work for him,
and he went inside, right? So, that means it's probably okay, and
everyone is not an animal, so
remember
that.  There
are a lot of themes, and it's a
game where the hunter has to catch a random theme from among them.It looks
interesting.Oh, I'm sorry, I just have one more question.
People who aren't here are already running and doing
things like that, so they're running, so they're running away.  It's
like running away by making full use of it, and I see that you're running
away. Well,
now you're kicking the lead. It's fun. It's so easy and fun. I want to play it quickly. I've said that this game requires everyone to participate.  That's
not an
exaggeration. I'm really looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it. It's
amazing.
[Music] The more
fun I get, the more suspicious it gets. Is it
really fun? I wonder if it's true. I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
Well, that's all for explaining the competition and
deciding on the competition. Thank you
very much. Thank you. As expected, you're an amazing senior. If you ask me something, I'll say it and I'll hear it. Thank you. Looks like it's okay. I
don't have any questions.
Oh yeah.
[  [Music]
Yeah
, it's okay, thank you, senpai. I'm
busy. Please sleep well.
Hey, I'm working. Are you
sleeping? Let's go to sleep. No, I'm sleeping. I'm
sleeping. It's okay. I fell asleep. Thank you.
Good health,
please get some sleep. Yes, then I guess that's it. Even if
Kan-san or I are gone,
everyone seems to be okay. We'll all be practicing here. It looks
like we'll disband the broadcast here for now. I'll continue.  Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, people who leave here, once we're done, we're gonna be disbanded.
Tired  I'm
so tired.
[music]
de
yo
[music]