oops
[Music]
follow me
i oh need no drinks tonight
[Music]
foreign
hey
[Music]
me
i'm tired
[Music]
it's not quite my birthday yet
not even in japan
there's still some time to go
hello everybody welcome to
the um countdown call-ins uh for my 2022
birthday
yay almost birthday yeah i mean we can
definitely
oopsie act as if no that wasn't the
right one act as if
it's going to be my
my birthday sorry this piano is in the
way sometimes whoop i haven't used this
room in a while
ah i'm very nervous about today and
tomorrow
[Music]
um but i have a really packed schedule
for
the collins at least for
the beginning i think
so
before it turns midnight
let's i guess
it already gets started yeah why did i
start when did i schedule a call in so
early
no time to talk no time to waste um
after a little while uh there will be um
merch announcement
so
don't don't worry of course we're gonna
have merchandise
so stay tuned
[Music]
one second one second wait can you give
me one second
[Music]
do
oopsies sorry sorry sorry sorry okay
let's start
[Music]
one day auntie your birthday
sorry for the wait no no no no no
problem no problem so
you were busy again so call my heart
thank you so much thank you and you're
awake
nervous right
[Music]
me and i i wish i wish i could
go to japan and take a picture of you
but i have to rely on twitter oh
twitter
oh beautiful
is
[Music]
how are you doing
yeah it's it's good and fine but a
little bit busy but maybe you were busy
too yes yes very busy
oh yeah
busy working day you're calling into my
stream thank you so much
well i i'm very happy to
i'll say
congratulations on your birthday and i
can't wait yours lady first live right
first lifeline
yes tomorrow tomorrow ah do you know
that
what english mean
yeah i know i love this
i uploaded some
imitation of inner souls
oh can you try starving
okay tomorrow
okay yeah that was good your voice has
to crack
all right
perfect perfect i actually have um a
little
little not really a game but i have like
um
if you give me a number between one two
six okay
okay then i have a question for you
okay okay i so if
i i'd like to choose okay so
first one
okay okay okay that one is easy i think
that one is an easy one so what is your
favorite thing about kiara
i think favorite favorite favorite i'm
so favorite world favorite part favorite
it's too hard to choose one right one
you can say several things
okay
first i respect you because um
your
language skill is very good and so
fabulous i respect you you are my
teacher i think
are you practicing like day by day yeah
yeah i've been practicing english for
three hours a day
now these days honking easy so serious
wow you're so serious because i never
forget the promise to hold a be host of
whole talk yeah
you
even remember that
i forgot that
yeah you forget
i forgot it oh no
please remember now okay good to know
good because uh whole talk is gonna come
back sometime soon and um would be nice
to have like a backup host yeah yeah
yeah yeah so i would be the host
[Music]
and japanese and translator scale is a
very so good so too good but so i i like
to oh
yeah
if i go to japan it will
be better again
yeah you must come in japan yeah
yeah and then we can go eat something
together again
yeah right
[Music]
there
we can't wait right
yeah but have to be patient have
patience yeah a little bit a
[Music]
oh
okay okay she wants you to tell the
japanese fans about something that needs
to be looked at in the yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you for hard working bye thank you
bye bye congratulations thank you i love
you bye
i love you too
she said i love you
okay it's going fast fast fast
happy
[Music]
is
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
english proficiency
okay
please introduce yours himself and tell
me your hobbies maybe in english
i hope
yeah hobbies hello um
[Music]
um watching movies
watching movies me too me too hey what's
your favorite movie
favorite movie harry potter oh
what if you would be in harry potter
what would your your house be you know
the i don't know how you say it in
nihongo
the character um
[Music]
yes
do you guys think
is she gonna be gryffindor really um
yes
uh
hufflepuff hufflepuff
[Music]
[Laughter]
please choose a number between one and
six
yes okay okay number two
two
or six
okay
one
one two three four five or six
[Music]
[Laughter]
for real really really really i wanted
to do i wanted to do the australian
collab
what yes yes
okay
okay okay okay let's do it within july
or august because every time every time
somebody says let's go
soon it's like one year later
[Laughter]
no problem it's not you it's me
okay thank you
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
i actually made a discord group for the
australians like months ago yeah but
then things
didn't work out yeah yeah it would be
like that sometimes but uh oh yeah i
think that wasn't hot and i went into a
break and then the timing was kind of
bad oh but
uh we oh dear now i have a list of
pictures so many pictures
uh i think i'm
i'm ready
uh
zombie
dick the masseu died y'all got this dozo
[Music]
[Applause]
i wanted to talk to you i wanted to see
you
hi
english
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
go go five okay one two three four five
oh
uh
uh if you could travel to with kiara to
which country would you go kieran
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
chad
thank you
bye bye
ah she's so sweet
i love her ah let's try to prepare the
next picture for the next person if i
can find it in this sea of pictures i
can't i can't
i can't
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
[Applause]
i don't know which face to go with i
want to combine these two faces
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
go
oh
so
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
um
a
come
[Laughter]
[Music]
then she counts you know all these girls
and we
were for it but then she kicks me out
because she said my my color recently
was not red enough so
she kicks me out that's so so such a
chameleon move such an entertainment
entertainer
[Music]
um
that's nice talking to them
uh
that's an interesting idol unit though
chiara marine bales
uh and only
just because of the red orange colors
i'm not sure if that works so well
i think
upset
upset i think the next
supposed guest
i was about to say
they may have forgotten it but nah they
couldn't forget huh
[Music]
yo yo
[Laughter]
[Music]
today i have a present for you really
but my
your
this present is not much you are lube
no problem that's okay
no problem hey show me show me some me
yeah i send you a discord
i love i love this
so
you love me maybe
yeah you rub this
[Music]
do you know this
battle
no only but no ah main present
my presence is not bad
no
but
is
[Music]
you had a peanut pinata before
so i know
and
this miniature is so
you don't have to
[Laughter]
no no no no this is a pinata okay
i believe i believe there's lots of um
love and and um air that was consumed by
subaru before in here on super
immediately
oh the hero is somebody who is
everywhere love is in the air
is in the air
they are scary
[Laughter]
please choose a number between
one and six
yeah i chose
two okay okay okay and let's go what
this is simple this is easy the easy one
there's difficult ones here too what do
you want to do with kiara if you have
one day with her eating it
[Applause]
[Music]
that that sounds like um
[Laughter]
really fits in well into disneyland i
think
duck
because duck
[Music]
same thing
[Laughter]
you know
yeah i i
i love
[Music]
maybe
[Laughter]
[Music]
jet coffee i like chad costa but ah
i'm scared of jet coaster roller coaster
yes sorry no
scary is
the fast only fast
[Music]
that would be so much fun go to
disneyland mr duncan would be so much
fun
please send me
[Music]
excuses i will steal super du senpai and
bring her to a vacation so that she can
take some days off of work um
[Music]
[Applause]
please watch
yeah i'm looking forward to that thank
you
thank you
[Music]
okay
do your best thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
it was a pinata i thought it was you
know
a baseball bat and a christmas ornament
i might just hang it up on my christmas
tree this year too yeah yeah yeah ah
sweater senpai so
my beloved my beloved duck i'm not sure
if donald duck is really her favorite uh
character
feels like she felt the need to say it
for character reasons or joke reasons
meme reasons
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
i'm
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes please please please there's some uh
some sexy dance too maybe maybe a little
bit
oh okay sexy dance
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
i got beer i hope it's non-alcoholic um
oh well uh we have to show you guys or i
have to show you guys something so
let me let me show you yo
what's
birthday celebration 2022 on sale july
6th uh japanese standard time which is
in like five minutes or so yay
yeah yeah it looks already killed right
let me turn on btm
i thought really hard about the merch
this year if you remember last year we
had a
an apron for cooking and slippers for
hanging out in your apartment although
some people even wore it outside
i really like my merchandise to be
something original that other members
haven't done yet and uh something useful
so let's see what we got this year
oh
it's already overwritten there but let
me immediately go to the next slide oh
let's look at this first okay kiva
i came up with the name
it's a big ass blanket with a super cozy
illustration from uh
thank you for the super fluffy art with
my cats and everything they threw
everything i wanted in there it looks so
perfect
and i said i want to be hugging a
chicken plushie in my arms really
tightly and yeah i want it to be really
cozy environment because you will be
using it as a blanket
it's 120 to 200 centimeter if you don't
know centimeters that's okay but it's
really really really big yeah
and it's fluffy
so this is kind of like i would say
fitting with the slippers
and since it's kind of like a almost
like i don't know good night theme
fluffy good night theme yeah yeah yeah
so you can collect it and combine it
with last year
and next up we have
a kibaba magically magnet set to put on
your fridge yay
it's with eyes by teda we have five
different ones it's a chicken on my two
of my cats and it's me and then a nice
cute little kfp store
yeah
if you put it on your fridge then people
will come to your home and be like yo yo
what's that that's cool cool stuff you
got on your fridge
you can also put it i guess on any other
magnetic uh surface of course you just
cool any way you want baby yeah man it's
baby
and then we have the kiwa wing
protection armor that naming was also
made by me now this fits with the apron
and i'm the most excited about this one
and because i thought you know it would
be freaking adorable
[Music]
yes
don't get burnt i obviously don't need
it but your chickens need it it will fit
all sizes of wings perfectly fine
there's kotoni on the lining and yeah
it's it's really um
protective yeah so you don't get burnt
be careful though okay don't forget to
put on your mitten when you cook
and so this obviously fits with the
apron
proof could you protect yeah
and then
uh
there will be a voice back there is a
voice pack situation voice point of view
having a cold with english and german
fairy tales i took two different
versions there will be an english fairy
tale version and a german fairy tale
version and it's basically you having a
cold look forward to it if you like um
voice
packs then this
[Music]
yeah it's the comeback of the fairy
tales and then as a full set if you get
the full set and then you get the the
magnets as a sticker sheet with some
extra stickers there also by teda and
yeah so this comes as an extra for the
full set and i need to check something
okay
um so there's one extra thing though
that i want to mention
really important uh because after
document i was like
i wondered
i think i talked about it on stream too
so it will happen uh details will be
soon i am doing um a meet and greet
lottery
for everyone who purchases
uh a minimum of 5000 yen
of merchandise so i think you don't even
have to buy the whole set
yeah um minimum 5000 yen details will be
announced very soon um but basically you
can enter a lottery and then you don't
have to be anywhere it's an it's an
online meet and greet through zuma
whatever
[Music]
okay
yeah
i wanted to give some more people a
chance for meeting great who people who
couldn't come to like the events
and
so on eventually
[Music]
and i think since it's midnight in japan
now i think it's already uh
up i think is it if yes then my
manager will probably link it in the
chat in a moment
or two in a moment or two
[Music]
emerges live
don't um
run over the other chickens
be careful on your way
oh sure
okay okay give me a second
um now i will make this
an automatic slideshow
[Music]
there we go automatic there we go
is it is it changing will it change
don't change oh there we go ah okay
just when it was about to change i
changed it back
yeah powerpoint like powerpoint have you
read the japanese oh yeah wait yeah in
japan it's my birthday now
it doesn't quite feel like my birthday
yet because you know here it is just 5
p.m
[Music]
the countdown
is basically over but not yet there's
still kind of a countdown to my concert
yeah yeah yeah so don't don't forget
that uh here we go i'll put this here
there's okay this is always the thing
with birthday streams there's so much
going on everywhere
i'll put this
put this here
on top of the pinata happy birthday
thank you happy birthday
congrats
[Music]
we're still continuing
the calls there's still many calls to go
okay
i think
let me take one more sip of my water
because this is like oh it all goes so
fast um
[Music]
hello
because in japan it's your birthday now
i will say happy birthday
yes
thank you you can say it i already um i
i
i expect it now it's it's okay everybody
can say happy birthday hey
thank you
it's been a while talking to you
yes it's been it's really been a while
but i'm so happy to be able to be here
okay
this is this is this is not a nice happy
birthday but i can i ask something oh of
course of course of course
this this has been my uh
greatest desire oh no since
a while i'm worried instead of something
about nuts
[Laughter]
can i call your mommy kiwawa
for tonight okay i mean there's actually
quite a lot of fans who also call me
mommy kiwawa so it's okay yeah yeah yeah
go ahead wait do you would you want to
call me that because
um i am so
so caring like a sweet mom or is it more
like a oh other mama kind of thing
i like it because you you're like uh
first it's cute
thank you i like that you're still
carrying it's just so nice
very mommy energy no
a lot of people say that sometimes but
i'm confused i don't quite see myself
like that but thank you that's very
sweet of you
okay my child mommy
yes my child my sweet summer child then
i shall ask you uh
to choose a number between one and six
can you do that i will choose
[Music]
three free
okay you have chosen to praise kiara
okay
you know that your hair is so lovely and
you're so pretty and awesome i cannot
wait to see
oh
hey but you say you like my singing but
you know i really really really love
your original song
it's so beautiful
but you are beautiful yeah it's
beautiful
[Music]
apparently kubo is jealous though
because you get to call me mommy yeah oh
no i don't worry we can share yeah you
can share
it's nice to feel popular wow
yes so thank you because you're so
pretty oh happy birthday thank you
i've seen your merch oh yeah
i just revealed it
yes i really want the stickers the
stickers well the stickers you only get
if you buy the complete set
so guys don't forget to buy the complete
set yeah the full set you're at school
but maybe maybe we can give you a
discount
at these countdowns
maybe i can i can ask to get give you a
a these
count
these counts
[Laughter]
these count
these
okay let's see
no i didn't i didn't do anything i
didn't do anything
thank you
for stopping by
wow
[Music]
a sweet sweet sweet sweet thank you
i think
oh
there's a chotto uh
i don't know who's gonna come next
there's two people in the waiting room
now
in the waiting line i think
we're gonna have
i think the times are all messed up at
this point let's go
hello
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
which country would you go to
it
[Music]
romantic
um
[Music]
oh
um
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
um
ah
[Music]
hawaii
um
[Music]
oh
by the way
i was waiting to like i don't know when
to show this oh where is it where did it
go
oh no that's me all right
i have
oh that's it ah see i got this from from
mermaid
because uh she won't be calling in
uh but i also got this
bucket with berry sauce kfb bucket from
women just wanted to put it on the
screen thank you mummy it's cute
berry sauce
actually you know a lot because there's
um
lingonberry we each nestle with
lingleberry i think you know generally
berry sauce is not such a crazy idea
for uh
fried chicken and by the way since she's
been waiting for a while let's move her
in here
you've made it you finally made it here
you can unmute yourself it's time oh
oh
kuronichiwa
hello
oh happy
it's been a birthday
yeah it really has
like
i i saw your i saw your announcement for
the 3d yeah i'm really excited to
look at it
it'll be amazing
it's kind of early and you already sound
uh tired now
[Laughter]
i woke up just for you
and you'll do the same thing again
tomorrow
right yeah of course
oh thank you
i think it's gonna be worth it because
we worked so hard on this you she's
crazy
yeah i know like you you work hard for
everything that you do
and i'm sure everyone's going to
appreciate that i i hope so thank you do
you want to choose a number between one
and six for me
yes five
or actually no one
because you're number one
all right then you have to tell me your
favorite thing
or things about kiwawa
hmm
well
i guess you like i
i like just one thing just you like just
you can say more than one thing if you
want
okay okay good um
i
really like how hard-working you are and
like you
pump out a lot of projects and
ideas and
like it's honestly kind of creative and
it's something to look up to for that
and oh my god you sound so so wow it's
nice listening to your voice continue
continue
and
i
appreciate your honesty like
oh really when it comes to yeah yeah
thank you
i'm i'm like kind of um worried
sometimes um
that maybe i'm i'm too my european
openness makes me a little bit too
honest and too open sometimes
but that's nice to hear well
well to be honest i prefer
people who would be
uh rather like upfront about what
they're thinking
even if it
you know might be too blunt like i
appreciate that a lot more than sugar
coating things wow so
thank you yeah
no thank you thank you yeah just like i
i i really worry about that recently um
this and all kinds of things but it's
good to hear dan kitchen
no
yeah no no of course and anyway i'm just
excited for you like
the
the movement looked really smooth too so
yeah so far from what we've sneak peeked
so far and don't don't don't you don't
worry it's going to be even more amazing
in the actual concert
yeah and yeah that's crony
me yeah i
you could teach me hi
i don't know if i i don't know if i can
be saved but
uh
if i'm gonna learn i might as well learn
from someone who actually knows oh how
to dance but no no i don't really in
particular know how to dance like i can
only learn choreos but it's not like i
can suddenly like
bust uh some sick ass dance moves on the
on the disco floor like that's for
example something i i really can't that
intimidates me and yeah
did you ever go to the disco before
disco yeah
no
i've hit the club before but then i
guess what
i thought disco was like i thought it
was a theme party or something
like for disco i don't know
but yeah
oh the club
oh
you hit the club before and what kind of
dance would you do when you're in the
club i'm i'm once again getting some uh
things out of you that you never talked
about before let's go
okay oh i think i just
do the i just said the jelly bean or the
popcorn where it's just like you know
hopping on the spot hopping on the spot
you call it the jelly yeah the popcorn i
never heard of that before
yeah yeah you you call it that because
i'm i'm assuming it's like you know
popcorn being oh popped
bouncing yeah
okay really simple i see
yeah i think i need to teach you some
things even though i i don't really go
like i i don't go to the
um club either but i think
i i i can think of some moves maybe to
help you out there
i'll do my best
what am i gonna do with all the
the ladies and gents with all my sick
moves now i'm gonna be swerving around
you and nailing in front of you when you
dance oh yeah they're gonna form a
circle around you and you're gonna like
spin and swoosh and pop and lock
oh man
yes invite me to your dad's class
let's get down on the dance floor all
right connini
um i'm gonna let you go back to sleep
unless you had something else to say
um
i
i will let you go too but i just once
again i hope you enjoy yourself cause i
know
um you worked hard to
make the birthday
enjoyable for everyone so yeah have fun
no thank you i hope you will enjoy it i
i had fun and i suffered when i recorded
it but i hope that the result will make
everyone um happy and excited and hype
so thank you for obviously thank you
for calling in thank you for making time
in your day for that thank you i
appreciate it
yeah i really wanted to make it so okay
let's play diablo again sometime
diablo or just anything really okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
love
made her blush a little bit at the end
again
oh i'm scared of the next one i'm
scared i'm scared
oh coy
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
get on my level
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
uh
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
what the heck man i kind of oh man i
just damn it she got me she got me with
her cuteness
[Music]
[Laughter]
but
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
cute
all right i'm not sure who's gonna come
next oh
someone
ah
you guys make it out between yourselves
who comes next
or should i move them
[Music]
i shall
do i'll i'll wait for whoever there's
like three people waiting
i don't know who's gonna come
daddy
yago is not gonna come no no
yanko is not in my schedule
[Music]
good time to drink water ah okay
i think yeah you waited the longest
[Music]
i missed you too
careful for the opening i have
[Music]
a little song oh my god
happy birthday
have a wonderful
one
may all your wishes and dreams come true
i
love you
i love
[Music]
i have you in my eyes
my sweet child
you're the best child
you're so cute
i love your singing voice
[Music]
oh yeah i have one more
present i i send you one
okay okay okay okay
oh cute
oh yeah
that is that is adorable here i got
umbrella in kfpq style oh that can
shield me from all those flower petals
that are falling down now it's getting
crowded in this
thank
you it's so cute that's a good idea for
merchandise but i think i asked before
and they said umbrellas is no no
umbrella too dangerous or something i
don't know
[Music]
choose a number between one two six
from what to what
something is a
but
i have a decimal
a number from one two six
one two
six
yeah yeah
oh one
oh uh
ah
five
[Music]
um if you could travel with kiara which
country would you go to
um
[Music]
where where would you want to go with
mommy kiwawa
you know that place that full of ice
what is that
antarctica
[Laughter]
there's other places that are snowing
and cold we don't have to go that far
okay
um
can we see
yeah yeah yeah yeah because
because
uh we don't have snow here in new
zealand we also have a lot of snow in in
austria in my country we go skiing and
snowboarding and all that skiing yeah
yeah yeah skiing
yes
if you come in like february
then we have lots of fluffy snow
yeah and we won't die from the cold like
in antarctica that's a little bit too
cold i think
ah
yeah you're right yeah
yeah
where else in europe
maybe like i don't know finland or i
think finland maybe has good snow
i'm not sure
yeah yeah i think so finland has really
really great winters and norway norway
as well
so scandinavian okay you don't know
thank you i'll take you with me
don't worry about it
it's like you know when
when when
when you were away we were a child our
mommy would plan the vacation and we
would just come on
don't think about anything you just come
along i'll take you don't worry
have you have you seen do you know the
northern lights
northern lights yeah wait maybe
not
[Music]
um
yeah we can see them in in no way in
finland i think
yeah yeah yeah it's really beautiful
i really want to see
okay oh i wonder if we can capture that
so well we have to try let's give it a
try
also i think next week we we will play
portal 2 again right i play together
again finally week one
yeah sorry mommy
was very busy
okay it's okay it's okay i'm going to
die
i'm going to die
yeah cute holy you take your time
okay
i love you
i love you too
as an ending i will sing it again okay
[Music]
and dreams come true
i love you
oh my god
[Laughter]
if you don't go now i have a heart
attack you have to go
[Music]
oh my god i'm gonna die
all these children are too cute
i need to assert dominance
hello
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
um
i
foreign
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
foreign
uh
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
i feel like we're way behind schedule
not good oh
[Music]
m okay i have the present for you
oh oh so sweet thank you
wait there i put your picture wait wait
wait
okay okay doko
[Laughter]
i will
do the stuff you will do it
yeah that's so nice
one time one time or how often
ah
any time any time not one yeah
they will make use of you all the time
though
um a week once one time
one time per
week oh dear
oh my
gosh
oh thank you the kefi is very happy now
oh
one of us one of us
yeah
and
i want to go to australia australia
because i love the sound of music
oh thank you
yes
we can do sound of music tour
yeah
i want okay so please guide for me
i'm glad oh you saw the movie before
when did you see it long time ago i
yeah
long time ago i
yeah a long time ago when i
um the school oh
and
music class
watching the movie
[Music]
austria is not not so famous uh like for
example australia so uh most people know
austria because of sound of music or
mozart or
orchestra so thank you for joining
austria
yeah i want to go i want to go
yeah
i want to show you austria it's really
beautiful it's just like in the movie
the same same
thing i i want i want to look the inst
innsbruck
it's book
it's
inspiring it's very it's beautiful right
why why why in spock
like uh
what look the picture when i looked the
picture in the book oh very beautiful
but most of the
location of the movie is in salzburg
oh sciencebook
is nice it's pretty nice yeah yeah we
can we can look at many cities
wanna go i want to go
in
okay dan's broke okay
okay i will thank you thank you for
appreciating my country
[Music]
baja is also
australia australia right
alps yes we have alps in austria
oh there is a there's a place called
alpbach in chidolu
[Music]
on the bridge you fit you mean
yeah yeah i know i see it i didn't know
this one oh that looks like fun
the i've been yeah
bridge
okay let's check it out
thank
you
i'm looking forward to go
your country okay so i have i have one
last thing to say to you louie yeah we
zoo robot okay i say i say one last
thing to you okay one okay
and
nice butt
thank you
bye-bye
i mean damn did you see that butt
damn girl
oh
hello
[Music]
oh come on i know exactly who you are
you're good for me
you can fool the viewers probably
only
hey yeah
yes happy birthday
bye
thank you
i wanted to talk to you
i wanted to talk to you too but before
that i have a present
yeah
wait did i
did i get
some
buns last year too
because i feel like i did but these are
not the same in any case wait they do
i don't know
they look fresh but i feel like you've
been giving these out for a long wait
wait last time were you even around
i'm not sure what was that
dude
i'm confused did i get so much here yeah
we were around
but i guess you didn't give me any last
year i just saw you giving them to you
know everybody else i love that idea
it's so cute
my head is white though uh unless i make
this huge i won't fit in between maybe
if i cut and i i only put one here
cute yeah
or you know you could put them like
innocent by on on her
donkeys
ah
yeah she probably just did that because
she does she needed to cover them um
to not make it too obvious that there's
nothing there uh but anyway
thank you for that that's so cute i love
buns i want buns in my hairstyle too
someday
i'm glad you like it
it's really cute maybe you can help me
make a bun in my hair
if you want more buns in uh some other
places i could do that too
wink
maybe um some yummy bread buns yeah
okay
and then and i'll cover them with
nutella
i i do but don't buns go well with
savory food
um
i think yes but also with nutella
everything goes with nutella
now only tell me a number between one
and six
five
five is one two three four five if you
could travel with kiara which country
would you go to
anywhere dad has a church so he can get
married
well coincidentally
[Laughter]
coincidentally austria has a lot of
really beautiful churches yeah so i
guess you could just come to austria
it's more comfortable for me if i don't
have to go anywhere
awesome so uh when do you want to hold
your reception
um uh
i'm already married actually sorry olly
you know why have one when you can't
have more
kind we kind of don't do that culture in
austria i would probably get into
trouble if i would do that
dang it yeah but you can be my um
what's the what's the english word for
that wait
uh
i mean a really
fancy word
by mistress oh yeah my mystery
like a concubine
wait what's that that sounds like a pig
what am i thinking of it
it's like a mistress yeah
if you're happy with that i can i can
see i can check what i can do
i'll take my wins
awesome no but more than that i just
want to collabo with ollie
oh i was picking a porcupine
yeah
that is a pig i was thinking of dad
you're so cute now you're so cute
shut up it's your birthday let me
compliment you shut up you're getting
sick no you're so cute
thank you for giving me me your energy i
need that energy
you still have a lot more to go i'm
surprised you still didn't get me to say
anything in indonesian
um i mean
we can save that for later
instead of indonesia i i i would
appreciate some body language to get
what i'm saying
you're fire all you did yeah you've
recently you wrote something to me on
twitter
where i was like even even the fans
were like holy only are you okay oh
yeah it was
let me show it on screen
give me one second i need to
i wonder if you know what i'm talking
about
i do and um
i just have to say that i'm just hiki
horny
all the time or was that a specific was
there a specific reason for this
i i'm just
i just i just smile
i guess i i just maybe i've awakened a
new fetish in me and i kind of want my
ladies to
yeah okay cause you seem more horny than
like a year ago and that kind of worries
me
horny buns don't worry
honeybunk i mean i'm just i'm i'm just
very um grateful to you that uh you
haven't done an intervention yet
thank you i need to do that
okay you know what i'll revive maybe
just even for one episode i'll go with
my whole invention idea i will do it
let's go i had this idea like over a
year ago and i never made it happen uh
but you seem open to the idea so let's
do it
gosh
all right
okay ollie thank you so much for coming
i love you
i love you happy birthday thank you
please watch my concert tomorrow
bye bye
bye
this tweet shocking shocking but also i
guess not surprising
[Music]
hello hello sorry to keep you waiting
yeah it's hell it has been a while i'm
fine how are you
oh my god
like
oh you're using that picture okay
wait is there a meaning behind that
twitter picture
oh just like
i'm watching some drama with popcorn
oh that's nice yeah oh i love papa
what's your favorite flavor of popcorn
oh i like caramel me too i do like
caramel yeah sweet popcorn i like i like
oh i like the the savory the salty one
and the buttery one and and the sweet
one but yeah all popcorn are good yes
have you tried like um like the oreo
popcorn no
they sell it in indonesia and it was so
good oh i need to check it out but you
have seen like stores that sell like 20
to 30 different flavors of popcorn like
really crazy ones also like wasabi
popcorn and so on yeah yeah i need to
try a bit more because i always go with
like the safe thing that i know
i like it so i won't be disappointed do
you also do that or do you try out new
things
uh i rarely try out new things
really okay then you're kind of the same
yeah i just like um i choose the the the
food that i've already tasted and i like
it
[Laughter]
and you know in german there's a phrase
that a phrase that we say
that has that meaning it's uh
it's it means what the farmer doesn't
know
he won't eat
yeah yeah we're very picky
very picky yeah i'm very picky oh do you
want to try repeating that
it's a bit difficult maybe
oh okay how can you write it for me yeah
let me let me let me write it on on on
discord oh sure
oh thank you so much with a mouse that
sounds tough i can't draw with a mouse
at all
right so i wrote it to you it's vast
vowel nist can't that's first and it's
too long can you say it
watch the bonus plan the poison pretty
close wow
luna german muna german muna german
i wonder what's what will be my name in
germany oh wait now i see the art your
name in germany well um
the the moon is moond
moans yeah
but mo but i think
yeah we would just call you muna
muna
actually no wait there is a there mona
m-o-n-a with 1-0 i have seen this name
being used in german before
oh yeah yeah actually now that i think
about it there yeah some people not many
it's really rare but i've seen people
called mona or
uh monica before
monika yeah oh it's similar to english
monica
i think that probably comes from
the moon maybe maybe that's the origin
of the name thank you for the art oh
wait i put it where the collins are as
if there's someone calling me with that
thank you it's cute
cute
[Music]
thank you it will be very soon in less
than 24 hours it's kind of late in your
time zone but i hope you can check it
out
i will i will check it out because the
last time i saw your performance in holo
fest it just was so good ah thank you
that's all i i felt very pressured after
that but i did my best so
hopefully i can live up to the pressure
and the reputation now
thank you very much i think the
letting you speak german was um your
individual challenge so we don't need to
do the other one thank you for coming
muna
thank you
go eat that popcorn thank you
bye bye
muna german never heard her speak german
before that's something new
oh sure
um
you can come i'm gonna pull her right ah
there she is
[Music]
i was hoping to hear some german from
you yeah
nice
nice one
yeah oh it's avid okay
i'm proud of you
my st my german student
thank you
you did so well at dokomi
thank you for watching
your lessons really really help yeah you
made use of them so much good job yes i
did that was like half of half of my
emcee was pretty much
that's pretty much your lessons
even though i think a lot of the
audience was english speaking because so
many came from outside of germany this
time i think they they all appreciated
to hear your german anyway
yeah yeah it was
german but you know
i'm sure it was it was germany you know
what else will i use that language
exactly oh where else in austria for
example because our language is also
german
oh yeah yeah
the eu has a lot of stuff like that even
in switzerland uh there are places where
not not everywhere though because their
switzerland makes it really complicated
some places they speak french some
places they speak switzerland some
places they speak uh i think even
italian
there's like a like a mixture is that
it's like a german that's very
up
oh i see yeah yeah up it sounds
fun though it sounds really funny
oh
like when i listen to it i'm like oh i
could almost understand that maybe
maybe maybe maybe roughly interesting
interesting
number between one and six go
uh
three
praise kiwawa go
oh
kiara senpai is so creative and she has
such a beautiful singing voice i love
her original songs um and she has such a
beautiful beautiful hair today her hair
is wavy and so pretty and that just fits
the occasion yes and the buns which ones
ollie always gives buns
like the moment she sent it i knew of
course all he was gonna get done yeah
and
and the tiara fits you so well
um
yes you are queen you are queen kiara no
no i am not queen
huh i'm a lady
oh yes a lady
a beautiful mademoiselle
that fits the beautiful roman you are
the star of the party no matter where
you are you
you your resistance shines like the sun
like a phoenix wow
flirt much
i must say though i'm not satisfied with
being a lady i will uh go for a queen or
princess next so
please support me in my oh yes adventure
to becoming royalty next
i think there's a lot of steps to that
first you have to become like a duchess
no i just have to make one of the one of
the royalty fell in love with me
ah that's true that's true just your
seduction i create my own country
and
well
genovia
exactly yeah i can buy an island you
know and then wouldn't that be
how easy is it to make a country i need
to look that up let's let's investigate
mm-hmm oh i'm sure there's a lot of
islands up for sale oh yeah we'll find a
good investment yeah good investment
good investment
but probably it takes a lot of
money so
please please buy my merchandise iris
yes yes your merchandise is adorable i
love the magnet set as this is
that's so sweet i personally my favorite
is the oven mitten though
oh yeah the oven mittens i don't cook
that much so it's cute though it is
adorable so get started so when you take
out that uh pizza you don't burn your
hands your precious hands
oh wow making pizza is kind of hardcore
though like i i don't know i'll just
buy the frozen finished one from the
store
oh so you don't actually have to spin it
yourself okay no no mama
no no no no no
no no no
no need to do that
the oven mittens is adorable it is
adorable though but yes i do i do like
how the whole set comes with a sticker
sheet though that's
yes
sheet yes exactly but it also comes with
a chance to join the lottery of
joining a meet and greet but details
will come later
oh a meet and greet
is this the makeup for like whoever
couldn't join the meeting during diploma
not necessarily makeup but yeah i was
thinking you know it was so so much fun
so i want to do
that more often and give people the
opportunity even if they can't come to
germany yeah yeah yeah
oh yeah
it is true you can do it awesome yeah
so thank you so much iris will
thank you so much for inviting me
alrighty then i am going to head out
happy birthday again i can't wait for
your beauty concert bye ring you bye bye
ah
my um
people are very confused um
there's some problem with the schedule
um but they'll
hi yes um
so i will just bring in the next person
[Music]
hello
is
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
okay
thank you
[Music]
oh that's the first time we talked
oh dear
that made me a bit nervous too because
like uh first time oh my god only five
minutes what do we talk about although
although i feel like i've been talking
longer than five minutes with a lot of
these people
[Music]
bye bye
i actually in japanese i say
goes other sometimes too
i don't know why
but i do
but yeah now now people
uh always say ah you know
yeah it's cute
a very cute way to end your sentences
yeah bye bye
next person please
i'll move you there we go
hello
[Music]
thank you
i played with you in hollow cure
yesterday and you're so big i love it
it's fun
i know right i'm just so destructive
yeah yeah it's invincible and oh my god
i love that axe
actually
i've just heard that everybody was
saying like yeah you're just so you're
just so strong i'm like really i didn't
even notice so i was just crushing
everything i was just crushing
everything what's your favorite planet
what's my favorite planet and of course
no besides um
actually i've been watching your stream
and one of your questions was like which
country you want to go to right oh yes
yes yes like like instead of countries
how about how about a planet that sounds
good nobody tell you about
have you ever heard about this planet
where
it rains um
i think it
rains sapphires and rubies what the
what wait wait wait i remember like it's
had something let me just google it um
hot planet hot planet i'm curious
sapphires
yeah you you care you take care of so
many planets so of course you sometimes
this is yes yeah
that's just like very names my god
and you're the one well the human the
humans are the ones that came up with
these names
you probably just go by like number one
number two number three number four i
like the shiny one
and what chad says that yeah
diamonds on neptune
[Music]
or jupiter's moon apparently apparently
it rains rubies and sapphires yes the
clouds the clouds on this planet hat p
7b it rains rubies and sapphires hats
pieces
what
that's crazy
would you like to go there i want to but
i also want to know the reason why it
does that what does google say
i didn't know it's science wait um
it has clouds made of the mineral that
forms rubies and sapphires
apparently i guess like the clouds were
just made out of it so when it rains it
just rains
that's like fantasy that doesn't sound
real like how wow
that sounds like something someone would
made up in some kind of
yeah fantasy
rpg game world or so
um love that you know
what if like we go to that planet and
like just grab lots and lots of rubies
and sapphires hell yeah i think without
you i would never be able to go so i
would definitely need your help
oh thank you and it's like pull through
because you can't die
let's go
get like we'll get like the rubies and
sapphires and then we'll name the planet
after us yes
yes all right that sounds amazing
like you know we could pay off um
everybody's bills in the kfe industry or
they're like here we go we could do that
but then like they'll still keep working
because they love you
right
i
think we just should not tell them about
it at all
okay it's always all sacred
yo thank you for telling me that i also
learned that there's uh plans where it
rains diamonds and all that that's
really cool and want to learn more about
that thank you
you're like uh
[Music]
you don't even have a big brain like
it's not empty it's not hollow
actually it's pretty it's me hollering
nobody really feels like speed and
feed and cute stuff and ye
sorry what can you repeat that
what
sana
um
um i'm looking forward i'm looking
forward to going
we can we can bring your mittens so like
you don't burn your hands
i'm so sorry you i think you flirted and
oh my god
oh sana sana
yes
um
i love you
oh one thing let's make that australian
weapon yes okay i already talked about
them about it today by the way by the
way yes i love you but we gotta make
that australia i'm gonna make that
australian collab happen
okay okay don't worry i'll i'll i i will
um after all this birthday stuff is over
i will hit you girls up again mm-hmm
please
okay i'm so excited for your life thank
you yeah i know i know you work
so hard on it i would not miss it for
the world
i hope you don't miss it thank you for
working so hard for just making
everybody have a good time you're just
so good for that and i love you
thank you
[Music]
cute
cute oh my god i'm smiling so much my
face hurt
my face horde
[Music]
[Laughter]
so
um
[Music]
hey
[Applause]
[Laughter]
eh
[Music]
[Applause]
um
ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
sorry guys it's a big mix of japanese
and english depending on whoever comes
uh if i had the time to translate i
would sorry guys
speaking of translation another person
who could translate really well if they
wanted to
oh my god hello hello
senpai
i'm not as good as you of course but
hello no you are happy birthday really
like polite japanese i admire that
yeah and and it's taking my life span
every time i try to like
speak prove a kegel ah it takes some
years of my lifespan cause it's so hard
yeah it's so hard to get
[Music]
thank you
for having me
do you want your videos
between one and six
between one and six um
i'll go with six then
oh dear you will regret this on there
oh no um
oh my god
is that how you do your love wait what
oh god
is that how you love because like
because like he's like people love your
love i i love your love yeah it could
have been me
should i have she like should i do the
kitty one yeah yeah oh god
oh my god i don't know if i got the
voice like close to your voice because
maybe a bit higher
oh
oh my god
i like how your voice kind of broke down
there
yeah
there's gotta be there's gotta be like
an alternate universe where you do you
kick category like that
you're so good at that
[Laughter]
what the hell are we doing what are we
doing yeah what the hell are we doing oh
but i saw your um pekora senpai
monomoney before season mm-hmm you're
good yeah it's good isn't it so good i
was surprised too it got better even
though i wasn't practicing
[Music]
oh my god all right
do you want to watch my concert tomorrow
i will definitely watch your concert
tomorrow like i'm going to set an autumn
and everything
thank you catch your tv i can't wait to
also some someday see your 3d as well
because i feel like oh you're gonna look
so cute with your with your barefoot
cute toes and your smile and that fluffy
dress and the fluffy hair oh my god i
can't wait i want to see it oh my god
please please wait for the
day like
yes yes you guys destroyed me too you've
waited for a long time too so
yeah
okay but it's your birthday today so
let's talk about you yeah
actually do you do you have any hint on
what songs are you gonna sing in your 3d
life
if you don't mind me asking i've already
talked and kind of confirmed that my
originals will definitely be part of it
yeah
i know
spicy virus i need to pick it up again i
kind of lost it somewhere
um yeah yeah so more than that i i
cannot spoil
just kiwawa songs and then some others
but i cannot say what i can't wait
i can't wait please
[Music]
if you invite me for anything like
there's like 99 percent chance that
outcome
all right i got you
from me
same thing the other way around if you
ever want to invite me to a collabo
because i don't get invited a lot it's
always me inviting other people
[Laughter]
oh it's okay me too
sad life
is good
yeah you know thank you happy
[Music]
i think the last time i talked to her
was on my last birthday
yeah that's true
vacation
[Music]
i was gonna like wait you guys gonna go
like a vacation vicki issue like
together i was gonna like what i didn't
hear anything about it
yeah we're actually i think ahead of
time we already like talked a lot about
it on stream
um but yeah um it was beautiful it was
amazing it was really really nice yeah
and i got to meet elena but she told me
about you know some of uh because i was
curious she told me about some of the id
members so i'm really curious i want to
meet you guys too
arleigh want to go there too oh my god
i think we should feature the
officiative next time
all right
because i think it's easier if one
person goes to indonesia then uh i don't
know six or nine indonesian girls coming
to us austria
i think we're we is different
oh yeah you can save some money then
yeah
yeah it will be kiara ferris is
speak spicy a lot after meeting rain
i did but now i kind of lost it so uh
you guys are reminding me of it thank
you very much it seems like like you
guys can't get rid of it though because
you always talk to dana
yeah it is it got i don't know it's kind
of like getting into me like spicy
you're like spicy i didn't know the
spicy word is so good
it is i like it oh nice spicy package in
part two you have to choose a number by
the way one two six go
five oh
if you oh that's perfect
it's kind of overlapping with what we
just talked about if you could travel
with kiana which country would you go
because you went to the beach last time
with iron i don't know maybe mountain
yeah i don't know where it's a good spot
though
like you know watching sunrise from the
top of the mountain that's nice
we can stay in a cabin on the mountain
but going up oh yeah i think it sounds
really exhausting
it isn't it is i know right i mean i
watched that working like an elevator to
the top of the mountain that would be
great a cable car a cable car would be
nice
oh yes cable car i think i think there
are some counters outside oh like yeah
we have a lot of cable cars that go up
to the mountains but really um skiing
people like to go so there's a lot of
cable cars
[Music]
again i am advertising austria because
we have beautiful mountains
like i really want to go there
you're welcome anytime
also you speak german so i think
actually you don't even need me to be
with you but
you need i i like i understand it when
people say it to me but i can't really
speak it back you know like it's kind of
like my brain is not isn't that working
would be good to freshen up your german
have you ever been to germany
oh no actually i haven't i only kind of
like hear it from my for my
teacher and kind of like um what's it
called again
i actually learned german third comic
books oh
what yeah there was one time i found a
manga but it was in german so i was kind
of like hey that's interesting
it was good it was like a clump man it
was crazy
so yeah i went to this old bookstore and
then i found it i was kind of like oh i
thought it was it was japanese right
when i opened it what the heck it was it
was german i was gonna like oh i guess
this is this is the sign from the
universe that i should kind of like
start studying it again uh-huh
it's about freaking time that you visit
a german speaking country then to test
out your german skills let's go
my god oh okay
i'll do my best
oh my god
[Music]
bye
a lot of people in the chat are
surprised yeah she speaks a lot of
languages pretty well
and uh
i was always thinking we should like do
a collab in german sometime yeah yeah
hey
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
um
[Laughter]
m
kiara your favorite thing is
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
is always a lot to take in because of
that erotic voice oh spicy
and speaking of spicy
are we at the end of my list
they need my spicy beloved bird hello
hello i love you hi hi
are you having a spicy night tonight
you are spicy
[Laughter]
now that you're here
you're such a dork when you say that
it's like a day fun smile
teach me something that's not dorky then
um
what do you want to say
something that's not dorky by your
standards
if i say something you're gonna then
it's gonna be dorky again so you know
you pick
[Music]
oh wait you're putting me on the spot um
how about um
um
how do you sleep
it have thick leaves yeah it means i
like you
oh
kind of spicy i already forgot
you're kind of spicy yeah
yes now i know something that's not
dorky you clap so excitedly when
sometimes when something's spicy it's so
cute it's so cute
you're spicy you're dressed all very
fancifully with your um with your grand
piano very spicy you know i don't i
don't i think the schedule got really
messed up but you know there's a reason
why i put you at the very end
because i love you and i i think i
wanted to save the best for the ending
that's literally what
my thought was
but i'm not last anymore
yeah i think yeah there's going to be
people after you probably
everything is okay
[Music]
it's a thought that matters by the way i
have a gift for you
should i should i
where should i put it in schedule
anywhere yeah i know maybe a private
message is better
oh okay i'll do a private message
love story ruined
what the
[Music]
let's look at this okay so later likes
making keyboards would you like to talk
about this
okay so this is a um
are you showing it i'm showing it are
you showing it it's oh okay so this is
like um so this is like a keyboard i
remember like you said like you wanted
you wanted like a board and then okay i
think it would also be my first time you
know like
doing a board for somebody else uh so
these are just basically the original
color of the board is actually blue but
i got to be anodized to like a mix of
colors of orange of what sorry
re-anodized what does that mean yeah
re-anodized so for it it's just it's
just like basically you change
the color of a board like you know
you order not the order like you make
somebody else do it you pay and then
they will
yeah because it's
aluminum right it's aluminum so they can
like
give certain color combinations so i
changed it
i got it changed to a mix of orange and
black i should have taken a picture of
the back oops
the back is like special tunnel
uh oh the back is exactly just like that
but because there's no keys it's like
basically clear oh yeah why is there is
there something hidden behind that emoji
when's there an emoji on there
oh i don't know i thought it was like
pretty lonely so
i think you put the sparks logo in there
it looks really cool on the on the cap
yeah i wanted to make like a
yeah
like a sparks i wanted to make a sparks
board but then like yeah because i
wanted like a kiara general board but i
don't know for when you want to stream
sparks you put the sparks enter and then
for
every day and you can put the regular
end i get it yeah it does now that you
say it does look like a spark spell
keyboard yeah oh that's so cool
don't stop don't stop just go your own
way start the fire today oh my god
that's so cool yes it is stream sparks
you gotta send that to me
yeah i'm gonna send it to you uh i gotta
like fix some things and then i'm gonna
send it to you it's i'm gonna figure
things out thank you time that's so cool
uh
and i like i think i i told you that um
you know because we talked about it in
the maldives i probably told you but i
like that you made it into a
japanese keyboard so i think that's more
i don't know useful
i like the japanese keyboard with the
japanese oh yeah
they're mostly for aesthetics i was like
wondering it's like what do you what
layout do you use because like your
laptop's like different right but then i
kind of realized like this layout is the
easiest like
this one my current keyboard on my pc is
a japanese keyboard too and i it's like
really and old so i wanted to get
a new one but i was like i uh on
austrian amazon they don't sell japanese
keyboards but i wanted a japanese
keyboard so yeah finally i got a new one
yay
like the switches are called vermilion
birds they're actually like pretty new
and then
they're like wow this is the right
switch it's perfect
yeah thank you so much it's a really
cool game
also now you have to choose a number
between one and six pick a spicy one
um
i want to choose from three
because three is rotated is like m
stands for the maldives yeah
you miss the maldives don't you i miss
them too
yeah the phrase
praise kiara
kiara yes
oh kiara is so pretty and talented she's
so good at dancing she has a beautiful
voice i like it when she's mature and
she um helps me pack up and you know the
floaties
yeah and i like it when she's very very
excited about hermit crabs i could go on
and on but you know it's a totsumachi so
thank you
i can be very mature sometimes at least
in comparison to you
in comparison to me well i mean that
just means it's the perfect dynamic
right it's like teamwork you know yeah i
miss your names
let's spend more time let's go again
someday like wherever
yeah
thank you very much
i love you animal stream animals guys we
have a song cover um from before on my
channel currently released just a few
days ago so check it out if you haven't
yet it's really fun because we
translated it not we i mean we just sang
it we got someone to translate it to
english and we did our best singing it
and it sounds really cool so check it
out check it out check it out right
[Music]
it is really spicy though yeah stream
animal
oh
next up
finally
finally we have a miss memphis
hey yo
sorry i moved you
oh hello
your mic is not working i think
okay are you dead
hello
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes i can hear you
oh
come on
oh my god
did you wake up literally 30 seconds ago
because that's what it sounds like
i mean i've been waiting
i want to tuck you in
oh you can join me
it's wine oh i want to i didn't get so
much sleep today um
oh you can get some sleep off yeah
you're so sleepy that your pronunciation
of words is very blah blah blah
it's hard to hear you but give me a
number between one and six inya
uh
three
oh dear choose a different one that why
not that one has been chosen too often
oh
what is my favorite
okay no
okay okay one one one
one
okay your favorite things about kiara
it's basically the same as free because
free is praise kiara and number one is
your favorite things
it's basically the same thing okay go
are you basically all the same questions
no no no lord
no
no actually not
so everything like your um
i like that kiara always looks up her us
she's like this
uh
really warm bright
ball of energy
thank you yeah
thank you sleepyna sleepina
it's me
that's you
[Music]
yeah you sent the video in case you
couldn't make it but i do want to watch
it now i'm curious
oh it's it's uh
you know what i might watch it anyway at
the end because at least in that one you
are probably not sleepy at least not as
sleepy as yeah
i was awake for that one i think okay
then i'll check that one out anyway
okay
happy birthday i'm really looking
forward to speaking to live yeah thank
you i'm excited for it i need to see the
results
now go back to sleeping yeah
[Music]
goodbye thank you
too tired to leave the room
now she's just
alone in a waiting room
very sleepy huh
all right next one
hello
hello hello
what's up what's up what's up
good morning
good morning sunshine
happy birthday
thank you
happy birthday to me
good
i've been awake for like three hours
hey for three hours
yeah i've been watching your stream
well that australian accent i was like
what what was that word
i was asleep later later later you're
actually the final member of my
australian collabo i've already talked
to hannah today
and to san diego
and we need to we were saying
we need to revive the australia collab
idea
yes we do we do
i will i will i will hit you girls up
for that oh now
tell me a number between one and six
uh two uh okay
what do you want to do with kiara if you
can spend one whole day with her like a
date or something
go shopping go shopping yeah you were so
fast people when i saw you kind of
very different
i think because you tried to dress fancy
um your style was very different from my
fancy style
um yeah but i wonder how you dress
i can't imagine i mean
um
hold on sorry i'm hearing double
uh
so i have your stream open as well
casually i mean i'm dressed casually now
i'm actually i locked myself in the
bathroom oh because i was getting ready
i'm just wearing sh i want to see
shorts in a crop top that's it
that's my presentation
you have a different
present hold on
nonny you already yeah you already uh
packed a present into the australian
snack box i'm going to open that in my
snack box review stream
oh it's not a snack though that's okay
the rest are snacks so
yeah true okay hey my really getting a
picture
yeah hold on
oh my gosh
excited
okay there we go
what am i hey
um that's uh just really normal
it's cute is normal yeah casual
very you just have to see her belly
button i see her thighs like there's a
lot of skin
um
[Music]
but it's a it's a
it's good clothes for hot weather
yeah
nice belly button
nice bathroom
thank you let me see let me see what i
see
oh cute cute oh cute
i see i see i'm looking at your
toiletries
oh zada
okay i can't really see them there's not
much interesting stuff here
yeah there's a there's some jewelry i
think
i like the the shower curtain but that's
probably not yours oh thank you
good stuff thank you for this precious
image
oh you'll bring it out i'll print it out
and i'll put it in the frame i'll
treasure it
i'm so excited for your life tomorrow
yeah i hope you can watch it
please watch it i'm gonna try i'm gonna
try wait what let me see let me see what
time it it's it's at wait what time is
9 am jst 1
am
oh easy i'll be oh let's go
i'm a watch i'm the one i'm so excited i
heard you're quite the dancer too so you
know between us dancers i hope you can
appreciate the effort i put into
learning all the choreographies
oh my god i feel the pain i i'm so proud
of you you did great thank you
thank you bills for coming i'm so happy
you came
and it was really nice even though even
though like we we barely talked when i
saw you because you know we were
streaming and then you left pretty soon
now yeah but i was so very happy to see
you so i hope i hope we can repeat that
and then we go shopping when we have
some more time another time
yeah
thank you
thanks and enjoy your day bails
the rat's not leaving there she is
that's actually goes
around um
i think
that might be it
oh because there's no one in the waiting
room i think that's it
but i have uh i think
you know the
videos i have two videos
[Music]
okay
let's watch this let me put it up to the
top
could anyone choose four no i think in
the end every number got chosen at least
once yeah yeah yeah okay go
this
wait
i had it set to the wrong
it's fauna obviously but i don't hear
the audio
right
um
you see and i see what you're doing
there fauna
i shall
is this
was that double i think that was double
let me mute it on that side okay
happy birthday kiara happy birthday
well happy early birthday because we all
know your real birthday is tomorrow
tomorrow with your first ever 3d
birthday live
and i'm so excited i really can't wait i
was
i i'm still just feeling so grateful
that i was able to watch you firsthand
yeah see a little bit behind the scenes
and see just how much
hard work and love and care that you've
been pouring into this for so long
and i can't wait to see how it turns out
in the end i just know it's going to be
amazing and
everybody watching let me just say since
i got a little bit of a sneak preview or
in for a treat
kiara you are really amazing and you've
earned this you deserve this i'm so
happy for you and i just want to give
you a huge congratulations and wish you
the best
birthday ever i hope it's amazing and
that everything turns out just like you
dreamed of
and
everybody watching
[Music]
prepare yourselves i don't think you can
be prepared for what you're going to see
it's going to be pretty good i'm so
excited okay now i'm nervous again i
will stop rambling i just want to wish
you a happy birthday kiara thank you for
being my friend and thank you for
continuing to be an inspiring senpai to
me with all your hard work and your
amazing talent and singing and
dancing
happy birthday
and
i will send you this png just in case
you would like to become kieran too she
did send it to me
thank you
why didn't you take up the whole screen
that was very sweet oh phone is so
charming oh
thank you for making that video she did
watch me um a whole day on that one day
where i basically had to record
everything in one day from originally
you know the original plan was recording
it in three days but then a lot of
things went wrong and took time and i
had to do it all in one day and that was
coincidentally the one day when fauna
was there and you know
uh i felt i felt bad about you know not
being able to
talk and hang out more because we were
busy the whole day but she
seemed to enjoy watching me dance all
the time so
yeah i hope she had a good time anyway
yeah
thank you fauna for being there and
sending that video i have one more
i have to fix the audio though one
second
why shop there we go
uh
this one
obviously that's amen
ame could not call in so she sent me a
video
okay
and
go
hello
sorry i couldn't call it in person but
i'm going to say happy birthday kiara
i can't wait to see your concert hey i
love you i love it i miss you
oh my god i can't wait to see you again
and for all of us to be together again
because it was the best yeah yeah really
we're really excited to see how the
concert turned out and
i know you work so hard it'll be a blast
the best phoenix in the whole world
sorry i kind of have the sniffles at the
moment but oh no oh happy new year
we speak happy happy birthday
happy birthday to you
[Music]
sorry the audio on this i think it might
need to be boosted
[Music]
i like i like the music
howdy
[Music]
anyways quiet i hope you have a
wonderful rest of your birthday
countdown collins and thank you for
being you no you heard it
all right
hey
hey you heard what she was saying right
you're confusing me all right okay okay
okay okay that's such a confusing
meme
okay bye okay bye
she's so cute thank you amen
i think the people who worked the most
on this whole thing is amin me and now
kanauru for like editing it all together
in a short
period of time so
yeah it's like it has our our sweat and
our blood and our tears
engraved in it so
i i i'm really
happy
if everybody can um you know praise
amitu for and kanorutu for the hard work
that they're putting into it too not
only me okay that's important
now yeah we can watch the
ina video where do i have it oh
did i download it already i think i did
it did but i'll download
it
cancel where is it
oh there it is okay it's great for some
reason
why is it grey
one second
the inna video when she was not sleepy
as
i wonder we will probably have a
difference like night and day
here oh
wait which one was the red one this one
was the right one
and go
my dearest
takana shikiyara it's like a god if
you're receiving this message
it means i
know my emails have overslept a whole
lot of english myth
has failed
to wake up in time you didn't i'm proud
of you
i'm sorry it's okay you woke up but you
were tired
um
jokes aside
color um i am sending the message just
in case
i don't wake up in time it's very smart
as as you have
noticed before a couple of times
but
i just want to wish you a happy
happy
happy birthday
and i am really really really really
looking forward to your 3d live
and um i just want to say as as your gen
mate um it has been
the most amazing
um
almost almost two years now since we
debuted
you know you've always been that
positive uh warm energetic ball of
energy
in our group
and i really always appreciate how
you always look out for us
and how much uh speak so slowly
how much you put in all the effort you
put into everything you do
i try i really want to say that i
respect you a lot chiara
i love you um i love you too um i hope
that we can do more fun things
uh yeah more fun things because the
recording was suffering i'm sorry i'm
sorry i'm sorry for making you something
kfp i just want to see the chiara has
worked so so so hard
in life
so i hope you guys really look forward
to it
let me know maybe maybe um there will be
some
fun surprises whoa
strange lion
i don't know if i can see this no you
can't anyways
happy happy happy birthday how are you
king kiara
i hope you have a wonderful wonderful
wonderful day
and um get some good rest after after
everything is done okay
take care of yourself
and also
i hope that one day i can visit you and
pet all your cats
and yeah again you have very soft hair
anyways i don't know where i'm going
about this
[Music]
and i guess i'll see you next time okay
thank you bye
bye bye
bye
[Music]
i know i say what a lot too
it's just
why such a good word isn't it thank you
eno for that video i'm so proud you made
it there's another special video i want
you guys to watch with me but before
that let me put on something that
where is it
i got this from football green standby
because she couldn't call in but she
sent me glasses of course because she's
the
glasses
so millier
but now i have
a video from the fans that i already saw
like the thumbnail of it basically so um
i already know what it is kind of uh but
i'm excited to see this
how do i not spoil this
oh
wait wait wait wait when
i think i have to spoil it
no wait
wait
i need to fix the audio because i don't
think you heard that
ah
or did you maybe you did
okay go
[Music]
is
the power steps
[Music]
i love that i love when they do that
[Applause]
hi hi
[Music]
this
oh
[Music]
just so powerful too
yes i can do some of these
[Music]
i
damn son
they were perfectly choreographed
amazing that's that's like the really
hardcore
highest level of otage
absolutely lit don't be super lit
and i want to know who's behind that i
was sent this by manager's son through
the fans
uh
but i don't know
who these people are
were they hired by kfp or are they kfp
but now i mean when i do a concert i'm
not expecting you guys to go this hard
on on otage because you usually don't
have the space for it anyway it's it was
on youtube but it was unlisted i don't
know if if they want to share it then
they can send me the link on twitter and
i shall um
uh post like retweet it or so
so you guys can all see it again and
appreciate it on on in the youtube
oh that's so cool hire them for the next
cons oh
yeah like last time i took me i had
backup dancers now this would be kind of
a different type of backup dancer huh i
like the idea
it's very cool because
like overseas people
don't know this
thing so much but
uh
i think it would be really impressive
and hell i love light sticks
yeah i actually have one more one more
yes yes
[Music]
you
there's one more one more guest who was
able to make it after all
[Music]
yay
[Laughter]
[Music]
is
yes yes let's go let's play okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
me
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
um
i
[Music]
yo
um
[Music]
okay
glad she made it uh so sweet so sweet
she originally chose number three number
one but i thought you know it's more
interesting to ask her um to have her
answer number four
so
uh that's it for the collins and uh for
the videos that i've received i think so
uh
i hope you enjoyed it i had a good time
being appraised and talking to these
sweet sweet sweet chicks and girls and
what's the real deal the most exciting
thing is happening tomorrow
my concert after this i'm uploading one
more countdown video and then after that
the only thing that's left is
birthday 3d live 2022 and i hope you all
are going to be there feel free to take
screenshots and all that and then post
them on twitter with the hashtag i think
it was
it's in the title of this stream what
was it i don't know i don't even know
kiana birthday canada 3d birthday i
think that's it it was really simple
so
make sure to do that maybe with the help
of the hashtag screenshots we might even
reach 1 million twitter followers
because coincidentally we're really
freaking close to that
so let's stress let's try to make it
happen
yeah
hashtag in the title thank you so much
i'm glad you all were here today to
spend the countdown to my birthday with
me
um yeah see you tomorrow tomorrow and in
germany we say au vida zen
kyo amino
get the merch get the merch get the
merch get the merch
it's like covered by all kinds of things
but get the merch oh bye bye i love you
kfb
i love you
[Music]
i love you love you lovely
you