foreign
[Music]
Advent calendar
well for me it's still the fourth of
December a Sunday the Second Sunday
since the whole Advent uh Reef thing
so I want to light a candle of you guys
and then I'm going to read you a lovely
Christmas story
so uh as you may remember I told you I
made this whole thing in
um a stream in the hand cam stream and
by myself from scratch yeah so now every
Sunday until Christmas I have to light
the candles on the first Sunday
oh
wait I'm bad at this
on the first Sunday we lit the first
candle
and now on the second Sunday
we're lighting the second candle yep
[Music]
yep so now while we're looking at my
beautiful Advent wave let me tell you
the story of this will be a long video
by the way a little bit the story of
The Elves and the Shoemaker maybe you
already know it I heard about it before
it's a Grims fairy tale I used to read
Grimm's Fairy Tales as a series on my
channel in German but I'm reading it in
English this time all right let's go
that once was a Shoemaker who from no
fault of his own had become so poor that
at last he had nothing left but just
sufficient level for one pair of shoes
in the evening he cut out the leather
intending to make it up in the morning
and as he had a good conscience he lay
quietly down to sleep first commanding
himself to God
in the morning he said his prayers and
went down to begin his usual work but
behold
shoes were already made
stood upon his board
the man was amazed and knew not what to
think but he took the shoes into his
hands to look at them more closely and
they were so neatly worked that not a
stitch was wrong just as if they had
been made for a prize
surely said he in a tone of Wonder it
must have been a master Craftsman who
made these I do not know a Shoemaker in
the world who could have made them so
beautifully
presently a customer came in and as the
shoes play pleased him very much he paid
down much more than usual and so much
indeed that the Shoemaker was able to
buy with it leather for two pairs but
evening he had got his leather shaped
out and when he arose the next morning
he prepared to work with fresh Spirit
but there was no need for the shoes
stood all perfect on his board
he did not want either for customers for
two came who paid him so liberally for
these shoes that he bought with the
money material for four pairs more this
also which he cut out during the evening
he found already made when he awoke and
so it continued what he cut out
overnight was in the morning turned into
the neatest shoes possible this went on
for months more and more people came to
the shop to buy the shoes which his
unknown friends made so well and those
who bought were so pleased with their
purchase that he told everyone else
never had a Shoemaker and his wife been
so busy not only did the lucky man
regain his former position but he became
more and more prosperous
one evening not long before Christmas as
he had cut out the usual quantity he
said to his wife before going to bed
what's their you to stopping up this
night to see who is it that helps us so
kindly his wife was satisfied to do as
he wished and fastened up a light and
then they hid themselves in the corner
of the room where hung some clothes
which concealed them
as soon as it was midnight in came two
little mannequins who squatted down on
the board and taking up the prepared
work set to with their little fingers
stitching and ceiling and hammering so
swiftly and lightly that the Shoemaker
could not take his eyes off of them for
astonishment
he had never seen work done so quickly
before they did not cease until all was
brought to an end and the shoes stood
ready on the table and then they sprang
quickly away
the following morning the wife said to
the Shoemaker
the kind little man have made us rich
and we must show our gratitude to them
for although they run about they must be
cold since they have nothing to cover
their bodies in this winter weather
I will make a little shirt coat
waistcoat trousers and stockings for
each and do you make a pair of shoes for
the not very nicest for each
the husband very gladly agreed to do
this and one evening when they had got
everything ready he and his wife laid
their presents instead of the usual work
on the board and hit themselves to
receive the result
at midnight in came the elves jumping
about and soon prepared to begin their
work but when they saw no leather only
the Nutty little clothes they at first
were astonished but soon showed their
pleasure and Glee they'd ruined their
coats and smoothed them down and sang
smart and that dear boys are we cobblers
will no longer be
and so they went on hopping and jumping
over the stools and chairs and at last
out at the door after that evening they
did not come again but the Shoemaker
prospered and all he undertook and lived
happily to the end of his days
the end
thank you all for watching this day too
yeah
um don't worry I will not be here every
fourth day it just so happened that I
needed to fill up this day I hope you're
enjoying the Advent calendar so far
don't forget to check by tomorrow and
don't forget to tweet out with the
hashtag Holo en Advent
bye bye
foreign