[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
is the most
thrilling stream
okay
this okay okay okay hey welcome
everybody
[Music]
nice
[Applause]
let's just introduce ourselves
[Laughter]
[Music]
I can't help it
Bakery
[Laughter]
yeah it is
[Music]
not framingo
Flamingo beautiful
nice to meet you
yeah
I I am Felix not a chicken takanasiki
oh my
mama oh hi I'm nanashi mume I'm an owl
not a kiwi hey I thought you were gonna
say another towel
oh right no I am I am one oh okay
okay
she admits it okay
and then the money maker in Hollow cure
that's a weird introduction hi and I'm a
p foul not a turkey I'm popular from
Whole Life Indonesia generation two hi
thanks for making so much money for me
you're welcome
I'm uh
[Applause]
[Music]
duck manager
my name is
[Applause]
[Laughter]
you can't help it it is what it is so
we're gonna play Pummel party which is
basically like Mario party but on PC and
for more people than four so let's have
fun together
I hope the settings are okay
I'm just praying you know it's the first
time for everybody yes yeah first time
this oh oh what are these numbers let's
freaking go oh my God
he's wearing the chicken head
oh treasure we have to go here didn't it
cost money okay I think so
today is a test
what is this uh weapons weapons
oh nice yes
today you know oh my God jump
the sparkle shows you what's the closest
route I think
[Music]
it is
my first time
I landed on a good field
Reaper
would you like me oh
[Laughter]
okay nice where do I go where do I go
where do I land I'm just like oh my God
[Music]
together big birds
oh
[Laughter]
hey here we go
uh you can claim the lands
[Music]
okay
gifting gifts Griffin gifts get as many
presents as you can bring them back to
your tree
okay okay
jump action why is action Orange
here's the color that you are
um
okay
okay how do you how do we steal
I don't know
maybe we'll find out yes yes
we'll find out
just do it wait where am I where am I on
the bottom middle middle probably let's
go
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go
okay oh but we can still see it
[Applause]
thank you
[Laughter]
[Applause]
oh my gosh
um
be careful she's got a gun why do you I
don't know it's a very violent Mario
Party
um
Mario Party
[Music]
okay
uh
[Music]
some kind of yellow yes
yes
[Music]
thank you
praise bomb is a space key okay okay
okay
what the structure to Triumph okay
we gotta play it okay to understand
not understandable
oh wait
why you die I thought it was chicken
me died too
I thought it always makes you in the
middle
really
oh
they blowed up my body again
[Music]
where is the strategy
the strategy is still alive I couldn't
feel there
hey I want to play too yeah me too much
um
oh
that is Reina
no I died oh
let's go again
[Applause]
another chance
another chance okay down to how many
rounds
ah good questions
[Music]
until the timer is over
oh my God
I'm shocked
[Music]
stay there forever yes
your chest use 40 I open oh
oh my
God what's up
[Applause]
[Music]
treasure
it's also a weapon
um
oh
but this is good this is good okay
[Music]
um
go horsey go no oh
how do you look at the map what do you
press oh oh
the keyboard or a controller keyboard
[Music]
press try M for space I will trust this
okay yeah that's the closest if it has
the but you don't want to take a ride on
my Cannon to a nearby Square
yes maybe yes yeah yeah
I feel like it would get you closer
isn't it 40 keys I wouldn't have enough
10 10 Keys it says 10 keys
yeah
the treasure is 40. last time maybe you
can still get some in the mini game but
maybe I can
she's thinking
maybe I can't oh
oh I decline
oh
No Doubt
you should have gone on the phone oh
is it even worth it going towards the
treasure I feel some someone will reach
it before me but
oh well no
am I going to the same you know what I
will take the boat to see where it goes
oh wait it's a cannon not a boat what
the hell yeah
ah
memories round and moved to dodge okay
like it's a memory game
okay okay
I I definitely understand
hey I don't know which one I am wait
what did I know yeah
[Music]
okay
lucky like human it's so confusing I
keep on looking at them
did you ever find out where you were I
found out after I exploded
I saw where I was I didn't look maybe it
wasn't me
maybe it wasn't me oh oh yeah wow
board event
yeah now you can't cross some of these
paths anymore I think hello hello what's
this what what's this what events
oh yeah
the blood water is toxic
is it poisonous oh my God
I got Robin thank you I only have one
anyways don't don't take HP no
no yeah
okay let's not it up this time is
it rhythm game
I don't know which one is I don't know
which one is beef
Rhythm games
[Laughter]
it's a chance for me okay okay
[Music]
wait which one am I on purple I think
wait which am I I'm not any of these oh
okay I see it okay yes I am
oh okay easy easy okay it will get much
more difficult I guess
uh
okay let's go okay
okay
okay okay okay
[Applause]
wow
okay
imaginary rhythm
yeah in your heart the rhythm is in your
mind
um
is it also like the better the timing is
the more points you get I wonder I think
so
[Music]
right
[Laughter]
am I lost again no way
oh my gosh
I need key I need key I need
get those keys oh get them
me oh my God
it says use item what's that for
to blow the person right next to you up
yeah
hey you have a bump right let me choose
like it's I think maybe if we scroll ah
oh what happened I don't know you can
choose who to blow up you're choosing
right now maybe scroll or
yeah yeah it shows you
maybe go for the strongest person
yeah maybe
oh my God
[Applause]
[Music]
just second
doesn't matter
this time oh you got some keys though
noise
everybody
first time first time first time
birds have to fly
nice landing damage
okay oh look at the blood sorry
raspberry
cute okay
okay
dog is there a dog in the room
no no no
foreign
[Music]
wait can I reach the key maybe if I get
a good
roll
oh it's a med kit so you don't die wait
I could reach it
no what the
yeah I would have had enough keys
all these kind of party games hate me
no
[Music]
okay then I go here
next time I guess okay okay thanks
it looks like worms
use your tanks turrets to destroy the
terrain ah yeah yeah it's like warming
left right
okay and I'm orange I don't understand
don't mess it up okay perfect to
understand okay
I don't understand
how to shoot again
just click click for shooting
none click what is Click
Mouse oh I guess hmm
oh okay you can't land in the water I
suppose yeah I I don't under
yeah
okay
[Applause]
I will have a big comeback surely
someday if I buy a water bye-bye
merry juice
[Music]
mine
congratulations I guess
oh no
wrecking balls oh
[Music]
you have
teleportation wait how can you where can
you go with that I don't know
[Music]
I wanna open this present oh I'm
sniffing it what is it good thing right
it has to be a good thing I don't know
well you don't know them how to choose
you already chose now
yeah but like the thing is I couldn't
even like what's that
oh
look at the magic wand
Magic Stick
oh it's empty because somebody already
died
you have so many
yeah she does but no teleportation
um
yeah she won't use it yet
okay okay bless you
thank you my town sorry oh but you can
get yeah
property that's key yeah oh can I get my
no no no area but healing okay that's
fine
you chose this game we're helicopters
oh
[Music]
okay play me through it by shooting down
the most players
okay yeah boy
oh boy
oh it's so retro no no no no
oh we respawn yeah yeah
I'm orange guys where am I somebody was
blue
I don't know remains are black
pepper is strong
ER
no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
me
[Laughter]
okay at least I'm not fifth I share
fourth let's go what the heck are you
holding
[Laughter]
I need to play this game more often so
then I'll get better at it yeah Nana
you've played this before right no
literally it's my first time
you're struggling with language and
resolution
uh you're just you're just good she got
a shotgun I'm just good I guess
you don't do not hurt anybody
yeah I haven't had the chance to use
anything
I don't have any items sadly except
teleportation I think
one two three days how many steps does
she have oh yeah
foreign
big big number please
okay
medium uh our art of your map uh what
how many more steps
or it doesn't say you either have five
four or five
okay even if I go down I have to go
yeah down is like you have to go the
other way I guess so then I go this way
but I don't know where I land
[Music]
on healing
the last person standing wins oh my God
it will not be me
it will not be me no okay
no it won't I'm so unlucky today
yeah make sure you know where you are
yeah no
[Music]
yeah no oh I am shooting I wasn't okay
maybe I'm shooting but I just don't see
it
I lost track of myself
[Music]
oh
ing
[Music]
I believed
first time it's impossible
if I take if I use an item I can still
roll can I
uh I think yes unless it specifies
otherwise okay maybe I'll open present
ah it can be something good or bad it
says
no no oh teleport teleport with who
welcome back oh my God
[Music]
who's close
is okay
oh wait four steps one two three four oh
actually I hated that we have to
actually count
eh what's this field again the the white
uh skull is just losing something can I
attack that no no no no no it's um good
I don't believe you I don't believe you
I'm gonna go to the action one I think
it just changes the water maybe ah
blood
um
I'm So Far Away what does this do magnet
yeah
oh
how many did you take
almost all of my remaining
oh my god do you see how many Louis has
Lou has 83 degrees
I didn't get trophy yeah
in your head
yeah that's the thing like I never know
I don't
I don't I I believe in the game or luck
I I believe in nothing like I thought
the skull was bad but then like the guy
was like I will be your master Get
Wrecked
[Music]
it
didn't hurt too bad what is this
I'll pick up those keys when I pass by
what are you gonna use huh
I wanna add some mooses
[Music]
dark magic oh
oh
what oh what is this you get a friend
why don't I get a friend I guess
this is the money bunny from
it stays there
if this may happen if I go towards the
bunny probably
nothing good I assume maybe it eats you
alive
it kills everything in its path
apparently
oh
[Music]
well would you look at where I am baby
let's go
[Music]
come on wait what the I'm just on
the side now
yeah
I see but he didn't do anything
the bunny's still a baby I think bubble
bubble bunny no it has to get bigger I
don't I don't know I literally I don't
know I was like wait what a bunny
Polo bunny
[Music]
zero yet
happens if you get zero HP nice why am I
still on the side
what's the bunny doing ah the Bunny and
the bunny doing
what
that's the pony
what the what does that mean found
Tigers riding pandas
okay okay
wait how do you count
uh just um your action button whatever
that is oh okay okay
it looks right
it's not working
huh
wait no
it's not showing yet but you
have to put in the actual number or
no you can't like you know like you're
like
cars passing
your action key space space okay I think
I got points but why did I get zero ah I
still don't know how to count though
um
I don't know how to to count what
the
I got points what
what am I doing
I couldn't count the single time
[Music]
apparently it was space foreign
I accept
what the man
I don't have enough
use item
you're the item
oh
you want to teleport you can switch with
somebody
eh why you make me suffer even more oh
I'm sorry I don't care where I am I
guess because I couldn't buy a treasure
chest anyway
yeah why did you want to change with me
because I can't get it anyways okay
I see I see I see
um okay
fine
no bunny the bunny is just there
[Music]
mysterious what is mysterious bunny
mysterious mysterious bunny
nobody knows oh maybe I just collects
all the keys on the path and then brings
it back to you also the description says
it does something evil hmm
we'll find out when it's too late
you're on the bunny I will protect you
bunny
now you want baby I have no money
baby bunny
baby bunny safer to go here
I would like to open it but I have two
keys
oh
my gosh
not baby oh my god oh what do you think
good baby it's like Tetris
[Music]
check where you are
oh
okay oh
oh okay
okay
some people are really nice
okay I think they become faster yeah
[Music]
finish
come on come on come on come on
okay okay
[Music]
oh
oh yeah we need so please don't let me
finish to that
um
oh my God yummy yummy
yummy I was thinking of umai
plant evil evil eggplant
teleport with who
yes
[Music]
all those keys on the ground as well
in the graveyard oh
she can't move can I I can't move
I mean I mean Louis can't move anymore
after teleporting
so somebody could teleport oh my God hey
go for it
and then the next person made a
teleports with you
oh my God
oh
[Music]
no no one no one no one
I just like
lonely lonely
okay what can I do
yeah yeah oh oh okay from the graveyard
teleportation
okay
where's the oh look at the map
oh
um
there's the treasure box over it's still
the same place
there
and how many do I maybe maybe you girls
should have teleported to where I am
because I'm standing on it
yeah but also
stand on it does this count I don't know
I've never played yeah not sure because
like she already was like offered right
but maybe I really don't know yeah but
yeah I don't want to give uh you can't
move but can you maybe buy something oh
well maybe oh well I guess we'll never
find out yes we'll never find out that's
so true
well I hope the rabbit's nice to me I'm
still mama I need more items I sure hope
so not anymore
thank you yes a rocket I need weapons
okay strong yes
everybody's going the other way I'm
still alive
[Music]
hold on
survive longer gonna get more points I'm
playing with the most but okay after
three rounds up for free rounds Disney
yeah three rounds okay this is fun this
will be fun
[Laughter]
sorry okay oh
well done this nice okay
[Music]
gently let's yeah let's chill you know
no ikioi yeah
it's so slippery
gently wow they just they just they just
do it on their own I don't even have to
do anything
in life and this was one of them
foreign
oh
yeah oh my God
[Applause]
[Music]
on the sides very
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah not lonely I'm still here oh
I'm oh oh maybe close but no money
oh no
where are you gonna go you have no money
even though yeah
better to save money
foreign
[Music]
there's someone right next to you
oh I think everybody you pass by You're
Gonna Hurt No no no no no no no oh
protect
yes is it ah
okay natural and Cactus that's natural
um
what does it do maybe she also just
turns into eggplant no okay
okay can you blow up the cactus let's
see oh oh right
now
I know okay eggnog is Time Bomb okay
is it gonna stay forever
now foreign
though
it's not middle
what does you know we just always go
after oh okay wow wait what you're not
oh
something like that
yeah how do you grab it
you have to punch me
[Laughter]
I think that's a win for me let's go
give me more keys not just six Keys yeah
foreign
[Music]
cheers
[Applause]
[Music]
shut down
me again because it's only defeat look
where the laser goes look where the
laser goes yeah like the hitbox is kind
of crazy
[Music]
duck duck noise do it
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
I meant to go back oh
do it Revenge
she likes paints
you shoot in the
Suites
orange so what
someone if I'm Orange it's closer to red
logically you should shoot the one who's
number one
oh my God
yes wow many many dangerous people yeah
don't trust the cute face
your face evil minds
[Music]
I mean yeah you you try to shoot her
twice so yeah one time miss one time
mistake the first time time I purposely
didn't shoot her the second time I also
meant to know really
um how about you just don't shoot them
okay
but still alive
no 130 forever no no no no no today is
[Laughter]
bye now
yeah
[Music]
okay game time Baby Bullet
I'm
not my not good at this me neither
okay
[Music]
so what the
Jew juice what
[Laughter]
the hell yeah
okay there was a
dog
apparently yeah
you're gonna kill me yeah he's going to
kill me
do it do it
bye bye bye announcement
do they know
a shotgun oh
I got a beehive
[Music]
it was a grenade
wait I have
this
you can blow up to people yeah
I know
let's go wow
[Applause]
[Music]
oh no I'm still in the reach oh look at
her body okay body dancing
[Laughter]
wow that present present what present
I'm safe for now presentation
where oh
no you can buy this treasure
nice good choice
[Music]
now only Louis left for a treasure it's
okay
JP
basement okay
okay okay
[Music]
my graveyard a homie
um wait uh let me see
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
Subaru body still having seizures yeah
somebody
ever dancing
why
is the Subaru senpai
yeah yeah
[Laughter]
uh my homie in the graveyard oh
maybe there is no Auto there
um
why laugh why laughing it's your body oh
God oh God so scary
endo
[Applause]
This is the End World premium
okay
there's so many controls we use items
and drop on me okay
I don't know if I can remember so much
okay uh if you die once I guess it's
over now
I don't know
um
I am good at first person shooter maybe
yes
[Music]
foreign
we're having fun in the middle
how do you how do you go somewhere else
can you jump that far easy easy okay
this is the kind of FBS I like oh banana
come back
oh it's so hard to aim with controller
[Music]
is that heal
Ed that oh um
I love you I love you
nobody know what
yeah
we're on a different Islands
no heel for you every time I move I also
move up and drop him down
oh yeah
I can only do this well now we're all
over here
oh my gosh
yes
[Music]
oh my god oh how much oh one more
minute one more minute
[Music]
oh it doesn't reach
raise a purple item purple
I love you
[Music]
Sapphire
hi
[Music]
hi hi
[Laughter]
oh my God
one two finish
[Applause]
[Music]
for me
towel
I am towel
laser op Nerf the laser yeah
[Laughter]
these are so cringe
okay
no camping campers
oh my gosh try hard okay
toxic yeah
[Music]
which one did we choose
I still have no Kiana area so sad so I
have no rain area I have no roommate
area JP takeover
yeah JP takeover yeah this land is JP
land this belongs to JP where where do I
drop this can I oh
Out Of Reach
um maybe not because I don't know
[Music]
the quinoa where are Treasures
um
[Laughter]
but maybe after me mume will try to
switch with me and then you don't have
it what about you Dana now what if she
lies you don't know
[Music]
I have to risk it I think I have to risk
it see that's a gun
teleport Festival
yeah they're probably gonna switch with
me now
are you gonna teleport
I don't think I have
but I don't have money I don't know I
don't have enough money anyway you're
you don't have to worry about me but I
mean if I'm not first then somebody can
still change with me
okay I feel like if I drop this behind
me
so it's one of the bees hurt me too hmm
or is that not how the game works but
the thing is like why would you drop it
on me instead of other people because
like I
senpai
Senpai violence why
Senpai respects
[Music]
oh but you only have 11 Keys yeah
beautiful
oh
wait pause
that he the middle one like you have to
make a
oh the face from the picture but you
went with the car one
okay
oh
um
maybe controller is best for this
[Music]
also so difficult
okay okay
[Laughter]
I think I I think I think I got it now I
think I'm gonna but I I got it too late
as long as I don't finish last oh
hey mother don't go why the I got
uh
oh cool man
where's the goal literally I don't know
this is the second time I'm passing here
I guess there's more than one oh I guess
whoever is the furthest
one more
time for sure still so much time go
you have troubles of the controls but
you're so good
uh I I don't know where the accident is
there's no exit whistle
no eggs
[Music]
okay okay
come back are they all behind us
I was close Lena
[Laughter]
oh my God
[Applause]
that means I go first
right oh my God
no way oh
my God
oh love it I just need a lot of points
please oh yes yes I mean a lot of um
yeah okay oh my gosh
[Music]
[Applause]
Japanese team
foreign
chat yes okay
ah okay okay okay okay okay
uh thank you foreign
okay
we've been playing for one hour
and okay
okay speed speeds go golden okay okay we
have to hurry a little bit
because
huh okay okay okay
yeah bye yeah bye yeah bye I mean did I
accidentally do something no right it's
YouTube
uh the RTA
wait next door
[Music]
it was my turn I clicked out for a
second okay
this way
run mommy run I'm running run run run
everybody
yeah we have ten turns left so yeah I
don't have enough coins okay my Tom what
town oh
look at that
why
you you yeah
[Music]
I might not have enough money
scary I know it's a little bunny turning
whenever he moves I just
[Applause]
[Music]
okay make the curry space for picking up
items space okay space space button okay
oh okay
yeah all right okay
oh
[Music]
okay okay
why is it wrong because you don't have
it in your hand anymore already I think
oh so it's not that it's wrong or
something yeah since you already dropped
it anyway
okay okay okay
[Music]
should we take them from where from here
anywhere anywhere
okay
none of us are doing this correctly I
think I am oh yeah
why okay
everyone has zero points though
I don't understand maybe afterwards they
counted oh
okay okay okay
the right order too
ah
okay maybe
[Applause]
[Music]
wow okay we have to gather
everything and then put into the pot
everything at the same yeah I thought
you can only carry them that's what I
thought too
well done
um okay
oh yeah
figured it out
weird though I mean not too late I guess
I want okay yeah
um
[Music]
no movements okay
what's up
golf
huh oh action
oh my God two two HP I'm sorry
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay
[Music]
yes important don't forget your HP HP
present
that's a lot of damage
15. a lot of damage but you don't have
to shoot Louis she's already dying she's
not shooting
oh you want to help us get out of the
water
before she dies we're gonna make sure
okay
bye
moment now has so much we have to take
it from her mommy
[Music]
I represent
s in ID
I do too
take some Indonesian then
hahaha
oh ah R.I.P what
rest in peace Louis
in peace this position is better maybe
yeah maybe this better you can go ah no
you can't go up
really yeah I don't know you have to go
around
[Music]
for now who knows for now last time I
think it was like for two rounds the
water was up underwater right yeah
oh foreign
don't push
time
just gotta wait for them to fall off I
don't like the camera right here yeah me
neither I can't see wow oh someone fella
oh
[Music]
cute music
yes
like a Christmas
okay I'm losing this one
[Music]
what just happened
goodbye my friends
my friend
I'm not last I'm not lost
[Music]
behind me yeah
I love you oh
[Music]
okay no no problem no problem no problem
no problem it's okay Sometimes You Gotta
Lose sometimes you win
you're so right oh that's a lot of keys
that's a lot of keys there
another player
what are you looking at hmm
okay
[Music]
Luma is taking flight oh
mermaid okay
see you later you or you can take a
break you have free trophies
[Laughter]
trophy
I don't have enough
[Music]
um
no I can't okay I can only use my
speed speed
gotta go fast for Louise
okay cactus
don't touch her she has a sensitive face
going on okay
but it protected you right you didn't
lose anything
[Music]
he he
is
okay change with Reina
ah you can't
foreign
will she stay there hmm
yeah
hmm
okay next last song what item do I have
the other fourth oh do I you don't have
teleport yeah it's okay I don't have
money either I'll just use present
but if you delay but Subaru will be top
if she gets the um oh no no may still
talk I know the first game
oh
the boy no thank you
finally okay
first
quinoa area bunny
somebody killed the bunny please bunny
bunny I'm still here so this is my slime
Oh wrong that's very um I don't know
yeah I played this before so I chose it
but it doesn't mean I'm good at it
okay what drawing roll uh barrel roll
roll roll it
okay okay this is maybe a better
controller
oh there's also aim
what oh no
no just automatically
wow
[Music]
where is everybody good question I only
see this guy
oh my God oh my God I
feel very low
well I really
I need a Kill
no no no no no no music
just like I'm in the sky
birds flying together
take care oh it's raining it's raining
fire you might have two kills too oh oh
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
yes
who was that who just died
[Applause]
[Music]
oh bye bye water again
I drink it
[Applause]
[Music]
okay well oh present again but
mats kalka
open
gotta use it while I have it but please
don't teleport ah I choose the game
again again
these ones I don't know I'll just go for
the shoulder
what did you choose the shooter
you like the pew pew I guess okay
[Laughter]
well yes we'll see it don't wait a few
months
what it does I just I don't have
anything against you I just want to see
what it says
10 damage
[Music]
it's fine
why is my corpse on the floor when I
didn't die
if you take damage
silver is gonna get it I don't know
which way which where should I go
duck noises
I hope that it's not if you dance on me
I want to take a chance do it do it go
this way oh
oh
um no
okay
I want to go to the other side
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
I did I took the wrong chance perhaps
you can fix it maybe
today
I have no pee
no Kiana
what
is the easiest chance
okay
come or I don't know moment
Just moment yeah
something more violent perhaps
looks like a okay
oh
no let's go
let's go
back to the graveyard
graveyard people
[Laughter]
the first trophy
yes I want
I want you
bunny is six members
oh okay make sure you don't use the Box
shoot shoot oh there's two shooting
buttons
foreign
yes I don't know yeah maybe don't shoot
Bakugan
which one am I I don't know which one I
am uh
okay
the one with the fireworks don't oh okay
oh no oh okay okay I get it
okay okay okay
yeah no no no no no no no no no no
I see
slow and and fast bonus
my Point's very low I think oh no
okay
the control they're so difficult really
maybe should have played with keyboard
maybe I always prefer keyboard
oh
[Music]
wow no bump ever
I was looking at somebody like the first
10 seconds I thought it was okay
happens sometimes oh okay
oh kettle shaving it
saving it for the cactus yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
why sad face happy face happy face happy
Louis happy
happy happy happy
where am I oh in the graveyard
[Music]
can we finish in 20 minutes
we can
let's go faster okay uh
I think we can can we
chat what do you say
oh okay if we oh oh
good timing to use item
oh I should have but I just wanted to go
fast uh
um
yeah
bye bye treasure chest
s
area for Keys key area
wow nice word play
the cactus it looks maybe suspicious but
it's actually
who is it a change with oh no I think I
can change with cactus who is the cactus
right now
oh my God you could not deceive us oh oh
you couldn't you couldn't do it
yeah why
why defense we should be violent safety
oh no no no no
[Music]
no
um
building blocks catch everyone stepping
okay okay I know what it is
okay okay oh muted which one are we oh
my God it's so hard to see I'm Orange
[Music]
this is good
bye
cut them off
[Music]
I can't go I think that's how it works
house
I can't do it anymore
together
[Music]
cut the path off but I died
maybe I can get out of this faster if I
had used a rocket
maybe I'll try okay I just need to get
out of the water oh my God but even with
ten I don't think I get that far
oh okay
I didn't want to hurt people I just
wanted to get out so easy
four steps one two three four ah
area
you are my area yes
yeah orange domination once again but
this time I'll take
I'll take your blood
begin it's our turn are you I want to
get it
um
oh
it's right there
uh it would be more taina if I don't if
I didn't use this yes use your items
it's so slippery oh my God I think you
can only reach yeah
no heart no hard feelings
I would have been impressed but you
chose the easy target
wait can you even reach that I don't
think so I think the stone would have
been in the way
next Target next time
[Music]
you should heal yourself maybe though I
don't know uh am I hurt I'm kind of hurt
you know
yes okay first aid kit um
take care of your body
oh
who's that cactus
Cactus manager
yeah
oh okay okay I think is
big damage so punching is die I think
why'd she go this way no I think
my king
thank you
stupid bunny
working blocks try not to fall into the
lava
ah okay okay
can you know beforehand oh yeah yes you
can okay
and jump also exists
[Music]
I don't know uh
okay
good day come back yes okay
what happened there
okay okay optical illusion
I thought it wasn't going
hardcore look at that beautiful lava
jelly
looks like jelly
okay jelly cubes delicious don't fall
into the orange jelly
oh
that wasn't the first time
continue
I wonder if in final score the mini
games that you win also count like a
Mario Party maybe they better not I hope
they die
four turns four turns okay minutes
um
[Music]
okay
um
see
I have no idea where I am
oh no I'll be faithful now
[Music]
um
who can afford I'm gonna afford I can't
Affair
[Applause]
oh my God interesting
can you get two people try we're gonna
try try try try two people
I don't think it's lethal but go for it
I don't know if you can hit two people I
can't oh don't do it
don't do it it's like through Louis now
don't don't eat it yeah like I don't
know if it can shoot me I don't
understand
it will this might actually reach nobody
no no no no no no no no yeah oh my God
you got this one one person I'm sorry
I I
I want you to try attack yeah Louis you
know who to attack now
[Music]
yes I want to attack
you no yeah I I don't believe you
I don't know
I wouldn't happen have had enough keys
anyway okay what the hell
I drowned I rejected
oh
you can't do oh oh oh let's go let's go
let's go
will you pass the treasure though
oh my god oh
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
number two who made more keys
[Music]
Where'd I go
lost forever
funny
funny that bunny does not take the trash
ah bunny does not care
bunny just exists now no I know like a
six foot
okay in front of bombs Okay
jump pick up aim
okay
[Music]
back
yeah what the
I don't understand
[Music]
oh Rocket
no cactus
she go oh
okay here
is going please
[Music]
[Applause]
maybe not that job
where am I oh what what oh
now
oh you you love me right yeah yeah I
love you I love you
seven minutes you like horses
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's dangerous in this game yeah
always dangerous yeah
high five hey
that's with ball
[Laughter]
I touched
six minutes
why me I'm in the graveyard
no I'm I'm nice hey I'm tired
she wants to fix her reputation
nice
to meet my child come to me
all of you why are you taking so much
space from me
wider locate
um it can get their key yeah look at 10
steps I think rocket 10 steps one two
three four I don't know but the key is
does she pick up the keys
let's go
[Music]
come on
oh only five minutes left oh no yeah oh
no oh no
okay okay
[Applause]
but I need I need them please more yay
okay maybe the next Treasure Chest I
could get maybe no no
no
oh my God
[Applause]
[Laughter]
why do you like sports victory
foreign
[Music]
whisk
[Applause]
000 points
like snake
three minutes
but only two turns speed speed three
minutes
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
you little oh
no
in the shadow
s
bunny kill what bunny is kill no I don't
live
[Music]
oh
my God
I love that big kabulous okay
um
[Music]
let's go
right man oh
[Laughter]
[Applause]
okay I can't do anything
I oh no oh no don't go to the planets
wow
coming back to the graveyard
who may change the frost too small
navigate
okay okay
what's punching again
[Music]
[Laughter]
Maybe
it's hard
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
I accept my defeats man no
no relax relax the world
that's one whole minute of this oh my
God
cancel game cancel game
oh
[Laughter]
anybody who reached the goal
s
for us
this
nah
just ended up
[Laughter]
oh my God free firsts oh okay okay Speed
come on
something quick don't think don't think
my time my tongue okay
score is Not Gonna Change probably
anymore
wow okay okay I see how it is
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
high speed speed speed I just I just
care about speed so I will just no item
no item no go go go go go go oh yeah
yeah into the water water okay why not
laughs
oh
Just moment
just a moment
[Music]
okay
okay okay
no no Wrecking Ball oh
[Music]
eat your veggies she's saying here
[Laughter]
yummy yummy yummy yummy treasure
[Music]
no treasure no treasure
but maybe I could get four more coins
maybe she really wanna get on that
leaderboard
[Music]
hi
[Laughter]
[Music]
buddy hi buddy hi buddy hi bye bye
but it doesn't seem to hurt the one if
you stand on it yeah yeah it's like when
it pops and then it reached somebody
okay okay last game last game
game
all Elemental escalation yeah
[Music]
okay
maybe okay
oh that looks like a the red one looks
like a chicken foot
[Music]
nice
element is candy yeah
[Music]
oh 20 seconds
yeah yeah I'm not winning this
[Music]
yes yes yes yes oh how is that what do
you mean you're not winning this oh my
God
okay yeah okay okay okay okay okay
um you're the only other one streaming
right uh yeah is this still
I don't know
yes yes yes
7 PM okay just uh just uh
do nothing just go to the half minutes
okay yeah okay I'm just doing nothing
I'm not gonna do it yeah
[Laughter]
no matter what yeah
[Music]
thank you
that's it
it's so hot summer is
[Laughter]
[Music]
welcome
[Laughter]
area is nice
Senpai text it was cool high tax Subaru
Santa is senpai
oh
oh oh it's time to learn to switch money
okay let's game last game game
no game okay
okay oh
the pommel Awards we're here to shine
the light on your achievements and
failures yay
if you would prefer we judge other
things you can always change it
there's two trophies
I want for most damage most damage down
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
most keys
[Music]
beautiful most mini games maybe
ultimate winner
[Music]
[Applause]
the pictures
of course not okay I closed this
is winner so Subaru read first line
um okay
are you ready the picture of course not
okay yeah somebody can read first yes
please read number one number one so
what's the original
hola yes
this Sunday
yeah
20th 20th of August yes yes
[Applause]
which pictures
everybody
and then the digital song will be
available later at midnight or on all I
guess Spotify
Etc yeah and yeah
how about uh
number two
[Music]
Japanese only Louis
oh
[Music]
I can read it okay and finally on August
21st Yeah dance related shorts with all
of the whole attorney members I'll also
be uploaded yay
so to sum it up we have a song coming
out on the 20th of August and we have a
Holy Ground coming out this weekend I
think and we have dance relay shorts
coming out the day after the song
release so please check out her life
English Channel at all times
[Music]
please look forward to
Italy okay yeah no no no we stay
together
thank you guys for watching
for promotion
oh there's waiting room up now I will
link it in my chat soon
it's in a couple days anyway
yes okay I'll paste it there okay bye
bye guys
oh my God
[Music]
foreign