[Music]
[Applause]
do
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
hello
[Applause]
do you hear me
is it
laggy or anything
all good
okay we're doing it with wi-fi today so
just as a warning hello kids
movie
yes
wi-fi
please don't don't disappoint me
don't destroy my setup please
okay
this pumpkin is gonna be full
[Applause]
uh
wait
one second
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
i i need to set up my
my myself again
give me a moment
wi-fi please bye-bye
come on
[Applause]
[Music]
so
[Applause]
do
i fixed it
[Music]
all right all right
kfb level
welcome
hey
oh my god my cat started fighting on my
yoga mat
[Music]
nice to see you all it's been a while
since i've been using the setup can you
guys hear me well um i hope so maybe i i
should should i move my microphone
closer a little bit i don't think it
will change much
[Music]
so kfb
[Laughter]
so
thank you for coming
[Music]
it's okay
you like knives
i got a lot of them
well today i actually well i'm still in
my kitchen but i actually brought uh
an extra table here so that i can
actually sit down while doing this and
uh
my future flashing before my eyes on
y'all
so i have a a good
white surface um
a lot of space now one big table
decently big table
that is not my pc table but my laptop is
on it as well
gordon is here again
is gordon here again
gordon what's up
be calm today i'm actually not really
gonna cook
but um we are going to carve a pumpkin
today
i already did the inside or at least i
tried
um but it's not probably not the
cleanest pumpkin that you've ever seen
wait a second
okay
let me try to show you um today i tried
my best to fix
the camera so that it won't be like um
wiggling and jiggling all over
no
[Music]
i can only do this angle now
uh so if i want to show you the inside
of this pumpkin wait a second that might
be
a little bit difficult
why is it flickering do you see that why
is it flickering why you flick it stop
there we go oh don't don't stop
flickering
i don't know why it's flickering well
look so basically
when is this flickering i tried
you see that i don't know maybe it's a
light reflection what's going on
[Music]
okay i'm still very nervous this is
supposed my
spoopy flickery
and looks good you think so this is my
first time doing a pumpkin carving i've
never done it before in my life
and so i'm not quite sure how to do it
um i originally wanted to get
uh a couple like actually like five
smaller pumpkins
and on each pumpkin
i wanted to
um now i remember again when i forgot i
forgot the pen i need to bring the pen
over but i wanted to have
each holo mips
members uh icon you know our little
icons
i wanted to carve that on the pumpkin
but i went to supermarket and they had a
lot of small pumpkins but they were all
like kind of weird looking like they had
weird
weird colors and patterns so
um i wanted one with this perfect orange
color and i know a thing or two about
orange you know
so uh for that they had like two
two they were like decent size
and
uh this one was huge though this is huge
like compared to the other pumpkins i
saw this one is huge
like
i mean okay if i put my hand on it
[Music]
imagine this is a chicken
it's going to be okay
it looks like a butt kind of the only
choice
my hand looks so big that you can't even
comprehend but actually this the other
side is a looks bigger because it's like
if you see this it's kind of lopsided
like here it goes down
i feel like this is the perfect size
this is the perfect size or the perfect
angle
[Music]
pumpkin
[Laughter]
[Music]
squeeze those cheeks i can't squeeze
them this pumpkin isn't very squishy
so um
i
i don't have like proper carving tools i
only have like knives and stuff but i
i hope that's gonna work um but don't
worry they're not reflective and i have
like uh
i have this and i know it's reflective
but you don't see anything
like i tested it i'm trying to see
myself in it but i can't see myself in
it
like i could like
do some
i don't know if that's even gonna work
this is for apples
and then i have
i mean this i guess i don't really need
any more this is like an act like a like
a
shaver but i don't think we need it and
and i watched some videos
i watched some videos about how people
carve pumpkins and i've seen most people
do it with a knife anyway
most people live with a knife anyway so
here i got i got a lot of knives though
um
knife
i don't know if we can really do
something proper today i i
it's probably gonna look horrible
um but i can already say i feel
much better in this setup right now
because i can actually sit this is
wonderful um i'm still very nervous so i
don't even know how to get started one
second let me move the microphone a
little bit over here and just
just a little bit over here
and then you come a little bit closer
buddy
okay
so basically like for example here we're
gonna have kotori and then we turn it
around a little bit and here we're gonna
have like the
uh uh
shinigami sensei for example
and then here we can have like gouda's
symbol and so on you know what i mean
that's what i've been thinking about we
will see how long one one single
uh sign is gonna take me and i don't
even know like like i've seen techniques
so there's two techniques
one is just like completely carving out
a hole and the other one is just taking
off the skin
uh
and i asked ina to send me
the
reference picture
where did it go
oh god it's so hot with those sleeves
[Music]
yeah i don't know where i went i need to
go back to
uh did you practice no i didn't i
actually i only carved like the inside
so that we at least have that ready
because
i
couldn't do that with sleeves anyway so
um the messy work is done
supposedly
the messy work is supposedly done you
know what would be amazing for the
future let me write this down
the the wall that you see
over there behind the pumpkin
is a kitchen wall for me i think it
would be amazing to have
a monitor mounted there
just for the purpose of having a second
monitor when streaming in my kitchen
that would be so cool i could look up
there
and have the comments there that would
be so nice
okay let me go get a pen
and you uh
talk to the pumpkin i guess yeah have
fun maybe we should uh
[Music]
that's me
[Laughter]
that's funny
[Music]
okay
i am back
[Music]
uh give me my headphones
it's a headphone stand i'm making a
oopsie i'm making a headphone stand yata
[Music]
uh where is chat come on i need more
screens
i need more screens
[Music]
maybe i should nah i'm gonna try to work
with one screen
i'm so nervous these kind of streams
always make me so nervous
[Music]
are you sure okay
okay ah this is too
ah
it's very nerve-wracking but we're okay
like at least the camera is uh
a portable well i mean i have my i could
use my ipad but whatever i don't i don't
want to use up any more space on this
table i want as much space as possible
okay okay okay this is this might be
good
so we're gonna start
uh either one of these should one of one
of them should at least work i hope
maybe this one works let's try to
my three d then what do you mean
what what we mean these hands right you
don't need you don't mean this right
is there anything you want me to do with
this pumpkin before i um
draw something on it do you like any
pose you would like me to do
i don't know what i can do like i can't
show you more than just my hands and i
already patted it and i can't kiss it
slap it
shouldn't i draw your guys's face wait
you know what let me draw kotori on it
and then slap it because then you can
feel like this is you
how about that
okay um uh
wait um
oh
oh wait
i need to move this around so that i see
i should have brought my mouse over
goddammit
wait one second
let me get my phone
[Music]
okay my
one of my
phones
let me just look at
the reference on my phone trying to not
show you my phone but i mean
[Music]
i shall wear my heart monitor for this
shouldn't i
now okay i don't want to set this up on
my
laptop now
but uh
but i can tell you my heart rate is
probably a little bit high right now
because i don't even feel like i can
breathe well
okay
all right all right all right i got my
phone as a reference
let's get back into position
but also let me move the chat again then
ah sorry guys we need to be very very
careful today what's in the kids can i
take
at least i am started on time hello i
mean not really on time i already moved
the time yesterday
make the window bigger
chat window please
this doesn't work well with gloves
come along come on
come on come on over here why are you
not coming over here you little [\h__\h]
when i slap the pumpkin i'll also call
it your little [\h__\h]
okay there you go you're patient nice
thank you
okay
[Music]
so
peekaboo
[Music]
uh you gotta consider that uh i'm doing
this in an awkward position like in
between me and the pumpkin is the camera
so i'm trying to like reach out to the
pumpkin and it's kind of weird
um this is a weird angle but okay let me
try this will probably look really ugly
drying on the pumpkin is difficult i uh
i
i can't imagine like it's like so round
let me lift it a little bit okay baby
okay baby
it's all good it's all good calm down uh
we're gonna be fine um
okay
give give me give me your best cute face
uh
[Music]
is this is this height okay
it must be oh this is kind of small
[\h__\h]
well
that's fine that's fine
i can still make it bigger
okay
[Music]
i'm left-handed yes uh how have you not
noticed that yet
but if now the question is do i do i
just carve the whole thing out for this
one i think i will
[Music]
because kotori is pretty simple but the
other designs i don't know how i'm gonna
do that
okay so we got here and then here and
then oh that's a very
very intricate
form here
[Music]
drawing stream but with like
no drawing pro
program
yeah bloop and and yeah all the others
except for me and the takodachi
are
difficult
okay so like like a bit more like this
plump make it plump
and then
like that
[Music]
ah
like that like that
[Music]
you understand
okay now unfortunately this will all not
matter and i can't even give it a face
right because i'll be cutting all of
this only the outers the outer line
twitter
this is that twitter
stop it with a verification mark
so basically this is
[Music]
okay so this one is easy because i just
have to carve it out come on i can do
this how do we
how do i how do i do this how do i
how do i even do how do i
[Music]
there will be so many cat hairs on this
pumpkin so i think i'm not actually
gonna eat it afterwards
[Music]
i'm scared of the impact that this will
cause
yeah a bit a bit escape
[Music]
we're getting
started okay okay
i don't know did i get through to the
other side did i i don't no i didn't
and this is my short this knife this is
the shortest this is really short like
hello
it's like
like it's short
oh
come on okay
uh
[Music]
oh god
this is gonna look so ugly
how do i even make curves
[Music]
i can't do curves
i mean this is my first time carving so
this is okay right
i'm being careful don't worry
the knife is not aiming at me it's
aiming in the opposite direction
okay so far so good
okay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
this from here
to here
and then
why are you guys so worried
no need to worry so much this is
impossible how am i supposed to
make this shape can i maybe just carve
this one off maybe the feather here
[Music]
i'm not sure
don't hurt yourself don't cut yourself
[Music]
you should be more worried about the
camera not about the
knife
[Music]
i should have gotten like a proper
pumpkin carving like specifically for
pumpkin carving set i guess
that would have been helpful
[Music]
let's hope i don't have to go through
all of these ships again
[Music]
oh that was a huge cut
okay
ctrpg
and i didn't see a comment about don't
do the same thing that i did in
titanfacio
oh you know what i could do i could do
this thing where you go like
challenge
it
i can't go very fast
[Music]
[Laughter]
where was i
here
oh right wrong side
oh this is fun
oh my god it's shaking the earth is
shaking
trembling
oh i got something like a crab yo
okay i can't really
yeah the shape of the feathers is ruined
[Music]
where did i stop here
that's a weird angle
why are you guys the chat is literally
just
a chat is literally only consisting of
because
oh my god
just calm down calm
down
[Music]
do you think i've never handled a knife
before come on
i'm potential
i also carry a sword with me i'm i'm i'm
sure i know how to handle a knife
yeah
oh my god
[Music]
supposedly this is it but i guess i yeah
it didn't cut deep enough
it doesn't want to go through
where did i not cut deep enough
everywhere
oh wait
wait
[Music]
oh don't destroy the beak this has such
a cute shape actually
i don't want to destroy it
[Music]
how do you do this
i
i feel like
[Music]
we're like so close
i'm guessing this part is not very good
[Music]
you can do it yeah come on out
oh
[Music]
there's something
okay bye bye bye bye pumpkin
wait that was the beak
i've lost the top part of the beak
heart rate monitor yeah they're really
really necessary actually
come
[Music]
it looks like [\h__\h]
wait
ah
i'm muddy kittens well we can like make
this even better wait you just gotta
like
improve the shape here right yeah yeah
it seems like doing stuff like that
yeah yeah yeah i have nowhere to put
this
like here okay scarf a bit more off
three and
it's not over
by far not oh i threw something in there
there it is
[Music]
okay
i guess that's why it's important that
the inside is also pretty but you know
what we can try twitter
give me this is me asking twitter for a
verification mark now you know what we
can try at the end like we can turn off
the lights and i can put a candle inside
although wait i think i only have like
big candles though
i wonder if they will even fit
but okay um
anyway
this looks okay
where where this is my first time it can
be scuffed right so
for the first time
this is amazing
okay can you eat pumpkin raw
i'm left-handed yes
second time i'm saying it
can you eat a bra
[Music]
yeah
i would imagine no tanjo yes yes
yes most people say yeah
where is the piece that doesn't have cat
hair on it
let me take this
i'm gonna eat this
[Music]
i don't know do i really want to eat
this
is this a good piece
[Music]
oh oh
it
it doesn't really
doesn't really taste like pumpkin at the
moment i think you got to cook it to
really get that taste
yeah it doesn't taste great but it
doesn't taste disgusting it just tastes
bland yeah like like nothing particular
it tastes like a vegetable
that has barely any taste to itself
[Music]
this part is not so pretty
oh come here
come here
okay does this look like company
i mean it looks like a bird at least
right right so with angle because i'm
looking at you you're looking at from a
downward angle you gotta look at it like
this oh there's something hanging down
there
[Music]
gotta look at it like this
i mean this part is like what the [\h__\h]
is this right
but other than that
i think like if there was a light in
there i think yeah the silhouette is
fine now the question is how the hell
are we going to do the other ones
because this was the easiest
kotori is like as simple as as you can
have as simple as it gets
[Music]
wait i need it to slap you guys
okay let's put on your little hat
[Music]
where does it go how does it look
wait where do you go here
well you don't even see that oh well
okay are you ready
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
it's not really like smacking a face
it's like smacking like
the sound is just not a slap
[Music]
do you hear that sound it's so
enough it's like so
it doesn't even make a sound
[Music]
aha
all right then let's continue
[Music]
yes i was just poking your nose
kotori
do i need to slap you again slap some
sense into you
okay which side do we do next
this side by the way is gonna be
difficult to carve because it's
look it's that's so nice this is the
ugly
[Music]
however
when we only do the
outline
i'm not sure it will look like what it's
supposed to look like
[Music]
well let's draw
let's draw it on first okay so it's um
it's like
like this
the halo
tankodachis have a [\h__\h] halo can you
believe it
[Music]
a halo they are claiming that they are
angels
i don't know about that
[Music]
and then like a little bit more
roundness and then it goes down kind of
straight
[Music]
and then it's like four
four
[Music]
wow
and then theory the face
would be here
[Music]
but we're not gonna see the face
so it's only this blobby shape
[Music]
but it does say wow like remember it in
this shape because this is the best it's
gonna look like ever
now we're gonna make it look bad
smile taco it's cute though this taco
dutch is so cute like generally
takodachis are cute
not as cute as my chickens but
almost almost
okay i'm going in
[Music]
this is actually not that difficult
you know what i mean like this this
little part wait let me lift here
this little part
[Music]
that's like
hm i i can't i can't recreate that
[Music]
it's gonna be connected
doesn't matter right it doesn't matter
it doesn't matter or ah cut off the
hammer should i cut up the ignore the
ham should i just stop
i think it'll it will look a little bit
more like it yeah okay let's do that
that's a good idea
no halo taco that's it
[Music]
and are there taco batches without
tables
is that a thing do you have that option
[Music]
it's optional really oh i need a back
massage can someone step on my back
but
i already did my stretches today by the
way
and i had a
rehearsal
[Music]
i was productive
thank you for the pinky
is that gordon ramsay
well let me say what he's saying
i don't know what i missed my internet
went down so i'll just assume carry your
wheels and knife like a caveman of a
club
um
she can stop packing up and use a knife
i'm using a knife
you're killing me
[Music]
i'm trying you can't do this much more
elegantly what i did see in the video
though was like um
was uh
was that no it was a like someone used
like a tiny tiny really thin uh saw sock
is that how you call it and they say
again
and they
in the second
i don't have a small knife this is
really tiny if you look at it in real
life you would see
yeah like a really really thin
song and you can make perfect shapes
with that but i couldn't get that on
such short notice i mean i knew that i
was gonna do this but still
still forgive me this is funnier
because it's gonna be more scuffed
and i mean i wasn't sure if that's
really necessary we're we're gonna learn
from this and eventually gonna
have better equipment for next year
i'm so hungry
maybe i should eat the taco duchy once i
have it
[Music]
you know in the corner of my eye when i
look this way i see the shadow only in
the corner of my eye and i just saw a
yellow super chat
uh coming through the chat and it scared
me because i thought that
something was happening with my camera
like it was lifting itself up or
something because
yellow is almost the color of this
pumpkin i don't know if you understand
what i'm trying to say but i was scared
you scare me
uh okay so i think this thing is done
this was even easier than
totally but it's gonna look worse
[Music]
can we get you out of this shape
i shouldn't be using my right hand for
this is dangerous
get out get out
what
[Music]
get lost gordon ramsay i'm the only one
that can judge kiana now not you never
you chiara's pumpkin
boo
boo and what no why are you spooking me
stop
stop that doesn't work when i'm looking
at the screen happy birthday
happy birthday
to you congratulations thank you for
spending your birthday with me i would
put a candle on this pumpkin if i had
one right now maybe at the end
i'm gonna make a candle for you
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
you're missing your ear and your halo
that doesn't look like anything
that looks like pac-man
[Music]
oh man
here your ear i saved your ear
i might just eat it though
[Music]
let me make this shape nicer
you know what i saw today
i saw
and socialized
a little bit
with a with a baby husky
and
11 year 11 weeks old
baby
[Music]
it husky so cute
it was so fluffy
i couldn't like it was very scared of
strangers it it it seemed to have a big
interest in me maybe because of my cat
hairs that i have everywhere but um
it was like like constantly sniffing me
my legs and stuff and trying to like
get to know me but i i realized that
touching would maybe go a step too far i
asked the owner by the way
he was like no he might be uh still a
little bit scared but you can try
and
i
i eventually
after fangirling over it i let it sniff
my hand
and and
the wet snoot touched my fingers and he
snuffed me it was so
[Music]
adorable it was so adorable
i don't even know like oh my god oh wait
now you see this drawn on them maybe i
should do the halo you know what i'm
going to do the halo
i'm doing the halo 2.
otherwise it looks like pac-man
okay
[Music]
i mean
it literally can't be helped if
if this is like i mean what i could
probably
do if i were a professional if i had a
little bit of experience in here i could
like take like these parts and then cut
out like specific shapes and then i
actually
i brought
toothpicks
so i could uh
like squeeze like certain things in
there but you're gonna see the toothpick
so what would be even better is uh
see-through toothpicks now
now i realize
wait it does look
it does look it does look like discord
oh my discord are you watching this
one's for you
super glue i mean but when it's like if
i were to do a face it's like in the
middle
but i could have just i guess also
carved only the skin
and then
you know
try to go from there but i don't know
that that's really difficult but it
seems to be inevitable
for the next ones
i will have to try
let's see how easy it is
um
[Music]
okay
what's over there
[Music]
okay
we're done with the taco dancing
look
wait
let me put the
push up
[Music]
oh no
huh
[Music]
that was the perfect
shape though
[Music]
you deserved that slapping oh my god it
doesn't really oh stain how do you make
it stay
it's falling down stain
look so now you can see the
uh
taco that's your
[Music]
it looks so bad it's not my fault
okay
let's go to this side
who do we want to do next
[Music]
oh my god bloop is literally just gonna
be a bloop
we could do bloop in its um
in its bubble and just do a round
circle
[Music]
but you know what would be nice
to
have like let's say bloop is like here
and i only do the skin
part of the pumpkin and then around it
i
am like i guess the way you would do it
is that first of all you just get a
circle
and then you take the circle separately
and then carve a bloop into it
and then uh slice off the outside parts
of the bubble you know what i mean and
then put the thing back in with
toothpicks
[Music]
but
is that too high level for me
[Music]
let me drink some iced tea is that too
high level for me do you know what i
mean
that sounds difficult
[Music]
although that would mean that i would
have it like directly in my hand in a
small shape so
it would be easier to hold maybe
easier to shave it
i mean that's kind of what i wanted to
do okay let's forget the bubble
let's um
oh god
let's see let's see um
we can
i know how to do it okay so for example
for example
the eyes gotta be perfect because i'm
gonna keep the eyes let's say um
[Music]
this he's gonna look so derpy
[Laughter]
um so basically i'm carving around the
eye the eye
the eye white will be the outer skin of
the pumpkin
and the pupil will just be the black
color
okay
[Music]
i think
that's my current plan
[Music]
this is way too difficult i don't think
i can really do this
[Music]
looks like kermit the frog i just got
started but you're right
[Laughter]
carve a circle and that would be too
easy
no wait the other way around how now
she has a lot of
layers
[Music]
i have to say this drawing is looking
gorgeous so far
this is so cute
oh you got the color
it looks cute
so far so good
not bad not bad
[Music]
and then we have another
x
here
and
well
i made him too big also this pen doesn't
work so well
[Music]
the hat
oh dear
[Music]
the flaps the hands are here well that
looks gorgeous
yeah go smiling in the background yeah
i'm just i don't want to do feet
i mean trucks don't really have feet
anyway if you think about it so can i
just leave the the feet out
[Music]
it's getting too low here i can't even
go that low
or maybe like
just like
okay it's easy let's just do it i don't
know something like this
okay
and uh here and then thin like this
and then
[Music]
this is so cute
and then like this
what do you think bloop's a minion
[Music]
all right the sketch is done it
thank you for streaming spikes and
watching the music video on youtube
thank you
[Music]
please continue to stream spikes
and spanx
and
the upcoming song cover that's coming
soon how do we do this so if i do
this part
orange this part white
this part orange this part why the teeth
white that would be perfect and because
this part is
but this part is orange so at this point
would be no wait a second
orange white
or like
inner skin
like in our flesh
skin
flesh
[Music]
um
i don't know
skin flesh so skin skin this will all be
skin
flesh flesh
[Music]
skin
understandable
[Music]
you probably don't know what i mean how
do i do this though how do i do this i
don't know i don't know
how would i go about that
i guess first of all try to make little
cuts and then just don't go
too deep
okay so let's say
[Music]
let's say i want to cut that
can i do that
oh
no no
it's gonna be something i'm i'm
literally peeling off the skin of bloop
that sounds
bad i hope gouda isn't watching this
sorry i'm doing something
to your mascot but you don't really use
your mascot anyway do you where is bloop
tell me where is bloop bloop is here
bloop is in good care don't worry about
bloop
don't worry about bloop i'm taking care
of bloop
this is this is gonna take a million
years to do
see this is where the cutting starts
this is where it starts but i'm wearing
gloves
[Music]
is this really how you're supposed to do
this
[Music]
oh
all right not a hold up
i think i can do it
confidence
have confidence
oh
[Music]
where are my cats follow it
um
[Music]
wait a second
how do i do
she's gonna go deep
we just gotta go deeper kfp
are you guys ready for a halloween a
spoon
how
i don't have a non-reflective spoon
just don't look
i mean
yeah that's not so good
don't look okay
i need my second hand though
[Music]
use a cheese grater
i mean i have
that doesn't really work either
that's a little bit easier to use than a
knife perhaps
that's uh
yeah put the good old potato peeler
[Music]
uh
we're good we're good are you guys gonna
do any carving of pumpkins but what
about my audience are you guys doing
anything like that i mean if you live
alone like me
there's honestly no reason to do
that right
[Music]
yeah
but if you have a family
[Music]
or if you just have a beautiful garden
or like a
a beautiful balcony
wouldn't it be nice to have some
decoration up like my image from for
like
um let's say
no north american people i see
you guys in a lot of tv shows and in a
lot of those tv shows it shows you guys
as very competitive when it comes to
um
decorating your balcony or like your
your garden your front porch
especially
around christmas but also around
halloween
but i'm guessing that's
actually kind of a rare thing in reality
like people that are going like really
crazy
about decorating their
uh garden which one is it is it true are
there a lot or is it really really rare
some people are like that no it's normal
it is
rich people do
yeah i mean i i wouldn't expect it in a
city like i don't know new york city but
like in in like
big neighborhoods that have like big
gardens and big houses
[Music]
yeah like in modern family you know that
that family with claire and phil dunphy
claire loves to decorate her garden
that's like her thing
especially during halloween she loves
halloween
and i also remember what's that show
called like in my childhood i watched
this show a little bit um
this family that where the guy has a tv
show that's about like
um
handbag
is that gordon
what's that called it's a really old tv
show home improvement
wait was that the show the name to show
the show of the name of the show in
english
they had i think two sons
tim allen
see i remember that from when i was
younger much much younger and i remember
that he also did something with his
garden i think oh did she
well maybe he did did he
remember remembering wrong what's gordon
saying my internet's reconnected so i'll
catch up what god's name is that i will
cook it i will cook that pumpkin okay
please go ahead i've seen spastics with
better hand control now she'll caveman
other pumpkin i'll cook this chicken for
thanksgiving now my chad died i couldn't
finish reading
my chest is that my chrome
had a timeout or whatever like it's too
much
cachet
cachet too much stuff going on wait wait
wait i fixed it what is he saying
he says
where's the rest of my gordon ramsay
there he is
you're you're is this it no yeah this is
it no wait this is not it
no where's the new one it disappeared
[Music]
where is the new gordon ramsay
it's just cash
oh god i'm so hungry
i'm so hungry
it's already been an hour and actually
you know what i think we've done done
good process proper progress
english stucco
okay okay okay well i lost the rest of
the super chat for some reason but i i
got to a good point
yes okay
actually have you guys seen in the
supermarket when you when you ever did
you ever look at the pumpkin section
[Music]
because besides the normal pumpkins
i was always wondering if they do sell
hokkaido pumpkins here because whenever
i i like look at a a menu in a
restaurant in australia and i see
pumpkin soup it's always they always use
hokkaido pumpkins
and i was wondering like if where where
would i get hokkaido pumpkins and i saw
in the supermarket there were a lot of
hokkaido pumpkins
but they're like pretty small and
they're more like a reddish color
i don't know
if
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
okay okay wait we already got a big part
done it comes it
[Music]
is just sorry i'm taking a lot of time
with this
oh i'm trying to make at least this one
look good
it's actually
difficult
so this was actually this one was just
labeled as carving pumpkin
it was five dollars by the way
a five euro to be except
foreign
[Music]
that seems pretty cheap yeah it seemed
cheap
i looked at the others that were smaller
and they were about the same price so i
wonder if maybe the taste of this
pumpkin wouldn't be so good i wonder how
different it is i wanted to make a soup
out of this pumpkin as well but um the
more i thought about it the more i
figured that we should maybe just focus
on carving today
and i think that was the right choice
[Music]
what do i do about the x and on his
forehead
maybe i can
[Music]
even i'll carve it and then draw on it
again or
let me try to carve around it
[Music]
sugar pumpkins are for eating carbon
pumpkins are for
i didn't rate the rest of that
are for are pretty gross oh really
oh he's not so so maybe it was a good
choice also because of the taste that i
didn't decide to
make something out of this
is that so
[Music]
i imagined as much because they labeled
it at least at least the outside looks
pretty and i i realized something i
never noticed before
in the supermarket
around
the
pumpkin section where all the pumpkins
are
i saw
buttanus
[Music]
and
whenever i heard butternut until now my
whole life
i didn't think of it as a pumpkin i
thought of it as nuts
a butternut squash yeah yeah yeah
i thought that those were nuts
i didn't realize that's a pumpkin too
i realized that today
so
[Music]
what does it taste like does it still
taste like a pumpkin i never ate that
before
anything with butternut
squash never never i didn't realize it's
a pumpkin what the hell i'm so surprised
butternuts it's not nuts no
it unerratically tastes nice
sweet pumpkin
it's does it still have that pumpkin
taste because it's like brown right like
when it doesn't look like a pumpkin i
don't know if it really tastes like a
pumpkin
[Music]
it's made with brown sugar
but that squash is quite tasty i pretty
dislike its taste personally butternut
squash is so good but not squash is good
oh you guys all love butter i've only
heard good things like people
people um fainting over butternut squash
so i've always been curious and now i'm
even more curious i didn't realize wait
butternut squash is is the the thing
right not something you make out of it
it's the whole thing right the whole
pumpkin it is a pumpkin right it's
officially a pumpkin right i'm not wrong
with that
because it was in the pumpkin section
[Music]
it's better than pumpkin
it's a whole vegetable it's a squash
what's a squash
pumpkin is a squash what's a squash
what's the word in german for squash
help help
squash is for squashing what does that
mean
[Music]
what i got it backwards pumpkins are
squashes
[Music]
is the mother of the pumpkin what
what
gourds what's that gordon ramsay
gordon are you a pumpkin
gordon is a pumpkin
that's squash squash squash
squash wait german word is also squash
no way
oh it's like howard zucchini i guess is
also related to the pumpkin in some way
because is it zucchini
is it zucchini a squash too
spicy cubes oh
[Music]
wait is it zucchini a pumpkin it's from
the gourd family that makes sense
because it kind of looks like it yeah
that makes sense i guess so
[Music]
oh no
well that's okay
uh wait a second
i messed up
no this wasn't supposed to be carved you
haven't
i think the inside part this part was
supposed to be carved
well that's okay we'll just switch it
around that means that this is skin
this is carved and this is skin
and this is quite ah it's okay that's
okay
that's okay it's my shine
shania
let's try to make the eyes
even deeper than the skin
can i do that
like oh my god
this is the this is gonna be the most
cursed bloop that has or anyone has ever
seen
like a skin peeled bloop this is what
happens when you come to kfb
as a non-chicken and you're gonna go to
the usual room
i mean i guess it happens to chickens
too but um
getting your skin peeled off
but
i think bloop
doesn't handle it as well as my chickens
do because my chickens are used to it
this looks so funny
[Music]
this is so fun
this is a fun stream
it's something else isn't it
[Music]
i need some kind of line
look at this
it looks better from this angle i
shouldn't show you guys up front what it
looks like
let me try to um
yeah gotta cheat a little bit
you gotta cheat
yeah
give it give him some eyeliner
i can smooth it out after can i i wonder
does that wreck
maybe with the spoon
anyway
it does need smoothing
[Music]
okay now i do
this little flap here
[Music]
my hands are feeling
a little bit crampy but
we're doing fine thank you
for the membership message
[Music]
oh sure
thank you little parts carve more deeply
ah yeah they're gonna look different
right when when light is inside and it's
dark outside right they're gonna like be
brighter so
it's a good thing to have like
he's not saying kill me kill me okay
he's living a happy life right now
you know maybe he lifts off some weight
from bloop to be skinless he's gonna be
happy don't worry about it oh look at
this uh carving trophy professional
right now
prophy that's german cute little idiot
look at that
look at that i did that in one go
that carving
portion
make that a little bit nicer
all right all right all right all right
skinning a shark alive
[Music]
what about the feet what about this
whole outline
i guess the outline should be carved huh
yeah
at least the outline i guess you're
gonna see that are you gonna see that
when the light is off
[Music]
skin the feet
but they're supposed to be the same
color as
i guess
wait are they i don't actually know
and vada
but they're down there it's kind of hard
to reach but i'm gonna give it a try
should i send this
you know what after i'm done with this
pumpkin i'm just gonna
like cut out this section only this
section and i'm gonna send it to a good
app via
mail
[Laughter]
she's gonna be so happy about it that
she has decoration for halloween who
wouldn't be happy about it
yeah i'm gonna send it to her let's hope
it doesn't rot but apparently two two
three day three to five days
a pumpkin is fine up to uh five days
after you carved it so
i just gotta use fedex or something like
that to make it quick
[Music]
or i'll just take a
an airplane and go by myself directly
deliver it personally put it in my hand
luggage
food is allowed in hand luggage you know
what that might be the safest option to
uh
go
by myself and deliver it personally
uh
a threat it's not a friend this is this
is it i'm just being a good colleague
okay
this ain't a threat
i'm i'm a nice gen mate
i'm just trying to
you know
be a good gen mate
anyway let's make sure the mouth i'm
done with the feet
naked feet
naked bloop feet
now we're doing the mouth
are you guys excited for the light out
moment
i i have a yankee candle like a smaller
one i think it fits inside but i wonder
if it will burn up the inside shouldn't
happen
i mean it would be good for like
streaming content if the pumpkin catches
on fire
right it's gonna be good streaming
content
[Music]
oh you know what because we haven't
actually
uh like completely made a hole yet we
could make the
pupils into
actual holes
it's like you're giving him a root canal
that's funny i'm a dentist and i'm an
eye doctor now
i'm going in deep
oh dear
seems like an abdomination what are you
talking about
huh
it smells like nothing right now
pumpkin
doesn't really like as a raw doesn't
have much smell to it
unless like if i get like really close
but at the moment it's fine
[Music]
oh you're looking funny
bloop
[Music]
okay
i am so proud
i'm so proud you're impressed you're
genuinely impressed thank you me too
this is my first time okay remember this
is my first time
the pants don't work so good on this
thing
[Music]
i'm not impressed why why am i impressed
this looks beautiful i don't know what
to do with the hat maybe he should be
headless
it's taking me too much time
or i could carve out the hat
i'm gonna do that that seems easier
right now
will i regret this
carving out like um
yeah carving it completely i'm i'm doing
it
there's no going back
hit
step step loop
die
sorry
yes
[Music]
i reached the other side
okay
i think we're ready
to unravel
come out come on
come on
sorry
it looks like he is in pain
[Music]
no he's smiling don't you see his
beautiful smile
[Music]
oh wait i think this part was
lacking okay
i can't get this out
there go
yeah hat
[Music]
okay now look oh wait let me move on
before i show you
hi smokey hi
nice movie
ella you want some pumpkin
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay okay okay
now
[Music]
look at this masterpiece
it's not so bad
i would like to say it but you know what
let me uh i want to carve out this card
like not cards but like
carve out completely
[Music]
like super thin
carvings are
not so easy
[Music]
what vitamins do pumpkins have tell me
because actually yesterday i had pumpkin
soup
yes meow did you hear that
vitamin
a and c
p there's no vitamin b
no no no no no no no no
[Music]
vitamin
no there's no vitamin p
are you making a fool out of me
oh that's too big
oh well
[Music]
cutting it this is like
the x is literally literally literally
telling me stab me right here
yes please stab me
[Music]
kiana please stab me right here
it's telling me this i hear the voices
don't you hear them too okay i'll give
it to you
i'll stab you
i'll give you what you want
do i look like a psychopath to you guys
today
he also has one on his forehead though
ah
one second
i didn't crack it okay i just need to
stretch
but it will accidentally crack i feel
a little bit exhausted
in my body this is
quite
uh exhausting
oh now that's by accident i correct a
little bit
okay i'm so excited to light them up oh
my god i'm gonna light them on fire
from the inside
[Music]
okay
i think we're done with bloop we spent a
lot of time with blue that took me like
how long 40 minutes
we're gonna do
and
let's see how does uh
uh how does bubba look like
baba is
uh
on the level of difficulty pretty close
[Music]
pretty close
bubba looks like a dog yeah well okay
let's drop
don't go
time
[Music]
[Applause]
okay so it's gonna be
[Music]
somewhat round shape
oh man
drawing time
[Music]
there is no going back on the drawing
so this has to be
perfect
[Music]
was a snoot
almost as cute as
the husky that i saw today oh my god
whenever i see dogs i'm thinking about
turning into
a dog
dog person i mean i will always be a cat
person but i do kind of want a dog at
some point
[Music]
okay
like having two cats and one dog
would be quite ideal for me personally
no he doesn't look so good
what the egg looked like tonight
no it doesn't look cute oh it's okay
he's gonna look less cuter after i'm
done with him anyway
there's like nothing you can do about
that oh [\h__\h]
it's wet up there
[Music]
i know what i'm doing okay
okay something like that he looks bad he
saw things he looks depressed
hey
amelia your dog is being carved and
peeled alive let's go
[Music]
amelia your dog is being peeled let's go
um but how do i do this um
either we just
not but if i carve the whole thing it's
not gonna look like anything
[Music]
i think
how about we carve
the skin we peel the skin
here everywhere
we keep the nose
skin and we keep the hat as skin as well
i think
it will take a little while again but i
want to do it
we peel bubba skin
yeah
[Music]
that's
or or we do it the other way around
we keep the orange
skin on on bubba but we peel the hat
because then we can keep like the the
drawing on it
that's better
and then his eyes we can get rid of
okay i'm on it guys i'm on it yes
[Music]
i can't believe i've never done this in
my childhood before have you guys done
this in your childhood before
[Music]
i think i'm getting not gonna do the
outline here or maybe i can do like uh
i know what i'll do
yes yes yes no no never did yes yes a
lot of yeses wow
yeah did you do it with your family or
like in school
plenty of times well
[Music]
family family both both both both family
both oh
yeah that's cute
maybe i can inspire you guys to go for
it again do it again
[Music]
we're almost done we're gonna finish
bubba and then we're gonna do death
sensing
and then i'm done with this pumpkin
pop my fingers
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
thank you cracking did you just call him
boobah oh maybe i did i meant bubba
[Music]
finger cracking
it's a little bit hypocritical that you
guys forgive me cracking my fingers but
you don't forgive me cracking my neck
but okay
i can't
awake
okay guys
they're cramping
[Music]
okay
i'm all
[Music]
hello oh hello to you too who are you
are you old too
do we have the same name perhaps
are we all bloomers here
[Music]
exhausted
oh
you guys are not that old huh
[Music]
[Applause]
okay this is looking good
thankfully we don't have to
uh peel the lower part
of his head
only the hat
[Music]
oh my god
did you guys see it i didn't actually
see the whole thing but i saw that like
a few people or like one person probably
sent me some trailers from the
playstation
presentation
some games apparently look interesting
even to me
i was sent like this this star ocean
game
and another
couple
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
i've never played a star ocean game
before
but i've heard of it so many times
[Music]
it has a at least this this anime
aesthetic that you guys know i do like
it and
it's
it looks pretty good that game
this the graphics are oh there it goes
there the pumpkin goes
i'm gonna have to clean afterwards uh
the graphics look pretty good to me
and
uh the battle system looks fine too
but from my memory like
star ocean always looked good like the
graphics were always good but i don't
know about like the actual game
[Music]
what was your favorite did you guys
watch the whole thing i need to watch it
was it worth watching
state of what's it called stadium play
[Music]
it's so cool
yeah i'm doing football right now
i haven't watched it yet star ocean is
kind of related to tell someone i'm
sorry i'm free certain playstation pc
but
what stay don't play play up did i say
play upstate
sharpen you this is new i literally
bought this before uh
uh
today but then today not not before
today i literally bought it today before
the stream
it's sharp but i'm just like being
trying to be careful and have a
delicate feeling for it you know
[Music]
see i don't want to go too deep you know
i want to go very close to the surface
and i've read though that like there's
white pumpkins and those are way better
for carving but nobody uses them because
they're white
but um the orange pumpkins skin are much
thicker
than
the white pumpkins
so now i want to do the outline here
wait what did i just say the orange
pumpkin skin is much thicker than the
one we had
yes yes
is that gonna be a pain in the ass if i
do that
i can just try to do a slight
slight outline
[Music]
use the knife for the eyeliner should i
like should i go like really deep and
just not cut it
[Music]
i want it will it shine through
this
if i just go for like that
who has experience here
will it shine through
[Music]
yeah oh man
depends on the light
i'm gonna try to
get the tiny parts here
ouch
[Music]
oh that's that's good that's good yes
that's what i want to do like everywhere
but i don't want to take too much time
[Music]
yeah that's good that's good oh that's
good oh that's good that's a good
outline yeah yeah yeah yeah
now we're talking
[Music]
the ear wants to leave me
don't leave me
oh
there's pumpkin on on my camera right
now
that's smooth is it good does it look
good i mean it's gonna be fine
it's gonna be fine
i am probably gonna give you guys
that puzzle piece as well at the end of
the stream if i don't forget you guys
gotta try to
remind me
[Music]
if possible
because we're doing this halloween
puzzle
again
just like last year
but this year it's not drawn by
us smith girls but by someone else
the whole
illustration
yeah are you guys collecting the puzzle
pieces how many do you have now
how many do you guys have by now
who's that good boy a good boy
a good boy you're a goodbye yeah good
boy
four eight oh some of you guys are
missing some i only got two
four
five six
three okay a lot of you guys are missing
some but i guess that's it can't be
helped
because you would have to watch
literally everyone's streams
[Music]
oh that's difficult
leslie knope
[Music]
that's your excuse for not having enough
puzzle pieces you know what i'll take it
i'll take that excuse i think that's a
good excuse
[Music]
okay come out nice that's a good outline
i'm learning so many techniques
yo
ah
[Music]
okay
i went away a bit how many pumpkins did
i miss oh i'm doing it all in one
pumpkin but so far
bubba looks absolutely gorgeous
uh kotori looks okay the outline is
simple enough
takodachi looks like the discord icon or
a playstation controller or pac-man or a
lot of things but it just doesn't look
like taco tachi
yeah kotali is literally twitter
bubba looks amazing though i'm proud of
my bubble
and i'm a bloop bloop i mean blue bloop
looks amazing i'm proud of my bloop and
boom is looking pretty good too so far
i would say
[Music]
i gotta
i think i got the hang out of this
outline thing now
see
you see
i got the hang of it
try carving the next one what
from
what
try carving the next one from inside
what inside how would i even do that
[Music]
i don't i don't know what to do though
should this be one thing
[Music]
i don't know i already started whatever
come on speech
[Music]
and there we go okay
guys i slept so early yesterday i was
like
you know how i ruined my sleep schedule
because of that uh holo
en among us collaboration i stayed up
until 8 a.m
for that
and
obviously
i can't fix that so easily and ttrpg was
like going on until 3 a.m or even longer
as well
so it was
it's very difficult for me to get back
on track but
yesterday i was like in bed watching
desperate housewives
as
kiara does
usually
and
i was getting a little bit tired when i
was cuddling with smoothie
[Music]
and then
it was like
i think it was like um 11 p.m
when i
fell asleep but i i actually i knew that
i was about to fall asleep and i and i
said uh i set an alarm for one hour
later i was gonna take a nap at one hour
before midnight
uh because i didn't think i could sleep
for the night completely
but then i woke up i woke up after one
hour and
i realized
[Music]
i'm gonna make
this into
complete holes later and i realized out
after i woke up at midnight that i was
so tired
and now it's midnight
i should give it a try and i should fall
asleep so
[Music]
even though i didn't take like
the usual procedures that i would do
before going to sleep like
you know going to an idol meeting and uh
drinking a medicine and all that kind of
stuff
like i skipped all those steps so just
so that i wouldn't wake myself up again
because otherwise i would definitely not
be tired enough anymore
so i did that
and i fell back asleep and it was really
comfy and i was sleeping sound
until 4 am
[Music]
4 am i woke up
and
i was
planning
sleeping more
but i needed to go to an idol meeting so
i went to an idol meeting
and then i went back to bed but then i
had issues falling asleep again
surprise surprise
and i checked my phone and that was the
biggest mistake i knew it was gonna be a
mistake
because i looked at something which
actually was uh the
audio from my upcoming song cover
[Music]
hello
i'm reconnected i'm back
hello i'm back
you see me we're back i'm moving right
i'm moving right okay okay good good
good
the eyes scary
that was just saying
[Music]
i was saying youtube back okay we back
okay
sorry the wi-fi is
at least so far so good i would say it's
pretty reliable so thank god
um i was saying so yeah i i listened to
the music
because i got curious because my mix was
done i couldn't help it i had to listen
to it
i couldn't help it
yeah
and
then i gave a little bit of feedback
because i didn't want to like waste any
time it was like there's not much time
left so
i needed to give feedback
ah come on
oh god
[Music]
so
at around 5 00 a.m i was like okay i
want to sleep again but i couldn't
anymore
actually i probably tried back falling
back to sleep at like 4 30 but i
couldn't so
i took my muscle relaxants
and
actually i ended up falling asleep
just fine after that
but
i
felt very tired when i woke up at 8am
which if if i would have slept through
from 11 p.m to 8 a.m i probably would
have been fine but since i had this big
gap in between
[Music]
it didn't work out well
so i
slept until
12 a.m
i guess that's 12 p.m
i ended up oh my god it flew away tong
jacked up
i ended up sleeping pretty long even
though i i fell asleep so early
[Music]
but
it's i guess a step in the right
direction because i gotta fix my sleep
schedule for the whole live sports
festival
[Music]
oh my sports festival
yeah
do you guys want to know what i uh
what i am
uh
like we can choose like which sports
part
which sports uh
we wanna be part of
do you guys wanna know which one i
volunteered for
[Music]
i gotta practice a little bit for it
because it's gonna be very important
that i do not fail
yes
i volunteered for the flying section
which is
the only one the only game that needs
one person only
bubba is done
he is so done
it's basically so
from a high platform i will jump off
with an elytra and i will try to
um fly through two big hoops and then
try to safely land on a specifically
marked area on the ground
which already sounds a little bit
difficult however it's not just that
[Music]
the other team will be trying to
shoot me down with arrows while i'm
flying
it is
i think a little bit difficult and and
while all the other games have more than
one participant this is the only game
that only has one participant so you
feel the pressure of
not being able to [\h__\h] up
[Music]
but
the other teammates seem to agree that
it should be me because apparently in
our team i am at least one of the people
with the most
elytra
experience and i want to try to at least
practice a little bit
i wonder if we can practice with the
actual thing but i will need people to
like shoot me down in order to practice
properly
i watched the one from last year where
aki senpai
flew
um
through those hoops and she was fine she
was fine until the very last second when
she was literally one
millimeter
away from landing
a meadow senpai shot her
and she died in this in the same very
moment when she was landing
so actually i'm wondering because it was
like five six people trying to shoot her
when she was flying
so i'm wondering
maybe it is actually pretty difficult
to land your hit
while that person is flying so you don't
have to worry too much about that part
but once you get closer to the ground
and you're about to land
that's when you're also like slowing
down and they know where you're gonna
fall down so
that is the moment where it gets really
clutch like how are you not gonna get
hit
at that very last moment
right
or
since i would have full health
[Music]
instead of landing really really
smoothly i could try to land
somewhat not smoothly but in exchange
for that i would land faster you know
what i mean like a little bit of a bunk
a little bit of a damage
in exchange for
banning quicker and then not being
hit by the arrows
but i wonder once you land let's say i
landed but it's such a close finish
someone hits me
one
zero seven zero two red zero zero zero
zero point eight no zero point zero
one seconds after i landed
no one's gonna be able to prove that
i really died after i landed i wonder
how that how the rules are gonna work
for that
you know what i mean
i'm scared i don't want to mess up but
let's practice yeah but i need people to
shoot me
like i need i need actual people to help
me practicing if i do that
gotta ask some of the
myth and council girls if they have some
time
um
but i need more than one because it's
gonna be like six people or so aiming at
me that's a lot of people
recreating that by only one person
shooting at me is not gonna
have that much of an effect you know
what i mean
okay let's let's do the last one
let's do death sensei how are we gonna
do
death sensei
[Music]
the easiest way would oh you know what i
have a good idea i have a good idea we
carve out the whole thing okay because
that's simple and quick but
we are then gonna create glasses
and then
the sunglasses we're gonna like put in
yeah with the toothpicks
or maybe even the whole face
or no i think i'll just do the glasses
it's easy
because the glasses would be pretty
close to
each side of the outline
and i think the toothpicks won't stand
out that badly
okay new technique let's go
ah
[Music]
okay the shape is like a ghost shape
it's got like a little fin up there like
a shark
sus
and a round round body like
a like a moon shape
and then
kind of like
this but we'll we'll need the scythe
here too
okay
[Music]
like this
and then
all of this will be hollow
see
here okay all this will be hollow but
we'll be
sticking in toothpicks
here
[Music]
to here
you know what i mean
here this is where the toothpick will be
okay okay okay okay
that should be fairly simple
okay i'm going in
i don't think it hurts death sensei that
much if i stab him
he's already dead
right shouldn't be a problem
with
[Music]
where are the dead beads where are the
beads
show yourself
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
oh present
that beats represent that beats lurking
now
they do be lurking
[Music]
oh the scythe
oh it's gonna be a sharp
very sharp sign
[Music]
okay
actually i mean we could just
do this part
like this
if we wanted to
[Music]
i can even do it with the knife now
i'm getting hecking good at this i
should
i should turn this into my job
[Music]
okay scythe done
that feeds carving now
see for valentine's i remember when we
did the valentine's day chocolate
i love doing like seasonal stuff like
this as a special stream
now we're doing pumpkin carving for
halloween next year for easter i kind of
wanted to do it for easter this year as
well but next year for easter we're
gonna do um we're gonna draw on eggs
we're gonna be painting eggs
for christmas i'm thinking either baking
cookies but i feel like a lot of a lot
of people will be doing that and in
hollow yen i think
gouda is the type of person to be doing
that so i imagine she'll be doing that
so maybe a christmas cake instead like
baking a whole cake
or
[Music]
i would like to decorate a tree
but that's gonna be needing way more
than a handcam
a way bigger angle
it would be nice though
maybe if i wear
what if i wear a green screen suit
and half the tree behind the greens
which is probably gonna be a blue screen
because the tree is green
what if i wear a green screen suit with
those sleeves
so you only see them
oh
my
god
[Music]
okay it has to be a blue screen suit and
a blue screen behind the tree
and then i'll decorate the [\h__\h] tree
would that be fun like it's gonna be
floating sleeves
[Laughter]
you know what i could put on
a christmas like a santa outfit on top
of the uh blue screen
uh full body suit
[Music]
i wonder if i i would be allowed to do
it
like
there would be a floating body with
clothes on that's what i'm imagining
oh my god in one way or another i want
to do this now
i'm gonna do this
what do you mean risky if i help the
whole if i have my whole body covered in
like a green screen basically
that there won't be any issue
i'm sure
because it's just gonna be floating
hands maybe if they say no about the
clothes then i'm just gonna do the
floating hands maybe that sounds like a
lot of work to set up but
the only problem is if i wear a full
body uh
suit
to
color key myself out
that means they're my my face is gonna
be covered
[Music]
oh you know what i'm just gonna
forget the clothes i'm just gonna be
sleeps and then a printed out face
of myself
a paper
face and then put that
on my
green screen full body suit mask maybe i
don't know
[Music]
today
oh that's so that sounds so
hype i don't think anyone has ever done
so something so stupid before
i'm sure people have uh decorated their
trees their christmas trees on stream
before i'm sure someone has done it
before but who has done it in a full
body green screen suit huh
[Music]
i will be the first one
i mean no one until now had the need to
do that i suppose
right
yeah
i'm gonna be the first one
all right christmas i am ready you can
come right now i'm so ready i'm gonna be
i'm gonna be
green
or blue whatever color
i will be it doesn't matter or i could
get a green screen and a white plastic
tree or something i want to get a real
tree that i think
get out of there get out of there
step six
[Music]
get over there come on
no i'm getting exhausted please
i think this part isn't
cut well
please i beg you
[Music]
i beg you
difficult push it from inside
[Music]
something on this side is
kind of
problematic right now
i thought i was
thrilled there we go there we go i think
it's ready
[Music]
[Laughter]
i got it oh look how cute callie should
i send this over to you
should i send this to you
all right now the glasses um
[Music]
how do i do
how do i do this
[Music]
this is not that difficult
okay
just carve around it like like this
no no hold on
you know what this is so much fun i'm so
glad i'm doing this like you know
cooking streams like this
it's not really cooking but still
our
um ori is a little bit of a
annoyance to prepare a bit troublesome
and always of course
a huge risk for me
makes me very nervous and all that but i
just want you guys to have some
content that is different from my usual
content very
different and i want you guys to see
something original that other people are
not doing so for a little change you
know
wanna be original
so
that's why i'm doing this even though
my heart is racing
and for some reason i'm always like out
of breath when i do these type of screen
streams i don't know why
i don't know why
this table will be fun to clean
afterwards
[Music]
yeah it's very stressful but at the same
time having fun too like doing
doing
stuff that's
different from usual it's it's fun for
me too like change of heart change of
whatever
and being creative and also learning to
cook the things that i learned until now
that was fun too
what was i getting at though what was my
point i forgot
i forgot what my point was
damn it this shape is actually pretty
nice
and now
we're gonna do
a toothpick
strategy
[Music]
like so
and then another one
[Music]
on the other side
variety is the spice of life yeah what's
a variety on my channel and i really
hope you guys are enjoying it
uh wait a second
uh
how did i
plan on doing this
oh
okay
as
deep as possible i think it broke
i think one side broke
but let me try to push it in
okay
oh my god it's working
it's working what about this side though
i have to bend it like
this oh wait let's make it shorter maybe
[Music]
okay
i mean it looks messy
hmm can i put that back in here
yes yes oh it's working it's working
oh my god
see
oh it looks nice
[Music]
it looks so nice
that beads you're looking beautiful you
might be the best one out of all of
those i've made
the deadbeats
bubba
and
bloop
right
bloop with the hat
[Music]
kotori so simple
and
taco dancing
do you want to light it up guys are you
ready for that special moment
okay let me grab my the the one candle
that i have that might fit inside i hope
it fits let me grab that
and
let's have a
bubba
listen to some music
[Music]
all right
i was like wearing my headphones
okay so i got this really nice
[Music]
a cherry vanilla
yankee candle does it fit and does
[Music]
don't worry
and i'm gonna start the fire today don't
stop don't stop just go your own way
do you want to see how i started fire
today
[Music]
let's start a fire today
i only have these because like i don't
i don't rarely start any fires
uh
on a day-to-day basis so i don't have
the what do you call the proper thing
that goes like pew pew fire
i have the traditional
method
[Music]
obviously as a phoenix i could just
snip my fingers and then there would
yeah a lighter i was talking about
lighter but i could normally i could
snip my fingers snap my fingers and that
would a fire would come out of my finger
obviously but
we're gonna do it this way
[Music]
i'm really bad at this though i'm really
really bad at this
i hope my gloves don't get too quiet
it's tight
[Music]
that was a
surprisingly quick
oh i stopped the fire today oh my god
it's a big flame
wow now it's calmed down okay i'm gonna
place this inside but what if the lid
falls on top of
the fire i hope it doesn't
[Music]
okay
oh it's hot
stand out for this
okay okay
[Music]
okay no sorry
spooked me but my my arm touched the
microphone okay all is good
now
uh
don't fall
i have a bad feeling
i guess i gotta
use
some of the toothpicks
[Music]
oh something broke but i think it's okay
it's okay it's okay i'm gonna turn the
light off now
[Music]
should i turn more
oh
[Music]
yay
oh my god you don't really see it but in
the background i want to show you you ah
let me try to take a picture for later
but the
behind right behind the pumpkin
there's like a light shadow light
reflection on the white wall behind of
dance death sensei
oh my god let me take a picture
let me take some pictures
oh my god it looks so cool
the dumpster series was so cool
oh my god i'm so excited
this is so cool
[Music]
oh my god there's a ghost on the photo
the shape of death sensei literally
makes it look like a ghost
okay let's see if i can get a good
picture of uh
bloop doesn't
light up that much except for the hat
[Music]
on the photo
it looks pretty good
[Music]
actually it works better on the photo
[Laughter]
you were you were you were the audience
was taking a picture
did you feel like a photographer now
oh my god don't look at death santa yet
because it looks absolutely perfect
don't look at him yet
[Music]
oh god the smell i feel like the the
pumpkin
is getting roasted
oh my god i i looked inside and it looks
like a little bit black on a tiny piece
of black on the top of
the pumpkin lid
like but it's not touching it so it's
just roasting it slightly by heating it
[Music]
all right look at this
yo
oh my god
[Music]
it's spooky
this is so cool i'm so glad i did this
what do you think guys which one is your
favorite guy
i kind of feel sorry for kotori for
kind of like making it so simple now but
at least it lights up like the most
i like i think i like deaf sensei like
as a
the way it works with the light inside i
think i like deaf sensei the most but
from like
the actual piece of art i think i like
bloop the most
you don't see it so well but i'll upload
a picture later you're gonna see it well
death sunset
[Music]
definitely death sentences booty bubba
looks cute
death sensei
boba
bubba
i like i think i like bloop and death
sensation most
those were great models to
carve
really challenging
looks nice too
it's really ironic
when i have
kotori right in front of me facing to
the camera the reflection behind it
you don't see it unfortunately but the
reflection behind it i mean what do you
call it is this a reflection it's not a
shadow either
because
it's lighting up the wall in the shape
of death sensei
what do you call that
it's not shadow it's not a reflection
it's a projection ah
i guess so
that's true okay
i'm projecting
death sensei
on the wall right behind
kotori because it's right the opposite
it looks so cool
i want to take one more picture
this is so cool
[Music]
the whole area around it is a mess but
that's okay because it's dark
[Music]
i'm going to upload those to twitter and
maybe to the community board if you want
to see it
wait let me take a pic a video too oh
[Music]
i always say bubba when i see blue i
don't know why right
[Music]
and you saw it
on the back but here's def sensing what
[Music]
i took a video
i'm gonna upload that later get it
checked with manager song but i think it
should be fine
all right
[Music]
again applause for the effort we made
something wonderful today
thank you for watching today i hope you
enjoyed it i wish you all a happy
halloween but halloween is not over yet
tomorrow i'm playing
outlast with good eyes my mental support
and then on saturday what am i doing
again on saturday or is that saturday
no way what was saturday again
i forgot
what's happening on saturday
[Music]
little nightmares oh yeah i've never
played that game before but you guys
also seem very excited about that one in
particular i'm playing little nightmares
on my channel on saturday and sunday
why am i moving so oh because it's so
dark
but my my camera is trying to do its
best right now but i keep on shaking
actually surprise is still
capturing me so nicely
uh on the puzzle piece oh yeah yeah yeah
one second one second um
this is so cool we have a glowing
finished pumpkin
oh my god
let me go grab the puzzle piece one
second uh i need to go to discord
oh
[Laughter]
jenna actually sent me that gordon
ramsay super chat so that i could read
it thou shall caveman other pumpkin i'll
cook this chicken for thanksgiving wait
what the hell
oh no no battery mode well that's okay
because i'm almost done i actually don't
even have my camera
uh connected
right now it's doing so well i'm glad it
all worked out even with
wi-fi uh okay let me get the puzzle
piece
today
i will give you
this one last time was a corner piece
uh this time it is
not
but
[Music]
can you guys cut it out yourself like
maybe here oh no my phone did
ah come back
you're you're at 20 percent get your
[\h__\h] together
hello oh no okay well we're done for
today that's okay i would have to
reconnect it it's okay
[Music]
but you guys still hear me right
now
this is the puzzle piece doesn't that
look like cali
could that be cali
oh yeah yeah it definitely is a side
piece though because the wrap the right
side is flat so
uh should i make it bigger for you guys
a little bit bigger i mean you guys will
have to cut it out yourself
i can't help you with that today uh or i
don't know yeah
you guys are good at that stuff aren't
you
yeah you guys know how to use photoshop
right let me show here
that's uh oops oh my god
i need a mouse
hey this is the piece
piece of the day i have one more left
i'm gonna give that to you tomorrow
[Music]
keep on collecting guys keep on
collecting
and i will now have a little halloween
party with my pumpkin
and clean up
[Music]
i will have to clean up this whole mess
um but i had a great time thank you so
much for watching the stream today i
hope you enjoyed it
and i hope all went well so far i think
no yeah byes no yeah by incidents
i'm proud i'm very proud good job
carvings thank you it was my first time
but i had a great time i want to do this
again
i want to do it again
waiting for the pictures oh yeah look on
twitter wait for the pictures and
perhaps the video as well
because it looks a little bit better on
my phone camera i think than it does
with this webcam
yeah the house isn't on fire either
the pumpkin is uh
getting closer to it perhaps um trying
to look inside but i don't really see
anything
all right then thank you for watching
i'll see you tomorrow
uh
it's kind of difficult to read super
chats in this setup so i hope that's
okay
um i'll read it after outlast 100
uh or
uh unless unless i am
mentally so exhausted that
it's not possible for some reason but i
think i should be fine
[Music]
hope hopefully
hopefully
so in german we say
[Music]
thank you guys
see you tomorrow
love you love my chickens
thank you for watching
bye bye bye
[Music]
you know what i love that smell when you
blow out a candle and it smells like
burnt but like the good kind of burnt
you know what i mean
[Music]
yeah
that's so good
[Music]
and as a as a child i used to whenever i
would blow out candles i would put my
finger into the candle
and have that like the liquid hot
um
wax
all around my finger i love doing that
it felt so nice
did you guys do that too
yeah i would put it into the pretty hot
wax my thing did you guys not do that
i wanted to wrap my
my uh fingers in the wax
[Music]
yes yes okay i see a lot of people say
that we're doing it a lot of people are
like what you missed something in your
childhood
yeah the hot wax but it would cool down
like really quickly
[Music]
it's not so bad
i definitely did it nice nice nice
never touched the pumpkin what
youtube unsubbed you what the hell thank
you for fixing it guys you you might
have been unsubbed from my channel
this is a good reason to follow me on
twitter because that really happens
sometimes youtube just unsubs you from
channels
so
follow my twitter
but you could definitely feel like
something is off if you don't see a
stream in your subscription box for
more than
one day
then you're you have to
get sucks at that moment you gotta be
like
there is no [\h__\h] way that kiana
didn't stream
once in two days that is impossible
then you gotta check my channel
and see
if you still sub to me
very important
thank you guys
bye-bye
[Music]