[Music]
This
program is
brought to you by the sponsors you see.
[Music]
[Applause]
Iknowbabyfo is heading to the new studio. It's been
a while since I last saw it, and it probably isn't that different from the previous studio.  It
may not look like it, but it's
definitely different, but I wanted to create the same atmosphere.
[Music]
Senpai
Before I call Hane, uh,
this studio is a bit of a new studio.  I
want people to watch it, so I ask them to watch it first,
so my
seniors are taking a little break and taking a quiet break here and there.Okay,
then, and un, isBend
saveman. It's
been 7 months.
[Music]
A little bit of that,
hmm.  Not only did I go to America and get sick,
so
I purposely took a seven-month break, but things
didn't go well for a while, so
if I hadn't done that,
a lot of time would have passed, and by the time I got back, I'd have
something new.  So I decided to go back with some stuff, and
then I kind of
took a break, but
yeah, I'm
going to check it out
andthenewstudy.  I
'd like to show you this, but
when I was looking at the cutouts with the guests, there
wasn't anything in particular about the room, but now we
have a room.
[Music] The
pattern on the wall behind me is interesting, isn't it? I don't like it.
[Laughs]  ]
That's right, this is new.
For example, if someone were to enter, it would look like this and there would be a
music video in the back.
Music. Do you
want to show me one more thing?
Jean [
Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Ayame-senpai must
be there somewhere too.  There should
be that stage on the right. That light.
Stage 3.
[Music] There's a chicken
with a camera. Now let's move
on to the action.
[Music] On the
5th, we're going to
do it completely in 3D, so I
made it in 3D so that everything is connected.
Thankyoufunkingmy
NEWS
This talk
is a special prize for the interview of the English-speaking model.The purpose is to
let people know more about herbal medicine, mainly Japanese celebrities, and artists.It is
provided by Takanashi Gala of the broadcaster.
Yes, yes, OK
[laughter] Nice, OK,
sorry to have
kept you waiting.
Thankyouforcoming
andwellcomeevery
WalkerMygusmys,
go ahead,
Yami-senpai.
Naru
[Laughs]
Please, please, you
came to this really special episode. I'm really
happy. Thank you very much for inviting me to this new stage.
[Music]
Hey, here too.  I wonder if it's a big deal. How about I
raise my voice a little and lower my voice?
OK,
yes. Where is
my
[Music]?
Okay, let's get into the questions now.
[Music] Let's do our best, let's
do our best, let's try our best. Yes, these days.
Ayame: What kind of activities have you been doing,
Senpai? Lately, have you
been streaming games? What kind of
games are you playing?
Splatoon 5.
Also, I've been playing Valoran,
so I've been
thinking about playing Horoki, and
seriously, Senpai, too.  I've
never played it before, I've never played it yet. It's a game I'm addicted
to. I really
want to play it.
I think everyone will be happy if you just lie a little faster and do it. [
Music]
[Music]
[Music]  ]
So, just to give you a little bit of
information, I really love
Kobu-chan from my daughter Kobo-chan's Hololive ID,
and I'm so
into it that I think it would be a good idea to collaborate with her.I
would love to do something with her someday.
When Kou-chan and two other people were collaborating with Bararan, he got so
excited that he joined
Discord and participated in the collaboration. That's
how much I love him.  That's right
. That's right. That's my
favorite question
. Ah, right now. That's
right. That's probably my
favorite question. Okay, okay, that's perfect. Let's move on to the next question. Okay, I'd like to try it
with Kobo-chan.  Ii-ko-chan is
really cute, so it's true.She's really
cute and her songs are delicious.OkOk
Next question is,
is there anything you've been unable to say due to the language barrier that you wanted to convey to people overseas?
But, well, I
can't really speak English very well.  But
yeah, yeah, yeah, but I just
want to understand what everyone is saying, so I've been studying a little bit lately.I
want to tell you what
form you study in.
Do you study with a teacher, or do you do it on your
own?I bought that book, and I
studied vocabulary.
Really,
for example, what movie did you memorize earlier?
Well, it's difficult when you're told a word you've learned recently. You
have to do your best, right?
Well,
wait a minute. I
'll translate it for you.
It's fresh.  Wings of the day
Select
Did you find it?
Found it
What I learned recently
Increase this The word yasu Why why
why Edemo It might come up quite a bit in a vocabulary book The
Japanese
word for maintenance
[Music]
Eh, OK, I think it's quite a difficult word. I
feel like it comes up here and there in things like listening.Ah, OK, then I'll
teach you some sentences in English, like Takanashi, the teacher.
Hey, tell me. That's what everyone said earlier.  "I
understand,
please turn up the volume, Ayame-senpai.
"
[Music] I can
use it even in such situations. It
was just the right word. Now that's what I'm talking about.
Okay, genius camp. Ok,
then, uhm,
studying English.  Hane: No matter how
hard I try, I'm still
struggling to learn English.Speaker:
I
'm a member of the family, and it seems like this is my first collaboration partner.Yes, that
's right.I'd
like to collaborate with other members of the family.  I
'd like to know if there are any members, but I'd like to talk to everyone,
but I'd
especially like to talk to Ina-chan.
Everyone, Ina-chan can
speak Japanese, so she's easy to talk to, Ina-chan.  I feel relieved because I'm good at Japanese.You
know, I'm
good at Japanese.You know, I'm a Japanese person from overseas.For
example, when I meet a foreigner and the foreigner
just says, "Hello," I'm Japanese.  People
say that I'm good at Japanese,
so I
thought that even my enemy on stage was real, so
thank you for speaking with me today.
[Laughs
] No, that's not it. OkOk Google, I'm going to overline Japanese. [Music] There's
something about this that seems like a really good match.  Yes, I guess.
Actually, Ina-chan loves puns as much as Ayame-senpai.
That's right.
Both men and women have been using them for a long time. Oh yeah,
yeah, there
are puns in English as well.  Please
use Net Tiara as a project and as an opportunity to
collaborate with the members of the family.I
would like to talk to everyone.Really,
please, please feel free to do so.It
may be a Japanese employee.Gaze
[Music]
Okay, next question.
Okay, I might have been a little confused at first,
but I'm not sure what
you like most about it.
For example, games, karaoke,
chatting, collaborating, etc.
[Music] I
like all of them, but
think I might like chatting.  No, I
don't think so. I think I like talking to everyone. I also
have the impression that I'm doing a lot of collaborations with senpai. It's a big collaboration
[Music]
Yeah, that's
great. I'm always invited. I'm so grateful that I get invited.
But I'm really
shy, so
there are times when I can't talk when there's a lot of people around, but I
like to talk.I see, this program is
perfect for me.Yes, that's
right.But I'm a little nervous.It's
okay, don't be nervous.I still have a
lot of questions.  So,
slowly, slowly,
do your best,
do your best. Eh, and then turn around. [Music] There's no need to be nervous. I'm sure everyone in the chat will say the same thing. Hey, I'm a senior. I'll do my best with confidence.
OK, now it's time for the next one. Here's a
new
question.
For those of you who are seeing it for the first time, I
would like you to explain the basics. First of
all, I see.
Are you called?
Finally, this is it. I
don't remember reading it, but
when I noticed it, everyone was calling me Ojou.
No, what?  I don't think so, but for some
reason people started calling me 'Ojou'. I wonder if it's
been like that from the very beginning.
Or maybe it was just after a while.
At first, everyone started calling me 'Ojou'.  I think she was called Ayame-chan.
Everyone in the chat, I
think there are fans of Ai's seniors, but I wonder
if she's a boy or
has a lady-like vibe. Oh, she has a tea-like vibe, and her
fan name is
Cry-Gumi, so she's a
lady.
[Music] When you
add the word gummy to something, it sounds like a
yakuza.Ah,
ok, ok, ok.That's why the
leading lady among the actors is called Ojou.
[Laughs] To
put it simply, that's what it feels like.
OK, easy to explain.
[Laughs] I
didn't think of Gumi as a yakuza, but I
guess that's kind of what it's like.  It seems like something like that. Let's
get a member who failed.
[Music]
Yakuza-buying
[laughing]
[Music]
OkOk
Next,
what does your condition mean
? And you're also calling yourself Yo.
What does that mean?
Umm, Japan.  I
don't know if I should say ``Eh'' in the past, but I think there aren't many people who call it ``color'' these days, but uh,
people are noisy these days, and I
don't say ``I'' in Japanese.It's like an old version of that.  The
people who used it, the
people of that era,
ah, and those
things, for example,
hmm,
for example, the samurai especially used it.I
think there was a way to say it, but
the point is, it was used by certain people.  It's
kind of like the old days. I
thought there were a lot of great people. That's the
image. Oh, OK. I see. It's like today's
first person. I see. Oh,
and one more thing. Which
song is that? Which one do
I know?  But
yeah, I don't know.For everyone, that
was a Minecraft broadcast, and
when I was going to my destination, I
didn't know which way to go, so I
improvised and said, ``Which direction? Which direction?'' Some
of the fans made up a song for me.
For some reason, it seems like
there was a time when it was really popular around
me. Have you
heard that song yourself a few times
? If I were to ask you, would you be able to
sing it? I might not be able to sing the full song, but I could probably
sing it just a little bit, just a little bit.  It feels
like the Japanese members around me are singing.
Everyone around me remembers it.
[Music] I'd
like them to sing a little bit.
So which one?
Which one?
Wait, I'll play that, then I'll play around a little more.  Shall we
move to the stage now? There's
no sound source, it's okay, a cappella. Let's
move.
Please show me your whole body,
ok.
Ah, I'll pay you.
Well, behind the microphone. Okay. It's
nice to be able to use it. It's embarrassing, but I remember the lyrics.  I wonder if
it'll
come out or which one It'll
come out or which one It'll come out or which one The song lyrics will be there Yes, I'll
send it Yes, I
want you to send it to me This is a strange site, but
if I scroll this, it will be
there.It's a little
strange, but
I sent it to
you.  Yes,
there was, there was, there was,
yes, okay
OkOk
[Music]
Well, let's just sing the chorus a little. I'll
keep it quiet. Let's go.
Eh,
wait, wait, remember the notes. You
can do it while listening. Ah, the
chorus.  Which one is colder?
Wait a minute, there's no sound source for this one. Apparently there's
also a karaoke version. There's a karaoke version. I'm
looking for something here. They
're not singing.
[Music] Yes.
Walking karaoke probably
won't play, but this one. Yeah.  It
's okay, I'll go, OK, mute.  [
Laughs] The
fire is almost ok.
[Music] I
'm going back.
[Music] I'll
make it louder. Which one, which one, which one, which one, which one,
which one, which one, I
remember.
Well, you know, I've been researching it for far away. It's
just been coming to my mind lately.
Thank you. Please
sing a little.  Thank you
very much for that.
Now that I know more about it,
I want to see Ayame-senpai's cute paulownia tree.
Wow, that's
embarrassing. Oh, this
place is already here.
What can I do with it?
[Laughs]
[Music]  ]
Seniors
gathering
[Music]
What are you saying?
It just made a cat meow.
[Laughs]
Pretty Cure,
crying, crying lady.
[Laughs] That's it.
[Music]
[Applause]
Actually, that's from the fog.  The tree was
made by a
certain staff member,
erm,
Ayabe-senpai,
I always say that I want a cutout like this,
but this time, the staff
member somehow managed to make it for me.  I was being selfish and
asked if I could make a collection of cute sounds.What
happened?
Oh yeah, that's right, this is a masterpiece.It seems like I
wanted to make it no matter what.Thank you
very much.
Well, well, well, this
seems to be Ayame-senpai's charm point, so chan-
chan's laughter is chan-chan's point, and
cute sounds are chan-chan's
point.Then, the next question is about Ayame-senpai's unique laughter and happy energy.  Memes
are popular among people overseas, but I'd like to
know if there are any similar ones among Japanese people who have
heard of them.  I wonder
if you're using my brother. I'm
making it. I'm using the
same thing. Sei-
sensei. I
wonder if this was first thought up by people overseas. Well, I guess
so, but I
think I first heard it from people in Japan.
[Music]
National World  The
world's
common language is Kirium, which is the common language of the world.And maybe
even today's All Talk is
charging everyone with crying.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Oh, that
was really good.  The
clippings are already
so-and-so.It's more fully charged than just the clippings.It
was written in English.It
's
easy.It's
easy.It's an easy
answer, so let's move on to the next one.Well, I
heard that Iam-senpai loves making puns.  But do you
have a favorite pun? And if you
have any good puns, please let me
know.Hmm, didn't you just ask me what kind of broadcasts you like?
During a match,
when you lose, you make excuses.  I do it, right? Yoga. I
tend to make
excuses, like it's because of what happened now. [Music] When I'm making excuses, everyone says, ``Okay, now I can make excuses, so I can make excuses, too.'' That's why I
like it so much.  But I
see. I understand this, but it's a bit in English. I'll try
it anyway
.
[Music]
Excuse me, make an excuse.
[Music] I
think I was able to explain it. It's
easy to understand. There were some puns, too.  I
wonder if it's a little bit, a
long time ago, when I was broadcasting Animal Forest, there
was an Easter event going on, and I had
collected a lot of eggs, and
when I opened the item run, I saw this
egg.
Japanese
[Music]
Atsumori
[Applause]
[Music] Don't
tell me, I'm a simple family mart shopper. It
's normal for things to become less interesting if I explain them.
Okay, since it's a joke, I'll
tell you Ino. After all, this
is also a pun about eggs.
Eggs!
Only one word.
The word for that perfect value.
Or the word wonderful.
In English, it's
exce. When you
soften it
and add the egg, it goes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
For example, that
morning, if you
fried an egg and
made a beautiful picture, you
could just say "Eki-chan." I
see. That
doesn't mean "excellent."
I'm
not as good at making puns as Ayumi-senpai, but
no, no, no, no.  I
'm going to do it next time.
[Music]
What kind of
changes have you seen in your streaming content and personality since you debuted? I wonder if there have been any changes like that.
In the past, maybe you were a little
calmer and quieter.  No, it
might have been a little darker.
[Music]
It was dark, but it was like being in middle school.
Car: I
wouldn't say it before, but it's not as crazy as it is now.
[Laughs]
okokokiUSBMycomeand
&
dogs
[Music]
Others  I wonder if there's anything else?
Well, I don't know what else to
say. Maybe I wasn't making a joke. Which is it? I mean, I
might have been wearing a cat mask.
Now that I've been wearing a cat mask, I
wonder if there's an accident, and where is the cat?
[Laughs] We
were really talking about cats.
[Laughs]
Wearing a cat's head is a
proverb. It may not be a pun, but
when I said where is the cat, it became a pun.
[Laughs]
No, this is a pun.  Well,
[Music]
That's amazing, is
n't it? But it's amazing. It
seems like this is an idiom, but I know what it means
. I
hear the words, "cat mask, imitate, koko hide" quite a lot in everyday Japanese. That's
amazing.  All right, all right,
Japanese. I
want you to see it. As expected,
I found this
and thought it was interesting, so I
had it made for me. It's my
birthday. I'm in the middle of this, so it's not my birthday. I
was sent a saran lamp as a present to die for.
Saran Wrap came so fast that I didn't have to buy it for the rest of my life,
and Barry and I were both rich.They came
in all kinds of sizes, so I guess we ended up with
about 10 of them.
[Laughs] I got
900 meters of Saran Wrap for my daughter.  It
took quite some time, oh yeah, that's right, the
culprit is
throwing matches. I'm
going to carry it out. I'm going to buy a lot of Saran Wrap with this
[Music] I've
been getting yelled at. Even with this,
let me buy Saran Wrap again.  I came here to try it out, but
thank you.The
other day I used up only one long one,
so I got a new one.Seriously, I'm
laughing.I still have it
left.I seriously got it, so I'm only
down to about 4 bottles.  Isn't that right? It's
already worth 900 meters.
[Music] There
's no saran wrap. Wash the dishes. I don't have any of that either. How much does it cost?
Well, that's true. The ones who want it
are the souvenirs. What kind of a senior is this?  Right?
[Music]
What do you think?
I'm the Saran Wrap senior.
[Music]
[Laughs] I
have a question about this. It's different. Oh,
what's the order?
So far, how much Saran Wrap have you used for that 900-meter run?And
this is the strangest gift you've received in the four years since you joined Hol Live.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Well, Saran Wrap...  It's a bit of a
mess.
There are several sizes of Saran Wrap in Japan, but I've
used up all of the large ones, and I
still have about 45 of the short, medium, and small sizes
left.
But I think I used it quite a bit. I think I used it a lot,
half 50%,
half a little, half a little.
60%,
about 65, 65. Did I
get this
or that? When was this? I think it was two years ago. I've
used 60% in two years, so I've used it quite a bit.
Well, I wonder if I'm using it, I can't wait, it's going to run out, so it's going to come again, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'm not going to give you
a present. Good, good, good, it's going to increase again.  It's
just not safe because they won't send it. They
might even tear off all the Saran wrap and put it in the letter. I don't
like it.
Saran wrap letters are coming.
[Music] It's
like a love letter.
This was the weirdest gift I've received in the four years I've been a member of Hololive.
Or the weirdest thing is, I think it's
something that
babies
put in their mouths. I do
n't know why. I don't know. I'm going to play with that pacifier. I'm going to talk. I'm going to use a
grip strength measuring device.
[Music]
Wait, I saw a cutout of it. I
wonder what they'd call it.
[Music] I wonder
what they were hoping for when they sent me that one that measures grip strength. Hmm,
maybe it's that Japanese member.  Ta-chan
has a grip strength of 50 kg, so I
guess that's why I thought Ayame-chan sent it to me because she wanted me to measure it too.
Oh, my grip strength was probably around 25.  I don't
think I have it at all.My arms are so weak that people
say my arms are nude.
[Music]
No, but I
can't get enough grip strength because I'm 50 kg. It's
amazing from the stars
[Music]
[  [Music] [
Music]
[Music] It
seems like someone on the amazing chat is saying 60.
Eh, 6056 Akana-senpai is 56. It
's about 5 o'clock right now, so she's 56 right now. I
wonder if she's been exercising. Oh, I really want to hear about that
next time.  Senpai When I meet Kanata-senpai, I'll
ask him to give me that lift.
Well then, I'll
use my senpai to measure my grip strength. My hands
will only be here.
[Music]
OkOk, well, I hope that weird, strange gift
never
comes.  Yes, but let's
move on to the next question.
[Music]
Your senior
is a demon. What kind of
demon-like things do you do?
Eh,
demon-like things? I'm not saying you're doing anything,
but yeah,
demons are Japanese.  So, I do
n't like beans as a food.Mame
So
Mame
Bibin
Kira Aso or that kind of
demon I want the demon to go away There's going
to be a fire, so you throw the beans
Ayame
Senpai says that it's going to be tough that day
[Music] on the side
But read carefully I don't like beans I
really
can't eat them in any shape I don't like them anymore They're
perfect Sichuan
Demon Oh Japanese
[Laughs] I
see, there are other
things that are demon-like.  It's normal for a demon to do something.
He's kind of scary, isn't he? He's not scary at all,
senpai. Maybe if he gets angry, he might be really scary. I've never
seen him
get angry.
[Music] Now
streaming  No, but Ayame-senpai got so angry twice that she
punched a hole in the wall.
[Music]
[Applause]
That happened, too. I
thought I'd cut this out a bit. You
know that well.  That
's right.
[Music]
When was that? How long ago was that
?
Well, that was, but it was already 78 years ago. Amazing. I'm
not scared of Ayame-senpai after all. Ah,
but
maybe she's kinder now.
Well, I guess there are demons like that, but
kappas are also called demons, right? Leaf, leaf, kappa, kappa, kappa,
etc. Kappas are not demons either, so I
understand. I wonder
what they are. They
're monsters, but
[music]
So,
next
time, I looked at OkOk and
asked a question, but what is the
island incarnation of Mim?
Could you please explain that to me? That's probably
Minecraft, but I was looking for treasure in Minecraft.  It
was written on the map that there was a treasure on a small island, but
while I was looking for it, I dug it up and it seems like the whole island was erased, and
almost all of it was erased.  It was
used as a dresser, so it
was said that they would destroy it and sort it out.What happened to that turtle?It's so
nostalgic.I
feel like that was right after I debuted,
but there was something about Mako's
island erasing.  I understand how it was originally created, but I
think the word "sorting" has come up many times since then, but when and
how do you use it?
If you get angry, you'll be erased from the island.  You
don't have time,
do you? What are you going to erase? Ah, but I see. There are ways to use it like that. It's
interesting. It's scary, but it's okay. I
just said it, and I'm not saying it right now. I
see. Hey
Kamekamekamekamekame
[Music]  ]
English Ah
[Music]
What is it? Turtle
Turtle
Now
Turtle Turtle Yes,
Dougs and
Originald
And
yes, I think I
explained it well, thank you very much.
[Music]
[Laughter]
OK, one more thing
Mim,
I'm glad you understand.
Yes, this is Ayame-senpai's cute hobby.I
heard that she has a hobby of collecting goshuin stamps when she visits shrines.I
would like to know what kind of hobby she has and how much she collects.
Well, I'm
embarrassed to
say that you really looked into this, but in Japan, there's something about shrines.To put it simply, it's
like a stamp rally, where you get a stamp sound,
and I really enjoy collecting stamps that are
unique to that shrine.  I
'm collecting about 15 of them now, visiting various shrines.
[Music]
Senpai:
I want to give you some knowledge about that point that doesn't matter, but I
actually lived in Japan.  Once upon a time, I worked as a shrine maiden
at that shrine.
That's
right. I wanted to see it. She
worked at that really big shrine, and there were
quite a few
tourists and Japanese people there. I
wanted a goshuin stamp, so I
asked Chiara to do it for me.  That's right, I
didn't play the character, so I'm going to hand it over
to that person this time and
ask for 5 wins.'' That's
right, that's right, that's what I did when I brought it back again.
[Laughs] It's
good to imagine.  I saw a tiara at a place where they sold fortunes
and charms.Eh
, I wanted to go buy some, but
this
was at some Tenmangu shrine somewhere.Eh, the
top is a little big, it's huge.It's
amazing.  It was fun and I learned a lot.That's why
I was a little happy that I had a hobby of stamps.When I heard that, I felt a little familiarity.  I've
been talking about that, but I've never received a goshuin myself,
so someday I'd like Ayame-senpai to
teach me how to do it.I
want to go there with you.
[Music] I
want to go to a shrine that you've never been to before.  Let's go, let's
go. I'm looking forward to it. By the way, Chara, I'm going to Japan in December. I want to go. I really want to go. [Music] Yay! I'm so happy. Thank you. [Music] Yay. [Music] - I'm really excited.
By the way
[Music]
- What?
Yay, I'd
like you to answer in English if you can. OK,
do your best. That
's it.
Next time, that's it. Which is better? It's cold.
Food is the main thing.
Last or rare?
Gusto
Same
Twitter feeling Instagram
Twitter
Apple or
orange
juice I'd rather climb a mountain or run a marathon
[Music]
Marathon is OK I'd
never put pineapple on pizza
[Applause]
[Music] I'm
going to cry I
prefer spicy or sweet food
Tea or coffee
?
Traveling on the beach by the sea or studying abroad in a dreamy big city?
Hmm... On the
beach by the sea.
When I sleep, I'm
naked or clothed.
[Laughs] My
favorite events are Halloween, Christmas, Issa,
etc.  Don Tanabata Setsubun
Ah, I wonder
if Setsubun will be rolled up?
Christmas
Seven or Family Mart
Son Which one do you
like? Seven Ok, I prefer Momoshi Moshi Seven Which would
be better, a text message or a phone call? Eh, a
phone call
Giving or receiving a present,
which one?
[Music]
That gentle Saran from the Hammer book that gives away  I do
n't need rap
[Laughs]
Walk the distance of one station Or take a car train?
[Music]
OK, what's your blood type? I've
never done it, right
? I've
never done it. I
know
[Music]
So what color are your pants? Huh?
Nao Nao Nao Oda
[Laughter]
[Music]
You know, actually, Ayame, I
asked a question about your blood type for my senior. I did it, but you
knew I never said that. The
iron was made
by the staff member who made that cutout.  I
said to that person, ``If you know anything about Ayame-senpai, please let me know if you have any questions that I should ask.'' It's
not there, but I've
never told him about his blood type, so I'd like him to tell me.
Unfortunately, it was a secret.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music] I'll secretly
check it out later and tell Chara-chan,
thank you. You
know, actually, I've been living abroad, too.
It's been like that in the past, and it's like that now, but somehow it's my
blood.  There aren't many people who know about your type, so that's right, that's right,
not that many. No one asks what happened to your blood. No one knows what happened to you.
There are Japanese people who
think that it's somehow connected to their personality.
No one thinks about it, so
no one knows your blood type.
[Music] Why are you
talking about the color of your body parts
?
[Music] There
's a saying in English that says, ``A woman must have a secret.''
There's something about
this that's
going to be an eternal secret.
[Music] I've
never
said it before, but I just don't
think there's ever been a reason to mention it before. OK OK
[Music] I
want you to calm down and watch it. Please
[Music]
Everyone.  I'm a young lady, but even in a situation where
an impostor commoner is mixed in,
if Mr. Button Button says something like that, I
would think that Mr. Button is suspicious.I see, it's
easy to blame him, so I
'll do it.
[Laughs]
That's too funny. I'll keep an eye on you. I'm all alone again.
" "
Good morning everyone.
Where did you go? You disappeared in an instant.
[Laughs]
On top of you.  I haven't been there, Miss
Melon. There are
too many people.
You're not a young lady, are you? The
family's budget.
No, no, no, there's no money to give to the common people. The
young
lady won. In the end, this is how she
speaks.  It's more interesting.
In English, there's a way of speaking like this. Well, that
's it. The English subtitles have been made to sound as lady-like as possible. That's what they're doing.
[Music]
Oh
no.  She
spoke very much like a young lady, but she's a princess,
so I wonder why she doesn't always talk like this.
Even when I say young lady, I mean
young lady. It seems
suspicious, minus Shirai-san.
Yoshi-san's.  Lady &
George Fong
is a young lady. It
was
cute. As expected of Vacuum.
[Music] Have
you all calmed down? Ayami-senpai. Have you calmed down? Have you calmed down
? Your tension has loosened up a bit. That's
good.
Me too. I
always get nervous when posting holo posts.  I'm nervous because of the people. I'm
so nervous. Yeah,
well, it's almost over. It's
okay.
[Music]
Hey, I hope you don't
understand. The
next question is
based on other Japanese culture.
[Music]
Yeah
Design The
members gathered together, Myu-senpai and Fubuki. Hey, you
're in Yurito, but do you have any good memories or
interesting episodes?
Yeah, maybe good memories, but Kouko's
members are called Iroha Nihohe or Yahoo, and that's their
name.
Please say ``Ayafumu'' Irohanihoheto
Ayafugumi
Irohanihoheto
Ayafugumi Irohanihohe to Aya Fugumi
Really OK,
please go on.All the
members are
working hard on dance lessons and such.I wonder
what it is.We all went to dance lessons.On the
way home, yes, we
all went to karaoke.  I went there and it looked like it was fun. I wonder
if they sang a song by these three people. I was
watching. It was about three people singing a song by three people. Oh, I see.
But I've had enough of that.  It
seems like Beauty Senpai and Fubuki Senpai's mirrors are a lot better than the other members, and I
guess just by doing this we've become good friends.Originally, the three of us were really good, so we decided to try something together.  It
feels like it's
not the management, but the three of us.
No, um, I wonder
if it was the first time. Well, it was almost
like a flow. Well, the
visuals were done perfectly, so yeah, we're all
good friends.  Right,
you can hear Irohanihohe and Aya Fugumi Yuki
[Music]
Right,
Irohanihohe and Aya Flavor are, you know
, Japanese people in Japan.When
tourists come to Japan, they go
to karaoke and look for Neko's live songs
and Irohanihohe and Gummy songs.
I want you to sing it.
[Music]
There's
so many e-debuts. [Music] It's hard when you tell me who.  I
'd like to team up with Rui-chan as well. We're
good
friends. I've hung out with Rui-chan a few times.
Oh, that's right, Ii-chan and Towa,
Senpai, and
Korone.
This is so interesting.  If we formed a 4-member
country unit, I wonder
what kind of group we would have with Louie-san, Corona-senpai, and Anime-senpai.It
's a new combination, but I
wonder if there's anything you'd like to do
[Music]
English words
can be seen as rice
T
[Music]
[Laughter] It's
boring if it's just a little far away
[Music]
It'll disappear after I fall in love with you It'll
be taken away
Stop it Every day I put out the
knife Oh wait, if I
change the order of the lanterns, I can say I'm going home That's how you
say it in German  That's
cold,
cold. If we
were to name that as a unit, we'd have to
give it a cool image and be
cool and sing well. That's
cool. I don't have any delusional stories or anything like that anymore,
so I do
n't really need a medicine to help me get sick, but thank you.
Thank you very much.
Maybe. I don't know.  You know, I
usually
play music,
Irohanihohe and Ayafumi.There's a
very Central Japanese
feel to it, and the
music they use,
such as the instruments, is
really
something.I wonder what it's like, especially for foreigners.It's so
cool.  Yeah, I guess
people from other countries like Japanese instruments and sounds. They
don't really come up in foreign songs, so it's just because they
don't feature things like the shamisen that it
feels so refreshing to hear them.  It's
fresh and I like it.
Yeah, I'm happy
. I've sung it many times
at karaoke. Yeah, I'm
happy. I've actually sung it at karaoke. I
might just have to go once.
[Music]
Some other 3D  There are live shows, but you
may have never thought of it as karaoke.
Karaoke,
yeah, it's a little lonely when you're alone, and
yeah, the three of you have to get together.
[Music]
Senpai is myself as a Hololive member.
What do you think is your greatest accomplishment? Did
it have any influence on Ayame-senpai's current high school students? I wonder if it's a
mineral or something.
But I tried to sing that song, which has been
viewed over 20 million times.
20 million
won. How do you say 20 million won in English?
[Music] I see, that's a good-bye
declaration, right?
[Music] Congratulations. I do
n't think it's okay to call it a jewel. It's
always been that way. It's an
accomplishment.  I don't think there are many people who
do it online, or maybe not at all.
Yeah,
no, I don't know. I guess they're doing what they're trying to do. There aren't that many, so I
think it's amazing.
Hmm, I'm happy about that, so that's the
second thing.  Question:
Did phimosis have an effect on high school students?
But I have
n't really told the Japanese people about it,
but
there have been glimpses of it, but I
tried singing it after it had been played 20 million times, but I had to put it
out due to a bit of pressure.  I
feel
like I'm going to go. I'm going to
release one. I'm
nervous. There's a lot of pressure, right? Me too.
It's the same with the original song. I'm
releasing one that I tried singing along with the original song.
Ah, that's right, that Reaching By
declaration.  Cover
[Music]
[Music] I
think it's probably a problem of overthinking things like this, but I can
totally understand the feeling of pressure.But I wonder what the
fans of Ayabe 3 have to say.Their
support is so
strong and
passionate, it's
probably safe.  Even if I do this, people will see it
and
come to see it, so I
feel safe and will do my
best.
3D concerts and things like that
are gems. There
was a place where we could show the results of our hard work.
[Music] -
For us, life itself
is probably an achievement.
Ah, that's right.
[Music]
Next I'm a senior, I've been
playing this live for a long time.  It's like, ``I
was once a member of that group, but I'm no longer with you.'' Have you ever
overcome any hardships from the beginning?  The
guest also talked about this. I wonder
if it was a difficult time.
But originally I
never imagined dancing or anything like that, so oh well, that's right. I
couldn't even dance, and apparently that was difficult as well.
Even now, it's hard to practice singing.  But
a lot of things are
difficult.
[Music]
Dance is a good thing, Ayabe-senpai. I've been joining this show for four years,
so at that time I probably
didn't know yet that Hora Live's direction would be what it is now.  I probably
didn't see it even if I thought about it, so I
still couldn't imagine that they would do so many live shows, do so many activities in 3D, and dance.Oh
yeah, I never
thought that the members would grow this much, and I was like, ``I'm an
idol.''  I
never thought I'd go through
all the
troubles and hardships, but I
feel like every day I'm
working hard to grow
[Music]
Direction
The sex was like this, but it's all live
But Ayame-senpai
feels like she can do just about anything. When I look at her, she's
dancing cutely, singing cutely, and she's
definitely an idol.
[Music]
What did you overcome was dancing?  I did something else. Ah,
but can I say I got over
it? I guess I got over it a little bit. I see,
OK, yeah, the
end is
near.
And what is your favorite activity? What's your
favorite thing?
Yeah
[Music]
Everyone is considerate.  I
guess I like it when everyone is so considerate and treats me in all kinds of ways.Everyone is so
kind and other than that, what's my favorite
activity in Hololive?  What do you
mean, is it fun to do this? Is it an
activity that I like?
Well, I
guess it's singing. I love it, so when we sing together or form a unit like this, I really like it.
Everybody's
[Music]
Fifth Moth
This is a standard question, but
for Senpai,
what does Hololive mean
? It's life, right? I guess so am
I.
Thank you so deeply, so deeply.
Senpai, I guess I
wasn't able to answer all your questions.
[Applause]
[Music]
For the revival.  Thank you for being with
me. Thank you for watching.
ThankyouforJOY
on.
[Music] I
hope we can do the next All Talk soon without having to take that 7-month break.  I'll do my best.
From now on, I
want people to see our new studio in a variety of ways. Please come again.
It's in the explanation, so
please jump over to it.
Please. I don't
think there's anyone who hasn't registered yet.
Ok.
thankyouametime
[Music] Thank you for
being with me today.
Thank you everyone.
Finally, is
there anything you would like to say?
From now on, please be naughty. [
Music]
Please take care of this beautiful castle.
Thank you for your support.
[Music]
This is Chara.  This is my last greeting. I
wonder if I can say it in German.
[Music]
[Laughter]