[Music] Hello
everyone, it's Komi and Aa. We
might be the strongest team. Maybe we were. Eh,
Suba has been Suba for a long time, so go ahead and do your best. We're doing a
manual
pose.
Yes, we're counting. It's bad, it's
bad, it's bad, it's bad!  Congratulations to
Aqua for being the Kirikiri master who has surpassed my height
[Music]
Yeah
Ruata wa Pinkpin
[Music]  The
one I should believe in was Nebuchikiri After all, the
one I should believe in is Toa-sama, you're a real angel. Hello
everyone, Aqua. My name is Mito Aqua.
Aqua is Aqua.
[Music] It's
Aqua Aqua. I'll make a club just for you.
Yo
Aku.  It's Pachampang.
Don't get too excited, don't get too excited. In the end, I'll
leave it to Luna.
Worst check check
[Music]
[Applause]
In the check test, I got a cute potato.
How many potatoes can I use?
No, I don't like meat. I don't like meat. What
's that? That's funny, seriously. Wait,
wait, wait, how many potatoes?  It's so salty and salty. It
looks like I'm doing something wrong with this and this pepper.
I made a boyfriend and came here. I thought I was making a real boyfriend,
so I put it in.
Maundouun Meat is delicious, soft and delicious I
guess I forgot this It's meat and potatoes
Atan curry rice This is meat and potatoes I
would like to give you a score for the test
Minus 100
points I don't have it or not It's a
fast start
Please do your best 43
43 Well, I'm
going to talk about it here as well.The reason why we were thought to be a three-person set was because the
team was starting the deciding match.
Isn't it because they participated in the competition?
Ah, that's definitely what the three of us
have in common. I
feel like if we play, we'll be the
best. Oh, that's probably because we're so competitive. That's
right, that's right, that
's right.  What do the three of us have in common?
After all, we don't like to overdo things. We
do what we do. [Music] Hey everyone, I'm back. I'm sorry. No. No. I'm sorry. Is there anything you would like to tell your past self
?
Yes, thank you for trying to get along with the two of us. It's
sudden. Sei-chan likes me.
S
UK
Ai
[Music]
[Applause] I
like you DET