[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
failed eggs
[Music]
hey hey
foreign
how are you guys
yeah that wasn't the crack it was my
bottle it was a bottle
bottle
today's discord's birthday apparently
eight year birthday hmm
laughs
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah wait wait
wait
there
let me put that on my list
[Music]
um
okay
I have a tangent list a small one but I
have it this good birthday life I wonder
who Discord invites to their birthday
concert their 3D birthday concert
[Music]
hello oh this is I I don't think you've
seen this armor before I got it
somewhere
I don't remember where but I got it it
lights you up a little bit but it's uh
Skype but it's honestly like
kind of useless and it's just a top for
now I wonder if there's more yeah it's
like the light it's a light emitting
armor but it really doesn't emit much
light I went with it to the dark
place
where is
I went to the dark place and
it didn't feel very helpful I still had
to use the the light plants
disco armor
yo you guys should check out what I did
so basically I did some more shrines and
if you notice I added some extra one
more bar of stamina
and if I do one more Shrine I can go to
the goddess statue again because I did I
think I did like six or seven shrines
on my own
and I went exploring so don't worry I
didn't continue the Lord the plot the
main plot but
um
I played for like
it felt forever I felt so bad I couldn't
stop
once I started playing I couldn't stop
myself it was really bad but I I set up
my switch in my bedroom and at my big TV
normally I don't do that because I'm too
lazy to move everything around from my
streaming station
to my
TV that's why and also one reason why I
never play offstream
but I did that yesterday and
I
I did a lot I went to get the
um Tower down where is it uh this one
the uh is that that one yeah yeah this
one I just fly this is only even like I
don't think really supposed to be here
yet but I suddenly felt like
you know it's it was fairly close like
to the border so I felt like it was
reachable I got a treasure chest
somewhere and uh for no I got no I got a
treasure map for the underground
underground I also activated one more
Tower uh this one I think
oh what's this ah my last location
um and uh two treasure uh two Treasures
oh one is already the x is gone but it
was like here I think
uh and then this one but this one's so
far away that obviously oh and this one
I'm not attempting to get those
they are too far
underground is scary yeah I also spent
some time in the sky let me try to
remember what I did
um
[Music]
what did I
this this stuff I did
um oh yeah the the mountain area
Sky I checked out pretty much I think I
checked out oh
I I think I checked out dessert did I
well I definitely checked out this area
that's for sure and then I flew over
here or or did I
yeah I did
or did I
one of those flower Islands because
apparently there's more but I checked it
out and I saw yo this is probably
related to the story later
um then I think
here or here and I'm probably here that
was uh or that oh no maybe in the lower
level there was another construct
uh big boss monster but
I tried fighting it and that one is
level two I couldn't kill that one that
one was difficult
strong a one one shot me every [\h__\h]
time like the first phase is okay and
then in the second phase it like is up
in the sky and you have to fly up
it was difficult
um yeah but I did some exploring on the
islands I
I've uh
where was this
I went to an island
no that is also maybe here I don't even
know I went to an island where there's a
shrine but it's missing the stone and
you have to bring the Stone from one
Island to another possibly with a
torpedo because that's why the Torpedoes
are placed there probably but that was
too difficult
um so I failed at that I was like I'll
do this another time
what is it
no I don't [\h__\h] know that since I
didn't activate it yet it's probably not
on the map yet the same thing I found
um was it here
[Music]
yeah yeah probably was probably the
shrine that had the same thing you had
to find uh you had to bring the stone to
the uh Shrine but this one was a bit
easier because the stone was in a cave
and you had to bring it up that was a
bit easier than sending it over a
freaking flying Island yeah I'm using
markers so that I kind of know this one
I placed because I know now that I
didn't attempt it but there is one of
those Horsemen
one of the Apocalypse Horsemen is there
um I I let me tell you I checked out
because I was I is looking first of all
I wanted to make money I was looking for
ore because I'm breath of the Wild on
the mountains there was always a lot of
ore I've come to the realization that
there is no [\h__\h] ore on the mountains
anymore after uh looking for almost all
of the mountains I checked out
like all of this
I checked out all of this
checked out all of this also all of this
but I didn't go to the top I thought it
might be too cold for me
yeah they're all in caves now well
somebody could have [\h__\h] told me
before I climbed every [\h__\h] Mountain
here
I think I mean the game should have told
me like what the [\h__\h] I did some shrines
on the way I found some Crocs I went uh
into a cave I think it was this one
where also there was a side quest I
finished the side quest
uh
I went to this cave I
what did I do
went like everywhere man
why did I
ah
this is
I think me marking a uh one of those
Stone Big Stone thingies but this one I
think
I think I fought this one yeah
and I had so much
more of it
because I when I when I found him
um first I thought it was just a normal
monster Camp yeah
yeah battle Talus I thought it was a
normal monster Camp so I was actually
like up here
on on top of a hill so I started
shooting the monsters from here and they
were all dead but one so I jumped down
and I killed the last one and then then
the talus
jumps up from the ground and I that was
the first time I saw that happen so I
was caught by surprise
um but I was like okay well
maybe I'll try finding it I remember a
little bit from Dom tendo fighting them
in breath of the wild how you supposed
to fight them but this one's a bit
different because you can't just climb
up I've realized because the the camp
is built on top of him so it's blocking
you from climbing up
and I tried several times from every
angle but you cannot climb up and then
uh God I I tried a lot of things I still
had some
bumps but not many I had like six bombs
or so
essent
I tried that for a moment it didn't look
like it would work what
really
really burn the grass use the wind to
fly up yeah you know mostly what I ended
up doing is just like I I was running
around for so long because I ran out of
bombs
um
I I I just I just learned his fighting
pattern completely I am not lying it
took me 40 minutes with my strategy to
fight him
um
but or maybe even 50. I was always
questioning what am I doing with my
[\h__\h] life
um because I would always wait for him
to throw both of his arms at me
I would Dodge them at some point
perfectly always
then I because I noticed when he does
that right after he picks up his arms
from the ground
leading him to
lower his platforms
basically really to the ground but only
for one second so I always waited for
that moment to climb up in that one
second but even that uh eight out of 10
times it would fail
because I would have to anticipate
exactly on which centimeter of the
ground the platform is gonna land on
like where he would where he would lean
himself on
um which is really difficult to
anticipate
um
okay it was more like 18 out of 20 times
but like two times I made it and I made
the most out of it I would jump on
immediately and and do my best to get
all those hits in as much as I could
it was so so frustrating
um and after I did that I was like [\h__\h]
this [\h__\h] I need more bombs but I could
not find any bombs eventually I also ran
out of arrows elsewhere like man I need
bombs and arrows
uh
yeah and then after spending like three
hours in the mountains exploring looking
for Meaningful things and clocks
someone here found one here I did some
stuff here
uh because I found one here
I want to find the korok guy too because
I have now a decent amount of rocks here
that I could get an extension of my bag
actually like most of this was pretty
empty uh the hot spring was cool but
most of this area was like pretty empty
some I was kind of like disappointed
um
yeah I I bought like one set of arrows
but it was so expensive but I really
needed it because I was suddenly from
100 down to zero when you're like 100
you're like oh like I have plenty arrows
I don't need to be stingy with them one
turns out you do have to be stingy with
them because then quickly you run out of
arrows when you when you rely too much
on them then so I went on the ground and
I explored a little bit underground and
I was shocked
um
to find
uh nothing just kidding no I I was a
little bit overwhelmed by some enemies
no the ones that come on a horse
they ride so fast man and they throw
[\h__\h] at you the day they they were like
damn
and what else happened and on the ground
not much I was just like Gathering
materials trying to explore and get this
one treasure
well
underground version because I also found
a talus in underground version
I did not attempt to fight it it was
terrifying
or maybe almost every enemy almost
almost
yeah
um
yeah and then I went around a little bit
here I tried to do this one
this one side quest
uh or actually I tried to do two or so
where was it maybe it was here I know
that's no I don't know
um where was it by a forest and the in
the lake or a uh God damn it I don't
even know but the problem it was there
was this thing this quest with with the
bias stable
uh
uh maybe this one
Riverside stable maybe it was here
[Music]
oh maybe
um basically it was a quest with like
some sick uh Travelers that were on
their way to the stable and the people
at the stable tell you to look for them
so I went there and I found them in the
woods like being sick from some food
that they ate from Princess Zelda
cooking recipe but they're like here's
the recipe we are dying
um and so I knew what I wear and but
then I didn't know what to do and maybe
I need to cook the thing and then feed
it to them and then they feel better but
I would need Hylian rice and I just
couldn't this was also one of the
reasons why I went down here I was
looking for Hylian rice everywhere and
then I realized okay it's not here and
then I've read it's like in a specific
place but I don't know where that is so
I gave up eventually but I also found
out about the fairies there's some
fairies in this area everybody talks
about the great fairies in this area so
there must be a lot but I I didn't go
yet I didn't go yet
um and some people told me about these
like special outfits there's one here
and there's one here
yeah Special outfits that have like I
think Thunder resistance and another
resistance
yeah
where
you mean the Lookout Landing
what do you mean like like I don't know
we'll eventually find it I guess but for
now I guess I just don't have rice I
just wanted to make more variety of
foods
um
you're going to the top right outfit
cave you should see the cherry tree
ah you mean this one
there's a cherry tree there what was it
what was the thing about the cherry tree
again
[Music]
you are literally ruining the
entertainment of gaming nice job what
what
was your problem
what I'm just um updating you guys on
what I was doing what
the [\h__\h] is your problem
huh
points out caves with bubble gems
what the
the sakura tree
the the cherry blossom tree what
what
but there is not always a cherry blossom
tree and a cave that would be like a
Azalea
Azalea thing oh like in Minecraft
maybe maybe he meant someone in the chat
is ruining the entertainment of gaming
or what
hmm
[Music]
let's give them the benefit of the doubt
oh well uh yeah anyway I just wanted to
tell you I did so much I just couldn't
stop playing what was what did I what is
this
well I stamped that
ah I think I know why I stamped it well
here is the tower I know that I stamped
it to go there easily at some point I
saw it when I was flying and I think
this is a mural Maybe
I think I stamped it because the one of
the murals was here and I saw it from a
distance I think
yeah there's probably a lot of things
that I I don't know I can't even tell
you that I did them because it's like
Ugh
too much
um
yeah the hot springs were nice uh there
was also of course cave cave here
somewhere oh yeah I guess this one yeah
yeah yeah
oh yeah yeah
so I don't know if there's something
worth to go up for the top of this
mountain
but it was kind of too too high up I I
gave up eventually it was too high and I
think maybe too cold maybe
yeah sense of achievement yeah I did so
many things man
who don't even know but I just want rice
I just want more cooking stuff
ah wait why do you see it uh
[Music]
I guess on the loading screen later the
the amount of Crocs and shrines and all
that
wait actually
I took some some screenshots I guess
I'll show you
I I made notes this wasn't a shrine fav
uh in a in a in a stable farther away
wait doesn't Chase
I thought if I take a picture of this
it'll be useful in the future to charity
so what do the cherry trees mean
but I thought the location will be
useful in the future
fountains in the middle of nowhere
um this one's funny this was the stone
that you have to bring to the shrine and
the stone is in a cave with these two
monsters but these ones are really
difficult because they they uh ice you
they freeze you and oh look look I have
on my weapon I have the Talon heart the
big ass town or uh but yeah the they
were so difficult and I didn't have uh
like a lot of my tools anymore like I
had no bombs and stuff so uh because
they kept on freezing me when I got
closer to them what I did I played
around with like confusing the the warm
and memories yeah
uh and then he started he tried to fight
the other one but they were a little bit
too far from each other so he couldn't
reach so well
um
yeah I know I know you can take pictures
thinking but this is easier and faster
you just have to press one screenshot
button
um eventually I figured out a way a
technique a strategy to do it without
getting Frozen it was a bit difficult
but you figure it out eventually
um
oh yeah this [\h__\h] this was so
difficult
yeah I tried for a moment I tried the
ascending thing but it didn't didn't
work it didn't show me also I was
stressed out maybe I'll try again now
that you guys tell me that that's how
you do it are you sure guys
are you sure
I was struggling so much yeah because I
ran out of bumper otherwise I would have
just done the whole thing with bomb
arrows but I ran out of them
really
damn I tried everything uh this was that
this was a pretty place I just wanted to
show you this pretty place it was a
pretty cave
when you when you go deeper and deeper
you have to crouch under
um like a little little path under some
Stones you you spare you can miss it if
you don't pay attention you can miss it
and then you come out in this glowy cave
it's a cave in the cave it's so pretty
right it looked prettier in real life ah
here I wanted to show you my genius
um construction
falling over it pissed me off I I used
almost every piece of wood available
okay
he is indeed standing though
the one by the hot spring yeah yeah I
think that's it oh that was Fire Emblem
yay
yay that's nice I'm showing you my
picture album 40 minutes already oh
[Music]
what I want to do is first of all I want
to ask is is the the big Coral command
is he is he reachable for me like where
is he again
can I go to him
[Music]
he should be right here
really in this Camp
[Music]
I didn't even look like I just went here
at the end of my 10 hours okay maybe not
10 hours but when I was playing alone
I just came here and I was like okay
ending it
I didn't even look around
okay let's see how much we can do
because I I think I got plenty unless
now he immediately like asks for five
and then ten and then 15. that would be
a problem I got 24.
well well I tried my best I looked
everywhere but there weren't that many
on the mountains
so yeah I won
uh wait how much are you asking for now
I'll take a bow stash
two okay
Nico
[Music]
um
I'll do as many as I can
ah
um no weapon stash
two
such a big broccoli man
so cute they're so cute
I love when he's singing along
oh
yeah
one oh I guess I didn't expand my shoes
yeah I only have like you only have like
three or four uh spots
so little
[Music]
is it dance different for each stash
and the melody
my imagining
[Music]
all right let's pay attention is it
different
see for the shield it was red blue now
it's red
the
dance stop is it I don't know
[Music]
only the color okay okay
cute
[Music]
thank you
my Kiana hopefully everything end good
already give warn after all don't attack
me again bad for your life hopefully
learn the less
are you threatening me
what's going on is that the same person
no you're right definitely that's not
the same person right
[Music]
what's happening in chat today
oh you guys uh
uh we're being entertained
[Music]
we are being entertained
oh my God
[Music]
does anyone enjoyed us as much as I do
oh my God
I don't even use Shields that much they
barely break for me
because I never used them
maybe never never
bow one
foreign
Shield surfing so far hasn't broken the
single shield for me I guess I gotta do
more Shield surfing
yeah I only have one I don't think I can
afford anything that's true but I'll be
back you're staying here right I must
dance oh I I feel you me too me too
okay
we got that out of the way
I can fill this up even more I'm happy
wait in that case
let me take some of these
sickening weapons are they gonna fill it
up again or is that never coming back
I would like to come here every couple
days and pick up a weapon please I am
your hero after all and I'm doing this
for you guys so you better provide me
with weapons
come back oh really
[Music]
did I get my my yeah I got my second
horse uh on stream right wait I never
went into this world did I did I did I
did I did I
if I did
you know what oh
no I didn't
oh oh it's you I'm fascinated by the
many old Wells across High world but new
wells are pretty interesting too like
this one have you come to tell me about
the location of more ones you found oh
yeah sure what do I get again for
telling her
one of them and we found one
only from the one really
dwells some funds
what about this one huh I just found
this one
oh man
do I have a weapon and I can break this
with
um
I mean
I think this could work but um
how many bombs do I have
why is it none oh I collected so many
food items like so many tomatoes in the
forest
there's so many items in general but no
bombs bombs
I must have some
for oh
what
just happened
[Laughter]
I was unexpected
oh well
I thought I was putting it on an arrow I
guess I accidentally threw it and like
right in my face
Royal Claymore he has a powerful flurry
Rush
we're gonna do gotta try to do some more
flurry rashes
um is that a stone no
it is a stone but it's not a stone that
I can put on my weapon
okay
link has to carry even more things than
ever before in this game
foreign
what are we gonna do I guess we're gonna
continue with the main story now because
I did so much of nothingness
in my private time
so
tooling of riddle okay so I found uh
this to be close I guess
because this is where we're gonna go
right
what's gonna happen
30 minute recap means I did a lot I
guess so hope we got some more German
Zelda yes more German like I've read I
found this video today recommended to me
uh like Zelda another canon in German
being
Superior to English Canon that was like
kind of the video
and there was like a lot of comments
saying yeah I also like to have my game
in German for once because
the voice acting is actually really so
good
so it seems to be a popular opinion
uh oh yeah wait it was this is just you
don't have to come here but
um
I should change my clothes again
oh should I
oh wait no he's fine but
but the jacket makes no sense let's at
least go for climbing gear
seems fine temperature wise
short sleeves let's go uh what was it up
here
huh
Boomer is playing in French why
I do find it actually quite
endearing now the idea of changing dubs
oh FPS
changing dubs every other time
still you know what's up
really
ah so I think here that's why we have to
go
all right let's talk to her she'll tell
me more unbelievable that these huge
things are raining down on us what is
happening up there in the sky
oh sorry I hadn't expected to meet a
highly in here what are you doing in the
mountains in this weather don't you see
how cold it's gotten blue blah blue
oh if you go further up this slope
you'll see the Hebrew self-summit cave
my friends are there now Gathering
Provisions they are glowing mushrooms
and fish that we had yeah I already got
all of that I think
no no
tell me about that I want you to tell me
about something else is it where which
way which way is it
huh
uh
um yeah here
oh
she did go to the Hebrew self Summit
cave for real
before I went there already
okay
I think on the way to the Toronto Peak
cave is the Hebrew South Summit cave
gosh
so rough going up snow
fish
all right
snow looks familiar why
uh oh the monsters are back
I already fought all of these before
don't bother me
I said don't bother me
I'm busy
I was close
so possibly here
oh
[Music]
yeah here I haven't gone to before this
Cavalry Channel
today on Discovery Channel give yourself
Summit cave
didn't think I'd be seeing anyone else
in these mountains anytime soon well
what would the blizzard and all I'm here
because I'm
I'm here because it's a good place to
find food for my people why are you here
oh
looking for children huh fair enough
he's farther in this Cave of juzan
they're Scavenging for food
no I'm not going to show you the way I
need to keep an eye on what it was a
mess so far you could at least point me
in the direction though
probably won't bother you if you stay
away from it good luck finding tune
we don't want to waste my fire fruit
because I also ran out of those oh
[\h__\h] hell
and I also don't want to waste my arrows
thank you
what can I miss two times [\h__\h] at least
I can pick those up again
[Music]
come on
oh there we go
it
that's what I thought
uh-huh
precious arrows you know you saw how
little I have
is it even necessary there
[Music]
heat resistance okay
that's nice that's all there is here
okay
maybe I will fuse
a weapon
[Music]
I need a box stick
well yeah
oh yeah oh yeah
oh is that a horrible in up there
yeah
I know
[Music]
what I don't want to go so deep [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] out
oh well
we'll be able to get up somehow surely
back again
civilization
don't hit the rock salt why anyway
even even when I find some or finally
it's still always most of the time only
the fire stones or salt
man
but that's gotcha
we need to find one that Sparkles golden
Niche oh really
well it will need to find me
don't hurt yourself don't hurt yourself
where am I where am I where am I here is
this where it came from
[\h__\h]
I'm so bad at this
oh is this where I need to go or where I
came from that's where I came from oh
well I didn't do it this time I figured
I had so many lizards by now I don't
need to get any more but
no wait is that where I
yay okay
I did that
successfully
yeah
looks very good very good
wait I need to use more
I need to use more of these like
attachments
because like the amount of items
is as I expected
uh just too much
I need to use this
even for my arrows
to make them stronger
you're gonna come here oh
wow
yeah these these horror plans aren't
even
oh they aren't even that strong
providing the eye nice crit you know
aim is not local aim is here
I've got the AIM
[Music]
oh
this is a story related cave but it is
still a cave so I wonder
there should be
it should be a frog here too no
let's go
yeah one of those glowing froggies
since every cave has a frog
but they don't have my frog
I don't have a froggy Wawa
okay I guess we gotta make a start a
fire today
and let's make it
uh the way you're supposed to make it I
think would have I never made it the way
you're supposed to make it I need a
one of those stones
uh
Firestone flint and wood
right or I mean there's wood already
there
do I even need wood
how do you do it
wait maybe if I drop it right on there
no
smack it eh
you whack it
how do you whack it
how do I
I have to Wagon after dropping it okay
okay
whoa
and then we add pine cones because this
is not enough right to fly and I got a
million pine cones
I'm happy to do that
[Laughter]
did I get the fish
I I kind of knew that was gonna happen
with all these forms eventually it was
bound to happen Maritza
oh wait what pine cone pine cones
what are you doing what am I doing
wait I wanted
there's a treasure chest there
I want the treasure chest
well then wait where is it
what about this path
well
Ultra hand well the thing is I don't
even see it now
far
what the [\h__\h]
and for Amber these things are so cute
but you always need like a stone Hammer
ideally
to fight them
um
oh I used to have way more food than
this
um but I guess I used it up a lot on
certain things like the talus
you can eat them too really
cute
cramp I mean I'm personally not a fan of
it but
I chose the right path it seems
um what are we going to do with that boy
it's just like him to fly off on his own
and leave all the food we collected
behind
oh
well I'll be what is Riley and doing all
the way up here in such a fierce
blizzard
I am
streaming this game
on YouTube yeah you're on YouTube now
you're on not on TV but you're on the PC
and so on probably
[Music]
I mean who knows maybe on you're on
someone's TV
someone's maybe watching this on their
TV
yeah
no not twitch YouTube YouTube yeah yeah
you can stream on YouTube yeah you
didn't know you thought you can only
stream on Twitch no you can stream on
YouTube too yeah yeah
they also have something called YouTube
shorts nowadays you know things have
changed
yeah
a lot of people watch on phone too yeah
[Music]
our task was to scavenge food in this
area but we just saw flock of monsters
fly past outside the cave the same ones
that have been cited around the village
lately in fact I told the others we
should return right away to report them
but tooling clearly wasn't listening at
all he said I'm gonna follow him back to
their nest and flew off alone before I
could protest
if you leave the cave and head north you
can spot a lone cheddar tree cheddar
said
cheddar cheese grows on trees
that's where we saw the monsters no
doubt tooling about the mirror
Cedar see ther
I know he thinks he's unbeatable but he
really shouldn't be taking his chance
okay if we already had to leave then let
me go back
hopefully it's worth it
probably won't be worth it but
oh no another another suicide lizard
oh man
where where
let's check out this one too
oh
oh that's what a Frugal is
God damn it this
uh so much what the [\h__\h] ah no he's hurt
no
this is so see this this is this too
much
when you like to go Scavenging for food
like me
and all kinds of materials like pick up
everything you find
this is just too much stuff
bubble
oh
every time
I one shot at him normally he falls down
and you get have to give him another hit
sheesh
yeah the frog is really mysterious I
want to like hear more about the Frog
I must be isn't it up there
look good let me try to climb
yeah it's there
oh why is that jump take like my whole
bar of stamina
I won't fly up again we're doing it like
this now
is that
that's not it
well at least I have a good view from
here
where's his chest
what
this is also not white
okay
um
I am down here again so
yeah yeah
does it like burn longer the more I put
in there
I wonder
where's the stupid chest
is it wait was there no chest
huh
was there another chest
guys
am I did I think the stone was a chest
you didn't see your chest
oh no oh no
call isil
I mean would I see I don't know I don't
I guess science I guess I hallucinated
I gotta watch the VOD because I really
feel like I saw something that was
silver but also more shiny than
then the stone
oh well oh more
at least here they can't escape
like why are you so annoying
I feel like it would have been nice to
play suggest there but okay
what did he say what the mountain no and
he also said nor for a song
wait what
okay there's some enemies there
oh there's another
another sign guy but oh there's no
materials
nearby
do I have to use the the Snowballs
can also use
he's got it on
um
a wood plate so if we put a lot of
weight on there ah
just need the stone actually in this
case
yeah
normally he doesn't have that wooden
platform though
try and let go and then go home
nobody cares about your sign in this
area there are no humans who or any
anyone really who chills around here
yeah he's standing
easily
you know I've been watching them to
handle he's still really far behind but
he's met like five of these or so and he
doesn't understand that
he has to do this and save the signs he
tried once with the time reversal and
all that and it didn't work so then he
gave up even though there's always
materials right there it doesn't click
with him and he has to build the a
support system so now he's like why are
they everywhere well I guess I just have
to talk to them and then eventually I'll
get something no he doesn't get it
no there is no chat function it's only
vods
only videos
I wonder when he'll know that he's gonna
go back to all of them
and fix them
perfect need you to back seat I think a
lot of his videos are like pre-recorded
days in advance
so
the comments feedback he won't notice
until a while later red ruby
[Music]
see you guys I don't need this
awesome I like perfumes because they're
very useful like I tried some of those
yesterday
try to use them
I'll take them the mushroom onigiri
please do
please
you have my full support
see like what the [\h__\h] uh no what what
the [\h__\h] did I just
no
not the herb
s
first of all I got those I didn't know
how to use them
but I learned
I learned how to use these very useful
because
especially not necessarily necessary
here but
in like you know there's this ah in that
Tower
it was it was pretty useful in the
the Skyview Tower of of this area
because I don't know if you guys got the
Skyview Tower but it's like the Skyview
Tower is at a huge enemy camp
well I mean huge is really huge
they have this like big boss
and uh
yeah
I I got a bit overwhelmed oh swallow
unless we drawn faster than normal cool
cool cool
long stick Soldier spare
arrows thank you I really need those
ah
let me roast some things really quickly
just because I all the things I cook
they have some effects and I I don't
know I don't need them now so
um
[Music]
oh
can't roasted tomatoes
I didn't know that
now I know the more you know oh no maybe
you can I just
couldn't drop anymore
[Music]
no don't go away
baked Golden Apple
baked palm fruit I just want some small
food things
not everything has to heal 10 hearts
my show
oh that was
way too
and
way too far
sorry my scream of despair
when wasting stuff like that
why
[Music]
roasted highly and tomato I only roasted
one thing
come on
how do you
how do you successfully
roast everything without it falling off
again only one item
set them on fire
yeah drop it in the fire I did that but
they were still full they still went
different directions
see
still only one of them
this is the Tomato oh
[Music]
do not add a pine cone
yeah that's probably good advice because
that would be too much yeah the slope is
a problem
okay anyway what did they say
is it over here maybe
huh
it doesn't seem like
where toolin would go but tooling can
fly so who knows
what was what was that about one tree
this loan Center when they say loan I
thought it was standing alone did they
mean like a naked cedar tree
half of the mountain
oh that one maybe
that one
[Music]
oh
they're like patrolling the area
um
[Music]
hi
what should I use
I got so many weapons
[Music]
oh be careful You're Gonna Roll Up the
mountains
your little [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay okay okay
no problem no problems
what hotel would be delighted
butt crack
oh what's going on your leader is dead
what you gonna do what you gonna do
[Music]
oh he's running away the other one
but see that's really useful right the
the pops room
I think that will be one of my go-to
options
in the panic situation with many enemies
my combat better than yours really nah
nah
desperate situation is called for
Desperate Measures
no
oh yeah
I know
icicle Club
what are you doing today story
hopefully we'll get so far in the story
that we already move out of the snowy
mountain area
I wonder should be uh uh wait
[\h__\h] A Little Too Late
are you hesitated you can't get too
close to these [\h__\h]
get up get up get up
[Music]
at least he so kindly waits for me you
know what [\h__\h] you
interesting structures
oh
that is an obvious invitation for us
[Music]
but if we take this path do we not miss
anything
[Music]
oh yeah I know I can set them on fire
but I don't want to waste too many of
those materials because I'm just
running out of them constantly
I am at the tree
yeah
on the tree
yeah there you are what the hell you
Blended in
with the scenery
what are you looking at hmm
stupid monster
wow then where did you come from oh oh
you see that rotten monster took my good
bow
oh
see wait I have one of those I can give
you mine
and this one we can easily shoot with a
with a one of those eyeball arrows
see that's in my little [\h__\h]
thank you did you know I can blow a
strong gust of wind anywhere I feel like
I'll do it for you too that way you can
glide over there where the monster went
thank you just tell me where to point to
guys and I'll make it for you
[Music]
will he stay here
okay I might not even need that though
do you even need it if you use an
eyeball
is charged he can create a stream of
wind that blows straight forward this
can be used for bursts of speed while
paragliding
okay
oh
oh you you follow me oh God
uh [\h__\h] isn't this like still yummy what
what if I fall down
um
the OCTA work I was working till today
nah those those don't work
see easy easy mode are they good really
I thought they they make a balloon on
the victim
Wow first try
if I didn't put the eyeball on I'm sure
it's much more difficult though because
I didn't get that close with that wind
there we go I owe you a big time link
without you my phone might have been
lost but good
oh
don't worry about it
'll be fine though they're just dropping
their kids off at the kindergarten
those
horns those those are really good for
putting them on weapons too
and skull game together
you said
[Music]
really
are you even gonna lift the finger oh
Falcon ball oh I'm too strong
[Applause]
[Music]
sorry for the roast
we did it did it I did it but yeah sure
we did it let's do it for your
confidence
hey look I think this might have been a
hideout for those monsters
oh
oil
well this is all the mushrooms and make
me hallucinate was that one it could it
couldn't have been there's no way it
must have been something else
sorry the wind was my sneeze oh boy
foreign
people
real birds oh
[Music]
they found the music is nice
oh that was some impressive teamwork you
two
you saw that
very thing I didn't listen tried to stop
me I thought I could handle it but I
just ended up losing my favorite both of
those stupid things I thought I was
fully fledged but there's probably no
way I could have gotten it back on my
own thank you guys
oh membership thank you
I bet now you see why we are treating
you like a small chick
you were right it really is important to
work as a flock just like kfp does
I think I finally get what dad has been
trying to tell me all this time
is that all there is to the story it's
it's it seems unlike you to let you go
be taken to him
oh yeah funny story about that there was
this whole thing of with the Princess
Zelda oh he saw her too
I spotted her getting attacked by a
monster it was such a surprise that I
dropped my guard and just stole my belt
but I guess she was fine because then
she zoomed up above that cloud
Prince Zelda flew above the cloud how
can that be
seems like a stretch but we're not going
to go to the bottom of it sitting around
here oh Dylan link came out here looking
for Princess Zelda you should go with
him and investigate the cloud you say
the princess sword into the clouds
ah but I thought I wasn't allowed
I got a report before coming here we
think it's likely that the blizzard is
coming from inside the cloud after all
um
I want to see for myself as soon as I
can but the strong winds make any
approach from the sides impossible the
only way in is for the top but
through the top you say
you mean it's open like in like an ice
cone
[Music]
there's not a rate of a life capable of
Crossing this stormy sky and making it
all the way there well except for one
I'm talking about YouTube
only you have the skill in training to
create costs at will tolin will be the
finest Street Warrior of all once he
understands the value of working with
his highlights you know who said that to
me you hold that tebasaki yum yum yum
yum
that said that oh yeah and I'll make
sure he knows what you accomplished here
today now it's time you go with link to
find Princess Zelda and whatever is
causing this blizzard
no problem the two of us together got
this
I saw Princess Zelda up on the sky
islands near Hebrew Peak let's check
there first whoa
oh I already investigated a lot of the
islands but I didn't see any Zelda
well maybe now she's there
looked like you like to win more than
table there's more story to win
um
wait
a second sake
wait the mom was actually called [\h__\h]
no way no way no way no way no way no
way I didn't pay attention wasn't really
so wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
for real
[Music]
wait her name is really sucky
oh my God last time we were like looking
at both of them and I was making the
joke about tebasaki and I still didn't
realize
that the wife was called saki anyway
that is so you know if you don't speak
Japanese you won't realize this
they kept the names
in English too but like in the English
version but it's still Japanese names
and and a joke a joke you wouldn't know
if you didn't know Japanese
foreign
hmm
way over my head well now you know how
are you headed just like me I mean I
knew it already I told you guys the day
before yesterday
[Music]
till it doesn't mean anything right
no I also noticed in Japanese they call
him churi
because there is there isn't really a tu
you can make a tu with a t t o a small
well you that's more like two two but
there's no clear two you can only do
t-o-u or c-h-u
for some reason I don't understand why
why there's a chew and and a suit but
there's no two
there's also a move but there's no two
in Japanese
okay
let me pick up all the things Rusty
Claymore
oh
wait when you're in this state you can
still switch right okay
nice that looks powerful
that's it all right
um horn
[Music]
noise and maybe we get some arrows out
of this yep
most of the time these have arrows
yeah
oh it's always okay the child is
following me now
um
wait what how do we how do we what how
do we do it we just what what
we want to fly up right and you can you
can you
shouldn't we just like fly up to the sky
together
and then
it's a long journey up oh wait from
there
it is kind of connected to the mountain
interestingly is that the it is the
hebra peak well then it's good that I
skipped everything uh only that
okay oh
all right
I see he can he can only do oh
uh like sideways though can you
oh honey has to load up
okay
only horizontally yeah yeah that's why
it was like how are we gonna go up okay
I I see there's still some climbing
involved
foreign
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I don't know about this
toolin
I don't know if you're that useful to me
I should just go on the sky view Tower
fly all the way up
and then let myself fall down
can you do this oh well let's say like
oh Quest failed
yeah he's speaking in German
good
whatever climbing is fun too
oh he's got an explosive no a stone
kind of stone
oh
oh Shish what's going on here
because the island is actually connected
to the mountain the constructs made it
down here oh and at the the vocal Blends
they're actually like
trying to protect themselves from them I
guess because they're too powerful
oh
Ah that's a cool dog where the [\h__\h] do
you want to go
oh dear
I guess
will help the Kodak
which way
oh
yeah
[Music]
can I stick him too
my bird friend no right
no
how
I can't stick into myself either do I
need to use one of my capsules oh come
on
wait wait wait no
that is not good no
yeah ah
wait
rewind him
Bakugans have some stuff that's true
true
oh no
ah
he doesn't oh no
[Music]
oh
made it worse
made it worse oh well
let's take care of these
ah
come on play with me
they all got those ice weapons up here
[Music]
[\h__\h]
oh the construction oh
you're actually helping me
a contractor Loki helping me too but not
really
wow
oh my God I had some fairies
thank you
[Music]
whoa
he's a good help
now at least
not bad next flag trespect
it's nice Shield
[Music]
ah I saw her
all right let me
get rid of this
um
I'll take the flame another Shield
I actually when I was exploring the
mountains I made myself a [\h__\h] ton of
those ice weapons too
man they're all gone by now because
that's the ones I went elsewhere but
they're really useful indeed I don't
know if I want to do this
what
you guys said they have some materials
but can I even take this wood
oh wait they have a balloon here ah
okay okay okay
it's not worth the effort well generally
no but I mean if I find one right here
then
it's fine as well
and I need I need uh should I use one of
my own
okay
take out device
sorry I'm like still always scrambling
with
all the controls
bringing them over there
and then well
the thing is it only goes up it doesn't
go sideways
the girls feel clunky really I think so
I mean I thought I just generally like
always get confused
well hmm
guess we gotta test it out first
who dares to come out of nowhere and
disturb me like this
[Applause]
hate octoluxe oh this one has a fish
with them
[Music]
okay I have I don't know are we um
I wonder if this is gonna work
[Music]
I am ashamed
I don't know how to show myself anymore
in front of you guys
I am just ashamed
to call myself a part-time Warrior
really
it is it is just unthinkable
um I I I I I was I was going to
while uh writing this thing
in the air
animation but maybe I'll try to do it
with just I hope he he doesn't fall off
and he already fell off that's different
okay
maybe wait
and I'll be fine I will be fine
[Music]
it didn't even make it all the way up
there I think I'll have to
I'll have to
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
what a pain in the ass I don't like
these like delivery Crocs man
no
okay stay cool
yo
the waste of my precious time
oh he's stuck on that's not good
[Music]
oh man
okay nobody's gonna fall off this time
I have it under control
they sent him so far
this time otherwise I'm gonna strangle
this clock
I'm gonna strangle him no oh well
this is some episodes okay if it doesn't
work you're gonna use the rewind okay
this episode so far today is not going
so well is it
thank you
how can I how can I pick it up
she doesn't want to be picked out
oh he's chilling now he's chilling now
oh no I'm not moving
oh yeah what am I doing I don't even
know I don't even know anymore
stop rolling
really need to get rid of that big
backpack a lot of your problems would be
solved you wouldn't be rolling around
anymore and you would be able to reach
your friend on your own
just saying
okay
oh I should have asked him for help
I made it anyway
are we going around or are we going this
way we should go this way right
that was that was the worst caught up
delivery ever not only because of me
though oh blood moon
means all of those are coming back too
yo this one's strong huh
but there are much easier to tackle when
you have a sonai weapon
so freaky this is so freaky
Bend this Blood Moon's list
[Music]
don't be like that sometimes
it's a construct back to where he was at
no
um
German good right thanks for the
membership thank you
oh
his skill
would be helping me much more if it was
upward
look at all that [\h__\h] we have to climb
we're kidding Liam
oh God
[Laughter]
making it easy for ourselves
yup
well
no one of the precious Goods that we're
losing
oh [\h__\h]
God damn it
what a waste of good good materials
those eyes can do that yeah all of the
eyes
have a a tracking function
extremely useful
even for things like the bunnies
I think you could use it for them but
you just gotta be really quick
in selecting like
um drawing your arrow and quickly
selecting I tried it but
I'm I'm still too scrambly with the
controls to attempt it
oh
smiling here
what
if only it were possible to find out
what's inside of this blizzard
oh
oh why if it isn't dual and that was too
focused so on the cloud to notice you
but if you've come here that means oh
[Music]
thank you the rotten apple
did you buy it because you were already
a World of Warships player or did you
start or downloaded for me
great motivational voice acting
yeah yeah yeah
I I wanna you know I I had to be
energetic and I know some of it maybe is
a bit cringe but
[Music]
interrogation time I played it back in
the day when it came out for a bit Ah so
now you felt like because you're oh she
is in it you have to revive it
yeah understandable thank you you
sounded native wow
thank you so much
I download for vowel only thank you
Kiara you are my Oshi dot dot say it
more confidently
say it look confidently with an
exclamation mark
scream it yell it
everyone has admired your wind gust
technique since you first demonstrated
it
You're My OC
[Laughter]
you may be the only retail capable of
rising above that cloud oh thanks for
the pinky
to find a truth among the turbulent
Skies give Your Best Shot I'll be here
watching for your turn
thanks between link and me you won't be
disappointed
yeah okay
you ready
blah blah blah blah he's a Flappy Bird
uh oh are these for me to stand on I was
gonna try to destroy them but they don't
look
like you can destroy them
to get some height
I assume away one thing I completely
forgot about
ah wait maybe on top of
maybe on top of them
[Music]
dude where are you
not hi okay
now we can go sideways again
I'll aim for the round thing
perfect German always works
uh where can I beam up
oh I don't think I can do here
it's too high
yeah German always works
uh here
okay here this makes sense like using
him his abilities we can switch between
ascending and flapping and sanding and
flapping
oh
where to now oh over there
okay so we're gonna climb a little bit
from here over there right no wait isn't
that where we yeah the lower one is
where we came from okay
yeah
ah then I can descend through that
long
Tower
for real really
are you
yo let's go it's easier for me than for
the bird at this point flying all the
way up there
straight up
I think it's more comfortable for me
gonna take him a while
where are you
oh I feel like you're cheated
oh you just got teleported
uh oh there's a Temple there
I don't think oh no I can make the tall
one too noise
I was around here that it was around
here that I saw that a lot you were up
here but now I don't know where she
could have gone
huh
we can probably move that too
what is that
hey wait you little [\h__\h] how am I gonna
there's sad music here
oh no the music's so sad
I like it though
look at that is Zelda there again
no support yeah I saw it from the
distance
you little ship oh
are we gonna see her again
oh
yeah
whose voice was that was it coming from
somewhere out there
we go there's more ships there's so many
of those shippies
oh
wow do you see that thing inside the
cloud oh I wasn't oh it's a huge ship
sheesh
is that another boat it's huge
there's tons of those little flying
boats too you know what that reminds me
of
a line of ships soaring built as a
passage skyboard the god ascended to
Heaven leaving behind an orc orc
Act
this whole thing is just like the song
of the Stormwind Arc
oh was that the children's it wasn't
chilling songs
you like that strange voice too right
link I'm sure I heard it say in German
though come to me it's like it was
calling us up there
I don't see anything around here that
would lead us to Princess Zelda maybe
she went over to that ship well now
nowhere to go but up come on
okay
German always works
so true so true
are you okay you can fly too you know if
it's easier for you
we gotta do the shrine first
can we move the ship
just curious no okay
uh wait
I'm not kind of high
ah we can go there and then yeah yeah
what
um excuse me I got jump scared by a job
okay
[Music]
let's go
Jesus
scared let's truly I never got jump
scared before
you don't have to come with me Bonnie
I'll do it alone
[Laughter]
like a jump scared a lot a lot but I
never get jump scared
foreign
[Music]
it's like a warm-up tutorial for what's
ahead of us maybe
you'll think I got jump scared before
should have
[\h__\h] up some
some kind of
construct weapon oh wow
[Music]
uh where'd you go
did he fall down or up
while he's gone now
[Music]
this will be fun
does that lead to a chest maybe I'll go
here first
or maybe that's the intended Direction
wait for me
[Music]
that is fun
and it's something new and probably
oh never gonna see oh
what do you do here never gonna see this
kind of shrine again huh
oh did I just
land normally on that
[\h__\h]
I can't do that here
how
there's there's how do you get in there
I need to open that first
maybe I shouldn't be here yet oh wait
um no
well
I'm not gonna get in
maybe there are they
something else
to do
yeah
[Music]
well I came from there
actually
that is the only way to go
I must have missed some Crystal debunk
somewhere
all right let's try it
maybe gotta do it from here
okay
this is fun trampoline
trampoline boats
oh is that already it there was no
Treasure Chest though
did I miss it
I missed it it was
out in the open area what the [\h__\h]
of course of course I missed it was
there something good in there do you
remember
anyone who did it
is it worth going back in
10 hours oh okay well everyone's will be
nice for me but I'm not gonna go back in
for arrows
not for that
ah
there you could see
now we can get another heart I think
next I'll go for a heart because I I got
a good amount of stamina for now no no
do you think there would be a Colo cup
here
they wouldn't do such a thing
where are we going next
wait
a pond
the pond has yet to be explored
I'm not good for now no I want the heart
oh
[Music]
okay
we did not come from here from there
right
do we need
his help again
thank you
[Music]
ah I can
shh okay
can we get much higher
can we get more tires
we have to oh no
[Music]
so high
I want the things he drops me and
yeah
can you come here
buddy buddy
yeah now he follows okay
okay don't fall down don't fall down
don't fall down don't fall down you can
climb that right yeah
okay
and a big bounce
oh
[Music]
beautiful
how do you do I want to try that thing
where you fall and you hit
I just fall and I hit do I or is there
something special you have to do
any ends we want them to play much
anyway
[Applause]
he's shaking is he cold why why are they
shaking so much
hey come here come here come here let's
play here
no
no I wanna
I want to do that
you think you're cool doing that huh
I want it's drops wait
should I go over here instead
It looks interesting with the icicles
gonna melt them maybe and then you can
teleport up
but we can also go here
that was perfectly timed
cooling is a little bit too eager
why why would I go there if I can go
here
is there a reason there's some stuff up
there
kill Steel
happy
[Music]
birthday congratulations
your third birthday
wait in in uh is it for me tomorrow on
the 17th or is it actually 16.
that way I have to go there in the end
anyway
I have to worry
from here
I won't get anywhere
[Music]
for me it's tomorrow
okay okay uh what the [\h__\h]
do I have to melt that too in order to
get through from the bottom or so
let me just try one
because I don't have so many
now okay nothing happens so it seems
impossible
he's got a chest
maybe this one we can manage to kill
before making them fall down yay
hooray hooray
oh no I didn't want to drop that one
and then I wanna pick up this
[Music]
I'm gonna make myself
a fancy new weapon
I guess I could have done this before on
my own already
um
drop it and then it feels
should work right
wait cute it got red completely of the
like wooden part
it became a proper
Soldier blade
extra durable
I look good
some of the oh I froze some of the
um combinations
look kind of weird
yeah but then some others
look pretty decent oh yeah oh yeah this
one I have to
melt
oh
[Music]
twenty
wow blank what's up also why do I why am
I still frozen I think well we just had
like an update or something because my
app
is like loading
slow I think yeah I think the app just
updated
and now my only my ah there we go so it
always takes a moment after opening it
where only my eyes are moving is it
looks funny
looks like I'm I'm I'm
imprisoned imprisoned in my own body
wrong direction but okay
yeah thanks for so many memberships
thank you
are you ready let's go oh wait should I
go here first
okay and then like over there come on
come on
off to sleep good night thank you for
coming bye
good luck catching up in the future
holy [\h__\h] okay it's time to send him
down time to send him down
thank you
I can't do so much dance for them even
even now with the new weapon the hell
are we going there
we're going there
and I'm guessing
like jump I I there's actually nothing
underneath
how did that water build there
if there's no ground
oh there's the construct
I hope it's level one
if it's level one I can manage if it's
two of them
does somebody know
got to apply for US Visa tomorrow oh
damn
yeah I mean not a normal reason like a
proper one here's level one okay
what should I eat
they have like a defense up or so yeah I
got this one
um
should I check this place out first
there is a ship stuck in there
and there's just Pawns
what
what the [\h__\h]
okay
I hear screams from enemies
oh nice shot nice he was right there and
it's hard for me to see right now
are you shooting horizontally only again
or
[Music]
nice there one shot they're all one
shots yo
just pick up items for me
he can do that
oh he's like a pet
oh I'm so stupid
thank God I have so many fairies I think
we're maybe out of fairies now though
okay
or do I still have let me check
I got
more
bombs are dangerous don't play around
with bumps guys
where is this boss
down here
okay we actually have a helper this time
too
let's see if he'll actually be helpful
more of a problem oh he's got it on his
foot easy
easy yeah
I could just be a distraction because he
will always look at me
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
is he like preparing for something when
he does that or
you gotta shoot a little bit from a
different angle buddy
but he knows where to shoot
[Music]
I could literally do this alone
wait a second I'm a bit scared about my
HP
hmm
[Applause]
actually I could I know I can just drag
his leg out
especially now we should be doing nuts
I'm gonna do it again oh now he's
the shape oh
[Music]
yeah
yeah sorry I'm a bit dorky
I'm okay though I think oh nice nice
shirt oh
all right
it's hard too
oh I got it
[Music]
[Applause]
is actually really useful oh now he's
got it on his shoulder okay now I really
gotta drag it out
[Music]
I love the feeling when you have to pull
it out
it really feels like I'm pulling it out
there
because it doesn't just like go out like
butter
it actually takes some strength
wait it's somewhere inside
[\h__\h]
did you just stomp my treasure cheese
I don't see how do you I guess I gotta
take some other parts out first
[Music]
trivia
what we really want
I see and it's in the middle yeah
what will be left of him
oh okay eventually he'll just
fall apart it seems
[Music]
hey I love these fights
these are some I think maybe my favorite
boss monster type of fight in this game
and I already have one of these weapons
I know they are extremely
um
effective against the these big bosses
but I I used it last time uh I think
like I I killed one of them off stream
and I used one of the Pounders for it
and it is super effective but in the end
I lose a pounder on the monster that
gives me another pounder so it's like an
endless pounder
a cycle
no
so now we have a pound of spare they're
really really really powerful
[Music]
not only on the constructs but yeah
chest somewhere in the underground this
one is also really far away
last time you fused it on the bone web
and Goldberg easily oh
okay maybe we'll break less often on the
others okay
yeah but basically I will always use the
pounder to get another pounder
oh
so that makes me think should I be
really using the pounder on the on the
constructive
constructive construct monster
am I even gaining anything then
come on that sounds like a School uh
break it
[Music]
[\h__\h]
a pound of spiral
and Bell
the court opponent are we talking
Burgers now
oh
have we created an endless Stone
um
oh
now it went elsewhere I think wait
what's going on
you're smarter now where do I go
ah let's go here first
a ball girl
hmm
[Music]
guys when you default a chicken breast
fillet
uh
and you don't you end up not even eating
it on that day
can you still need it on the next day
yeah but it is in the fridge yo
[\h__\h]
come on okay
foreign
[Music]
was that even enough
oh
[Music]
I can just hit him oh well
oh well
I wonder what awaits Us in the big
hurricane probably a boss monster I'm
kind of scared
I hope it's not gonna be too challenging
although if it's challenging it'll be
more entertaining right
is momentum a thing when jumping on
these trampolines will I jump even
higher
I saw I saw
I saw that
um that's the second time I see one of
those is there is there uh shooting
stars in this game
what the wild I see it I see it
ah
star pieces because in the past it used
to be like dragons items wasn't it
oh that was close
uh okay
cool
oh did he just
how did you
I was not not already like falling
straight down
I need to learn how to do those kind of
shots
in the air
so I just attempted it
I think I figured it out
I think I got it down
oh
good it's like a Pier
no idea who created this but you could
cook here maybe I will
maybe I actually went after
fighting this
um
I think I'm gonna cook some things
indeed
okay let's try the OCTA Rock eye
actually
It better work
it did work even though he hid after he
hid behind
oh that was
they're fighting that was too far it
seems
distance to five
okay
yum yum yum yum
[Music]
yum music here is really creepy isn't it
let's do something
[Music]
guys yesterday
you know it was my day off but I was
doing a lot of work but even besides
playing because after playing for so
long you know I felt actually pretty bad
can you make something with this
I felt bad for ah wait
it felt bad for playing for so long so I
was like okay I gotta be productive now
and I had a to-do list
for sure
and I did everything on my to-do list
yesterday day off what's that that's
right I
even on my days off I do a lot of other
things
but I recorded two songs actually
one of them for my EP thingy
does this create maybe like an oyakodon
that'll be nice
no mutes meat skewer
maybe with rice
maybe in
addition with fries
[Music]
yeah the recording was difficult there's
like especially with the oh yummy a new
dish with the
um album song that I recorded
it was again a song that has like a lot
of harmonies a lot of shouts and a lot
of like oh and stuff like that like
sounds the background yeah
do you also had that for do you I also
had to record so so so so so many
different lines
fun though it's fun
when I do that I basically like the main
part I record
uh usually like in one go and when one
part didn't work out so well I like
um redo only that part and then I do
that for the main main lines I do that
twice or three times
and then for the harmonies and because I
have to learn them
on the spot
I just listening to like each single one
even if it's just two seconds long and
then I remember it faster that way then
I record that and I move on to the next
thing listen to it for two seconds
record it for two seconds
Etc
yeah that's basically the process for me
oh yeah speaking of that
uploaded the dance video of do you
yesterday
challenge isn't dead yet yay
what I don't hear sound anymore
what happened
what happened I just switched something
in the sound capture because I heard the
crackling and now I broke it
one moment
I'll fix it
uh
uh where'd it go yeah yeah she kept on
tweeting about the now she listens to
the song
on her little private account
yeah
where did it go
I restarted and so it's just suddenly
gone
I do the things I always do and it's
just suddenly gone let me
go here
[Music]
um
got it
why did what the [\h__\h]
what why
were you when audio was killed huh
it makes no sense
nothing's muted everything says it
always is
here
that's right you were here
I'm switching things around but
it should suddenly gone
full
um
[Music]
I already brought it back I think it was
just in that menu the music is gone
what
that didn't happen that didn't happen
that didn't happen
anyway
cat hair
holy [\h__\h]
anyway yeah do you
I wonder like I'm kind of curious I wish
he would tell me
like
I want to hear about what part was
difficult
and you know tell me about the process
of learning it I want to know tell me
about it
I know what to cook I want to cook
something special that I can only think
of the most basic recipes
um
the place talk to her about it when she
sent me the video actually a couple days
beforehand
um can I make something with this
the butter I don't want to just
um
make random [\h__\h] maybe the butter
with a fish
no but
[Music]
um
I want a normal fish
maybe buttered apples buttered and and
sugar oh that should become something
don't you think
that should be something
specific
Bingo oh
the Apple sweetness has been enhanced by
smothering it with butter and baking it
oh
can I do that kind of the same thing
with these things
I'm cooking
now that just becomes simmered fruit I
wasted my
[Music]
butt what a waste
I can do a cake well not anymore
probably not without the sugar I bought
that sugar to make something fancy
man okay anyway now we have a lot of
like Loki mid dishes
because I don't want to overheal myself
that's good
okay
oh are they no the cons the constructs
survive oh there's still a dragon over
there too they're still fighting
they're still fighting look
oh
how can they all they need is one shot
on those how are you not capable of that
oh I wasted my OCTA Rock ball on you
guys
Arrow too
hmm
oh I think they finally did it
oh it's dangerous it's dangerous here
one could just slide down and fall down
we don't want that
nice
what do you got an old wooden Shield man
that stuff is so outdated
[Music]
anyway yeah
I am I'm really happy to laugh without
you did that because she kind of
single-handedly I mean I don't really
see much coming from it but she's she's
low-key revived the doing challenge
with her passion
so I'm grateful for her promotion on the
song
because you know it's been a while since
Stewie was released
yeah bye bye
it's been a while and obviously the the
original hype from releasing it is gone
so I appreciate any kind of promotion
I think if she likes do you this much
she will love oops
my upcoming songs too
thank you
[Music]
did
cooling just
[Music]
cause this
with his floppity wings
no
cause I feel like
he made the camera
where do you see anyone
oh no he's got bumps for real
[Music]
oh
my God
yeah um
yeah at least I'll get my my fairy back
if we reset
[Music]
uh did it's safe like after I cooked
please because I cooked so much yeah
okay
damn oh my God
go away go away
I'll go straight to him
no
[Music]
man I'm scared
okay okay cool and take care of him
please
I got no weapon
Berry I'm so stupid
no what a waste
oh man
oh my health
I need to be more careful I feel like I
was more careful off screen
and I am on screen man
um okay these bombs
yay
you oh once you touch them there's like
a countdown okay because I was wondering
what's gonna happen am I gonna get in
trouble if I
throw this now
really good and he estimate when the
people released I don't want to really
say it because I mean there's an
estimate but what if it's
what if it gets delayed a lot and that's
not good anyway
and I want to keep something a surprise
be able to announce something
out of the many things that I'm already
in
um
revealing
yeah yeah but I've been working on it
and
been discussing things I did book
for the sake of music video creation I
did book my my flight
and
and my hotel and everything
why are these things here to amma's
place
I just booked it yesterday I was one of
my on my to-do list things
please
yeah
but I
I don't know maybe I'll only make one MB
because I already know even with one MV
I am going to only lose money because
music just
it's
it's in the end at least as long as I
don't have like a label a realistic talk
uh as long as I don't have a label
I will probably always only lose money
from it
um
yeah
I was like
I wanted I wanted to do two but
I I asked a little bit about details of
like how previous songs did and I mean
do you did well yes
um and and in theory maybe on the paper
on the black and white paper I didn't
lose
money on their on their paper but on
mine I did because I still uh spent some
extra money that isn't accounted for in
in those notes you know what I mean
[Music]
for doing like a choreography that
that's that wasn't included in the
budget for it to begin with
um
thank you but you know uh realistically
it's like
um 10 times if not 20 times that
yeah no 100 times what
no 10 times or uh yeah I don't want to
say
anything exact but it's shocking
at least if you want like a high quality
Envy
and I do want
something like Julio you know
but I'm I think I'm gonna just settle
for one now
and hope that everybody who sees that
one MV
well still
feel motivated yeah
to check out
the rest of the album
but it's not only about that it's also
because I think the the two songs that I
have so far are like damn they have so
much potential
they are so yes I want the second one
they're so good for like do you style
and beans
I want a choreo for both I will get a
choreo for all these songs even though
it's all out of my own pocket because I
want to be able to dance my album songs
whenever I want
in future concerts and all that
you can always give them an MB later
down the line well I was hoping that I
would be helping myself with like
promotion and all that
as well by making these
and these
that it would have like several effects
but I think the money that I would lose
from it
is a little bit too much
I just gotta make
some business decisions even even with
one I'm probably gonna lose money but
at least one I do want to have
I cannot
cannot just let it be without a single
MB
at least one and that one will be
amazing
it'll be really really
good I will stay in everybody's brains
and everybody will watch it several
times and be like damn girl she's
shaking those hips again
um
yum
I I can still do some like really simple
ones maybe for the others like you know
I think I said it before I want to do
like a lyric
simple lyric video style not proper MB
just lyric video basically so that you
can listen to it
on YouTube as well
on my Channel having some kind of
promotion some kind of
um existence on my channel
um
but not all at once I will like stagger
it
you know no no no no Unison is
not cheap either
I mean
not as
a expensive first do you style Envy but
yeah
yeah yeah
I helped with that
I guess so I I made you know uh
difficult to afford for myself
I can afford you know but uh is it a
smart decision for
uh you know business
yeah difficult difficult sometimes maybe
not always
hmm
yeah
yeah no I get it animating takes so much
time so
it is what it is
it is one of these
yeah wherever I should and I mean
sometimes yes that's why I'm saying okay
I I I will do one MB
the second one I'll have to think about
oh
I just
I don't know I think in Hollow you know
I'm really happy making music but as
long as I'm not in the label making
music is really only for the sake of
making music for me not for making money
because
I won't be making money it's just a
harsh reality that music on its own
isn't isn't really the
thing that brings in the
the money you know
um and that's okay because I do want to
make money uh music I don't want to make
music
but I just I just can't do it in the
pace or the amount
of someone like Cali for example
because of those reasons those terms and
all that yeah
brings promotion to the channel at least
yeah in the end like
the music is
more like
a fun thing to have to be proud of to
to show hey this is something I did and
then I can also use it to perform the
music I have later on in like in like
concerts reading
the lives and all that
um
yeah yeah yeah yeah a passion project
yeah and I mean just something to show
off
and and
[Music]
um
yeah
a part of my repertoire exactly part of
my Empire yeah and it's like music is
not it cannot be considered my job
streaming is my job
I make a living out of streaming but if
it was just the music I I'm not making
music a living out of music
that's the harsh reality
but
that is the music industry
I mean not only it's not only the music
industry but
blue blah blue
yeah I'm in the same place as you well
then you've gotta play alongside me
at least you can make the music I want
yeah I can choose what I want to make
and I'm really happy with the songs so
far so I'm excited about creating it and
that's also why I'm okay with
um investing a lot of money into the
music video that will not come back just
because I'm really really excited about
the song and its potential
yeah
yeah yeah
I was up until 4am to finish this before
me cheers
you're calling it a dungeon is it a
dungeon
is it really a Dungeon Because breath of
the wild didn't have proper dungeons
they bring back some dungeons here
or is it like
it is
oh [\h__\h] this whole Ascension feels like
a dungeon or like a whole thing like I
would I would assume that up there once
I arrive
is gonna be
already the boss fight
because this is taking a lot of time to
get up here
yeah yeah thank you yeah that's
basically it
that's basically it it's just another
way to promote myself
yeah
hopefully but then in order for it to
have that effect it would have to go a
bit more outside my usual
um fan base
so
I hope that
the song that I do choose
will be shared around a lot
um
hello fresh
foreign
back
yeah
hello hello hello hello hello hello
are we back are we back
thank you
thank you for holding the fort yay
uh sorry I don't know what the [\h__\h]
happened I just left my desk for a
moment
and I came back and everything's broken
I didn't do [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] it was
like smoothie running over my keyboard
while I was gone or
what happened
ugh
my God everybody come back
um
what the hell
yeah I had to open the door for
hellofresh because apparently now
now they want me to open the door all
the time they used to just put it down
there in front of my door but the thing
is if I don't open it they also just put
it down but now they ring and wait for a
signature even though before they never
did that
hmm
oh
they kick me out
[Music]
here we're gonna take that you away from
me but I love you let me just say that
okay
[Music]
oh no this is so [\h__\h] I I uploaded a
screenshot on Twitter because I got an
error message but now it's updating
again and I'm like I can't do [\h__\h] like
when I when I go with my mouse over the
update window it has this like you know
the the loading loading loading Circle
um
uh
uh oh my God
I don't trust it
I don't trust it that's probably gonna
randomly start trying to update
something again
I don't trust it because it worked for a
moment when I restarted my PC
last time too but I'll give it let's
give it a moment
um
[Music]
please
please stay this way
uh
uh oh I'm scared mommy help me I'm
scared
ah I'm scared I'm scared they're gonna
take me away
I'm gonna take me away again
[Music]
do not take me away oh my God
it'd be nice
please I just want to stream Zelda
this
okay
oh this VOD is gonna be a mess
okay it seems okay how fast did it go
away last time
um
longer is it longer than last time it
feels longer
maybe it's calm down now
maybe it's Gonna Leave Me Alone
okay
are we good
I'm scared
um
okay I'm gonna
I'm gonna continue playing now
Suzuki
oh my God
what the [\h__\h] was all that
oh man I think we're good okay okay pray
pray
I will never forget this
go excellent you little [\h__\h]
I will never forget this little
bamboozle
hmm
last time your voice had some sort of
artifact before adopted it again this
time your voice sounds fine oh
interesting artifact wow am I like a RPG
item
[Laughter]
oh okay okay didn't hear it on the phone
oh okay wasn't it like that obvious
I think we're good
let's just move on oh my God
this is my first time flying this hide
the air is pretty cold up here huh I'll
be fine but what about you link make
sure you don't freeze okay
like my my life today also froze when I
had problems like it was it even like
for a little bit froze like my YouTube
chat and like my YouTube window and all
that as well
like overall
I was I was like
having issues but just because of
government are like killing everything
it didn't freeze the whole PC and it was
more like one moment it will phrase my
life today that it will phrase my
YouTube and all that
um yeah it talk about the resources
the [\h__\h]
um
oh wait is there another shrine
is that like free shrines on the path
too up there isn't this the third one
damn they don't know where else to put
them apparently
or just so that we don't get bored I
wasn't bored anyway though is it the
second one it feels like the third one
oh
because uh
what kind of shrine will this be
sorry guys for the wear troubles
sorry about that
it came out of nowhere why did it happen
when I picked up my hello fresh order
it's a blessing
what a blessing let me tweet that we're
back because it took so long
oops Yeah that's my stream
I'm on my phone
copy link
[Music]
copy link haha link his name is link
uh we are back
sorry for the issues
okay oh wait will I will dummy tweet no
okay of course it won't let me tweet on
my phone sometimes it will let me and
sometimes it'll crash the app but that's
another problem I have and I think
there's more on Twitter
on the Twitter app
it's their issue
all right let's do it on the desktop
copy link address Link's address I don't
want a dog's link
uh
I will copy and paste Link's address now
we are back sorry
for the issue I found Link's address
[Laughter]
they will people who aren't watching the
stream right now will not understand the
joke will they
don't think they will
following centers
we can go visit him now
back to the game I'll have to make up
for all that [\h__\h] by zooming through it
honestly it's probably better if the
game or if it's like genuinely the
situation forces me to be slower because
I'm I know I'm going too fast for you
guys oh I'm 10 thank you
I know I'm making too much progress and
you guys can't keep up
you got a life you got
so you got a job you have to want my
dreams
is all so long the streams are so long
the work days are so long and you need
to sleep at some point
[Music]
oh you just finished the dungeon of the
time it took to fix the ghost alarm
issue that's not really
reassuring in terms of
it being an actual dungeon that sounds
more like it was like just Shrine
quality
in terms of length
the music is changing again
it's not a traditional dungeon
um
yeah interesting
I mean in breath of the wild they had
this what did you call them
these big
not also not dungeons but if anything it
was the closest thing to a dungeon
yeah exactly
and I I mean those were kind of cool
but still
dungeon Zelda fans are you know asking
for dungeons
should I be using him up in the air here
too to be faster I'm not sure if it will
even help
[Music]
a little platform here
docking docking on this level
platform
oh nice this one's
on the way to me oh [\h__\h]
hi
can we get much higher we're almost
there
I wish I could
go up to this one can I can I yeah
huh have you tried reaching out them for
a sponsorship
oh God
and I think I asked our team
to reach out to them and they did
something
and then I think they told me they
didn't reply or something like that yeah
oh
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
all right this was going so fast
you can dive too oh well
actually
interesting idea
I mean I don't want that's too fast I
don't wanna I don't want to die because
it just goes too fast
we lost a lot of height
but we're gonna get back up no matter
what
oh he can't help me with pushes like
that
hi
that's actually that was a good push
okay
we're here again
by the way I did also
message the
that thing the message
not message but I called DHL
[\h__\h] hell
call DHL
then they were like
oh
they were like okay please call our Book
cartoon
um
the people who you know do the book
stuff
did the office work so I called that
department
bookkeepers yeah the billing department
actually
and they couldn't tell me
whoever it was something
legitimate
they couldn't really tell me yet
they were asking
if I had like a a bill number or
something on that leather
from the
can we make it
snow maybe not
I don't want to mess up
and no there was nothing on the left on
the leather
that sword
so yeah they couldn't they didn't say it
was a scam out right but they they were
like please send us the bill and we'll
take a good look at it
they didn't say all these are from us
they don't say this was a scam I asked
them if like this is normally the
company they work with like the the law
law firm they work with for these kind
of situations
and they said we don't know because like
when it gets to that point they just
give it off to the next apartment and I
guess they work with several law firms
or so maybe for these kind of things so
they don't they can't really say that
but it is possible
but yeah I don't know they couldn't
really help me so all I did for now was
send them the
the
a bill for email and they said they'll
look into it for me and don't tell me
what they think
but the deadline for the payment is like
pretty soon
who's that Thunder
so now I just go in
scary
I hope it's a scam because it's too much
money
we're in baby
it's pretty calm in here
do I want to go are these birds no those
numbers
what they they call it a temple wind
Temple
so it has dungeon potential
[Music]
not small
interesting where should I go
middle wait where do I go where do I go
where do I go
oh
oh it landed us here okay
babies
consider everything leading to this a
dungeon or like a part of the dungeon
just ignore the ways that could happen
is another letter from the law firm yeah
but I don't want them to raise it even
more
if they're legit
wow so this one was waiting for us in
that huge cloud
this is the Stormwind Arc from the kids
song
huh huh
what are you doing
yeah it was the first time I explained
that to them too that I didn't get
anything beforehand
we all I don't know I had no idea what
it would be
oh yeah so far they don't know either
thanks for the membership renewal
just finished this dungeon have fun okay
well good there's some people in the
chat who can help me if I'm confused
it's not something that can be
arbitrarily raised it'll be fun I hope
so what the
wait was she just like blown away this
present link the blizzard that's been
pounding Rachel Village is coming from
here oh yeah didn't I see someone here a
minute ago oh yeah Zelda
weird I could swear they were just here
they
did you not recognize it as Zelda
what happened with those Bird's eyes
aren't you supposed to have good eyes
oh these things are intimidating at
first but pretty easy to handle
well I hope
this will not be too difficult
I don't want to embarrass myself
[Music]
I see
a beautiful looking dungeon
foreign
[Music]
I hope we won't need wait can I I can I
can wait wait you guys said I can bunk
this too
maybe with the
big hammer
no maybe this one not the icicles but
not this one huh
[\h__\h] but it needs like so many
fire flowers
all right oh thank you for reminding me
of my Shields
that is so convenient I just have to
um
what do you go there it is
thank God
[Music]
oh and there was a fire here too
and anyway what you look at bread of
oh
are we gonna be fighting tonight
uh not so nice constructs
soldiers spare sword
I don't know what to get rid of
maybe this boring thing
a bit of them
okay
bye
is that just for going back out what
why did they start
the wind turbines
just look around out here for a little
bit and then we'll go inside wherever
the entrance is
is that an enemy behind sometimes
sometimes there's enemies
behind
Soldier constructo no I'm okay
oh
[Music]
that is one entrance at least
and here
possibly see another one
do I need to attach a stick to it
to make it work
s
I could attach the icicle to [\h__\h]
hell
no more flame emitter Shields
really
hooks
it works though
that's all it needed
junk
I didn't start the dungeon yet
and
is this
okay but it does it does kind of feel
like a dungeon
it does already give me dungeon vibes
oh Dome tender will be so happy
he was like really really hopeful that
they would bring dungeons back with tltk
oh my God you little [\h__\h]
um
time to eat something proper
look at all those simmer tomatoes
[Music]
oh
what
an animal heart
I almost want to go down
to the ground to a god of statue to get
another heart why was that a one shot I
mean I had one last heart
but still
talks to Tulin
oh
okay
hi wait where are we
what
sometimes it seems so frequently
and then other times
very much not
but it's okay
can I make it like this
yeah okay
we are going back inside
let's touch the center thingy oh I can
get a teleportation point
what okay
my bad
yeah yeah we already saw all this
[Music]
Hudson
there we go another one
I don't know
we already talked to him in the cutscene
so
I thought that was it
huh
and he just lets me go
[Music]
princess
really mysterious
[Music]
okay I'll talk to him now
what's that here before
hahaha
did I touch that last time
I didn't
I don't know how I didn't see it and I
made fun of him boys bird eyes didn't
die because he lost track of the Zelda
or like didn't know who she was
I mean in that very moment I made fun of
I was busy making fun of them
oh
looks like it's shot times but the
source of the blizzard has gotta be
right under that hatch
isn't there some way we can get it open
oh
that's something
um
he will show me the way
okay I heard it for sure this time it
was calling out to me loud and clear
the source of the blizzard messing up
the village has gotta be under this
hatch if that voice was right it will
open once we find a way to release all
five blocks
we're so close come on link let's go
figure out how to open up those locks
okay will you follow me again
no
what are you just gonna wait here
well now he's following me
like
then oh now he's following now he's
following
yay
how do you spell music
not anymore oh nice nice shot
not as good as my shadow
oh thanks for taking care of the other
dude
[Music]
okay
wanna go pray if I wanna true we can
teleport here now right
yeah okay
uh world map
I want to go
somewhere safe
no wait not here where am I going
look at Landing
thank you yeah please please wait a
moment I'll be right back I'm just
getting one more heart so that I'll be
even more prepared thank you for the
membership
eggs eggs
very effects oh yeah wait do I have no
fairy right now
I
I wasted all my fairies
so better armor what armor should I get
I could still buy the rest of the cold
armor but oh no it's not even that cold
I'm I'm fine with like the top at the
bottom
oh
although the pants I'm wearing are still
from the very beginning true
under
from the first from the tutorial map I
think so I could get the
the
real
proper
[Music]
hebra pants Maybe
it's a really easy dungeon
okay ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'll get the heart and then
um
maybe no need for pants maybe I maybe
it's not even that cold inside the
dungeon maybe I could switch two
different pants
foreign
[Music]
what here
gosh this map is too big
hmm
here went Temple entrance so is there
gonna be a fire temple
and a water temple
and an Earth Temple
feels like tradition
has come back
[Music]
oh
let's go
he's motivated
Gracie about to talk to you again
follow me number one
we
open
this again I know
the music is so beautiful
and
I still in this timeline have my flame
emitting Shield [\h__\h]
take that
okay done oh wait put that away
[Music]
and
I'll go on this I actually also have a
flame emitting spare remember that guys
don't let me forget that
after I lose my shield
[Music]
now why do we want to enter through over
there like I was going to
is that the
the best way to enter
you have a flame emitting fear thank you
for telling me
I would have forgotten
[Music]
um I'll just I'll just only uh
thank you
I'll do this side first I'll just go in
now
[Music]
I have I have I have a few
okay wait okay Mama remember how to
fight you know how to fight
[Music]
polarizing
what's up
perfect this is how it's supposed to go
lances are the way to go
I wanna pick up the spare but I guess I
have no space
[Music]
I won't be will it um
I won't need it I think
I'll be able to solve whatever
with
the ball stick as well I think so many
arrows nice
[Music]
now I got two
range pokes yes love range pokes
okay that was just that one room
this thing
then I'll open up this one again
although I didn't know what to do in
that realm I think
this music feels so medieval
beautiful like a like a clock
Like A Clockwork
okay
there's a chest there
um
oh oh he's pointing it out this time hey
look at that is this for one of the
locks it's kind of shaped like a
windmill
we want me to make some air or
can I turn it no
when I rewind it no
no do we want me to make some air
is there some
some something behind
no
you can use him okay okay thank you
thank you from the front
you know that show me what you got
whoa
[Music]
a Fame of hitting here
suddenly voice acting
so it opened
One open
okay how do I get in here
can I not get in there yet
I want in
and
go to the other side
it's really intense so he does sound
like a silgaki so I think that's good
sounds like he's pissed off aggressive
no
no it's good
yeah shoot him shoot him
I want to show them yeah there we go
at least these ones he can take care of
alone on his own he's so independent
yeah he's supposed to be extra gaki I
feel like this aggressiveness in The
Voice
let me uh
shows that
quite nicely
okay what the hell
I'm having trouble
I ran out
nah this is all on purpose I am just
trying to
find everything outside before I go
inside it's all on purpose
I don't think I would like fee
anymore
in German nah
what where do I go
I don't see anywhere to use in there
either
have you seen the video of the German
fortnite kit with the Coca-Cola no
I don't think so
what's up here
nothing
side of the ship
[Music]
can I
oh wait what the [\h__\h] is that Cannon
anyway
no more Ganon here is a cannon that we
will have to fight
Ganon has been reinvented so many times
he is now a cannon
okay
do I hijack the cannon
but is someone in there Moshi Moshi
let me in oh no
can't enter from the top
unless can I enter with a bullet uh
usually would
will that kill me
oh wait there's no there's no real
opening there
it's fake
I wanna buy did I have the option to
go in like if I do it like here
no no no no no that is Canon territory
can you make air
here
there's something there I can move that
but I don't I don't think this is
the solution is it
you can come here from below so that
seems to be
the way to do it
look at all the par parts of the Ark
well what exactly is the arc the ship
you mean
and go on the flippy flaps
oh there's more cannons
which flippy flap will let me enter
maybe one of the middle ones
there's also
a shrine what
what
that's not as true is it
who got shot
by the cannon
does it actually shoot you
oh oh okay
um
[Music]
when Temple be one yeah okay
cannot enter here
[Music]
on it well at least there's uh plenty of
warning
now well but there is some icicles so
I'm gonna enter there
he
he I found my way in
[Music]
I leave a tail you do it nice
hey
we're inside the ship let's go I know
what to do here time reversal
rewind follow me to Instagram
Frozen when I do that
how's he gonna catch up Mommy
foreign
Magic
[Music]
oh what's this for
eign
[Music]
a little more
this one's closed too
Maybe
I wanna turn it
oh wait this one's missing one of those
Wheels
oh can I not take that one
I feel like that's what it wants me to
do though
I need one of those Wheels
should I use
the eyes really I was gonna ask am I
supposed to use the ice
no way
how do I get a download that using a
bump
I don't want to use a bomb
there's a normal Arrow
oh
okay I genuinely did not ow
did not think that that will do the
trick
[Music]
turn like this no way
uh
what
I can't get it any higher
I don't think that's it
I don't think what
oh to the other one
ah it's like forever stuck
let me get another one
just to pull it you mean I thought I had
to make like a cross but then I was
still gonna ask you guys like how how
would I even
how would I turn it yo yo no no
oh
but then when I reached this point maybe
the other way
huh
come on no way I should if I can turn it
with the icicle then I should be able to
turn it without the icicle no
no
why not that makes no sense to me
once you realize it it's gonna be so
funny
and then why can I not do this one
why am I stuck here is there something
already yeah
well I I rewinded it and nothing
happened and then
I can't get it out any moment now
oh connecting now
[Music]
oh this one's too small
man
[Music]
huh
what what
don't break it please don't break it now
it's working now
yay I locked it in but ah it's the wrong
way no finally
[Laughter]
finally come here dude
I need the magic
no you guys cooked thank you for cooking
for me
that looks like we have three already
Ben can I go back up
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] yeah I mean
if I do that and then do it again
foreign
do I come out on the surface
you'll get the name from stay cooking
I'll try my best
okay next one we were on this side now
so let's go to the side
oh
[Music]
not letting you take oh my God
uh
uh I dropped one of these because that's
a strong one
why did they come back the constructs
came back while I was down there was it
blood moon or what
oh there's one of those
eyeball please
so the ice ones work too
yes
it just falls down as an ice sculpture
beautiful oh
how did I get the item
normally when they fall down
Falls with them don't doesn't it
then press a or anything either
where is it opening oh that's already
open completely
[Music]
what is that
okay
no problem whoa
I like having him around
first I was like no not that beautiful
yo five fruits thank you
but now I gotta say
foreign
[Music]
okay
this one
don't worry I will understand oh wait
where's this room should I go here first
oh no my rock hammer is dead
what is this it's closed
okay probably that for later
official kfb in my book well he is a
bird
looks almost like a chicken he's white
mostly
it's basically a chicken
don't tell him that that will probably
upset him he thinks he's something else
a shrine that I did yesterday on my own
time that had
[Music]
passage like this
Matrix
or something no not Matrix more like I
don't know secret agent or or or Thief
simulator what I don't know
wallets wallet and grommet or whatever
they called
[Music]
Wallace and garment wallets
okay impossible okay that's also
reference
[Music]
we don't
good that I have a backup to support me
oh
we're gonna we're gonna fly over there
wait a second wait a second
teleport up and then we fly over
giving us a little bit of height
here
hey
the wrong trousers
I as a child I was a bit freaked out by
that movie
ah we opened another one
but
quite all right oh that's a good movie
oh okay he's protecting a ruby
oh
oh thank you
no thank you
yeah I I do hope I can continue making
music oh he only saw my friend until now
oh he's trying to connect no save the
Ruby I don't want you to connect that
because I want to keep it what is that
well now he can't
thank you
so at least he can't uh anymore
I noticed I was I was saying last time
that I can just sell those Sapphire
swords but turns out
oh I don't know if I'm being stupid but
I feel like I cannot sell the sapphire
uh swords I can sell any weapons
they're not
they're not for sale it seems
yo we saved the Ruby let's go
let's go up here
[Music]
there's a shop later that can separate
weapons oh you know it's okay it's last
game too oh really not being able to
sell weapons I find that quite odd you
can sell like
all your other items but no like weapons
the armor I kind of understand because
you want to keep all your armor don't
you
for any case they seem very unique you
know
you can't get those back when you sell
them but weapons you can always get back
in weapons you can like everywhere
Captain one Reaper cool
so I feel like it would make sense to be
able to sell them you can sell what
you can sell some armor
hey that makes no sense why can you sell
armor but no weapons
[Music]
they're all vacation who wants to buy
the Kate weapon I will not take that
excuse because
something like a sapphire sword
obviously has a lot of value
[Music]
trust me you'd want that oh no
yes
I see
[Music]
I get it
I wonder if one is enough
hey hey hey hey
[Music]
enemies
maybe you guys regained some respect for
me now that I it
understood what to do
oh
sometimes he uses that as an attack too
not just a oh this is the run that I was
looking at from outside not just the
[Music]
not just using his arrows
but now you used it up
what what was with that direction eh
[Music]
huh
well I always respect you thank you
thank you
foreign
's got their brain empty moment right or
head empty
[Music]
two more in German please
and this one opens up too nice
okay
can we get much deeper
into the
right
what am I hearing
[Music]
let's look at the map so
um
we've been here there was one place
somewhere where there was I could go
even lower right but the door was closed
there too
I'm not sure how you would open it
anyway
but that's probably this yeah these
stairs lead to this
[Music]
forgot to map existence well I was
I was kind of forgetting about it too if
it weren't for the chat
to look at the map
and you notice guys the bgm is even more
dramatic now
I already entered all the side entrances
didn't I
said I look at the same
um
a little
Corridor again if I if this is the right
one I'm not sure
chubby
now that's the wrong one but I mean
we could still look at it oh wait oh
wait wait actually that's the right
direction
keep going keep going
oh wait so
this is
another
oh I didn't open oh there is however a
little window here
[Music]
and Bob and then go through this little
window what is that window for
wait I don't know oh do I know
[Music]
attach this
it's sent from above how
it does that work it could actually fly
through
[Music]
for real for real
good why is that in such a weird
position
why is it in such a weird position
[Music]
you didn't even try it wait is she
cooking I don't think I'm cooking but
I'm just doing what you guys say but I
don't really believe in it
why would that
why would they make me do such a silly
thing oh
no no no no
that's stupid
foreign
I have a really stupid really silly idea
[Music]
bear with me
this is the solution that I have to say
silly
snow way
that is why that's it is that no way
is that why the opening is that size
no hey
that is so silly
who's so young
no way no way
for real for real
wait a second bring it back a little bit
see it's hard to see
[Music]
no one
oh thank God I can still Bridge
[Music]
I thought I couldn't reach anymore
because I dropped it no no no no really
oh my God I got I I thought of it on my
own at least but
damn that is silly
[Music]
I do not need to fly through with a
paraglider
oh and Sapphire okay
well that was that room that however
doesn't lead us any further deeper into
the
ship was fine with me fine with me
at least we cooked
I'll go to the other side
and see how to how we gonna get through
[Music]
how are we gonna get through
[Applause]
um
that
a dark closed door
was there something extra here
[Music]
I mean
that's never close thing that should
open up somehow
is the solution close by
[Music]
I don't know
we came for that one of the clothes
oh
[Music]
don't mind the enemy
focus on the go
okay
I am back
there was this but
we did go up here right
but the other smaller room was I think
on the other side was it
[Music]
you can't send your last one really
maybe it's uh
oh no
credit card
being mean to you
[Music]
how do I get there
I guess I could climb
I hope that works
help me
okay no problem
do I still have my flame limiting
pair
portable pots and a time bomb okay
where was that small room
here and and then there was a speaker
with another chest
well I don't think
I don't think I can do anything here
wait this is outside
yeah and there's a wind turbine I could
try to fly in from outside huh
okay okay
dangerous
fully we don't
[Music]
we don't so from the Sun
I see it here right oh
I'm I'm about where it is right roughly
I think
slowly slowly uh
[Music]
um
do I get like
yeah okay
[\h__\h]
and this had to happen at least once so
that we have a rough feeling for what
we're looking for
let's land on here
there it is there it is
that's really difficult to get in
there's an easy jump point
is there
a bit
[Music]
I don't know
how do we
[Music]
okay is it from inside after all
what ice
[Music]
oh my god
of course
oh that's so much Shield why does it
look like a button and why is it the
first time we get
all right
okay do we have something to fuse
and a rusty house
[Music]
that
great little flamethrower
is that so
got it one more I think
well I feel like there was still a two
or three rooms that I couldn't enter
what if I oh the music changed again
I wish I could teleport in from here but
it seems like I can't so how am I
supposed to get back
what about here
oh really
[Music]
there's a door
wait I think I just saw it
what's my name
[Music]
laughs
is that
where I think it is
[Music]
huh
that's not what I thought it was that
door open is open now
[Music]
it was just for coming back
how do I get into that big ass room
[Music]
the room
that I'm looking at oh is this one
from above Maybe
in this case from Below
but there's nothing
stand on the roaster
all your Phoenix whoa
congratulations
let's go back to the top
we've entered from the sides we've
entered From Below now maybe we'll find
a way to enter from the top
this thing
[Music]
no that's not good
let me just get up here
[Music]
's the wind to Glide up
thank you
oh nice shot
was this
I don't want that that looks unspecial
sturdy long stick well I guess I picked
I don't pick it up okay
have we been up here before
this oh there's some ice here where does
it lead please don't burn booze on me
[Music]
there's a pool here
is a handle
do I still have my flame emitting pair
yes I do
what
is
there's a chest Stone
I want to ride my eyes so cold
[Music]
another Shield nice Shield and I don't
have space for it okay good
that was nice but not the room that I'm
looking for
may I get back up please let's see
thank you
but the fact that we found something
over here makes me curious to look more
around before we move on
even if I may find nothing
I still want to look
the
beautiful structure after all one has to
appreciate every side and every edge of
it
the other side
good
[Music]
oh another eyes
time for my
favorite
it was worth coming here looking around
oh okay
I I specifically do need arrows right
now
wanna shoot that maybe
I didn't see us
go
that was far enough
come on
so should I try to get to the very top
oh okay I don't think I can actually
climb all of that after all because
there's ice
so I will take your advice
[Music]
there we go
yeah yeah I remember this part how do I
how do I open it up
um
what are you doing
see I think here
for some reason
like the game is like okay okay you
would lose a lot of the drop if you kill
the flying mobs out here so we just here
created a system an option a function
that will let you pick up
um
everything
pull these doors on
oh
don't get stuck underneath
well one is enough no oh no maybe
let's open the other one too
[Music]
hi
and then I see the room okay
[Music]
let's use our flying gear shall we oh
actually it's pretty slow when we just
chill like this because the air is still
pushing us up relatively
strongly
this place wasn't a trailer
ah yeah I think
I think I know what you're talking about
I don't really remember
most of the trailer but now you say it
yeah
do we get a boss fight now
is it down here
I listened intrigued yay so you can
cakes
[Music]
there's two of them how they're exciting
is awesome
[Music]
that's the room
and
I think I was in that room
[Music]
God damn it
uh I guess I got rid of the spam
or this thing
ah
okay
I think I might as well teleport myself
to the top
you can't just not take it no I don't
wanna
this boss fight makes every boss fight
and breath of the wild feel like
watching paint dry oh they're saying
it's a really good boss fight
okay then in preparation I will need
another cookie
ah
um if that works then I think um there
must have been like one word that
triggered it to not be able to send
um
wait this thing didn't open
hmm
maybe icon
[Music]
is it supposed to happen
oh
I'm scared doesn't come out let me find
up here
in the air
so we go inside
here we go
[\h__\h] I don't think I'm gonna do well
it's gonna stress me out close
what are we going here
[Music]
sees its monsters
um
cold era so we shoot it
oh oh wait
I can't I can't go low oh there we go
maybe should I send something with it
maybe not now because I want to try it
out first
oh oh it works I could even jump on it
couldn't I
know
no I do need a lot of arrows maybe
that's why they they spammed me with
eyebrows
right now okay
what the [\h__\h] is that
are we following it
the curly was a better way to dodge this
but I'm like I'm like so unsure about
the controls right now
when flying
[Music]
give me a second one
you know the angle
pretty bad
I can't go lower than that
you're in the way
you find the way
holding it
you're gonna go through one of those
holes again yeah
[Music]
so get some fight again
gotta be above it
epic music playing
oh it's already happening
still a bit [\h__\h] angle but okay
will let work go oh
and fell right through it
wait there's more in there
I was just leaving
oh
really
icicles or the Whirlwind
[Music]
okay so same thing but this time we have
to be very careful where we're gonna fly
for so many
[Music]
[\h__\h] I want to eat something small
that means mom
[Music]
should I go above them can you go above
them
[Music]
oh yes I think
them
cooling can protect me from the tornado
[Music]
shoot from Below
okay I guess so yeah because I saw it's
on his backside he just protects it from
can I reach
maybe now
uh really close
oh [\h__\h]
yeah this is a pretty good boss fight
though I gotta say
uh
especially for me I'm mama duke for this
kind of stuff
[Music]
I'm taking my chances
yeah
gotta save my time yo we ain't got all
day
not too far I think I'm too far away oh
wait it works nothing
oh yeah about the angle now
there's no way
sniper
Pizza
that second round one side once I had
the confidence actually went pretty damn
well I actually crashed yep yep yep
hey hey
Crystal
[Music]
good boss
yay
oh we got a heart container
from this I didn't realize
I got some breath of the wild you also
got hard containers after the design
piece right I didn't realize that
completely thought we had to get all of
them from the on our own
a big tier
Tata
food containers
that was epic
it was a good dungeon
was a good boss we had a good actually
useful companion
get a nice heart
hell yeah
ah airports are quiet I don't really
want it I'm just gonna sell it I think
give me give me
give me give me can I have
how do you take it
do I shoot it
it's like a tattoo
[Music]
you want it you can have it
oh it's small now
airport size
what oh we got another McDonald's memory
oh
she
top tier
um
he looks funny oh the mask is inside
hmm
[Music]
the store monsters
foreign
[Music]
oh
God damn it is
[Music]
they all have funky masks
the mysterions
[Music]
of course
Creek
how did he do that though
[Music]
is
that site
um
[Music]
what happened
but he was talking to me in that other
time also yeah here normally
what the [\h__\h]
yes so
we saved
again
foreign
[Music]
they should make a movie I totally agree
but after the the fact they made a Mario
movie I'm sure they'll make a um
it would be a waste not to
oh foreign
[Music]
Roblox
why does he have a farm when you guys
don't
[Music]
oh do I know
in this game
no way
too
where
huh
it's a construct it's only ring
[Music]
huh
oh
you good bro awesome
[Music]
I didn't uh I didn't think I mean I
wasn't sure like once when he was like
introduced to us and they told us yeah
he's got the super cool Talent
I thought maybe but I wasn't sure if we
would really get his skill
so in breath of the wild our bird flying
skill was going all the way up right
flying straight up but this one is
forward like a dash
in the air or even on ground
okay so it's different but it's similar
I wonder what the other is gonna be
oh
[Music]
it's really gonna be melting oh my God
but is it gonna turn back completely for
the original thing
temperature and wine really
I like it snowy though
but only the Villas right the mountains
are still gonna be snowy I would hope
unless yeah it's just the village
wow
now that melted quickly
foreign
[Music]
so now does it look the same way and
look before and breath of the Wild
I know it wasn't snowy before
you guys you did it yeah holy [\h__\h] we
did
unbelievable
[Music]
yeah it turns out it was easy once we
started working together
[Music]
this was no small feat
I still can't believe the storm went Arc
from the children's song was real uh-huh
me neither you could have knocked me
over with a feather
[Music]
he gets a new bow oh
for a job well done Dylan oh
[Music]
there was always my intention to give it
to you once you came of age as a warrior
[Music]
I'll prove that you have become a
warrior worthy of carrying it
[Music]
hey link that woman in the vision my
ancestor showed us didn't she looked
just like Princess Zelda to you
do you think that was the real princess
I mean it seemed like a long long time
ago
there's still a bunch of unanswered
questions
I gotta know more about the figure we
saw on the stone with Arc so I'm gonna
go look into it personally
next time you see me I'll have more
information about Princess Zelda so
check in with me sometime okay and
remember with my Sage's power the two of
us can keep working together no matter
what
use it to summon or dismiss the Avatar
of Tulin
mmm so he's gonna like follow me around
and I can use it or is it like a
one-time thing
like uh before
I gotta try how do we use it
um how do you use it
Sage's vows on the key items menu
uh
how do I put it up there
is Miss cancel where is it
huh
outside oh with the paper back
[Music]
almost ran by you because I'm excited to
test it out
oh dang one meet again when I came here
to see a geoglyph sadly that we were
frauded by the blizzard and grounded
nearby after it finally calms down we
made our way to this Village we plan to
get on we're finding the tattoo glove
shortly
the ancient literature indicates that
the Forgotten Temple is here in Hebrew
at the bottom of the canyon we believe
the temple holds the key to unlocking
the mystery of the zoo Cliffs but even
if we find the temple our work will not
be done there may be zero clubs look at
it all over the world We Must Praise for
a long audio search
can we go to that like straight away
gonna make new arrows
we can are your arrows cheaper than
elsewhere
oh wait I can just take him
oh those are yours
oh yeah
oh
she said it's hers but but if I need
them right now she'll give them to me
sometimes man I always need arrows you
know I'm the hero I'm Gonna Save the
World like I just literally got rid of
this chaotic disasters uh
weather here
okay where was it again oh hello
hi hey if it isn't the guy who worked
with tilling to save the village
everyone in the village is happy to
stretch their wings again without them
icing over so thanks for that and the
end of the blizzard has improved
visibility too it's much easier not to
find caves where
wait I mean
ah there's still snow but the snow storm
is gone is that
so should I've explored after doing all
of this number four
I mean nah it was all right the way it
was
um
uh I saw one just the other day in fact
while I was flying around but I forgot
exactly where it was it had a rock waved
in green light inside it ah that one I
already found and I already did thanks
for the hint though
eh what
Shrine quest uh
um wait maybe I didn't do it
it was a white bird
white bird
ah
have you ever looked up at the peak of
the Spire here in Rita Village
oh that [\h__\h] shutting out sideways
looks kind of like a bird's perch right
we call it the vam Meadows perch vamido
part of my morning routine is to head up
there and bask in the Sun as it rises
that day I was getting some sun up on
the perch same as always just When the
Dawn was breaking right about then I
looked to the west and saw a white bird
resting Atop The Long shadow of the
perch
it
[Music]
oh it's with Wilbur to rest on a shadow
right I was curious so I went to go have
a look where I saw the bird the thing is
I couldn't find the white bird again
after that instead I found the cave
entrance
must be an optical illusion
do you want a hotel they're huge divide
beasts out of there right like that and
all the shrines and so many things still
I I think that is one of the things that
the developers do not want us to
question too much
there's not answers to everything
yeah
I don't know why I can remember all that
so clearly but not where the cave was
over there no I don't think that was it
well okay I'll find it
so I should look from up there or should
I just maybe I'll find it randomly
I don't want to go up there now
cooking station
buy the rest of the armor I still feel
like we don't need it
because we're gonna
I mean I'm done exploring the mountains
and even the mountains at the at the
peak it wasn't cold enough for me to
need more armor
[Music]
yeah and I can't afford it anyway I
better waste I better save my money for
the next armor
there's too many cyclists in this game
I want to do many but oh they got weight
oh man
where do you get the weed from on the
caban for planes can I get them by
myself top on for planes
Frontier is here
one of the taban for planes
happy birthday yesterday Alcatraz
I was just a band for Hills too
[Music]
well I don't see any taban for planes
maybe it's at the Topanga Hills or maybe
it's like past here like over here
could be maybe we should go there oh he
was also a
evil evil man
Horsemen of the Apocalypse
oh I got a very random Croc over here
I'll check out the temple what Temple
Temple I already hit the temple in this
Village
sounds
thank you
I'll buy one I wanna try but I want to
get in myself
[Music]
forgotten temples yeah I've been trying
to use some markers yesterday when I was
playing alone also so that I can tell
you what I did so that I remember
huh
[Music]
ah wait what was it about the Forgotten
Temple
what was that I had was it was it about
the the big
big mural where's the Forgotten Temple
shouldn't that be on my map
the [\h__\h]
they don't give you a question right
yeah
still forgotten that
they don't even give me a question why
is the Forgotten Temple
open the subquest menu
trying quests
side Adventures
uh
uh this one right
yeah
[Music]
ah all right we can do that one now
oh it's pretty far
uh is that where the where the mural is
if it's there then maybe
I can go from from here from the stable
and ride up
[Music]
I can glide from the sky tower
oh
the one
in Rito area
oopsie
but I love horse
oh no my closest Tower No One near me
yeah I know I can reuse them
oh
ah now we can see how that works
I can someone who's Avatar yeah but how
well how
what
he's here why ah oh he's now always
gonna be there
[Music]
hey let's go okay
you don't know
but he's not gonna be shooting right
also where did you go
oh there he is
he's not gonna be shooting I think
I think
[Music]
what
no no I was just nope
what do you think I was thinking
misunderstanding
oh careful that partner you went and
scared
you go storming around like that even a
real storm and it won't just be the
birds you sent flying over the hills
it's fine though I did hear some
interesting trips and Waddles from them
I don't want to say this too loud and
starting to panic but rumors are
spreading about Princess Ella that she's
been she's been riding seen some writing
some mysterious Beast it's said to be a
mountain of abuse to one of a huge
brutal Tusk my little reporters had
never seen something so frightening of
course what made his thought worse was
that it seemed like the princess herself
was controlling this terrifying creature
I find it hard to believe a beast like
that could really be lurking in Hyrule
but if this terrifying monster exists
and the implications make this a very
very huge story
mm-hmm
some guests here
number of sightings in the subtropical
region in the south
if we want to learn more we should dive
break be first into disable others
oh my God
I'll be playing this for a long time it
seems uh
legendary weapon you say give that a
little more thought things were
legendary in the title are usually the
stories there's simply no way it exists
but that room would be still after
that's what's just the story no go to
any stable and Hyrule you'll find people
excited about the room at Beast Stables
are places where information gathers if
it weren't true you wouldn't hear about
it in so many Staples oh even if I grant
you that we don't stand to gain anything
by finding this Roman piece
with his weapon is legendary of Britain
useless
Stables to gather information tracked on
the room with Beast sure okay uh maybe
not now
go by horse or maybe not
uh this one or this one's closer
I'll go with that one
the game would recommend you to go to
the South Region last
I think I saw a map
um when I was looking for the Skyview
Towers
uh which ones are where and close which
ones are close to me when I was
exploring
and it marked them with numbers that
felt like numbers of like in which order
you should go to demo in which order the
game wants you to go to them
and yeah that South area
was later we're basically going
from
top left to
right I think and then down and left
again okay is it this thing
I'm looking straight and I'm seeing
something there
what isn't it there
I saw the wrong one I guess
oh there's something funky there too
but what is that then
is that a different mural that I'll find
later
wait wait
and we're looking for murals and that's
a geoflip isn't that just the same thing
wait what I mean the murals on the
ground the grass paintings
I'm confused
there's not a mural
oh
that shrine
can I go to the shrine first
foreign
[Music]
I'll go there and we can always jump off
the cliff
the table to the left
oh well
[Music]
I don't think so not right now
why does this field so big and empty and
there's just one random he knocks laying
in it and some in some trees in between
laughs
dive bomb nah
if I read that correctly
another Helix oh yeah I guess he ripped
out all the trees those are the only
ones that are left over
[Music]
here's the reason Fire and Ice Queen
Fire and Ice huh Fire and Ice you say
Fire and Ice
Song of Fire and Ice
what is this
[Music]
I'm gonna melted so much that it fits in
there huh what if I just do it with my
fire
okay
well plenty I think
geez
wonderful
there's another door there
oh that's the end the shrine okay
go back
oh
it
wait
can I
I can't take that one right so I'll take
one that's produced up there
oh no
that was Tiny
all right
no I'm pretty small but I think it was
already
work
or what I need it for
um do I just fly back
I guess so
so I'm thinking to put it up on the
second level so I can climb it
here
know with my special tool
foreign
[Music]
I could attach the donut spare to the
donut spare
don't like spare spare holy [\h__\h] that
thing is long
okay but that was just for the chest
what about
the actual thing we have to do what
what
thank you
I can pull Vault now
that would be fun if you could do that
I don't know man I don't know
I'm tired I'm getting tired
but
let me Brew
what what do you do here
I'm just stupid
it's been five hours
oh my my Obits only says two hours I
don't even know how long it really was
it doesn't feel like more than five
hours
there's a panel at the top that you can
glue
[Music]
ah
I I bought
that was part of it and just it was
brighter because of the light
so
what do I need it for though
do I wanna surf on it do I want to stop
the fire
foreign
[Music]
I don't know what this will be used for
but
I feel like
this is a bit too wobbly
uh good luck
oh it works
[Music]
and then
I don't even see like anything we have
to solve
fire Maybe
ah there's a
h
something
I don't know
if I'm seeing it right or what I'm
seeing
ah it's a button
that couldn't be pushed because of the
fire okay
wonderful
I was easy I just didn't see it
I didn't see a lot of things
[Music]
are you an only one with a big ice block
mine was pretty small it worked fun
that would have taken you so long really
damn you so you're so good at flattering
me
or is that Pooch if you have a friend a
dog may lead me to something interesting
yep I've also tried that yesterday
blue Nightshade oh for stealth wonderful
oh my God you scared me
especially when you're like
in your Shadow form that is actually
kind of creepy
not like a ghost yeah
good that I have a really long spare
I don't need any of the arms I think
I only need the extra things thank you I
was going here because I thought maybe
there's a court up here but no
no
no there's an arrow though
that's also nice to have
but maybe there's one easy
oh all right
swell
can't enter it
it's corrupted
oh wait wait no you could enter it
should we try
I think
oh but don't you think maybe they'll be
those monsters again the hands the hands
okay I just had a shrine so it just
saved so even if something bad happens
oh oh
those are underground because that goes
pretty [\h__\h] deep
oh it is
[Music]
yep it is well
well that lady will be [\h__\h] that's scary
that lady will be very surprised when I
tell her
that this world leads into the
underground I hope she doesn't check
this one out before I can tell her
are we trying to go straight to the
light
I can't see [\h__\h] but
you light up the area but before I land
who knows what
I'll be landing at
uh wait I'm
my brain can't process
did I go past of course I did
hi baby
stamina
[Music]
[\h__\h] I'll go in again nonetheless
oh oh
very convenient
there it is
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I can use
one right
the [\h__\h] is it
what
ah has passed the food
okay save the land
ing Lightroom is that the shrine that we
just did because apparently all these
plants are connected with the shrines
above
where the [\h__\h] is this
wow that's really far
but I don't think I really want to spend
much time here right now at least we
activated it
way
that is a different statue than the
others I yesterday when I was exploring
I found even more of those
um
digging people's statues who the [\h__\h] is
that
maybe root a treat why is it up so hard
well yeah I found more of those but this
one's new
is this a
[Music]
should I already take a picture of it
because probably we'll get another Quest
huh one of those
wait the face doesn't look like a bird
the face looks more like a lizard
what is this
should I know these because the other
one looked very familiar
this one
oh my God oh my God
I'm so scared
life is just the whole jump scaling I
don't know how to live one day one day
I'll get a heart attack from something
completely self-induced ah my microphone
oh man so scary Hold Me can't be hold me
um
that was a
very concerning well okay let's go to
the place where we actually need to go
but actually that was a good a good
Discovery though
what is that bull
oh yeah
Mario's Sunshine fluid to clear the Ooze
hell yeah
I love Mario Sunshine I mean
I was struggling through it
but
because it's still like such a a game
that's so deep in my heart you know
[Music]
has a very special place in my heart
people have a bad conscience can start
more easily and has nothing to do with
that with me getting startled nothing
I don't know what I would have a bad
conscience about
but you know
you know I don't I don't know I don't
know what I would I could have done
just like you know with the police like
it makes me nervous that the police was
at my apartment
well first time the first moment I heard
that I was like what did I do you know
I didn't do anything but still
what am I supposed to do here there's no
input here why is she late
maybe I'll go to the
very front of it
I purposefully went all the way to the
other side thinking
that's where I should go it turns out
is that the front goddamned
of course she is
she's there I'm late of course yeah yeah
makes sense because that old lady who
just told me that she's gonna leave soon
not now
you're telling me she was faster than me
I mean okay I fell into a well and I did
a shrine yeah but still I feel like she
still wouldn't be
faster than me
oh where are you at forgotten Cotton
Bowl
yeah I think I remember this from
Dom tando's playthrough
the one I watched uh four times
oh
oh wait that's her isn't it
or at least it's him
hi Alex
she fell
oh link I'm so pleased that you've come
here as well to be honest lady input
deduce that there is something related
to the Geo gloves here it took some
effort for us to get up here but we
managed it and then lady Emperor grew
impatient the moment I took my eyes off
her she went deep into the temple all by
herself oh my God
how can you how can she be just
wandering off without you noticing she's
slow
once I finished mowing the balloon I
plan to hurry after her oh my God
useless
this looks I wait wait where could she
have even gone like she can't just jump
down here
where could she have gone
that makes
maybe she really fell
oh what the [\h__\h]
I'm curious this this Forgotten Temple
uh
the inside of it is this a what like in
breath of the wild does it look the same
[Music]
dragon bone 24.
it had Guardians inside
I was filled with guardians but like the
structure was the same
oh can I climb that
yes well sorta
was there something here though like
storm related or was it just like
some place you could go
I guess I'll go down and fight
there's nothing really here
oh it's a bit Story related
foreign
I gave you some time to prepare oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh I'm gonna just quickly roast some
things
[Music]
maybe this time they won't even fall
down ouch
yes
ah
okay not everything cooked
we got pretty close to Greatness
foreign
[Music]
I don't buy it
okay we could fly over and we could
build a bridge
I choose to fly over help me
don't run away
I pressed too eagerly we're now building
a bridge
plans change sometimes
no not there
right
also wander off randomly though
it's too short
oh wait here is not sure
it's coming
what about me
back
but from the other one
tomato soup short come on
unbearable Heat
something else
[Music]
oh there he goes
he doesn't shoot very often because I
guess that would be overpowered
I understand
was this one stick
wooden shield now that is two
who do you think I am I'm not gonna run
around with a shield that only has two
defense
too weak
not gonna bother with something like
that
[Music]
don't tell me that this is like a uh
like we find impa and then we have to
walk her all the way back so I I have to
I'm gonna regret that having built those
bridges
nah
wooden Shield crying I know what's this
on top
hey
well that's more how I like go to Dragon
Ball shoot 25 man let's go
[Music]
good night wow it's time to bed good
night sleep well hope you have happy
dreams Ascension is a thing yeah but not
for her
by the way guys speaking of Ascension I
finally recently I haven't been watching
that much
I haven't been watching that much um
Charmed
but I finally arrived at the season
uh after
Pro dies and season four now so hey
pet is finally part of it oh my God
I'm excited
you know for
like a series that already like
established it with a certain cast and a
certain set of characters where it isn't
normal that one of the main
characters would leave the show it's
just not normal right
like unlike something like Game of
Thrones or so or important characters do
tend to die
but for a show like that I find it
really incredible how they they
continued
on in such an epic way that like people
think back and many people prefer
Charmed even after Prue died over before
she died and that really tells you they
did a great job
as story writers and all that
not the first time shine of the Hardy
left the show really also I can't find a
history down here
[Music]
there's nothing down here either but
there's a ladder
oh yeah
the other one they killed her off
because she left the show yeah they
killed her off
um but I'm guessing they didn't really
know yet
because they would kill her off at the
end of season three because
um
then they could have already prepared it
better I would say
season four it just starts with everyone
mourning proves death and in connection
right after season three but it doesn't
make hundred percent sense and probably
when I was watching it as a teenager I
probably didn't really understand where
the [\h__\h] she went and like did I miss an
episode or something because
this is confusing
she left Beverly Hills what's that I
don't know that show I'll wait this up
up there there's something
another one
yeah but I just I mean I liked uh I like
to show both with and without Pro but I
just want to say like it's really really
impressive that
they managed to
continue
the epicness
of
a long running show
keeping the audience happy
keeping them entertained and satisfied
when such a huge change happens
a soap opera Beverly Hills 90 what the
[\h__\h] is that name who needs that number
why wasn't it just called Beverly Hills
one
some mushrooms don't need that
oh you got bullied by your family when
you once Charmed oh man
I'm so happy nowadays when I talk about
charm there's many people who are like
oh I watched that too oh my God
Nostalgia oh my God oh my God
I mean I understand there's a lot of
dorkiness and all that about it
it's not it's not a perfect show it's
very tacky
but it's my childhood okay
I'm sorry
I don't even need you but you look so
cute so I wanted to take you with me
that or life doesn't matter hi infa
oh link thank you again for your help
with the balloon I believe there's
something related to the jail live
somewhere within this Temple
with something you will you watch with
your mom oh sweet that's cute
I'm searching but so far it has been and
buying the Champions here are enormous
so it will be a difficult task at best
where could it be
I know I'm just gonna do the shrine
really quick
are those hour long season summaries on
YouTube worth watching of Charmed you
mean why would you watch that just watch
the show or do you just want a rough
understanding of to show that I am
talking about
yeah
um
no no no no that's just for someone
looking back on it maybe not not if you
didn't watch it I did the same well to
understand me better
no
what is this Tetris
oh
this guy
this guy this is a this is like how you
solve some Kodak puzzles
okay literally that's what they want me
to do huh they want me to make the same
shape as the other one
what do I look like to you preschooler
huh
I'm having a really bad angle right now
otherwise this would be no problem
foreign
that tries to force a star shape into a
square or so I don't know
there we go
except um yeah a toddler
uh okay do we got more like this
well hello
[Music]
hey we got another flame a bitter I
don't think I'm gonna take it with me
though because I don't have space for it
anyway
could you melt this kind of metal
[\h__\h] help that ain't even supposed to
be open
no it's not a flame pair it's a flame
Club
what oh my I I thought it was a sapphire
okay rupees are fine too
um why are there so many
interesting things lying around
was it just for him to fight buff
seems so
curious very curious
do I need all of this
don't like this piece makes me angry
it induces anger
oh maybe I need all of them
beautiful wait before
I use all of them
saw
unbelievable you need to
how am I gonna get up there
oh wait I can attach them too
easy reward
s
[Music]
so far
I haven't
really found a use for those at all
have you guys I mean surely there is a
good reason why they think that the
thing we would want
oh yeah oh yesterday I saw the Mecca
that someone built which is like
um
I feel like this piece has to go here
[Music]
which like you can ride at the top and
you walk around and then you can attack
things but I think the only way of
attacking is with the the fire
experience so it's actually not as
powerful as it looks like
um but it's very impressive but yeah I I
have to say
I'm sorry like okay people having fun
with it and that's cool
but
I I don't know that's like it's really
weird that you're able to do this and
it's on the game it doesn't feel like
Zelda that's weird but okay I will just
ignore that completely
it's not
like what I will be doing
in this game I can tell you that
I don't even have the patience for it
anyway
it's impressive
but will I play around with it hell no
wish I got it
ignoring the best part but you guys
build some cool stuff and then show it
to me and impress me okay
have fun with it but it's not my kind of
thing y'all you know I don't like
building in in Minecraft either
but Minecraft is about building I I get
that
sell that going that far I mean
developers think or like expect
people would go this far like how the
[\h__\h] can you even build that like such a
functioning
Mecca that you can control and walk
around with and you're like perfectly
protected it doesn't do much damage but
I feel like you're perfectly protected
in it
this is when the six years of
development went into
a motorcycle
that's interesting that I could get
behind but I don't know if you guys all
saw what I saw but the mecca is like
five times the size of Link
like tall really really
funky
walking cat no thank you but if you can
build that can you build an airplane or
like a helicopter or something like like
actually not just a platform that can
fly but something like really it looks
like what it's supposed to be you can of
course you can well I don't know
I don't want to put that much effort
into my builds I don't want to be
Billing at all
sorry I'm not gonna be building in this
game
some things are okay some simple things
are okay but
otherwise
save bills and all the buildings
hopefully
I would hope so you oh wait I saw pepper
is always a fire
there he is
horrible
berries and cool
if I give Betty's berries to Cobble
will that revive my favorite Idol group
of Alton
and I will be happy again because Normal
shoes are back
[Applause]
and I'd be able to live through where
are we going where are we going are we
going outside
oh
see ya
oh it takes time to go back down too
[Music]
I just wanted to see if there's
something there but it turns out no
oh
that's uh the same structure where we
got our tear out of now that I think of
it this is also flower shaped just like
the flower Island that I found
that had no function for me yet
stones in the grave oh my God
wait I'll look at it in a second I'm
just I'm curious wait
could you see this in breath of the wild
too
all right it's the Puro pad or does she
that's the Chica and the the Chica Stone
[Music]
is that oh
that's the tear that's a tear
maybe that's new because the tear is
there
it's black by the statue
I mean this is also gotta be new right
oh
wait so no reaction
what do I do do I just walk in there I'm
gonna cut scene or so
yep
got a feeling for that
wait it's a map there's a small Castle
cute
ah this place
oh lady input let's head down we must
investigate up close
how are they going down
oh
there up on the walls all right that was
not geoglyphs
um what could those mean ah
ah the one the first one we found and
the next one next to it I also already
saw from the sky
I believe the one we saw first was the
geoglyph on the left edge of the wall
as for the next painting
yeah okay the map even shows where they
are
and this near retail Village oh
wait how is that
like crazy scary monster looking thing
up there at the
peak of that mountain where I went to
because I didn't see it
I didn't even see it
I can hardly believe what my eyes it
isn't behold
who could have guessed this old ruin
still held such secrets
so the east of it oh okay
in the valley
you just said that the geoglyphs
appeared all over Hyrule during the
upheaval when Princess Zelda went
missing how are they connected to these
images here there is no time toggle let
us hurry and investigate the remaining
jail Cliffs oh they did but perhaps you
should rest a bit before such a drawing
Journey
link if you happen to see a geoglyph
during your travels I urge you to
investigate this matter as well if more
strange Visions are waiting at the other
Gucci who lives just like the one you
already experienced well
perhaps they will provide clothes that
could lead us to Princess Zelda yeah
that's why I want to check out
this one immediately
because I know where it is
also implant you're gonna be there when
I go there or what
hope so
whatever now from above I would like to
take a picture
how do I get back up
there is stairs
oh
wait
could I not just use the ascending
functions anyway okay
uh
[Music]
there's an order to the gloves if you
want to do that that way
do I have to
[Music]
let me take it like this
more useful
only if you want the cuts in order oh
yeah that would be nice also how is she
not gonna comment about this
Let's ignore this one completely
well anyway it was like somewhere here
right so I'm gonna go fly there now is
it like
stupid which one is the SEC the next one
I should go to then
lpnt there is no need to play it because
I'm playing it
oh
the one near Rita Village
there's a specific what I should do
um
the order ah
yeah okay wait
yeah then that was the next one is that
one that I'm thinking of
and then there's the weird Ganon looking
one
oops Yeah
yeah or is it nah wait no no it was the
pure pad
yeah
pure pad uh weird thing one weird thing
too
um
uh yeah no Peter Pan I know I know I
know I already corrected myself okay
then I can I can go right I can I'm
ready to go
and she will be there hopefully
yeah yeah yeah the castle looking one is
the one that I was looking at when I was
flying and I'm like hey look at this
shouldn't I go there
um I
[Music]
think
okay
oh wait that's the Ghana one wait and
that's that's this one that one I mean
but hey we also see the gun one now how
did I not see that one before
fall too fast
wow I'm flying I Believe I Can Fly
I believe I can touch the sky
[Music]
oh
my God
yay
I see a little house over there
is there a stable
unless I'm blind I do not feel stable
oh I see a little Camp don't know if
that's from humans or
in padoko no that looks like an enemy
camp
aign I found it
far
away should I just
straight go here
oh yeah
yup
[Music]
salmon
eggs
[Music]
foreign
German
read the subtitles guys
stemmed
okay
[Music]
foreign
oh
hmm they're stint
is
[Music]
her hair's so fluffy
her voice sounds also like a Zelda voice
[Music]
and
it's for
eign
foreign
moment
to bring
me
yeah
[Music]
I want to go straight to the next one
but I don't know I don't know where it
is
I want more story though
what do I am I able to go to it
what was the next one chica slate
[Music]
I want more I am hungry for more
is it worth exploring this area where am
I
um I was wondering if there is a field
around here too but if the taban fails
are here
oh it's about the frontier
would be nice to have the Skyview Tower
of this area
I don't see any rice growing anywhere
though
I'm gonna check out that house though
really quickly
find the sky view Tower yeah that would
be nice
I wonder maybe if I go over the two I
can see it
I see it uh-huh and I see a weird
prison box
uh wait
yellow yellow
[Music]
whoa It's so far holy [\h__\h]
um
trying did I do that one
foreign
that I still want to do I'll mark it
with this remember that guys if I ask
you what it means
tell me it's a shrine
is that the one I mocked oh yeah it is
okay I'll go to the house
I'm paying it because I'm not planning
on going there right now oh there's
enemies here
oh
nice Dodge let's go shush
oh it's a white jelly Shield
Peppa
[Music]
anyone else being a lag lag in the
Stream or in the game
yo someone's inside
I don't worry I got rid of the monsters
maybe someone's come to help what are
you saying why would anyone help us this
place is crawling with my
oh I I actually yeah I really came
because I was wondering about the random
house in the middle of nowhere
the monsters I can't hear them anymore
come on Joko what's taking you so long
quick you gotta unlock the door oh okay
hello oh hello
I got a crust reward you defeated the
monsters
I took a break in this here A vacant
house to get away from the cold and
before we knew it monsters had us
surrounded
hey you should be nice thank you thank
you oh my God okay ever since still
people they've been more and more
monsters we were trying to be careful
but I don't know how to thank you enough
please take this
all those cold resistance when would I
need those guys
maybe if I wanna the only thing I can
think of is when I when I uh want to
wear different armor because it's more
protective
and I need to protect myself from the
cold but
like what
You Were Meant to come here by the first
time
eh
really
hmm
but I already had the the pants from up
there and that was enough for a long
time I didn't need
anything any medicine until I arrived at
the Rito Village
[Music]
and I Rockets are hot air everyone to
help you get up for good views
are you just saying it for good views
for having you know a romantic time up
there with beautiful view at sunset or
are you telling me this because
you want me to see something specific
[Music]
why don't you tell me I told you I know
how to do it thank you though
oh yeah yeah thanks though thank you
[Music]
ah complete okay
besides that I guess you could cook in
here
well it's empty
okay
um
a
stable would be nice to ride there there
where
holy [\h__\h]
and what that's so close to the Hebrew
mountains
look
could I drop myself
from the wind Temple entrance
nah because when I when I fall there it
always like respawned me didn't it or
does it not do that anymore because the
hurricane is gone
yo big brain
of course that is romantic I mean
showing a lady a beautiful view that is
normally not something you can look at
under normal circumstances of course it
is romantic
laughs of course it is
[Music]
back to the wind Temple
and we are going to
jump ship
before it's too late
oh the cube is I wonder if you could you
could totally reach the cube from here
what is on the cube
is it a new
a new uh generation of whole life
members
where do we go where do we go
immediately got distracted
um
oh I can't reach that one
going
huh
where is that oh God it's so far okay I
don't see it
I won't see it from here
um
no white is closed I just I'm just blind
maybe it's the clouds above
oh wait I'm there
oh I'm there it's kind of confusing when
you're up so high
oh easy easy
look at this dance
oh
yeah
oh this one's a bit difficult to get to
if you don't
go there the way we're going here
easy mode
he does don't grow Skyview Tower
[Music]
okay open the game against
show me the map
interesting mating dance romantic
birthday it's not a bird mating ritual
no it's just Birds having fun
among Birds
I want a snack on something
Japanese rice crackers Sam Bay happiness
[Music]
you got a burger oh my God
give me
along the road there's a stable in
between what oh my God huh
in between the sour and the shrine
in the Forgotten Temple
along the road there's a stable
well now I don't need it anymore because
I flew to the
describe you a tower that's why I was
saying oh is there a stable because I
want to ride there but I can just fly
there so never mind now
um
that that square that funky square up
there
is that maybe
yeah that makes no sense that the mirror
would be there
but probably on that Big Empty field
up there in the top middle
ah
so that cube is directly on top of the
other
Square
no not tips I'm eating
um
Japanese rice crackers senbei
very different from the rice crackers
that I know from Western world
I take the opportunity again oh there's
that one but we shouldn't go to this one
yet huh
put that spoiling me
cause you guys say we should go by order
and that one
is very late but it looks like a gun on
related one doesn't it
reminds me of some form of Gangnam
that one's a huge spoiler man they
should make it very clear to go I mean I
guess they did in the right order
um
actually I don't know if I'm in the mood
for an island
what's this
oh
this is a jumping no this is one of
those control thing is
oh
okay okay there's still new tools being
implemented I'm not in the mood though
I am not in the mood
snow field
hmm
wouldn't have rice with it rice doesn't
grow in snow
there's a taban for plane that I'm
looking for still
when I'm in the mood somewhere between
this and the next stream
I would say
oh it's about a great great bridge
is like everywhere maybe it's down here
why is there so many birthdays these
days happy birthday too that's about
happy birthday too that's about happy
birthday dear that's about happy
birthday to you
[Music]
um congratulations
what should I check out is there an
interesting place here
oh I saw that dragon in other places too
is that a very challenging enemy it
looks challenging
definitely a new thing
[Music]
yes incredibly so oh really what is that
swirl in this in the is that a crook
go away from the Dragon
foot away
let's do a shrine oh this is
that what you meant maybe not
for this and funny coincidence
oh there's a quest you get at the stable
involving beating that enemy
oh [\h__\h] also maybe all of the other
dragons like this
you also get a quest at the stable
shrine
but then I want to do my story where um
where do we go next are we done with
this like region
where did the game tell me to go next to
tell me to go now anymore now so should
we just follow one of those four markers
that we were shown in the beginning
where we decided to go to the one
with little village first
okay
any of the three oh well okay I think we
would go to one on the top right of the
map courage to fall
I've got courage to fall
[Music]
subtitle
why are you waiting for me do you have
cards to fall
[Music]
don't drop my bike
oh
took you a little to figure out I'm
currently on this one please solve it
for me you are
a coin this is inside you're following
this like Wherever I Go
oh
it's like a maze so far at least
can I do this
oh [\h__\h] I don't know
I accidentally shoot
I want to do the cool thing where you
jump and then you go slow motion and
then bam
really strong hit
up
damage
I can't show my skills to do
I am embarrassed how's your costumes
be careful yes
I'm going
let me use one of my
millions of materials and craft the
weapon how about we
craft something like this
oh that is a sick looking ax yeah
I want to make another one
because we got this one too
sturdy long stick
how about
this moblin horn
y
I don't know how it's more like a fork
but surely it will do a lot of damage
I don't know
okay more Mission Impossible
not a challenge unless my stick
gets in the way
[Music]
God that's good damage
nice nice nice
17 and 21.
you guys also have like an overload of
items because you you get so many things
thrown at you to craft to combine and
all that
it's like
I don't actually need that money
maybe I should sell some
gonna need some for upgrading armor oh
really these kind of items
um okay
I hope I'm not like unknowingly wasting
certain items though
[Music]
there are items things but you haven't
come across them yet oh my God okay
we need a ball here
what is this this place is huge
huh
I mean
wait
before I go there oh there is the ball
okay
but
this door this is weird
there's like a looks like a keyhole even
[Music]
can I attach it no because
um
in some Shrine you know I just suddenly
was introduced to these like steaks that
are in that color you know which ones I
mean
I was like I I didn't know what they
were so I didn't know how to use them
took me a YouTube tutorial to understand
how they could be used that you can like
melt them into things
you know so I thought this one was also
something that like melts
[Music]
I already walked through that no way
look I see the the shrine entrance
I don't remember seeing the ball pit
there I just ignored it maybe
courage to fall so I guess I fall here
it doesn't really
I've been here before though
yeah I've been here before huh
why do I need to fall
ah wait
um
wait wait wait wait wait
uh maybe I know
let me cook
I think I know where to fall
or do I
uh no I don't
know
I need a key yeah no
[Music]
uh
that's why also where I came through
ah
[Music]
the lasers
foreign
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] that's
and when is it good to fall and when is
it bad
hear what's bad just so you know
what the [\h__\h]
that's fine that's not even
I think you have to test that you can't
even know
by looking at it it's a [\h__\h] trap
okay really
well
I mean
what about the others oh I came out
right in the right place uh
I just opened oh
wow we never worked with keys before
now we bring this ball with us
wow
and that's it is there isn't there like
an extra chest still
this was just for the key but normally
you don't expect for items
ah wait yeah
well there must be
because there's two spots to put
oh there's a glider
oh what for
is
here
is that how I send the ball down there
[Music]
I don't I don't I didn't even see any
chairs open
no one really needed anyone
just now this ball better not fall
good
let's go
let's go let's go
um
come down come down come down
oh
see I shouldn't have even
tried to de-attach it I thought I could
take it with me but of course I can this
is just like the [\h__\h] with the Kodak
[Music]
so it's the same
I got away lucky this time
but
is there a chest there maybe
[Music]
I don't care maybe the real chest was
really that one and there's just no
reward here
the middle one of the lasers
maybe uh [\h__\h] ah [\h__\h]
oh well
is it something good please tell me it's
not something good
who was stuck here who said that they
were stuck now you're hopefully not
stuck anymore and maybe you can actually
get the chest unlike me
arrows okay
my real chest is just off screen below
the visible area
okay
stop the shrine
snowflake Staples
we are a recipe
oh is that Curry
[Music]
is that that looks like milk because I
bought it before butter
wheat meat the pepper and milk
I want to remember this though
I guess it's a stew I know that with the
golden and
spice
uh you can make curry
what are you doing thank you wow you
have some new stuff
yeah your clubs really are not
no you always got the same stuff your
clothes are not for this kind of weather
uh selling
[Music]
we're getting the money that we need for
future clothes
oh
yeah give me the other one too
okay almost a thousand
[Music]
now let's go thank you for the Super
Chat
let's go to uh
[Music]
let's see let's go to let's go to
I want to go to the next area
um let's check
the quest
is this one
so
I think here would be good right
[Music]
I don't know what they call this region
Joshua and pure will tell you the best
route really okay should we go there
first John
[Music]
Alden
grones what do you call them in English
is it
somebody says it's aura I thought that's
where the groans are
guns groans oh okay
wait I got four shrines again I'm gonna
get something
should I get stamina I guess I should
cut Domino you guys are very insistent
on getting stamina
[Music]
oh man that means I have to do a lot of
voices like this uh to voice the
characters
it'll be a little bit hard on my voice
Maybe
I mean it's not so bad for my voice but
it's hard to do this
[Music]
give me stop me now
sorry thank God thank God it doesn't
give it to me immediately
amen
[Music]
that's not really husky
squeaky Gardens I can't do maybe a child
coronia
[Music]
wow wow
we're almost soon coming full circle
get it
[Music]
okay let's talk to pram
is she here even
also I I collected some of these things
some pose but apparently you can't
really do anything with an E yet
[Music]
I'm sorry Tower you're not the right one
for the job oh
oh is it is it about the post
pause you've got to let me cast my line
through the devs too I'm capable of the
suffering some don't I script who else
can tackle that stuff ah I mean your
skills would be super helpful to me
you're the one in charge of the donut
server team after all but aren't you
heading up to the ring ruins and
investigation
in the kakadiko village anyway taro
that's where your focus should be those
following ruins are huge and exciting
big enough to see from Lookout Landing
so please finish your work there before
asking to join a new research but would
you read the first Sunday history
debates too juicy to pass up
what a guy
ah it starts man who's someone else here
for the job already I guess it's a lost
cause
I'll head back to kakaiko Village and
just stare up at those ring ruins
[Music]
yeah I hope you'll stay for many many
more months
you didn't get this cutscene uh why I
wonder how why
maybe you
arrived at the wrong time
Tower is such an amazing person and he's
a third-grade archaeologist too I have a
cat hair in my mouth
uh
uh what [\h__\h] I don't know if I got no
[Music]
no maybe I got it now
he was already in kakariko for you oh
maybe you went to kakorikutu kakaliko
too early
nah it's still there I'm just gonna I'm
just gonna drink it now
[Music]
yummy foreign
21 months incredible
[Music]
thank you
but he loves online research so much
that he'll bought from a project to
chase any new discoveries I've been
looking for some for someone to help
with with my investigation you'll be the
best one I actually already have a lot
of new info for you I have a picture for
you but you probably don't care about it
yet
let's talk again this way okay okay
we'll get faster faster faster faster
why you so slow
oh I could even pick those up
I want that
please give me huh
um
[Music]
well then
yay
you're still not done walking
[Music]
how about now because you moved like one
inch
okay
so remember the fragment I had the one
that showed the single mysterious figure
wait a second
they are all around your map I thought I
would find the only way there's one
different one
but that's not the one that I saw where
is the one that I saw I found more
fragments among those things our server
team brought back from the dance
and guess what they fit together like
five little pieces oh wait oh
yeah at first you only had like one
small piece of this oh
just look
I just want to say thank you thank you
kiss your eyes upon this amazing mural
and maybe put your weapon away so you
can see it better this scene shows that
there's a whole series of statues down
there like the one you found for me last
time but what really caught my attention
is the way they're already oh
each figure is pointed out toward the
next one in the series oh that's where
they were pointing until it ends of the
last statue facing a final destination a
building that looks like a temple mm-hmm
also see the those large ears on the
figure at the front of the building
that's got to be one of the Zona
and then there's that strange hand
symbol that seems to be responding to
whatever that zonai is doing
so to collect my thoughts on all of this
I'm pretty sure if you follow the case
of each of those statues down there
you'll reach that structure
was it really in a circle like this
because that would mean
[Music]
um
well I'm also putting into the
temple-like building holds something of
zonai origin I've heard that the Zone I
will with mysterious Powers I wonder if
this correlates to those powers of
course all this is still just
speculation on my part so that's why you
come in only to find the temple
structure depicted in the mural
initially I figured I could just go
myself so like I have a bunch of
problems and supplies but they pulled
the kid card on me so I couldn't go
so you go now oh thank you huh
oh they're gone oh they're actually gone
any messages
I like how it disappeared from the table
okay
another distracting Quest
so much distraction
you must dance I still don't have any
more products than I feel like I didn't
collect a single one since I met you
damn it I was so bad at collecting
codecs
okay
um
we're going here right they got rid of
my quest again
we're going
I'm going there so maybe I should go
over here on the way we could pick up
this
I would like a horse though
maybe I'll find a
a stable nearby
hello Kiana hello
this one is main star plus two yeah
don't worry I won't do it
um off screen
um
maybe I'll
maybe I'll try to follow the statues
because probably gonna be a long
distance until the place and once I find
it that's that's where I'll stop doing
my thing
hmm horses
hmm
I got a new horse
or is there a stable close by wait
cherry tree
[Music]
oh you're quite a handsome boy aren't
you to meet in such a romantic place
could you be the vote I was destined to
fall in love with no no I can tell just
from the look on your face you did not
come here and search for your one true
love that's too bad but in some way in
some way everything I'm doing here is
for my one true love Zelda
but until then let me tell you a rumor I
heard about cherry blossom trees
apparently there's a strange creature
called a Satori that is sometimes seen
near such trees Satori
never seen it myself but I really want
to I also heard that the Saturday likes
fruit I guess I should have brought some
kind of fruit with me huh any fruit
there's a lot of fire fruit around here
but I want to keep it from myself
does any fruit work
and what is the Saturday
I don't see any
thought it was you for a second
[Music]
is it here only sometimes um should I
put down some fruit
oh wait I probably have to I'm probably
gonna put it on this like offering wait
huh
[Music]
Endura carrot
is it the the thing that we saw in
breath of the wild oh no way
same thing
oh special horse
oh doesn't mean that I'd ever cherry
tree you can summon this special horse
and use it for a while or
oh
wow
[Music]
again for me this is such a Ghibli thing
glowing locations why
is this thing because it looks like one
of those oh it's a gun
but is it connected to the cave as soon
as it's showing me caves close by
is that giving me an easy way to find
them
what's happening oh there's a bunny
there
bunny there is
dumb
oh so that's why there's several
territories so it only always shows you
um
like the nearby ones and that one
actually seems to be where the treasures
there's a magician there too
maybe we can shoot them with some ice
but this oh this current is really yeah
bye
where's my body
come here
okay try the one shot him again oh what
isn't in that corner I hope it doesn't
it doesn't scare the bunny
or something
okay ice this now
[\h__\h] that makes it more difficult oh
laughs
[Music]
God damn it
ruby sword oh
uh
since I can't sell them anyway I guess
I'll go one of those
basically
alrighty Flawless gameplay
notice um next to Dom tendo a life hack
how to get more rubies
at rupees out of
the bunny
normally you're always like approaching
it
naturally from uh
far away from the cave right you like go
into the cave but if you do it from the
cave it will always run through the cave
so normally it will like run straight at
you
if you like you know in a direct line to
the
to the cave
[Music]
so I'll probably still panic
and mess it up
don't move you little [\h__\h]
but what the [\h__\h] are those drops
didn't even make it to the cave and I'm
still getting the shittiest [\h__\h]
drops ever
really
um
I don't care if the aluminous stones and
goes unless I can
foreign
[Music]
is that the right kind of rock I hope so
yeah okay
can I know that here too oh oh yeah
oh my God it's almost broken again
I didn't get anything out of this [\h__\h]
there's another one
but no
yeah but there's so much
there's so many luminous stones
maybe for another time I remember if I
did Lube in the stones here gems
feels like the hands could show up again
please don't
I'm so traumatized by that man
oh oh that killed him immediately
enough
[Music]
that's it in this cave just a lot of
stone okay I mean that's good
I know
[Music]
thanks for the spare
this one I can't reach though
to blow it up
okay
oops
I can't even blow up the whole thing I
think or or I could oh this one was
important
it leads to
another cave deeper inside
[Music]
I just got sick because my controller is
shaking what
no oh okay at least this one doesn't
have you know like a top okay okay I can
do this but without one I don't have
for this one I can climb this one I can
climb
[Music]
okay
one hit really one hit
okay okay cool
um cool
yeah
it was was it this what what
was it this
that wasn't something I couldn't reach
where am I
I know it's there it's there
that's it only awaken after you open
that up
but I do kind of want to fight them
especially because he's like easier to
fight
wait also I wasn't even fully healed
maybe I can even tank ahead
if
if I feel myself
thank you
don't fall off don't fall off
let's go
this is so weak can I do it with
something else
okay that's barely the damage must go
yeah I'm already very trained in this
what
even do anything
what killed me hello Raiders what killed
me
[Music]
then right you guys don't know either he
didn't fall down nothing happened I had
plenty of space
I have plenty of space there I'm telling
a little scam
lies lies lies lies lies
oh is it already after I did yep yep yep
I'll do it again I'll do it again
and again and again and again and again
because it's not fair
and I'll start up
[Music]
okay yeah shoot nowhere you're not doing
any damage
[Music]
this is what I would always wait for you
know on the fight that I told you about
at the beginning of the Stream
foreign
[Music]
look at it
[Applause]
I'll do it again
I hated one he just randomly climbs up
something and I don't want him to climb
them
I can do it
[Music]
scramble scramble scramble
scramble scramble
um
scramble scramble scramble scrap
scramble
[Applause]
okay at least I stayed on top okay
it makes it a lot easier
no just don't die
I see that coming
[Music]
give up yet
who would I be to give up huh
I'm takanasi Chihuahua
okay part-time Warrior
I can do this
same thing same thing
climbing over
foreign
[Applause]
already failure
quick recovery baby
let's go Amber
wow that took him a long time okay just
don't mess it up okay Mama
bro it's frozen baby
[Music]
I told you I could do it
I knew I could do it I believed it
myself even if he hits me with one hit
who just
just need to not get hit
it's that simple
[Music]
okay before I pick that up and and fuse
it to something
I'm gonna break my weapon on something
else like that
alden's bringing logic yeah
uh
what do we have this one yeah
dropping
oh we still have another bump
there are flowers still here so I think
we're good
what I'm more worried about is having a
weapon to fuse the the big heart onto
okay that is
cleared
is that the entrance
oh yeah I want this one
let's go
oh there's more bombs here too
there's a chance in there as well before
you leave oh yeah yeah I'm going up
there anyway
just didn't go yet because I wanted to
fight
the towel on and this one a million
times easier
then come on I took 15 minutes to beat
because I had no bombs
um
and had I couldn't even climb it no
it was rough
okay I think I know it just feels
gonna get rid of
this one
yeah
and then eventually if I need more
Lumina Stones I'll just come back here
now the platform one because I you guys
are telling me I can
just uh Ascend up there I didn't know
that because it didn't look like there
was even
oh no
no I'm so regretful
that I spent so much time
but I really got good
after a while a dodging his
froze yo
this is the second time I'm getting one
of these but the last one was the shiny
is this one
that looks stupid though on that weapon
last time I fused it I've used it onto a
more fitting weapon I think
you did good thank you you can also
rewind the Rocks they throw oh really
I made it yesterday the platform one
also took her really long
damn
I found it I'm a get yesterday in the
story does someone know anybody who
watched her
and now it's so crazy to watch my
long-ass stream as well
finding Spirit raises your attack power
wow okay let's go
is that the one that they marked from
well that they marked for me
[Music]
no
oh no
the the sign is gone the x is gone so
maybe it was
good second best armor really but it has
only three defense but I guess you can
you can always improve it right later on
the other one was lightning armor I
think
but I mean
you don't even need that so often do you
think I don't mind this
yeah upgrading later would be noise
okay where are we going
here oh well that's far away holy [\h__\h]
can I do that with him today right it's
11 P.M
uh what the [\h__\h]
I'm tired too
why is it why are why I want to stream
24 hours
what the [\h__\h] man
why are there so many dragons here
what
what are they protecting
uh
maybe I'll go there from my own Palm
describe the tower
that kind of stuff anyway like Ugh
no wait that's not even where the
Skyview Tower is but um no
it would be nice to get that oh there's
another platform money one
what does that mean
that painting on the
oh there's a corner
on the ground there's a painting
oh
[\h__\h] I failed let's do it again where'd
that go
I know you have to catch it
my bird friend
tooling by accident
[Music]
but looks like it didn't mess everything
up
[Music]
tomorrow though is a member stream right
at 6 PM I think
[Music]
so
I'm sleeping I'm not gonna challenge
that one now
no way
where am I going that's the wrong way
follow purple
yeah
epic time yeah gosh I'm already so tired
[\h__\h] oh
my eyes are tired but I want to play I'm
so sorry because I didn't think I would
get this addicted
a problem guys
I've been playing for so long yesterday
but don't worry I still I still love the
things I need to do and play I still did
everything on my on my to-do list I did
the scam thing like I called them I I
started looking for clips for home I I
booked my slime Hotel I recorded two
songs I did my weekly schedule I did
another thing I needed to do okay I did
plenty of things oh is that the tower
is that the Tower of wait
I could get there
scamfing yeah yeah the DHL thing
okay I'm gonna go there
and
there's a stable we should go to the
stable and the shrine and then and then
to the Tower
so much to do oh there's a wizard
oh we're gonna ignore the wizard
we already have a flame sword
open trees
oh
I lost her yeah I lost the man
man
this is gonna be such a long play bro
and I don't want to rush it because I'm
really enjoying it but damn guys you're
gonna have to deal with this for a long
time man
uh
count stable
trying
I just saw it
[Music]
I lost track of it wasn't it like right
next to it
[Music]
there's a cave
and some weird balloons
was it on the left side though
this game is fun to watch really I'm
glad wait there's a fairy
[Music]
variable wait the fairy upgrades the
armor right
now I want to go there wait let's get my
horse ah there's the shrine that's my
horse first oh my God oh my God
there's a stage I saw a staging a
different stable too wait I don't have
time for this I don't have this oh give
me my horse give me my horse give my
horse I need to cook after the stream I
mean I couldn't make pizza too be lazy
but I need to cook I really need to cook
[Music]
where the game dragged on
that is true
suddenly 10 more things to do right
no not a harness
of course
[Music]
can you stop talking so much all the
time I don't have time
huh Death Mountain is done erupting huh
okay so lava in the caves okay
[Music]
tiredness
oh thank you guys
oh
[Music]
I'm so tired
where to go first let's go family first
fairy
now there's one of those very bad I mean
what else would it be sorry
what was that a squirrel yeah
huh it'll play until your eyes stop
working well I didn't see the answer
I'm gonna play very long how much how
far did you get what the [\h__\h] is this
all around
hello
[Music]
I know what you are Monster you've come
for my blessing up close and a clothing
enhancement I've heard this land is now
smothered with Gloom and overrun with
monsters oh I'll never hear a musical
trip pass by again and the sweet notes
of its violin player I'm staying sealed
up in my flower but for the rest of
Eternity or until I hear a violin in the
world once more I came here to be close
to a stable where I could offer my
blessings to Travelers but now until I
hear a violin played by a musician in a
troop I can't be bear default of ever
going outside ever again
oh man
oh man I thought I'd be able to see the
fairies the beautiful fairy for the
first time with my very own eyes are you
sure you don't want to come out
huh are you sure
I'm beautiful fairy
okay seems to be like a quest where you
have to get the musicians
well I don't have time for that now
the world's smallest violin maybe I can
get kodaks to play huh they're also
great musicians
oh
okay
let's see if we can do another Shrine
with my current brain capacity
cool way of jumping off
okay what's this one about
rise and fall
it continuous run
please be easy
I know what to do
[Music]
no match for me
oh
thank you
two phones
but that's how you do it right you jump
on that one too right
no no
um
[Music]
that disappeared right in that moment
when I chose the tool though
wait
okay wait I know what to do
I'm just like to move it there on my own
maybe maybe I can go up with the same
one
Zone Knight shield
um
all those buttons
[Applause]
Bring It On
[Music]
yeah pretty simple it's like literally
an entropy Center puzzle yeah I know
right
like I keep on having to think of the
answer presenter because of that I feel
like I have a natural advantage
thanks to playing the enterprisanta
yes
[Music]
I know what to do
hmm
okay
I think
uh it might be like a double thing
that also is a skill I have learned
in my time with entropy Center
putting things on
um twice
you know uh she's considering you know
the times
the many times that I will need it
in the future
[Music]
all of this
all of this I've learned before
basically Andrew Crescenta was my
training Arc
yeah I am a genius
but you know not every genius is natural
I've been trained myself too yes yes
okay
easy peasy that was actually one time
was enough but you know you have to take
it off first
you have to take it off first that is
important that is what I wanted to
demonstrate
yes yes so you can get on first
yes I've done my courses
[Music]
so moving back and forth to this day
I wonder if they'll do something like
that though
like next level [\h__\h] that I've seen an
entry percent
um if they'll do that here too with the
time rewind tool the figures of entropy
Center you could rewind but
uh could you also go forward I'm not
sure anymore but
I feel like maybe you could
it was it was more intricate even than
this in mind I mean it didn't have an
ultra hand tool or did it well it kind
of did
stick things to other things that's for
sure
I'm guessing those path leads to
all the tower
and there's a cave here too
hiya
Yeah well yeah yeah it does go forward
when you let go I guess yeah true true
hey I'm not gonna help you this time
next time maybe oh blood moon beautiful
it's like a
very extreme sunset
um
wow Skyrim horse yeah I'm still here uh
am I
why is there
Ah that's just for overall direction my
battle off just going by foot now
what does the path really lead to the
teller
oh they have a special chest I'm gonna
kill them
foreign
[Music]
hiding from me
I know that weapon still from breath of
the Wild
yo breaking rocks let's go I have space
even
amazing
exactly what I need
um
let's just ignore
the very uh
Gary oh
everything's normal
word going on here this blue monster
I'll just skip it you might have seen it
plenty times now tried to cook during
the blood moon you got really good
criticals
like wildest weird stuff is going on you
mean right before the cutscene hits
oh I feel so bad to kill it
this is like so happy
oh man
but look at that good [\h__\h] me
I'm sorry
it hurts it pains me too
it's gone
oh I hear garone music
I think
it's very groanish for me
wow
baby
true what is this
little stool
oh why is this one so easily accessible
oh that must be a catch there's a person
there
you can't open it or what
hey
oh
by the way an easy solution
is you going to see the sky view Tower
sorry everything around here has been a
mess huh the jungle bone Rose fell to
the sky and I describe it what the [\h__\h]
a night of the lead that curls the hole
at the top of the towel no problem I
need to I need that to be open anyway
I mean the hole at the top is open and
that's not all after the impact the door
got struck too see maybe if you use
terminal inside that would force the
door back open without a way to get
we'll figure it out
figure it out let me
let me
you are stuck what is that a meme
is there is there a hole
but now nowadays at this point the sky
view Towers they always have a catch you
can't just one doesn't simply enter the
sky view Tower
maybe is it at the very bottom
please don't make me go there for
nothing
okay I probably went there for nothing
huh
top
what no I meant because enter From Below
somebody said enter From Below
is that why there are so many uh Falling
Rocks
Swift oh moving speed nice
okay
nice landing
[Music]
they know how to light it up nicely
though
I am inside
and as I said we don't need the top to
be closed so we can just keep that
until maintenance comes
it's okay
I fixed it
ah
yeah okay thank you bye bye
[Music]
here we get our
Migos
[Music]
I think that's the second one that we're
uh
opening up today
[Music]
yeah yeah it is
and one I did off-screen off stream
oh wow look at this
shrine
lava
I don't think I can skip this one no
this one is unskippable I think this
looks like Germany
laughs
[Music]
lots of really tiny
uh Sky Islands
oh
what
they're all connected but
rails and there's
ah
I don't feel like it either I don't feel
like it no I don't wanna
[Music]
mmm
is it possible
for me to reach this
area
by Air transport right now
I feel like no
[Music]
that was that stamina
are you sure
I'm not really getting much closer
there's another Tower there though is
that the other one
I wanna go there
well I'm not going anywhere soon
don't worry don't worry I will um
survive uh I will just eat something
foreign
[Music]
well
I need to heal anyway but hey this place
is very familiar to me
I remember this from breath of the Wild
that's like
where am I
like one of the first places you come in
contact with
before going to the groans
and you're starting to feel like oh damn
it's a bit hot around here
oh there used to be Lava damn
what a glow up oh please don't tell me
we're bringing back the live adult by
whatever thing we need to fix here
but the water looks great now
wait was this lava before for example
[Music]
or a restaurant
look I'm sorry on Wednesday but asking
me to bring you another marbled Rock
roast isn't reasonable how about this
instead these mysterious things were
only discovered after jail people looks
a little strange I know but there's a
hard curio to combine
stole my chef that's where it went
more Muppet Rock Rose is in short supply
and high demand around here everyone
wants to that's barely been keeping up
letting our hottest commodity go to
waste is unforgivable he's really angry
you can make up for it by bringing me a
fresh marbled Rock Rose now I'll get the
thing out of my side
if I was able to get you some clue you
have done it by now I checked out the
cables plus the car trucks just like it
told me I couldn't get anything you know
places like that are way too dangerous
for highlighting like me not my problem
and I don't want that hunk of junk I'm
not letting you off the hook till you
get me a bottled Rock Rose
uh-huh side quest traditional
oh my God
[Music]
yep I've got a lot of exploring to do
off stream
oof
shrine
what time is it maybe maybe time for
another shrine
oh
then I can teleport here
yeah surely we can squeeze in one more
Shrine yeah yeah yeah
hmm
one wouldn't hurt right
man when am I ever gonna Read Super
chats again
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm sorry guys so I guess the floor holy
damn
look at that magma
why is this difficult
you coward a bad
don't fall into the lava
it's very very hot in there
you're gonna melt there oh no who knows
maybe this material
it doesn't melt in magma
we wouldn't know until we tested right
there's a there's a ball there we need
it
over here
why can't you not change the camera
[Applause]
[Laughter]
wishful thinking
I slept
well it's not gonna happen again just
send me more platforms now
come on
oh
first time is the charm slippery lava
yeah I don't know why it was slippery
it shouldn't be okay I will not move
wait a second oh okay okay it's pushing
it with me
uh-huh
oh there's also chest there
I'm I
think
[Music]
oh
hmm
no no no no no no no
no okay I think it's time for me to stop
today huh
yeah
how do you get over there
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
maybe ah we have to like push many
platforms back so we wanna yeah okay
have a good amount
yeah
of stock
maybe this is enough
I should heal
doesn't that look good to you
yeah
yeah okay okay don't worry don't worry I
got it oh strong donut Shield one
don't even get to use any of the other
Shields I don't think Shield seems
[Music]
I can't
I can't anymore today are the platforms
completely stuck no
I can't I'm I'm I'm
I don't know
um I don't know
I don't know I don't know I don't I
don't know
foreign
how about this one
we're gonna reach dad
scary
now
[Music]
welcome to the exciting part guys here
comes the exciting part
What About Us
all platforms move
oh they're really stuck
I've done it
well then can I for safety try not
I'll I'll catch it
I wish I could attach myself so that I
don't always throw myself back down
there
wow
oh we want to have it emerged a little
bit
oh it can even go underneath
I'm on it oh it doesn't move
okay
now move okay
um
foreign
guys
I hope we didn't give a help up yet for
me and my future with this game I'm good
I'm good
I I I'm very good at playing this game
it's been it's been a long day
I'm I'm just a bit you know tired
and the floor is just very slippery
this is just not my fault
uh
oh is that what I see one of those um
controlling mechanisms
it actually looks more like one of those
uh
foreign
oh maybe it does actually spill water it
does doesn't it
fire hydrants
hmm
if I spill a lot or dough
is it gonna
actually
go anywhere
oh yeah it goes our Direction but
and I wanted to put you ah I just make
one platform and then I put this wheel
on so
wind
creationist yes
um
I got it I made one
look does this work
is this with a little bit of wind
[Music]
I don't know if because
magma seems kind of like a very thick
substance doesn't it
can we really fight against this big
current
a little bit of wind
hopefully
it's not very straight oh well
oh it works
it will straighten itself out
has someone ever tried this before
in real life can you no
good maintenance on the ship directly
no problem
you'll melt if you do that's what I
thought
it doesn't seem very realistic
but it definitely was a fun shrine
with many accidental
baths into a really hot hot bath yeah
I can't stop poking it
too aggressive
ain't never Shrine down let's go how
many do I have for you for
because I think I would get another
heart
two no four four that's the wrong side
it is it four or three or two
eh
was it two or four because I don't know
which one is a real son what was the
four four if that was two is it
um
two
what's the four four
I don't know I need four but what was
the there was a number that said four
and it looked to me like a shrine
that was light Roots ah
see that's what I meant yeah okay yeah
it makes sense I do think I have four of
those
it's like a restaurant
[Music]
like it's very hot in here whoa
yeah I should I should stop
I don't wanna and I still even didn't
find the Ryan's man
I really wanted to find some rice
[Music]
military training camp
oh
does this mean
that the mountain has the same stuff
the middle of the mountain is corrupted
like this and it leads into the
underground
Rising far away
maybe I should just play soccer no again
[Applause]
uh
God yeah I need a break
I've been playing for three days
straight basically ah you can't break
this
[Music]
um
okay I'm just gonna leave the stream on
and sleep now okay and I'll see you
tomorrow
hmm
[Music]
nah nah oh you know what I need to do
need to open up whole talk questions
and other things
oh oh
I
need to end this dream there's something
there's something I need to listen to
immediately
[Music]
and it's not my album song no no
no no
okay so everybody
thank you for watching today
my beautiful professional
series of the Kingdom stream have we
made progress I would like to think so
not as much as I thought I would but
probably
a normal amount
can't help it it's it's a big world and
all that hi
hi meow indeed
I yeah I did a whole Temple that's right
and or the whole Ascension to the temple
so it took so much time
Young
that was quite something
yeah I'll do some maybe some side quests
and stuff off screen until the next
stream hopefully if I got time um
yeah it's on Sunday next time it's on
Sunday guys
yeah I love this dream since we're
playing this I'm loving it thank you
yeah trying to get ahead of me please
[Music]
thank you guys you did a fantastic job
today thank you thank you for crazy
drinking well thank you this movie's
telling us it's time to end it for today
yup I need to cook
making it a struggle to stay ahead of
your play for in my own game well you
got a couple days now until the end of
the week
hmm
oh and then oh
you know uh soonish
well
not next week but then soonish after
I'll be at uh Amazon I won't be playing
well a little bit for a couple days but
okay then I'll have time to in the
airplane and all that oh my God
I'm not gonna be sleeping in the
airplane I'm gonna be playing tears of
the Kingdom for the whole airplane ride
oh let's go
yeah yeah it's not that soon
next week I'm still completely here
[Music]
don't worry
a battery pack nah I can charge in the
airplane I think
they
a lot of airplanes nowadays have USB
sockets but uh
get rid of the normal electric electric
socket surfing that's actually a problem
if I want to charge my switch
I'm gonna charge it somewhere
[Music]
is there a USB charger for the
uh
for the switch
huh
come whatever I need to go
together
there's also so much to do oh my God I
don't know how to handle it I need
therapy I need totk therapy
[Music]
I'll hear her
hey baby
what are you doing
I picked her up
you're so cute say hi to the viewers
they had to kfp or do you want to eat
them
you're so soft
[Music]
thanks for your stream wait you smell a
little bit like pee again but I didn't
touch your butt this time get away from
me get away
what the hell's movie
I think she just came from the toilet
and she didn't clean her butt yet
okay I don't want to make her feel bad
though
okay I'm apologize goodbye guys in
Germany
the music does fits well
uh
goodbye guys and in German we say I'll
be dancing
[Music]
and super chats will never be read ever
again
[Music]
super chats don't exist anymore what are
super chance I'm gonna eat them for
dinner
I won't even remember myself even though
I speak German
bye-bye
[Music]
thank you for the rest of my chat that I
will never be reading
[Music]
tltk is my escape from Super Chat
okay they'll never get me
you'll never get me
[Music]
hungry oh my God
oh my God I'm so hungry
I'm so hungry bye bye
bye
[Music]