[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
sorry for the winter
there it is
hello oh my god oh it's happening again
where you only see the the
super chats and the member messages what
what
come to my
countdown stream wait I will fix it and
I will try
to fix you
um is it like you know for sure
maybe if I switch this code is it the
same thing
[Music]
let me test it
come on come on come on give me give me
proper chat messages
oh there it is
no I would not I would never do that
what is this ah okay
bye
not yet not yet
oh if you look
above my head
we are going of course by my country
where did it go
we're going by my country
which is a
c-e-s-t time zone
Austrian a Vegas GMT plus two now
I don't know it's confusing because I
think it switches between GMT plus two
and GMT plus one depending on summertime
and winter time
foreign
[Music]
I think I can do math this is accurate
hello
yeah
I I feel nervous because I I never did a
Birthday Countdown before
um I always see Japanese members doing
it so I thought why not do it this time
because I just want to stream as much as
I can to make up for the lack of 3D
birthday stream this year I mean
I'll talk about it again later but it
will happen it will just happen at a
time that does not feel like my birthday
at all
AKA December
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
a birthday I mean officially we will
have to but it will be more like yeah
exact date they didn't give me an exact
date they just gave me like a like a
month
so I don't know if it will be around
Christmas or if it will be even later or
if it will be the first week of December
or whatever I don't know but
I guess no I don't want to fame it the
thing is okay and the thing is I don't
want a famous after Christmas because it
was supposed to be
ah you know
not not Christmas themed so anyway I'll
stay by my plant because I I made up a
whole plan of what songs and what people
to invite and What stages to use Etc
uh I did that like in January or
February
so I made like a PowerPoint presentation
I would show you even
yeah I wrote up everything and I sent it
in like really motivated I was really
motivated after my Freddy birthday debut
I was like here there you go you can't
tell me that I asked too late because
here I'm already before you even telling
me I can do it I'm already sending you a
powerpoint presentation very very
detailed of what I will do
who I will invite everything when I will
sing with songs
Etc everything so you cannot tell me
later on that I did not you know early
enough sign up for it
and what did it bring me nothing
oh yeah
[Music]
so anyway
um basically
um what we're doing today in this stream
this is the first stream since I came
back from many travels
um so obviously we also have some things
to talk about as I'm thinking you know
maybe tell you some stories while we're
waiting for my birthday to come but also
maybe you have noticed on the title
there will be some Collins
only some like most people I gave the
girls two options and this was more this
stream was supposed to be more of an
option for the n a girls
because they thought this would be
better than my baking stream for them to
call him
but somehow I don't know if they like
overlooked the first slot
but most of them signed up for the
I don't want the baking one
night
and I I kept on
reminding them like girls girls you can
also do the other one the first one
um because like yeah I thought the other
the baking one would be for ID and Japan
but I made the mistake of kind of
inviting the Japanese girls through
blank asking jenma to notify the
managers to notify every member if they
want to come and yeah I should have
known that nobody is gonna answer to
that unless I directly DM them on my own
So currently which is it's fine because
I need time for baking anyway pretty
much almost every single ID member is
gonna call in though and a bunch of
Indian girls but so now we're also gonna
have them call in and then here here's
the schedule originally this was
supposed to be oh
feel free I forgot to change the number
to Two
genius that's just a sign of proof that
it was supposed to be more but then I
realized
um
um wait one two three you know
where's the two where's the rest of them
yeah right I mean one two three it's one
two three
[Music]
well this is my plan for tomorrow
um no time zones because freaking
annoying to ride the million time zones
on there but the baking stream is
basically starting 14 hours from now
okay maybe that's helpful and then the
jackbox party stream is starting in 24
hours from now
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
let me do go XLR
what wait a second chat chat wait how do
I do this again like um chat mic system
here say something
okay perfect um uh oh God you know what
that reminded me of
was it was you right who appeared in My
Fire Emblem stream
oh back in the day yeah also I hear
myself here ah
um
it's been a while it's been a while
yeah
okay so on on Discord yeah you wanna set
the input device to your own mic
check mike
yeah no broadcast yeah it's chat mic but
I routed your voice into chat Mike also
you're so quiet apparently on stream
wait wait wait wait wait wait
yeah but also in my ear you're quiet too
in my ear I want to I just want to put
you to my music there wait it in my
music maybe how do I
[Music]
fear oh
I don't know how sorry it's been a while
since I streamed like this uh here sound
uh sound settings and then oh uh go to
the details and then Discord
um oh say something
oh let's go you're in my music thingy
now so now I put the music
but you still hear yourself so let's
change this still yes I'll change this
into system say something
hello wonderful now we have double inner
on the stream too and then and then we
unroute him from the chat line
[Music]
yay
because I was just like looking at my
OBS screen and just explaining things
and suddenly
scientist that scientist is my stream
now I don't even know which one is yours
ah there you go I'm now Chad yeah
[Music]
hi I haven't seen you since the concert
you know louder even louder what louder
okay okay no problem here let me in the
loudest she could ever be
me
you were so good like I really really
really enjoyed ghost oh thank you
[Music]
your your performance man always a blast
nah but let me tell you I had to I had
to um actually you know put my feelings
about your performance together for
something
um specific for something special where
I talk about the performances uh people
will understand later on what it was for
um but ah I had to like write a or like
say something about you and and hmm I
was just like saying that you may you're
you're from the same generation so I've
been like watching you since the
beginning and just following your growth
and that the ghost performance just
showed your growth with like uh every
angle and so like every every facet of
your growth was like visible in your
ghost performance and then me so proud
and
yeah that's some of the things
[Music]
[Laughter]
I just wanted to let you know it was
amazing oh okay who killed me so long
coming from you you know you're always
always giving your best for all your
performances and you know even when we
were training for Dancing Yeah
everything you know you were always like
hyping on top you know let's go yeah
yeah
seeing you try hard you know makes me
want to try hard too so thank you on the
record I love you for that you know I
love you for your hard work you know
honestly like maybe like a couple years
ago I wouldn't have imagined like
dancing in front of so much people I
would have been like you know like I
can't even go to karaoke you know and
sing in front of my friends how could I
like sit and dance in front of all these
people but like now it's like after
seeing you and you know everyone in
whole life I'm just like you know maybe
maybe I shouldn't be you know so so shy
or embarrassed about dripping out you
know are you perhaps also like enjoying
seeing the results of your hard work hmm
I mean I'm I'm I'm happy to see that I'm
willing to do this in front of so many
people because otherwise I would have
been just been like you know a Hermit in
like my room yeah you're opening up I
think it's great
you're getting to know yourself from a
different side and you see what you're
capable of you're capable of like
anything basically so you're just
proving individual speaker right now
you're like oh you know try and fall of
positivity and sunshine no you know you
know I have to tell you how proud I am
of you I'm proud of YouTube
[Applause]
and yeah I'm stealing your slot your
time slot right now I know thanks for
not letting me stream today I mean you
could have though you could have there's
no like overlapping you know engine no
no but but I don't want to you know
steal your Spotlight for you to count
down can you sing me Happy Birthday
please
um what instrument
um you got a couple choices whoa uh yeah
automaton
um you got the recorder
yeah
[Music]
I'll be right back I need to bring the
record okay I trust you have the most
skills with the tooth machine
she scared me
Fire Emblem flashbacks oh my god do you
guys remember when I was in the middle
of saying because we got to get back to
that afterwards oh
dude
it's been a while since I played uh
three quarters so I might have to warm
up oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay let me try
[Music]
okay what I'm talking about
okay we're doubting yourself there for a
moment you know stop doubting yourself I
forgot I forgot what what note was damn
I'm surprised you even knew it out of
your head uh damn that's what you get
out of like ears of clarinet playing
card is pretty much the same you learned
the clarinet yeah I played it during
school that's so sophisticated you know
I was the I was the music nerd in school
with the thick glasses carrying their
musical instruments
[Music]
wow clarinet that's so pretty I wish I
could have learned something like that
like squid what is Squidward learn
clarinet
the flute
it's been so long as if he would play
such a beautiful sophisticated
instrument yeah he'll probably like the
flute or like the saxophone or something
you know apparently not the clarinet
suspicious reaction there okay
oh wait I'm gonna give Calliope Mori a
role what role
staff or admin what I cannot give her
what okay I guess I'll give her stuff I
have a role no because you're still in
here from last year I think
or last but I guess I guess you're not
supposed to give up
rules told me to give people roles so
that they can see what's going on but I
only have the right to give it back
because you can you can give her admin
rules she'll do a fine job I guess so
but staff also I think Steph is also fun
okay well weird anyway enough thank you
are you gonna be in my jackbox collab
too yes let's go yeah there's like a lot
of girls participating in the Jack books
class it's gonna be fine it's been a
while since he like gather like such
huge huge groups yes yes checkbox always
makes me so nervous because I
I have no idea what's going on I no
there are no secret here yeah I don't
know what's going on either great great
then do me a favor and then don't don't
do so well
one Jack box unless it was like a
drawing one I've never won it oh yeah
yeah yeah you're always strong with the
drawing ones there are a lot of drawing
ones I still have to decide which
jackbox party game I should go with
all right I see final lighting so I'm
gonna kick you out I don't know you're
gonna kick karakimi
well thank you
[Music]
not in a little bit in three years maybe
three years it took you so long to play
within three years I know
because I got lost like for the open
world games I needed video chat star you
got blood understandable okay have a
nice day okay bye bye bye bye
[Music]
damn give me a heart attack
scary
scary okay fauna is coming up oh oh and
then I have okay okay wait um
can I move her
whoa I can move people
now
[Music]
thank you oh my God
oh
fauna have you ever heard
me on one of those occasion where I try
to impersonate you I have and I think
that you're almost like really accurate
[Laughter]
so apologize because in hindsight when I
look back on those times it sounds like
I'm making fun of you but I just really
don't know how to impersonate anyone but
pick what I said but
is I have heard you oh before oh like
the regular impression like of course I
can tell that it's not me but I've heard
your ooh like out of context and I've
been like wait is that is that me oh oh
really there's some really accurate ooze
I've heard that but una how did it feel
to oh in front of thousands of people
I'm always I'm always oohing
oh my God
uh are you also in my jackbox party
collab I am I am I'm very excited let's
go let's go let's go exciting
exciting this party for your birthday
yes yes no I mean it's in 30 minutes but
yeah I thought you know I thought it
would be nice to have like something of
a birthday party so I invite everybody
getting everybody together again it's a
nice like opportunity not opportunity a
nice time and a nice whatever I cannot
speak
um with times when you cannot speak you
can just oh
[Music]
see wow that opens up my eyes
when you don't know what to say just
fill the void with random noises oh I
should do that more yeah
tell me something what are you up to
I've been working I've been kind of
behind on my work lately I'm trying to
catch up oh making a thumbnail right
before I called you how is the ketchup
game
um I lie I I know it's too well
maybe you should try some mayonnaise and
that way
vegan mayonnaise
wait why why why mayonnaise because
everybody is always about oh catching up
Ryan
Ryan well I guess you would prefer
ketchup because ketchup is generally
vegan so easier yeah hey what's your
favorite dip
favorite dip I really like honey mustard
I kind of knew it in my head I was like
she's gonna answer honey mustard I
should know it I don't know something
about you screamed honey mustard girl
what do you think what's what's your
favorite it depends what it's for but
for chicken nuggets I I like to
um this is a dip that's really common in
like Europe or German speaking countries
here
it's a sweet sour dip but it's not the
one the same that you get like at Asian
restaurants for example it's different
flowers
yeah different it's different it's not
the same thing but then but then you
know it depends sometimes I like
lingleberry jam but very specific things
or I like I like mayonnaise too with
fries you know it's really depends but
honey mustard I never have honey mustard
yeah do they have it
in Austria
I mean I don't think it's an option like
at McDonald's for example or is it do I
just not see it it might be it might be
but I also don't think it's like it's
not one of the most popular choices I
think it's just like a cultural thing I
think yeah it seems very American yes
they're not a mainstream option yeah
yeah honey mustard eh what do you eat
that with
I eat it with like
fake chicken
oh fries oh fake fries or real fries
real fries really I can have real fries
[Music]
what are fake tofu are fake friends made
out of tofu oh oh well you can have like
deep fried tofu and that's pretty good
oh it's a bad in honey mustard you know
what I want you to take me to a vegan
restaurant someday
I'm interested that'd be fun although I
don't really like tofu so I wonder what
else they can offer me that in mind it's
not all tofu I promise okay tofu
[Music]
it all comes back to I need to practice
my phone impression I'm not good at
Impressions either I can't do like
anybody can you do me ah
[Music]
thank you
that's just you
um
hi Kathy
Kiki hi kfp
yeah right see that's that's it's so
difficult to impersonate people it is
but she she also loves kfp I think
I do okay I will protect them from being
turned into chicken sandwiches
they want two of them a lot of them want
to actually no I think maybe our fan
bases can relate then sapling is also
one to be turned into trees wonderful
maybe I shouldn't judge you too much
yeah it's just they're kind of like
hypocritical about it because like
they're they're like oh I want to I want
to sacrifice myself blah blah blah and
then once I like you know start talking
about it and they're like and no why are
you so evil right right oh is it the
same for you oh my God you're not
they make up their mind oh my God okay
wow wow make up your minds guys make it
up make it up do you want to sacrifice
your soul and body for us or not or not
what's the answer what is it
it better be yes yeah see they were
already on fire wonderful I like both
um
well yes volunteer yeah okay wonderful
okay you know I guess we have a few I
will lock in that answer
no going back yeah you can't change it
anymore all right fauna I'll see you at
the jackbox party collab
yes good luck with all your streams
thank you I canceled one already so I'm
I'm feeling better about it now
[Music]
yeah okay I'll see you soon then in 24
hours or so a little bit less all right
I'll see you soon happy early birthday
thank you
[Music]
did you guys know uh her mommy her
artist she drew me before but she didn't
upload it because it's like inside a a
merchandise book for like comic Market I
have it though
this is so pretty
mommy drawing kiwawa is so pretty okay I
have somebody else
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
I took my shot sorry
I love you I love you
[Music]
Pomeranian
pomeo Pull Me Owen a Chihuahua yeah
all right I'm trying to find if we have
like you know like a PNG of you in my
chat but I can't find one so I'll just
show
this
this is the person that's calling in
right now
oh
yes from our stream together
I love that I love the gift that people
made of that it's so cute oh yeah good
memories we should do it again yeah we
haven't done a one-on-one in a while I
yeah well you know you're so busy you
have you know you just had a concert and
you you know you would assume that after
the concert and after my birthday I
would be less busy right
I'd never no it never ends I think I
mean I'm going back to Japan for one
single thing for a really short time in
like a couple of days weeks and that's
stressful but besides that like in
theory there shouldn't be like too much
crazy going on no but no okay we
can do something
figure something out
mama
sing me Happy Birthday
okay I'm prepared I'm prepared I'm
prepared yes yes yes because because you
know you got a recorder version earlier
from Ina but I'm going to give you an
omnichord version what the is that
what's my omnicore is that just one
chord like one
I'll play it for you okay
oh why is it why what is this there we
go there we go oh it's like Pokemon can
I hear it yeah okay
happy birthday
to you
happy birthday to you oh happy birthday
[Music]
happy birthday
to you
what is that how are you doing Dad
it's mine it's the omnicore how do you
do that is it pre-recorded
no it's it's it's it's it's it has like
it does the chords automatically
wow you sing in it and it adjusts here
I'll send you a picture I want to see
what is this mysterious instrument that
I did not know is it easy it's like a
keyboard yeah it's super easy it's super
easy so you have all the notes and you
have like the majors and the miners and
everything and then that slider on the
on the on the right side you just strum
that like a guitar why does that look so
old school
because it is cold
you just had that on in your own hands
right now
well did you have it connected to your
PC or so because it sounded like so like
there no it was just to my mic
wow
wait how wait the the key the key how
how what what
I need to try it I need to understand
okay whenever we meet I'll bring it with
me we can play Everything can you play
like Sparks or do you or hinotoni or so
oh
probably if I had like look if I had
like the guitar chords for it probably
oh
wow you're such a girl
what
I mean yeah
then what's your panty color
um
a check
subscribe to you you little weeaboo
they're not
[Music]
you know I'll let you call my panties
cheap it's okay
can you still I mean I still you know
sometimes I I bought like you know
specifically you know the nice ones
right that are like color coordinate and
all that with top and bottom but but but
then again I always I don't know I often
most of the time I just go back to the
sets
fine this is It's Just Gotta cover up
down there what's your favorite uh fit
yeah and like bris there's like
Brazilian or like hipsters and then
there's the the the one that goes really
deep into your butt I think
I don't think wait I've never heard of a
Brazilian really that maybe that's just
how they're called here because I I like
the hipsters I think yeah yeah I was
gonna say I like the hip ones because
we're such hipsters probably
we were yeah it was cool no granny
panties okay
but that's actually I think
I think it's you know we need to
um in my opinion normalize the the at
that as an adult you can still buy the
sets you know oh it's it's not something
to be ashamed of you know I agree yeah I
agree it's okay to talk about it too you
know you don't have to buy from the
fancy section you know they're more
expensive and also like in the end I
never wear the top because they're
uncomfortable the bra so I why why not
just only buy a set of panties then you
know sometimes I'll get like a bra and
it'll be so cute and when I try it on
the lace or something and so itchy like
touching
and I'm like well not when am I ever
gonna wear this
I like uh making the talk about
sensitibu topic
free the Wild Ones free to watch
no Pomeranian
[Music]
thank you for calling in into my you
know you're the only one uh you know
who's not in Holo who's calling me um
because I specifically like asked you if
you want to call me well yeah I wasn't
gonna miss your birthday
like pull my birthday in 15 minutes when
was my birthday
um it doesn't matter because today's
your birthday wait did I was it
what I don't remember it reminds me
please it's it's uh it's next week
holy wait what what date the 12th
what are you doing on your birthday
I don't have much I'm just gonna talk
just talk yeah if you do Collins let me
know I can call in unless you just want
to keep it you know need to send you
oh I think I'll have Colin
then I'll talk to you in one week
maybe in between maybe just maybe yeah
yeah you know for feeling yeah
um
thank you Pomeranian oh thank you
have a wonderful birthday I can't wait
to buy your birthday March everybody oh
yeah yeah birthday merge I need to say
something about that so I'm gonna kick
you out okay okay
I love her oh my God
uh
there guba is confused and what is it
now I thought it was tomorrow there are
two uh possibilities
now or
um in like 12 hours
it's okay not now
unless you want to
no she was planned for tomorrow anyway
uh birthday merchandise just let me tell
you it's um
during the baking stream and because
there's limited uh limited uh this time
you know with signatures
uh I want to warn you guys beforehand
it's it's going to be at the second hour
so the stream starts at 1pm right so and
then the merchandise The Limited one or
like everything should go up at the
second hour so that will be like 3 P.M
my time
okay
[Music]
um
okay okay okay uh so that you guys will
miss it I know it's kind of like a
shitty time for my anime viewers I think
I think
you know but I thought it's better to
have it in the baking stream rather than
in a countdown stream I don't know
because I don't know I don't know I hope
it's okay okay
um I am now just gonna wait for whoever
uh there's not so many call-ins during
the countdown guys because as I told you
everybody's like eh okay I'm gonna call
in during this baking stream at this
time please
and I don't realize you can call in now
too
yeah let me let me switch the vgm go to
oh
I'll go to here
we go there we go
you took off work what for me
cute oh my God
so okay what was I in the middle of
saying we have the baking stream Collins
and merchandise yeah that's at 1pm my
time starting and I already bought
ingredients and and I know what cake I'm
making is actually a tart and with hand
camera and then there will be a break I
wanted to do a a 3D karaoke in between
like at home pretty
but it would have been so much it's
already a lot of work to set up for the
baking stream and then I would have to
set up for the you know wearing the suit
and then I think have to charge
everything set everything up and and see
what I can single play a plan and so on
so to charge the camera no
I don't even know where it is right now
but I'll find it
nobody no no karaoke that's another time
no and then jackbox party with a couple
quite a lot of Ian members yeah
um
okay
so
if
[Music]
happy but thank you
ah did you guys see oh my God
I don't even know I'm so unorganized in
my head I don't know what to do first
um or to say first but did you guys see
okay Papa
drew me
oh my God
well the first time in a long time while
I was so shocked I did not expect this
the last time
he drew me
where it wasn't like a commission
because of like birthday merchandise or
so like in the first year I had birthday
merchandise made by Papa
Papa
so before besides that it was I think
I think
what that art you know when I was in the
middle of a flower field
was the
last one which is like two and a half
years ago and and maybe maybe a sketch
for one million uh maybe that was after
um
so
that's a long time ago
[Music]
um
and I feel like his art style like he he
can draw in so many art styles
and I feel like he threw me every time
he draws me he draws me in a different
art style like this looks so different
right like me and this is
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I found this really interesting I
noticed he uses like you know these like
like patterns
all over like on the hair on the clothes
on the skin even but you gotta look
closely
half tone patterns yeah yeah
[Music]
heart attack every time
I don't know what you're saying it
doesn't work so well
thank you it's almost 117 minutes yay
yeah what are you feeling yeah I'm
feeling all over the place
all over the place yeah my brain is
everywhere
yeah I mean you got a lot of stuff
prepared so that's gonna be exciting
what do I have
a gift it feels like it feels like I
mean you're always so prepared and you
know okay yeah you're always
like so much content oh yeah I'll just
I'll just keep up the illusion the
illusion is important
[Laughter]
in jackbox party stream
yeah well the answer is always yes guys
the answer is almost always yes
oh jackbox party games I mean yeah let's
go the more the merrier books party
games
uh you know that's kind of wit and luck
so I I just like I don't know I'm like
okay wait I don't think yeah I I I I I'm
not good with but also my problem is my
language brain is too slow for jackbox
but I want to play it because it's fun
anyway
yeah it's fine I mean I'm not good
either like I don't think I ever got
like first place
the time you will get first place
tomorrow for sure
and you never know you might get first
place too awesome but that's never
happened maybe maybe I'll get a Pity
first place
well I think I think you're pretty Woody
like you know recently I saw your like
short video like the one that's like
leave me alone I thought that was pretty
funny that was right funny right
and making so many movies recently
I I approve like as a mean brain I
really like it really tickles my brain
seeing all these memes you knew the
reference right
yeah yeah
if it was crony how would it go
yo
yeah
I I can't I can't come up with on on the
spot no you give me you give me a leave
me alone and I'm saying and then you go
like okay
okay right now okay okay it starts with
you leave me alone
uh leave me alone
oh
I could have used a little bit more
suffering and frustration and anger
I mean I can't I can't exactly make
those sounds right now I'm oh I'm kind
of outside
being embarrassing oh okay well you do
sound like you're on your phone okay
okay
it's okay this way one day I want to
hear crony version like the real deal
uh I mean it won't be as good as yours
it was pretty it was a pretty solid tank
so yeah I'll try I'll try okay thank you
Colony can you sing me Happy Birthday
yeah
oh
is that okay even though you're outside
yeah it's okay I mean it's better than
like
groaning okay uh happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
dear Kiara happy birthday to you that
was very cute thank you
I'm flushing okay great what does stop
it stop it
I hope you have a great one you deserve
it you deserve all the love and support
[Music]
bye bye have a nice day see you in the
jackbox collab
yeah bye-bye
okay I see Kyla in the waiting room but
Kayla if you're listening maybe wait
wait wait because uh us two minutes
until my birthday give me give me a give
me a moment give me a moment
[Music]
Kyla this one
I I I want to watch something I think it
will be perfect uh maybe I don't know
how long the video is oh it's exactly
two minutes and uh and 30 seconds
um I have a video from kfp and I have
not spoiled myself on what it is
Okay so
let's see what's behind this video
and Go Happy Birthday to someone it must
be someone in the chat
it's someone's birthday
probably someone's birthday it's my
birthday
[Music]
yeah that's true I know someone there
has birthdays
[Music]
not the chicken
Phoenix congratulations
[Music]
are they reading that off somewhere
the movie had no idea what's going on
[Applause]
[Music]
the acoustics
what what's cool
[Music]
[Laughter]
so bad but thank you oh my God the
background the nail light looked like
they were made for me
[Applause]
ready three two
one
happy birthday thank you
[Music]
hey happy birthday
mate comers
what's my birthday oh
[Music]
thank you
that's so cute real life birthday
message from so many people
thank you
and that guy again
that was the moment I think where we
when he was where he was stumbling he
wasn't sure if he was gonna sing you or
kiwawa I noticed that one
and thank you and this is
[Music]
yeah oh my gosh should I sing like a
proper happy birthday song for me really
quick you know not someone but like for
me
oh wait wait where's my where's my
birthday
I'll try I'll try here Here Comes
improve visitation
oh
what should I say
[Music]
happy birthday
[Applause]
to this Phoenix
[Music]
there once was an idol
who also works at a fast food franchise
[Music]
[Applause]
so there is now
[Music]
happy birthday
to this Phoenix
so cute and so lovely
uh she's even oranger
then an edible orange
can you believe it
she's just so orange oh my God I
want to sing more
what a great birthday song great quinoa
great great wow I'm so impressed wow
okay please please save me please please
save me Kyla wow
why
hello kiwawa happy birthday you sound so
cute today
what I'm cool ah I'm always cold you
really don't like being called the cute
one yeah I don't know it's just like
I don't know it's just weird like
calling it's called cute I don't know
oh interesting facts you know nah I'm
cool I know that I'm cool right right
right right right right right no no no
no I'm not cool when I met you all my
father was damn she's cute
you have to try a bit harder to be cool
maybe shape like one side of your head
and and put some piercing some more
piercings in your ears
yeah and thank you so much
how to be cool
well I should know
wait
um so how I don't know I've been
practicing how to say happy birthday in
German but I don't know how how
to pronounce that well I want to hear
what your attempt first oh okay wait um
please Google translate you don't wait
wait I will listen to the Google
Translation okay
okay all is good as the wait wait wait
wait give me another chance
stock
[Laughter]
good try pretty good I mean I 100
understand what you're trying to say
that is
bad City good job good job
if you pronounce it a little bit more
accurate it's Alice not good good
good day good good day
some some really strong sets
[Music]
wait the the the GE is like
yeah
Alice Alice oh no why German is so hard
German music all is good Alice good is
oh no guys forgive my pronunciation but
I try that's really cute how are you
trying no it's cool no it's really cute
hey are you like uh did you just wake up
or are you still awake what's going on
no no no I yeah I I I just haven't slept
oh I am working I'm working I'm working
on some stuff yeah it's okay well I knew
and I knew you could literally call in
at any time for me you would do it
yeah yeah because actually I want to
call in later but yeah because
complicated yeah yeah complicated I'm
sorry no no problem no problem I'm happy
you want to call in Conway
thank you for having me I'm so happy
yeah I don't know actually every thought
so much I was like really nervous you
know
you nervous yeah yeah why are you
nervous why are you nervous do I make
you nervous no no no no no like every
thought so much it was just like
it's just like
I was looking at you at your the art of
your like you know Discord thingy at the
mask it looks like a monkey right and
you're making oh
[Music]
that I cannot really call cute I think
that would get be closer to cool
return to Monkey reject Humanity return
um wait um I'm I'm just making the
birthday girl to be like a monkey now
yeah yeah people always tell me that I
sound like a monkey when I panic
oh really yeah do people tell you you
sound like something like some animal
oh
oh I I don't know I'm I'm always be like
the monkey the gorilla one but I don't
know oh oh I think you have potential to
become a really high quality gorilla
monkey
um I really I really I really hope
someday maybe if there's like a voice
acting
I don't know um competition
competition maybe I can join I don't
know I need to practice more should we
do animal voice acting competition
before yeah I hope someday
chaotic everybody chooses an animal and
tries their best and it would just be
like a zoo we're in the middle of a zoo
oh okay now you gave me another idea for
a stream
unless you want to do it what
competition
uh okay well Kyla can you sing me Happy
Birthday of course I'm listening give me
a cool I guess you'll try to be cool but
actually you'll be cute I know I don't I
know wait
it's just like a cool test or what wait
know what I do it's gonna be cold you
know no no what what do you mean no
you're not only kids the whole time I
don't know man
no no I'm kidding
no how hot what what what no no no no
I'm just I'm just like oh oh it's
starting okay oh I thought okay okay
okay okay happy birthday happy birthday
okay such a scattered brain
oh
okay three two one happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you yay happy birthday
happy birthday happy birthday
that was cute no that's cool I know no
no no no I okay okay one one more one
more chance one more chance yes
okay
this one is better
happy birthday
it's scary you scare me
[Music]
happy birthday happy birthday
no get out you scare me
you scare me
is that cool enough no I mean cool would
be more like yo yo Happy Birthday you
cutie pie happy birthday I'm not gonna
lie happy birthday I love you happy
birthday it is true yo yo what freestyle
rap let's go
[Applause]
throw in some yo-yos and yo yo
yo yo okay okay okay one more one more
one more one more time okay
just just throw some yo-yo okay
okay yo yo Happy Birthday Happy Birthday
Happy Birthday Kiara yo yo yo yo yo yo
yo yo yo yo
I think you have failed the mission
good try maybe try again sometime I say
started shaving a part of your head only
aside one side shave it I know it's it's
kind of scary like if someday we get up
meet again I don't know someday if
there's a chance to win again and then
I'll make sure that I don't know I'll
protect my hair then okay I will not for
CE you but you know it would help you in
becoming cooler
think about it just think about it you
know how much you want to commit to
being cool think about it
later doing anything I'm always cool
okay okay you just keep telling yourself
that okay Kyla okay okay but yeah thank
you so much for having me here I I hope
you have a lot of fun today
whatever
yes it's fine it's morning it's 5 a.m in
the morning but it's okay
okay it's um it's good night good night
yes okay good night okay okay good night
enjoy your day
[Music]
okay
but my rib my rip my wrap was really
cool I think
yo I came up with some good lyrics there
on the spot that rhymed even I was kind
of struggling at the last one though but
it worked out it's like that does she
ever sleep well you know her
she doesn't need sleep I mean I always
like to prioritize sleep because because
sleep is just so comfortable so
comfortable if only this movie wasn't
stealing my sleep so much uh whoosh whoa
at the moment but maybe you saw on
Twitter
I got some I got some cool stuff
the on the the machine the robot
although I don't think I can get it to
work immediately
um I don't know I don't have time I need
to busy busy
follow rap battle good question good
question
ah I think that that might be
um
for now I think that's all of the
Collins so
let me tell you
something
let me tell you a story okay my gift to
you on this beautiful birthday is a
tangent yay attention
I have photons
so which ones do where do I start okay
how about
how about how about
[Music]
the other day as you may remember I went
out with oga you Senpai and gubidy bar I
basically just joined them as a
translator because originally the plan
was for it to be a double date with
coldness and bye and all guys
said I couldn't do it
um kind of last minute so I was like
okay we're still doing it doesn't matter
still doing it for the sake of okay you
and Guru team
yeah professional third wheeler
um so let me tell you about this
wonderful joyful day
okay I mean I think I already told a lot
of it on my Twitter space
[Music]
um
well basically yeah this is how it
started and then there was still like a
hope that Corona standby would come on
the actual day so we kind of waited for
a while waited like uh good I still had
some work to do so
um I was waiting at the at the studio
for her
um
and no it's not a retail I'm telling it
in more detail
I was waiting for her and I was updating
by like how
how is how it's going and you know that
is taking a little bit more time and
then at the same time I was hoping you
know that could still join and and okay
I already left her place so she came
over to the studio and she brought me
sun sunscreen because it's I forgot I
didn't have anything and I didn't want
to buy a whole bottle for like one day
of going outside
um
so she brought me the the sunscreen so
she arrived and I I saw her for the
first time and I gave her I think I gave
her a hug right away I mean I I felt
like I wasn't sure if she would be okay
with it but I I just went with it
because I thought um
I will be forgiven I'll surely be
forgiven I'll get the the Gaijin pass um
[Music]
and then yeah we just waited in the
studio and Ollie was there
so because good I was somewhere
shut in doing work
we just watched Ollie and do her thing
and um and and Ollie was very happy
because like okay but I wasn't you know
originally she wasn't supposed to come
here right so I told Ollie's Empire is
coming by the way
yeah she was so excited she got to meet
Uncle Senpai because of that and she she
got the signature and everything yeah I
also signed something for Ollie
um
and then you may you may have heard the
story of only asking okay Senpai to step
on her
and then I'm like
like she asked it to me she asked me if
it's okay to ask Oka you said bye she
asked me in English and I said
I would like to do that I kind of I
don't know
and then okay but I was curious so I I
ended up telling her what she's asking
for and okay Senpai is like no no no no
no no no no
really like gently
um
and then I I offered instead because I
don't care who's playing oh I can step
on you Holly I'll step on you
is that a big deal get down so she gets
down and I stepped on her butt and she's
like yeah
yeah she was so happy she's so full of
energy and and so
so excited always
she's so cute like she would randomly
start working for me
I'm like go Ali go Ollie go Ollie I love
her Anna Jean but like when we're when
we were like outside I had to be like
only only you know what if you're only
around you know somewhere outside with
me I don't care so much I I wouldn't
like tell you all the time to be quiet
but you know now now we are with with
Gouda and amen so I have to tell you
only you know for the sake of them let's
be a little bit more quiet okay
because we had that that dinner and the
Twitter space right
yeah
yeah okay so much if it's just us but
you know there's more people involved so
I'm like only only I know you're really
excited but you need to like calm down
and you need to chill
yeah it's difficult though I understand
because she was so excited and she gave
she gave uh souvenirs to everybody I
received
um like an Indonesian fan that was
really useful
um I received it the day before I met
okay I think it was the day before and
then on the day I brought it because I
thought oh it's so hot outside this will
be perfect so I brought it and then okay
Senpai uh got one from Ollie too so we
had matching fans hey
because all he had leftover souvenirs
um and she was like oh thank God I have
one more souvenir set with me right now
because you didn't expect me to all oh
guys and by right so that was lucky so
that and some Indonesian snacks like
small uh packages and then also a batik
uh like scarf like a really thin summery
scarf
um
and she gave that to everybody she met I
think
um
[Music]
no the buttock is like the the pattern
like Indonesian style pattern
yeah any catchers no cat treats why
would you give me cat treats thanks guys
for the Super Chat tonight so far I hope
I find time to catch up sometime
uh yeah and anyway back to you know that
original story
um so we're waiting for good on it took
a while so guys came over she met oh
yeah we were waiting we were having fun
and then gouda finally is finished
and you know they meet yeah yeah yeah
and it was it was some
it was like you know shy and all that
but it wasn't like too awkward or
anything it was pretty chill like yeah
and I tried to like
communicate between them and translate
everything yeah and oh yeah the thing is
I wanted originally I wanted us to go to
Disneyland Disneyland date
[Music]
um but then eventually you know we've
noticed that some like scheduling is
like overlapping so we can't have a
whole day
so instead I I had to think of like
something to do
um that wouldn't take a whole day but
that would still be fun I didn't just
want to go for dinner you know I wanted
to do something special
um
so I
find gooder to do some sightseeing you
know you know how we we were in Japan
for like a really long time January
February I thought
taking some time to go out to do
sightseeing right there was a long time
where I was also not there but she was
still with like Ina and so on and then
there was a time you know where I was
back again but
it sounded like she told me oh no not at
all like barely she barely saw any
anything in terms of like you know
typical sightseeing things I'm like
not because she's not interested just
because like I guess nobody took her and
she also didn't ask anybody to like show
her around so it just didn't happen and
I'm like okay leave it to me leave it to
me you should you see you have to see
some of like the typical sightseeing
things you have to
um
so I I thought what would be good is
asaksa asakusa is like pretty like
Central it's like you don't have to go
so far you know there's like a lot of
cool things you know like Kyoto and
whatever but those places are far but
within Tokyo what you can do for like
half a day of sightseeing from my
experience is asset stuff
um
because asxa has this big Temple big ass
temple one of the biggest I've ever seen
uh senzoji sensual
and you can get fortunes there you can
get
umamuri uh Fortune no um those
protectors like lucky things
and you can you can get lots of food
interesting food and it just looks
really really impressive yeah and when I
went there before I dressed up I I went
to like a rental kimono rental and I
dressed up oh yeah charms
I dressed up uh but I I kind of wanted
to do it this time too but then in the
end like it was kind of last minute to
decide what we're doing
and so I thought maybe maybe another
time it would have been nice though
not a shrine maidens but as it just like
you know people like to dress up when
they do when they go to asakusa um
so actually
I god well surely she went before
surely she must have gone before
and then she tells me she also hasn't
gone to asakusa before not just Gouda
I'm like what
what have I seen more of Japan than okay
so I showed them around both of them um
but we took like a taxi right and okay
was sitting
um in the front and me and gonna in the
back so I felt like I felt awkward about
like shouting to the front to have a
conversation with okay so in the taxi
was just like me and good at talking in
the back in English and
we had quite the conversation
um we were talking about hotels hell and
Gordon Ramsay and stuff uh talking about
specific episodes like which ones we
fought were the craziest so just like
being like what the right oh my God
so true oh my God that episode was crazy
wasn't it yeah the one that one that one
with the with the old lady who was
collecting baskets yeah oh my God that
one I saw that one too and then I was
like what's up with like what's actually
up with Gordon Ramsay getting naked in
every episode and showing his butt when
he goes into a bathtub you know we we
were talking about what exactly he's
trying to trying to do with that
[Music]
um
I was really happy that we had like this
this common topic watching uh the same
things we really oh sh my phone is dead
how I like look at my I guess I don't
need my tension notes but we watch like
similar things on YouTube at least I
don't know about like Netflix or
whatever but on YouTube yeah because
like before we got into
um I remember in January February we got
into this like discussion of
um the
the what would you call it the the
murder interrogation documentaries
analyzation yeah the True Crime things
I was so surprised that she also is like
really deep into that so yeah we watched
similar things
so we're tested it for a while uh until
we finally arrived but can you stand bye
I don't know exactly what like goal she
entered as like a address but I mean we
got out somewhere well it looked
familiar to me but not exactly where I
would start
um sightseeing asakusa so I was trying
to get us to like the the ideal Street
you know because maybe I can get like a
map of Awesome
[Music]
um
or I could draw it
try to draw it
come on there
really not that necessary but you know
you know you know
[Music]
perfect
that's fine
oh yeah paint
there's
this is just like from my memory of
walking around asakusa a million times
I've been to Essex a million times not
really for sightseeing but I I once
stayed in a hotel there okay so there's
um where's well okay here there's this
like big street mm-hmm
[Music]
and then somewhere maybe here is the the
temple and then
um no yeah it's like kind of like
there's this there's this big gate
and you go through and there's like
rows of shops and they go sometimes
sideways okay then actually the temple
is more like here and you know sometimes
they go sideways
um but mostly it's like this one street
and then one time it goes left and also
a little bit more over there but if you
go left and you go to the temple the
temple temple is here okay
yeah
Archer and then and then this big stream
yeah here there was there was a
restaurant that we went to that will be
important because I have pictures and
then if you go further and further and
further that's where we got off of the
taxi but it's like really fun really
really really far so
if I would walk down the street to get
to here which is kind of what I had in
my head what I wanted to do it would
take probably like 15 minutes so instead
I thought wow I guess we'll just go
through the streets the little streets
and eventually we end up there but I
wanted to get to this street first and
then go this way but
I failed a little bit as
[Music]
that's that's the tour guide you guys's
face is what what are you trying to tell
me with those faces this is not
understandable
attention Okay so the good thing though
by going for all the side streets where
the whole time it was like I was telling
them just just so you know this is not
really what I'm trying to show you this
is still not what I'm trying to show you
this is kind of cool and has a Cool vibe
but it's not what I'm trying to show you
this is not the typical like asakusa you
know Street you know where there's all
the food okay just just so you know so
we first stopped at like a gacha
which was fun though it was not at all
but
about art school
plays and got the place there was lots
of Taytay yeah because
matching things from Nagata and then
because like good I got something first
I think and then okay was like well I
went I want uh matching with gura and
then I was like watching that online
[Music]
[Laughter]
oil is
so I just it's just also tried the same
gotcha
so pathetic
but it's okay it's okay it's okay it's
okay
um but I also got some other things yeah
because ah that was the
okay I said by apologize to me later on
Via DMS
um I I first saw like this Chi color
there's this character
let me look up what it looks like so I
can draw it for you
Chicago
uh
it's like
Chicago looks
I'm this
like this uh
uh
Chicago uh
alien
and then
but I think this is not too bad
[Music]
it's not too bad can you see it what
Chicago
is like this like I don't know some some
cute mascot thingy and there's like
several characters and they all kind of
look like that and
um oh shut up
and there was this gato machine because
like it's really popular right now in
Japan Chicago and I was like oh isn't
this the thing that
um likes right now and okay was standing
to me and she was like yes Kiana you're
right her favorite is the bunny one
[Music]
because I mean and the moment she said
that I was like hmm I guess that makes
sense because pick one is a rabbit so of
course you would like the one that's a
bunny character
before which character is her favorite
but in that moment I would obviously
believe okay because okay with so much
confidence yeah so I was like okay nice
you know what maybe I'll get something
for pick what I said but because I'm
going to meet her the next day
actually
yes
for the second time no it wasn't on
purpose though I should have yeah I
should have trusted my instincts but
damn it so I tried several times and I
failed several times
uh I got like this lion this this one
that looks like a lion and I think I got
the OG Chicago that one that I drew and
I got the bunny eventually so I was like
yeah
and then the next day
you know I was like take what I was
there and I'm like really really nervous
and like awkward what do I do I can't
even properly say hello or start a
conversation so you know what the
conversation starters just gotcha ball
that I have perfect perfect this is my
conversation starter so I walk over and
walk around the table because we were
sitting around the big table and walk
around the table in the first sight
because Muna was also there and I swear
to you the whole day I was so thankful
for Muna being there because she was
like I swear she was my rock
is my rock that I was holding on to the
whole day
I was so nervous the whole day and I
felt uh out of place
um
and I I the whole time you know because
Muna can't speak Japanese so she also
had some problems you know being like
communicating
so I was like Muna
you're here for me I'm here for you okay
okay we're here for each other okay so
the whole time we clinked clingy
together
but I walk over I Look to I look I I
look at Moonah the whole time I'm like
when I feel so awkward what do I do I'm
really so weird I don't want to be weird
I don't know what to do
[Music]
thank thank God she was there so I walk
around the table and go over to pecorro
Center and I'm like uh I'll pick what I
said I know
I know
um
and I give it to her and I'm like
like you like this one the most right I
got it for you at the ganja and she
didn't say anything she didn't say no
that's not it
she didn't say it but she was probably
thinking it and she's just like ah
sounds exactly like
and I'm like yeah you you're welcome and
then I walk away
it got better over the course of the day
it got better okay eventually I warmed
up thank God
um
stream and and that's when I realized
when I was like
yeah I noticed oh oh I got the wrong one
[Music]
about it and then okay Senpai dm'd me
and she's like I'm so sorry
I'm like it's okay it's okay
that's okay
[Music]
spaghetti it's okay though for real
because I I really warmed up I later on
I warmed up and I was able to have like
normal conversations with her thank God
because for the people who don't know
first time
how do I
how do I make like a new one
by the way I make a new one I don't get
rid of this
Maybe
yes okay
ah okay so
[Music]
what the is this
okay here is a door
with a door
this is
and then and then
Chihuahua is here
and there were like a bunch of
um
a couple of other people in the room uh
and I'm writing Senpai I didn't I was
actually I was here because I was like
you know I was using the little booth to
even I was doing a stream or I was
[Music]
um
I think I was doing a stream or I was
doing a small recording on my own and
foreign
so I was told you know oh here there are
some some whole life members you know so
I want to say hello and I'm like yeah
I'll go say hello so I will go and say
hello and I I talk perfectly normal to
everybody I'm like yeah what's up what
are you doing hi
hello
looks really chill you know really cool
and then I I noticed my name is Senpai
minus Empire is here too so mine is it
by minus it but it comes in
and she's not alone but she's like
yeah and be like
[Music]
greeting each other in a really you know
happy energetic way and then she's like
one minute later she's like pointing to
the person next to her
and she's like yeah
and in debt
in that moment
my face
[Music]
turned into this
that was the first time we met and I was
not prepared mentally for it and I was
embarrassed and I was like
what did I do
um I didn't recognize her from the ears
yes she had like a hat on that pushed
down the ears um
so I'm like ah I'll pick myself
and she's like I
oh yeah
yeah
God I'm so good I'm like oh I'm using
I'm using the little booth the solo
Booth to do some work yeah yeah and
she's like ah so so big
and then
since like these couple of words and
then the others are you know very used
to each other so they you know talk to
each other and in that moment I realized
oh oh I don't know how to
include myself in the conversation
anymore
so I I'm like silently standing while
everybody's having a conversation I'm
just like standing there like nodding
smiling
and then no and then I'm like okay
this is just getting more and more
Awkward I gotta get out of here I gotta
get back to work
and
I leave
and this was just like
a few
like maybe two three minutes hmm
yeah so
then
you know I always felt very nervous
about reading pekua sepa again because
if you look down on the floor here
you will see very obviously that I
dropped all of my spaghetti
I dropped it oh
yeah okay
yeah so I thought this time I cannot I
cannot I can't drop my spaghetti again
and yeah I tried I I think I held it
together
[Music]
I was just like mostly just
I don't know being quiet and then later
on
because there was a couple of hours
together
I finally could talk more normally with
her like I would we were like just
waiting and I'm uh everybody's like kind
of look tired in the room and just like
yeah we run we ran out of talking topics
at some point so I I threw in one I'm
like pickles
[Music]
what do you like to do on your your days
off where you don't stream
and I love she would be okay with me
telling it so I'm not gonna tell what
she does
um but then we talk a little bit about
that yeah so I I got I got pretty
um comfortable
at some point I would say
yes at the end it wasn't awkward at all
so
[Music]
but I want to thank Muna for being there
because she gave me like the mental
support that I needed just by existing
[Laughter]
yeah I clinged so much onto her
[Music]
foreign
yeah I I met Muna quite a lot in those
short days a few few couple days and it
was like stick together hell yeah okay
back to the uh
can I get back to my asakusa drawing
the drawing
so we got some gacha time right we spent
some time at the Gata and I was like ah
this is not really that sucks I want to
show them but at least they're having
fun yeah they got some stuff there and
then and then we move on and we found
um a cafe
which was which had like a
um like some some food pictures outside
that looked really
delicious like Crepes but traditional
Japanese flavors like
beans uncle and uh green tea and all
that yeah yeah
so I was like do you guys want to get
something and they were like well
actually maybe yeah yeah so I didn't get
anything besides a drink
but okay got like a uncle Bata
red beans butter crepe which was more on
the on the crispy side and it was like
kind of flat folded like a triangle and
gouda got this the one that's you know
the most aesthetically pleasing I took a
picture of it
wanna see
it looks really good it doesn't even
look like a cut like legit
it's a it's a it's like you know the
cone like ice cream shape
but they filled it with so much cream
and it just has this perfect round shape
like I've never seen this before and
then they top it with like as if it's
like some latter art with this matcha
powder but this one was much softer and
so much cream although said there was
like some kind of cookie inside as well
good I was eating this
[Music]
um and that was just like drinking
something and but I got a bite of
um
of okay senpai's Bean crap
good like I don't have like oh I don't
hate uncle but I would probably normally
not go for uncle
um but it was really good that Uncle
Bata I think the butter really made it
amazing and the crispiness of the cup in
combination was really good
um and then
what was it I think
um
yeah
was like okay I was like oh you want to
try gouda and good is like no because
she was like
she was saying she doesn't like Uncle
oh this is interesting she was saying
she doesn't like Uncle and I was like
you know translating back and forth you
know and I'm like well what have you
eaten with Uncle before and she explains
that she's had like Uncle red bean
kitkats
and that's pretty much it and I'm like
oh no no no no that's you cannot even
like make an opinion about it for Kit
Kats because Kit Kats just are not a
good representation of any flavor
um so I tell her and I translate that to
okay and she agrees with me no no no you
cannot make an opinion based on that you
should try you should try like this is
really good quality and I think you
would like it if even I like it then
I've been good I would like it too
though
um
yeah yeah yeah I mean kitkats are great
and all but I just I'm just saying you
know the flavor isn't really accurate
sometimes and tastes very much different
if you have the real deal
um
so we convinced Guna to take a bite out
of okay use
red bean crap and she liked it
we fixed her dislike of red beans um
yeah yeah but I think she learned the
lesson um
yeah and she liked it she was struggling
to eat her crap but I know I know you
know I took her before I took her to a
Ramen place where you know ichiran where
you can eat kind of privately people
don't look at you which I prefer to when
eating Ramen so I know you know she
doesn't enjoy eating in front of people
but this is not why she was struggling
with eating The Crepe it was her first
trip she didn't know how to eat it it's
a bit difficult if it's like it when
it's wrapped in a paper like this I I
agree it can be difficult you need like
a technique and and then the other
problem was that it was so soft that you
basically you could not like pull it out
of the paper so once you got to the
point where the paper starts
you can't bite into it anymore unless
you pull it out or you you rip off the
paper but she couldn't really pull it
out because it was so soft it would rip
and she would be you know
messing it all up
I was trying to help her but it was
difficult she was struggling with it
because of the texture and all that but
she enjoyed it yeah
so we ate that and and drank that and
then we moved on and I was hoping to
finally reach the actual
destination but eventually
eventually we
reached the site the side of the
Temple you're supposed to go through
here and through here and enjoy the
beautiful front view of the gate and the
big Central Century Temple and
regretful about that and we saw it
backwards
side backwards but I'm like ah here
there it is this is sensody and then
actually the problem was we arrived kind
of late
um so by the time we finally arrived
here
the lock charm shop was closed and all
we could get is uh the fortunes The
Fortunes are like always available and
you just pay by throwing money in a box
there's not even staff there they just
trust you
um
oh my God it's almost uh 1am okay not
much more I'm just finishing my my
tangent okay because I still gotta make
font nail for tomorrow and food and
sleep somewhere yeah
I took pictures of everything to show
you guys
so basically there's like because this
Temple is so popular and so big there's
like a lot of
um these
[Music]
um
places
oh wait
oh now it's
um
I can get rid of this place okay
[Music]
huh
there's nothing weird there there's
nothing weird there yeah yeah yeah
I don't even check Reddit anymore I'm
sorry Reddit
I used to check I don't even check
Reddit anymore
it's okay it's okay it's okay uh but at
least the console is working again so
yeah there's so many of these yeah
because it's so busy there's so many
people
there so they need a lot of them there's
like always crowded these are always
crowded
resident samples so
fine I just you know I don't have time
to check it
hmm
so you pick um out of this like uh metal
box you shake it you shake it and you
take out one of these sticks
it tells you a number of the drawer that
you should take out the paper out of
and for me the stick just did not come
out at all but okay so if I took it
first and I was like let's not look at
it uh yet let's look at the fortune
together at the same time okay
okay so we all got our paper slips and
then
I took a photo of them the good thing is
because this place is so crowded so
popular the back side of the paper slips
isn't English
[Music]
partially in other languages
so
let's read through it I have yet to read
properly through it
all right
okay here we go
good ass bad fortune lack
if you look at it like that I guess
she's just lacking back Fortune
yeah although you do your best and
sincerity to others is this Google
translate it's useless just like burning
incense to this
but maybe a small loyalty a good deed
prevents causing damage okay okay you
will spend a long hard time working on
many useless
your wishes will not be realized a sick
person will recover but take a little
while making a trip will not be good
building a new house and removal are
both half fortunate marriage or
employment should be served the last
article will not be found the person you
are waiting for will show up after a
long while
my thing is that it's not even Google
translate it's because
um the Japanese version is written in
quite
mystical and difficult nihongo Japanese
so Translating that is on another level
you know
but this is
spread a long hard time I'm working on
many useful things oh my God way too way
to kill her motivation man oh my God
that's really bad but don't worry she we
know okay I said by the whole time was
like trying to cheer her up like oh you
know the the possibility of getting this
bad fortune is way lower than the others
so in some way you're really lucky to
get this one
um
[Music]
and and yeah she was cheering her up and
I'm like wow how can you be so positive
that's actually amazing quite a skill
but we wrapped it around the rack and
you have to wrap the bad fortunes around
this rack and then it will supposedly
make it go away it will give you a
chance of you know this not happening
next we have okay senpai's Fortune
think yeah it should be I think so the
five
yeah that's hers the final and last four
what
is it the final at the last one it's
supposed to be just translated to like
decent luck is she okay
[Music]
ominous ominous oh not ominous
those so many articles are kept around
you you can't get them in your hands
goddamn is because she has no thumbs
maybe as a cat you make a deficit and
harm sometimes be very careful that your
house will be burned so keep the thick
guard around your house
I don't know about keeping fake guards
if that really helps do believe in God
guard yourself with deep care then your
future will be in peace forever your
request will not be read
the patient will take long time to cure
the last article will also not be too
bad you have to wait long time until you
meet a person you wait for stop yeah she
I mean she met gurado she waited for her
stop building a new house and removal
stop starting a trip stop any kind of
marriage and new employment okay wow wow
wow wow
[Music]
if you just copy pasted from a
translator that couldn't happen so did
they type it off
what they saw and then forgot the G I
don't understand
stop starting
[Music]
damn luck right yeah
actually surprising
[Music]
show
hey the fire one in Japanese it doesn't
sound so stupid it's just the English
it's really just the English
okay okay and then Here Comes mine
because I got big luck here Thai Kitty
the fortune your gem has no flaw and it
will glisten better when you polish or
good character by Nature becomes much
better I need to polish myself okay when
you polish yourself you will become
known better really
can we get to 2 million
subscribers
you become wealthy and you may have a
repeated stroke of good luck let's go
your help will be come true
the patient will be sure to recover
a patience the last thing is late to be
found but I will find it building a new
house and removal
perfect because I'm in the market for uh
buying myself some place to live it is
good for you making a trip wonderful
because I'm traveling quite a bit
both marriage and employment are good
let's go let's go guys
okay
you know I waited until now to read the
English
um translations I'm so glad I waited
um
so funny oh it's 1am yeah
[Music]
you're welcome here you're welcome I
share this with you you're welcome
yeah and I think there's a bit more is
there
yeah yeah okay so just so you guys get a
little bit of um image
of what this looks like
um
yeah we stood in line it was like the
sun was not setting but it was pretty
late already
so actually it was good because then
it's like less hot but this is the big
Temple it actually
I I'm losing a wide lens angle
uh lens wide lens so it looks like
really wide but it was actually much
taller it felt much taller much bigger
much overwhelming
um yeah we were standing in line for a
while and you go up it's pretty it moves
pretty fast because everybody just goes
up there and claps and makes a wish
Frozen some money yeah so we did that
together
yeah yeah we did it together
[Music]
um
so we did that and then as I told you
you know the shops we didn't see them we
went backwards so after this we went
through the street that has all the
little cute shops and they were all
about to close a lot of them were
already closed
[Music]
ah
um so that was really unfortunate for me
but we still saw a few
you know like window shopping even
though there's no windows
uh and I got some souvenirs some
um oh and we made good advice souvenirs
too I'm like you should buy some
souvenirs while we're here and she I
think she got
oh what did she get I'm not sure but she
got some fancy souvenir
um
um and then we were like okay what to do
now we're actually done so early because
all the shops closed already
um
we don't want to say goodbye just yet so
we were kind of I guess in the mood for
dinner even though it was like early it
was early for dinner I would say like it
was 6 p.m I think
[Music]
or something like that
and so
[Music]
we were like you know at the beginning
of that street and we were looking over
you know remember the store I showed you
and it said
and originally I asked gura what she
hasn't eaten before that we could maybe
eat today
and she said okonomiyaki but I didn't
want to eat
let me be uh selfish for once so I
instead suggested how about tonkatsu
because she hasn't had tongkats since my
favorite food so we were planning to go
to tonkatsu but then we walked away from
the place we wanted to go to so far that
we ended up in front of this Gil katsu
place which was at like a really good
location so it was very busy like people
were standing in line yeah people were
standing in line like crazy for this so
we were like should we try like I wonder
how long we'll wait this might be
might be a long wait but it looks
delicious and I haven't even tried Gill
Cuts before I think you'll Cuts is a bit
different tonkatsu is from
um pork
and and you get it served already like
finished cooked and all that and Gil
katsu is made from beef and uh every
time when you see pictures of gilkatsu
you will always see pictures of the meat
being really red like
like raw red
and that's why I never ate it I think
because I was like I I don't want to eat
it like raw what the
this doesn't look good are you supposed
to eat it like that I'm not I don't
wanna but I didn't realize
that you
finish the cooking process yourself yeah
if I'd have known that oh my God
so after like I think one and a half
hours if not two of waiting we spent the
whole time like chit chatting trying to
you know Chit Chat because like what
else can we do when standing in line uh
in front of the restaurant it was a long
wait
um
trying myself to bring up topics and
translate between everybody
and then finally we got in
[Music]
this is what you get for the taisho gun
the set you can get other things too but
everybody got like different amounts of
portions I got the smallest portion
which was like I think
130 gram Maybe
and good I got like uh one and a half
like if this is what I have is one then
she got one and a half and okay you got
the most yeah wow
for terrorism I'm sorry
yeah so you get like uh two sauces you
get a miso soup and you get some rice
you get salad you get some pickles or
whatever you've got some potato salad
and you get the Gil katsu which is
already breaded but you see how red it
is
always turned me off because I didn't
know you finished grilling it actually
[Music]
so actually
the picture of the grill too because
they're kind of cute they're like they
put these tiny grills
on the table
and they're like
um
there's like a little
candle thing in there
that will heat it up and then you grill
your pieces uh to however much you want
to grill it
um Stone Grill yeah they look so cool
yeah
and you grill it however much you want
it hmm
really cool and so we were grilling it
and mostly
I had my own Grill and Ohio and gouda
share the grill oh no wait never mind
never mind wrong memory we had three
grills you actually I think you can see
it everybody had their own Grill until
the end where
um we only had like a three pieces or so
left but the grills were already dead
um the the flame was dead so they just
um re-flamed one and we just shared the
one for the last couple pieces yeah yeah
[Music]
hello
especially my pieces were the red is for
some reason the other girls pointed it
out like kiwama why your piece is so
especially red I don't know
it took quite a while to get it
to the state I wanted it in this is raw
yeah
I don't know how they even bred it when
it's like this no it's not completely
raw they must have grilled it like a
little bit because the edges are like a
little bit a little bit fainting
[Music]
so yeah that's fun I like in Japanese uh
food Japanese cooking there's a lot of
dishes that are like kind of an activity
you know like Yakiniku and shabu-shabu
Teppanyaki and there's so many like
foods that feel like an activity and
here again you like doing something
actively
um
I really like that because you're you're
your hand is doing something it's fun
it's fun social Foods yeah
[Music]
um
that's why
all those um like
foods are I think great to eat with
friends
yeah it's fun and this was really good
we enjoyed it definitely
it was good stuff and then afterwards
okay oh my God
afterwards yeah we were really full and
then we were like what to do now what to
do now
point I was still hoping there was still
a possibility that Corona Senpai would
join us
but after the dinner that's that's where
I gave up my hope for real for real
um
but then I don't know we still had time
it wasn't so late yet because yeah I
think we ate at like 8 P.M or so
uh in the end and yeah so we decided to
go to karaoke
and we had fun like everybody sang a
song after one another uh
and then at the end we sang One all
together and I sang One with Gouda that
was fun when okay yourself I went to
Idol meeting
um uh we only had like five minutes left
of our time
uh so I threw in one last song and me
and gura sang
um from Frozen Love Is an Open Door it
was so fun because we both got so into
it we both got like really fired up and
emotional like we had so much drama in
our voice and we you know you know you
know there's this part uh we finished
each other's sandwiches that was I was
gonna say and then jinx jinx again
all those parts we were like look at
each other really excitedly with this
big excited expressions and like
did like a little robot dance it's so
cute we had so much fun because she
really likes Disney right I don't I
don't know that many Disney songs but
Frozen songs leave it to me yeah thanks
not bad
[Music]
and that's great that was great
yeah yeah
I'm gonna love Disney ow I know I know
yeah I was like we should sing something
together what she was saying oh we
should sing at the end Queen
oh and yeah okay if I was praising me
for my singing
and I'm like oh yeah you didn't know huh
but that was just like kind of I wasn't
like it was kind of a joke I said it
just as a joke really but
um yeah she I guess she just never heard
me sing before
um
only listening to Gouda never heard how
I sing and I would say I'm pretty decent
you know I sang a lot of like Paramore
and I sang Evanescence
yeah it's good every time when I was
singing my songs My edgy songs she was
like
she was enjoying it so much she was
vibing
[Music]
and and ah then I sang some cuter songs
I sang some Vocaloid too I chose a
really
nostalgic one and yeah both
they also like Vocaloids so you know we
all recognize each other's choices
basically when I chose uh
[Music]
I
haven't heard that one in a long time
hmm
Casino
yeah
yeah I know a lot of
older ones yeah and I was cheering like
uh what what songs was that some songs I
would be like
and oh hi
hi the mood's up
but we had a lot of fun yeah
no okay I said by saying it no Google
sang recently as an homage I guess
um
yeah yeah
so that went on for a while then okay
stand by you know she went home with a
taxi and me and guba I I brought us back
into our hotel uh
where we stayed where we by the way all
had our separate rooms I don't know how
in the Twitter space
something
oh YouTube is back
it was gone I was just talking about
leaving
uh each other after the karaoke
are we good
we're good
okay I was just saying we were leaving
and we were saying goodbyes and I I
brought goodyba home and we were we were
just you know uh
together looking at my phone she was
like mama can I look at your phone like
just because there was nothing to look
at and I was like scrolling for my phone
while we were transporting so we were
scrolling through my Twitter timeline
and
um then then I got the really sad
message
uh
uh right after a really fun day right it
was it was right there and we were like
talking about it and like what the
yeah
um but we were still yeah we're spending
quality time together and then we went
you know back to the hotel
but I just wanted to say we all had
separate rooms in the hotel okay I don't
know what what it what it was in the
Twitter space that made people think
that gouda and AMA stayed in the same
room
clearing it up there in case they didn't
get an opportunity to say they probably
forgot already
we just stated that we had separate
rooms yeah take your meds
context no some people thought I think I
don't know what it was but I think
generally in the Twitter space you know
some voices have been misheard and like
Miss misassigned what's that message um
that my birthday will not be until
December and then also like regarding
because I asked about or we asked about
um
having a myth
of 3D anniversary together and I was
kind of like saying hey I think we all
would sacrifice solo 3D anniversary
chances if we can get uh one together
just kind of like trying to have
trying to I don't know help them out by
giving them less work by only doing one
stream
um
and I thought that way we also have
higher chances to get it on time also
because it's a big event if it's all
five of us
but yeah for that also we got told it's
not happening in September if you want
to do it it will be
I don't even want to say it very late
and because it's that lane it's not even
um I don't know I don't know if we're
still gonna go with it just just letting
you know it was just um
I hope but uh if it's that late you know
it kind of like ruined my motivation for
it if you know what I mean
um
you know when something is just not
happening when it should happen and it's
just so much on a different date then
it's just like
I killed my motivation not only mine so
yeah I don't know maybe we're doing
because because then I was like okay if
it's definitely dead late and instead I
kind of
kind of all insist on having a solo
anniversary so we will see I don't know
if that will happen
um but if it will happen it will be late
um
well no
hopefully in 2024
um there won't be as many delays and
maybe I'll get something
I'm a studio I'm a studio is great but
she can't really capture more than one
person
it's not a problem of Suits she has more
suits than one but it's the problem with
the cameras and they're really expensive
and you know
but I don't expect her to like upgrade
it
that much it would be like tens and
hundreds of thousands like if she wanted
to make it so that she can capture five
people she would probably have to invest
at least a hundred thousand dollars
um at least
probably
I would I would guess so
she can low-key do too now but it's not
like you know I don't know I guess I did
did something change because last time
we did it it wasn't
like she was wearing different things
than me like she could do for example
mokopi while the other person wears the
actual suit but you know but yeah she
she still wants to upgrade it yeah but I
don't know about getting so many crazy
cameras
I don't know anyway I don't expect that
from her and it shouldn't be her like
job or anything she's into it though
she's into the technical side of it and
she's motivated to improve it all the
time
but I don't think we should expect her
to
you know
get on that level that cover has
in terms of quality yeah
but anyway this was the day me and guba
walked back
and I'm happy I could make her happy
foreign
[Music]
a good time
she and ukayu had the best time
and we had good food we had fun in the
karaoke and we did sightseeing
it was a good day in the end
[Music]
yeah I'm a good wing woman I guess so I
just wanted to be with coronation
okay
tangent present for you guys including
pictures tomorrow I will have the
cooking stream which will have the
baking stream which uh will have the
merchandise announcement so in case you
guys want to get the limited signed
merchandise there's a printed sign and
then there's the actual limited hand
signed one
if you want to get that be ready for it
it will be
uh at the second hour like after like at
the second
of that stream
so maybe set your alarm you can go back
to sleep afterwards but if you're like
in a time zone that that stream is gonna
be in the middle of the night for you
I'm sorry about that but
um yeah maybe set yourself an alarm if
you want to get it and then go back to
sleep after you ordered it um
my I never did Limited merchandise
before but I I'll probably mine probably
will not sell out in a second don't
worry
yeah
I doubt it so it shouldn't be too crazy
um no it will not no probably after 10
minutes it will still not be sold out
it's okay it's okay
I got some cute birds for you guys this
time as always so yeah
and then we'll bake a cake and we'll do
some more
um Collins
tomorrow and then jackbox as you know
see schedule
no times because I told you baking
stream 1pm my time so like 11 hours 40
minutes from now I think
and jackbox party at the same time that
this stream started at and make sure to
use that
use half day in 2023 throughout my whole
birthday streams if you want to post
something
um if you want to post some art then use
that in combination with the art hashtag
maybe yeah thank you guys for your love
and support and I'm happy to spend my
third birthday with you guys
um I may not have like super crazy
things prepared for my birthday but I
have cranes prepared for probably next
week I'm working on an album and I'm
working on something that maybe will
come next week so look forward to that
and
yeah I think I hope me just being here
me just me being me is enough for you
guys thank you for your sweet kindness
everybody I will try to catch up on the
super Jazz eventually you know how it is
at these times and let's have some fun
tomorrow I gotta go I gotta like think
about
how it'll be fine it'll be fine it will
be fine setting up everything will
probably take an hour hmm
it'll be fine it'll be fine it'll be
fine I have to sleep and I have to first
eat something though it'll be fine it'll
be fine it'll be fine I'll be fine it'll
be fine I cannot delay the stream
because there was like scheduled
call-ins and everything so that's
stressing me out
and Merchandising but I'll do I'll do my
best I'll do my best
I'll feed us in I'll see you in the next
stream I'll uh I'll be there hopefully
you'll be there too much
foreign
[Music]
should be correct um
yeah yeah let's talk more soon I have um
Zelda tltk planned for the whole weekend
so we'll have a lot of time to talk
there too
yeah
in German we say I'll be dancing
bye bye yeah I gotta go I gotta go I
gotta run I gotta run bye bye
thank you Happy Birthday to me happy
birthday to me happy birthday to this
Phoenix Happy Birthday to me
[Music]
hey
foreign
[Music]
thank you