[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
yeah she doesn't understand how how
amazing all your stock is all right
I use dova syndrome because the syndrome
no don't say that they're not gonna let
us use their music
oh my God you see what I deal with every
day
don't
really all right why do you say that
because any stuff it's so easy to mute
no it's oh man hello
gang's all here
finally gang's all here
howdy yay
[Applause]
yeah also by the way guys we're trying
our best to make do with One mic in the
middle five girls so if someone's kind
of quiet that's okay we're trying to use
our outdoor voices so
yeah and I'll turn down the bgm just so
that it's extra extra hearable okay yay
we finally did it yeah the power of
having several different Wi-Fi you not
username networks networks that actually
helped indeed where Kelly's place and
she has cats yeah the cats greeted them
right when they walked in and the whole
time when we were preparing the whole
time they're like running around and
messing around and then trying to like
kill each other
oh yeah both both Ina and Ahmed had like
jackets over their laps and they were
like putting their hands like like they
were like bopping their hands around
yeah ghost cat was really excited about
that weren't you ghost cat he's hungry
now
but uh he also made me bleed twice
yesterday I was giving him treats
someone's saying you have to count the
cats after we leave because maybe
if you take my cats I will come and take
them they're a little bit too active
right now for me I can't okay I'm not
awake enough for that okay but but I was
like I was um looking at something on
the floor and so I was like on my knees
right and then suddenly I feel something
climbing on my back because I was using
a toy because you're like get one of the
cats to cross like jump on my back and
then it jumped on my back and was like
chilling there
that was fun I felt like a mountain it's
so cute mountains
[Music]
yeah it was really cute actually well I
guess we should do little introductions
but if you are here then there's
wow thank you
I feel like the deadbeats are always
extra nice during these little these
little get-togethers when like other
folks come to the channel because they
want to spread the love to those who
maybe don't have membership to to the
Maui channel welcome you know how to
keep it just you know if you want it so
there's like this whole time there's
just like a cat suddenly running through
everywhere yeah they never calm down
yeah it's crazy hey have you ever seen
them calm
yeah I have I've seen oh my gosh come
back yeah after they eat a ton of food
and like sometimes I'll come downstairs
and they'll just be passed out on the
ground
ghost cat always eats tutus food yeah
he's gotta stop doing that what the hell
he wants to become a big ghost yeah the
ghost cat
well uh I guess I'll I'll go ahead and
start off hi everybody my name is Maury
Calliope and I'm the Grim rapper hi hi
hello I also do I also do a lot of
regular singing these days so I guess
just musician is fine hello thank you
for hosting us you're welcome yeah no
problem no problem cool place you got
here I'm glad you like it it still isn't
quite as wide as some of the other
members but it does the job and oh my
God cats she made us she made us hot
chocolates
[Music]
I do prepare snacks
next who next maybe that lady next to
you hi
it's you stop looking around
it's you it's me
hi nice to meet you why are you being so
polite welcome to my home my party my
friends
[Laughter]
slept how many hours hmm
you know I saw her I was like you know I
was trying to fall asleep for quite a
while and at 1am or so I checked like
real quick my I wanted to write
something to Gemma because you know and
when you lie in bed and you suddenly
like ah oh I forgot something so I
checked and I see Ina streaming and she
started like really late and and and
she's like trying to finish the game I
know and I'm like wait I know where she
is in the game I know this will take
quite a while longer
and I know at what time we had to wake
up so I woke up
but the deadline man the deadline yeah
are you okay though yeah yeah really I
mean I've had worse you're used to not
sleeping so I thought you were gonna
tell me that she got a ton of sleep and
I was gonna say it's about time but just
kidding I guess wow all right
so deadly yeah
[Music]
I also was awake until three I did like
a girl of Valentine's karaoke thing yeah
it was wild it was insane there was some
[\h__\h] moments during that stream
thank you stream elements I guess you're
always about to see who was that thank
you stream elements you have stream
elements commenting in your chat yeah I
mean that's like a moth thing right
there yeah I need to take it off I need
to take it off
it's it still reminds me of twitch I
don't know yeah yeah I don't know I
don't really use it anymore but um okay
how about AME say hello
it's a really nice place you got and the
cats are very very cute yeah they're
actually rooms yeah
yeah
[Music]
I'll show you guys later if you guys see
anyone looking down like anyone looking
down like this there's definitely a cat
by the way they're playing with a cat
and if I look over there and I'm looking
at the other girls because this is not
quite accurate on the screen no it's not
I'm like hey Ina
regiara
what's up
it's so [\h__\h] weird it's fine we do
the best with what we have so we're
somewhere yeah
it's cool
talk loud hello
projects use them
she's here
it's very comfy yeah also please
remember that go ahead and stream really
early this morning so please do not
expect her to scream
oh my goodness
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm also kind of back but like
but I didn't really leave your bag and
then you're gone again and then you're
back for real and then I'm gone again
for just a bit and then I'm back again
for real it just depends
um anyway I'm front by the way oh yeah
front absolutely hey what was awesome
wow you're such a card Kiara
that's okay you want to explain the joke
Kiara because everybody's saying I'm
back I'm back again I said well I'm
Franz I mean
oh my gosh yeah ghost cat always is just
like constantly following too anyway
she needs to defend herself and then
they can start playing without feeling
like she's getting bullied
one time
it's just kitchen things
it's her fault for a waving her tail
like that
is messed up
come on babies oh yeah we had a special
task today oh yeah
a couple days ago I was streaming Fire
Emblem right and then uh the girls were
in the background and we were talking
about you know I guess Valentine's or so
oh and then we had the idea
how about we do Secret Santa Valentine's
Day Edition yeah that's right yeah
who's getting who yeah yeah and we all
got presents for it yeah
[Music]
dude exciting oh yeah white elephant
party I think that's what they call it
I've never heard that before yeah I feel
like I've done it like once the white
elephant in the room showing her dresses
yeah
well who wants to start
um give each other give one I think one
by one then we take a photo put it on
the screen yeah okay okay put it in the
Discord I saved all right put on the
screen
the thing is Kelly said she got gifts
for everybody though I did
yeah it's like the thing where you say
oh this year we won't give each other
presents for Christmas or whatever and
then somebody brings presents for
everybody anywhere and then the others
feel bad about it but it's okay it's
okay I'm absolutely happy though I feel
happy though okay hey may I borrow a
charger from somebody who has lots of
powers
mine's on ten percent thanks only have
so many USB ports in this house allow
this don't allow forget that forget that
all right well
um let me see I guess I'll just tell you
guys what I got for everybody sort of
because I don't know where everything is
but I will I will hand it to them later
um so I got Ahmed like a little
terrarium thing yeah this one we've seen
yeah but right now girl is using it to
pop pepper no she's not using you should
I take a picture oh is it gonna be this
is the same oh yeah everyone knows my
carpet looks like but it's just a
plastic I wonder
I got a little terrarium
super close-up picture
you should put that bag that could have
had behind it oh yeah smart
yeah try that hold on
picture time
enough time
uh let's see let's see where are my
other ones because I got a bunch of
things and I like stored them away
in some shelves
watching the cats
okay it's really hard to take a picture
of this thing that's okay you know we
don't need to take pictures of these
gifts
this one this one this one works okay
let's put Blair filter on it yeah I'm
sending it so there's this one yeah
it's like a girly thing I thought that
you would like cute I got it while I was
in Singapore it's just like how do you
know my cuticles are [\h__\h] I don't know
man
yeah so that's for you
other one
things are getting moved around the cat
sitter must have ruined it wait cuticles
are these things yeah yeah under like on
your nails it's like nails yeah uh here
yeah the line people like push it back
to put on fake nails
[Music]
to get your nails
what fell out the hole there yeah what
no no no no no
no no no guys let's see if we skipped a
little too fast from cuticle oil
this is why I don't get a public house
okay I'm gonna
is there like a filter I know it's
around here somewhere well I got that
we'll put all of them on the screen
after I
this is
good he's good ghost cat Latina's code
warning
if he was asserting his dominance just
don't worry about it let's see um I'm
not sure if I can find the others but
I'll tell you what I got because I just
don't I'm not sure I can find wait
hold on no that's Nintendo um here it is
okay so my gift this is so silly my gift
for Ina is it's it's a marimo it's a
little Moss ball that lives in the
kitchen
it's like a living it's a living
organism so
yeah I know right yes I sent two
pictures for now you can download it on
this girl yeah
[Music]
yeah
should I take a picture of the money
Moon yeah go for it uh the only one that
we can't take a picture of right now is
girls because I actually don't know
where it is I know it's in one of my
three suitcases but it's a necklace
yeah
I didn't have to but I wanted to I
wanted to welcome you guys you know
[Music]
yeah I'll go grab them or oh they're on
Discord gotcha leave it to me
so cute
oh yeah and here's some extra these are
some extra things for your
terrarium there's like a chicken and
like it's more of like a decorative
terrarium than like an actual one but
yeah it has Santa Maria too yeah okay I
get pictures oh they're so big all right
let me see it's cool it's just don't
worry about it makeup oh yeah that's a
safe picture and then open another scene
and then put it in there and then shrink
it and then switch over oh nice idea
actually honey we'll save English
preview okay well but yeah I wanted to
do some extra homework I guess
thank you I will go next yeah next I'm
over for you my secrets
Valentine's was your Secret Valentine
who is it who is it uh by the way um and
I was kind of short notice so I didn't
have um uh present wrapping that's okay
and the shop boy I bought it there was
no present wrapping either
so well no no present wrapping press
okay because you would unwrap it
afterwards anyway
everybody close your eyes okay everybody
oh me too no you're good okay closed
eyes okay okay who will it go to ah who
really got to oh they're so big
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
it's the cat shark mascot oh
cinnamon rolls
[Music]
so cute because you like cinnamon rolls
I just learned that recently which was
such a nice coincidence that's a nice
hint yeah yeah
they're so crazy you're welcome yay I'm
your Cupid oh that's so sweet wait I'll
take a picture
stop doing that ghost cat
stops
that was that description I saw that I
got good at I knew that you would be so
easy to give a gift to
and it really was easy do you have a
little picture that we can show to the
class yes I'm making one now yeah
did you show the others too yeah I'm
slowly Gathering them
wait should I go because yes because you
were the last one yes
belongs to the company so we have to
give it ah what what the [\h__\h] are you
she's just a paper bag that has to be a
meme that can't be real
in the back
ground why cover wants a paper bag back
it's a paper bag give them 10 cents
I truly live in a freaking Society you
guys God I can't even believe it
by the way for the first time I was
Joker and now I understand I live in a
society yeah you wouldn't get it you
wouldn't get it you wouldn't get it
how could it be
crayons I want to know crayons
look up figure
it's a it's a bath bomb with a surprise
oh it's got the surprise in it
oh
yeah I I I I saw some in the shop I was
speaking of Ina too oh so cute
adorable oh no it's not just chocolate
it's not just chocolate
I think this is
that's the one thing that I was trying
to get Amma to buy but she was like no I
can't bring this back oh yeah well I
think it should be fine I have to tell
you it's fine I got it back to Japan
from Singapore so I brought it to Europe
yes there it is there's a little guy
they can last over a century with proper
care yeah mine's the last thing I bought
it like five years ago but I'm not
caring for it at all though I didn't
even try caring for it it's gonna
outlive me
yeah
what did you oh cool are those like lint
chocolates cookie
cookie Ina loves cookies so this is good
all kinds of cookies
oh wow I'm not sharing this yet
[Laughter]
oh should I take a picture yeah is that
a real place
stop eating the cactus ghost cat I am
photo station over oh thank you yeah
we'll post pictures of these ones in a
sec as well
[Music]
yeah just a little one
it's not like a real one or anything but
you know it's it's better that way yeah
yeah exactly yeah yeah yes it's my
problem now ena's Gotta Give a gift
[Music]
let me get a gift the bag is this moment
not related to the items
okay no movement
um my secret I guess yeah
Oh
I thought Kelly was the one through
her and she got one oh no that's just I
got gifts for everybody
oh yeah
it's like
[Music]
like one day you can learn to read oh my
gosh is this manga
that's why you needed to go to the
bookstore
oh my gosh
[Music]
I love you
hey go sky can you not do that
you're so cute yeah okay yeah we're
taking pictures
I know you're very curious this is scary
um
[Music]
this one's cute hey buddy what are you
doing
do you know all this we've read them
she's she's nodding by the way
in case you didn't in case you couldn't
tell
yeah
I can keep it yeah
thank you there's so much excitement
there's so much excitement going on yeah
I know there's so much excitement I know
he's walking all over the table you
can't drink the chocolate ghost cat
you'll become a real ghost it's [\h__\h]
dark
baby I have to protect him okay I sent
the gift from Gua to Ina
they are sent
and you get this back thank you
[Music]
yay
I know who your presence for yeah I
could figure it out I can figure it out
now because I know who I got oh
[Music]
sketchy what have we got give me the
goods I mean give me the goods okay I
can always take a picture of the inside
okay okay
take a picture of the inside
what's in there you get to see what's in
there first
should I take a picture like this
however you want to do it
here oh the crayon Shin Chan stuff oh
you're a little battery down
oh no I tried that twenty percent it's
fine it's fine we're just gonna
mix no it's okay just go back you'll go
back in the same place okay you'll go
back in the same place we've done we've
been through this Rodeo it'll be fine
we're fighting on the cat tower
they're having a standoff
yeah that's what I can't stop her from
doing that I've tried so many times
please two two please don't
like a paper bag okay
yeah they might like the bag actually
they'll be really excited about that
so one second I think I sent the the can
we back here's oh my God it's so
high-rise
which is very big this is Ina's gift
Sorry my phone's just too good after you
shrink it you can double click and then
change the file and it'll be the same
size the last one was oh really wait
it's okay hold on so Nick you have the
other one you could just replace the
file oh yeah I'm putting them underneath
everybody though so you can see that
everybody's like yes
oh
that's smart you guys you guys are smart
all right I've been doing this for two
and a half we have been doing this for a
while hey
I don't know why this isn't it
a long live the king
brush so dramatic they're having a crazy
stand-up books too okay so I'll get the
the book picture and then
see oh this is so cute look at the
cookies oh
yeah
she looked at the picture first I see it
on the front look at this it's a little
um
and I got cookies cookies special coffee
cookies yay I'll never go to sleep and
then a cat toy look at that and more
sweets here you go
again stop fighting with dudes they're
so engrossed with each other
but it's a good one yeah it's a really
good toy
thank you amen I love it so many good
things dang which means you had me I did
but we're gonna have to wait a second
while I well I grab these photos I'm in
charge of the photographs today hold on
a sec
hang on are you sure you can do it you
can do it I got this we're only a little
bit behind on the on the images
it's fine hey baby stop stop doing that
you're getting so rowdy stop babies
it's basically seven people I'm going to
block you here are the gifts uh for a
man a book so much to read so much manga
for amen yay yeah look at this will you
will you when will you be able to finish
all these books
yeah there's a lot going on there you
know exactly curious about the ocean
oh I've actually read that one really
yeah I read it for like an award thing
that I had to announce it was the manga
what's it about
I don't know yeah buddy because
oh yeah kind of like yeah unnecessary
yeah the cause like you can give or take
yeah but in this scenario it's actually
oh yeah
oh like that's the whole story like
someone has a child who and the parent
says that's my this is
[Music]
a child Idol um
the child of the ocean because oh she
has a child
sounds kind of comfortable she's a child
what
what happens what happens the favorite
child
the favorite the favorite Child I want
to read it too give it to me on my
afterwards can you read that one first
maybe you'll get it yeah
okay hey hold on
don't push it off to anyone else there's
an anime coming up let's go yay now I
have my gift for qawwa another one this
is this is Valentine this is the
Valentine
so first I got you cocoa dusted truffles
yeah that's the international store so
it's from overseas so it's Belgium yeah
thank you yeah but this is the best one
I got this from Singapore you can look
at it
yeah fancy I have to download it from my
email
oh the prices on it no that's okay but
they look a little bit like my my yeah
yeah so they are feather earrings yeah I
guess I'll have to
get some holes again do you not have
your ears pierced I I got them pierced
like maybe three years ago for the first
time in my life
and then I I kept those things in right
for for months because they said you
have to keep it in at least like a month
or so but I kept them in for like four
months or so then I took them out
finally because I had to go to the
dentist and and then yeah and then after
I swear after five days
they grew back together
no can you believe it so since then
yeah and now I have a reason to do it
again yeah see that's why I thought to
myself I've never seen you wear any like
feather-like earrings or anything like
that like for real for real these are
not earrings yeah isn't it your hair
that's inside my head yeah just it's
just grown out it's in your head yeah
it's all cute yeah they're Swarovski
Crystals Cali maybe how about oh my God
here's an idea yeah you buy an ear gun
and you just next time I come over for
an awful laugh you
[Music]
see I'm the one suggesting it but I
don't really feel up for it oh okay it
doesn't hurt that much
oh my God
not even piercing the ears just straight
up giving her an ear infection
I don't know man that's a little messed
up let's think about it well maybe we
can get a professional to come here and
enjoy it yeah do you know any
professional ear pierces no but I can
ask around yeah you know and of course I
can always look up a YouTube tutorial
I'm sure it'll be fine a lot of people
do it themselves though right they learn
it and they just do it right I don't
think
it's gonna be that difficult when so
many people try it themselves like right
yeah
[Music]
okay coming soon ear piercings
okay I'll send you this one oh wait show
the money oh don't don't do that to Wawa
it's okay you can take out your claws on
me but not on Wawa
[Music]
he loves the toy yes he does oh you
happy boy yes you are a happy boy oh
he's really happy oh look at that boxer
oh he's a little boxer oh my gosh she's
so happy are you a happy boy
did you know that Swarovski actually is
from Austria I didn't know that
one of the few things that are famous
from Australia
Swarovski it's the ski well apparently
yeah
cool wow I didn't know that that's so
cool
foreign
found it 18.95 in Austria yay what a
lucky coincidence
you have like a Swarovski world where
you can go inside but they don't allow
taking pictures what which is like what
the [\h__\h] that's very strange it's just
so weird about it
maybe maybe
I'm gonna take up this check and I'm
getting home
all right yeah we got the presents we
did the present Happy Valentine's Day
Valentines and even though you guys may
not be hungry for chocolate right now
you guys can take the chocolate I
prepared for you let me go home yeah
yeah and also I got um chocolate covered
potato chips so we're gonna try a little
bit later
[Music]
and now something for us
way past seven minutes
awesome Oh I thought it was wait I'm
such a donut oh okay
I'm so dumb I thought it was 10 30. time
isn't a concept to me hey would you mind
passing me the chocolate covered
potatoes
let's do it all right
is this like you know dipping potato
fries and ice cream no it's much
different these are Gourmet Gourmet I
don't know people hype them up a lot so
it's like chocolate covered Pringles
yeah
it's the Japanese size you can put six
in your mouth
there you go
I don't know if is it okay
[Music]
um
they're good they're good though they
pour chocolate like in a chip mold um
that's dangerous that's super dangerous
I can't eat these anymore this is
perfectly fine this is not like
controversial or anything dang it it's
just a shape I was fooled it's just a
shape that's weird sorry Chad we were
robbed I'll get them next time
come on ghost cat we have three glasses
of water on this table please don't
knock them over
please okay maybe one more
he's interested
he's sniffing everything
very interesting
he's like you guys are telling me no at
everything I do what should I do what am
I allowed to do yeah
[Laughter]
so cute
and his belly is so soft but yeah
I was explaining this um to the others
before my finger I was explaining this
to the others before but um
so his breed is actually munchkin
um they're the cats with like the really
short legs they kind of look like wiener
dogs but for cats but he was the only
one in his litter that didn't carry on
the short leg Jean
um and so his legs are super long and so
it made him super cheap and I'm like why
that's why I want him yeah I want him
for his long legs that's so ironic that
she the the healthy one is cheap yeah so
sad I mean no it made me sad but I was
like nope I will get you and I will love
you forever isn't that right ghost cat
oh you love him I do think munchkins are
super cute but like you know
that's just sad yeah it made me sad love
every cat on the world ever camp
[Music]
he's super long too he's getting longer
every time aren't you you don't think
you're just longer
years longer oh and tutu has an Audi
belly button I didn't know until Ahmed
told me that is so weird I've never seen
that on a cat before yeah did you feel
it no not yet because she won't let me
touch she won't even come over
she always stop there because you two
are playing so much
thank you be careful though because
ghost cat is gonna get kind of weird
I I listen to your to your eyes so much
[Music]
yeah it sounds really weird
my cats react to when I shake the
children don't they react no I don't
think they know what it is yet hold on
[Music]
it's chicken
all right
motivated
you gotta you gotta show it to her
you gotta let her smell it oh my god oh
[\h__\h] he's here I want to get rid of like
this question yeah don't forget your
mission no no no no no no no the treat
is here
treat is here oh yes she's very healthy
cat
or that one it's popping out yeah it's a
bump but it's like soft it's like a soft
bump wait sorry here there you go there
you go there's something
she's really excited she'll start biting
the wrapper
oh my God
more aggressive than my cats
oh my god
oh the smell of the of the chicken is
like wow hungry right you just wanna
take a bite oh
dissolve it in some hot water I don't
eat chicken noodle soup oh God
a real sick from this chicken smell holy
[\h__\h] that's really really cool are you
holding it right under your face I don't
know because we're in this position now
it's difficult to change it now touch
the belly button
it's like holding on to my my head but
it's like it hurts
but it's good but as long as the cat
hurts me oh
[Music]
I just I just can't breathe for the nose
anymore oh yeah cause it's uh
[Laughter]
I didn't have purple breakfast
I love you
bite my finger off probably at this rate
because you're not squeezing it out
on her
[Music]
loves you look oh she'd never hurt you
did you touch the belly button yeah I
think so a little bum
it's not that bad in the snow and her
underbelly's so soft
smells a cat
sniff the cat I'm in so much pain but
it's okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
do you have like a wet tissue or
something like that it's okay I got a
plan she's got it on her hand oh
my God
are they gonna tweet it or not no no no
we're gonna do it in two minutes or so
okay
thank you
my fingers are stinky now I got you I
got the wet tissue I got all the cat mom
the whole cat over here thank you thank
you here you go
come on yay okay all right it's
announcement time
oh
yeah we have a video right yeah foreign
[Music]
well I guess instead of hinting we
should just go and show you yeah
gonna go show you all right here we go
here we go get ready for a special
trailer are we gonna be mutant
um yeah okay okay here we go muting bye
hello
[Music]
everybody
your oh she's waiting
for mythical beings
[Music]
whoa you know just slid away
oh boy
[Music]
yeah
oh geez
[Music]
yeah
where is Kiara okay now now I need now I
need to take a ticket you can have mine
you can have mine there we go it's time
everybody hold on let's move the Bell
out the way so you guys can see the time
again
yay yay it's finally here finally
we waited so long it was about time yeah
starting from February 18th which is
this Sunday this Sunday with Emma oh
Saturday yeah
yeah
it wasn't just for fourth Fest you
sillies we had other things planned that
was also starting to feel like kind of
bad because I know you know some of my
friends were like oh a lot of school I
was so busy and I'm streaming and I'm
like I'm sorry but it's really like
like happy what's
up
and talking to people takes a lot out of
you rehearsals and all kinds of things
are you know behind this kind of stuff
it's not a corner of my party that does
not ache right now yeah
really hard oh but I guess it doesn't
show on this schedule that you know
after all of us having our individual
showcases that we're doing uh wait a
minute actually there's oh there we go
hold on I'm gonna work you know what we
need to get the [\h__\h] out of here so I'm
gonna show everybody what's going on
okay there we go only Wawa yeah 3D
stream on March the 5th at 12 p.m jst
March the 4th 7 P.M PST uh which is
basically so this week is Ina then the
week after is me and Cal and me and
Carly right and the week after is good
on Ahmed and then after in the same
weekend yeah is the food yeah
the day after Ahmed so it's like and
then collab yeah yes March 5th 12th
I am
it's finally happened let's go we waited
for so long we did wait for so we did
finally
used but like finally use them you know
yeah like yeah you know like really
yeah like really for real like there's
just no good place to put us here
yeah that's right down oh true that's
such a good idea actually hold on a
second let me I'm gonna do that but
gravity to fire myself let's see very
nice we'll do once clockwise oh my Lord
all right I feel like we've been through
this before hold on a second uh flip
like vertical uh
180 degrees why did you not just run
through I'm just not the smartest
I'm just not the smartest
hold on just chill we're coming we're
coming
there she goes I'm Australian after all
we all knew it we all knew it nothing
nothing bad about being Australian it's
okay to be Australian sometimes yeah
yeah so we're happy starting this Sunday
Saturday you know I look nervous
[Music]
you know it it's gonna be great and you
know a lot of other fantastic things are
going to be happening too
um so keep your eyes peeled because this
month is gonna be big and so is next
month yeah
there are other things happening we
can't tell you about it what
like what you guys know I mean
what else have you had done what else
have you have had to record
with like your voice and stuff
oh you know what I'm saying
the other thing huh
okay okay
[Music]
yeah I didn't know what's happening I'll
tell you later it's so many things it's
a thing that I kept asking for over and
over and over again but yes soon yeah
what does that mean you're gonna find
out sooner rather than later yeah
so starting this Saturday Sunday yeah
it's gonna be like a festival right up
until you know
it's so fast it's finally our time to
shine we waited two and a half years for
this unbelievable but the time has
finally come we're here together to do
this and we're gonna do our best to you
know get everything out of our bodies
that has like accumulated until now yeah
all the that sounds kind of energy oh I
mean that is you know I just gotta call
you out and say something strange about
this okay I think our brains are still
asleep we're just like baby sleeping
yeah honestly me too once I actually
fully woke up and fed the cats I was
like my friends are coming home
it's gonna be cool you guys are finally
here in Japan yeah of course it wasn't
just gonna be for for fourth Fest of
course we were gonna take the
opportunity you know to get everybody to
be able to debut their 3D finally gosh
finally
hope you guys are excited for it as we
are I'm so exhausted my calves are
killing me yeah lots of dancing
[Music]
oh it's cutting more more dancing
I've been I've been practicing uh Scythe
choreography science choreography yes
what does that mean you have to come to
the the 30 debut to find out because
I've been practicing with a professional
what yeah a professional weapons person
so a professional side fuser yeah
because I'm really rusty with this well
I mean you don't really use I mean
humans don't use Suds the same way that
Shannon got me do but like some of the
stuff with like using like swords and
stuff
grassing some grass well yeah initially
initially we were like talking about
like you use it like this and like the
the dude was like
and it was like very like like low and
like low-key just going back and forth
I'm like this is how he reap Souls I
just don't I think they'd all get away
this is how you realize it yeah I'm
misusing the set you've been misusing it
yeah yeah yeah you can tell that to
death
you can't tell that's a death Sensei I
mean technically We Are Farmers of souls
we are harvesting you're a farmers
that's why I love Harvest Moon yeah
[Music]
yeah it's cool don't worry about it not
endorsed not endorsed let me play your
game though uh We're not gonna do this
again we're not gonna do this again I've
learned my lesson
well I guess that's what we had to say
also additionally if you guys haven't
checked out the Valentine's merch you
really should that do not feel cute the
videos are so cute yeah you guys can
look to everybody's Roots You Better
Play Everybody's you completionist yeah
you guys go on the whole live English
Channel if you haven't seen it there's
one like public starting video and from
there on oh I disappeared I guess it's
not charging from there on you um go to
unlisted videos yeah yeah also if you
haven't played through it yet if I may
suggest
um there's no real order to play them
but you should do my root last
you kind of did like a uh what do you
call that lady
which one from the uh that game the
visual novel game with the crazy oh yeah
yeah who acknowledges that you were like
you know there and you spoil it don't
smell it
yeah breakfast oh yeah definitely me
going down to rain like killing the
viewer oh yeah definitely that's what
happens right guys fake spoilers in chat
fake spoilers in chat
it's okay go go go watch it though go
play it you should you should do mine
last look at my eyebrows
she's raising them I can do that too if
I have big white eyes
only then skill issue I know right truly
said
[Music]
something else is moving more than my
eyebrows excuse me I'm sorry
I see
seriously you're cute oh
that's so adorable I love that look at
the flaps you know you're so cute
completely covering her
she's smelling the back of your head
I said Ina's so cute
stop that I have the power here I have
the power here there she goes no no you
can't no you can't I will fight for my
room hey guess what this has a limit
this has a limit
I got him
you gotta say sorry
[Music]
Mama because there's tools who's the
real one
she's showing off you're showing off
here
well give us your cues oh one question
what just happened
um yes we announced that was I guess the
question the three Bizzle it's good at
sleeping
[Music]
she's just tired yeah that was oh there
goes my phone that's okay I can be in
this pose for the rest of it it's really
fine it's fine
how does yours survive without being
connected
mine was
fun
it's a skill issue
[Music]
and oh not always on my phone
the taxi I was just staring outside the
whole time
oh yeah if I'm not looking out the
window I'll throw up somebody says in
the pop-up parade is the 3D merch
good timing coincidentally yeah
definitely go check out the new the new
figures but I want the rest of the crew
where is everyone yeah
I'm lonely
um
from the Korean Cafe that we had to pull
out the face I have the pile of eggs
I just don't really use power Banks and
then I'm always like gosh I wish I had a
power bank oh yeah they exist good merch
there is but you could only get it in
Korea huh yeah
[Music]
it's Lumber party which one of those
yeah yeah we're too busy today probably
yeah but while everybody's here I mean I
wanted to off collab with everybody at
least once and then also a lot more time
too yeah I also uh Ian and I kind of
talked about it but we wanted to do like
a little trip with everybody like a
little one it doesn't need to be far you
know
preferably one that we can like take a
train to or something yeah what was that
neck cracker yeah I am in pain don't
mind me cracking my neck
hold on a minute here I recall you
telling me not to crack my neck ah well
it's too late for me
or yeah
um
what what you thought of catching Ina in
the elevator what
I also run into you randomly when I came
back I think or when I was leaving you
would say brought you together and you
were coming back and I'm like oh I think
I was shocked when I I came out of the
elevator so I saw him like
[Laughter]
that moment I see her and I'm like
oh my God I'm too easy to like scare
incredible heart attack
I know that well well you're probably
gonna come to my place for sock puppet
and Rubik's Cube families perspectively
and I guess ear piercing too is that
really a thing we're gonna do because
I'll buy an ear pierced gun hold on
Amazon yo don't don't mess with me I'll
look at I'll look enough
any other cues what other cues do we
have ask us anything
within reason
I wanted to do it probably at our place
so that I don't know Kelly can come over
but I wanted to do a movie watch along
because this is like you know we can
actually cozy up together
anything but you know I'm always up for
Lord of the Rings let's watch the next
one I have to know what happened hey
Kiara oh it's cheap disposable ear
piercer instant ear piercing with 1
100th of a second one 100 what does that
mean it's really fast can we get any
faster maybe maybe practice it on on
something somebody says who's the
strongest we already had arm wrestling
games
probably yeah
I don't know wait maybe you feel our
muscles
um is pretty strong I feel like me and
Amir yeah
[Music]
oh I was just holding it
I don't know why like at the room
on my table
um she's lying down she's a table
Callie's first coffee
that's warm yeah I have a heated carpet
three minutes
what's up
okay well this clearly won't be I don't
think this will be the last off collab
that we do together but I'm gonna
rematch me
we should do let's just wait till I go
to y'all's place please Kiara please I
tried guys I tried I got a list
again come back I keep on leaving
because
yeah okay I'm not I'm not a [\h__\h] I
promise I'm not it's just there's too
much stuff on my table also one of the
legs is kind of wobbly and like it's
this one right here because okay so I
got a faulty product as I twisted in the
legs it turned out that like this little
area where you twist it in is smooth and
doesn't have like like
um what is how do I describe like I
couldn't like screw it in it didn't have
yeah I didn't have grooves it was smooth
so I had to use a hammer to try and hit
it instead it still didn't go all the
way in so it is what it is I don't want
to break my table I have to put my books
back under the table also because I have
my books under here so that just in case
it falls down my cats don't get hurt oh
yeah I have a bunch of books in my Eldon
ring book that was the one that me and
Nina looked at together yeah
yeah you know you look so comfortable
right now it's warm and fuzzy yeah you
fall asleep
but yeah but at least you can sleep well
on the floor she looks very comfy oh
gosh she's eating on the floor yes she
is why is anyone surprised no one's
surprised actually
hi babies did you calm down
yeah they seem pretty cool well I
haven't eaten dinner they start to chill
a little bit but they're still a little
frisky I kind of have to force them
[Music]
I wonder what's for dinner oh sorry
breakfast
breakfast oh my God
again like I said I have no concept of
time is Cali's Florentina certified yes
looks like it looks like it
oh
in off the floor what is your wisdom
um
you still have more practice because we
we're like gonna be practicing up until
our each of our
dates and then for the collab stream too
yeah
yeah sold this and that oh yeah so yeah
her belly button's so big
come here come here how many hours of
sleep did everyone get today not enough
I got four hours ten four seven three
some two I got six when I woke up and
looked in the mirror I saw my eyes were
inside you know they were all red some
veins popped are they still red
no but I saw them earlier I noticed they
were a little right I looked like I
don't know I I don't know I drank
alcohol or something but I didn't I
didn't I know no alcohol consumption was
consumed wait no except maybe
except except you know
hmm which is one just one yeah
what just one hmm did Dida even feel it
did she even feel that
she said it was just a what a sour a
sour lemon sour or something
pineapple sour yeah
um
oh yeah I found a bunch of restaurants I
wanted to go with you guys that have
cool looking drinkies that are like
mocktails also oh my God yeah yeah with
the beachy themes and stuff like that
because someone asked why are you upside
down there's a good question at this
point
details of the 3D collab stream let's
switch also oh yeah the other one see
the other one as well hold on a sec good
are you sleeping
good enough
there she is is she moving they're
Australians
oh you're moving yeah
karaoke oh
or a song or something today
I'm just suggestion but yeah I don't
have time to do we should do like a for
reals singing off-cola
um like like when we were
over there yeah acapella now
[Music]
we should we should make a acapella band
where everybody is an instrument one of
those things where like everybody joins
in with like their own sound like okay
Boom Boom Beach
[Music]
Christmas is
fun
oh come on
we're always fine we're YouTubers come
on
are you a hater of Pentatonix is that
what you're saying
you
on the level of Pentatonix excuse me
I feel like you've done more cringe
rings than that
yeah right
it's okay to be a little self-aware
come here
it's cool
with all of our powers combined
here
ghost cat loves to do the the limb it's
like the sticking out
them I'm gonna let Callie's drinking
he's not really a fountain it's just
like oh
it's like a bird bath where they drink
out of what was
what was the idea to put this right next
to the office
stepping in your water water fountain
next to the power outlet what could go
wrong
oh somebody said that the Camellia just
uh released a song with Ina in it yeah
help them out
yeah I provided for one of this one
she's saying she provided vocals for one
of the songs in case you're not hearing
it because she's too far away
[Laughter]
like three meters away
they're fighting over the toy again yeah
yeah but she was looking at her phone
it's always too far away she's growling
over it well Lads this has been a fun
time thank you so much for coming over
to my place
of course I was happy to where'd she go
is she gone again ah because you oh it's
because I moved sorry that's my bad
somewhere sorry she's around here I just
can't there she is there's what are they
doing
you guys
all right
finally it's out finally finally can't
contain yourself
[Music]
um
I'm taking um
[Music]
no it's because I'm prepared for my own
life
you're gonna do so great
I was actually like you know surprised I
tried to teach you know something before
right I try to teach you too yeah
something and but like I feel like this
time you've been
uh picking everything up so fast you
know I usually do I just didn't
it wasn't in the movies yeah you didn't
feel like it I know that
yeah you were not motivated by then but
now you seem very motivated so let's see
that motivation in motion this weekend
on Sunday or Saturday depending on your
time I'm gonna cheer for you let's go
so get excited you guys
yay thank you take care bye everybody
is super
[Music]
foreign