hey
hello hello hello
[Laughter]
exactly hi my audience
thank you chad good game
okay i'm still uh just giving you a
mistake i'm adjusting audio
how is the volume now everyone can you
hear
with with me in comparison to the others
yes
hi can i have some food please i just
gave you some steak
oh thank you oh thanks
hello hello hello
thank you for the steaks how long is
waiting for those
huh yeah all right put them away i don't
need them anymore i'm making a weapon
oh wait where is this girl he's my cow i
mean my hair ah okay
my house
if you guys have weapons we and you have
like any xp
i have some stones here you guys can use
and you go into this basement and you
can enchant your weapons
uh you guys haven't done it yet hang on
a sec
yeah i tried it earlier today let's put
them on
whoa wait did you enchant your uh
arms my what your iron sword or diamonds
oh yeah yeah yeah no my oh okay i didn't
make a diamond sword i'm just like
i just mind more times skills
oh may i borrow some lapis lazuli oh
hey is this the good one
[Music]
do you maybe first of all want to tell
the viewers what the hell we're doing
i don't know even i have
and then we're going to the never
together and all going to die
to the nether i want to ride a stride
fine hang on
i'm trying to adjust my i've never been
there before what's it what's it like
what kind of things happen hot with lava
that makes you stronger for like uh 20
minutes really
okay cool yeah i'll do that i'm level
one i can't enchant anything
now where is my bed in the house huh
i'll make one
do you wanna chat something girl i can
do it for you
uh yeah wait why
i have a lovely down below 27.
it doesn't take away it takes away your
level though you do this
it just takes a little bit oh okay here
we go in the 8 9 27.
you enchant my bow for me of course
is that i have pirate speak on my game
so everything is pirate language
so um that's cool i want that
okay girl they're both unbreaking so oh
wait i thought i thought it had never
ending bolts i thought that was never i
thought that was uh it's random
i think it had never ending bolts over
here
i'm going to give you guys a piece of
gold armor because i'm breaking
nothing wait give me you know you know
all right wait give me you guys rather
have
pants boots or a hat gold um
a golden snapback i guess it depends on
the person yeah it's per player it
changes on purple layer okay
you have to unlimited yeah yeah i have
unlimited on that
i have the boots because it has a curse
of binding and i don't want i think i
should wear them because i don't know
i don't know if you could take them
thank you though thank you
no problem we're going to banana
yeah breakable unbreaking hat
i'm breaking i thought no grab my i need
to go grab my hat i'll be right back get
out golden snap bag
oh golden snapback yeah i'm just
pretending this game is all about
pretending so i'm pretending it's a
golden snapback
oh i know this seminal oh my goodness do
you see all this
you know i want a gold hat oh
i don't know what that is vanishing it's
like harry potter
nothing right yeah okay i thought you
were still enchanted
where are you oh i need a sword
if i die trying to catch fish that is
wait does anybody want shiny pants
ooh i do are they free yeah i'll take
them how do you like shiny pants
yes i'm very behind in this game because
i don't have time to play games
so please we got you yeah
[Applause]
is everyone okay what's going on
having a crisis over there uh-oh
i don't know what's going on hello good
are you coming i don't know i hear
screaming
i'm just scratching over there he's just
kind of oh he has an enchanted bow he
might start shooting at us
that's the cave where i wanted to live
oh no where's that yeah watch him let
him
go yeah make a shot make a shot take a
shot yeah come on yeah i dare you yeah
yeah you're a coward he's a coward a
coward
put more uh angry in your voice yeah
really get it
hey you mother f word no more cursing
guys no more cursing from me
hey stinky
he doesn't like being called stinky no
he doesn't
i'll get him oh no i'm using the wrong
weapon hang on i don't mean to use uh oh
oh no i just threw it with my pickaxe
away where'd it go
it's gone i lost it it's gone forever a
smoker
okay yeah i'm eating
hello friends uh i need him
hey somebody needs a picture i just you
have an arrow in your head
watson you have an arrow in your knee
and in your
hand i hate that i used to be a
traveler like you oh
it's in my hand we're mining again
apparently there's a lot of gold
oh okay i have a question
um i have how do i hold things in two
hands and how do i switch
like haters
you can scroll through your your hot bar
like the stuff on the bottom
yeah you mean yeah but uh you guys are
holding things in two hands right
oh yeah yeah so if you if you press e
and then you see there's like a little
square on the right side next to your
feet that's like a equip hey callie say
hand again
hand i like the way you were saying it
before your like hand
oh really my left hand
oh my left hand oh apparently you can
just press f to switch them
okay between the two hands okay um i
only have one slot and it has a thread
in it
um yeah and then you can you can use
your hot bar on the bottom and you can
scroll through other stuff okay yeah you
got it
sorry i pressed what i have no memory
you you're doing it you got it
but i hang on oh the idiot idiot i got
it you want to switch
hands you could press f yes got it oh
sick okay understood understood
got it so i was i wanted to say an
announcement really quick
the holo rail is now complete
[Music]
it took us so long good job once
on your roof the thing on your roof
looks amazing
how do we build this portal i have
obsidian in my hand do i just complete
it
uh yeah yeah oh yes where did you get
the obsidian
from i mined it with a diamond pickaxe
that i made
yeah the nether
yeah what is that is that okay if we
leave it there
oh well if it doesn't complete itself
then we can get rid of it
do i make it one volume taller no i'm
making baby cows hold on
okay i got i got the music
okay do you already have like a [\h__\h] ton
of weapons with you
i like to have
look at everybody glowing over here
yeah we're shopping
wait are we guessing how do we make this
wide five pounds are we breaking out the
wiki
i need one more thing uh this and this
and this is
okay now maybe oh i gotta remove that
block i think
wait one two three three four
i don't want to go get okay oh my mine's
close my house is right here
okay oh
um i'm playing the minecraft soundtrack
from the internet
because oh yeah i totally forgot about
music
yeah i think we talked about them we
don't
i mean my minecraft doesn't even play
music so i guess it'd be best to play
what doing what kelly's
yeah that's that's what i've been doing
hey where did you guys get your shields
iron and wood oh okay cool i'm gonna do
that real quick
let me just whiten me up
you don't even have a house i guess it's
over here
yeah i think i have a house you gotta
build one
yeah i guess so huh oh they like you
moving out this area
up here this this mountain what do you
guys think should i fly it out so we
have more room to build
yeah over here wait what mountain door
what
i'm gonna flatten this out this big
mountain what are you doing
kelly i'm looking for my chest i know i
had one i mean yeah
oh do it watson do you only have a quack
okay i mean i guess it was okay
first portal to the nether
[Music]
created a uh first yeah no problem
thank you yes you need a shield yes i
will create the shield where was my
house again um
it's i think it's gone oh yes my chest
is here but i have no house because the
creeper blew it up and then i got tired
of a new one i'm gonna build you a
temporary house
just live with me i would keep you safe
i'm good
i'm gonna i'm gonna throw this down here
i know that i have iron
iron
let's see can i make shields out of
anything else
by chance oh i need i need arrows for my
bow wait
oh i got some arrows oh i have feathers
you can use two
oh wow you made
like a farm damn wait how do you make it
yeah
how do you make arrows stick
and iron something maybe iron nugget i
don't know
i give up this is too much
[Music]
i really miss playing video games i just
i'm not good at him anymore
gosh back in the day
oh no i took it again in this stream
it's called pointy rock
[Music]
okay what do we need and food sword
pickaxe food
uh need a bed um i have one i have a bed
i have already i took it from my own
first okay okay okay oh yeah make sure
don't
don't forget your breads okay you want
you want to heather
i have 10 shots and then i'm screwed
that's not a lot that's fine whoa
there you go you have sticks
[Music]
oh chicken okay i need to kill chicken
ah
i need to kill uh do you have um
pointy rock pointy rock
yard lassie is that an actual item have
you a pointy rock
i don't know what that is it's a flint
oh oh yeah i have a bunch of flint here
who is mr pierce
lincoln i like him thank you
have you seen bradley and his family
callie
no i haven't can you introduce me yes
come come listen
thank you i want to meet them how do you
me
how do you get that what hang on
[Music]
it's interesting actually because every
every time that i call
an animal or for example a dog or a cat
a default name i always call them
but because watson has a dog named
everyone
get me
yeah he's dumb he's too tall uh he's
going to chase me forever
oh that's unfortunate i love your dogs
i think i can kill him uh he can't get
in the three-way he can't get in the the
door so if you uh
i don't know he's gone no he's right
here but he can't get
we gotta get him to stand in front of
the door cause he's only he's three
blocks tall so he can't pass under a two
block
oh jorgen hey buddy
oh i feel like he's gonna die
no no no no no no no i got this listen
oh wait you guys are in the mine aren't
you now we're we're at my house right
now
is trying to kill the intermittent
sounds really odd
yeah something sounds strange something
there's water on the wall over there why
is that how do i harvest my
my my crops uh with an empty hand
you just touch it yes just yeah which
reminds me i need to
put the game slow this is my home from
now on
this is my home come on come on enderman
an extra carrot i could have i have some
dirt yeah for my carrot form
okay thank you welcome
you don't have any beets or melon i have
melon
i have beer roots oh wait what
beetroot carrots beer roots
beetroot this is my swimming pool this
is my swimming pool now
mr england's area i think it's mine now
okay this is not a swimming pool yeah
it's it's in here already for me
i think he's gone already
you scared him off i think i did
my home is perfect well not yet but it
will be
sorry i'm just very excited let me know
when you guys are ready to go by the way
i don't want to hold us back
did we open the uh open the gate i
forgot uh no
not yet i have other okay okay oh wait
it's just the one block right yeah hold
on
yeah okay i'm just gonna pull it away
get prepared probably should make a
couple pickaxes huh
oh yeah we need that uh maybe we should
craft some materials yeah
i will help you shortly in just a moment
it is dummy
okay oh there's a gap in the wall
what's on this side it goes outside evil
witchery of disappearing
my house is big well it will be big uh
let's bring it in
okay do i have iron nope
what do i need flint and steel for i've
never used that for anything
um
i thought i knew that but i i don't
remember there's something
something nether is there water in the
nether no
no there's lava though only lava lots of
lava
you can make a lava boat see lettuce oh
that's what you use the strata for
do you guys know about the striders
no what's that the striders are
for you ride them
you can walk on uh lava with striders
what else
in the world renovation is done for
today
yeah so if we see striders we can uh we
gotta get some stuff but then we'll be
able to ride them they're funny-looking
and then oh great look at my pool
everyone is wonderful anyway this is my
house
congrats on the new home thank you whose
house is this what is this
is this a farm it's not very safe cali
that's very cute it's not very safe
it's it will be it i'll i will format it
later when we're not visiting the nether
i don't want to hold this up
wow okay
i'm ready yes i just need to put in my
blood who has a llama
yeah i still did you steal this from it
she stole it from the merchant no
i borrowed it
[Music]
sounds like you stole it yarn
hey that's fine i i don't have a problem
with it i want a donkey
yes what am i gonna okay okay i will go
to the gates
okay this is this tall building it's a
farm what is this
ah a blast oven
[Laughter]
wait i need to make out does anybody
have a pickaxe lying around that i can
have
maybe uh yeah i have like uh
i have two extra oh nice
hey you mm-hmm
are you feeling breaking things anyway
oh yes now my chest is protected thank
you for whoever
that protection are on my chest you know
i think i stole your llama
huh i think people are saying that i
accidentally tamed your llama so i think
you need to
reassert your dominance did i say callie
i think i meant inna my ben
yeah look he's looking at me
oh
yeah yeah yeah now he's looking at you
okay okay okay okay
i want him to spit at me how do i make
him spin it i'm farming
a bad girl that girl i hit it how do i
make him spit
at me consistently no don't hit it no
a little tap on the butt little tap on
the button all right are we ready
okay we're ready yeah i'm ready okay
okay
go ghost rider's
[Music]
let's fix this up it's happening
here we go
i think i know what you need you need
that little uh thing that makes
dip and then it's there what what zip
huh flint and steel anybody have flint
oh
are you here let me drop it oh i will
oh it's in my box what do we do we like
right click with it and then it like
does like a chat
you gotta light it on fire uh yeah here
somewhere only a ring of fire
there you go pointy round you need point
you got it you should whoever has it do
the honors oh okay
okay
i shall make our first ever
[Music]
what happens in here everything
all the fun okay in one of your chests
i'll put it in one of your chests okay
okay how do you hold up a shield by the
way
right click oh okay you gotta do that
like if somebody's shooting arrows at
you you have to
you can't you have to block i mean you
walk really slow with it up okay
it's not just like a passive thing yeah
okay nevermind sorry
i'm gonna bring the rest of the obsidian
with me just in case we need to make
like another portal or something
we can do that right it'll like lead out
just somewhere else
huh yeah
juice yeah i noticed i'm missing shoes
i can make you shoes yeah i might have
some just kidding
i cannot buy stuff we need shoes wait
what do i need did you grab your bed
yeah i have one okay perfect are we
supposed to
keep in the nether really yep yeah we
have to save it just
in case uh we die oh okay
that doesn't sound right in my brain
yeah
what do you know about minecraft i don't
know that much about minecraft but
that's something something's telling me
that
there might be a little bit of trickery
going on yeah i have a weird feeling
right now i don't know
what you guys are saying do we have some
cheeky people in the chat today are you
guys trying to mess with us
[Music]
why would we no this is our first time
in the netherlands together come on
come on don't worry about that for
everyone we just wanted to go well
just want to have fun wait what
[Laughter]
i'm only sleeping in the nether if you
guys are sleeping i have my best friend
i have
my bed i'm totally sleeping in the never
i brought my bed
oh boy let's see it's another
slumber party i'm coming
[Music]
all right who wants to go first you can
do the honors
no no no all right all right i got this
thank you all right let's go first you
got to stand in it
there you go there you go
oh there's something here
it's red and square and has wings
that might be a strider what was that
[Music]
bye
that's we can ride them if we have uh we
need a saddle and then we need to uh
we
[Music]
what's this block there's a much less
more powerful mushroom up there i need
to
pass out yeah what's this um
i can i can is this soul sand question
mark
looks so
coordinates
i think like one block and another is
like eight in the world or something
like that
it's like multiplied yeah whoa oh that's
not great i don't like that oh gold
i'm good um um i think something to
just to keep in mind i i'm not a
minecraft uh encyclopedia but you see
these pig people down here
uh-huh yes they uh don't touch them they
won't hurt you if you don't hurt them
okay okay oh okay yeah just watch it
well they'll see me and know that it's
fine
i want this goal oh my god careful
what it's fine huh be careful
i'm not going to say anything i'm not
going to say anything
yeah okay nope not going to die
wait my the lava lava
welp i think we're up pretty high there
i mean who is up there
what are you doing i want to get the
gold in the ceiling
here's gold oh that's i guess that is
gold huh you guys
so there's pink people right that uh
won't hurt you but there are other types
of characters that will hurt you
yes yes you know
oh this is the pig people will hurt you
if you are
close to them and uh mine some gold
i think really
if you fall away then they don't care
but if you do it like somewhere close to
them they will follow you until you
die there's more gold we should go down
i like him i want him as a pet can we
bring him back
yeah we just need to get down there
we need a station and a mushroom
maybe build a stairway it's hard
build a stairway down it's okay we'll
figure it out yeah there's some details
um
but it's kind of dark adventure
i have some touches okay
this is good guy look at him the white
um
[Laughter]
yeah i think so maybe
this music is nice does anybody else
hear that no
i have a no i have my music yeah oh okay
what do we do there's a big there's a
bubble we go up here
blob oh what there's a black bob thingy
what is that lava slime
oh we're still high up should be
somewhere
huh
[Music]
how do we get anywhere
okay parkour everybody
yeah that should be easy where the
the red rock is
oh oh there's a guy up there with a
sword there's where do we go
there's a dude there's three guys there
it's like
okay i really like this place
rock oh black world yeah guys be careful
tina's going the other way you guys oh
no i want to come back
okay um i'll follow the group we can all
do
no say we can all dig down on this but
is there going to be like a gap
underneath if we go down
straight down does everybody know to
hold [\h__\h] up
stay on the block yeah oh no i didn't
know that thank you
yeah okay just reminds you from falling
yeah
as long as you hold [\h__\h] down over here
you're digging down oh boy okay
i'm
straight line
i'll just follow you guys
well true it's mining time
[Music]
not that you suddenly fall down that is
very impossible
oh hiya fellas well this music is
amazing
wow hey guys how are you doing
where'd you guys go uh we're going
inside
i'll put a light here so let me know
where we are some gold lava
[Music]
ah
i can't put water down i can't put water
down
[Music]
well that makes sense doesn't it how do
we put out fire if we get
caught on fire stop drop and roll
[Laughter]
don't get caught on fire oh no they're
friendly right they're fine
yes friendly oh they're friendly until
they're not
exactly this gold is far enough away
from them for me to move
okay no don't take it don't take it oh
they're not look for science
oh they're coming up no hello just let
them leave we'll trap them in your hair
they don't want any trouble but listen
oh no they're coming out excuse me
should we set it up he's gotta protect
his doubloons
oh yeah oh somewhere else don't worry
there's other yeah we should set us one
point guys
well this this area is kind of nice if
we if we want to just
maybe make this the the place
no beds chat says no bed why i have one
yeah be my guest
because they want you to not get the the
buff you know
what happens what happens when you sleep
you get a 20
uh armor buff yes you're lying speed
boost
you're lying what happens
i don't know out of here no don't try it
go what are we looking for in another
what do you do here
yeah well i think we're looking for
materials what kind of materials i want
soul sand
oh oh [\h__\h] she's doing it yeah i just
wonder what dm oh man
wait where which way do we come from we
sound angry oh wait strider okay this is
the way we came from
oh there's the bed no don't don't let
them out don't let them oh oh oh
sorry i didn't know i didn't know wait
okay this is the way we came from yeah
look for the little lava boy
i'll put i'll put a lantern here so that
we know
we're done
so what are we going to do i didn't even
get oh i got golden nuggets uh-huh
or mine in you want to go down here
there's stuff down here if you want
to go here no
[Music]
who's going to be the uh sacrifice i
mean who's going to be the uh the test
subject i mean the who's gonna
who's gonna
kiara you sleep now i mean i legit wanna
see what happens
go to bed we'll pick you up from home
and then give it back to me
[Laughter]
okay wait let me get a good angle ina
i only trust you with my stuff i don't
like what i'm hearing from chad
i like your phoenix
set a spawn point okay that makes sense
they want us all to die all right i see
right and uh potatoes and
one month remember to take off your
cords but oh yeah
take like that take this
take that picture take the flint and
steal and what's up here this is
whatever whoa
do you have a dog
[Music]
it was nice knowing you all uh-huh
see you later alligator
wow fireworks
well that's one way to get somewhere wow
are you okay yeah okay
i didn't think you exploded you're going
to try and make me do that
even even the pigs are like what is
happening
see we have an easy way out now it's all
cats
more times like in a
homemade tnt thanks so this is your job
let's just blow up a path for us
when you got kiara exactly well
really dev does not scare me so
i'm i can do i can do it again and again
i gotta stamp out the flames oh [\h__\h] i
have no gold armor
give it to me oh wait where are you
here oh wait the door wait
yeah i think i went this way
[Music]
honey there's a paddle over here guys
it's another course you know wow
bread uh bread
yeah thank
[Music]
torches yeah follow the torches okay
okay
[Music]
it's the the big floaty thing
wait what's this do you see this what is
this behind you
behind you give me here's your shield
thank you chad what is this okay
i want this for my friend
my new home a fortress a biome
oh
go go go we fight it yeah
oh i don't have a bow
is it is it is i think it's just
randomly shooting or isn't it oh
i think that it knows that we're here so
it's going to try and kill us
oh yeah
well we can go this way uh maybe i'm not
close enough
yeah do your worst yeah let's go this
way
up the stairs okay go go go i got you
like a pig hut
hey guys our friends can we kill that
thing
you can deflect the fire you can attack
the ball when it shoots it and it shoots
it back at the guy
does anybody want to try that oh it is
oh well if i'm going to die anyway i
might as well give it a try
oh
[Applause]
nice easy so easily what the heck what
i thought it'd have wait it was one hit
i think we're extra intimidating
yeah yeah sir our dominance you guys see
this
i want to go see what this is
oh oh are those the glowstone thingies
are these close up here
but there's a pigment oh
yeah there's a forest over there let's
go that way oh we can build a bridge
forest
oh there's a way yeah we can build a
bridge here a bridge
[Music]
i'm gonna grab some rock because i don't
have any i'll leave this to you girls
you work
i don't want you guys at that team
whoops seriously wow i'm impressed
it's nice that this stuff comes apart so
easily
you have to hold shift right yes hold
i got you
so what happens can we make another
nether portal does it exit out somewhere
on the other side
but it will probably be really far away
from where we came from
like super far really yeah
right that is correct that's what i
thought callie
were you wrong uh i don't know
get more rock this is it's possible see
hold on no
this far away enough from the piglets to
to get the gold
guys it's the btf the music is so loud
for me there's like music and game and
it's like
[Music]
i have no music you guys learn my music
i'll sing yes please
minecraft another
oh you're sick whoa what's this red rock
is it looks different bush
wait what is this hell's wart
red grass oh [\h__\h] oh wait i have pirate
game hold on don't listen to what i'm
saying
i like i like can i if i take this
to the real world i want my walls to be
this color we should we should probably
try to go back after we collect some of
this stuff because like uh if we collect
too much and die it'll
just be like oh wait wait yeah
so collect as much stuff now and then
we'll go back for like a few minutes
there's another and there's another
floatie
what is that is that a light star oh
where's floatie right i'll shoot him
down where is he
there what's that sound do you hear that
it flew away yeah
a shiny zone morning
ah i heard something explosion
that was right behind me yeah fight me
on the open
yeah yeah don't be a coward i'll be a
coward i'd say as i run away
yeah coward
oh you missed you gotta be quicker than
that buddy it's
tactical returning to help i want a
garden with these plants
here a plant what is it these ones
like i thought they saw a fortress i'm
gonna go to the fortress wait this is
wood
these are trees yeah yeah
oh what a cutie hello who are you
oh are these villagers oh
is that pumbaa
it looks like there are other people
here they don't look uh nefarious or
mean
i have a sneaking suspicion that the
pumbaa is not so friendly
but we shall see
ah i kept my outlet and now my
chat says they're hostile so maybe we
shouldn't go say hi oh
take out the little one to mr dominance
all right cool i'll help i'm behind you
oh wait they're fast hold on hold on no
wait wait wait wait wait don't shoot
first there's so many of them
it's fine we'll be okay well it's easy
see they're all equipped with swords
so if we taunt them and we get them to
come at us then we just knock out the
bridge and they fall to their deaths
[Laughter]
come over and fight us hey you want to
fight oh
we can give gold to them and maybe
they'll be friendly let's try i have a
bunch of gold
oh yeah all right i'll go
wait what's that huh i was i was ready
i was ready to shoot it's fine
all right i'm gonna i'll be back up i'll
be back up
okay yeah we're here to help i don't
have a i don't have a bow and arrow
though so i'm gonna
wait that's really far hold on i'm not
prepared
do you believe
maybe i tried right click okay throw it
there i throw it maybe are those the
ones that won't attack you if you're
wearing gold
okay well hold on they're not aggressive
they give you some items back i think oh
oh
[Music]
well i'm glad that things ended
peacefully but
i'm more i'm warning you okay i want to
taste blood
i'm ready to start swimming thanks chad
i'm no coward
i also want to try the gacha i want to
do the gacha the gold
so many of them
i'm not going over there it's too far
okay oh here callie
i'm here
[Music]
wait come back come back away from me
why did you kill him i can't keep
okay all right we're good this one wait
i want to try this guide to machine
are they are they the gotcha well i did
the right one
shield instead when i right clicked so i
left clicked and it hit him with
it
i didn't give you one here yeah the the
piglet took it right away from me
wait let's pick oh okay pick it up okay
right here take this hold it in your
right hand
and right click on them stop okay now
give me something good
now i'll kill you i'm going to kill you
he gave me a meatball
hey something is teasing me
i have something too it gave me [\h__\h]
maybe we should build a portal here
he gave me a meatball what am i supposed
to do with the meatballs
assistance i need to equip my thing i'm
here thank you i need to equip mine
okay wait can you did not drop the
harpoon though or what is it the
crossbow the cotton
tatter bottle i got a water bottle pay
that time what does it do
hydrates you run away
gotcha don't you run away oh wait
wait what does this do wait hold on
that's right
wait do we know how to you can throw the
spicy meatball uh
oh yeah here's our bridge okay our
bridge is here
hey so the meatballs uh it's like
throwing heartburn
when you throw the the the the spicy
meatball they give you it makes fire
uh-oh
come here let's play i'm ready to party
look at this wide open terrain
you mean [\h__\h] you a hand-to-hand combat
come here
bring it squid oh you dodged my bullet
oh dodge my bullet
up all right bring it squid
i'm just getting the way back for us
okay oh it's coming back yeah
i gave it to him i gave it to him
hello little one hello little one
the noises they make are so interesting
hey come back
it's so cute hello
aquarius what are you doing you're too
young to hold a weapon
hello and i get the soul sand
maybe it's a different biome oh is it
something good
oh you got some yeah i got it uh for
gold
i don't think that's oh sorry i you can
go look for more gold if you guys want
to do that i don't think we could take
the gold from here
there's more striders here is that good
what else
my sights swinging twitter instincts
were kicking in
when i saw the little one really great
apparently i got something amazing
what did you get 10 spectral arrows
and the chat is going like wow
what do those do special arrows you
can't see the person you shot that's all
it was
oh it's like walls
oh we can't we probably can't mine these
gold darn it
yeah mckinnon i'm addicted
to it we can find gold on the way back
just build gold yeah that's why there's
a crafting table here you guys
want yeah all done
crafting table yeah let me find out
i'm gonna give him more something
crafting table wait i want to use it
wait inside my house
crimson roots i like them and gives you
water
what is it worth the world stuff i like
it yeah
okay i want to save my
actually i don't have to save my gold if
anybody say anybody want to go again i
have three left
i have some i wanna i'm gonna milk them
for what they got let's see what you got
give me some stuff
wait where are they they're all here
yeah kyle you wanna go again
yeah you don't want to drop in here okay
okay
why is he running away from me give me
your pickaxe
oh wait that's a bow crossbow
give me a crossbow yara
i got another piece of gold but you
gotta go don't give me a meatball okay
there you go over here over here
thank you goldie yeah
here you go amma is the dealer for
everything he robbed me
did they all aggro if you attack one yes
i think so
yep oh okay let's not do that okay what
did he give me
yeah enough did you take my item oh
do you guys see this inventory you guys
gotta come see us
you guys gotta come see this
[Music]
what what does a chicken do in the
nether oh i got
um he's riding a chicken
crying obsidian ooh what is that chicken
doing here
he's uh
look at him riding on the chicken stop
running i'm going to give you something
rare it's so cute
it says very rare can we keep him ken
gravel can we keep it yeah shake the
puppy
back to the real world you guys want to
build a portal here and see where it
goes
yeah i have one give me something good
come on come on one two three four
five two three four four friends
i like the gold sword little one oh
this is nonsense all right
again everybody has who has the flint
yeah
they're the owners i will do
let's oops
sorry my bird brain is uh not being
activated three two one go
oh
[Music]
we're in some sort of cave oh
[Laughter]
oh like an exciting
outside area that we never saw before
like a nice new body oh wait
wow wow really really far in oh i put it
i put it just now
hey how deep are we
[Music]
the what that uh deep in the ground
we'll just see where wherever
we come where it comes out
feel like it's not going to be like
before oh they
glow or unless
there's
[Laughter]
hey everybody get ready to uh swim
[Music]
oh sorry i took here wait where's
oh there's watson and he's gonna be the
ocean
sandstone's making me feel like it's
gonna be ocean
yes okay maybe we should go back
what could possibly go wrong no it can
also be a
pyramid or something like that i died in
one before where's king
king tuck we should build a pyramid how
cool would that be
we should be pretty close to the surface
actually right yeah yeah yeah yeah
i'm struggling hold on a minute are you
good can you help me i'm okay i just
can't
i can't climb i can't play this game
okay it's okay
i'm sorry i was trying to find this all
right it's just a scratch it's fine
don't worry about it
sorry
oh i think we're close to getting out
yeah yeah yeah oh we're fine it wasn't
my fault
okay ah we did it
whoa where are we ah hello hang it out
i need to i need to keep mining so i
might hit oh the desert cactus
oh hey
desert oh we are we're really high up
whoa yeah no wonder it took us so long
it looks like dystopia like we came out
oh
can we take it i should have brought my
diamond pickaxe
fireman shtick oh gold hey
i only have can we can we throw in this
portal is it like continue in the lava
right
does it what's in the chest i took it
there was a shovel
and a hole yeah yeah yeah yeah for water
yeah that doesn't give me the gold
i can't it's too high up hold on i'll
build away uh sit here
oh what there's a village nearby yeah
but this one is too long i think we
gotta
oh no no it's fine it should be
wait a second no it has to be and i'll
see one more yeah
we just have to get rid of these two
blocks we're not gonna be able to save
it but we can remove it and then replace
it is that a village have an opinion
if this is a village i have to go see if
you're crying
apparently we screwed it up oh really oh
yeah we can
there's a village over here you get a
new one it works
we don't have enough obsidian to make
there's one there's one i have three
okay how okay there's a three
three six eleven wait how much do we
need in total it's four
by what is it wait
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven twenty
ten some people are saying it doesn't
work the one that i have
oh no no it doesn't oh the bright
obsidian doesn't work
which way did you guys go uh
i know that way
hello let's just leave this place yeah
yeah wait okay we can come back to it to
retrieve it
which way did you go there's a temple
over here i'm in a temple
hold on did you guys empty the chest yet
no no i don't get it what am i doing
here guys
do the what mind the what
where are you guys you don't need the
corners
oh yeah but
i only have three blocks and kiara
here how many did you have three
three oh uh but they're not the glowy
ones right it's just regular obsidian it
says obsidian
wait is it trap you might be able to
build it then
let me try it all right we already have
a meeting here in the floor so if we do
you guys said we don't need the corners
does anybody have tnt
one tnt
we just need to lure a creeper a rabbit
the carpet is a glove idea and i tried
oh oh
two bottom tops why are you in the
desert
oh i see what you okay come here come
here you guys don't like my eyes
i mean okay i can just do it here then
okay so like this
no i have to oh okay i see i see
i replace this with sand like this
no yes this is right is this right
this seems like a difficult problem
it's like a puzzle huh hold on okay
okay i'll i'll do a mock one okay this
is one two
three oh no we don't do the corners so
we do
not the middle my nails and people are
saying mind the orange
and then is that too
short yeah okay yeah oh one one longer
longer yeah perfect holy
[Music]
yes
okay okay all right now i just replace
the sides so one two three four five six
seven eight right guys yes
wait wait this isn't this is long enough
he's fine they said chad says yes
um yeah this looks okay imagine if this
was one higher on the ground then it
would make sense
yeah it sounds good i have the
coordinates don't worry
we have the right amount all right cara
i'm waiting for you i
i think i see it coming home i got lost
a little bit but
i'm i'm back almost oh it's like a real
pier
i'm i'm there i'm there are you
i think i see it
but we can't mind the obsidian so we
have to try again because it's not tall
enough
yeah and we don't have a diamond pickaxe
with us because i didn't bring one
because i was scared i was going to lose
it
yeah i see him but i don't mind i'll
bring it with us if we get back home
because like uh i have more diamonds
it's fine gotta see him
yeah honestly
[Music]
i'm in a pyramid
oh wait that's just the bunny give us
your coordinates
i've been trying to say i'm in a pyramid
could you hear me
i was trying to look for gouda but then
i got lost
oh yeah there are cats yeah but that's a
bunny
that's the bunny there are cats though
in the desert
i am a paleontologist
that's a dinosaur person though right
yes
still a paleontologist oh my god this
wizard is like
endless who discovers mummies what are
they called historian
mummy mummy mummy excavators
i'm an excavator that's a truck isn't it
what i probably i mean they stole it
though
um what should we do where are you guys
we're we're still at another portal i
don't know which direction
you guys want i like the whole i went up
high and i saw what i thought was a um
is here
[Music]
now let's try with the flint
wow nice job
hi where is
hello hi me too me too let me in
okay it looks good hey we're going back
in
yeah or last time the little one is
still here
are we in the same place oh we didn't
move that far
my yeah we only went up
i just didn't want to go back down i
mean we had [\h__\h] but we came
back in from the same
same gate because we put look at these
guys jumping
oh oh oh this is the same
oh that's what cali's looking at hello
okay
okay i'm in the cave in the cave
okay okay well the cave we uh we uh we
started how do we get eddie no
way
yeah this is right this is right this is
right yes yes
they weren't bad dudes all right i'm
ready to fight there's another pumbaa
i'm ready too no yeah
he's running away all right i'll let you
freak out deserve her off
uh cowards cowards okay
got him all right okay this is like this
is wrong
out of that pig nice
right there's a bridge here we'll follow
this bridge
okay i'm is so reliable honestly out
it's like oh it's okay we go back up
this way she is the detective
hi attention to detail watson yeah
then be careful on these stairs easy to
fall
okay one at a time at a time nice and
easy
too nice
yeah this is where kara blew up sorry
i'm like
through this wait you're burning uh no
we're gonna find the it's here it's
right here
off the sleeve hey wait hold on i'm just
gonna make a
like a bit of room there there you go
yeah cause he's the little strider fella
hi
he's our little landmark he's so cute
i did not get any gold because i gave it
all to the gata
[Music]
goodbye friend i hope i'll see you again
soon
we did not i mean the only person who
died is me right
i died on purpose yes
we're making exactly progress how many
times have we died
last time too many and there's an
enderman
huh
golden sword
it's not the one that's mad at me right
yeah
enemies here don't see me enemies coming
back from the nether
i can't die right now i got so
no much booty inna alone i'll kill you
i got it i got it do you want to sleep
or do you want to just
no i'm good hanging out hitting things
um well i got more gold
i just
i did it i'm so unorganized
you take this take this this this
[Music]
purple purple i got purple wood
purple one two me too yeah it's like
those are two underwear that's purple
oh did you kill them nope they're just
walking around did you make
sense yeah you should be able to
stem oh whatever that is it's probably a
good door
i'm working on my house now no you can
oh yes you can i'm dumb
okay oh oh i see
dragons in the bag those aren't
your friends you sleep you have phantoms
what what mushroom wait
maybe we should sleep one night just
yeah
good idea all right i'm in my bed
just a moment
good morning good morning this morning
oh they're
guys i'm gonna take the i'm gonna go get
us that strider i'm gonna go
bring him home oh yeah yeah
bring stuff to like yeah it's a good
idea
saddle and the mushroom and stick what
flavor mushroom does he eat though
i have a bunch of mushrooms i have got a
blue one
a brown one and a red one
depends on what i need some red these
blue mushrooms
i got a blue one i don't know do you
have one of them
i have one yeah that's what he eats
apparently
okay so i don't i don't know who i guess
he dies if he's outside of the lava
i don't know you can only use them in
there i mean that's still pretty good
can you i wonder if you can make a
little pen
hold on right bring it in or something
all right i brought some fence wait well
would catch on fire in there
you put it down uh i don't know
another outside of the uh portal
oh yeah that's good yeah i bring some
materials
no no beds no beds
just like furnaces cute
ah no i didn't mean to do that
oh i can't stand hang on oh how do i get
up i might get up
oh okay
high ceiling because i am tall oh cali's
house to be
yes i'm working on my house
welcome ina i'm still living full yes my
pool
do you like it it was here when is this
for your not you
um yeah
if we go back in i don't know uh
screaming
well we can just build a house in there
and then we can like stay
pretty close yeah yeah it's it's just
like a square house
cool in another okay yeah yes
yes wait do you have that mushroom wait
oh yeah i got it
nice
[Music]
hey
are you gonna take him hey where's emme
oh you guys going in already okay i'm
coming
there's no crafting table in here hold
on wait wait give me the mushroom
what where are you i don't i see you is
the mushroom for crafting
yeah there you go
hey you welcome i'm going back in
did you make our little base here oh
wait like right here nina's got a
crafting table i can use this one it's
close
okay here uh i want to use these blocks
hold on
there you go okay how do i do this
alright i want to help
[Music]
uh is it the usual
what you call it the usual like horse
armor
it should be different uh okay yeah
i guess yeah hi y'all buddy
later losers
[Laughter]
why is he purple oy
[Music]
he's just a little anemic that's all
he's fine he just needs a nap and uh
he's fine he's fine he's a champ he'll
be good he'll be good
well he's faster than the lava he's fast
in the level whoa whoa whoa
now i see okay i get i understand that's
like you're standing there
you have a fence if you want to build
him a little paddock
maybe we can build him a path hey girl
a lava path yeah look
oh i see what you mean can you walk on
magma rock because that might be safer
for all of us
you can but it hurts a bit see easy way
easy way down now
now we can easily see it
we can perfect it later but for now yeah
thanks for your service buddy he's cute
i know right maybe we can connect over
here today
it will do the roof with the red rock
oh the rest of the roof with it
[Music]
that's too bad oh something's over
go that looks like that's how it's damn
did he look where'd he go where'd the
straddle go oh
he fell oh
is it my fault is he dead
[Music]
oh
he's spinning like a maple leaf oh god
sorry my my keyboard is in japanese okay
hold on back to the game
okay he's down he's landing the eagle
has landed
he's okay okay he's [\h__\h] he's fine
okay yeah he's fine as long as he's
alive it's okay
wait but how are we gonna get him up
here i'm gonna make sure
[Music]
i want to be the hero yes be the hero
i'm going to you're always the hero in
my heart
uh our neighbors are here our neighbors
say hi
[Music]
oh um i have a pickaxe do you want mine
oh yes thank you uh here let me is it
okay
it's got a little bit of juice left it
should be good yeah i want to use that
oh wait i picked it up hold on here here
here
oh anybody have one yeah yeah yeah yeah
wait i picked it up again wait okay here
yeah i need i need
okay i'll bring some from my house
i'll be your moral surprise thanks good
evening
we'll get them what should it cara you
want to name
i think he's right below you right below
okay so as long as you make your way
down
nice and easy you'll be fine all right
i'll go save our friend
oh that looks cool hang on
okay um this is gonna take some brain
power but i got it
done
oh i think we can only give the gold to
the villagers i guess not these random
pigs yeah
i i tried
i was like oh you tried to give it to
anything and this is this is
there's probably a roundabout way to go
let's just keep moving this way
maybe i can make some stairs wait hold
on just kidding
okay no i can't there are no stairs that
will be made here it's okay
i'm gonna move to i'm gonna move this
way until hang on
it's fine we got it i wonder if i can
build actual stairs
of this is this soul sand
beautiful house amy thank you
beautiful you guys okay we're making
progress
you could be a architect oh thank you
architect watson amelia architect
watson
no i didn't die i just came out to get
some wood
wait where where is everyone in the in
the other in the oven
went down here i went back i'm back
cali and gouda are making their way to
save
strider yes is that his name
that's what he's called you can name him
if you want though i don't know he likes
that it's okay
we keep striding up
what i'm gonna make a jump let me get it
on camera
okay um
okay getting closer i bet i can put uh
you made that jump
yeah brave wasn't that bad
i know i got to save our homie
should i extend the i have two more
chests should i put it
um
is he moving is he on the move i mean
he can't be far there's no way he didn't
go that far yeah
yeah yeah he's dead no he's not he's not
done
i saw him with my own eyes liars
oh no pencils
neighbors i'll pay to visit wait what's
happening okay
did he open the door did he just watch
it he made it we made it down
nice oh we got a crosstalk
oh a crash on your head
on it i am okay
hello i come in peace i wonder if
there's another village that's close
i guess i guess that one we found is the
closest one yeah
no i found him
i'm riding on him but i'm i'm on fire
i'm on fire
yeah i died oh no well it was the
valiant effort but i found him i found
him
okay
i'm here i'm here whoa okay nice and
easy good and nice
okay i think i know oh oh so well
oh this is a bed yes
i caught on fire i found them but then i
caught on fire oh
i don't know where i am um
[Music]
are you okay fine we're fine we're fine
you play calm we're calm we're calm
we're cool collected we're comical
collectors
okay oh we're fine
we didn't pay no no no we didn't panic
we're good we're good
i'm scared i
[Laughter]
sounds good this area is familiar i
don't know where i am but there's a
village i'm going to go look in
we're it to see you i don't know where i
am actually oh yeah
i turned up somewhere random hi buddy hi
i'm buddy go to a high place and look
for the h and that's the entrance to the
tunnel and you can just take a mine cart
in there from uh
hi i need to get where you are go back
home thank you okay
do you see the age okay uh i'm in a
village hold on a sec
right now i'm good i'm good i'm with
strider and i got cali stuff
hey you got it you're
where are you yeah how are you going to
get can he jump
i see a house i i this is a rando's
house
i don't know how i'm going to do this
can we swim up lava probably not right
so it is all my fault no no no no no no
no no no
down there i think oh probably i should
have my pickaxe here yes
yes yes yes yes
hi friends you can the house looks like
a face
listen you gotta move friend you can
walk already
i require assistance i require
assistance for house no
[Music]
where are you where
what's going on don't panic glitter
don't panic
don't panic don't pay any goodies oh i
guess i can't
get out of here okay um assistance is
required in the nether
i'm okay are you okay i'm okay
give us your coordinates i'm right
outside i can see all your names
um um there's a ghast you see
oh oh they're on fire
oh wow can you guys take out the guests
which one but
i think so it's getting closer to the
pig village because there was the path
that went
sort of in this direction over there
she's down there i'm i'm i'm i can see
your guys's names i'm like
right down here well i'm so scared i
don't like hiding
i know you're fine it's fine it's all
good it's all good since tennis right
um i don't think our friend will leave i
think we can leave him here so i'm just
gonna
yeah just park him there it's his
parking spot
yes it's a really far far a parking spot
can you guys clear my uh headspace here
oh wait it's good okay yeah yeah oh nice
i have you stepped out of the house we
got a panic room
i'll be oh wait i could have written it
on the strider but he's so fast i don't
trust myself
well if you guys want to play gotcha
before we go i got i brought a bunch of
gold
i brought some gold too that sounds fun
but read up is alive
we'll we'll wait for cali to get back
and then thanks
does anybody have a chest i can put
cali's stuff in oh wait
there's a bunch of guests thank you for
doing that by the way i will make it up
to you
oh no worries it's okay i'll put it in
uh what did you
have this um i just want my nether stuff
like uh to build my house with cool
things like uh
there were some i feel so stupid why
didn't i put that
stuff in chest before i ca no that's
fine
welcome back i'm here thank you everyone
we're speaking about another one the
gate had a really cute face
thank you gouda top chest tippy top
chest thanks
yeah let me know if i missed anything i
think you got everything thank you
nice to meet you
baked potatoes yay i'm hungry
yeah so strider is down there where we
left him he won't really go anywhere i
don't think
oh okay huh i wonder
um yeah i guess there's not much we can
do about that huh
darn it i can come back when i don't
have anything
yeah yeah i think we can build like
staircases for him to
walk up oh very slowly yeah dying
outside of lava right so we can just
build him a really really long
long staircase yeah yeah
we have enough rocks
he'll be fine that's the project for
another time i suppose
yes yeah we'll save them later oh go
let's go
where are you kara i'm where are you
guys yeah
we're going to stop right there oh i
just
okay i just left let me put some stuff
away i'll come back
whoa i'm right before the ah yeah i want
to go put some stuff away too actually
just complete your armor fine yeah oh
that's right all of it came off huh
um i'll continue to mine the path to the
village
sorry i lost the gold snapback hello
[Music]
oh yeah do you need some gold armor so
they don't yeah
oh yeah it's gone huh oh well i don't
know i used it i panicked and i used it
so oh it's okay oh that was yours oh
my god i'm so sorry it's okay you're
good
thanks again i'll i'll make more for you
i'm sorry you don't have to it's okay we
haven't
panicked i don't know how yeah it's not
that far
what does it do anyway i don't know it's
purple it's pretty
yeah it is very purple do i really want
to waste all my gold at the gacha again
do i
have gold for you i feel like a ton more
at home
oh my god oh wait we're playing gotcha
amelia
the gold woman i want to play gun jazz
me too let's go let's go oh i don't need
this railroad oh it is
i thought it was the stairs
uh make this
have and i don't have any rock no i
haven't just mined something from here
is it called rock or rack rack
rack like quack
yeah yeah another wreck
are you guys should i take the pig
village path uh yes
yeah okay i'll follow the torches
nice shiny swords you got there buddy
oh so i guess nether spawn points can be
used instead of beds i didn't know about
that
we used the crying obsidian to make
those oh
the bright the bright one mm-hmm
the crying one sorry i used greed
it's okay we'll find some more okay oh
we can mine it back with our
diamond tic tacs i brought mine wait
where is this
yeah almost died
almost died oh gold armor
is this where the ender dragon is i'm
just making it so we don't actually know
oh okay good idea this is not where he
is
where's the ender dragon i wanna see him
maybe it's for another time how do you
summon him
what do you gotta say then we have to
find that gate thing and then like
complete it
and then like you gotta go find him
i'm ready knock on his door
i think we have to be like all diamond
everything to do that right
and no no no no i mean like for our own
safety
uh uh i watched like 20 hours of uh
uh and and uh rta
and the dragon rta so i know how to do
it
but we are not
why you kind of make a different kind of
portal
but you know ender pearls and there's a
few ways to get the ender pearls but it
takes a long time
sir you look like you're having a hard
time down there ready
are you okay do you need help getting
back up sir yeah
well i hear it oh i hear lois yeah
no he's above oh yeah
i'm okay oh there he is oh i see you're
gonna break our bridge i think he's gone
oh he's right there yeah
hello i'm happy hiya
oh we taking down the the big jellyfish
in the sky
come here uh that would be the safe
choice
go do it girl i don't think i don't
think i can make that shot i can't make
this shot he's still
maybe a little closer no it's so far
away i don't think i can make that
there's our other portal too nice let me
shoot him out in the open
well here we are
no he's too far up where are all the
villagers there were so many here before
they died what what
there's some homies over here maybe
they're sleeping maybe it's night time
for them
yeah do you have a crafting table
they're they're training the little one
uh no but i can make one i think
hold on
runally all right i have one
put it right here put it right here by
the bridge
[Music]
gold gata
thanks amelia for the free gold yeah big
ups
thanks oh you're picking you guys sorry
he doesn't he really doesn't like me
girl why is he
going oh god i'm gonna die it's fine
i'll help
ah all right nice wonder why he's not
yeah i have one heart we'll see what
happens wait do you need food
who's that girl yeah okay
are you kelly yeah i am sorry
hey he's our party i thought we were
just gonna do gotcha so i didn't bring
it
that's what's up because that's so many
steaks
thank you yes or cow's at home
it's okay with me
i do where's the gotcha dude hey some
gadget boys
sorry amelia give me something get me
the gold you accidentally picked it up
again i don't know
yes give me something good
okay i'm okay
thank you oh thank you thank you big ups
thank you
boy that's
where are the villagers yeah it's
probably just dead dudes huh
i see one he has a gold helmet come here
oh he's running away
why are you scared of me here
no i died oh my god callie
i'll grab your gold kick
oh my god take his oh i'll take the
stick
yeah take the steak cali
hallie dead again yes yeah oh my god no
i was just gonna give him gold and then
he turned on me
i think i think if you're holding gold
they'll attack you because they're the
they're not the villagers it was their
villager though it was a regular dude he
wasn't like a zombie
guy or anything not a single good thing
came out of this one
i did something weird this one looks
rich this
[Laughter]
not a single good thing
uh a string i think it's the end for
your boy
on this one here hmm yeah we should
probably call it soon because
cali's got a stream yeah time to wrap it
up
wait did did anyone find any of the
trader
gotcha traitor i thought i did
he started blasting didn't drop
anything actually that's good because
then i can
take the gaps at home and don't waste it
all right we can go back to okay okay
i'm in that same village too i got lost
again
oh no no
oh cara
tried this
are you still in the villa are you still
in the village i'm trying i'm looking
for watson's uh
tennis racket okay what's he's got a
tennis racket
okay yeah a big one glass
my god wait where did you die canada
because
well yeah i know but like way
[Laughter]
clearly this is the wrong direction got
it okay
are we gonna do operation find kelly
sorry i will find it don't worry i'm
getting up high
hold on let's see
yeah what did they gain from it you know
okay so listen i wasn't i wasn't wearing
any gold armor
and apparently that's a thing oh yeah
yeah remember
it all makes sense now yes
all right oh okay you go you don't have
to i'll mix all my promise i'll start
minding my own stuff i don't want you
guys to have to do everything for me
no no no help we help yes
yes team we are one
we are one thanks guys i want to be good
at video games
yeah maybe someday
playing gosh where is watson's tennis
racket
where's watson that's the real question
where's waldo where's watson where in
the world is
watson here in the world is watson
hold on i'm coming wow i thought i had
steak
but oh i do okay
wow minecraft is so pretty another soap
i see an incredibly tall buildings this
must be the right way
like we're digging one block building
kiara
oh no
wait how did you drown she drowned in
from my house i just kind of watched it
what was i supposed to do
all right gotta call the lifeguard
okay hopefully our house will survive
i'm in the basement okay
all right
[Music]
it's okay it'll be fun
all right we're all here yay
you can do the the ending right here by
the tennis racket
i magnifying magnifying glass
yeah it's right on it you guys will see
yeah it's a beautiful magnifying glass
mustache record
wait where are we meeting myself
do you want to do a minecraft stream
with me where we build a huge chess
field
oh my goodness
all right we can do that
ah yes the chest feel to always
commemorate that legendary chest stream
professional oh i think this is your
stuff
okay oh yeah thank you hold on oh
thanks oh sorry i don't mean to be
getting in the way here you're right now
all right good here i have a present for
you too a present for me
let's go over here turn look at this oh
[Music]
oh
okay she got it oh uh cara i have a
present for you too
here we go
oh you don't have to oh wait what
nice betsy good old
betsy you can because you can draw it
and then you can just have it drawn and
then you can shoot it
oh baby
the one and only now i want to give you
a present too so here you go
yay doors purple doors
yeah actually i just changed my door to
the purple one thank you it matches
yeah yeah yeah
the color i'm in santa claus
dude thank you i appreciate it
[Music]
okay sure come on what do you want for
christmas little girl
um you i
[Laughter]
she wants me as a friend
i just want a friendship that's all
a keep friendship to friendship forever
and ever
yeah okay guys let me gather up
okay yo what up they are right up here
it's magnifying glass i'm sorry i know
it now i understand now yep yep
wait wait ah there we go yay
oh we didn't yeah take a screenshot
previously i want to take one now
look i'll take off my i'll take off my
oh yeah i was trying to shoot him down
it's okay i missed photo options
look how cute wait i need to see
f1 there you go this is fine
[Music]
successful another trip yay
everyone who watched maddening thanks
for coming
yeah thank you for watching thanks for
coming
bye thank you
for coming oh yeah yeah
well i'm gonna play uh well we're
planning on it me and gouda are planning
on playing
uh minecraft together next week so tune
in yeah
minecraft i'll be there yeah it's gonna
be fun
i'm having another whole japan
collaboration next week
with whoa
uh schedule for me will be out uh
tomorrow or the day after
tomorrow yeah new week
all right okay thank you everybody for
[Applause]
[Music]
watching
bye
[Music]
i guess i should turn off the
you