[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
ah
[Music]
sorry ah
oh my God
why is it already so hot again
I there's so s it's so like low
temperature outside and yet
and I had the window
the doors open constantly
and it cooled down for a second the
moment I closed the [\h__\h] window
one minute later it's already hot as
[\h__\h] I can't I can't I'm going [\h__\h]
insane and then I tried to take a nap
because I couldn't sleep well at night
and I'm just I'm telling you just
because I tweet at 11 doesn't mean that
I just woke up at 11.
some people think that the moment I
tweet is the moment I wake up I think
Raina tweeted something similar today
she was also like that doesn't mean that
I just woke up okay
yeah
I woke up way earlier than that and I
was trying to sleep you know I tried I
tried and I couldn't and then I just
woke up and I started cleaning my
apartment and I did that for like two
hours because rmt was supposed to come
by but then she didn't she just wrote to
me five minutes before the stream sorry
I woke up late
even though she was supposed to come to
bring me something important today now
she didn't come
so so what did I clean my apartment for
well anyway so I also I also I also
aired my apartment uh for the whole day
because it's outside it's so so cool and
it comes in but it's just I don't know
what happens with it
apparently it's just it disappears it
immediately heats up into hot as [\h__\h]
air
and then I tried to take a nap you know
before the stream uh I gave myself two
hours of time to fall asleep and maybe
sleep a little bit but I feel like I
didn't really sleep it it took me too
long to like get like tired again and I
think I always was just half asleep just
dozing and that's not properly slapping
[\h__\h] that
but partially I woke up early because of
the Heat and because of smoothie because
she wants breakfast early these days
always wakes me up way too early this
[\h__\h]
oh I couldn't really sleep mostly
because of the heat again which makes no
sense because I I I I I I I can't I
can't with the seed it's not even hot
outside
I'm gonna cry I'm going crazy I'm going
crazy with this weather
oh wow cry
[\h__\h] this apartment [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
apartment
[\h__\h] this apartment
yeah so that's why I didn't sleep much
and now I'm in a bad mood
and I tried to at least make up for the
lack of sleeping by having a snack
before the stream now I couldn't even
finish it
yeah yeah
wow
um
where's my tunic logo hmm
where is my two nickel over here hmm
[Music]
we had this talk before I don't want to
get a like a window AC unit because in
the room where I needed like where I
stream
it would be too loud
and generally it's like
pain in the ass to like set up
and yeah blah blah blah blah blah blah
can't get a permanent one apartment
renting blah blah blah whatever
and I want to talk about it again
tunic will cheer me up I know it will
because tunic is the best game of my
life
but I haven't played it in a while
so I'm not so confident about it
and we'll see
yeah
[Laughter]
um
sorry panko
[Laughter]
um
I mean it would be maybe nice to have it
in my
in my bedroom but if if they're as loud
as people tell me they are
then I couldn't I don't know
can I sleep with that I'm not sure
but whatever it's summer is almost over
[\h__\h] it I'm halfway through the summer
if not already more
I can get through this
[Music]
um
no you know what I'm I'm stubborn these
apartments nowadays they should come
with a c to begin with
incredible they don't adjust to the
warming of the earth okay
they don't adjust
it maybe was okay 10 years ago but it's
not okay now it's been getting gradually
warmer every summer
it's reality
hmm
I'm almost done I have like a sandwich I
made a sandwich
I made a sandwich
with cheese and salami pretty much all
there is
hmm
it should be a stand at least like I
don't understand why it's not even it
doesn't even come with expensive
Apartments
like if it's a cheap apartment okay I
understand but okay what
sorry I'm mad
I'm mad at the [\h__\h] summer why are we
not shooting the sun yet huh [\h__\h] this
one it's only hurting us
the amount of sunburns men that I got
[Music]
no but watches will not skip 15 to 20
minutes they have to suffer with me just
like you guys
hmm
your sunburns are your fault
you little [\h__\h]
no
no but in my last vacation I didn't even
get a sunburn so
I have one
against the Sun
um
I'm trying to write something to rmt one
second
um
okay
she's gonna bring me the thing that I
need hopefully
hopefully
okay
so say the line here at what say what
did I forget I said I said
no no no RMC does not have a RBF no no
no no no
RBF is not does not belong to rmt I
would not ask rmt to get me to get RBF
to do something not gonna ask anybody to
do anything anymore anyway
[\h__\h] it I'm alone
I'll do I'll do everything alone and if
there's something I can't do then I just
won't do it
I'll I'll just if I get a new piece of
furniture I'll just I just I just won't
get it because I can't build it
um yeah we're having a little bit of a
ranting session
independent not very independent though
when I can't do [\h__\h]
um
but you can learn how to build a girl
we're not even two rbfs can build by
[\h__\h] dining table without it like
going wobbly wobbly wobbly then I don't
think I can do it
if if they can't even get it right
together after two hours then I can't do
it either
oh no man that dining table is
I mean you can eat on it but
it's it's kind of shaky
okay
I'm gonna play this game or what
um
the wobble is a feature I feel like the
table is gaslighting me to things the
same thing
you know we just couldn't get it right
so at some point I was like maybe tables
are supposed to wobble
maybe that's normal
hmm
I mean I can't eat on it so
in in theory it's functional
the legs are
not uneven
it's a weird system where maybe I'll
maybe I'll paint it for you guys at some
point
but it's like spider legs they over
cross each other and and
um
they do have different
lengths today
wait I'm not sure anymore maybe not no
no they probably don't have different
links but
um it's kind of weird
um we tried it in different ways and
uh it's just huh
yeah nah I can't even explain
a squirrel is not lost we're trying to
make
a missing we tried loosening them we
tried tightening them we tried changing
the arrangement of the legs whatever
don't even get me started we did rate
the manual
we did
um what would have been nice is like a
video because the manual was [\h__\h]
a video would have been nice
oh hey this whole past 10 minutes I've
been playing the game
have you guys not been able to see the
screen
[Laughter]
just kidding it wasn't
[Music]
gotcha
one more bite man oh look at this
killed
um how many three bosses in the last
episode free
free boss monsters man
hmm
no one can stop me
um
if I knew where to go now
one last patch and then I'll Focus
now the screen is kinda
um
[Music]
why does it have like um
I think it had that last time too black
black um borders on the sides
[Music]
um
no
okay
so
everybody how do I play this game uh
after a roll
I can run
[Music]
mm-hmm
a square was magic
and
that was the other magic okay
now I want to
[Music]
sleep here once so that I just get back
what I just wasted
put my sword away it's intimidating no
hell no
now uh
menu is lb
or at least inventory is lb okay I mean
we have some with some Dynamite
we have some stuff
okay oh [\h__\h]
and oh blocking is this
hi hi hi hi
hi hi hi
and this was no
this was
the guidebook that we get
that we keep on collecting the pages to
wonderful still missing a lot of pages
reloading controls yeah it's been over a
week
yeah
uh I feel like I'm missing something
wait wait wait wait wait wasn't was
there any way of anywhere where the game
tells me what to do now
uh
how do you pray again ah okay
Emmanuel
um well hmm
well what are we supposed to do we uh
maybe we go up here again no no I mean
up here the door and I wonder if we can
go here now
the cathedral
did we check that out already is that in
the mountain
gosh those coffee stains men or the
cheese whatever it is
an iron door nope the Quarry we have to
go to the Quarry
this place
wait what is this place
have we seen it before well how do I get
there
how do I get to this place
[Music]
really do we really have to go there oh
the water jug is so heavy let me pour
some water you guys want some water too
um
babe in the water
mm-hmm if we're lucky then the publisher
of tunic might be watching
so sorry if you heard my venting I
sorry about that yeah yeah
but uh
looking forward to that
gift
professional first impression that
wasn't even the first impression that
was if anything already the third
impression also
oh
you have a grapple hook now which you
can take which can take you places okay
let's see I guess let's just go to the
Oval World is that what you're saying
which one is the right one
I don't know I don't remember I don't
remember any of these
um
ah okay here's a ruined tour
not necessarily what I want to go to
because here I already had the grappling
hook up see
although maybe what if I go this way is
there something interesting this way
it's too many time baby oh yeah
grappling hook how do I use the
grappling hook again do you have to
equip it
right where is the crafting hook I was
uh it was this thing
okay ah [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
okay there we go
how do I
[Music]
what
Ah that's some that's that ah now I see
it I
okay ah
as Focus
I still got it
I think I'm not sure this thing what was
that oh yeah that was already dead
that's already taken care of
oh Do It Low Bob
okay
so now we're uh oh can I get that piece
of paper nah still not can I
oh [\h__\h] look at that green dude there
holy macaroni
there's always so many mobs around oh my
God
look at him try to
threaten me he's threatening me okay
well I'll kill you then
I'll do you that favor
you want to challenge me
[Music]
[\h__\h] I forgot how to fight
I did it anyway I even though I um ended
up um
um
falling apart what was the Redwood
I rolled instead of hitting him I wanted
to hit him
[Music]
all right
okay okay all good so can I take this no
I guess not because I'm not even like
tall enough
I really need some kind of jumping on it
to him I didn't get a jumping out to me
at the door
and we were talking about it but I
didn't get one I think
ah he was guarding something surely but
I've already been there yeah yeah
whatever he was guarding I've seen it
already been there done that uh where
could that place be
we've done this
yeah we've done this thing
I've done this
we've we've done this
yeah Overworld we are currently ah okay
down there somewhere in the middle you
guys probably can't see it can you
and uh we're gonna go where wait don't
talk to him yeah we've been there
[Music]
there's nothing really obvious that says
ah Maybe they've been in the past
uh how do I zoom in again here maybe
that place sets us did we go here before
I think I've stood in front of it but
I don't think I did anything there
Bingo okay
[Music]
I hope I will reach it safely
oh Jessica
my beloved
[Music]
and then uh we choose how do I
change targeting oh yeah okay go over
here oh the chest below there I hope
I'll get it someday
here dice
wait what oh what just
[Music]
found another one that I could have
found before but okay
uh I am here okay I'm getting closer
um yeah if I go left I think I'll
yeah maybe I'll be able to reach it
another one yeah I find all the secrets
easy peasy lemon squeezy are you gonna
come out yes
but it will not frighten me
remember I remember guys I remember that
it's gonna explode
thing
okay we go through here
I don't I never went for a hair before I
think
down here I don't think so so can I get
this dude to
um you know what never mind just do this
ah
[\h__\h] ah
even when he's iced his shield blocks me
okay I have another trick in my pocket
ah
you little [\h__\h] are you for real how do
you I guess
[Music]
interesting
[Applause]
[Music]
arriving
maybe I don't know okay let's try
something else you hit me and then oh
that's that's it oh what
another question
oh I have bombs yeah but I shouldn't
have to
use them
shouldn't be forced to do that you shall
not pass indeed because Empire is
watching Lord of the Rings today on
Twitch apparently which I hope she likes
it I was really excited just to hear the
fact that somebody's watched somebody on
this Earth is watching one of the Rings
and it gets me excited
and weird but yeah it's Miko Senpai so
I hope she likes it and told her I wrote
to her I don't know if she saw it but I
told her to watch all free movies
because it's [\h__\h] good
Harry I tried I tried with my shield but
um he got through the shield
I mean I did some damage but
uh
I'm not this one I'm not uh
I only use my bombs for this
well I did notice that when I grabbed no
and I have no magic Lefty but how am I
gonna do this
no no I'm kind of forced to use the
button but the bones are one
was
uh if you use enough bumps you get free
ones what
I just used to hook the bums will just
bounce oh oh well then I'm glad wait
that's definitely a secret here
no
no okay
then I'm glad that I didn't use the
bombs though because if they just fall
off I'm gonna be really salty but now I
can't use the hook either
oh [\h__\h]
how do I how do I do this now I can't I
can't I don't think I can do it now
uh do I really have to like refresh
where's the closest
statue
where is the closest statue
[Music]
oh I hate you guys
[\h__\h] I'm just oh I should just run into
that room
[Music]
Mommy
okay
well but there's no statue here even
yourself
[Music]
um
didn't show the statues on the map
those are the teleportation thingies did
you show the stuff this this one right
there is no [\h__\h] statue here
nah that's that's there's more than that
that's not the sign for it
is it because wouldn't there be more
than one I think I'm close to one though
now it's still far but
if I go this way
and then here and then here and then
here I think
uh I think
wait oh yeah okay
and this is just so few of them we need
more of them
okay we're gonna challenge that bastard
again
um
shortest way
I wonder if I can just go straight to
the left somehow maybe there's some
no maybe there's something I can hold
the question is if I can go down then
I'll check I'll check
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
I'm gonna try going this way although I
have a bad feeling
uh
that's not the right way is it I don't
know
you need to go down yeah see that's like
going too far down
uh
tricky
[Music]
yeah no I want to hold on to tuning
forks I was hoping for that but I can't
do it from here uh maybe add that one
okay
I remember she remembered
and then
now what do I do about you so I say what
we do is we grapple him
and then I tried to attack him while
he's like you know going like
[Music]
so I should
I was hitting but I didn't reach him
Grandpa and Ice yeah oopsie
and hoping he freezes in the in a
position where his shield is not in the
front why is this so such a pain in the
ass water
uh okay
oh perfect oh
Pearl he was just turning around you
know the ice attack needs to charge a
little bit until it actually happens
oh we got a new card
a new like little skill thingy
but that was that was too much of a pain
in the ass and we shouldn't have been
like this painful
foreign
[Music]
I thought I would have to open it
somehow but no not quite
we just have to
walk around it
looking for Secrets don't mind me
[Music]
I should see what the car does it was
something with a with a with a with a
with a a healing potion or so maybe it
makes my healing potion stronger
um no wait what was that
I wish it would explain to me uh wait
and I stayed immediately
it makes my healing potions blue for for
Magic
but it still has a heart on it
it does change it and be okay
so I could even just do it momentarily
when I'm in a situation where
there's no enemies around me but I do
not have a fox statue close by and I do
not need magic so uh and I can when I
feel like oh I don't really need HP but
I do need magic really urgently
not a little
portion is
this place oh this place is so spooky
yeah
kind of um
omnius
I never know
about this
word I'm saying it right
okay you want me to go over there
uh what was it with this I just pray at
it right
and then the the magic will flow through
that packed
wow
um
yeah that was it
give me news
[Laughter]
why is it so so quiet
[Music]
oh wow
oh
wow
it was that no
wow wow
what's going on down there
[Music]
am I now
oh can I see myself now there
um
wherever that would be
where am I exactly who it has told me
I don't see myself on the map but I'm
not sure if I was was supposed to see
myself but it kind of
the straight path kind of
looks like it could be them but not
really
am I
am I here
am I in the Quarry
oh there's another one okay is it
continue make it make it continue
what is this weird place
it looks cool though
wow what is this oh
oh it's connecting all the way down
there
oh
it's falling apart I opened something
down there or maybe I'll go down there
oh that's cool to watch that from so far
away from so up high
um
koi
oh this is kind of dangerous
Oh I thought it was an enemy I
[\h__\h] statue that I saw on the
on the map now we activate that and then
we activate the teleportation portal
you want the bgm to be louder
well now it kind of calmed down again
here we are okay that's that one another
hold on let me just go back
foreign
okay this dude are they trying to
destroy it
kill them
come here
[Music]
[Applause]
shoot your friend shoot your friend I
I drink drink
[Applause]
again
[Music]
okay okay all good calm down calm down
you can just block it
shoot me
okay it's all good it's all okay no need
to panic
maybe we'll race it too
oh it's corrupted can I pray no I can't
okay
okay I think it's worth to um
uh
sleep sleep sleep through it actually
because holy macaroni I'm not gonna
take this
as the result no no no no no no
okay
yeah bye
can we um get the other one first
actually
here
nice
didn't do anything yet it didn't do
anything it didn't do anything yet yet
okay okay we did that nicely I did that
nicely
now you have to walk around it so that
it doesn't hurt me
rmt ride something
okay okay
[Music]
I'm scared
no please don't hurt me please don't
like me
okay okay
interesting how the magic still
continues to
um go through anyway even though that
thing is broken
hmm
okay come here uh it doesn't reach
wait are you a different one actually oh
what oh
God what
okay so there's one that can shoot one
looking for Dynamite and the normal
[\h__\h] who just shall have a
sword
all this there's another corrupted one
oh that one's pretty broken oh we can
see what's inside
yeah that yes
oh
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
ah you better come here
oh oh my God incredible [\h__\h] you
you know the you little [\h__\h] song I
think I said at this point but the the
little variations are so funny to me
when you think it's just another you
little [\h__\h] but no it's not
though it's not
that's that's
um nearby
what are they trying to gain from
destroying it what's inside that or
maybe there's nothing inside it's just
the act of destroying it that does
something
um
scared to walk around it
I'm gonna just find the spot hey
what the [\h__\h]
you're not supposed to see me right now
what the hell Berry
um
[Music]
it keeps on like recharging
it's not supposed to see me
maybe I can take cover just a box
you're gonna shoot or what
what is it is that a camera it's just a
an enemy with just a weapon just that's
just a
shoot
holy [\h__\h]
hmm just a box
holy [\h__\h] dude what
okay we just run through
hey okay I I you can't you can't not
possibly get me from here
um but
he will shoot me when I try to take the
bridge
stairs first baby maybe or I try to
quickly grab him
foreign
God damn it not the ideal way but okay
has to be done
come pick you tonight
when I go down first and take a look
what's down there
oh a chest another chest
oh what's some cheese cubes okay
I can't go oh no I can't go there
down here
wait why do Ocean's not
healed that much what the [\h__\h]
I drank one and it barely healed
anything was it always like that
money
keep it up I will thanks mate thanks
chicken
is there something here
no no really
though just that chest okay
don't have a lot
Dynamite
go back that's it
okay guys I'm gonna tell you
uh about my last day
with nami Mama the day before my flight
you want to hear the story do you want
to hear
um
um yeah yes please oh you want to hear
stormy
come here not gonna let you [\h__\h] around
with me no no no no
[Music]
[\h__\h] you
is this
they're destroying another one okay so
now on the last day the plan was to go
to the world's biggest inside indoor
amusement park it's called
[Music]
Mommy
he's coming here
have you heard about it
though not the world yeah yeah thank God
I still have my magic on my grappling
hook holy [\h__\h] this place is good you
really need the grappling hook oh my God
yeah so uh I think again on this day
again it was supposed to rain
um I don't think it did but if it rained
you know it would have been fine because
we would have been in a lot of world
haha
uh
oh God
this is so mean to sell me this is so
mean this is so mean
it's incredible absolutely incredible
oh I can get him fruit walls too oh my
God I mean that's not okay sometimes
sometimes we wonder how is it possible
for you to get me from certain locations
huh to to even see me
and it really makes me wonder how the
[\h__\h] you can see through walls
[Music]
I'm in the battlefield my field
not quite Fair okay you leave me with no
choice
[Music]
I I can't believe what's happening right
now
oh my God
oh
Mamma Mia okay let me just talk
can we just talk
about my vacation with Nabi mama can we
just talk without you sniping me through
the walls
Dynamite won't get too far
I have the grappling hook and I'm gonna
use it
oh is that a chest oh very dark hard to
see that one
have you seen anything really here what
the hell why is my light not working
oh
so okay let me tell you let me tell you
I'm gonna try to to tell you my story
so
um I wanted to eat lunch
like right no not before yeah because I
wanted to eat lunch right away after we
met after we were going to meet we met
like actually pretty late I guess I
think it was maybe like
1pm or 2 p.m already
oh
and um yeah she came to my hotel again
to pick me up
pick me up pick me up
[Music]
perfume song by the way
good song
[Applause]
of course
don't know why I expected anything less
so the miracle you didn't see me until
now
I feel like I missed something there can
I walk on this rubbish yeah
no please don't shoot me
there's nothing here
oh yeah yeah
okay
no no no no no
okay so and then and then and then and
then and she picked me up and uh she
gave me
foreign
you walk into like a alley thinking
there could be a chest there but no you
get surprised by an enemy what an ambush
holy [\h__\h]
she gave you an enemy
she gave me a choice
she gave my choice she was like they
wanna eat um
because we haven't had that yet or you
want to eat uh Kimba because that's also
another thing that I haven't had yet at
that point and was one of the things on
my list hold up topoky is usually
spicy
can ah money right if I throw it on the
ground
are we on the ground
I got money right
wait why is that one open is it just
decoration because I don't think I was
here before
did I create those stairs just now with
the
of this thing because I don't think they
were there before
now I can go up here again okay I'm cool
stuff
but I feel like did I miss something
oh no this is
foreign
[Music]
ers
that looks amazing that's the best thing
I've seen all day all week
ah man not even one today
is there something here
no
really
oh
I didn't uh
I didn't go up from there yet because I
went I went down first I'm not sure if
that's
that was the right option to do first
thank you thank you I'm glad you enjoyed
the giggle
giggle
[Music]
so tying off this now
I don't have any healing things left man
oh that's mean and I will almost am out
of grappling
munition
um
he's right there
probably
I really missed the giggle oh no you
missed something so important
yeah fobo that's why there's fomo
missing out on the giggles
[Music]
might want to go back
should I back to the viewing to the
statue
no no no no no no no I would still have
to pass for so many enemies again but I
might want to check out like where the
other path leads
um
if that's a smarter
half right now wait a second this one is
a secret oh
cannot
comment my eye uh uh Escape my eye
on it
can I get okay how did I
I wait okay
how did I get down here
oh wait
here
ah okay okay that's hard to say man
okay oh where was I so there was a
choice between topoki and kimbap and I
said I said topoki even though
I was worried about not being able to
eat it
the thing is
told me about the special tabuki
no why did I oh okay okay we're fine
we're fine it only uses the magic on
enemies right that's what it was oh
Facebook
[\h__\h] not that I didn't have much to
begin with anyway
[Music]
this is so mean the moment I go up there
okay okay he cannot shoot me so that's
cool but the fact that he can he can
even aim at me from through there is one
criticism I have to the game like this
has been the case
with other like enemies too
similarly yeah
so they should they should do something
about that fix it
um
I can also I arrived that is true that
is true but okay I guess I have to
thank you for reminding me I'm trying to
play the game fairly you know that's why
I don't even think about that okay now
my mama told me that there's a topoki
cream you know normally it comes with
this like it looks really red that's why
you know it's spicy but there's a cream
topoki version that's uh supposedly not
spicy and there's some places that have
that new card huh
some places that have that is that my
meat all good yes and
um so we were we're gonna go to like a
chain restaurant that has a topoki
buffet
um I'm not gonna walk over there again
right there's nothing there really for
me
I go down at least I got the chest
uh that that a chain restaurant that's
supposed to have it that like she she
saw it before and she never tried it
before she said she wanted to try it
anyway
um it's maybe not quite the
oh
and it's interesting yeah interesting I
just know 10 outfits
[Music]
so that's a that's a chewing gum from
the Korean company latte and I thought
Nabi mama knows that so I was like
singing and dancing that for her but she
was like what what what what
recognize it so I'm like
Lotus literally like
you guys have like a lot of hotels you
have a lot of shopping malls lots of
everything and you you don't know the
lot the chewing gum
because I know it's like I know it from
Japan from all the commercials they do
like a [\h__\h] ton of commercials maybe
that's just uh one thing that lotta does
mostly in in Japan and not in Korea
fascinating but anyway
yeah of course I know that jingle
oh it's it's like burned into my brain
from a million commercials
so cute like they always get these uh
celebrities and idols and all that to
dance to the commercials I don't know if
they still do it nowadays but they they
definitely used to do it they get like
famous people
to do the lot to dance and I I know the
dance because I'm famous just kidding
ah okay we're going up again was this
the way up
got it
okay so we went to a place haha sorry
you will have to listen to endless
breaks in my story
[Music]
please don't dance when you can do 3D
again oh I can't oh cow carrot good that
you're here you can like put everything
together
um
uh
okay so we went there yeah yeah yeah it
was oh my God in fact it was just
walking to the restaurant already made
me feel
overheated again the [\h__\h] humidity I
can't I can't this Phoenix cannot handle
heat okay
I admit it
and yeah but uh we went there and then
and then while we walked there we passed
through some cute streets not really
cute just normal streets but uh there
was like a tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny baby
kimbap place
just really tiny like it doesn't look
like anything special it was just like a
tiny place where there's like
um a tiny place where they were making
it selling it to go mostly but also
there were two seats inside two tiny
seats basically basically just uh the
the width of the space where you could
sit was like one square meter
um but you could get kimbap there and I
was like oh look there's game up there
but we walked by because we wanted to
get
oh I forgot about that dude we wanted to
get the um
no no you can't get me from there
no you're supposed to get this one
[Music]
that shouldn't be possible either
okay I will forgive because this isn't
in the game now I don't want to get
close to this thing because that looks
like it would hurt me will I use my no I
don't need to use my opinion
come here don't hurt me
don't hurt me hey I'm here attack me
oh I still bleeding already
oh my God
he's busy I guess
oh yeah bye
may I open the chest please kindly
so we walked to the Pokey place and we
enter and we um we take a seat and they
start like um it's like a like a like
one of those shabu-shabu places where
you cook on your own seat like there's a
heating plate and um
there's a heating plate and and they put
like they start by cooking some water
or in like a bowl thingy and then you
have like these these at least in this
case you you get like your own little
um
cooking pots like tiny ones out of metal
or something to go grab some ingredients
at the buffet
um
[Music]
so we we grabbed the pots and then
you're supposed to get like the sauce
uh the topoki sauce for the Pookie
you're supposed to get it at the buffet
so we walk around the buffet like five
times and we just can't find the right
sauce
I feel like I have no choice man
he doesn't I mean I guess if he doesn't
attack man just run around okay I'm
gonna die I'm gonna die I'm gonna die
I'm gonna die I'm gonna oh this shooter
okay okay just just survive uh the
dynamite guy hi
but how do I get to
am I gonna get an item where I can jump
finally
this little [\h__\h]
try it again try it again try it again
buddy sure actually you're
you are cornered here so [\h__\h] you okay
Mama Mia I thought I could just run
straight to the statue
[Music]
oh man okay
or straight over there to the light
um
I want to go up first
but maybe in the light I get an item
that makes me jump and then I can go to
the statue
I mean at least we can get the chest
first
unless this hurts me oh no I'm fine okay
so we walk around five times we just
can't find the [\h__\h] sauce
and then Navi Mama asks the the staff
and they're like even though they
normally have it at this place
they said they have every sauce today
except for that cream top
pers
and we were like men
we went all the way here we were ready
to eat
and you don't have the right sauce right
now ah so that was a problem we couldn't
find that so we um
left we actually left because we didn't
do anything yet we didn't grab any food
it was just the water cooking that's it
yeah so we were like sorry then we
actually we I really can't eat the spicy
stuff so we're actually Gonna Leave very
soon sorry
um
yeah we came for that so you know so
then we sat outside the restaurant for a
while oh Monastery did we have a map or
not
just that's the swamp
we haven't been there either have we
what Cathedral no we don't have a map
for that
um
yeah and uh yeah we sat outside and
navima was trying to find
out oh dear
I'm like about to die dude
if I can eat a berry I can eat a berry
she was looking up on the phone like
other places
um
uh wait I'm gonna do this again
just like the same chain
uh sorry menu problems
there we go that says she sent you
okay uh
wait this one's giving me give me money
right
I have three of them
or cheese cubes
are they right
don't use them oh don't use them
okay you know what I'll keep that
do this I'll I'll have some
um emergency berries ready
ah there was a decoys ah
you recommend to save them okay
up or left does that hurt me if I walk
by
oh there's a sniper there
is a sniper
I did it because I had it on the same
button where I had the grappling hook
before yeah boy oh wow
okay at least we took care of that
don't be scared
oh he got a hit he got a hit
oh yeah
up up oh oh another sniper can we sneak
up onto him
yeah oh
okay come here
because I changed the buttons like this
why did I do that just put it like it
was before
I'm gonna use up all the berries on
y'all he walked over that easily but I
can't right
I'm not even gonna try
I don't know
when in danger just greatness my that's
my life
that's my life
um principle
I did it again
[Music]
is there a [\h__\h] statue that I can
reach somewhere close by or not because
they went outside
the one outside I can't use
or wait can I
can I use my grappling hook on it
I'm almost there
just run okay
I'm so scared I don't want to die though
[Applause]
[Music]
oh is that
I know
one more Berry
just to survive
and we'll we'll get one of those over
here because
oh
yeah
oh my God I should have I should wear a
heart monitor today I'm so on edge
uh
just walking over that hurts me too um
[Music]
um
uh walking past that it's so narrow I
don't even think I
get through that oh
nice Dodge thank you
one as fast as you can that's like it's
like staying way faster because I can't
run any poster
they can roll right into that
no no no no no no no
you can't you can't do this to me no
oh no
no
no if I die now I'm gonna cry
[Music]
if I walk into its territory one more
time
I'm dead
but it's hard to even guess where that
territory is and where it starts and
where it ends
okay okay let me get that shortcut
or like open the door I mean I guess not
really a shortcut
please tell me there's a statue right
behind that with no enemies surrounding
it
I I I I oh wait it won't kill me at
least with one HP okay
well I guess
that's good
it's up here
Ninja
we'll have to look
okay that's the other side of that okay
yeah but I'll tell you
I'll tell you my story when I'm not
[\h__\h] dying anymore okay
I need a statue I need what is this why
is this game making me why is it
torturing me so much
why is it why is it torturing it even
showed me a statue outside but it's like
haha can't use
them on this guy Knockouts oh
yes and the depleting is so mean because
mean because I couldn't even hear myself
up now anymore open chest couldn't even
heal myself up if I wanted to because
look at how little my HP
um
is even like
like you know
the one that heals me [\h__\h] you
whatever the [\h__\h] that is
wait what does this doesn't kill me
right I just pray and then I look at
like ah look at the other world the
other dimension right oh no wait that's
not yeah wait yeah yeah
equip the Mask wait does it make them
think I'm one of them
was that it yeah yeah wait there was
something ah they can't hear me when I
wear that right that was it I think
uh where's the notes about that
[Music]
bye
yeah bye
bye bye
am I
I'm crumbling
I'm falling apart where is that where is
a memo
oh it's no it stops the radiation oh
there was at the last page it stops the
radiation
ah it doesn't say anything about it
[\h__\h] memos don't even help
um like the other one we got was
um does like something with a shield
right is that the orange gem
okay well I guess yeah we need that here
very
um urgently
which one should I replace so what does
this one do again
does that just make me stronger
should I do it like this maybe
um makes a shield me don't go down less
that lets you block more oh okay
whatever for now I'm doing this
but I still need a [\h__\h] statue
wait are we supposed to pray at that
statue at this one
oh I look funny with the mask
let me pray
I can come back easily now
yeah
is it really is that so
I looked at it but this is still like
nothing to me
um
I'm like
whoa
what
Mommy I'm stuck
okay
what I'm going in circles but
what is oh
what is this
what
there's something there
did I
no don't tell me I listened to the wall
oh bro bro
ha
if I came so far and then glitched into
something I would cry
rolling is just
seeing people tell you to stop rolling
don't listen to them don't stop don't
stop just roll your own way
ah snow
there's snow up here
are we like
I guess because it's next to the
mountain area that we went to before but
hey we made a like a shortcut now and we
can go down here okay
[Music]
uh what about the Statue though I was
promised the statue
man
it's not there left or right
um
thank God those are not explosives
living on the edge
that that statue is a tease
100 percent
so if I go here oh sniper hello
oh
[Music]
does that lead me to those to a statue
in the beginning
wait what where am I
don't do not
just checking just checking
can I go the other way
so why does this one lethal there's like
a there's a there's a door there that
leads to somewhere
oh and there's a Chester okay well we'll
remember that if you think
that's another path to get another item
okay let's take a look at the snow area
Okay Okay sometimes you know sometimes
in in a dire situation like this I need
your advice so thank you you seem to
know that the safer option right now is
to go up
rather than down but well I'll remember
that I'll remember that there was
something there
okay so we're going this way also first
I go this way nothing
okay
mustard
endless stairs yay
is this Heaven I think it's Helen guys
the endless Phoenix cycle of being
reborn again and again is finally over
sayonara everybody I'm going to heaven
where I was always supposed to go bye
bye suckers
with this
what is the Heavenly statue that heals
me huh
finally sweet Embrace of the fear
oh yeah I haven't seen enemies in a
while
oh
it's connected it is connected
I was wondering if maybe we'll reach the
same place we've been here before
and I
did I not explore this area I wonder
because I think normally I always
explored every single [\h__\h] corner but
in the snowy area I wasn't sure man
so it
what if I pray does it open no why'd you
tell me why don't you tell me to go here
for healing
are you tell me not to like go down here
just for healing
[Music]
there's nothing much here but I can at
least go through this place safely I
guess
you can easily hit the statue and then
come back with others wait what why you
say I can come back
you're saying that as if there's there
was a teleportation portal here
[Music]
was there one
foreign
[Laughter]
I'm not going to be killed now
[Music]
gonna take a throat candy because I've
been screaming so much
oh one more Berry so you're not in one
shot no no
I'm gonna waste my berries
[Music]
what do I do
lonely Fox
abandoned
in this endless scary world
where everybody just wants to hurt
these cute folks
the other path right
let me know
um
I mean look
[Music]
um
okay
ah
I am now at the very top I'm at the top
and down there is a statue
that I would like to use
um
how do I get there fast without dying
la la la
[Music]
don't wanna I Don't Wanna Hurt You you
don't hurt me and I'm not gonna hurt you
he won't he won't see me really okay
[Music]
I think this might be
the way do you know the way
no no I need to go
was it something
oh
were there enemies here
[Music]
can I go down
I want to go down
I'm scared didn't you me too but at
least the music is good
wasn't this a path too no
all right
if that that wasn't the path then
there must have been a path here to go
somewhere
where that must have come from I must
have come from somewhere
ah here there you go
oh man what where am I going
[Music]
I went up even higher now I feel like
is this really
it's way too intense right this is
really like what
their intention
I'm confused enlighten me
game enlighten me please
at least this is a safe place
no
see
I think
[Music]
ah
it took me five million 36
000 in two years
not that much not at all
okay now we go back into the
hell hole that we have just witnessed
okay and while we're walking back I'll
tell you my story
[Laughter]
okay
cream sauce so I'm kind of sad yeah but
yeah we were planning to go to lot the
world after lunch so at this point just
we have we wasted a little bit of time
it looked good and then
uh Navi mama said okay I'm gonna try to
find another place but we couldn't
really find something close or so
uh so what what we did instead
we were like okay how about we came up
instead
and then we went
into that
like
me not
nothing
uh came up place that I mentioned before
um with like literally
sitting space of one square meter
yeah
but
it was nice it was fine
um I mean that's the only kimbap I've
tried so far so I can't say if it's like
super good or decent or whatever Nabi
Mama did say that that kimbap was a
little bit different than others I don't
know how
but it was still kimbap definitely so we
got like four different
flavors uh it was like one was with
chicken one was with tuna one was with
something that translated to flying
some kind of flying fish
and uh
what's the other one I did I did write
it to someone on Twitter in a reply
somebody was like oh this is not even
fish
how do you know
it has to do there were four different
variations
like there's something like flying
flying
something it wasn't my it wasn't my
replies
and to be honest I don't like seaweed
that much but I tried to eat it anyway I
was like
I I did
you know I pick it with food but I I
will tell you that I did overcome
my fears and ate quite a few things that
I would normally wouldn't have eaten
so I don't take any complaints uh and I
I ate the oh
yeah I ate the kimbap I ate quite a lot
of it
uh but I mostly ate like the the chicken
at the tuna one because that one tasted
the best to me
yeah yeah so then at least we had some
kind of a lunch and you know what at
that heat
I think I enjoyed uh eating the Kimba up
there because uh it was like the kimbap
kimbap is like cold it looks kind of
like sushi
um but it's not Sushi hmm
we were eating one serving with two with
us too while next to us there was
actually for a little while there was
some some businessmen sitting there
eating the same serving alone in a
really short amount of time
much faster than we were
yeah and then we finished that and then
um I thought we were gonna go to lot the
world lots of Worlds then but I you know
it was kind of the last day
um where I could eat that Korean hot
corn dog that I really wanted to eat
was my last chance wait should I go down
now maybe I should go down now
it was my last chance so
um wanted to make it possible for me
um
but
yeah but uh we just couldn't freaking
find it we went to what was it what was
that place
she said that
we don't have to go to lots of world
right away because a lot of people go
like later on on the day like in the
evening so we can just go later and we
can try to get the hot dog first and she
said she thinks that she could find
um
she could find it in myeongdong
myeongdong was the place which is
another kind of like popular shopping
street I guess
um
so we went to myeongdong
and there were definitely a bunch oh the
Quarry and we're definitely a bunch of
street food vendors
and we were looking for one that sells
those corn hot dogs that were on my
members only one paper
but we were looking for like two [\h__\h]
hours
and we just couldn't find it we like
asked the other Street vendors like I
bought like I bought one one thing that
wasn't a corn dog it was like a like a
egg
on
like a kind of like a fried egg on top
of um
kind of like a cake
a biscuit
uh thing
so it was kind of sweet actually even
though it was an egg
kind of sweet so I ate that and then we
asked the vendor if we asked him if like
if he knows if there's any
any of those hot dogs around here
ah
what
there's a shortcut hidden there what the
[\h__\h]
yeah and they said oh like right now
probably not maybe in the evening
Mama really really wanted to find it for
me well I actually like I was like I
guess it's not here I guess I'm not
eating the hot dog this time sad but
okay and she really really wanted me to
get it so we ran around myeongdong for
like two hours even though we just
wanted to go there like for a short
moment
to receive
the
street food yeah
[Music]
um
okay
um and while we were doing that Nabi
mama's phone was like if this was the
beginning of the day okay we just met
and had some some lunch and her phone
was dead so we let her phone charge
in in a in an Apple store we just left
it there I'm like Mama Nami Mama are you
sure you just want to leave it there she
was like yeah I guess so it's probably
fine
um so she she left it there and we went
around looking for the food
and we uh couldn't find it but we ate
something else and then we went uh into
like a makeup oh the snipers
[Music]
we went to the makeup store
we went into a makeup store and um I
wonder if I can push that down and make
them explode
um because if I attack it it just
explodes at the spot
yeah
I see a Chester I see it I see it I'm
not blind I've seen things that I
haven't even seen
I saw them without seeing them
I don't don't run
okay okay
come here
him
you come here
I know he falls down
okay okay all good all good all taken
care of
where was I what was I saying
oh yeah we couldn't find it
uh yeah half a while the phone was
charged well enough and at this point it
was like 4 P.M and I was like Nami mama
I really think we should get going now
but yeah I was like we walked so much in
the humid heat so we were actually kind
of close to my hotel more or less so we
went there to to change I I wanted to
change clothes because I also wanted to
drop off the things that I bought like
some makeup stuff and so on
um
so we went to the hotel I changed this
was around 4pm
and we
then Nabi mama had a genius idea
of um
of uh just ordering food to come to the
hotel
uh I thought you know street foods
might be difficult but there was a chain
that does those hot dogs
and on delivery there's a story that
focuses on a restaurant that focuses on
it and you can also order from them so
this was our last solution and I was
like you know what I like being in this
air-conditioned hotel right now to cool
down a little bit so why the hell not
so we did that
should I go to the other place first
before walking down this path
oh is it a dead end
oh it's a dead end oh okay but there's
there's this oh I think I should go to
the snipers first Maybe
they looked fresh yeah I did upload a
picture on Twitter
um there were four and they're they were
pretty uh volumes
um it was a set of four but it was kind
of already set in stone what kind they
would be
there's three paths now
um
oh
I I got scared
[Music]
oh
but it
it just went first without hurting me
either
for money
I didn't have the shield out
it didn't reflect anything
or when I when I used the shield before
and those dudes I don't think it did
anything
I'm gonna break it down a little bit for
the Japanese Bros the few ones that are
here
[Music]
um
this is okay I think I reached the point
where I go back to English okay
so I had these four hot dogs okay corn
dogs I guess you actually call them
that's sort of
time
look at them glitching
[Music]
foreign
yeah okay
Mamma Mia
that'll be worth it
yes
what is in here
for me to pray oh
now we're talking oh we're talking how
to use this
two two shots only
does it use I don't know I don't want to
waste it but I need to practice man what
avocado
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay we're gonna use it on an enemy I'm
gonna assume that uh autofocuses like
the the fire weapon that we have
um
and I'm gonna assume that we're gonna go
to a statue again soon
we'll learn jumping soon
so it will be digital
okay okay where do we go next down or
right down or right
I said it down here
okay wait actually we could look at the
map for once
look at the map for once
[Music]
am I here no okay no yeah I'm here right
ah yeah
I love the map
uh actually where it cuts off so
that's interesting so that means it's a
dead end eventually so that's good oh no
[Music]
you can raise it but I can't reach you
oh but no no there he misses
I'm [\h__\h] up the controls right now
scoozy mi amor aha
foreign
am I supposed to just shoot them from
there
but I can't go down there anyway huh hmm
[Music]
it's a one-way ah I would just fall down
fall down now
is that worth it all right
wait
that means we would leave this place
once huh and then we could probably heal
[Music]
there's a sword dude there too
hmm
no the bridge was a dead end
but I think there was a
h
I think wasn't there a second a ladder
yeah okay
there was a second letter
that's so mean though
without the grappling hook man you're
lost you have to rely on it here
there's no way around it
unless you're [\h__\h] badass and
invincible
foreign
okay so we ordered we ordered the hot
dogs right
oh
no nothing here we ordered the hot dogs
it was four and you know there was there
were two that had those those cubes that
you saw in them those were potatoes
potato cubes on top and there was sugar
on top and uh so what's inside though it
was uh different
depending on
a little
depending on the hot dog so we both went
for the ones with the cubes first yeah
and then Nabi bites in and inside is
just you know the typical corn dog
filling and a hot dog a sausage okay
she finds it pretty early and also there
that it came with a [\h__\h] ton of ton of
sauces
really fun actually like all kinds of
different crazy sauces
yeah
um oh no
Over My Dead Body
so you put like a lot of sausage on top
and then you eat it and then I I take
the same one the one that looks the same
from the outside and I keep on
eating but inside was
um no sausage
so I was kind of like what the [\h__\h] I'm
being scammed
but there was uh what was it
mozzarella mozzarella cheese it was
filled with mozzarella cheese not the
typical corn dog filling
and I'm like
I mean this is really good too but I
want the sausage
[Music]
then I I ate it until half and there's
still no sausage so I'm like okay you
know what I'm gonna try one of the ones
without the the potato cubes
and then I I eat one and it also doesn't
have a sausage it was also filled with
mozzarella
one of the other ones without the cubes
and that one uh
I think
it had like a tiny sausage at the very
bottom also maybe I'm not sure anymore
but then she tells me to finish the
first one because there might be a tiny
tiny tiny baby sausage at the very
bottom so I'm like okay I guess because
I still I really want that sausage now
so I hated until the end there was a
time
at the time bottom but hers hers was the
the best one because there was actually
a long size sausage in there
and hers yeah just not in mine why I
chose the wrong one
I should have gotten that one
[Music]
okay well at least now everything's safe
down here let's see what happens if I go
down
[Music]
ah
but yeah they were really yummy there
was one also that was not normal
potatoes but sweet potatoes uh that was
really yummy too Nabi Mama enjoyed that
one the most
she really likes sweet potatoes
yeah she ate like a lot of the times
when I asked her what did you eat for
breakfast it was always sweet potatoes
she always said sweet potatoes
there you go info about Nabi mamas she
really likes sweet potatoes
mama
sweet potato
ES
that's why she's so sweet
[Music]
wow
good try oh
okay there's a pop there I didn't even
see that
surprise path
that's so sparkly man
pretty cold
I like it it's so original
I feel like very original this place
hey uh too late did I just kill him with
two hits incredible
so at this point it was like
it was getting it was turning 5 p.m I
think
so it was pretty late and I was worried
like it's really okay to go to a lot of
the world so so late because if it's
anything like Disney World and Nami Mama
did say it's kind of like uh Disneyland
with like standing in line for a long
time because the attractions are really
popular
huh
wait let me explore this I can't see
[\h__\h] though
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
what this place is huge
how can I explore all of this without
missing out on something
looks like Moria oh like well a mythical
version of Moria um
[Music]
thanks for the pinky
is there something here no it's so
sparkly wow
what is this uh Stone made out of in the
first place I wonder
is that like a real existing Stone
uh oh
shall I go in here this is it too early
should I Explore More I wonder
decisions decisions decisions
question my question my question mark
sis
would be too easy
I thought that would have been too easy
which I heard some sparkly sound but
these enemies are dead
that's interesting
very interesting
yeah why
[Music]
um
please don't be a boss fight
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
the [\h__\h]
am I like
somewhere where I have a map am I here
swamp nah
I don't have a map of this I think
do I
not in the Quarry anymore
foreign
[Music]
things
there's aliens or what
[Music]
was that
what is that
[Music]
Magic
it says the statue but it looks very
different but it heals me
oh
sci-fi ah oh yeah I forgot the upgrades
I forgot about the feature completely
uh
[Music]
that's how I like it
bye I'm going to [\h__\h] die
please go away
am I really ready for this one hit kill
you know the fire ones I guess so
or hmm yeah
uh wait how do I use this again uh
uh here right yeah okay okay
we can do both because I have too much
money what does this one do again
ah defense all right
[Music]
am I am I ready for this
you beat the others without a struggle
did I know did I feel like I was
struggling a lot today
they dropped more magic than the one
taste cat uh-huh okay
attack up
very nice
the librarian was the strongest blush oh
really I love everybody you think so
um
well that's a personal opinion I would
say but you might be not so wrong I
don't think
Nick here do I
don't know
I might change to my go-to option again
but whoa what is this though
please tell me does this make my shield
block uh things that it hasn't blocked
before does it make it reflective
[Music]
that would be epic
ah duration for black
I still need the mask leave it on oh
okay
[Music]
I guess we're doing this now
ah oh yeah right okay uh sorry sorry uh
sorry sorry Mommy
okay
okay okay I need to get used to the
stick again
where was I okay we ate the hot dogs it
was kind of uh
they kind of uh scammed me
but they were really yummy
good and the combination of you know
came up and then a little bit later
eating the
the
hot dogs it was really good yeah it
filled me up and it was a good lunch in
combination so it
I did not get to eat kimbap at all
anywhere
which is
I came up did I say Kimber I mean topoki
which is a bit unfortunate I guess
because it's a very very popular dish
a meal in Korea but you know then I have
something
[Music]
I have something for next time
wow is this really how I should do it
okay this one up
wait
charge I thought I killed it
[Music]
okay well at least it killed the other
one
to do it let me out of here
okay
um pink Chihuahua think
there's even more down there
it's not the only one
and there's four
[Music]
are you gonna shoot your friend yeah
okay two downs but at what cost
[Music]
I can just pass ah there's nothing to go
to
this music is cool
[Music]
what more
hmm
[Music]
oh I got that one okay it's dead
one more
I will try to just shoot that one
I think it needs one more hit
okay I wasted one but okay
probably not the best way to do it but
what you gonna do huh
[Music]
oh hey you came a little bit too close
for comfort did you
where was I oh yeah yeah and finally
finally we made our way to lots of Lotte
world and we took a train
and we arrived pretty late 5 p.m or even
later
uh but there's a ticket that's like uh
after uh 4 P.M
so it's like a little bit cheaper so at
some point when we realized that we were
gonna be late anyway we were just like
aiming to go after
oh what was this again
we were just aiming to go up
after
4pm yeah we're like whatever I guess if
Nabi mama says it will be fine then
hopefully it'll be like fine is this a
shortcut
it's a shortcut
so we arrived after a while and our plan
was to wear matching school uniforms
because that's apparently a thing that
they like to do there's even outside of
a lot of the world and inside there's
places where you can rent school
uniforms female and male
uh and they're like they kind of look
like cosplay they don't look too
realistic but
I am and there's some that look a little
more serious than others
um
and you have like choices of colors and
ties and you can have a ribbon or a tie
and you can have a Blazer but you know
it's summer so we didn't go for the
Blazer
um
[Music]
oh
what
[Music]
I
what
I was just telling my story comfortably
what the actual [\h__\h]
[Music]
what
[Applause]
[Music]
are you [\h__\h] kidding me now
I'm out of healing
yeah oh sure sure I'll [\h__\h] you up
[Applause]
[Music]
go away go away wait there's no place
for you right okay
did you see what just happened I I
thought I was gonna die so I wasn't
taking it too seriously but
I was like
[\h__\h] it
man that was such a such a troll I
thought I had to pray at that thing and
it was gonna go down like the others
that looked like that
what is this
getting dizzy
[Laughter]
okay Moravian clutch chill clutch
clutches
there's too many pads so I hope they all
lead to the same place
oh
this is confusing
where was okay I I remember okay we were
talking about renting a school uniform
uh
I am going in a circle okay
huh
um
so we we took a school uniform and
um and then we went inside now
everywhere we were all at inside we
chose one that uh was inside a lot of
the world so after you enter and
bye-bye
and then
what the [\h__\h] oh
I need healing
um
I need the healing
suddenly minibus yeah
the hell man
I was surprised
oh what the [\h__\h] it's like
the skeleton of my mom
like they took so much energy from your
dad at this point she's just bones
basically
that's heartbreaking
no comment to that fox huh really
say something
this is shocking
this is a shocking thing to look at
it
oh my God
is it my mom is it is it though
maybe it's a different Fox wait what is
this
do I pray
[Music]
should I pray
oh no brain just staying
should I pray or should I stay
what's that song again
I don't want to go deeper
all the foxes they're all dying
what's gonna happen to me too
my health is did I just see my health
depleting why am I going crazy
I feel like I just saw it like
going down a tiny amount but that's just
me going crazy probably
yeah it's getting really dark
I mean like literally and
um figuratively
haha
winter sweet songs
[Music]
no
I don't want to see I think no
no no
[Music]
what
but I've been shutting those down right
am I was like turning them on no I
wasn't shutting them down
[Music]
like when you say I killed them but like
at this point are they even alive you
know
like they've been
turned into skeletons basically not no
energy left what the [\h__\h] you can't
me like bouncy music
Whiplash what
what it's like a factory
it's a factory where you drain the
energy from the foxes to turn them into
these statues that
something ah why are they dead though
why are they
dead
why are the enemies dead
maybe the previous hero tried to save
but he came too late or he didn't get
very far he died in the process or
music is kind of loud man
the radiation oh okay
[Music]
okay
no problem
[Music]
what what what happens when they hit me
yeah bye
what's the best way to fight those I
wonder
[Music]
and I don't I don't like this atmosphere
the game had a nicer happier atmosphere
before
yeah what the [\h__\h] is going on I think
I'm gonna die okay
wait wait wait wait
what
this is not the right away they drain my
HP don't they
[Music]
this level is hard final level vibes
Vibes Vibes like that definitely keeps
like end game Vibes but I'm not ready
so we're gonna learn how to jump
still need that piece of map man
the one in the Overworld
oh man what the [\h__\h]
um
I think maybe I can try icing them
I wonder if they would still split but
maybe
when they go tiny and I ice them then
and I can ice several ones at once I
don't know
there's still a lot of athletes Oh Mamma
Mia well it's only been two hours so I'm
not surprised I guess
[Music]
rolly rolly
oh [\h__\h]
guys
man
huh
oh we're gonna use potion of slots that
is cool
um
okay
okay I'm gonna turn down the musical
it's a bit too loud
[Music]
crap onto that music shield to protect
myself
this is
suffering so far
um I'm just gonna just gonna run through
here
for a sec
okay hello uh wait oh
[Music]
wait um
okay I I think it's over no it's not
over don't give up don't give up
I know when I hit them then they
immediately I shouldn't have drunken
they immediately
[Music]
they don't stay I stay immediately turn
into the tiny ones
[Music]
it looks my house
I need healing I need more frequent uh
healing thingies
healing statues
Mommy
oh no
[Music]
oh shoot them shoot them shoot them shut
up
[Music]
I can't run I can't run I get wrong
it's not working
oh it's not worth it it's not worth it
it's not worth it how do I keep on
Surviving these situations just ask
myself
[Music]
yeah but it's a setback I have to walk
so fast if I die that's my problem
that's what I don't want to
[Music]
um
I could Escape by like grappling over to
the those Forks Maybe
but okay
I have no potions left so I'm gonna die
soon
foreign
[Music]
mm-hmm
oh there's the spiders I feel them
they're gonna come again
[Music]
Maybe
I can do a combination they do give a
lot of magic
[Music]
it would be really cruel if there was a
mini Boston you're saying that with that
face makes me feel like there is one
spoon
first time donating thank you thank you
God is AOE oh but yeah I haven't used it
but it only has like a
okay now it has three shots
but it loads up again with magic too
right let me let's try it and next time
I see them
let's try but I feel like I'm gonna
crumble under the depression
[Music]
wait
oh
boy
[Music]
mommy oh my God
thank you for that little piece of Hope
that I didn't think I still had in me
Olivia
and I've been using a new loading screen
since yesterday if you guys have noticed
it's so nice isn't it I can't stop
looking at it it's so cute
stacking up is so adorable it's the
cutest thing ever oh yeah so Olivia's
made it I put him into the credits in
the description I put dakuma and
Olivia's because I don't know I might be
like switching here and there
but he's been making like amazing cute
pixel animations and I feel like it
would be a waste to not use them for
anything I couldn't resist
okay so these last time I met these they
turned into monsters and now they're
still because I'm faking the middle one
it's probably a normal one and the
outside ones are enemies probably
even more like a boss like a more
difficult one because this is here it's
so close so it's okay to die
I have yet to try out the gun though I
guess we'll try it out now
[Music]
okay do a quick damage fast
oh did I got that I think did I I don't
know no I don't think I did
go away going okay let me try this
oh cool Leo
do it again hey what what
you guys
I don't need to I don't need you here
okay
we do it again
[Music]
but okay you get a lot of magic
oh I need the map can I [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I think I'm gonna die but it's okay
no I can actually make it if I don't if
I if I stop being stupid for once
[Music]
I can't shoot it's okay according him
however the [\h__\h] I did that on the first
try it wasn't that difficult if you lose
the gun holy [\h__\h] pretty op
could have done better could have done
way better
I'm like I have these moments where I'm
like I'm not gonna make it anyway so I
don't need to be too serious about it
but then it still somehow seems possible
to make it so then I changed my mind
about it but I'm like in this weird spot
where I'm not sure if I should try or
not if I should give up or not
um
would be funny if the middle one is a
monster too
you mean when I pray now
it would turn into a big monster and so
the fight that we just had was not the
real fight
oh that would be so funny
it's normal
so far it's all normal
okay okay
it's opening paths
uh I can heal myself right without that
respawning
[Applause]
about the free spawn just run through
them
but they'll follow me
what you did
cut the code on this kiddle
my
um they're playing with me like I'm a
toy
uh which way do we go
[Music]
I'm just running through now oh now I
feel like I should have gone a different
way
I feel like I should have gone a
different way
okay that's why they stop
uh I feel like I should have gone the
other way first damn it
foreign
[Music]
this is remind me of this like
overwhelming exaggerated amount of
Darkness
what does that remind me of
what came
where did I show you this the hidden
vault
not the Matrix no I don't even remember
I watched that when I was a baby but I
don't remember the content of it
yeah bye
bye
oh is that a healing altar that I can't
use
[Music]
oh no it's on the other side
second wait no it doesn't work it
probably doesn't work but I can activate
this and then the door will open
and maybe the altar will work too then
[Music]
oh
yeah oh wait did that oh
it work okay
um quite terrifying place to be in right
now
um
[Music]
gives you Doctor Who Vibes I do get Tron
vibes
there's one hot girl
in The Matrix wait I don't know where to
go first I'll go this way first
what's up
wait where do I go first I guess not
here
there was some something interesting
there
something very interesting someone who
killed all of these mobs maybe it wasn't
radiation afterwards after world because
they're wearing the mask if their
radiation was that bad then I would be
dying too
I mean they're probably longer here than
me but still
oh we can teleport here now
oh
that is gold
ah it's hidden
that's why it's back here and I can't
reach the other teleportation thing is
anyway it's useless basically oh wait I
can't reach it never mind
okay
but it's hidden still hidden
okay wait that's a boss fight the the
real boss this time
that's why we got the teleportation here
and uh another another healing Point
there's they're very generous with those
now they could have been a little bit
more generous before remember
would have been nice okay
this boss is hard
well somebody said that they found the
librarian to be harder so
I have High Hopes but I wonder should I
use the AOE gun or not because like
we're not gonna be killing that much
there's just one mob supposedly
he's probably gonna spawn all the mobs
the other ones did too
um is he gonna give me enough magic to
make it worthwhile
I'm part of the librarian oh [\h__\h]
this boss has a shield and it's
infuriating oh man
until I found out how strong a gun is
aha okay so maybe I should use the gun
yeah okay I used gun because it's
powerful okay
gun and we're just gonna go for the fire
now and then you know figure out how
this boss works and
maybe we'll we will probably need a
second try and switch around the weapons
are those things gonna come to life
we've seen those before but they didn't
do anything before
is that a fat fox or no it doesn't have
a tail
I thought it was like an evil Fox you
know
oh man
I'm not ready for this
but okay I I if I die the first time I
would say we don't even count that as
the first try we come to second try as
the first try because you have to get to
know your enemy first it's like no one
can explain to go in here blind and do
it first try although I mean I am a
gamer but still it shouldn't be
it shouldn't be the expectation okay
[Music]
I'm not coping
no the second try is the first try
um
should I just be Savage and shoot him
from behind
would it be nice if we could have a talk
you know
oh his shadow is cool
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh Shield okay
and now I understand oh
interesting
so far no damage oh I keep on dodging
she keeps on dodging
um but I'll keep on not making any
damage okay there we go um I got damaged
oh yes the same gun
I'm already sweating
yeah we're just gonna stay here for a
while
[Music]
um you know I want to be careful here
but you know it's a one time only use
loser
[Music]
I rolled the wrong way and he does it
again
oh my God
I'm just studying him okay but for me
just stunning him oh
I would say it's not too bad
hey
oh
[Music]
lots of damage
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I wrote the wrong way again
I can do it I can do a second fry easy
oh that didn't look man there's so much
going on oh
[Applause]
okay this is fun
that's so bad I I wasn't I wasn't even
you know I was mostly defensive in the
beginning so I can I can
if I just go for the offense it's not so
bad actually it's manageable can be
pretty aggressive with this one but he
doesn't seem to give me um what
has he been giving me Mana at all
[Music]
blocking
uh does my shield block him
he was threatening me when I fought him
I mean I do have five defense
and I I have the defense card
I don't know what you had
my shield box is blade hmm
freeze would be useful oh
could could be pretty good or even
grapple I mean I feel like you can use
all kinds of strategies with this one
Dynamite all of this works I think in in
my mind
just not quite the the this laser
because uh his shield reflected I'm not
sure if this is if the gun is like if
his shield reflects the gun I don't
think so I think it explodes just no
matter what he does
um
but okay then oh I think I want to try
uh putting him on ice
recording items is the way yeah holding
the dynamite until the end of the game
without ever using it because it's one
time use only and it feels like it's a
waste here
laughs
it's a waste not use it I guess but
still
I'm like worried that I use it and then
I don't have it when I actually really
need it you know dynamite dynamite is
just
too precious
oh yeah right there's my body there
give me my body back body back body back
um that that's an explosion too right
now hmm
how close do I have to go for him to
notice me
[Music]
all right
I'm doing actually worse to stop
oh
I don't care I don't care I don't care I
don't care
okay now I care
oh I have no magic left yeah
oh [\h__\h] perhaps no magic
I don't care
I don't quite care about your stupid
types of dynamite
it's so tiny it's like
maybe Dynamite
dude it's not
threatening dude
okay but I see I see I see okay let's
just kill me
trying to kill me then
I wanna try you know using my shield I
guess
hmm round fruit no this is round
two is now
not find free
go next
what if I just cornered him here
endlessly
I work
out
[Music]
the first one I dodged
okay but uh I tried to sword uh The
Shield ow
okay
that
I'm gonna figure it out guys I'm I'm not
even using my my full potential
[Music]
s
I want to try again
[Music]
halfway fertile
um but I'm not I'm not I'm not so
focused today it's not that difficult
this enemy is not it's not difficult man
pretty good easy
actually
uh my body is far away from him
I wish I could like go
do some starting damage with the
with the wand first but then switching
back to the ice weapon is kind of
dangerous
thanks guys
yeah that was pretty good um but then
I'm kind of corned too because like
running away there rolling away is a bit
difficult with the thing in the way that
weird thing whatever that is that he's
staring at
um
[Music]
okay
I'm not gonna get my body yet so I want
him to be close to it to get the damage
wow
[Music]
uh two Indians one spot
oh [\h__\h] I read them wrong I'm gonna die
oh wait don't die yet
I wanted to get it well he was like
right there with me I [\h__\h] it up I
[\h__\h] it up
[Music]
I want
more reach
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
that one happens so fast though oh
okay that's fine
[Music]
I need to I need to block my um
I know I know he's not so difficult I
know I can do it
the block
oh my body
[Music]
can I
um I was wondering if I can go to the
menu while blocking but no I can't it my
machine disappears once I got into the
menu
[Music]
I'm not coughing what you know I can do
it I know I can do it
but my my my
um
what's this finger called the the index
finger
it hurts from holding the focus button
on on the enemy
for pushing LT
hurts
[Music]
I
want to choose when I use my body
[Laughter]
why do we share one brain cell
s
oh
my God
oh he did that same thing
ah
[Music]
I'm gonna try this it doesn't even work
on it what or did he just block it
it's hard to get them
it's hard to get to him he blocked it so
it doesn't always work on but he has his
shield out it won't work
um
okay
[Music]
I might eventually if this takes too
many tries I might need a break for my
index finger
uh
under the ring looking real different
yeah it's looking mystical magical
uh carrying this
the thing is I never really successfully
used that so I don't think that in this
situation I would be able to
successfully use it either
ah
it's a stupid thought I don't like it
um
so
[Music]
what you gonna do what you're gonna do
when the tattoo comes for you
there's nothing
ah [\h__\h]
foreign
[Music]
uh I mean
[Laughter]
I'm trying to use my
skills more and more
didn't really get that fired up with it
all about learning the pattern
hmm
some of his moves are not
um like the when he shoots The Gun
there's like I don't I don't see much of
a like a warning there same for the
dynamite but the dynamite is super easy
to dodge it's just the gun
that you know have to be anticipating it
[Music]
yeah I want to Corner him hmm would be
good if I could do that
okay well then come here if I can't come
to you then
whoa
how did that hit me
[Music]
all right
hey blocked it
[\h__\h] him
oh I did I said am I doing damage I
think I did damage
sorry I'm getting like really quiet here
oh me that's really mean doing it two
times three times in a row is pretty
mean man
at the same time
what why don't we do it at the same time
[Music]
ah
I don't know I still have I know
[Music]
foreign
enough to go for the attack so so
bluntly
yeah but hey we
could start this time
why that got pretty far this time okay
I'll kill okay
harder than the librarian I'm not sure I
don't even remember the Librarians I
don't remember how the fight felt nah it
was too easy I guess because like the
first time we tried I was a bit
overwhelmed but the second time when
like when we came back with all the
upgrades I was too powerful at that
point of time and then this time I'm
like I think
um I could be more powerful Maybe
but the the way my skills are right now
is
um
I think
pretty uh low compared to
how we were before
if you know what I mean oh yeah I'm on
par
I know I can't do any more upgrades
right
this is it
I've done so far
maybe I should I'm not really using the
ice huh
I might want to try what's a grappling
hook see how it works to like bring him
over to me
if I can quickly attack him
um I will give it a try where's my body
oh okay
work
oh
whoa I like it
oh that didn't work
[Music]
interesting interesting interesting
interesting oh nice block
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] was brain cell
only one brain cells
oh my God
I'm gonna die
give me a [\h__\h] break
okay I'm too stupid I'm too stupid
oh
[Music]
I am video game AI yeah
which if we think so much alike then
instead of like the moment when I want
to use my gun is really the moment where
I should be blocking
I know he doesn't tune his attack no
and roll into him I try sometimes
I get scared
you're scared if you were you know
against this kind of enemy
I get more uses yeah I think I like the
the grappling
I can cancel some of his attackers I'm
grabbing oh interesting oh might want to
try that
foreign
here comes the second one though
ah you blocked it
I'm just I think I'm too stupid today I
might be too stupid to do this today I'm
normally better
I I just maybe just not my day
[Music]
I think
I thank you today is not my day today is
not my day today is just not my day my
finger hurts too you'll be guys I
secured them
[Music]
five minute break
yeah my finger really hurts
um
you'll be break yeah you'll be you'll be
uh no I want to I don't know how close I
am to finishing it but for some reason I
thought I could finish it today so I
mean it's just 7 P.M so
um
still have a lot of time
difficulty spikes 11 from this point 11
from like that
how are you counting that
no
our two our free locks in wait what's
our free
whichever ah this one
don't you mean Alfrey if anything
because L2 is focused
clicking in the stick oh really
actually not spawn uh any new enemies ah
it doesn't
ah it does it is all free
[Music]
oh that feels weird now I have to get
used to not pushing L2 down
it feels weird too but okay I'll I'll
give it a try I'll try to rest my ububi
[Music]
but you know you're so used to that
certain grip
now that would feel
unfamiliar you buy it
I could change the control so that the
lock on is L2
yes
yeah I would break my muscle memory
foreign
[Music]
I should have known this earlier
but usually like even for the boss
fights there were always more mobs
around so it wasn't
even useful I guess
[Music]
hey I don't know how to fight now how to
not push L2 I don't know how to
happen
then the left my my left hand is just
used for moving okay
kiwawa
just
don't don't push anything just don't
don't push don't push don't don't push
I'll know if I can do this
it makes me forget everything else
now I'm focusing on not pushing
it's easier
[Music]
just do it you're using my own my own
phrases against me
okay this will be ridiculous I'm telling
you already
I'm scared I don't know how to find
anymore
[Music]
foreign
so unoriginal
did he just throw a dynamite at me again
what is this thing that's lying around
there
what is that
I can't I can't
I can't I need to push
[Music]
hey I keep on hurting yourself
okay
oh shoot why am I doing that see I don't
know what I'm doing
[Music]
oh
it's not too bad oh but it's bad
yeah
what oh stop shooting
that's pretty bad it's pretty bad it's
pretty bad it's pretty bad I'm pretty
bad
[Music]
I'm gonna get used to this I'm gonna get
used to not using my left UB and then
afterwards I'm never gonna know how to
use it ever again when I need it Go
aggressive
um
you know the first driver wasn't even
trying wasn't even that bad
but now I'm overthinking right
you're so mean
thinking moments
[Music]
foreign
memories to make uh so much to give so
much to take oh yo
a brand focused on dodging sword attacks
commit to two hit and muscle muscle
well I mean
it's kind of what I want to do anyway
gonna be most of the student no no it's
like I'm I'm stuck here now because I'm
stuck in this mindset that you know I
can't do it
handsome thing about Korea
you know sometimes there's moments where
me tension thing makes me super uber
powerful but I don't think this is one
of those situations
no
[Music]
um
yeah
I can do it
I can do it I can do it just stop being
stupid just stop being stupid
[Music]
oh
yeah yeah I I think so too I couldn't
unfocus enough the tangent
okay okay okay okay mm-hmm
you guys said focus on on dodging his
attacks but
I feel like it would just turn into
another normal run
what is even the best way to starting a
fight like in in the library and you
know I got a lot of damage already in
the beginning because I could just
let him
now I wonder
let's keep it
up
[Music]
oh I tried to Parry
without success
foreign
[Music]
I thought I had enough distance
foreign
[Music]
okay
um yeah I did play better previously I
was I was you know having such a big
break will make me a little bit worse at
the game because I was like so in it you
know I was so immersed in it starting
first and I'm doing it two days in a row
what about using a rattling hook
um
oh no I want to switch I feel like I
kind of maybe even want to switch like
in between first the shoot shoot
now right now actually
um
[Music]
and then uh wait uh
okay sorry uh is he throwing Dynamite
yeah that is just too confusing
why do I still have the wand in my hands
[Music]
oh my God
it was like already up to this point
there were so many difficult sections
with those enemies the normal ones
and my brain is jelly
[Music]
I'm getting worse at this point every
time I try finding him
ah no we already tried Ice Ice is like
[Music]
let me try something
it doesn't get close enough it doesn't
even get close enough for it
foreign
[Music]
but also the reach of my sword is so
[\h__\h] tiny man
[Music]
I
kill them
now I'm just too stupid
I'm so sorry I was so good last time and
I felt so cool about it
I was like this is my game
[Music]
a cat break
you offering me that means so much to me
[Music]
but also is this really the best weapon
combination I don't know
I don't want to waste my Dynamite when
I'm still like failing so much
but I I know the dynamite would help a
lot but then the risk is that I'm gonna
use like I'm gonna use them all up and
then I'm gonna die anyway
if I had like if they were reloadable
that would be good
change mask oh what the [\h__\h] wait am I
safe here to change into something else
let me see
uh
looks like it
yeah
what was this again
was this attack
because I think I want attack
I'm not sure but if there's anything
else that's useful here
that's my block
oh
okay that's fine then too I guess no
yeah that's fine yeah that's good too
but honestly me not pushing down L2
really makes me feel so uncomfortable
even though my UV hurts but maybe now I
can push it again
um
I don't know this is the Run no it's not
no
[Music]
um
so close to me
foreign
this would make everything so much
easier
we all know that don't we
[Music]
wonderful
oh
[Music]
foreign
thank you
I've know my healing left
[Music]
ah
[\h__\h] oh uh no I have no more left
[Music]
stop that
I could have used the berries but
they're like two she's taking them out
and that moment is like
Sandra was thinking
oh so close and you said this is the run
and I said no this is not the run but it
could have been around it could have
been around right it could have been
around it could have been around okay
okay now now I'm more confident
what did I do differently like did I do
anything differently consciously or only
subconsciously
hmm
[Music]
yeah that one Dodge was the the the the
not the Dodge the the Parry was magical
yeah
if you guys say I did a lot of things
differently but I feel like I only did
it subconsciously
oh wait I'm not even focused
how dare you push me around like that
wait my help
oh no this is a background this is
officially a super bad stupid run
yeah and it's okay and wanna do a new
run I [\h__\h] up I know I [\h__\h] up
oh I know I know I know
I hate you
I hate you so much
[Music]
I hate you I know this is not gonna work
out so I'm just
says I'm saying [\h__\h] it
yeah oh the run right after really good
run usually terrible
um
why are you not using the grappling hook
my brain I'm trying to hurt to already
Dodge him
that using the grappling hook just I
don't have to yell you for it
he's holding my cats get him
hold my beer my non-alcoholic beer I
wouldn't even drink that to be honest
but but hold my known my non-alcoholic
beer
that's all you have to say
God damn it stop throwing up
why are you even getting all that from
[Music]
is this hurt yourself faster
not ready
the amount of times he's hurt himself in
this run is actually ridiculous
oh that's the first time you're doing
that one
[Music]
thank you
this is it though
I'm gonna [\h__\h] it up am I
feel like I am
[Music]
I swear to God this is like
we both had like
that like we hurt himself so often I'm
not he's not gonna do that again
it was one more hit he almost like hit
me baby one more time and I was like
okay I want to
be one more time too because I like the
song
I knew I knew it I knew it was gonna
happen
that's always happens it's the second
time it happened so close to to his
death I [\h__\h] it up
yeah I wanted to be hit
sorry but I think I'm back in the game
at least
maybe where's my body ah there okay
gosh I'm getting sweaty again
it was a good run only because he hurt
himself so often
um
I wish I could show you something
besides this boss fight really
ah
stretch
do a stretch
[Music]
it's like once I see him so low that's
where the pressure really hits
[Music]
stretch rotate those elbows rotate those
elbows
I need a massage
you know what I'm doing
I was rotating my head
okay
oh I meant I mean I guess I didn't mean
my elbows I guess not also rotating your
elbows I guess like for your for the
shoulder gilink
yes
good good stretch
stretch
joints yeah joints joints
I think I deserve a special chicken
massage after this
from you guys
okay
I forgot how to fight
problem with the game I played yesterday
I think the attack button was X and
today it's uh X is rolling and circle is
attacking which is again like a little
bit
it feels a little bit unfamiliar so
suddenly
um
additionally to the fact that I I
haven't played tunic in a while
it's stuff like that you know that makes
me uh crumble today
yeah last game had no stamina but that's
true
I'm not gonna alter the controls now
because that's gonna [\h__\h] it up too
[Music]
all right
foreign
[Music]
wait that was super delayed input I feel
like
I don't know that's weird
[Music]
oh but I was in trouble
foreign
again
[Music]
oh wow
foreign
yeah the beginning of the Run was good I
would like to repeat that copy paste
please
oh yeah do get him below 25 before I was
always 50 and I do get him lower than
before
oh my God what
[Music]
what let's go
ah
now I'm trying to watch my stamina
I'm trying
okay okay okay okay like the the try
before he was hitting himself so often
so that was fun and this one the
beginning the one before the hit the
beginning was good because we were
dancing
dancing the night away you and me in the
Moonlight uh
mmm
yeah if you want to get out of the chat
and focus on the fight for [\h__\h] sake
unbelievable this woman
I'm always like wondering about the
starch oh never mind
[Music]
foreign
still terrible
I don't rock late most of the time which
is kind of sad
that was a good timing
you're too close
foreign
yeah
I had no stamina
stop it
I
I have no more help left
hi goodbye
[Music]
I'm sorry
for having such little
HP I went pretty far there with nothing
to go again I wanted to be in a dream
okay okay next one is the Rundle I know
it
is
next one is the Run
a runs at least
um
I'm not stop asking for the dynamite I'm
not gonna use a dynamite
wait I didn't even use my no I did use
my body I didn't
yes
so this is the last run this is the last
run
believe me when I say this is it
I have trained hard I've trained enough
this is how the librarian would have
gone if I wouldn't have gotten all those
upgrades probably
if I would have just forcefully went at
it again and again and again
um
jinxed yeah
I believe in Jinx you only conjuncts
yourself if you believe in that kind of
stuff
that's basically you stopping yourself
I don't believe in those fairy tales
did it hit them
No it didn't
[Music]
oh
wow that was a little bit unexpected to
be honest and that was a miss so this is
not the run I'm taking it back
I wanted to time it well
I mean it's not lost yet
it's not quite lost yet
oh oh
yeah but it is but it is
I mean I still have a lot of HP
um thoughts but uh Magic wise I'm like
not doing so well uh
[Music]
foreign
but he's behind all of this [\h__\h] right
I need to get revenge for my mommy
for my of the lean friends feline
friends
I meant them the one after that yes
obviously obviously that
uh
I think I'm cursed I could have been
done like 30 minutes ago
with one more hit
could have even been done 50 minutes ago
foreign
[Music]
grappling hook even cancel out so far I
haven't seen canceling anything
see I'm getting worse again why am I
doing this
[Music]
I've been so good I have faces faces
when I'm good for a while and then I'm
bad for a while
foreign
[Music]
now let's get into a point where it's
making me very angry
it's making me very angry
yeah out of sync with the flow of the
battle that is very true
that is a good way to describe it
[Music]
how am I not hitting him
so close yet so far
[Music]
honestly
good dancers
[Music]
interesting
and now you're now you're getting a
little bit on my nerves again
[Music]
if you shoot at the back
oh I was so good in the beginning
[Music]
I see history repeating itself
why are you so mean
the ground slams yeah they hurt
especially when he does them so close to
me because like then the wave comes like
right into my face
go try go next yes go next
there was a hiccup in the Stream really
then you didn't see how I just won on
now
I won but you didn't see it so I'm
retrying
because I want you to see it he's
standing on my dead body how
disrespectful
you little [\h__\h]
a little [\h__\h] Dancing on My Grave
literally
[Music]
but that was the perfect
oh
thank you
didn't break his point this time a
little gun normally
I feel like it breaks
toys
that wasn't early death
that was too early I still had so many
potions
it's too aggressive
oh I feel like I'm in I'm an eternal
Loop
hey
sounds familiar
3-0
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah
yeah that's what it is that's what it is
I like being
I liked I liked the explosion in the
beginning last time
oh
you know
it wouldn't even be too bad like if I
couldn't do it today
there's more tunic so enjoy
[Music]
riding his balls
I hate you for doing that
oh
no okay he's just being super mean and
then from
[Music]
he's so mean
do you see this camping how how can you
let him treat me like this
[Music]
did you see he also just wanted to use
it
at least I'm using my Shields
time
oh
all right we're so close again I'm gonna
[\h__\h] it up again though
it's like I don't want to win
[Music]
don't go
up
not even deserved that was a terrible
fight I wanted to do better
oh
[\h__\h] you so much [\h__\h] you I hate you you
suck you [\h__\h] bastard everybody hates
you one million feelings on YouTube hate
you love you subscribers
hate you you suck I wish I could stab
your eyes and everything when you
actually
you look like you have a like boobies
maybe you're
a woman
sorry about that but yeah anyway you
suck [\h__\h] you suck I hate you
you made my day miserable
and I feel embarrassed for doing so
badly and I could do so much better
oh
you embarrassed me in front of my people
I won't forget that I'll take your head
and I'll rip out your arms
when why is it zooming in
I'm not doing anything
I've never seen the game zoom in like
that before
I swear to God I didn't do anything
um
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
you I'm so mad and that wasn't even a
good fight I wanna do it again
terrible
all of that was terrible in my head I
could have done all of that so much
better
now I don't even deserve it I don't
deserve
it but okay
is that the third one for yellow three
now here comes a Twist right because you
would think oh afraid of free you're
complete yeah yeah but no that's usually
you know when you have everything
that's that's what the second half of
the game ends but why are you still here
the other enemies disappeared didn't
they is this a glitch
is she supposed to disappear
because we're just leaving her like
alive standing here I don't like that
Second Face the moment I walk away
second phase
and this leaves me so dissatisfied to be
honest if I don't see her body fall
apart in a million pieces
kneeling them menacingly doesn't even
look that menacingly no doesn't at least
if the if the light in their eyes would
go out
the way it's still Shining
makes me think it's alive but it's not
breathing
it's not moving
weird
ah librarian didn't disappear really
I felt like that was more more
satisfying maybe just because I did it
so easily
ah
okay wait so I'm supposed to go in here
now
or maybe yes maybe they want me to leave
now but I feel like I kind of missed
some paths you know and that triggers me
so hard
I want to go back
I definitely missed stuff but the
question is was it important stuff or
was it not
there's a chest back the way I came no
how is it far
enemy should be gone you mean like
you mean like generally enemies are gone
because I took that stone or whatever
no no now it feels like you're making
fun of me by saying that today I don't
deserve it last time I played tunic when
you said that I felt like it was genuine
but today it's not genuine
oh man
um
wait those mobs are still there
I'm already taking a
where's the mask
is this
[Music]
no I'm fine
oh
why did you say enemies are gone they
are very much here
[Music]
wait why don't you turn around
[\h__\h] them
I hate them so much I should use my my
fire again
uh where is that chest
I don't remember seeing one
[Music]
um
maybe here
this one
yes yes it was this way
[Music]
will you let me go or what what
can you go [\h__\h] yourself please
[Music]
um
let me go
don't cook the metal sound makes it
sound like my head is made out of metal
oh wait that reflects
not you I hate you
[Music]
I'm not worth my time
okay we're just gonna run back right I
got everything
I have everything right
okay okay well I mean I wouldn't quite
say that the diamond Dynamite was worth
it because I'm never gonna use it anyway
so we didn't have to
go all the way here
did I check out what's on that side oh
can I even
um
because when I went all the way to the
left side I felt like there wasn't a way
down but maybe I just didn't see it did
I ever check it out
foreign
[Music]
about I don't know you know Nami Mama
she's really thin but there's this thing
about girls
um I think every every girl I met in
Japan and in Korea they're also
self-conscious man she was so worried
about you know look like as if her tummy
would look too big in the skirt I'm like
no Nabi mama you look super flat I mean
if that's what you want to look like
you're fine you're fine nothing mama
don't worry about it so so
self-conscious man
um but finally eventually we we got a
good combo of uh outfit but actually
because we came so late there were a lot
of things already taken a lot of sizes
were taken taken and a lot of ties and
ribbons were already taken so
um it wasn't ideal but no we got
something matching and then the first
thing she wanted to do was take some
pictures because they have some photo
spots some special photo spots so before
riding any attractions we went straight
to the photo spots
um
we took like one in front of uh
a merry-go-round that's what you call it
where should we go
where do we even go
up
is there something here now no hi Mommy
hi
sorry Mommy
Temple
what Temple which Temple the big one
with the big golden door
uh what's the shortest platform
the closest platform
the golden door okay
oh
the middle right
this one
okay thank you
yeah Carousel may we go around
oh
are you having fun
okay so yeah yeah we took a picture oh
but you know like ah there were so many
couples around like literally I would
say 70 percent
nah maybe 60 but
or like 50 50 couples and Families
it's hard to say
but there were a lot of couples who did
like a pose where the the guy would lift
up the girl with his arms locked um
around like right under her butt can you
imagine
um
can you imagine what I'm describing it's
such a cute pose and then Navi and me we
looked at each other what post should we
do can we do that I guess not I don't
think I can lift you Nabi Mama Tried to
lift me for a second I was like no
yeah but that was very some cute couples
they took cute pictures everybody's so
cute and there were a lot of a lot of
other people who were doing the the
couple look
the matching look
uh
[Music]
so it took some some pictures there
there's like a professional photographer
that takes it for you there
and then
um
and then we went to different photo spot
where was that
ah not a photo spot but then we went to
the photo booth they had one of those
purikura Korean purikuras
in there as well but they were really
strict like even inside uh the the
purikuda booth even there when you're
just U2 you have to wear a mask I'm not
sure if they check really but you have
to everybody wears a mask so on all the
photo everybody's just wearing a mask in
general everybody in love the world
because it was indoors everybody was
wearing a mask and you have to
you have to they were really strict
about that
um
and you know I was hoping since it's
indoors I was hoping for it to maybe be
a little bit air-conditioned but I don't
think it was really if it was then
pretty unnoticeable
oh yeah I put I put the stones in now
yeah yeah okay
number one
oh
yeah yeah well at least everybody was
falling in the rules you know I think it
was really nice to see everybody taking
it so seriously but even outside like I
couldn't wear the mask much outside
because it was so humid I was sweating
on my face you know and I saw all the
all the Korean people they all were
wearing masks even outside I'm like damn
respect how are you guys doing this
respect man
I I would I would do it if it wasn't in
the middle of a super humid hot summer
you know
in winter time fall spring I don't care
I'll gladly wear it even outside
I actually like wearing it when I
um don't wear makeup so I can hide my
face
hmm
well yeah yeah but it's nice to see a
country like really respecting the rules
so
um this disciplined
it's pretty normal probably to wear a
mask in general just like in Japan
yeah
probably mean that Santa mask
oh so what's gonna happen we put all
three of them in and this looks like a
like a R20 dice R20
what do you call them
like those those dice and final part
what now
do I hear something opening yeah
D20 yeah okay that's exactly what I was
thinking game you can read my mind
literally the chief and says what now
question mark
de Nani to you
achievement calculator
okay I guess I just go outside
um maybe maybe outside I'll find out
what to do now
what did that even do
mommy maybe I have to go check mommy in
the uh on the world
uh yeah I have to go to a portal then
right
maybe I mean I could be totally wrong
foreign
because I feel like maybe her prison was
opened the where she was
held captured
wow wait
I only got two of them
okay so we uh we took those pictures we
had to stand in line for a little bit at
the photo booth
um but now we took some cute pictures uh
and um then I was like Navi Mama which
probably
um locked into the locker because there
was a locker
um where we put our bags so we were just
running around with our phones basically
didn't want to carry the bag all the
time
and then after we took the pictures I
was like okay let's go let's do some
stuff let's do some attractions before
this closes by the way so it was gonna
be open until
uh at 10 they were starting to close I
think they were like the attractions
stopped and they were everybody was
leaving around nine to ten I guess she's
gone wait she's gone but I can't go any
further
why not
I went here and I see she's gone so
again what now
order
[Music]
in I
the giant sword
where's that
I wish that sword on it
real portal where did that lead
ah
when we first came here there was
nothing here I think
oh the sword was here the sword was here
never mind
so I'll just calling mommy's here Mommy
Mommy
ah there it is
we're like it's finally more reaching
summer reach you [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
these [\h__\h] uses the same weapons as me
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you
you're not my mom
also I had like not my usual health and
all that
I think I was supposed to die
yeah I mean look at the scene
could you have one maybe but I think uh
the game knows you're gonna die
that was not my mom no
yeah I'm like in in like you know that
reminds me of um Skyward Sword you know
the world where you're like a ghost and
you also don't have your weapons and
[\h__\h] I mean I do have my weapons but
still I'm weaker than usual
but I saw those ghosts in the world
right now in the Overworld
okay
I'm a ghost
and we start from zero it seems yeah we
start from where we began the game
and uh we're weak as hell but we do have
our magic weapons
right
Maybe
do I still have all the portals
oh yeah right this one is cut off
but this also looks so
different a little bit like the the
surroundings look more
corrupted
um so we put our stuff into the locker
the the pictures they'll turned out
really cute and
um then we were gonna go to an
attraction the closest one was like not
such a special one it was just like one
of those attractions where you sit down
uh it moves a little bit it's like a
movie theater and you shoot you have
like a gun and you shoot some stuff in
the movie hello
great I understand perfectly
swamp
and tell me to not disturb your swamp
Maybe
and speak English to me
get out of my swamp
oh chest is opened
so we went into that shooting Cinema
[Music]
and
it would show you the ranking sometimes
and even though I felt like I was doing
pretty bad because the the gun was the
like the
the trigger felt like I don't know it
was kind of hard to use it
where is the swamp I forgot where the
swamp is
um
in the first ranking they show you two
rankings in the beginning and then
sometime uh at the end sometime in the
beginning sometime in the end and uh
what was that
and in the first ranking I was number
two
and Nabi mama was second from last or
last I think maybe even I know I think
she was second from last
and then in the last ranking I think I
was um oh fourth maybe or so
maybe what no first time was second and
then third or something like that was
pretty up high you know surprisingly and
Nami Mama the last ranking she was also
second from last or so or third I think
she got a little bit better around the
end third from last or so
yeah sorry I was doing pretty well
Cathedral ghost
to go to the cathedral
wait we can now go over the path
that was not possible possible before
was it oh no
what was it
well can I now reach all the things that
I couldn't reach before once again
can I walk over there to get paper
please
let me fly
that's new right
oh hi guys
Cathedral moonlight
Cathedral ghost Cathedral Moonlight
swamp
big fight
huh
uh great thank you
I thought I could swim suddenly but no
okay so we did that and that took maybe
I don't know including waiting in line a
little bit
um
50 minutes already maybe even an hour
and you must consider we were already
late at this point after taking the
pictures and then
going to the first attraction
I was already like
past 6 p.m almost 7 P.M
and I was like yummy we can barely do
anything oh man so we quickly wanted to
go to the next attraction whatever we
didn't have like anything specific in
mind but why we were while we were
running to the next attraction they were
starting the parade there was a parade
going on or about to start so people
were like sitting on the ground in a lot
of places
uh and we were just trying to find any
attraction to be honest there were even
like some hot balloons up at the very
high ceiling but not real hot balls they
were like you know going through like
some kind of
how to say
ceiling
tram I wanted to go up there but I never
found out how to get up there
um oh wait I wanna see that
can I go from there
so then we were just like running around
randomly trying to find really anything
really because anything would have been
fine here we go
and then we
coincidentally accidentally found the
entrance to the line for the most
popular attraction
I would say it's probably the most
um
am I on the map
okay this is the cathedral I'm not on
here but uh
the swamp
what's up okay yeah we are in the swamp
in my Coco
no
and we can go to the cathedral here
hello
okay cool
maybe the cathedral we will be revived
no should you find our dead body
uh so that was something I saw like
people using it when we were running
around it was like oh kind of want to
try this one too it's one of those
roller coasters where you go through
water and then at the very end you go
through
part what that makes you pretty wet
because it's the water goes like Swoosh
you go right through it you know so it
makes you a little bit a little bit
drenched with one of those attractions
no
so
we found that accidentally and it was
right when the parade whoa
stuck oh they're pretty strong
I mean they have a picture
oh they have a lot of uh HP but they
don't do much damage which is that's how
it should be because they took all my HP
ah I feel what could that be a sword and
a necklace
more attack
or
I don't know what changed
you know
is that the last one I know I have one
more left
Maybe
looks like a gem
oh I guess so
they don't have any Poise oh cool
it's not they have a lot of HP
oh oh
really
what is this
I it ice magic necklace
what
it's fun well then what does it feel
maybe it gives me more free did I have
free before or maybe it's bigger I don't
know
mix your ice magic faster to use oh I
wonder if that's useful in here and
that's why they give it to me
um
you you have to be able to learn how to
jump
no way they're not gonna teach me that
where does that lead oh
really scary I'm not ready for Dad
so we I think we started lining up and
like
I don't know when does the parade start
is probably actually an official time
that would um help me
back up my story I don't know
um
probably already past 7 pm
the good thing is while we started
lining up ooh we could watch the parade
actually we it was right where
um all of the parade was like coming out
of
like where that door is is where we
started lining up pretty much so
it's actually pretty well I took some
videos too it was quite interesting like
compared to Disneyland parades
um
it's like Disneyland compared to lots of
world Disneyland feels way more tacky
and like childish
weekend question mark oh is that a shop
that's a shop
remember me
I got so much stuff
hmm
coins
I forgot
those were again that was that just the
money for myself
no I don't know what to buy I guess
maybe in this portion how much
just need a bit more money
got for the whale oh yeah
[Music]
is this are those bombs I haven't seen
them in a while
yeah how much are these 999.
you little [\h__\h] I'm out of here
oh there's a well looks I I saw it but I
I've totally forgot about being able to
use those like that
aha let me show you this one and he has
the remaining tool I got one he has two
but 999 that might take me a while
to make actual use of it
okay
yes and so the the parade I thought that
um
the hmm like they made some really
really big uh what do you call those
things that they roll around on
not sure what to call them but they
looked very original and interesting and
um
I don't know they looked so creative
floats I guess
floats
oh I can't go all the way up no I can
so it was really cool to see like a
difference in style because when I first
went in I thought this was just like
basically a off-brand uh
-huh off of brand Disneyland but no no
no no no
they even had like an ice rink and stuff
so it was it was pretty different it has
a lot of things that uh
the Disneyland doesn't have to offer and
I guess it's probably also cheaper I
don't know I didn't really compare
prices but I would assume it's cheaper
why is this one a different color
foreign
I can't hit it but I can move it around
what is this
where am I
aha
why is there um
what is that supposed to mean am I gonna
die four times here without a four four
dangerous enemies down there
oh
how can I die with
him
makes no sense
okay that's okay
I healed too late
that's not that far
I want to check here too to be honest
nothing can hide from me oh
I found a secret path I don't know where
I am
where the [\h__\h] am I do that yay
okay now I really have a lot of dynamite
I might as well use it huh
no
no I will not you cannot make me
24.
24 pieces of dynamite
where was I oh yeah the the floats were
cool the ladies the the actors
they were mostly like foreigners
like
beautiful beautiful foreigners looking
like models
barely any
like Asian looking faces but I think
they do the same in Disneyland's uh
Tokyo
use a lot of foreigners I think
especially for the princesses princesses
but this was just for like the random
dancers
no
maybe if I ever move to Korea this is
this could be a job for me
holy [\h__\h] one of them has a huge sword
yummy and a shield across Shield
yep leave me alone
[Music]
oh I think that did uh why did I not
make use of that I think
I think I did use uh less time to charge
[\h__\h] yeah
okay
humble as ever
what what did I say
what was that sounds ironic
what they say that was not humble
now honestly the the princess said I I
wasn't saying that I could be a Princess
at Disneyland or whatever
I'm saying I could be one of those like
side dancers or what was that
what what is that what is that
oh
is that supposed
look at that
oh that's what they mean with maybe
um how do I say it
away please
[Music]
hit it
well let's come down here probably not I
kind of want to refresh but then I have
to kill a [\h__\h] skeleton again [\h__\h]
this for now
I'll go up first blah blah blah
maybe maybe it will teach me how to see
them
somewhere oh there's one here too oh
okay I'll just hit whatever uh where is
this
[Music]
what how am I supposed
no where they are
London
hey
did that hit it
oh it's in the water
ah I can see it steps in the water
oh there's another one
once you hit them once you can at least
see them that's good
oh [\h__\h] you
oh holy macaroni that sounds so
nice man that's I mean it's pretty
original I like it I like the idea
I like it
as long as I talking about
okay so we were watching the parade but
hmm
the since the attraction we were lining
up for was so popular
we were waiting in line for quite some
time
and
at some point we were starting to worry
if we can give back the school uniform
in time
um if I remember correctly I think the
school uniform place oh wanted uh wanted
us to return it
uh at like
9pm
and we were still standing in line but
that's Happy
okay that's too many that's just
that's just
yeah that we're free you can't see them
yeah bye
like around like half an hour before 9
00 PM I think we called the store
because it still looked like we had a
little long way to go so we called them
and we were like sorry we're probably
[Music]
ah
We're not gonna make it
I got it
oh another one
it's so not fair
what the [\h__\h] is
this holy [\h__\h]
I I I I I
I I'm
I'm I'm shocked
I'm I'm
shocked by the difficulty at the moment
wow now this is where the game gets
actually difficult
still has some surprises to offer holy
[\h__\h] my elephant
man apparently heals
just gonna activate this now
um
wow it did Spike yeah wow hmm
so I was saying yeah yeah
[Music]
we actually returned it late because
we were like standing in line for I
think a total of I think two hours
and once we got like pretty close that's
also when the store was closing and we
were like where was we were standing in
line for almost two hours we're it's
almost our turn leaving the line now to
return the school uniform would be such
a waste so Navi mama called them and was
like sorry uh I'm sorry please forgive
uh
it's forgive we will return as soon as
possible and they were like yeah just be
there as fast as possible please
they were um Navi mama said that like
while we were in the changing room the
ladies that were working there they kind
of gave like a piano kind of
um
impression like they kind of had an
attitude they were like chit-chatting
like high schoolers
uh I don't know they seemed like they
could be a little bit of a mean girl
type of lady you know what I mean
so on the phone too Nabi mama was a
little bit intimidated uh
yeah but I mean we were late and I'm
sorry for that but in the end after the
attraction when we when we we literally
we ran there and they were oh hi they
were playing they were playing dancing
either way from twice so while we were
running I was like dancing it was
actually fun
um
so we ran as fast as possible and and
and and they were still the store was
still open we were like 15 minutes late
still was still open and people were
still returning
uh school uniforms and yeah I think this
is like it happens to them a lot
probably
so not such a big deal but I'm sorry for
keeping them waiting gumina sorry
I kinda wanna
kill but uh
there's only one Statue and then I have
to go for all of those ghosts again
oh
give me give me
give me I see it right there
ah where's the path something's there
something is there
what about this way oh oh I can arrange
this chest interesting
hey I opened that one do you think so
did I really
I don't think I came here before
wait did we just get another coin
don't have to buy it well I mean in the
end maybe we're gonna buy it anyways for
completion's sake but uh
we'll see
did we strike all the enemies
oh
so anyway for the attraction
I was kind of nervous about it because I
I like roller coasters but oh I'm also
really bad at them
another another coin
[\h__\h] come at me oh you're not gonna come
okay
that's better for me
I'm really bad at roller coasters but it
didn't have a loop
so as long as it doesn't have a loop I'm
I am okay
I've done maybe one or two roller
coasters in my life that have a loop
and even without a little I
I don't know I'm I'm so bad at handling
them
I'm really bad at it
[Music]
but I wanted I was actually the one who
said I wanted to do that one when I saw
it I was like I look like so much fun
to it
was the one
it's your friend you should hit your
friends
the time
you do it
no no
it happens
I haven't been on a roller coaster in a
long time
huh isn't life just a roller coaster
already
[Applause]
no leave me alone
[Music]
no no no no no
no no no I don't care I'm gonna go
straight to the graveyard and I just
visited
[Music]
I see you I see I mean I don't really
see you but you're right there
and that's how you [\h__\h] up
well
it could be like that sometimes never
pop is it weakness yeah then I easily
know where they are
[Music]
nice nice touch nice roll
so so it was basically a boat like a
four-seater and uh it went like up
and it was I think two times that we
went up and two tabs where it was like
really really fast going down
it was terrifying I I thought I was
gonna die I was screaming really loud I
I honestly
I was so scared that I don't remember at
all how Nabi Mama reacted
so unfortunately
I can't share
any
stories of how she
dealt with it yeah but
I think she enjoyed it
I thought she I don't think she was as
terrified as I was can you stop
foreign
[Laughter]
are we really gonna finish this today
how much do I have left of this game
it's been four and a half hours
I'm getting worried
make something up nah I'm not gonna make
gonna make no I always tell you guys the
truth always telling you guys true
stories
only the cathedral
oh yeah
a lot a bit
a lot
uh
two hours three hours and
I mean that's fine
I'll I'll just won't be cooking again
today
good that I bought some frozen pizza
I don't want to waste my hello fresh
food I hope I can still cook it like
tomorrow
we'll have to do a short stream tomorrow
a relatively short one
I should stop focusing
[Music]
I hate you
[Applause]
[Music]
want to finish this game today
said I'll finish it so I'm gonna finish
it
but it's been
ignored no but then I can't look
carefully for secrets and [\h__\h] if I
continuously have to run away and you
know there's a lot there's a lot hidden
everywhere
we can't just run and run and run
I'll miss all all the good stuff that's
why I'm trying to do everything
carefully
peace
I want to die again here
no don't block me
thank you
[Music]
I can literally not get past this point
don't
gonna go somewhere else
wonderful here
I'm starting to look forward to annoying
though
maybe I should do partial
but now we pour it to
monkey monkey hi
hey are you here to cheer me up
hi baby
she's just standing there come here
what are you coming for
you know what I did to my room to my
office
I put up honey
[Music]
I put up um those curtains that they had
at Annapolis that the the merchandise
they gave me there's like these curtains
right I put them uh on the door to my
office
it's really cute
it's really cute I found a good use for
it because it makes sense in my office
it's on topic on theme
she's she's on the floor she looks like
a bread she looks like a loaf
oh not anymore now she's scratching the
tree you're not in love anymore you gave
up on low flies I will catch you now
wants to play catch
I'm back with the cat I did catch her
now she's purring
I mean she always pursed the moment I
touched her look at her
yeah
cat chasing time
oh and I'm squeezing and massaging her
paws
[Music]
that's it
skip no Escape
we hear some poor
dry wait a second
nowhere to walk
I don't want to speak into the Minecraft
oh no Mommy
question
she's something
shy now she's like no Mommy I don't want
to be on your stupid stream
um
sorry microphone so
[Music]
ah it's so sensitive sorry
no don't go don't call baby
[Music]
yes
you let me go
no I need your mental support right now
chunky monkey
I need it I love you I love you
but I love you though but I love you
[Music]
well thanks for the red super chat yeah
what
I was holding a spare no way
you're saying that you were one of the
guards
are you joking you're just joking
you're kidding right
I'm not gonna lie
um some there were some uh record
recognition moments
during my trip
not many but there were some
uh but I don't believe you
I don't believe you but I mean even if
it was you then you were doing your job
and you you wouldn't definitely wouldn't
have been able to just go like
I'm your fan please can I can I have
your signature or something because
you're supposed to guard the palace
right
so I believe that
oh wait there's no way of going up there
ah I have to go from above
this is just a preview
oh man okay
so wait do I have to
do I have to go for the
that part that I hate so much yeah yeah
because it's connected oh [\h__\h] hell
ah why do I have so many troubles with
those enemies
I mean until then I'm already like
taking so many fights and that's a
problem too
I crouch um here again
back for the ground yeah yeah
let's talk again oh
oh
my God
you wanna fight me and fight me here
how
where's the other one
another one
let's just disappeared oh I didn't kill
it there was definitely another one oh
well okay
okay okay okay okay
so that's what we did that attraction
and now we had to run for our life
to return
the school uniform at a decent time
go [\h__\h] yourself
and so that was basically it so we
really didn't do much but we returned it
and
um then we changed into a normal close
and we could still uh enjoy the the the
um a lot of world a little bit longer
because actually like it uh the school
uniform was like you had to return it at
9pm I think but then the park was still
running a little bit longer until like
10 P.M
so we went back in but and there was no
time for another attraction and like
most of them seemed closed at that point
so what we did then was
um
uh
I think the only thing that we really
did
was
uh
uh checking out the outside because it's
not only indoor it actually
does have
an outdoor space
follow your [\h__\h] Hallelujah yeah and
they actually have also like a huge
castle
it's a wild Castle
um a castle is lit up and also they have
fireworks at least like we were inside
when we heard some fireworks but it was
only two I think they let go two tidy
fireworks we kind of saw some sparkles
and heard the really loud bang sound but
I don't know if that was fake
or if it was really happening but then
outside they did have um the the castle
lit up and they had also inside they had
some light shows going on after 9 pm
so yeah it goes on pretty long
[Music]
wasted uh would you mind coming
come on here
what [\h__\h]
[Music]
they
take your HP
wow
[Applause]
which means I have to fight those
[\h__\h] skeletons again
I'm not feeling it
I can make a wish
hi
[Music]
wait ah
what uh I had a new spot I I
sneak by them oh
I guess I yeah probably could do that
um I'm gonna take this
leave my defense back
okay I'll try that we fought them enough
times
I'll run through I'll fight the [\h__\h]
ghost [\h__\h]
in the narrow pathway
and then we'll sneak by uh
we'll sneak by the skeletons Hopkins
wow I got it right when she was
attacking me
okay
we dealt with it
ah because of the coin okay nice nice
nice nice nice nice nice
oh oh yeah you you so are you here I
forgot about you
you notice that the game is triggering
me a little bit
maybe on the right side is safer yeah
yeah
oh but my my ghost is there all right
bye-bye it's just it's just 20 cheese
cubes was it
I'm abandoning it my soul it looks just
like me right now
ghost reception
okay now the curls
you can get it and run no but then
they're gonna follow me and I'm I don't
[\h__\h] care for that for 22 skills
don't need it
what am I gonna do about these though
um
[Music]
okay I think
I need to end this today I need to end
it
I think I need no I don't wanna I don't
wanna I don't wanna I don't wanna I
don't wanna
I don't want to I don't want uh
we could sneak by the verbs even
probably yeah
okay sneak by everything
that's what I'm gonna try to do now
now we'll go around let's go foxy
wait my nose is itchy
okay I got stuck in favorite place okay
this time I'm not gonna get stuck
I know it
uh okay okay not the world sorry and at
the end we took some pictures and now
you might want took some pictures of me
we also got a another couple to take
some pictures of us in front of the big
big castle
and then we went back in and Nami mama
still wanted to show me some more stuff
outside but it seems like everything was
already like over oh my God how did it
get me
sorry I can't get it they're too close
[Applause]
run run run run
normally not such a cow coward but oh
[\h__\h] I'm kind of stuck here now because
I have to pray yeah this is not an
option it's not an option I have to
fight so they have to sit down here and
[\h__\h] parade
I don't know
actually
I saw another path but I don't think
that was um
a path that would have saved me
if anything it was probably a dead end
sneak past that goes how can I sneak
past them when I don't know where they
are
you think they won't see me they go for
the water
but the ghosts aren't even the biggest
see the ghosts aren't even the biggest
problem
kind of the skeletons and those [\h__\h]
Birds
stealth card
uh
uh-huh let's see I mean
it's not only
wait the stealth card works well if you
like sneaking behind someone you
actually see what you're sneaking behind
too but with the ghost it could be like
sneaking right in into them and then
they'll see me they might not hear me
but they'll see me
um
say there aren't any on the in the water
on the right side
so far so good
looking obnoxious man
I like the game better when I was good
at it
had life
um oh [\h__\h] I forgot about you
[Music]
I hate you
oh wait the story's not even over after
a lot the world
um so we left around like
uh 10 I guess
and then we were like okay well is this
goodbye it's really late but I guess we
didn't eat dinner so now my mama's like
do you want to eat dinner what do you
want to do
and then I was like you know what we
kind of failed to do last time
we didn't get that ramyon by the river
we could do that now because then it
doesn't matter you know we don't need a
restaurant because the restaurants are
mostly close to then
and I kind of wanted to do that you
wanted to do that
so wouldn't that be perfect just now
oh we found a spot that was
good to reach with a taxi from uh
a lot of world we took a taxi to the
to a good River spot and there was a
convenience store there and you buy your
Ramen ingredients there so I got like a
this one is probably not so spicy you
can probably eat that she says
well
yeah it was in the end it was a little
bit spicy
nonetheless
but I tried my best while my nose was
running and my eyes were tearing I tried
my best to eat it I put in some cheese
too and an egg a raw egg that kind of
with the hot water it turned into a
fried egg boiled boiled fried egg
oh
and we used those machines like outside
of the convenience store I think I guess
they don't have that at every
convenience store in Korea but they have
it by the by the river
so in this case they had these machines
out there when you cook the ramen
can I speak by or do I have to fight you
I'm gonna try to sneak
so I was like let me almost show me how
to do it but turns out
I think it was her first time doing it I
think she said even first time or second
time almost probably the first time
um so she wasn't quite sure about how to
use it herself either but I was watching
her figuring it out and then I did my
own
and then we sat down and then I used
this trick that Nabi mama told me about
oh
like when we were at the river the other
day we were looking at all those other
people and uh some of them were using
like a bottle of water on top of their
phones
um flashlight Torchlight
and it lights up
like a lamp it's so genius I was like oh
Navi mama that's so genius and she was
like yeah young people nowadays like
doing that
I'm like oh my God I will remember that
maybe that will come in handy one day
when I need
a good light in the dark outside I used
to do that really
I've never seen anyone do that ever
before
please don't shoot me oh
oh it's a ladder I thought it was going
to shoot me a shortcut though ah it's
behind the shop
oh that's good that's really good
should I I might as well
I'm mine as well oh I have a thousand
coins I can buy the
the heart the flask
[Music]
give me something good please I'm gonna
buy the flask now
why the hell not do it
then at least I can't really use too
much money whoa
whoa looks I have all those potions baby
you can simply put a bottle on your yeah
that's what we did though what do you
mean isn't that what we did what I what
I was talking about
yeah
and it has such a nice
soft bright soft but bright light you
should try it guys I think the bigger
the bottle the better the bigger the
bottle the better it's like a tongue
twister
um
hmm
so since there were no other lights
there were like benches and stuff but
there were no lights so we had to make
our own light and we used it and then
and then we ate the ramen
and it was really nice because I was
looking at the
I was looking at the scenery
the river
the city on the other side
and even though it's like not a five
star four course dinner or whatever I
thought this was the perfect way to end
the day to end the trip even
it was a perfect day like okay we we had
some troubles finding the hot dogs and
all that but I don't know the whole day
was so perfect we we had nice lunch
even though we couldn't find the topoki
the right one but we still had a nice
lunch and then we went shopping a little
bit
we ate some street food we chilled in
the hotel a little bit to cool down then
we went to a lot of lots of world we we
ran around
had like too much we used two
attractions at least good enough took
some cute memory pictures
we were late to return our school
uniforms that we dressed up in and then
late at night at the river close to
midnight we ate
some instant Ramen self-made instant
ramen in the dark next to a simple
self-made phone light
ah
but then I was getting sad I was like oh
man now I have to leave
it's so sad and then we after we ate
Namibia was actually shocked today ate
so much she was like wow you did a good
job
three
yeah I tried my best it was yummy hmm
and then we took a taxi to my hotel
nappy Mama joined me because
uh she was just gonna go with the same
taxi straight to her home
we asked her to get out of the taxi for
a moment to give me a hug
and then and then and then I gave her a
hug and I said thank you not be mom over
guiding me and thinking so much about
what to do and I must have been
um like it must have been annoying to
like choose fitting Foods in a country
where everything's spicy when you try
your best to find stuff that I can eat
[Music]
um
and and you spend so much time with me
although you're probably also busy thank
you so much and I think I really made a
friend
here
um
I really think like
we got so close and I wouldn't have
expected it she's just she's Amelia's
artist Mommy
I never would have expected to hang out
with someone like that for so long
and she was you know she was just a
normal girl during those days she was
just a normal girl to me who
was you know
just a normal girl with normal
normal everything just normal girl cute
very cute though but no more girl normal
human
and told me some secrets and intimate
stories too yeah
I feel like
I I hope I'm not imagining this but I I
think we had a good time and we got
along really well and I'm looking
forward to showing her Austria and maybe
some other countries in Europe and
returning the favor
yeah then she went back into the taxi
and I waved until it left
cried a little bit
I'm just kind of sad
because I feel like we're really made a
connection
um
[Music]
I really enjoyed being with her and she
put so much effort into
planning everything
hi Mommy
sorry Mommy
oh
oh I wish it was really nice the last
day I think just
ended it so nicely
oh what the [\h__\h] we have a cult
situation going on again looks very
familiar to yesterday
did we switch games again
uh those are wait they look like me
let me look at the map wrong cult
or is it is it though
now I wonder if I stop now and continue
tomorrow how long do you think my stream
would be tomorrow
what was I planning to is today Saturday
oh I was
possibly rust tomorrow but I guess I can
also play Rust on Monday or I can walk
and play tunic on Monday I don't know
whatever
two to three
four nah probably if anything probably
three hours
this is enough for a part at least hmm
[Music]
true ending I don't know about that if
that's even possible for me at this
point
because isn't that only possible if you
find every secret and
I was very very very
um
good at finding secrets in this
playthrough but I
surely missed a few
and backtracking
I don't know ah just all the manual
pages oh
I don't I don't know I I'll see and I'll
go with the flow if I feel like doing
that but
[Music]
um
very difficult to get without a guide
well you know these kind of things you
can just look up on YouTube and
see what how the cutscene looks like
in that case don't have to do it
yourself just go on YouTube
the last bed You'll Play if you're curly
with no fuku oh
oh man
I really wanted to finish today and I
mean it's not impossible but
maybe better to split it
um
[Music]
there's so many games I want to play
right now I want to play Cult of the
lamp too but if I if I split it then
what am I gonna play tomorrow
[Music]
we have fun continuing today
I feel like you know with that boss
fight I've already been triggered too
hard
so far
a break would be nice indeed
um
yeah
I know I said Rush tomorrow which is
probably what I am going to do
um
I have to cook dinner too
can you cook for me too please
I'm
too lazy
cannot start later than usual yeah
possibly possibly hello
foreign
says wearing this allows you to do
something extraordinary
what is that
very curious what
ah wish you could feed me
I wish
uh
I'll check what the expiration date on
my meat is
if it's today then I guess I'm forced to
cook that
if not then I'll eat a pizza
yeah and then tomorrow I think I'm not
gonna put up the reservation until
tomorrow I'm like too lazy to put it up
now uh
I I could either
start rust early and most likely run
into some Japanese members but probably
be like alone on my own
or I could start like really late
late as in I don't know 7 P.M
and hope that AME is awake
to or will wake up for it
as she offered
to hang out with me and help me in the
beginning
she did say that she would help me you
know
when I say early I mean my usual
streaming time where Japanese members
are also online like like the time I
started today minus one hour I don't
mean super super early like an unusual
streaming time I still mean I mean my
early streaming slot
um
hmm
and all of them say they'd help I don't
know who you mean with all of them but
Ahmed was the one who really seemed like
she wanted to do it crony hasn't even
started playing it how would she help
but Emma seemed open to do it
she said she wouldn't stream but she
would be there
yeah I think I'm gonna ask her and then
put up the reservation afterwards okay
guys
um I really think I'm
sick of streaming for today
so is it okay if I read super chance
another time
peace
[Music]
generally
today also not getting much sleep and
then
[\h__\h] boss fights
triggering me too hard
um
thank you so much I hope you enjoyed the
story of my last day with Navi Mama it
was a wonderful day it was a beautiful
day yeah
a great last day to make memories
[Music]
um
good storytelling
hmm
at the early time of 5 20th
yeah you can sleep early let's walk
thanks for the stream while I enjoy your
food thank you
it's fun listening to your time spent
with Navi Sensei yeah thank you
it was it was a nice nice trip really I
I was really sad about leaving
um it felt like one or two days extra
would have been nice
but
I shall come back and make some more
memories I have a little bit more to
tell you about
my departure
but I'll keep that for next time
it's not that much though
just one thing in particular
waiting to use the whole life coffee
oh thank you for working hard to solve
to travel so The Crew That's So popcorn
even if thanks and love you yeah when I
see like
uh organizational problems like that
going on behind the scenes not really
behind the scenes but like publicly for
the viewers and all that no matter just
not only popcorn but in other situations
too I I can't just let it go when when
it's like something that kfp is having
trouble with then I want to help so I
immediately bring it up to the
management and I'm like can we do
something about this please
um and back is this is this being taken
care of is this happening is this okay
is this daijuable like with my birthday
merchandise tool
um
like after the release I don't know geek
Jack stuff
I think other people just
probably uh don't even see these kind of
things or ignore them
but
yeah I'm too worried I want things to go
well for you guys I want you guys to
have a good experience
especially if it's things like that
where you do spend money on it I want
your experience to be good and if
there's anything I can do to
help out with that
yeah then
I do my best to
do my part
now I am very mentally exhausted so
excuse me if I go
there
[Music]
tomorrow probably first time ever rest
or tunic part two
we'll see maybe maybe I can even decide
after eating some food
thank you guys for watching today and in
June we say I'll freeze
thank you very much for watching today
the not finale of tunic the playthrough
yeah
it's not the end the end is never the
end it's never the end it's never the
end
more tunic for me
actually not a bad thing
um
I'm done with the funny yeah I'm done
with the funny
um
thank you thank you
bye bye bye bye good night good night
[Music]
I
think
foreign
[Music]