[Music]
[Music]
me
n
[Music]
N n
def n
n
me me n n eeeeeeeeeeeeee
[Music] It
was
[Music]
Men
N
[Music]
Ben
N
Hmm,
this kind of revision pain
Idol live tour is a folder
Dochipukuhotakke was in the Ukeido way
Dondoko Midna Minkutasa
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you are watching.
gm Mikan's super orgasm I'm
going to say good morning Good evening aet
fu ah postal election campaign 9
yeah I'm going to paint one stage in Spain
still you a It's a
lot over here n boy Ho
Park throat nonno
andere f 4
regclean
menus  King
sentiment predater zo
tarp 4 apbs
per worker bad
fore chonso see
ren dada pupu sa
areas all
rear derailleur
indore This
is actually the second time the leaders have been giving zorb talk.  I
talked to Pururusa-san a while ago.
Yes, I had a very deep and deep conversation with Tomizawa-san once.
If you're interested, please come
by. It was before the release. What's the worst 4? s
Yeah, yeah,
when is 9?  It's a proper cemetery day
center shop pottery.
N'ase monopoly walker mean to
do.
Interview of 4
Broadcasting is
a 4 star.
It's that loud recording Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
lookaaaaaaaaaa!
Just like in the tell job talk, I'm a little bit older. Wow, I
didn't have the confidence to convey the content, so the
subtitles are good. R Fork ios
b up to
Acme, we'll continue to watch!
Girl-chansare t
Aaaaaaa
testis party soy sauce  Won owned
waaaaaaan
i inside strangers plan
amazing eye blind there is a fish
ok
break out of the shell tomorrow
renderjre
anc is already
terrorizer it's getting cooler to 6
5 hehehehe
Hey, there's a trailer I'd like to show you, so please take a look.
[Music]
pattern
rester charles jointy
co
hardy screen name place
a clever
mima foretrex soria
[music]
voodoo
graffiti girls jr compilation
bonder 2 s bar
[music]  I've
been drinking
Baaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[music]
booboo
seara ah the whole amateur fukue
mase voodoo m sports e-
prize
and rap habu point game
n
ifaw  Monster web Yumu
Weber pink is getting better and better Lean naming
Ah mo 3 es main vein Kushiya
Actually, I think this Aisin is quite a sound topic,
but
if you haven't done something similar to horse riding, it
's quite a rough topic.  So I
think it's just barely okay
so
acore
gettweet please enjoy
amebagg sesami roux
de rinon bar &peing a
rin pro surfer a star
lever everyone please enjoy and
a
4 point job talk with my seniors.  Don't
worry ahkah
Eroliwangoo even
esp Arm birthday at the limit store
before the imperial palace a
howa skin 4
san It's far away Apis giant ghost same
report bird chase espa lsdana and
pop person and Pepsion we are
chitar
bundle
taso cesarean
riso
[music]
manen be some name
ermaster ice cream
window asr painting
in
rb zao
boob
ander phone ah soai goo
[music] do
volume osanai
asperge teens were
to
do ri so gd 5 gay
bar walker bow arere n suo
iso has no  day of
unpa way beads bas reb
hanyu point game
yeah yeah
ran b 2 dj ren beats
pro aboard maa piece 4 s
aket web alanui black
member Comet Senpai 2 maisto key a
life senior good evening
city hello
Hello, good morning, good
morning. From here on, it's okay to use Japanese, so I'll congratulate you. Reiji, please. My sign language is Star Moni, Comet. Thank you very much. Please give me a detailed self-introduction as a senpai. OK. I'll show up like a pod in a hurry.
Thank you very much for your support.
ig I want another one.
Thank you for coming to this industry today. It
's my second time. Yes, it's my second time.
That one time.  The second time I was so sleepy, I
felt like I was sleepy. The purser was definitely
heavy that time. ia This is the rice. My
wallet is
sorry, but my head has been feeding well since spring. Did it
reach the surface of the water? It's already today. Today.  Hey, the
photo with the badge was great. That's
right. I'm going to do it.
Thank you for your support. I'm going to show you the
show, and I
'm going to talk a lot about the Forerise and Body Loss series today.
But
before that, uh, before that.  I'm
going to share the details with everyone in 50% of this broadcast, but the
characters are so
special that Ubebe's medieval name is so
powerful.
That's right. I was
given the opportunity to learn a very nice technique from Toulouse Orb Arise's A staff member, Ranko Hane, so I don't know how
many times I should say that.  I do
n't know what's going on with all of this. It's still the first series, yeah yeah. It might not be Mach yet, but it's
something I really want, but I don't
want it. Seriously, that's it. I want that universal sword of flame.
Rena A's Kiara already has the power, so it's not
me.
Well, I think the Apen-san case would be better. If it were that Geara, it would be fine. It's
Phoenix, so that flaming sword
wouldn't hurt, right?  It's probably been
2 years, right?
What's up with this virtual internet sophia?
But yeah, there's a surfer coming. I was wondering if
this was going to work, and I noticed, and the
viewers noticed, too, but
it's actually a real thing.  Lines
are amazing. They're similar. There's
something like that, and there's a theme to that flame.
But there's also something else, like the sound you make when you drink.
But what about her personality and management? She
said something like, ``Yeah, yeah.''
Well,
there was a part where she was playing, so it was later in terms of personality,
so Shion-chan was the first.  I was
curious about the number, and
thought it would suit me, but
when I finally got to the end of what I was listening to, I thought, ``I am Alfe.''
The
cemetery and things like that aren't around anymore, and I'm saying
that I'm like myself, a
self-improving character, hmm,
a
eran, and there are
n't any characters out there,
but if you ask me, while I was playing that game, I was
always using Alfe.  I've
been playing lanes for a long
time, so I felt a lot of empathy
for the
main character, but I
thought it was him, and he had a way of talking, and I was trying to get into
Alpen's feelings, so I thought it was
meat, so that's it.  There's a certain Fen that I have a
lot of feelings for.It makes sense to
me as well.This
one is definitely the most similar to me in the whole group.Even
if it doesn't have a character or origin, it's my
favorite Japanese cap
after all.  Is it Alfe?
Ah, it's Ro, it's Ross, so
what's so surprising about it? It's me,
except for Karamuru. Hmm, Rasmurano, I've
fallen in love with blinds, and it looks like Soul. Hello,
polyrhythm is also moon.
Alfen was the one.  But,
uh, if there's a theory, do you like the sound?
He's a nice guy, but he's wearing a hoodie. I
like the front. I
think I'll see him. During the dance, why are there good seniors?  It
's Nezu's words, but I
love the front,
and Law is really Shoning, who's good at accounting.Yo,
come on, come on, let's say true.He's a
striker, so it's Law's
personality.  But it's cute
. Maybe M's is Sasachi.
As time passed, I started to like Michi a little,
but at first I didn't like it at first,
but I thought it was a bit annoying,
but there's a reason why I'm splitting it up.  Either way,
there was a story about Roan's father. I heard
that Roan's father died.
Well,
whatever started it all, it's over now.
So, it's like your proposal to
end Farlow.  I thought he was a foreigner, like this remote island used for mantras, so
I thought something like that too,
but as the story progressed, I couldn't help but wonder
what kind of person Law was and what his true personality was
when he first appeared.  But as I
started to see more and more of her bright personality and her role as someone being teased, I
thought she was cute, and I thought she was the mood maker at the party.That's
true.  Did you
put it in? Ah, I
didn't put it in the loose party.
Ah, I see.
Ah,
that's a lie. We're not here.
My favorite character is.
Hmm, it
's a bit of an irritating scene, but it's still delicious. A
character that makes you fall in love with teenagers.
Tower, a woman.  What's this?I can
feel safe even if I'm gay.Hmm, I like cute girls.But what do you
mean by cute?I like girls who look like they're likable.That's why I
love Kisara.Yes, I like Kisara
.  It's really Japanese,
but it's a burger shop, but it's
not just sexy, it's like they're
really taking care of the family they're heading to.And that's why I don't
like them, but
when the part of me that embraces them comes out.  I
thought that Kisara was a good idea, but I ended up
falling in love with her.That Kisara is very
serious,
and after her death, she did her best to deal with her head.I
guess that's what makes Shima so serious.  I'm thinking, uh,
this is just a bit of an
appearance aspect, but
uh, the
basic mother, uh, the
overall story view of the video game,
regardless of the
female character,
uh, equipment, the group is AI.  The
equipment that doesn't properly protect the body is height and eye-fi.That's the
case with the character design.The
Acura design
has a rose version properly, and I thought, ``Wow, this is really cool.''
That's what I thought, but then I realized that she
wasn't hiding at all, but she
wasn't hiding at all in the middle of the night.But
even Kisara, why is her back
so empty?
It's because she doesn't want to show her back.  I said something like that, so it's also improvisational.
There's a reason why Chikisouna-chan and
Kisara
have a really big shield.
Up until now, she's fought standing up.
Inside,
the
sound mirror is really good, yes, it's true, the
way the battle revolves around it is really disgusting.  I
was coming back from that day, but
that wooden plate is
a bit slow. I don't know
what it is, but it feels a little slow.
But compared to a certain Fen, it
has a very stiff wind,
and it's surprisingly easy to fight.  That's
right, that's right, that wooden plate was the only one
in that battle,
a.
How do you say it in Japan?
That opponent's
a. It was
more for the sake of opening up the opponent's attack, and he
completely accepted the stage, uh, yeah,
yeah.  The
school doctor is interesting, and really cool.Also,
a,
I actually started to like that Shion a lot too
.  She's a very strong,
strong woman.And the
color of her hair somehow
reminds me of her.For some reason, I think she's worth more than that.At
first, I thought we looked alike,
but she was kind of cold to me.I don't really want to interact with other
people.  I can't force it, it's accurate,
but as the story progresses, it
becomes warmer and more accurate, and I wonder why.It
starts to look like a human being.It's
true that Miller also became more sensitive and human-like.
That
's right, that's why wooden plates and salt are the most important things at home on ski
days.Hehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehe
washes dishes, dishes, earthenware washing, I saw the name and
thought, ``Maybe it was on purpose?''I was
wondering if it was fate.  What he
showed me was the review session.Heheheheheh, there was a
suicide note from someone who wanted to do something.A
customer who was proof that it was like a
flight.Well, it seems like he wants to give birth
to a child.  I
think, but in Papauchi's brain,
he is him. Even in my path, I will
make it come true. Thank you, Hiko. Yes,
then Root
Tail. Of Arise
Eight.
Hmm, I think it's the poop that I liked the most in the game.
Yeah, I guess that's it. Hmm,
graphics.
Phone. They
have really beautiful graphics, Dan. I
thought they were a little different from the usual Tales. They were
n't just 3D or Starbucks CG, but they had
textures that gave you a sense of the world.  It
looks like that watercolor or something,
but Suizansou's
water repellency is weak and it looks like watercolor,
and that CG has a kind of analog-like
feel to it, and
that
cc.  I've always thought it was amazing how it was expressed in such a way
that it didn't really make you feel him, and I
thought the graphics were so beautiful.The
graphics of Egg Syria, etc. are amazing.  I remember it being beautiful,
but it
had a very digital feel to it.It was free.It
was really good, but it was very beautiful and
had the feel of the latest technology.Hmm,
which one is that Arise?  When I said that, it
really felt like an ancient civilization, and I thought, wow, that's a great place to wash your head.I
see,
that's a noisy rabbit.
It's a story
from the Tales series.
All of them are very satisfying. I
wonder how they would say Pa's amazing Inspy Ring in Japanese. I
had it written in subtitles.
A Oh yeah, Sono Spy.  I was thinking,
hmmm, and
when I'm choosing a game,
I have to look at that graphic.  I
really
like the Japanese-style style of Anime A, and I
really like the style of the older brother's wife, and I
love the way it looks.  The character designs of Todo and
Aru Njare Sai's Maa Mobile Zo Rise
are amazing.I
guess I was just lucky when I first saw the final version.
But there's a part that has some equipment in it.It looks
strong, but
if you touch it, it'll
just crack and fall apart.I
wonder if it'll just fall apart, but it's a patient.That's right, I
drew a dog that saw a beautiful kami-kami.Let's draw it at the very beginning.
When the movie Reznor was announced, the trailer was made into a movie.
When I saw Chance Wave, Isan Al-
Sion turned into a cow coming down from the stairs. I
was so impressed when I saw him walking. I
felt like there was something really new about that.  I could
n't stop my heart pounding when I saw it, and
there was a scene where the chicken bones stood up like crazy.
Elegant's
Shion-chan left it behind.
Hmm, this Tales Handwashing
Arise is really cool. The
character designs are also better than ever.  I'm
sure the person in charge is different, so I really
thought it was a new Tales.Even
above, it's like
that Tales.  I
want you to say that's my favorite scene. I'm a
kid who loves music.
Momo. Um,
ah, the
old man sitting in the strange chair, Nishion,
was taken away. Yes,
yes.  In the
beginning, it's like, ``
Oh, what kind of thing is that guy?'' He's
been stalking us, or that guy, or that strange
old man.  I wanted to take her
away and let's all go somewhere together, so I
wanted to go and help my sister, but
Alpen
brought back that pain, so I
decided to help Sheen, even though I was in pain.
Then we went deeper, and Shion had already
fallen into a dark place,
and Hahn started approaching her and started to feel like it was you. I
didn't see that guy, it was really painful,
but I can't handle that anymore.  There's nothing I can do about that pain,
but
now that I'm in the throes of suffering from that familiar pain, I'm going to
push through it like this, like this,
Denny, it
hurts, but I'll embrace the scene properly and
say, ``Caramel Nuts.''
There's already something going on in that scene.
Think of Line as a man who never makes a mistake, who
wants to have a big spare, who
always asks for the correct answer, who
really does what you want him to do.  It
was a really nice scene,
but when I walked up to him, it certainly stayed in my memory, and
one of my wife's
nun, it's
nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo.
There's one scene where we talked a little bit about the hard-working envelope guy who died so quickly, but there's another scene where the
good Salah's
brother
dies aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah  The
reason why I died in the first place is simply because people
don't believe me, so I
have to introduce myself to everyone and put up a front.
So instead of delusional, I hope that all the women
will understand me, and then I'll scoop everyone else up.  There was a
scene in Toyonaka where I had to sacrifice myself in order to be saved, and when Kisara saw this and realized it, he burst into tears and let out a scream like that.  I
already had a heart, so cut it out.
From the lines, there weren't too many reporters at home, but at home I
played with English voices, but
Kisara-san's 8 voice actors
were really good.
[Music] My
heart was really sick.  I was so
crazy that
I had a Japanese grandmother, but
I was already very emotional. It looks like it's already very emotional,
oh, oh,
isn't it?
Behind my back,
everyone understood, but
no, there was
nothing else I could do at each store, and I
started thinking about it.Well,
well, it seems like they're
inside Zainami.What a
shame.  But thanks to that, I was able to
show off some truly wonderful performances.One
left and one Nishi-Osu was outstanding.A
Hey, hey, yeah.Next,
what I want to ask is,
Yes, there are a lot of those moves.Kako
's sister-in-law is so fast.  Well,
did you find them all?
Actually, I
cheered when I found them all. Ha, ha, I have
n't found them at all. No jamin. It's probably just the moon.
There's one,
but my favorite part was that one, the one
on that side, and the one that I liked the most was touching that one.
Then he has an oil fill and a full head attached to his head.A It
's cute, but I
added it to the sold L.
[Laughs] He
likes the Boober. Did he have an
attachment?
Actually, Comet-senpai.  It's been a
long time since I haven't run an attachment before,
but in the full version I used to catch some of them as soon as I found them.But,
back in the day, when I played Tales, I
had my own rules.
For the first round, I
decided to play with no attachments, no costume changes,
and I decided to play from 20 a.That's
southwest.The
reason is that the first round is
supposed to have that serious scene.  The
fake personality is wearing a swimsuit, somehow,
the words are written in the raw, and it's easy to deal with it.
Already, the circle of angels is going at the same rate. There's
one in the top mano car, isn't it? That one
will make you conscious.
Let's hold it,
uh,
in that state.  I wanted to enjoy Tales in that neutral state
first,
so I made sure not to touch the ground and the stones, and
after I [ __ ], I did a hot onion.
I also got a little scolded by the viewers when I streamed Saa Saa
Onyau listener support.For example,
it's so big, it's so big, the ground and that
tlg downloadable content, and
so on.  I
made the screen almost entirely from scratch, and I could
n't see the faces of the characters.I'm a big fan of Tafa, so I
'll ship it to you.Smile.
That's
right, the goal doesn't look serious anymore, and I'm wondering
who it is, right? Spot, the
director can't get in. There was definitely a heel,
but even if I don't understand it, it's
too late.
Everyone has their own way of enjoying the time with a lens, so it
looks like it's going to be windy. A pond full of water 6. It's probably inside a self-propelled car.
There may be people who think of it that way, and
there may be people who think of other ways of doing it, so you
can play it in many different ways.But there's
one thing that
Chiara did and the other thing that she did was
break the eyeliner, e4 style.
If I had the same hairstyle for each outfit, that
blue-cheeked mask
would come off quickly.With the
air trip,
it would disappear quickly, so I was absorbed in the eyes first.  He
's a human being. I
heard that in that true story, the opposition party was out of line, but
even though I didn't watch it, it made me weaker. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, the
emotion of that moment has faded
but it's my fault.
I couldn't do it, so I wish I had hair.It's all my
fault, Mr. Barndam, who is cool and in his prime, who has a cool hairstyle.No, no, it's
me, I'm 4 strokes behind.It's my fault that the
eggs aren't coming anymore.Well,
putting aside the winter story, it's all my fault.  I personally think that
finding the old door is the first mission of this game,
but it's full.Ah,
duffle bus
8.Next question is,
umm, what
was my least favorite?
Hmm,
that enemy boss enemy boss boss I want to ask you which wall it was.
To the boss enemy I hated the most. That's it.
Why do the houses
meet? Dollar. Oh, those witches. Please go ahead to that witch. It's
not a launcher, it's a ball run.  I don't
like Ume, I don't like Dora and I don't like that one,
but that story has a really
bad personality.And it's not because he has a bad personality, it's because
during the boss battle, he was fighting with Nagatori to Hate.
Well, it would be
very difficult if that were the case. It was amazing to defeat the flying enemies, but Anchor is difficult. That's true. It's very difficult. It's
because there's a voice. I hate
it. I'm
also an American, but I
don't know who it is.  It's not a problem, it's a
problem with the character of the phrase.Yes, it
looks very sexy, and it's
Usuki, but, ah, each of them, I wonder
if that boss is that a, Da-
Kan Pro h Appraisal, sa What is it in Japanese?  I do
n't know what to say,
but it's a bright contest, a
contest in which all the bosses are participating.Ah,
yes, it's early, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
everyone must do their own instruments to win.The guards and others
must
gather that energy.  For
a
a We
all have our own strategies.That
blue girl, I
feel like it was the worst.Ah,
mah, that girl was terrible, wasn't it?
Ee There was no such thing as a 3 difference.First
of all, I wonder
what it is.How
can I explain it?  I do
n't want to spoil it too much, but
it's possible.The
22 people were
summoned to defeat the Blue Eyes in 44 Day, but in the end, that
was the most important banner,
and everyone gathered together and
died.  That said, it
's the Doll Dobrella Garr that makes you go crazy. I'm a
Crown fan.
That's the story. I thought Aome Medora was the
best, and then there was
Rin Archer,
Blue Mirror, and Momo Ci.  I
got really emotional about it, and I
was trying to stop the a ring router there, but
from the perspective of finishing it off, I was thinking, ``Keep doing it!'' But then I got a
wiener cola, but I thought, ``I'm
going to kill you.''  I was really thinking about giving these clothes
to each other at Goro's, but
Furo-kun said they were too expensive,
so I didn't have to go through them anymore.
Oh,
there was that anime about Ume Dora no Kami, haha, yes, I
think there was an anime, but
there, at the beginning,
it
was like, oh, I'm about to get burned, and then
in the second part, please stop and watch it.
Taja Ume Dora is in the third layer of the zone, and the other
batting line-up is...
After I said that, when I saw him, I thought, ``He's a good guy.  I
think it's a
different kind of variety, so I'm going to be
a different one, but I hate it because it looks like it's like a dad, so I hate it.
What is the sound of the word?From the trend,
Nellis started anon Mysterious Black in
Fukuoka Hit
A It
also appeared in the trailer A
Isn't that man a color?Ah, from the beginning It
also appeared in the strange place
Super  It's a brand that won't answer that mysterious riddle,
right? After
that, I think I'll be able to get more and more confused about who this person is,
but
when I didn't know who this
person was, I sent out this character and
created my own image of what kind of person this person is.  Wow, what
was that? Well, it was a heated battle. That's right, I, uh, thought that Ryuk in Tales of Vesperia was a person of 81. Ah, I see. I don't know what to say, but that target.  I
thought he was the type of person who doesn't have anything and isn't an ally, but in the end he becomes the target and becomes the final boss.I guess it's not
that kind of thing.Harau's...
Well, Kiara-han un
-go
How many layers are stacked up? I love the conspiracy loan
gar,
and
actually, I thought this person
might be fighting in the future or in the past, so I was
thinking about it as soon as I found a good day to brew it. It's
like that.  I have a notebook where I'm writing down
all kinds of things like height and body size, and I'm thinking, oh, what's wrong with that kid's body,
and I'm
trying to draw out the roots of past or future evil in the processing, right? The
slider is so annoying.
Well, that's just what I wanted to ask.A
8Next question is,
if you were to live in the world of Rise in the transfer market, what would you do?
Where would you live?
That's where the eyes are, the
infield, the
eyes are shooting, it's really nice over there.
Nakayan Makalu's medicine is dangerous. Off whey
Cal is that delicious. It's overflowing with that hot water. Ah, there's an area that's
very clean
and there's no one in the head.
Hmm, am I messing up?
After being in such a quiet and relaxing place, I love snow, so I
thought it would be a good idea to go there as well,
but the
people who live in my sister who eat sushi are too strong, so I went to the
4th floor.  Everyone doesn't trust each other or the people around them. I
thought that life would be difficult in this situation,
so I wouldn't
have done it if I was in Sysrodia after the security people saved me.  Yes, that's right, I'm
sure the person who lives there is the
only one in the world where people are expelling terrorism,
and
where everyone is from.
It's so peaceful because we're all together,
and I thought about making a hand
strike, and I took care of it for 2 minutes, and
that door ringer, the third son's capital.  When I
saw it, I
thought, ``Wow, it's so beautiful.'' I went there for a while, and there were parts like that, and I was running it, and I thought, ``I don't know why, but it feels so good.'' Hmm, when I see beautiful fruit, I get that familiar feeling.  It
was a good design.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
so a
next brush too  If you
like someone, your
favorite hobby is fishing, right?
If you love someone, you'll tell the other
characters
that fishing is great.
That's right, it's really cool and cute to see them pretending to be at a distance,
but normally I'm not interested in this game, but
in this game, I'd rather just do the general fishing.Hmm, I
guess I
caught all of them already.That's
right.  Well, I keep catching the same fish every time, and when I'm
in love, I'm always caught by one, but I've been
wondering how to do this, and I've been
fishing all the time.There's a trick to it.But you know,
that rainy mountain, that
kind of amnesia,
Chantown.  If
you don't have one, it
won't come near you, but
even after the game, you'll have to go a little later to
get it.  At
first, it was just the same Yusa,
but I
used to like water, but
in this game, Arthur was a bad character, so I
said it was dark, so I
didn't remember the buttons on that controller at all.  When I ca
n't see it directly, I can't remember where the button is,
for example, where the egg type x is or
whether the circle is large, so I often make mistakes when I have to
press that button for fear fishing.  I
made a mistake when writing the song.The first thing I made wrong was, well,
Jobko was there with that LTRT.It's
good that there isn't that darkness in southern Hokkaido.Even
though there aren't many, something is going to happen.  Well, I
'm glad it's not just the house, I'm glad - I also have a lot of j  If you
look at the way it flies, it seems like it
's a Baikal.
Yes, it
looks like it's a fishing master. Now, all the viewers are fishing masters,
but I'm amazing. That
one's a little bad at taking pictures.
But if you try hard enough, you'll be able to catch that fish.  As I
watch their movements, I think they're disappearing more and more,
so next time I'll ask them to pay attention to me a little bit
and I'll move them back inside the house.It seems like they're
not there either.  Do you
have a favorite costume? My
favorite one is
Why Genesic? I'm King Orlan.
Hmm, amazing names, etc. I think it's a messed up one.
Ah, I wonder which one it was. I do
n't think it's pronounced in English.  That's
nice, evernote What is it
like to eat like a
dumb person? I'm not sure what you're doing.
Ah, the cause is the fence. Philippe.  It's
like Negative Gate, it
's like an evolved version of Negative Gate, but
Wow, it looks like this, and that's why I love it.The thing about
it is that it's called a giant Harim Triwel.  It wasn't that those two
hated each other
the most, it was that they couldn't understand such a huge amount of things,
but in the middle of 7 or so,
they both approached each other and realized that they were from
different countries.  It's
like there's a duality between them, and there
's a certain level of acceptance of each other,
and the fact that
these two people are doing that trick together
means that it's a good meeting, and
today, Ha Rim...
Picker's eyes light up, right? Yeah,
this landowner's route's Oreo oreo.
When that woman turns blue and turns into
a certain 6, it's really cool.
Ah,
yes, it's an overwork zone, and that Liberl dares to
say the words that make her an annoyance.  Tell me, I'm
flying in the sky like a witch It's really
impressively cool and I love it
So, I like Negative Gate or something, so
ah hmm, I'm going to
make a tax enforcement order that feels like an evolved version of Negative Gate.  I
thought it was really cool and I loved it.I
see, when I was editing the video, I lost the case, but
everyone could see it.
Even if it doesn't matter, I
like that Booth Sly child is the best, and
Phoenix is ​​the best.I
don't know the title of Japan, but it
was unraveled.Also,
Kisara and a certain side of the area, yes, fire, and
Tornado's angry guy
is Eduga.  - Mu is
incredible. It's an incredible increase in power. But I do
n't like any of the booth strikes that Kisara participates in. They're all powerful.
Oh yeah, the
festival that moved after that has a technique with Phoenix's name on it,
but that line's lightning.
There's a lot of Jeans Fee Nicks, and there's a
tech that jumps up, and then it's
like jumping off.
That's right, that's right, that's right, that's
right, that's right. Bamboo grass is cool. That's
right. People were bumping into each other.  It's
something that everyone has used.
Oh, it's so easy to use. Hmm, it
shines. Maybe it's something that's been around for a long time. I'll leave it
alone. It's
like that. It's not working. I'm sure.  It's
been around for a long time, so I remember the road that I thought was Mars
a I
see,
ok ok
a Let's
move on to the next person Next
is a Kihara I'm a little curious, but what is it?
One thing I noticed as I went along was
that the play style of Rise Kiara has completely changed from the previous Tales series games I've played so
far.  It
got so bad that I decided to go ahead with the battle, which I did, right?
After laying an egg, it was supposed to be the boss sooner or later, but
when I fought it, I didn't have enough bellies to sell, and I ended up
getting sold over and over again.
There are quite a few times when I fail, but
with Riser Bar Rise, various things are shocking.
For example, after a battle, you can immediately return to the map. It's really
fast, isn't it? It's smooth,
isn't it?  Compared to before, it
takes a lot of time, so
even though I fight, I don't get tired of Chiara at all.It's
fun, and I can progress more and more and
raise the level, and even if I fight a boss, I can
usually defeat it in one go.  It wasn't a problem at all,
but it may have been the benefit of the DLC,
but I'm just talking about this
now.I wonder if something has changed for that recommended senior
because I want to play my own role in Rise.  Do you
have something to do?I
said earlier that I only use the Alpen of Time to sing.It's
true.Well, it's
like Alpen in April, so I
guess that's the case.Pharynx
Originally, I used to play quite a line in which the
Wizard attacks from a distance.  I've been using it all the time,
but
Ramon: Yeah, that's right, it's been like that for a long time.A building is
nice.Anis is fighting,
but he's using magic with Jozu in the rear guard,
etc.Hmm, he's been doing that for a long time, and he's
using Harold, and he's even trying to
win.  Demon King,
I've started doing melee quite a lot,
and I've been using it for a while now, without using magic, and I've
started using it quite a bit, and I
used to think it was difficult.
However, when I try it now, I feel like I
used to feel that it might not be as good as I imagined it to be.  I
thought it was really interesting, but I don't know what that thin-skinned senpai just
said about the wizard character. Up
until now,
I've
always had him on my team in the Tales of the North series of games,
but I've always had him on my team.  I've never had anything to do before,
right? We tried the flavor and the sales, and it was a
bit more flashy, like Linbel.
Also, I think Shihyun was able to do it a little bit more.  It's
really easy to play,
and if you think it's easy, you don't have to dodge anything.When you
think about it, it's fun to play twice, and it does some tricks at
such a fast speed,
so I thought it was amazing and easy to use.Hmm,
use it.  So, the
next question is,
why do you recommend it to those who are doing research?
What is the
best part of it that you would like to recommend to the viewers?
And what
about the other games in the Teru Kakuso Upper series, like those
in September?
Let me tell you about it in a promotional way.Okay, so I'd
like to give you a presentation on Tizbu Arise.
Speaking of Ad Tales,
this character's chest shape has been
completely redesigned since there are only about 23 characters, and the
shape of the chest is different from before.
Isn't it 8 aa? It has been
used for lung cancer until now,
right? Well, since the word "screw" seems to be
common to people, why did they
use the same name as "toa"?  I was
thinking, ``Maybe this
is a new starting point for Fields,'' and since
Hearn has never changed, the
good points of Tales so far are still there, and the
anime is sandwiched in the middle, or something
like that skit.
It's such a neat picture, with chat and stuff like that.It still retains the Tales feel,
but it's really new.I
thought it was delivering that feeling to everyone.  What I
thought was that new thing about Arise was,
well, as I said earlier, it
's the skit chat. It's
completely different from what it used to be before the war. To
be honest, I like Chiara more as a
guide here.  That's not interesting, right? I
never get tired of hearing these stories, and I
find myself wanting to read them.
That's right. It's getting even more
elaborate. Up until now, it's been like that anime-like Last Day. Even
though it feels like an anime, it's
overdone.  That's right, that's right, there
are some expressions on the face.
But this time,
in the construction of Harbor Rye, it became 3D, and it's a chain,
isn't it? Is it true that it's gold? It's called skit chat. Up
until now, I thought it had a lot of bonuses and running elements,
but Louise is already here.
That mini-story is so dark
and so careless. It's like a foreign Japanese
story, but that's not the case.
As a fan of the Till's Off series,
there is a big difference between Okinawa and the strange part of it.  It's a
work that retains a lot of the new Tales elements, while also retaining a lot of the Tales elements up to m, so it's a
work I'd recommend to people who are playing Nails for the first time.Of course,
even if you've
played Tales before.  I
can recommend it
to people who want to play Tales but don't know where to start.
Hey,
if I were to do it now, I'd probably go ahead with one of these.
is
a I
would like to say that I recommend it.The
story of Real Server Rise is also quite dark.Even
if the story is muddled, that
Sensitive Soriona story 0 is highly
recommended.I highly recommend it, and the battle is also really
fun.It's so much fun, I'm already saying Imazaki.  However, Chiara
usually doesn't have it, but this shape is lol.Then, the
battle is so fun and smooth that I want to do it more and more.It
's more fun than the original version.It's
not just the main character who eats.  Other
characters It's
very easy to play and easy to remember, so I
highly recommend it to everyone.Aso,
please tell your seniors of the opposite sex to try playing the other
characters.I
want to play ecoo.
Once you learn how to do it, it's a lot of fun,
and the
door rim
has the speed of the heel, so it would be great if it was included in the video.The
dog's heel
doesn't need that much, so it's
fun to fight by dropping the tide yourself.  I
can say that I think the simultaneous official clothing is "Please use it" and "Mahler", and everything else is water-based. I think you've put it all together really well. I'm
getting a little bit of a point here.
A few general questions about the Obseries.  I'd like to
ask you, Mazon, my recommended senior, how did you get the chance to make the Increased Part series
known as Sitter's Ga? The
reason: Yeah,
etc.
My sister's friend got hooked on Tales, and
she was able to progress with the Boo Boo minutes.  So
Tales was
interesting, and we met at
Tales of Destiny 2. But
goo, the
sounds that my sister can do and don't do, Fern,
just cut straight, really. I was
watching her do it from behind.
Yes,
management I could
n't defeat that boss, sis.
Oh yeah, so
I said I wanted to do it too, so I
connected two controllers, and the two of us
defeated it together, making it the boss of Da. Let's
defeat it. Bye. Great work, you
two.  It was fun to play with them,
and I
started following that series all the time, and it was a fun game for two people to play together.
[Music] It's
new, is
n't it? It's a new toy for the two of us, or
rather, it's fun to play with.  Well, it was
like that.
Kisai grew up painting overseas, so the
afterlife was 6 stitches. The
score of the series was
quite different from that of Japan, and she wasn't well-known in the rain,
either. That character was also unknown.  When I was a kid, I was
n't very well-known, or rather, I wasn't well-known about it at all.The
first popular
game I played was Tail Increase Suspicious 4 Urine,
and then High Rider Advancement Meow
started to spread overseas,
and yeah, that
kid.  Back then, I didn't know about the city motels,
and I didn't know anything about Japan's first-year junior high school families.Back
then, I didn't know anything about Japan and I hadn't really developed an interest in Japan, and my
mom gave that ignorant brother
a present for Christmas.  I
was really into European-style symphoners, right?
At first, I was playing ``22 Big Brother''
all the time, and I preferred to watch my house,
so I'm starting to get excited about it because I do
n't really understand the game yet.
Grandfather's new option that I can accept
even if Pony is already a game that can be played by those two,
so in terms of freshness, I'm going to
participate eventually. When I tried participating, it was like this. The
graphics are cute, so it's cute. It's really
interesting.  I thought it was fun,
but sometimes I
started to hang out by myself, and when it was difficult to report, I
called him ``big brother'' and we
beat it together. That's the way we do it.
From there, I started to wonder
if there were any more games like this, so I looked it up and
found out that there was an increasing series, and from there I
was hooked.I get it, it's
vulgar.  Shunpo, I
can't thank you enough for your guidance. I love the
game.Which
game is the best in the Eyes Off series?
Ensono a
That's certainly a very popular run.There are some
scammers involved.By I love
Vesperia.Vesperia
and that.I was
really worried about it.Ah, I heard that she
loved Vesperia and the house.  The
thing about it is that the
story is so painful,
and I love it when the story is so painful, and
when you give birth to a child, there's something about each and every one of them,
right?
There's that Isla, or rather, your own thoughts, and you do it yourself.  I had to do it because
everyone was partying
like they were fooling each other.It
was really the party that had the worst relationship in Tales C.
But that party was the one in the middle of the party.  At the end, it's a
little gray.It
feels like a party.6Actually,
I didn't particularly dislike Luke,
but it's
like that.It's
really m.It makes me cry while it's delicious.Everyone is
different.  It's called an
RPG where you can really understand the meaning behind your birth,
but I
also learned about one of the works that encouraged my thinking, or rather my child's growth.  I
'm trying to play a really deep and over-the-top game.
[Laughs] It's
definitely one of those games where you can move forward.Kitani:
By the way, the ones I like the most are
Zone Songs, Xillia 1, and
Flow.
Why wasn't there anything special about it?
Well, I think you can understand.
There's laundry sharing. So let's select a tile once and make that choice.
Depending on the choice, the
whole game changes.
So, it's a very, very dark question. It's a
very dark question.  It's a tough game
in the series,
where you can choose from a lot of options,
but it's probably the only game that actually has any effect.The only thing I've
played is the
postsk-less route.  There were some weak points,
but what is that about Xillia?The main character
doesn't speak, so it's not
that
great.The main character doesn't speak, so it doesn't really matter.  In the
Bottom of the Wind
series and games, I
like it when the route is already decided,
but this is really fresh and I
thought, oh hey, it's fun.
Favorite
character
By the way, Mirror max l o xo
Hey maxwell and Hordy se I
also
love A and A and A and I'm
not surprised about Magiru-chan, but
Gil-chan is so funny I like it Who is my
favorite character I wanted to be like a support group  The child is a liter,
Revibo is a ritter ー ー ー ー ー ー ー ー ー ー ー ー ー I
like Rita Doi scanana
Return Gar's character
design in the first place.  My
favorite character is Dayner
Akane. I like that fighting style, it's not very innovative. It's
like a middle scroll, so I made it stand up. Why
doesn't the boy appear here? I
didn't really like approval in the past.
Hmm, I've noticed that recently.  That's me and I
like boys.I don't even notice the age.I
like that female character so much.That's why it's an
assignment with Anise.It's
not Arietta either.But I
loved Harold's rating, and
4 is cool.  I really like my sister,
Parita-chan, and I love her too, and she has a really crazy personality.That's
right.I
really like Washisu, and even Na-chan wants to be my friend.Fortunately,
she's cute, so I
can't help but fall in love with her.  I wonder
if I can understand it even in the game of my head.
For some reason, I like the wizard character every time. I
like Ushiki Natsune, I wonder if that's what
Magilou is like. He's really number one. He's a
rotten man with the power to quit. I
like that one.  You said you liked Ing Syria 2.
Well, my
favorite scene in Xilia 2 is that
one,
that big brother's
car,
later,
when Asaki stops, it ends with a dream, and then opens,
papa no 4. That's the part.  I
love it, so I used the senior wing chair. I do
n't want to kick you out. I don't want to be chased away. It's just that big brother
's singing voice. It's raining neon.
Line points, quitting, next question. Hello,
where is the part?
Els.  If you were to become a character in a Jizobe series game off-game,
what kind of weapon and character
do you think it would be?a
But hey,
if you're someone who fights up close, a
halberd would be a good choice.Big
cheeks.  Even though there are many outsiders, I
have a lot of images of that,
so I thought I'd like to use it in the future.I see,
but I want to use magic, so it's a little difficult.Of
course, I want to become a magician, so if that's the case, I'll
always use it.  Nagai: I'll
tell you about the cane too. I'm
sure. I
want to have something like a book or something for a night out. I have
a dream.
Chiara also uses the cat's vertical clock. No, she
basically uses it.  But,
no, I wonder
what it would be like if I were to come in. Hey, I kind of
like wizards, but yeah, to be
honest, I
want to hit the ruling party. oe Hey, I love you, I want to hit you right now. Just
like Natalia-chan in the middle of the night.
Natalia  I
might want a weapon like that in the past, but in the Middle Ages, I'd
like to take a little distance and fight against the enemy.To be honest,
armor To be honest, hahaha, I'm
sure that's the share of Radiant My Solo
G is
always doing 7  Yes, it's my choice. I'm
happy to hear from people who have a lot of experience overseas. I've
always been a hunter like Tomomi, and I'm half-hearted. I'm so
happy to hear that you're going to shoot it right now.  Sairai Amachi Ouji is that picture 8th place 3 is
warm 3 3
That's right, that's your own character - you
can make it Loan Soka's Teruzu uses a fixed main character,
but a is a loose benefactor himself.  It's
special to make it.
That's right, you can't do the day, the
characters are full of jerks. There
is a dream.
As a Teruzu fan, it's hot.
Yes, that's how we are. I have a dream.
Hey,
Ian and I met each other.
Well, I was asleep for a while and asked some basic questions about the Zoo Off series,
but
iaa, it's a bit towards the end.  We're getting closer,
just Aant,
hey, there's
one question I want to ask. There's just one more thing I wanted to ask you.
At Nadai Arise, the food looks
delicious, doesn't it?
How
about
that 8 recipes?  Well,
there are a lot of them, and each recipe
has a variety of effects, but
anyway, I'm going to play that game at that restaurant, and I
think I'm going to make that dish at my house,
which was my favorite and it's
delicious.  I wonder if there was
a day when I liked the dish or the
effect that I liked the most.The dish that I liked the most about the effect was the one called Yu Kanaoka.
I wonder
if the experience points increase after the
battle ends bash There are some cases where the experience points are increased after the battle is over,
so things
like broken brains are also dishes that increase the experience points,
but that one is true.  There are two things that go up,
so Ibii got a
fruit sandwich and that exb
boost l I think it's good that the preparation 1 is big,
right? The fruit should be excited.  Yes,
without the recipe,
yeah,
both sides
are close to experience, that increases the experience points b, and things like that,
and it's always been a-
a-man, right? It's dead, isn't it? The fruit
sandwich is growing all over the house. I think it's
cracked, right? There
were 4 dozen contents in the DLC.  Writer
Parker
Oh yeah
[laughing]
Well, it's
Shirley after all. I'd like them to
buy the DLC content too. Ah, I wonder
if it'll be red and I'll go to the leaf bank.
Is that an exp effect? ​​That's how it's
written.  Ketchup VIP
was born,
and that character doesn't really belong in Shio-chan's
pancake game,
but the 4-order cake
looks delicious, and even if I say apple based on its appearance,  The
pie looks delicious,
so it's a losing streak
rme Well, it's definitely delicious.It's also delicious.I'm
eating it with Hydrophobic Lois.There's
not a bit of purulence either.Everyone must have
thought it looked delicious while looking at this picture.She's already a
baby, right?
Skin, etc.
Wow, there's something I want to talk about about how stepmothers were good in the Middle Ages.
Well, I'm going to use a little English from here,
but I
wonder if I can wipe it off if I can hear it.
Movement
4-way
[Music]
Reverend 4 Badge Dig Dig
yasai
web menus Peace Aogei over
Attached Da Rua Nnu Game
Give Away
5 Face 4 Pre Heal Immediately Automatic Part
Attached Cup Less Carrying Hole Nyain
Green Spy Page Is Like Shoes
Highest Present Minute EU Outside
Speed ​​Statute See  Enza's
really serious about beats.Regional width part is Osu and Kiura's crap.It
's a
recipe book.Recipe burger
Let's make it together in the cageThat's
right.No
seriously, that looks delicious.Yeah, I'm
sure Chiara is into that recent dish.
Personally, I'm addicted to it, but I can't find any recipes for it in the book,
so
I'd really like to use it as a reference, but I'm asking you to
make some bread molds.So I
'll tell you how to participate now,
haha.  campsite space
a
char ustr par in pearl
trente
regenerate
hommes wish fundis good n
ore fa part a moment
form this good
no finger
spar the keyword of 1cm of contact item
is the back nine muinese ah bandanaa
kocchi buhui arrival  Yes,
yes, post nb 8 b, female tee,
5 ines pipe pack, now, 1st ward, I'm
pretty media, reverse one-two & size
fan, oh no, that child's Negoho,
3255 chicks, one for each five, I
'll finish it off.  I'll give it to you, please come
and join me.I'm
from the applife armee group and I'm going to star in the cap according to the schedule. s
renda some
elf full seg to
donda
rendered to do for
body name bos pains 4 seus
uh
ore to
do Actually, I want to make and eat this dish in real life.  Now
that I look at that experience level, I
'm worried about what Mr. Booth will be like.
No, the breakup is sour.
Now that I'm done with my mother, I'm going to close my c1000 playlist.
Hello, I mean, it's not just in my head.
Well then.  But I think it's absolutely delicious, so I
hope everyone will continue to read it. So
yeah, I've
reached the last book, so sma-senpai,
if you have any final comments, please feel free to do so.
Uemura
makes a lot of appearances, including Arthur, but what did he eat? The
contents of the octopus are real, and that girl isn't
even there. What's more, it
's because that festival happened during Tales.  I heard that you've had sex with boys.
Well, cda, I tried to shut up. I'm a
fan. I'm
a little more concerned about it, but my ovaries. Hey, it
sure looks spicy and I want to eat spicy
food. I don't like wash food, so I
don't eat funky food.
Wow, that's better than not eating him.
Thank you very much for talking so much about Nea no Teruzo today. The
9 schools that you created were so much fun.  I haven't had
anyone to talk to about my love for the Fields, so it
was fun. Thank you Hoshi, it was fun. Let's
talk about the Tataman Nantan Buildings. Let's talk about the Nantan Buildings,
Gakusawara City, Yasuya. Also, if a new one
comes out, let's do something together.  Let's look forward to the
10 dials
a
favor It seemed to fit
anode The degree is fashion unknown
but winter is s 5 Genuine
Gupper Water-saving senior so aop Safe
That's what you say you
do for s Copy you do
Cure Wing Smile  Scoopbirdway
Way Week 5 BRB PHIL
WOOD
AS Check
EHREN Superchen
4 A
Sucking light bulb and woman is Pass sparrow
tile  In the middle of the game park
[Music]
Standing
Awayama Hachin Business Department Oil Painting s Two Candidates Luna
is Bar s Wrapping Aboism Make Tech
Charwork Tuwa to Finn Weiner Boda
Ah Aya Uta Fortune Seasar es is Palo
Spray Meter and 4 Beret Jaan  No. 4
Tate Ah,
well, that's
all I can say, and there's a little more information from here,
so please stay.
Okay, Soarn, I'm
troublesome. I
have an iPhone. This point b,
Appelthorpe, ok, Skewer,
Nyan de Rossi, Herbert pad fee.  Kun
code male japan 2 is Che
wi-fi
When I found out that Kessler existed, I
said that I was disappointed that I couldn't go to Japan and see it,
but I
was like, Wow, move!
[Music]
me
N
aime
ni
dare
[Music]
[Applause]
ni se patch
parte f 2 re
releases day is chain
surf cast completed
anatano ash ie
ester vienna spec spec iijunsu arm ryukin cheke betube fu
Yasui urine with
asain dx 2 p 2 e 4
Avatar Uuuuhu Fanouf is an anti -ah, oh, a
former bar of the concept, and
Lydia is already like a spy.
Pink Pan Sweeters
Ferrocene funny Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa 3: MUCH
nostalgic songs are played that nostalgic songs are being played.  You
can actually see it now
minister minister
es 04 Adorable is branch 4 Moe
in the 5 passboa
Umm
a
sonota King Arthur mo Dry 2
Mention
Denso Mominamiya ask web Application
minute device ios so fa color
Dondon 4 days Bye  wither
raging backpack nets ah ah
won go for x ga
to do
sasoon moon baldy
fixspim nf 4 min
open [ __ ] 2 e 0
gold chain download betsey
42 minute device sss soccer
teyozousshissukasho games and web
Wow smart mu character
sah it's a mortal good
a yes
big story truth
there's a lot of stories
uhhhhh
it's a contested char sentence no no no sono furufure the
cup is the spirit of the Edo medicine way
jaaah wipe for me watch masunai
to do after sound  That's
right our story lampard
teruzo
a office shop iometer
roughing uniform goods my truth
i feel fine editors
bower an eye where
wso catchphrase
case alea
boreal
pou
dou
dou light rain amazing Yami Daiginfu power
game Wing Scopia  A challenge
parfait Niku Mine funny usb North
32nd place Nets Patt Gya
already cooking Is it one thing to stream since I was doing Anshin Raku? I
thought I should make a recipe for Taser life I want to eat it
and plum  DARSHAN
OP Goods Cosmetics Susa Ah, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, wake -up of Wegen
Can Do Do Me Qui Wife and
Conspiracy IS NEED YOU SO A FUNNY Ah
s enjoy It's a little childish,
Fenkubel Town 4 is Chen Yong,
public sounds and regular Goto-kun are more than this,
but I feel like you enjoyed it.Dual
xeon
e're senior big c
please  refer Muoh Moss Throne
Terrence
Correa and Proglide Power
Birdy Scarface I Scenery 1 pt
Scoop
Bought
nonbe
good rimi r 4 n d e
x Plain Dinner Show Window A
[Music]
render Armor web Plain
sa bar to do my bag
That's the study site par  as i can
see voice ono zu local web
press ntp 6 s 10th
Bryce Pension
Twings Okay, Reardonff
getta tareas retro
opc piece for
peace fife ft s 1
tik tox
sx xbox
sender
dynamic makeup change 1
ana b zaku s female spy  2
surf
Poi,
Sonja, that rice turn the
warlord
Urabuide, blame it on Enju
Aaah, feeder's winter
was a hindrance to strengthening in s too, let's meet tomorrow
oh baby floor special,
Hihara-chan's side,
asg is.  Yay this year 6 e-fair p 2
will be here
[applause]
[music]
hmm
me
[music]
hmm
no me
[music]
hmm
boohoo
[music]
voodoo hmm
Min
[Music]
N
Boof
[Music]
N
me
Hmm Boo
Hoo Woo
me Yeah
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuu
me
voodoo
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu nature type character
type to form  Attached n
[Music]
Yeah
me
me yeah
yeah
[Music]
Hoop
Uuuuun
Hmm
me
[Music]
Uuuuuu
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu yui nyan
play to your needs
ani
me
technique n
boouuuuuu
Uuuu
udun
us career woman's tar e to
do
[music]