[Music]
foreign
so
[Music]
so someone asked
in the chat if i'm selling my sword
and i don't think so i think it's a
reference to
you guys saying that my sword looks like
a popsicle
so i guess we're selling popsicles
[Laughter]
yay well i mean it's a cute dessert idea
otherwise we would only have like the
main dishes like burgers
and yeah now we have popsicles
[Music]
it's not a popsicle it's a sword
i'm on his side with this one but okay
[Music]
this is such a cute loading screen
so cute i'm gonna wait a little bit
longer than usual
just so that more people that come in
later see the opening
look at this beauty dakuma made it for
me
thank you so much
[Music]
ice candy sword
you guys are look so busy in the
background
everyone's running around panicking
and i have a large number nine
[Music]
oh oh has everyone seen the intro
now this will be a new intro
no more no more of this i mean that was
cute and i put a lot of uh
a lot of effort into it i drew the
character
myself
[Music]
i drew it and kelly animated it but
unfortunately
i got a little bit um tired of it
so from now on we have this one but i
like how dakoma
implemented the whole design of uh
of this store and made this look uh very
similar and also the kfb logo
which is not really an official logo
it's something
it's just a font that has some fire
on it that i wanted to use i want i one
day i want a proper logo
um but yeah for now
i'm still using this which i guess it
looks like a logo somehow sometimes
simple logos are fine right
logo contest oh should i do that
[Music]
yes new intro okay i think now everyone
has seen it so we should move over
[Music]
okay okay okay
are we ready to move over
look ma i'm on the screen
yeah it's you guys working
so if okay imagine this
your mom wants you to help her
cooking or something or your
girlfriend or boyfriend wants you to
come over
and you need an excuse
and i'm streaming right now then you can
tell them
oh i'm working right now and
if i'm really streaming at that moment
and if i'm in the loading screen you can
send them that and you can point out
where you are you can say hey i'm
working right now
[Music]
look at this stream you can obviously
see
i'm working right now i cannot help you
with your cooking or anything at all
sorry this is my life now
but you're on mama oh
interesting
so when i tell you to come watch my
stream and you
need an excuse to not watch my stream
you come to my stream
and and show me that you are working
here in my loading screen
[Music]
inception
i played this game i bought it and i
played it
one time i didn't even play it off
stream i played it one time on stream
and back then i did plan to play it more
often because i wanted to get that
chicken costume
i wanted that chicken costume and i had
apparently back then i had 21 days
time to get it well
i never got it and
i think i i felt a little bit nostalgic
so i checked back
on that stream that we did that i did
back then how many months is it ago now
is it four months ago
i know
so i felt nostalgic and i checked that i
couldn't watch much of it because it's
just uh
it feels very cringy for me to watch my
especially my old streams
but um i don't know for the people who
don't remember for the people who
weren't there
my debut was like at 10 p.m
japanese standard time 10 p.m
and before me was cali i think at 8 00
pm
so it was cali i watched that then it
was me
10 p.m for one hour and then after that
there was like a four or five hour break
until the next
debut from ena by the way there's no
music oh my god
wait a second um so i was like okay i
can't watch those unfortunately i can't
watch any of those
so hopefully wait did you hear that no
you didn't hear that
hopefully um i can sleep but i
after my w i was still so nervous
okay you can hear that okay i was still
so nervous
after my debut that i tried to sleep for
a few hours and i couldn't fall asleep
even after my debian was too
la so i stayed up all night
ended up watching everyone's debuts as
well
uh and then stayed up all night sit up
all morning
and then after everyone had their debut
uh
we did a collaboration stream at like i
think it was like 12
like 11 a.m or 12 p.m something like
that
right or when around one time i think it
was something like that
and then we so after that i was like
okay in between i'll be sleeping
obviously so i can schedule a stream
my first stream after my debut right
after the collab
it will be fine that's what i thought so
i i i had it like at
um 2 p.m i had the fall guys stream
scheduled or animal crescent goddammit
i told you this will happen often now
uh so yeah were you guys even listening
to what i'm telling you
you were listening okay okay okay let me
put that there
so that you guys shut up about it
and where was i though now this got me
out of the loop
oh yeah oh yeah so my first stream after
pulling an all-nighter
after my debut was this and
i was
i was very tired but after starting the
game
i i lost my sense of tiredness
and then and then and then i i don't
know
i i was really really really bad at the
game
and it was very frustrating i was really
bad i was so bad but it was funny and it
was weird
and yeah my friendly streams diapers
they helped me
they helped me try to get up uh like
some
cliffs is that really not not even a
cliff
i remember you almost free up really did
i feel sick
i was not i was not in a good day
you know i was
it was it was um yeah i just thought
that i
i i i could sleep after my stream but
the problem is i
was not able to sleep i was i was too
panicked still so we are challenging
fall guys again
i'm sorry i changed my plan i was
supposed to play
minecraft today earlier today but that
didn't work out can we get the old mic
back
the old microphone yeah that was also
i mean back then i didn't think it was
that bad and i still don't really think
it's that bad but it's kind of a big
difference to what we have now
and the the the microphone back then had
like some kind of
weird echoes going on anyway
um we're gonna get back into this
there is no more chicken costume i think
no more no more chicken costumes
oh
[Music]
let's go i'm still playing with keyboard
by the way i played one test round it
worked
okay um i forgot how i know how to
jump and i know how to like whoosh
but how do you grab again
use the front control it'll be fine it
will be fine it will be fine it will be
fine
you only have one crown
[Music]
i didn't i only played this game once
yes
[Laughter]
tilt control shut up no what what is it
really how do you craft
control is much better oh whatever links
click
ah is it left click right click is
grabbing
what for real
left click okay okay okay so all i need
is like
the move around buttons the space button
the e button
and left click right okay we should be
able to do that
and i feel like when i play a test round
before this
one test round
it was all right i would i did not get
in
i did not get to the goal but i i i got
far enough that's cute
the stages are so cute stay to kawaii
wait guys don't bully me okay i still
need some i need some time to get used
to this
okay okay okay okay nice up until here
i'm i'm one of the leaders
but yeah but i don't see [\h__\h] i don't
see it
the stages are so cute
can you stop oh my god whoa wow
get some punches
okay oh my god that's a oh
well maybe we should go down what's down
here i've seen this stage never before
oh should i have not gone down here
i don't oh well no that's fun are you
waiting for me
if you want to help me that's okay but
wait what's going on here
oh should i have jumped oh
stop please go move
mom oh it's so pretty
[Music]
i did that to myself you can't stop me
from winning
oh my god
last time they helped me
please let me always move
oh dude
it's cute it's orange has socks on it i
like socks
i think they stopped you from winning
i'm still winning because yes this is
cyber bullying
i will report it to the police
is japanese right now but i think you
get the gist of it
i think i think my steam is set to
japanese i think
also by the way we will only be playing
this for one hour and afterwards i'll be
reading uh
she's like but she doesn't know it what
i tell my life but she doesn't know it
what what was i just saying uh
he will call the cyber police no i will
call the real police i was thinking i
was gonna i'm only gonna do this for one
hour and then i really
really will read super chats
i got some catching up to do and i want
to catch up before the stream of armor
tomorrow
oh i think this is a first
time for me as well i didn't even try
the second season either good luck
thank you i'm getting bullied
if you guys wanna bully me i will drag
you all into the same misery
so good luck with that i will drag you
into my misery
i'm in the business of misery let's take
it from the top she's got a body like an
hourglass it's sticking like a clog it's
a matter of time before they all run out
when i thought it was mine she got him
by the map
i waited eight months she finally set
him free i told him i couldn't lie he
was the only one for me
to explore caught on fire started out
for me but i want a bigger smile
i'll stop there i'll stop there
oh we did it kiara's singing her own
songs lol
are you saying i'm haley williams i like
that
i like that way of thinking
we did it why is my name special snoring
feast by the way
what is that name i saw there was like
an update that people
don't get the steam names anymore
but they get like randomly thrown
together names now
weird but okay
that that was paramore by the way oh i
i sang that song before in one of my
unarchived karaoke streams
in my boomer cuddle yeah you can change
it
is it like you got like more options to
choose from later on
or do you have only options now that one
looks fairly easy
could it come down sort on it ah wait no
i i don't
i didn't play this one before i never
played this one before
boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
boom boom going wow
uh i'm going for this one hell yeah
hey i'll also this round doesn't have as
many
[\h__\h] snipers
that drag me into their misery
that's exactly what i was talking about
i'm dragging you into my misery if you
try
top fifty percent of what's going on but
this is i didn't practice since the last
time we played this so this is
already a huge huge difference maybe it
was really just the lack of sleep
now after four months now i'm a gamer
now i've been a get a girl all along i'm
sitting on a
pink gamer girl chair that's really cute
i'm looks actually feeling quite sad
that i have to leave
the chair behind because i don't think i
can bring it to australia
but it's really cute because it has like
a uh
um sakura design on it like a a
a cherry blossom petal design
it's like only sold in japan
that doesn't make you get of course game
of girl chairs makes me gamer
also oh [\h__\h] oh my god
okay i'm probably not gonna go uh and
win this one unfortunately
[Music]
but but but i'll get an a for effort
right
this is my first time i've never seen
this map before all of these maps i've
never seen before
i like how it's also so wintery
goddammit
i should have probably not not uh oh no
oh no
oh no oh no
i stopped at the
[Music]
no i still have a chance how do you get
faster here
no no no
[Music]
oh
are those people waiting for me just to
push me off the edge
go away what the [\h__\h] is that
you know one guys i have one thing to
say to you
for just looking there and and not
helping me oh my god oh my god
[Music]
i will not say it i will keep it for
next time
all of these stages are the first time
for me but we made it pretty far
we made it pretty far
[Applause]
i want it it was scent
nameplate sure where does it go
okay wait
ah it's like all covered up from that
stupid oops
are you for real did you just buff a
book at me
oh wait is that your pose
poser
okay i thought that was just too weird
to actually really happen
okay i'll go naked i don't want a skirt
though i do want a cute skirt
this girl reminds me of a tina for some
reason
okay wait no i want this
that looks like really really stupid i
want more outfits
to see
actually it does look kind of cute
it does look kind of cute
[Laughter]
in this louis vuitton pattern wait what
that on the skirt no that's just stars
the pattern is similar no it's not no
it's not i think it i think there's
something else going on in my brain it
reminds me of
innas you know papa's um
other characters that he designed the
skirt shape
remind i don't know what i'm talking
about i don't even know anymore
i remember this being your first stream
exactly
and i have definitely improved since
then even though i haven't even played
it
[Music]
since then abigail williams yeah
probably or hokusai i don't know which
one
they remind me this reminds me of but
some reason it reminds me of some of
them
your first dream was your daddy are you
smart ass i know
the first stream after my dab before
god's sake oh god this one
i i did this one um as a test
before my stream and i failed miserably
at this
part in the middle i i i don't
know
how do you get through there no like
like a normal person this is going to be
rough
this is going to be rough guys
this level excuse my rudeness but our
happy is this
not only difficult for me is it also
difficult for you guys
[Music]
oh no this is a horrible level
oh no oh oh yes oh no
[Applause]
difficulties are you trying to say this
is the most difficult
oh hi survive
what are you doing what are you doing
oh i thought he was like kind of
chilling there and waiting for me but
that's probably just a nobody
but at least that that green dude is
probably about as [\h__\h] as me
so that makes me happy go away no no no
no no are you making fun of me
okay it's okay we can do it just gotta
be smart oh yeah oh yeah next one nice
one nice one stop making fun of me guys
don't make fun of me i am not
i am not who you think i am
oh yeah nice oh wow okay so but here the
problem is here
i will die a million times
if it's not the the the rolling thingies
then it's the holes that get me like
everything here is just wait did that
person copy my style this dude with the
skirt
oh my god oh my god i made it through
here okay now this is
yeah baby
i need a checkpoint
but if all those viewers wait for me
over there
then this could go on forever oh [\h__\h]
what the hell was that i wanted to go
now i don't have time for this
no this is not just like the first
stream this is better than the first
stream
but
i still [\h__\h] oh my god no no no
oh oh yes roll over me
[Laughter]
now this this stage is just horrible i
can't do it
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm not the only person over here
except that snowman all these people
waiting for me
well i won't make it did you see that
was like at least 20 people waiting for
me
see it was 49 out of 43 that could have
been more people that
to make it through that round but these
people prefer to wait for me
than to actually go through the
finishing line
ridiculous oh [\h__\h] i didn't press it
press else god damn it
let me press escape
i want to escape
but i'm i'm glad
uh like even if i would have made it for
that middle part
the people who are waiting over there at
the finishing line they would have
killed me
they would have they would have mobbed
me and bullied me
to death let me escape
i wish i could have made it up until
here
oh but this is still this is a difficult
one magic relaxing fish
okay bye bye let's go
do me mean they say to what she suffers
it must have been funny yeah
it must have been funny to watch me like
that hashtag bring back old mike
i am not going to do that it's so
annoying to set it all up again
so no thank you
last time i played this everyone was
helping me now i don't know what they
what they're trying to do
just add an echo to the mixer that's
right
ah but
it was like only like every once in a
while it was like a weird echo
it's like a curse echo pickle
right
i don't know where that i still up until
this day i still don't know where that
came from
i still don't know
that it was it wasn't really an echo
either yeah
something weird was going on back then
your first life's voice your voice was
too gladly for the mic to handle it
thank you oh let's see did we do well on
this one the first time oh yeah we did i
think
okay oh oh [\h__\h] stop touching me
stop touching me stop touching me stop
touching me stop touching stop
stop okay decide for one side
[Music]
i want to report i wish you could report
bullying in this game
i mean people would probably use that
too often oh come on
come on just open
open the door
open open up and quickly wow
click it out of there you're not okay
next round we'll make it in but it's
definitely i don't know i don't know how
howard was so chaotic the last time i
played this game
how was it so chaotic last time
i mean i had to figure out the controls
first and i think i think you guys gotta
give me some credit for that
and because once i got the controls
right that it wasn't that bad anymore
even with my lack of sleep
okay um stop spamming
i will bunk you into infinity
nancy you gotta unleash your german
prowess to win
ah yesterday
be
uh
okay
i still need to do a german only stream
eventually
[Music]
started streaming i was actually
chilling in soda senpai's uh
fall guy stream i was chilling in her
stream
guys read the goddamn rules is it so
hard to read
i don't i don't understand
some of you guys just ignore the rules
please read the rules i will bonk you
[Music]
sold out senpai so
oh damn it i wish i could have stayed
longer with her
oh damn it oh damn it oh damn it
let me let me talk some i don't know
real accent
what accent is this maybe this accent
will make me better
go oh [\h__\h] i fell down again oh my god
can you [\h__\h]
lauren stop touching me i'm an adult
move get out of the way mo
mo am i scott scotland
person uh is it is it scotland
the the place where you ate this weird
thing called like something like haggins
or i don't know why
it's like someone's um i don't even want
i don't even want to describe it but
it's horrible
i think i mean the imagination of it is
horrible
but hot hoggies is that really egg
well that's disgusting i'm sorry but i
don't want to eat it
it's haggis and it's delicious well i
apologize i will never try
thank you for the membership
what you think about my accent i hope
you don't want me to do that more often
oh no um should i should i
do i want this to push yes i want it
is
okay this is how we this is how we get
rid of those
we filter those got them stream snipers
i hope they're gone now problem is a lot
of you are really good at this game
oh no a group game no i don't want to be
in a group of people
no just like back in school i'll be
horrible okay what do we do ah
close the balls over to the other side
okey dokey
probably something like that oh but i'll
probably not
help much but i mean i will try but i
don't think i'll be much of a help
what am i doing though what
do i want them to be on my side oh wait
i want it to be a mice
i want the balls to be blue oh
oh that's not quite the soccer that i
know
see okay guys i can't even help you
because people are bullying me
this is this dragon dragon dude is like
following me
or dinosaurs or dinosaur dude
thank you dude
okay i'm absolutely contributing nothing
i i hate you so much i hate you so much
i i can't help i can't help
i literally can't tell goddammit no
overtime red has five balls
damn son
red do you not want to help your goddamn
team
do you really not want to help your team
it's fun to snipe but um it's not so
much fun
when you're 100 focusing on stopping me
from playing the game
and damn it i missed the escape
goddammit
try hiding the stream when you're
clearing up i feel like they'll still
make it in
they'll still make it in
is it fairly easy to make it in
especially now let me try though
uh
i mean won't you won't you hear it
though
wait i have to wait though
yeah with how long the queueing is i
feel like you guys would
figure it out
boom anyways
[Music]
well yeah that's too much effort
there's a super test in between i can't
multitask like that
i cannot multitask that much
silence
painful mm-hmm
i don't think this helps at all but oh
well
that's okay though because uh we
should see it takes so much time anyway
[\h__\h] it um
we we will only be doing this for 15
more minutes anyway and after we read
some super chats
silence asmr no no no no silence here
also guys the mouse people came and they
they blocked the whole very nicely
and casper has been real quiet
passport has been real quiet i asked i
asked the professional
i told him that casper has been so quiet
and if that's because it's winter or
something
if he's saving his energy and he was
like no
uh he probably felt like a different
spot a different
house uh and is just like living in two
houses now and just you know
that's probably why he's not around much
anymore
especially if that hole is closed now
which is good to be honest
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
i don't want to go back no no that's not
how it is that's not
oh my oh my oh my oh my god oh
[Music]
oh my god i'm doing wonderfully i'm one
of the first ones
[Music]
nice so top 50 percent wow
okay that went well let's hope that the
next round
will not be a too difficult stage
[Music]
japanese viewers saying that i'm a
completely different person when i speak
japanese for
because my personality changes
[Music]
oh no and is that another team oh but
two teams what
team what we have to do
what what do we do what what do we do
not even i don't know
what what do we do is it the one of the
rings where you have to jump through oh
wait what's going on what are we doing i
don't see any rings though
[Music]
don't get tagged oh oh no it's that dude
again
wait what is going on i don't understand
i don't understand what am i even
supposed to do
please team yellow please please
i don't know what to do okay you know
what i'm not even gonna try i'm gonna
stop here
i hope it's fun i hope you're having fun
guys
[Applause]
if you if you
what do i do
what is it what is it
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
i understand it's a grabbing game but
have you noticed that two people
continued to stay right on my side and
to stop me from moving the whole time
that's not just random players
that's snipers targeting me
to a point where it's not funny
i mean usually i enjoy you guys
when you guys are stream sniping like in
sliver dot io
or mario kart and all that
but in this game it's cancer
it's freaking cancer
hmm
i'm like number one right
oh my god
messed up my perfect run my perfect
salty run
oh no wow that's fun
you know one of my friends recently did
uh
bungee jumping i want to do that too
oh my gosh
yeah [\h__\h] off guys bye bye sayonara
queen of style no
want to jump in that scary yeah i i
would probably
pee myself um
but it's one of the things i do want to
try
i do want to try that i want to try
bungee jumping
i don't meet him yourself yeah um
i don't go to the toilet but i do pee
myself when i'm too scared just kidding
just kidding uh skydiving
yeah one of those would be fun
yeah that is good
that is getting clipped i know it well
what can't you fly well
not in my current form and my papa won't
let me transform so that's a little bit
of a problem unfortunately
if i could transform i could become my
original phoenix form what is this i've
never seen this one before
the first time but we're going downwards
and at the end you just fall in there i
mean that seems
easy enough wait are we just like eye
sliding
pretty much like sliding with our bodies
no okay
oh my god this is funny
real hard there
my head hurts no okay that was
on me that was on me oh
what
you don't just fall need to fall in
there
where do i have to go excuse me
it's a score oh
but i didn't make it right
yeah boy
a message well thank you for the red
super chat
no that's not really much of a message
but thank you
yeah that was a that was an okay run
that was an okay run
the first one was uh
the first round was pretty good i was i
was number one for most of the time
[Music]
just run okay no problem wait did i do
this one before
uh yeah wait that's all that's the one
where i was doing so well yeah
okay okay okay
oh wait okay i'll show you again what i
can do i'll show you what i can do
yeah probably will fail really hard
right now
[Music]
okay okay we're filtering through
nice soup
the timing was kind of up there i think
that in the first one the timing was
so good that i just had to run through
i know i wanted to fly okay i'm gonna go
for the middle
didn't get the [\h__\h] so well
why wait are you waiting for me
[Applause]
no no no no wait i can do it
wait that was smart of me
oh
[Music]
what is she doing
one more one more one more one more one
more one more
one more
when you got to it zach because it
worked fine in the middle the first time
[Music]
you jinxed yourself yeah
no no not one more hour no no no no i
wanna get
get uh done today before midnight if
possible
with the super chats as well because
i need to um make a thumbnail and stuff
with a stream of ammo
which will by the way i think will be on
both channels
and um we decided on what to play but i
want to have a last
last minute check with ahmed she's
really fine with it
i know a lot of you guys are really
really wondering what we're going to
play
oh no not this one
[Applause]
oh no oh no this
is this person waiting for me
leave me alone leave me alone
is there any side that's better i wonder
it has less of these
okay oh no
okay i'm focusing i'm focusing i'm
focusing
thanks for waiting guys as long as you
are not gonna grab on to me
then everything's cool but this part i
can never get this part right
[Music]
okay so someone do it do it for me like
um show me how
no no no no no no no oh no
someone show me how you doing let me let
me walk right next to you
if only the gold was closer
if only the gold would have been there
i've actually made it through it
which was the biggest miracle
[Music]
at the end i just was like whatever i'm
just gonna
try to run as far on the edge as
possible
what a pointless effort
[Music]
this is this is this is the this is the
last one
this is really the last one
all right bossy scottish was pure green
oh thank you
thank you for the super chat it was it
disappeared too fast
it disappeared too fast
by the way is this like putting me
together with people
uh all over the world or is this is far
guys grouping people from the same like
country together
unless you change your ip
chocolate
original ow
but japanese stream snipers are usually
um not as bad as that
uh godzilla that was um bullying me
so i don't think that that was anyone
from japan
oh [\h__\h] wait is good
okay i'm gonna go over here i choose you
[Applause]
okay
i failed way more often previously
okay too many people here
that was nothing that was not any
language by the way
if you guys are trying to translate what
i'm saying
i didn't say anything oh hey we are
falling behind by a lot
but the difficult part isn't even this
it's not even that it's what comes after
this
what are you doing what are you doing
why no no no no
no no no
[Music]
we still okay a chance i think there's
wait there's so many people waiting for
me to decide with like the glimpse of my
eye but i'm busy right now
i can't really appreciate it okay hi
guys
okay now are you gonna teach me how to
do it
[Applause]
okay yolo
okay okay that was not the right yellow
there's a there's a certain type of yolo
that
[Music]
yes
i really have to clean up my my this
this part when i
come here before i come here
the the stamps always play automatically
us well that was that um
i hope you guys enjoyed that
[Music]
a bit nostalgic i'm remembering the good
old times thanks nate oh thank you where
you participating
weren't you participating wasn't me
are you battling me you better
don't touch me you for the stream 10 joe
no thank you
cool yeah today a little bit of a
shorter stream because we have
some super chats to read and where did
we stop last time does someone know
do you do you guys want big big ten show
today
do you guys want close ghost and chill
[Music]
yo what's
white potential is a rare pokemon
doesn't come that easily
[Music]
it doesn't come that easy
he made some some really cute animations
like gifts before one i think i
retweeted yesterday thank you guys for
the memberships
i retweeted them yesterday i think the
one with the with the cat ears and where
i'm like
on the hot chocolate okay do we have to
read anything before
among us or does it start from among us
i think i have to start it among us
yeah yeah i think so or did i read
you finished the mangas oh
i only oh i don't i read the manga super
jets
[Music]
really
really amazing
okay if you guys say so
is it only is it only animal crossing
[Music]
ah and i mean we could read the ones
from the hot chocolate one
i don't have a thumbnail for that but i
will hereby declare that i'm reading the
hot chocolate super chats now
[Music]
that was a really short video and you
guys squeezed in some
super chats thank you next up this one
isn't the art so cute
[Music]
um
where do i put it here
[Music]
the person uh who drew that was really
happy that i used
uh the art it makes me happy when the
artists are happy that i'm using their
artist
you're gonna
it's a win-win situation i use the art
that you guys make for me
and it it makes my thumbnails more
interesting and you guys are happy when
i use them that's wonderful
yes okay reading super chats from the
animal crossing stream from yesterday
that was fun
um i played uh all night
[Music]
so now um i just finished building
uh the museum is finished the the little
store is finished
and i'm just build i just finished
building the three houses
so tomorrow i'll get some of my first
villagers moving in
i time skipped like uh three days
got a problem with that
and did you organize all your stuff um
a lot of it there's still a lot of stuff
laying around but most of it
i was able to
wha what was what's with animal crossing
free houses what
oh
because no it's not a fire emblem
reference it's just because
uh at the beginning at the beginning of
animal crossing
um before new people move in uh tom nook
gives you a mission
to build three houses
animal crushing free houses
[Music]
that sounds like a nice crossover
that sounds like a good crossover it's
very very very fitting actually
i love that
thank you for the stream kiana no thank
you
[Music]
is that why you had the axe out
yesterday i don't know what you're
talking about
who you're gonna side with tom nook red
or blabbers
i don't know who red is oh by the way
yesterday i was surprised because i
i told you guys i haven't played it for
such a long time and there's been so
many updates since then
but yesterday i was just i i received a
bed
in the mail from luna
and it's like a really pretty bag i
guess everyone gets that in the
beginning so i put it in my room
and then i just wanted to like lay down
on it
and suddenly i'm in some kind of dream
world i'm like what and what what what
that's new right when did they add that
feature where you go in some kind of
dream world where you can
visit other people's like islands
dream bad they edit that over the summer
oh that's quite a while ago
[Music]
is that different from just visiting
someone's world with a mild ticket
how is that different i don't know i
don't quite understand because i didn't
really give it a try
is it just random islands
is it is it completely it's more static
than busy than normally
you aren't actually there it's just
looking at the random islands
the host doesn't have to be online
uh-huh
so it's just looking at them walls are
just floors but verticals what
what
you can't pick anything and the island
is frozen on time oh interesting
but is that random or can you choose
which island you're visiting
[Music]
is it random people from all over the
world or is it your friends or
either it's random it should be
cold
[Music]
your thumbnail is about fallout with you
to play it i just finished
you are late but i'm going to read super
chat now
okay let's get started
and harbor line that question oh thank
you for the red super challenge
power line says
time to simple spells along with real
cash money it's a worthy cause for our
kfb honey get the wallets out
gents you best be well prepared it's
animal crossing time be there we'll be
spare
[\h__\h] up be there or be square
nice one i like i like the
i like the cash money in this one time
to simple spells along with real cash
money it's a worth because for our kfp
honey get the ones out gents you best be
well prepared it's animal crushing time
be there will be square
oh i didn't [\h__\h] up this time
oh yeah dropping the vines with the help
of power line
harbor light how about we team up you
right you ghost right
raps for me and we'll just act as if i
wrote them
i'll pay you and then i battle callie
then i'll have a rap battle with kelly
i wanted to battle cali with raps
but i can't think of good stuff myself
i need you i need you
it's
[Music]
this would have been a red super chat
but you didn't add marshmallow cream top
into your hot chocolate what do you eat
in the
side with chocolate anyways what does
that question mean
what what does that question mean i
don't get the question but
i genuinely never add marshmallow
to my hot chocolate i would i would add
um
cream to it
uh wait what's it called whipped cream
that i like to add but marshmallow is
nah
[Music]
nah but cali likes to add marshmallows i
know that
we went shopping the other day and she
bought a hot chocolate
mix with marshmallows and she was really
really really um eager to get the
marshmallows
gasp
whipped cream on hot chocolate yeah it's
nice it melts away anyway so it just
mixes in
oh really you didn't get a kiss for a
red super shot really
you sent the red secret i don't even
remember but i will trust you because uh
you beat my kfb employees don't lie to
me
so i will trust you
thank you sorry for not seeing it before
sorry but maybe maybe i gave you
something else maybe i slapped you maybe
i've
to you which maybe you deserved
who knows who knows
well i need kiara ah thank you
i need you too
chase it
[Music]
okay there's been one person asking me
to ban him
since one hour why
[Music]
i just wanna know why
why
now i will
i will on on purpose
i will not do you the favor i will not
ban you and i will hopefully torture you
by not banning you so that you have to
keep on spamming and wasting your time
you're welcome
that's the life that you chose for
yourself
[Music]
oh my god um
i don't i don't i don't like the hashtag
or be scared because
the hashtag you added in your text i'm
not gonna read this thing
i think you guys should think you guys
should change the hashtag
casper duncashim
hi canada
i wanted to turn up i wanted to turn on
my pitch
my pitch effect and but when even when i
do that
i i changed my voice to make it sound
even more higher like casper like
automatically
and for a moment
did you notice that the the slight
change of my
own pitch without using the actual or
where's my pitch started there it is
okay
i forgot to tell you my uncle gave me a
basket full of pancake toys
oh my god guys
i'm gonna cry casper you are the
sweetest
the sweetest character existing in the
kfb universe i
want i want there to be a fan fiction
and written about you
casper and his adventures something like
that oh my god
that goes on
looks really similar to me almost like
twins and he told me he would be nice
but i've been hearing some stories
casper please come back casper please
come back i don't want i don't want
jasper i will kill him i will burn
him down even if it means i have to burn
down this house
i thought casper was here not some
freaking dude that's imitating you
casper no for real though someone write
a
like a like a manga or a fanfiction
about casper please thank you
if you need some ideas hit casper up uh
i'm sure he will help you writing
oh no jasper is writing his super chat
[Music]
oh boy oh
i burp wait but i did like a cute voice
with a weird accent right or burp i
hear casper's been asking you miss about
me now don't go telling him what i did
caspase
who [\h__\h] his caspers he's a good kid i
told him i'll behave
we want to disappoint the poor boy he
don't need to know
oh yeah it's like the australian casper
sounds like good huh
wait i feel like i can relate to that
like there was maybe a tiniest part with
a lot of imagination that that sounded
like gooda
i kind of i kind of see that
[Music]
but that is so stretched
he's meant to be an italian mobster
i thought it was some kind of nickname
for casper
oh my god i start working right
right away boss okay
oh my god thank you for the red super
chat well have fun
have fun writing dad casper casper's so
cute such a cute personality
well let me read that again though
pete's got a um place by the way welcome
home
cute girl all the rice you can eat what
else could it
ask for maybe um
ah
those are the favorite foods of jasper
i do speak a little bit of italian but
that was just messing around but i do
speak a little bit of italian a little
bit
[Music]
italian
thank you for greeting me so nicely
and in my own language
thank you bronze i'm glad you were there
i don't know if you're here right now
oh thank you wow thank you for always
being there
i appreciate it
[Music]
and one day if bronx lives in the bronx
how do people from the bronx
speak like do they say bronx
yo i'm from the bronx
yo it's kiara from the bronx how do
people in the bronx talk like
a new yorker accent or that's not just
it's literally no what how do new
yorkers talk like it's just
that that is i think normal english to
me
that's not it i know but what do you
know you australian
what do you even know about new york
accents you know
nothing
hey i'm walking here dude
i'm walking here that's just normal
english
that's just normal english
[Laughter]
i've gotta continue
[Music]
oh i can't read this name one second
one second i'll get it to talk yo man
oh my god and translate
[Music]
it
oh don't lie to me you like it don't you
you like it when i use comic sense
[Music]
i found one of the sakura tortoises you
mentioned hard to find but worth it
oh nice
thanks for the recommendation dancer
you're welcome
you're welcome rose gold kami thank you
and looking for the top thank you
john funko's love ski donkey shoulder
blade thank you and jake is monkey
duncan
imagine if casper follows you into the
game too and becomes a villager in your
town
oh yeah i wonder i wonder who my first
three villagers are going
um actually my that's not my first ones
i already have two but like the first
three after that
are moving in soon so i wonder who's
gonna come over
if i'm gonna get one of the really
popular ones or if i'm gonna get one of
the really unpopular ones
um exciting
but i did talk to i did talk to inna
i mentioned to her
i just checked my discord and my manager
sent me i don't know what you're what
are you trying to tell me manager
what are you trying to send me like um
nookiepedia
link to the chicken category
um telling me that there's i know that
there's chickens
in the game i know trying to tell me
that there's
a chicken villagers
i know that there are i mean i wouldn't
mind getting one of them
or two of them in my village
i wouldn't mind getting some burps
but anyway i was actually talking to
inna i'm asking her if she would
be willing to do a animal crossing
collab somehow i
i pitched some ideas to her who can fish
insert special fish here
first or like who gets the insert
desired villager here first challenge
like we both
stream on our channel and like we use my
tickets
and uh to get a specific villager and
whoever gets them first
uh is gonna win but the problem is that
could take like 10 hours
and i don't know if ina is in it for
like a 10 hour collapse
i mean she would i guess that's okay she
would just have to give up she
after three hours she would be like i
couldn't find it
um i guess you win kiara
and i'm like hell yeah i win
i don't yeah i don't think eno can do 10
hour streams
not because she doesn't have the stamina
but more like because she doesn't
she probably doesn't have the time to do
it
win by default
[Laughter]
yeah but i think i think it would be fun
it's like we talked about it yesterday
in the animal crossing stream that there
is not
much you can do collaboration wise for
streams
but these challenges could be an idea
so that might be fun she also doesn't
have stamina
okay well so she doesn't have time and
she doesn't have stamina
sounds like a default win for me
i'll take it
take it oh yeah and i also told her we
could uh
check out everyone's uh villages the
viewers village
uh uh islands together like we could
visit them together i wanted to check
your villages uh your why do i keep on
saying well just
i want to check your islands out by
myself uh
but actually it could be fun to check it
out together with vina
and just raid your uh islands together
well in one way or another we will find
a way
to do a collaboration
[Music]
what are you guys doing with the super
chats are you listening to what i'm
talking about
stop stop flirting
[Music]
the me cooler rest
foreign
[Music]
wait a second one
you changed your name to scoot
what happened very confusing
to change your name why are you screwed
now
of course i would notice it's a bummer
that not every day
is as bright and happy as your
personality but hopefully you streaming
can brighten things up as it does for us
plus you could always play sliver that
ayah with the with us if you need it
thank you that's sweet thank you
thank you what
hopefully you don't run into any jingle
dials in australia
what are jingle dells is that a thing in
australia
what's your favorite villager in animal
crossing oh i don't really have any
favorites but
last time i played my one of my first
villagers was mira
and i really liked her i miss her
[Music]
ah crash bandicoot reference
thank you soon
[Music]
well and you changed your name too
didn't you or did you or have you always
been takamori child
when you say nightmare cali my name is
callie for real
with k the name means hug in my language
oh
nightmare hug ah
that's funny that that's your name but
we would me and kelly wouldn't call our
first child callie
no no no no so you're not our child
don't believe this person razzie doesn't
shooting tv's frank's
yep it would be clara at least that's my
that's my input on that then more
restaurant
muchacho with stun kitchen there are we
wrote thank
i won't be able to watch the next couple
of streams because i'm doing my own
charity 24 hour stream but i'll catch up
on the vlogs thank you
[Music]
those german names like schweinstein
reminds me of now you guys really don't
need to
hear that but i went grocery shopping
before the stream and
i know i i told you guys before i go i
think i think i told you i go to this
supermarket that sells like um a lot of
like
foreign imported foods
so i spent like
almost 90 dollars in my grocery shopping
today
and it wasn't actually that much stuff
but because it's like imported food
partially
it got really expensive i bought like
um like italian salami because uh
there is otherwise not really any salami
in the way that i wanted like
the sliced fin salami
doesn't really exist in japan unless
it's like
imported from italy so that was
expensive then i got some prosciutto
which was also expensive and i got some
uh deutsche flagship which was also
expensive
from germany and i got some
uh some german uh
uh crunchy gherkins
those are really yummy good goodness
also expensive but i don't know i just
feel like really getting that
uh home uh that that taste from home
into my system right now we need some
labor case in japan
there is a i agree with you but there is
already one place that sells
liver quesadilla and liberty's like
sandwiches
in tokyo so if you're actually in tokyo
and you're like desperate for some labor
cases there is a place
it's called konig hmm look it up if you
need it
want me to send some over um i don't
think that's allowed
like you're normally like if you fly
from europe to
japan you're not allowed to bring any
like meat or
cheese or whatever and the other way
around eat
the same thing and i think you need some
kind of special
permission if you actually want to send
meat
from one continent to another it's
literally just
called king yeah in german
but people even have that as their last
name
in germany
[Music]
i want to crack my neck but it's not
working right now
even though it's like there is this
thing it should work
on the other side work damn it yeah
[Music]
number step number one
this
let's get a little bit of a slow mode on
wonderful wonderful
i know
a laughs and member
hell yeah members can't be stopped
[Music]
thought you said australia was fairly
safe from theft but i'm not sure my
bells will be too safe i mean i look
forward to visiting bus
huh i mean obviously you have to come
and give them to me i mean that's up by
the way guys i'm running out of bells
right
right now i'm running out of bills you
guys
can you can you give me some bells like
right now
i need some bells or yeah i mean i mean
i have like
i have like um two million now i think
but
yesterday i had like six million or
something like that but i i'm i'm slowly
running out i don't know i don't know
when my next animal crossing stream will
be
i need some money
yeah i'm spending it on my on my on my
on my house i already have um
three three extra rooms now
[Music]
[Laughter]
hit me up i got you
i might um after this stream i might
hit you guys up on twitter
no no no no no guerrilla animal crossing
but anyone who has money
and presents
but there's still a lot of [\h__\h] laying
around on my island i gotta clean that
up god damn it
okay no it can't it can still wait i can
still wait doesn't have to be right now
i can't i still have some money left
it's okay i'm just feeling like slowly
[Music]
thank you thank you it's just um
it's just kind of weird i i think i have
to
never mind whenever i do it i will let
you guys know on twitter
[Music]
hmm
ah you should expand your inventory i
got it expanded like by one
um the first upgrade i think there's
another upgrade right
i got one upgrade
[Music]
it just feels weird to suddenly randomly
dm you guys out of nowhere i feel like i
have to do like a general tweet before
where i ask you guys to send me
screenshots of what you want to give
me and then like an inventory of how
how much and what it is and then i might
you know
i might slide into your dms but don't
worry it's oh it's all supervised by my
manager
it sounds so good there's no no sketchy
things happening
i just want the money i just want the
money
ah maybe i should maybe i should visit
your
ah maybe maybe i should visit you guys
is that smarter because any of these you
guys can't steal anything from me and i
can only steal from you
[Laughter]
does you not need a supplier ah i'm sure
anna would be happy but
um i think she probably doesn't want to
be as spoiled as me
but if we ever do that uh that challenge
of
who finds this specific um
villager first then we might take some
donations
on mile tickets
isn't it easy to let people go to your
island and drop off 40 items at a time
yeah but then maybe someone will steal
although i
i do think if it's outside of a stream
then people
won't be as like
inclined to steal stuff and troll
you know i think that's probably
definitely uh
the case
spiders one is one is
okay for the museum but i think that
that can't be traded can it
let's stop talking about money guys
[Music]
i think i'm pretty sure now that this uh
um
super chatter japanese super chatter
that sends the the baby stickers with
the
with the that angel sticker baby angel
sticker
that must be the baby that is so dark
and deep the baby died and is sending
me super chat stickers from heaven now
yummy
[Laughter]
oh my god thank you but i'm glad he's
still here
i was gonna be real sad if that baby was
never gonna show up again because that
baby has been around for like
i don't know two months super chatting
every day
always crying it was literally there was
never any text it was always just crying
crying
crying crying crying
[Music]
thank you for all right super chat chill
thank you soon asthma gang sit down deep
breaths what happened there
y'all made the kuda stop could you
please explain what happened when you
sent
i don't remember what happened there
what happened when you sent that
what happened you were talking about you
dancing in 3d and then saying
you'd die from night
[Laughter]
[Music]
maybe i could do like i could dance
while i'm sitting
there is some like i've seen people do
like like
sitting choreographies before
[Music]
thank you for your support yamitakuda
stop virus
i will stay alive i will i will i will i
will totally
i told on on discord we talked about
um rig fit adventure the other day
i think i may ask uh us if if
if it's any good and then me and gouda
replied that it's like really good and
really like fun and motivating
and i told i told amadet
that i i stopped using it a long time
ago
but i will definitely i will definitely
you do
do use it again and do some workout
again so that i will get some stamina
until whenever i get a 3dw
and then she was like yeah right
she knows me too well she doubts that i
will
get started anytime soon forever
she was like yeah that's right kiara
i believe you
hey
[Music]
i've been watching your streams for a
while and i've been thinking about
joining kfb oh wait i read this one
before
okay
i know
[Music]
ah thank you very much
for scout yo scoot thank you very much
for that generous donation thank you so
much
are you i'm not gonna
i'm not gonna say what i was going to
say now
i gotta control myself gotta learn to
control myself
very important thank you as always
you're amazing thank you so much for the
support
thank you deal of 67 thank you soon what
is live thank you soon sir
thank you so much for fantastic
99.99
all the love for school damn
i bet uh what was the other's name was
was it cat i bet cat is getting kind of
jealous at school maybe
maybe some fights are gonna break up
between those two
oh no what if cat kills
scoot what if that happens what i'm
gonna do then
it's gonna just gonna pretend that
nothing happened no i will not let scoot
die
hell no cat is too chill for that i
entered the cat's house today and kat
was like listening to j-pop and like
she actually said that she likes j-pop
i'm like wow that is so specific it's
not pop music it's j-pop wow okay
wow
that was that was interesting but i'm
having
uh definitely a better relationship with
scoots than i'm having
with cats i don't know cats just doesn't
get out of her house yet
scoot is outside the whole time and like
running up to me
um cat is uh still needs some time to
get out of her shell
hentai is vlog thank you so much mwah
thank you soon
and i will totally not
intercept and take this money away uh
before scoot
gets it no no no it will definitely
reach scoot
100 um
just trust in me the money is
getting to the place where it's intended
to go to
[Music]
keep saying you love owls and nothing
else matters you can mispronounce
anything and i'll just go along with
it
[Music]
thousand thousand thousand thousand
after watching the latest hello talk it
was great by the way i noticed that when
ah 70 thank you i noticed that one's
about a mention then it seemed like it
hadn't heard of on the table i
definitely heard of it before but i
didn't play it i know that it's very
it's very famous and very popular
that i know if that's true people may be
interested in watching you play it blind
you really think so like what's what's
the genre
of undertale is that like a
2d side side dungeon scroll
crawler thingy what is it
rpg
[Music]
it's a bullet tail rpg oh hell now i'm
bloodhound
oh no no no no no no is it as bad as
tools or is it like actually like
human
no it's not bad no
it's easy okay interesting
besides too i actually oh that's that's
not true actually not
i wanted to stay behind beside stole i
don't know any other bullet hell games
but i guess like
[Music]
is ping pong something like bullet hell
isn't that in some way
like like okay
i'm gonna shut up
i think i'm thinking of something else
yeah no
i mean what about those uh really really
simple
old games where you like um
[Music]
never mind i'll just stop talking
[Laughter]
i just stopped talking though trevor
cheetah question melamed 9812 thank you
i am channel thank you thank you oh
that's the dude that uh
where i tried so hard to visit his uh
island
looking for the top thank you for an
iron channel danke sharon elvis limadan
sonic kundan today was my birthday i
want to celebrate with my first super
chat thanks a lot
for being there on my everyday live
greetings from spain oh
happy late birthday
now i'm thinking more of not the ping
pong more like the
the that space ship fights
2d like the really old ones where
you're like at the bottom and they're at
the top and you shoot at each other
yeah i guess something like space
invaders i don't know if that's it
is that a bullet hell game
isn't that in some way a bullet hell
game
tell me yes come on come on come on
i mean technically thank you you're the
good person here
okay then i really don't know any other
bullet hell games besides touhou
is mayonnaise a bullet hell game
oh my god someone's gonna make him
sidequest gonna make a meme out of this
it's gonna he's gonna be like is this a
bullet hell game with the hand out you
know that meme
she's on it right now
ping pong is this bullet hell game
oh my god i hate myself
i still play thank you soon i will
i wonder what was happening thank you
shannon thank you
thank you oh can't read that name
oh we're in almost a full rather
gentleman hi
kiana how are you i'm really sad because
i can't watch any of your streams live
this week because of my work schedule
that
sucks no but i will watch every
archive pinky promise thank you
can i snuggle under your theory mama
phoenix wings and get some comforting
words
why because you gotta go to work huh
well that's just normal
that's just normal everyday life
just kidding no no no no come let me sit
on you let me let me warm you up and um
now i know it can be tough
my vibe uh i've worked a normal job
before as well
and uh i know it can't be super tough
like
when you don't feel like going to work
at all
every day i know
but i know you can do it ellis nina i
believe in you
you're strong you're talented you're
skilled
and they need you they need you at your
workplace
so come help them out they would be lost
without you
and
[Music]
m
is
[Music]
yeah that's from bissell deutsch just a
little bit of a german tangent
german cooking tangent
something in german i don't know i'm
just a random viewer that's a horrible
translation
useless
next thank you samuel l jackson thank
you
[Music]
did i read that one before that that
wrap i feel like one of those wraps i
i read in my stream but i'll do it again
let's go
it wait a second maybe i can't do like
my own beat
boom boom boom
right let's go i recorded that i
recorded that
because his long prices are like
straight off highway 5 when you're done
you'd be lucky to have any bus loan and
he shamelessly paused ups for straight
look
with all his own friends supposed to
call him cruise
boom his loan prices are wack straight
up high five when you're done you'll be
lucky to have any bells left any
shamelessly pies jobs with a straight
look with vulnerance unfurnished it's
best to call him
tom crook
hey that worked somehow
give me another one come on but now i i
deleted my
my beat i deleted my beat how will i
give me no one write it now i'll do my
i'll do my bean again
boom boom boom boom
boom boom boom boom boom
boom boom boom boom boom boom
boom booms
okay where is it i'm done where's my
wrap
you can't rather wrap that quickly
quickly quickly
i'm waiting i'm waiting where is it is
my wrap hobble on
dude
is he even in the chat kelly hope it
has been real quiet in the 20 seconds
since kia i dropped the bar
oh what is this murasaki oh we're having
like i don't have any more cash
well let's try to ride it now quickly
what is this
oh my my thing my thing didn't work
boom boom boom boom boom
boom boom
okay let's go if you want rap sports you
should turn to me
because my rhymes are sick but no it's
not the c
how a line ain't got nothing on this
entertain this because my pplc
president of kfb got this oh that's good
wait my why did it not work again
huh i know what god dammit i messed up
guys again
boom
boom boom boom boom boom boom
you should turn to me cause my rhymes
are sick but it's not the sea
hubble and then got nothing on this yeti
harmony ain't got nothing on this edge
of teen this because my pplc president
okay if he got this okay
boom if you want rap buzz you should
turn to me and wait i'm not gonna die
[Music]
then
my rhymes are sick but it's not the sea
hubble i ain't got nothing on this angie
teen base cause my pplc person
okay we got this [\h__\h] it's trying too
late
it's so like too late no no no no
i had to feel it i i needed more time to
feel it
boobs if you want rap spots you should
turn to me cause my rhymes are sick but
it's not the c hopper line i got nothing
on this energy team base because my
people
see president of kfb this boom
give me another one guys give me another
one okay
i scrolled back down now throw your
wraps at me have a line
and give it to me you don't even need to
super chat it
[\h__\h] but you're back
chevron bang i don't know what that is
though
ah is kelly say anything she must be
real quiet
that's horrible what can
too
hypercam 2
on registered hypercam 2.
come on
in the house i thought you were going to
write funny chicken
oh there we go mudasaki dropped another
one
herbaline's been real quiet
lol bossa beat this fire line up our
lives with fire and desires
but take care not to take on the ire of
the cry
or else you'll get it lit up on the fire
that's kind of weird but okay i'll flow
with it
i'll flow with anything you give me
no bust the beat is fire you light a
ball laughs with fire and desire but
take care not to take on the eye of the
cry or else you'll get laid up on the
pile
zebedee ben
like a volcano trying to mess phil but i
know she don't play though
my rhymes complex so don't catch a
fruitful or syllables like trying to
stay
okay
can i be spitting fire like a volcano
try to mess with that but i know she
don't play though my rhymes are complex
so don't catch a throat full of
syllables like trying to say afiyah you
are cool
[Laughter]
i don't know how to say that
nail it down
oh what's that
[Music]
nutella french toast and crazy fried
chicken casper the ghost and writer's
flies thicken
and if he not only that just loves to
sing there's a few
few there's a few of my favorite things
good that i messed up because i had too
much time
the left is you guys don't have enough
emoji enough letters
boom chicken's running everybody
screaming in the back potential's eyes
are gleaming the employees flee
it is spelling doom it's just another
day in the usual rooms
nice one he
changed that was good
oh yeah i mean if harborland is not
going to throw anything out there then
i'll stop the tangent here
if you got nothing for me
i just bunked my glass of water against
my
teeth
what's that boom
tricks with the hot chick she truly is
clever haters whatever give up she will
never
keep in touch money forever
[Music]
in tassel clowns that's a good one
a trip there's some triple rhymes in
there damn but
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait what
last time tend to turn my lumerick into
a wrap making my poetry skills looks
like a real dumb
sap can't use rap skills could show the
soul
of death itself the worst but not
without charming and
boom last time tantra turned my limerick
into a rap making my poetry skills look
like a real dumb stab
dancers rap skills could kill the soul
of death itself the worst but not
without charming and batting her first
that's difficult that's really difficult
that's some long sentences
you gotta be more original than that
and then but how does it go again
ew
[Music]
for your mother double double super size
and don't forget the fries
that was from my beetle
they say the reaper is the only rapper
but i'm sorry i'm here too my darling
viewers the phone's about to be taken by
someone better the only unknown phoenix
talking about you can't hear a vet
no no i had no i had no rhythm with that
i wanted to do something like cali does
when she could when she like
wraps like like a freaking rap god that
goes
sick beats now sheets cooking chickens
in the heat tensions bunking all the
spamming scientific peeps ain't got
nothing to the phoenix dropping bursts
like a remix send them to the river
sticks
[Laughter]
[Applause]
don't you think about having a nice day
i'm your attention and you have to got
to pay
from empty red super chats the bells and
game i'll take your money and you will
end my turn
mess it up don't you think about having
a nice day on your attention and you
have got to pay for
empty red super chess battles in the
game i'll take your money and you will
have emma to blame
yo tango that was another good one
oh yeah oh yeah last one last one last
one
what do you say smoother oh that's like
that looks like a tongue twister
got me buzzed like a humble bee voice
strong on honey she fumbles this
bumbling here if he runs but with the
times she'll
wait is that not a wrap is that a wrap
is that supposed to be a wrap
well there's a german one
my name is mc ceo from kfp or nick from
mcd
mark spin on chicken wings last night
king jam this is foreign
oh rapper
we were well commenting for fun
that that was really well written
what is this tangent keeps going on
damn you guys have no idea that that
german lyrics were actually really
really good
because it had like a line that said um
i make ashes because i'm a phoenix and
in german
um making ashes kind of means like you
you're making money
kind of it's funny
no that was good
i want to stop but these are so good i
don't know i can't stop
childhood is sick that
[Music]
as soon as i regret every time we have
to say cheese
we say auf wiedersehen though
so pretty damn good
okay we gotta stop here guys we're gonna
stop
we gotta stop boys i'm not i know i'm on
fire
because i'm a phoenix maybe we should
maybe we should do a dedicated stream
like this one day
oh god now you come with all those wraps
guys okay
uh god damn it
phoenix burp girl on fire facing her the
wind goes right the battling for hands
of the reaper slash reaper and occasion
got a chance could take a moment forever
that didn't arrive at the end
it was so good what the hell was nick
cage doing there
aggressively gay doesn't like sushi i
guess that's okay when she strolls up
the stream everybody says hey
aggressively gay doesn't like sushi i
guess that's okay
okay that's it guys that's it guys
[Music]
i guess that's okay
oh my god
oh my god yeah yeah
charles james thank you shouldn't have
already read my music
oh no he wrote uh uh something in his
super chat
can i do that without reading it one
time
tom nook is the correct way to go by his
looks read the book the truth will have
you shook he's entrepreneurial his fear
will make you wish for a miracle take
your voids and give them a burial the
truth is simply empirical
oh that was perfect on time
thank you soon
thank you i did i do remember this one
now too i did read it before
yeah looking for the top thank you and
hot chocolate thank you
so much
[Music]
for that question true magician
and looking for the top tank um
crispy thank you so far
[Music]
those keyblade thank you soon mister
casper
thank you for always being there for us
you always brighten my day and make me
smile no matter how bad my mood is there
aren't another word to describe how much
i love you thank you for everything oh
i love you too oh that's so sweet of you
you brightened my day too all of you
thank you so much
what a sweet super chat you know what
you know what i approve
uh i am taking a second and i approve of
this message
a prop flint thank you
speed freak thank you margaret v g thank
you
looking for the top 10 kishen well next
thank you this is my first red super
chat to you boss thank you
i appreciate that thank you for the
support i just want to say thanks for
all the fun and energetic streams that
you do for us you always brighten the
day and make me laugh with how adorable
you are on another note i may just be in
a
wait i read this one before and you did
get your blessing a very cursed blessing
i just remember
i hope you recovered from that
if not then please take it up with my
lawyers
i i can't do much about that what
happened happened
can't make it undone
thank you shindo thank you for the
support once again
67 thank you for the red supercharged
wow she's gonna read super chat in the
number students that we're gonna make
sure we get a ton of super chats in
before then i don't understand
that logic but there must be some logic
in there right
something here is logical i don't know
what it is but
it must be thank you thank you
thank you so much thank you well next
time
[Music]
demon thank you fodr also another red
super chat thank you want your tension
pencil
no we put heart at the end oh
heart emojis make everything even more
charming
thank you effort i'm glad i'm glad you
like my tangents i like to go
um on them whenever i can
whenever i can think of one thank you
for your support and listening to my
can you imagine me as a grandma one day
kiana grandma tangents oh i'm gonna be a
really annoying grandma
i'm gonna talk forever and my relatives
will be like oh god this
[\h__\h] is going on and on no no no no
oh no i will be hated
i will die alone
i will never shut up yeah oh
[Music]
so in like three years from now excuse
me do you want to die
are you are you
are you challenging your own life right
now
you want to give your life away that
easily
huh three years from now
i'm eternal
[Music]
almost missed it thank you
wow congrats to everyone who got the
true running of the stream yeah
a lot of people left uh who was here
yesterday
and who left before the two secret
endings i mean everyone who's watching
this super chat reading it feels like
you guys would stay
until the end until the very end
but if you left too early yesterday then
you probably missed a lot
like me discussing these uh
merchandise uh from
animal crossing that they have in the
convenience stores there
if you were there then you are
the real [\h__\h] wait i mean in a positive
way is that not how you say it
oh wait i feel like i feel like i was
trying to say the real deal
i think that that was what i was trying
to say
that's the true ending oh that is how
you're saying
i felt the kind of bed after i said it
feels wrong
you're the real one you are the real
ones
so connected thank you also for staying
until the end and even blessing me with
another red super chat at the very end
thank you i
appreciate it thank you shin for your
support
south korea's thank you looking for the
top donkey shooting robot next to
sanchez and katie shadow danke shin well
next to stankish entirety thank you so
[Music]
much
and let me read this one next
[Music]
oh harbour lion is saying here in a rap
that is gonna be missed by him so he's
just not there i think oh
no
boom i'm afraid this stream is gonna be
missed by me but let's just with these
bars that i make a decree
i'll be sure to catch the archives
decide you swear have fun dancing and
best of luck
there
thank you you were definitely missed i
was looking at the chat the whole time
trying to see if you were dropping some
new bars but you weren't
wait but didn't you say you're broke
well you were actually there but you
said you were broke i'm confused
you didn't miss it after all
thank you you're like the rapper of kfb
now you should change your
i don't know what kfb minstrel means i
don't know what that means minstrel
but you should maybe change your name to
kfp rapper
kfb bar dropper
which could also be you dropping our
like right that probably doesn't we
probably don't say it like that in
english
i would leave all right you probably
don't even use that word
evil quality bar
no no no
minstrel is still musical it's like
old-timey bard ah yeah i feel like i
said
i heard of that what you know minstrel
unless you want me to sing this like
i'm afraid the stream is gonna be missed
by
me but it's with these bars that i make
a decree
i'll be sure to catch your archives
decide to swear have fun
and too and best of luck out there
what is that melody
[Music]
what is that green sleeves
and then how do you guys know what is
that what is that why do i know that
green sleeves what is green sleeves
how the hell do you know you know how do
you know how do you know
popular christmas that's not christmas
music
because i studied from studied music
history attention okay that makes sense
that
piece thank you for pinky that's a
designated taste tester i must try the
brand new swordsicle
why did i not hear that one before thank
you
tell me if it was good i didn't even try
it yet crack sir thank you
brian hichman
patrick chandan and
protection package has expired would you
like to purchase a one-year subscription
yes yes yes
yes
[Music]
um
william mcdonald duncan hobble lying
down
[Music]
thank you thank you i appreciate the
support you're very generous thank you
i'm glad you enjoyed the stream
okay i am refreshing and scrolling
and scrolling and scrolling swelling
scrolling
and scrolling and scrolling where did i
stop i don't know
uh by the way with that with that
this one
[Music]
do you guys know what i was trying to
imitate
yeah i was trying to imitate snoop dogg
didn't drop it like it's hot songs
i was surprised no one was like getting
it when i was doing that
we sound why did no one get it with that
alone
i thought oh oh everyone's gonna laugh
like hahaha snoop dogg
but no one in the chat was saying that
someone was like eh
isn't that what it sounds like
sorry i moved my microphone
i noticed but i didn't chat why
[Music]
yeah i also don't typically typically
listen to that but isn't that like
a melody that anyone knows
[Music]
i don't know the currency is that the
red super chat
i don't know i think no
oh well uh
thank you for the red super chat
chickens know who's boss wait is that a
wrap
no that's not okay chickens know who's
boss chicken's dream
experience rape rapid eye movement rem
sleep
chickens are just like human mothers to
talk to their babies a mother hen
begins to teach wait what are you
okay mother hen begins to teach claws to
her chicks before they even hatch last
but not least chickens are adorable
is that my red super chat to tell me how
cute chickens are
i know all of this because you guys are
all chickens you are my chickens
it's chicken propaganda
thank you soon thank you td
very sweet to share the knowledge of why
chickens are so
cute all of you are chickens all of you
you're cutie pies mmm
everybody are also with a red superhero
thank you
seeing the ac family reminded me that
seeing you play it made me want to play
and start oval as well
wait why would you have to start over
why did you not just continue
so thanks for making me want to play
again also one of my starting villagers
you also reminded me of utensil there
with chicken
[Music]
you think you can say anything by
sending a red super chat huh
huh you think i won't send you into the
usual room
[Music]
you better be real careful my dear
friend
do it
nobody did it and i feel so bad for
doing it
no bye-bye you have a little timeout
you go stand against the wall and talk
to the wall and think about your actions
your actions mm-hmm he didn't even do
that much
he just called he was interested in no
yeah it wasn't even it wasn't even that
deserved but he challenged me
he said do it he challenged me
no no no no no don't name you cannot buy
the usual room package you cannot buy it
you have to
deserve it but in like a negative way
and i don't want you guys to deserve it
i want you guys to be good
maybe we should maybe we should uh
re reinforce positive
engagement by making the unusual room
which is a positive room maybe we should
open up the unusual room
[Applause]
there will be like like like a lot of
baby kittens and
baby doggos a lot of puppies and kittens
that you can like hang out or even they
will they would like jump on you and
invade your private space
they will they will like just oh my god
all it takes is kittens and puppies i
don't even need anything else in that
cafe
uh cafes in that room although
for people who have allergies it might
not be
as nice of an experience as it is for
others but for me that's heaven
for me that is heaven
um maybe maybe if you go into the
unusual room we'll spray some
some special stuff on you so that you
have some immunities only for the time
you're in the unusual room so even with
allergies you'll be fine
okay easy peasy i'm gonna set it up guys
but it's not going to be easy to get in
there i'm not going to be
easy elbito thank you
jasper the douchebag
[Music]
can you guys even hear what i'm saying
when i turn on this this uh
this pitch
yeah okay i feel like it's hard to hear
but okay thank you for that
input jasper
oh jasper again
[Music]
thank you for writing the jasper no wait
no no no i don't want a jasper fan big i
asked for a casper fanfic
sodalia i think we're having a little
bit of a
communication problem here i was
specifically asking
for a fanfiction of casper and his
adventures and you're writing you wanted
a jasper fanfic i'll start working on
right one right away
no no no no no no no
no no no and you can include jasper but
the main character has to be casper
because he's the og
no no no no no boys love we don't need
that
they are mice guys it's that's i mean
what the hell
is this communication thank you andrei
[Music]
you guys are enjoying this way too much
oh god i will not read
i will not read it if it's a if it's a
goddamn boy's love
fanfiction i refuse to read it
i want it to be some cute adventures
like casper is writing those super chats
i wanted to be like dad is that too much
to ask why you guys
gotta make everything sexual
for real you guys are horny as hell
gotta send you guys to horny jail i'm
sending you guys to horny jail you're
listening
pornydale i don't know what they do to
you there that
you're gonna go there have fun
[Music]
send us somebody
m ah
this super chat goes solely to your
manager for her hard work and her being
so nice
yeah please direct funds
[Laughter]
i will and i will that's that's five
euros um
i will i will give her five euros
and then she will have to go to the bank
and change that i
actually do still have errors okay so
this is kind of like
actually putting giving her more work
because then she will have to go to the
back
super evil plan
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god
and no no we're not adopting anyone i
mean you can talk to kelly about that
i think she's gonna say no
to fancy i mean me and kelly were not
adopting anyone but i'm adopting like
every other one who's
like joining my membership is uh
basically my adopted child
[Music]
maybe you should make a shrine place of
warship on your island and next soil is
an empty space where people can drop off
oh yeah a kiana shrine
[Music]
it's kind of weird i would prefer having
a cali shrine but
uh the purpose of it must if like
is that people give me gifts so i guess
it makes sense to make a kiara shrine
maybe i can do both oh thank you patrick
jen for this genius id
idea called
no a shrine doesn't autumn automatically
make something a cult
what about the shinto shrines in
japanese uh shinto religion
a shrine doesn't make something occult
and in the shinto shrines every time you
visit the shrine
you insert some money into the
the donation box every time
[Music]
so if you're calling kfb a cult then you
know what else you're calling a cult
and that is kind of
stretched kind of a stretch
if anything okay if these are religion
what okay
we are okay everyone listen
everyone listen up kfb members listen
up i need to make it clear again
phoenix kfb fast food chain
tm is not a cult
we are a fast food chain i repeat
we are a worldwide fast food franchise
we are nothing besides that
we are not a cult we are not a religion
we are a fast food chain what we sell is
burgers and stuff
[Applause]
[Music]
that echo is insane
but i think everyone has heard and
understood yes
saying yes everyone otherwise you're
going into the usual room
and maybe never coming out saying yes
very good yes
yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
okay then i think we can continue
thank you welcome of course you're not
gonna lie to me or no
bruno l duncan travertini thank you for
the
how amazingly generous
super
cheap cheap cheap
[Music]
i tried
do yourself a favor don't stream playing
undertale backstage is dialed up to 1
million anytime anyone plays that game
like it would be voiced and
even you could handle oh
okay yeah i don't i i i mean um
i hear it's a very good game but simply
like
i for me what makes the game interesting
to me
is made up of 50 graphics
and 40 story
and 10 now okay maybe maybe 50
graphics 30 story 35
story and 15 gamer mechanics
mechanics so uh
from the looks it's not speaking to me
because 2d
games like these old old style games i
have to be honest they don't really
speak to me
of course there's more things to it but
um to
to these those are just three basic
things that i just thought of but of
course of course
i mean music and all that is okay uh is
a big factor
if i liked that game afterwards but uh
from deciding if i want to play a game
the three biggest
factors are for me the graphics
the story and the game mechanics
they don't speak their games what
yeah well the important part is that wha
what do the graphics look like i mean i
prefer like stuff like
um for 3d
and uh yeah mostly like
anime graphics but also like graphics
that are like like
zelda so the wind waker is that uh
breath of the wild
[Music]
and the tails off games and
near all the metal looks [\h__\h] good i
would love to play it
if i wouldn't suck at it
unfortunately i bought the game and i
tried to play it
i told you guys before i really failed
hard at nier automata
unfortunately
i don't think there will be a day when i
can play that game
but yeah i'm sure that game is amazing
but i don't know
doesn't doesn't look like it doesn't
speak to me from the outside
i mean if i if i had some interest
i could maybe give it a go even if it's
not my style but
[Music]
just set it to easy near i think i had
it on easy i think
maybe i'll try again maybe i had it on
normal nah i'm pretty sure i said it too
easy
at least after failing so many times
your automata gets easier after tutorial
then why the hell is the tutorial so
hard
it should get harder after the tutorial
[Music]
oh my god
so why would you do that i can't get
past the tutorial
i want to play the game but i can't get
oh man sorry thank you
[Music]
thank you in 10 dogs i played that back
in the day i played it and then 10 dogs
and then ten
cats was it called in ten cats
what was the cat version called
[Music]
what was it called
ah then 10 dogs and cats oh yeah it was
just one game oh yeah yeah yeah
it was just one game and they were
together oh yeah
oh yeah nostalgic
you thank you
i feel very confident thanks to you
lucas
and
[Music]
he
you're casting a spell or something
tension what
shut up speaking german
better educate yourself and learn some
german
razzie dances duncan logical paradox
thank you for a red super chat
wow hi can i apologize for not watching
you stream today because i was getting
busy
i was busy getting a raise since i got
one i want to pay it forward
oh my god you guys i can now send you
red access
more often but no promises i will have
to treat myself to some gifts too after
all yeah definitely oh my god please do
you deserve it i mean especially what
wow
especially if you got a if you got a
race it must mean you worked really hard
so good job on getting that raise yo
yo good job
uh i was actually massaging my shoulder
for a moment but
something happened anyway logical
paradox thank you so much i appreciate
that you want to share some of that
luck with me thank you i wish i could
share my luck with you too but
i hope i can just continue to entertain
you with my streams
thank you and good job
[Music]
is that some kind of like something i
shouldn't read when you read it together
is that something weird
in a shoe
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
thank you for a red super chat tinter's
extremely cute today even if she's
already always at max cuteness every day
oh come on
you're doing a flirt
oh thank you
i i i don't know what you're saying you
made me blush
why was i so cute today for you what
what made you think that i was
cute
which point of today's stream made you
think that way
thank you
[Music]
um having a job is important yes
if you have a lifestyle where you don't
need a job
but without putting trouble on anyone
that's okay but you're right that your
aunt is just
satisfied with your lifestyle so i guess
you're depending on her
um and if she's not happy with it i
think you should help her out and
get yourself a job yeah your
time to watch youtubers might be shorter
but
you you have to find a good balance
and you will so good luck with that
i think the important thing is just that
um you don't trouble anyone around you
[Music]
i know working is tough but whoever
you're
not only you but anyone who is in this
situation whoever you are relying on
and is yeah
you can't rely on the person forever
please give them a break it's just hard
as the person
who is like helping you out financially
or whatever
be it your mom or your father or
whatever um
in such a situation it's hard to kick
you out
obviously because that's family
so please at some point
i'm not talking to this super chatter
chattering specific but to anyone who is
in
this situation um think about
everything that this person has done for
you
and realize that it's your time to step
up and get a job and you know
support yourself and eventually maybe
support your family and give them
something back
just try just try at least
it's okay to if you have a support your
family except i think it's fine to
receive the support um
but don't only take you should also
always aim to give back
[Music]
andrea duncan plano plants
intestinal clouds
i kind of said some serious stuff there
but i don't know i was just
i was just rambling but i mean you guys
can
definitely just live the life you the
way you want to live it but
just don't try to please please try to
not
i don't know uh put too much
burdens on the people you're relying on
foreign
and normally i would want to tell you
guys guys stuff like that but that super
chat was kind of asking for advice
but i don't i don't feel like i'm in the
position to tell you guys
like anything like this oh by the way i
still have that comment pinned why do i
still have a pin
oh dear lord
[Music]
need i remind you i'm not gonna read the
rest of the super chat
but no you don't need to remind me that
is something different
that is something blessed okay that is
different that is very different
[Music]
you are making the act of giving birth
into something that it is not
i was watching i might have been i might
have watched a video
of a mouse giving birth to babies but
that is just
something beautiful and natural look
that is different from a boy's love
fanfiction between casper and jasper who
are two
mices mouse mice
[Music]
no that's what the people have been
asking for the people have been asking
for a fan fiction between casper and
jasper which is
they want it to be boys love and but the
thing is casper and jasper are mice
so that's why i'm like what the hell
dude
[Laughter]
this is getting so weird
[Music]
i didn't start this okay i didn't get
you guys came up with that [\h__\h]
oh god coo casper's blind friend duncan
hentais shanghai guy duncan
[Music]
um
what thanks for your wrap-up support i
make it
mama i finally done my busy thing and
grandpa fantasy and once i'm back i
found out the big hole deep in bottom
left of my heart and with some chicken
noise down there do you know why
no i have no idea what you're talking
about
what's your account in that question
[Music]
don't worry don't worry josh
k also done okay last refresh
speed speed speed
[Music]
thank you i've been happier since you
did me at all
it makes me happy too i like v thank
sorry i missed your stream i just woke
up for work today oh you can watch my
arcade doing work
and thank you uh lay on skateboard
perspective on what you think will be
best for us these heart to heart talks
are why you are my favorite youtuber oh
thank you
thank you soon but i don't want it to
sound like too much like i
i'm lecturing you guys i don't want it
to sound like that
definitely hentai is talking okay it's
over guys bye bye
in german we say i'll venus in i gotta
prepare some stuff
and play some animal crossing bye bye
guys thank you for hanging out today
and i'm sorry that it wasn't what it was
originally supposed to be it was
supposed to be a minecraft stream
but we have a minecraft stream this week
anyway which i'm not 100 sure what we're
going to do yet
but it will happen so thank you guys
[Music]
tomorrow
later around the time uh that we are
serving in right now
we are having a members only stream uh i
think it will be a drawing stream
possibly um
[Music]
thank you thank you
nah no secret ending today or
[Music]
no
ah looking for the top thank you soon
thank you
[Music]
soon
did you forget how to speak human
[Music]
language
there is no secret scene there is no
secret ending
[Music]
bye-bye
thank you this is your first catastrophe
what
thank you so much delicious noodles
thank you
a pickle cucumber oh yeah yeah i
ate some crunchy pickles before the
stream but on on bread
[Music]
199.99
i'm sorry ufo for sending you there
i'm sorry oh my god guys thank you so
much
thank you
[Music]
don't leave all i have to
do thank you so much
it's ending though right bye
cry tonight
[Music]
bye