[Music]
hmm
my
[Music]
do
[Applause]
[Music]
me
hello hello hello
yay can you guys hear it
i think she's probably too let me turn
her up
now it should be fine hello
audio test one two one check one two one
two
okay how about the bgm and that we gotta
show you so here the beautiful bgm
so you can concentrate
yes yes yes okay seems seems like
everything's alright
perfect welcome everyone to my first
one-on-one collab with gooda
um uh if you want to tweet about it
please use the hashtag
that's written in
[Music]
what do you think it means you probably
can get that one right
is shark yeah
perfect okay so today
um since uh i do speak fluent japanese
and good ass doesn't
i have decided to teach kuda some basic
japanese oh my god
wait you disappeared can you hear me
[Music]
can you hear me yes now i can hear it
can you hear me
i can hear you okay no i can't hear you
what
what what the hell was that wha okay uh
wait a second one second we will we will
um
this was fine the whole time let me get
back uh one second
one second one second
one second it's all good
[Music]
i don't um do you wait
well now i just have a uniform on the
screen you could read the with the chat
read the chat what is it
our chat not the stream chat oh that's
that
okay
okay okay
[Music]
uh well everyone while our ghosts are uh
explaining you what's going on
actually i can i think i can oops i can
oops no
no that's not it and i'll just
explain to you as a ghost
[Music]
we are today here to
teach us actually i'm teaching gouda
specifically some
useful shark knowledge useful for sharks
only
of course some japanese wait a second i
i i i i i i
i i i'm trying to find
my student
god catch me i'm skipping today
no no good this is your first class you
can't just
not come to class this is unacceptable
i'll find you i'll find you and i like
i'll i'll
force you into your seat
by my own means
you better get the duct tape hold on
let me let me try one more thing let me
try one more thing
why one moment one moment please
everyone
i mean we asked for your patience maybe
we actually go back to the loading
screen for a moment
let's go back there one second will
restart
what the hell
[Music]
okay one second guys we're almost there
pop
[Music]
hello
there we go okay not exactly in the
right position let me fix that
but gonna have to take uh
uh put on her school uniform again
adorable okay we got it we got it we got
it
you know uh sometimes um my students
like to
skip school or something unacceptable
but now here we are you can never leave
again you're in school forever
sorry for the dramas guys we are now
getting into
japanese 101 for sharks which doesn't
mean lala everyone thought i wrote lol
there on purpose but it's 101 it's 101
okay oh i thought you wrote lol too no
oh japanese for sharks no
no i mean it might there might be some
funny parts as well but
generally i'm teaching you some serious
stuff and to
to um to make something clear
and so you can read basic uh hiragana
and katakana right
okay and also always try to reply with
hi which is yes never say no always say
yes
oh hi hi okay
yay then today kiara
i actually i noticed it's actually our
our
height difference is quite perfect for
this so you're sitting
actually normally you should be sitting
but
you're still standing because if you
take a seat i'll actually won't see you
anymore
that's okay i got a nice pillow right
here
yeah you can lean on it as much as you
want
only for you my other students are not
allowed to do that
oh special privileges yes
okay my dear little guru
uh i think you probably know some basic
words like um
like probably like konichiwa and kawaii
and stuff like that right
yes i assumed so so we're gonna start
off with some
well these are somewhat basic but maybe
maybe some of them
you don't know right away i mean hello
it should be oh easy you probably know
how to say hello right
hi amen i'm in skipping class i'm a
should have been
i'm me i'm i'm you also need a class at
chiara's classroom one day i'll i'll
teach you some japanese as well
i passed out me in the hallway she's in
the bathroom playing on her nintendo
switch
she's playing smash bros just thought
i'd let that slip
what's in the toilet oh my god okay
thank you for that information but are
you um
i fought you too i i thought you were
working with each other but you actually
you actually i don't want detention
you sneak just kidding of course
gura wants to actually get all the
apples from me today because
every time she's being a good child i
will balance one apple on her head and i
think she just wants all the apples
hi let's see how many you can get
so how do you say
[Music]
oh
that was
people usually when they write konichiwa
out in romaji
they would usually write the va with a w
but if you are very correct about it
it's actually
h a maybe you know that kura um but
people write it out as a
w a well i'm gonna go with that i'm
gonna
i don't know let's go with ha okay aj
let's be
super correct should i write the
hiragana version on the screen as well
yes oops okay yes my brain is like
yes well i mean you did you wrote
hiragana there you go
all multitasking okay so that's what i
wanted to write
very good i expected that you would know
that much i expected that but
now it gets difficult maybe not maybe
not just yet
do you know how to say nice to meet you
this is very important to
sound polite oh
ah would
that was too simple i'll give it when if
you finish the whole slide
i might give you an apple hygiene my
step
exactly actually would will not even
fit on there how'd you make my step
okay wonderful you got that done so
basically
when you talk to someone you meet for
the first time you can just say
konnichiwa
and then you do your usual summer
[Music]
japanese pro people would already tell
you hong kong
you disappeared sorry amelia is calling
er with smash in the bathroom
wait can you see me
ah no
nice ghost voice
as well we'll fix that as well i think
there's uh maybe uh
in the internet problems in uh
in the in the ocean yes
why isp thank you
do you think you can get back into the
classroom or
or
are you trying to should i
should we go can i
should i hold on yes wait
no okay okay
why don't i go there please let me just
one moment okay one second
we have enough time to do it
i'm taking all my time to teach you some
private
private lesson stuff okay one second
um i see
i see interesting perfect
interesting and we are
back back in business
back from the bathroom some ghost powers
that's pretty dope it's amelia it's the
time travel
ah again that's amazing though i want
that
time traveling skill i want it i would
like that too
okay back on focusing on the japanese
okay
concentration in japaneses
yes shoot shoot
yeah quite a different uh quite a
difficult word itself has a quite
difficult kanji so i'm not going to
teach you that but maybe you'll actually
remember it
how good is the shark brain memory
um
goldfish okay
i got i have a similar oh damn i have a
similar
problem uh with short time memory oh
no oh no should i
put you there in a in a cardboard
possibly
i was just preparing that
here let's do let's do
this the good thing is
if you're a cardboard then i can easily
balance all the apples on the top of
your
head so they won't even fall off oh
that's cute
well-ish if you send me that cardboard
it's gonna be a bit hard to balance but
okay
i will try one second let me put that in
there
[Music]
hello sorry everyone that it's gonna
be like that uh maybe maybe um at the
end we can try
to get moving dora back in here
let me put you in the right position
okay small good as small
[Music]
i love how everything was working
perfectly fine and then all of a sudden
yeah no problem though i mean
even it doesn't matter if you're moving
or not moving you always look adorable i
like looking at this
cute face oh wait that's a better face
thank you
my god i sent me one more that's that's
even easier to balance
i can send you this one too maybe just
in case oh
where are you i'll take that i'll take
that one
okay alex
my twin doubletroll you have you have an
evil twin
uh
[Laughter]
can you imagine double gouda my goodness
i i actually
i would like to see that you can do that
maybe in one of your streams i did that
before as well also in my stream
two kiana yes double trouble
i like the book okay i hope this is okay
for everyone i'm ready to
continue uh i'm sorry good eyes not
moving but
you can imagine her moving
yes okay the power of your imagination
continuing continuing my name is
something something
probably maybe you maybe you know that
one this is also simple
do you know it oh
[Music]
shark brain is working
that's okay you don't have to have that
in there but uh to make it very correct
we can say
no
o makes it very polite you don't
actually have to do that
uh but yeah and you can also just say
samades or uh gunades that's also good
enough but
yeah to be super over correct it's
good
[Music]
yay
i think these phrases you seem to uh
have quite
the hang of it so you probably also know
how to say i come from somewhere do you
know that
ah i think maybe you said that in your
debut stream
maybe did you i i don't think so no
i don't know that i guess maybe the only
japanese you said was some of this
more than likely yes okay
so you don't know that one also don't
don't don't cheat with the chat i'm not
reading chat no worries
there's a few ways to say this um you
can say
for example uh
something something which would mean i
came from this
place but you could also say
[Music]
this this is a bit more uh difficult
uh where's my uh some something
something
this this is more like um this is more
like
uh where you born where where were you
born so
for example if you were born in atlantis
but you now live somewhere else uh like
in
into heaven because you're an angel
[Music]
oh jesus but this is too much text
i don't i don't i'm not gonna write the
okay whatever i'm gonna write it karaki
master
too much text goddammit she's saying
this okay have you heard of
that phrase before no that's new to me
oh there you go i learned something new
atlantis yes
that makes you sound very smart very
smart
right good smart
of course i never expected anything else
no
okay one very important phrase
uh that i use all the time japanese
people
use this all the time and you heard it
before i'm very sure how
how do you think you say please take
good care of me there's actually no real
english for that i would say but this is
how you would translate it
uh can i take some guesses yes
okay i'm gonna get uh please take good
care of me
[Music]
yes this is a very very often used
phrase
uh you can also just say you know school
if you're more like
for example if you're with a friend and
he will do something for you or he tells
you
or she of course she she tells you
to meet up at the station and you say
yeah whatever yoda school
or uh thanks for doing my homework next
time again
you can use it in so many ways but also
the most important thing if you meet
someone for the first time and
uh you're starting some kind of um
working relationship or any kind of
relationship really
uh or on the phone if anything anytime
you
always use this in every sentence you
always say
only
you can even make it more polite than
that you can even say
itashimasu instead of onegaishimasu you
can say
but it's really not necessary to
remember all those
polite stuff yeah as long as you know
as long as you know it's also if you
write
emails in japanese you always have to
have this phrase
in there as well always always always
oh at the end of the beginning
it can be both unlike um
for example in the beginning you could
introduce yourself again and be like
you're not going to get so much but
i guess at the end it also fits well
it's just you got to have a feeling for
it
just say it as often as you can suck up
to whoever you're talking to
as much as you can
get on the good side yeah so that they
think you're a very polite shark
of course okay wow this uh the japanese
font is really big so it makes
everything else pretty small hope you
guys can read that
can you see that you have good eyes oh
yes i can see this
okay so to repeat
uh if uh we can already have a
wait this is a whole whole introduction
actually do you want to
repeat after me
[Music]
[Applause]
that was adorable that was amazing he's
so adorable okay but good
oh it's not gonna get easier from here
i'm starting to sweat
don't worry no one can see it
okay do you do you ever
eat apple scuda yes
oh yes i like apples do you know what
apple is in japanese
hi oh
amazing i'm impressing my teacher
damn really really good really good ones
here comes the difficult stuff okay
maybe not yet
it's still a bit easy okay so we're
gonna continue
you also i think know this one how
are you do you know that um
my brain is telling me two possible
answers yes
oh yes or or or or what
a ganky does yes
perfect there's a there's a slight
difference in usage of the job
and genghis khan would be more like for
example if you
if you see someone who seems to be
stressed out
or hurt or something you would check up
on their health or
uh yeah something like that so you check
up if they're actually okay it's more
like are you okay
than how i ah okay it's like a wellness
yeah exactly but thank you this guy is
more the general how
are you um but by the way i
i heard that um in
in english-speaking countries like
atlantis um
that when you ask someone how are you
you don't actually
expect an answer the other person would
just reply with how are you
which i think is kind of rude okay
answer to my question
wait wait what how are you how are you
yeah i do this
yeah right yeah right that's so
interesting in my
first language we always answer and in
japanese you also should answer this is
not just some
random phrase you throw out there is
that you actually want an answer for
this
so uh i'll also teach you the answer
yeah you can play people often say you
can answer uh
i think it's actually a a bad habit that
i definitely have which is answering a
question with a question
it frustrates a lot of people i talk to
but i think the most common answer
you're gonna get
from an english speaker if you ask how
are you is uh good in you
yeah yeah yeah but that sounds almost
like uh gura
you what are you good are you good at
you
sounds actually exactly the same thing
well um it's so it's wrong
it's just uh the way people speak in
atlantis i suppose but
um here here we do answer uh
this question so the answer would be uh
actually pretty easy so you probably can
guess it yourself
uh yes or if you actually asked uh how
you
uh said it before it does you could just
say that
but that's again a kind of a kind of a
different situation there
but it's good enough so thank you
thank you thank you by the way do you
know how to
say the opposite
uh you can just
how do you say you can just negate wait
that's not the word
thing you could just say genki
[Music]
genki zhang yeah okay or
if you know any other words like for
example kanashii is sad you could say
kanashides
or if you say yeah or if you say
um if you want to say i'm angry you can
say
geki oko punto marudes
sorry i'm laughing on my own because
that's just funny to me
i'm saying it wait say again
japanese people are laughing in chat
it's a it's kind of a a meme
i guess
[Laughter]
you don't have to remember that it's a
it's kind of a cute way to say you're
angry
or you just say um you can say just
that's cute i never want to meet an
angry shark but
for now she seems to be in good spirits
so i feel safe
but if you want to say like mad or if
you
if you if you're not sure how you feel
or if you don't want to be honest with
your feelings you can just say
mama this
oh wait hey can you also say that about
food like if somebody asks you how the
food is
you say oyshee or you if it's not really
for your taste you can say
mama mommy exactly yes
ah it's like a it's like
yeah it is something in between but
it does um if you would say that about
someone's food
the person who cooked it would probably
be insulted
yeah but if you're if you're at a
restaurant and maybe your friend asks
you like oh are you good
is it good yeah to a friend you can
definitely say that
very good be open and be honest about
your feelings yes i like that
yeah uh okay so one thing that you
can use for so many things to express
your emotions
is saying i like something i like food i
like you
blah blah blah you probably know how to
say that
um
you definitely i think you used it
before talking about the senpai
probably nice key yeah
that's that's i like it very much or
even i love it but if you just want to
say i like something
[Music]
get rid of the guy escape
yes yes
everyone clipped the moment she just
said that ski and oh my god use it for
everything
just set it as your alarm or something
and keep on replaying it
sk
perfect that's what we wanted to hear
but yeah and you would say
something something ski but if you want
to that is enough but if you want to
have like an actual proper sentence you
would say
something something this but you don't
have to
this is enough to just say um
[Music]
and the dye skins is a bit more extreme
version
yeah so that would be
and by the way um the the you in
japanese
you pronounced it actually perfect uh
when when you just said ski
you uh silenced the you
[Applause]
okay that made my heart skip a million
beats
uh but i'm fine because i actually
instantly
revived after i had a heart attack right
now for a moment
i'm already back good morning i am alive
ohio
[Music]
but sometimes um sometimes you actually
do pronounce to you
like it's not a must but mostly you
you silence the you in most situations
but also in some songs you would say
uh you would say that you just to have
it sound better
yeah it's not a must i like style points
yeah you could say it that way
okay and one one way this seems kind of
randomly placed but
uh i'm just um i just put it there as an
example to say
my favorite anything is so in this case
my favorite color is
uh do you know how to say something
favorite
[Music]
it has it has the suki in it
oh no okay no problem
no problem just checking what you
already know so i know what i can teach
you
uh it is basically something something
ichiban number one life
is
or uh if we actually have wait that that
that is uh
the sentence is not quite uh will
translate if you translate the sentence
directly
it's um ichiban skina
ichiban skina iroba
[Music]
and i heard you adding uh an i at the
end there which is
okay in some cases um but in this case
he would just say
ow so basically ichiban means number one
suki means like na is like the thing you
uh see this is uh where the problem
comes in that i taught japanese myself i
don't know the terms for grammar or
stuff
not the particle yeah exactly
you know you know it's color uh why it's
another one of these weird particles
our is the color blue that you got on
your own
perfect perfect hundred points and this
is you know what that is
but by the way you could even get rid of
the desu it's not hundred percent
necessary you could end the sentence at
ichiban
oh but people like to you like to
put dazzle at the end to make it sound
more complete
i guess this okay
and then um that is a very
uh that is that that sentence in itself
but if you want to say for example
um
[Music]
or anything else what else do you like
the most out of a category of something
ah
[Music]
you say salmon salmon
for example what's your what's your
favorite uh
game genre rhythm game
oh yeah so you would say
[Music]
come on use your brain
actually the good thing about rhythm
game in japanese you would say the same
thing you would just pronounce it a
little bit more japanese so it would be
like
um
the reason why english words uh sound
kind of different in japanese
uh is and now i'm gonna sound very smart
here
is because japanese language uh the the
letters hiragana and katakana
uh come in syllables mostly almost all
of them
have two letters so for example ga is
one hiragana but comes with ga
right and
[Music]
also d a so that is why they cannot
like exactly recreate our words
in the japanese language but just try
their best with those syllables
syllabus is the right word right yes
is it is it yes is it yeah
um yeah i think
yeah so but but there's there's a few
letters in japanese that have only one
letter so for example
and was there anything else i think
that's probably about i might be missing
out on something but
pretty much that's it so these yes are
one letter but everything else always
comes with two letters and
um but the thing is that you is often
silent in japanese language
so for example there's a silent you
at the end so it gets it gets close
enough but
japanese people still like to say the
you
out loud in that case like
they in that case they do they do
pronounce it
yeah there's times when they pronounce
it in times when they don't but the hue
is very useful
in recreating uh english words
i'm not i'm not an actual teacher
actually i'm a fake teacher so uh i
might just stumble over my words here
it's okay i'm still learning a lot so
this is good i like this
that's how it is that's how it is okay
so we learned
another another many things
would you like to repeat after me
hi um genki desu
[Music]
oh
um
[Laughter]
oh yes this is this is beautiful
ichiban
[Music]
perfect student she actually puts in her
own words how smart is she
you know there's one thing that we have
in common guna
oh is that people um make fun of my bird
brain and people make fun of your shark
brain
but let's be real our brains are the
strongest okay
exactly we just need a bit more buffer
time that's all
there's nothing wrong with this software
it's the it's the internet
yes connection's bad that's all
you know what i think i think you earned
yourself
another apple
yes balancing the apples here we go
they're getting a little bit in the way
of me
so let me move myself ringo
[Music]
first of all it was only one so you
would have said
lingoka
the thing is with japanese you count
things really differently depending on
what it is for example um
[Music]
for example for people he would say
hitori futani
it it's really difficult to remember all
of these but one thing that you can use
for almost uh everything
and they will forgive you it's not
correct but they will forgive you
is iko
etc yeah yeah yeah
so now you have how many apples
yes
[Music]
my child is growing up
and it's all thanks to you
[Laughter]
okay okay serious time kiara
we are far from being done okay i
prepared a lot actually let's see how
far we can get
oh oh oh oh damn okay next slide oh wait
that was not the
ah nope no no no that comes a little bit
later
no no first of all
first of all we stay we stay pure and
say so first of all okay that was a
spoiler in in what's coming
because um i i think it's useful to know
some
some not so nice words as well so i'm
gonna teach you eventually but
not not too bad words but for now we
have some other
important words to teach you it's always
important to expand the vocabulary yes
good and bad yes yes okay
so i think sharks are often very hungry
so you might need
this uh this phrase especially
do you know how to say you're hungry
there's a bunch of ways to say it
[Music]
i think do you remember yeah i think i
remember asking you how i said this
uh a long time ago oh yeah i did teach
you a cute
way to say it yeah yeah i remember i
remember coming to keanu i was like you
gotta help me
yeah right that did happen
but you don't remember do you i don't
remember
okay so there's a cute way to say it
that i taught her originally
uh you could say
[Music]
i think is that what i taught you i
think yeah
it means that your your stomach is empty
but it's a very cute way to say it the
actual way to say it
would be um
or ona kagatta
is means like empty and heta means like
it has become less you know what i mean
so you can use all of this but maybe
it's already easy for you to remember
pekko pekka
because it's a cute word if you forget
about it think about uh pecora senpai
what i was thinking
yeah that's an easy way to remember it
but you always you should probably say
unaka in front of it which means
stomach so that they know
what you're talking about
should i write this in hiragana or in
kanji i write it in
kanji to flex
[Music]
and that's definitely something i think
a shark will have to use very often to
express her feelings
um but also very important one one thing
that i want to teach you
that i need to say to you is
you are beautiful now there's also many
ways to say this one
oh boy you can't see it but i'm blushing
so you could if you if you don't know
how to say this you can always say
kawaii because it means cute and pretty
but if you want to be a bit more exact
you could say
this
[Music]
you can say that not only about people
but also
about objects so you can say that
jewelry is very kidding
try to say some english words in
japanese sometimes it sounds
very uh difficult
how do you say uh the moon is pretty
do you know how to say the moon moon
[Music]
yes coincidence i think not
[Laughter]
what a good student i must give her all
the apples that i have later on
do i really have to write it down i have
no space on my chalkboard
squishy this or uh
there you go is that oh
yeah that's a good word by the way uh i
said i said
it fits it is when something is just
barely making it for example if you
barely made it in time for your
class you said kitty giddy money atta
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah exactly or if
my skirt is too short we all know it's
not too short there's never too short
skirt
but my my skirt is indeed very giddy
giddy very kitty kitty
that is very geeky repeat after me
chiara tiara
noscato noscato
[Music]
is for real very um i actually don't
translate it it's like barely
barely acceptable barely barely
ah oh so it's like uh on on the border
of
not not okay or on the border of
anything
yeah for example like how how we had the
example was like making it in time for
class
we're guilty kitty on time barely on
time
actually not barely barely barely
implies that you didn't make it right
gideon is more like you actually did
make it or like it's like
really like you almost didn't make it
but you did make it
yeah but that's difficult to uh
difficult to
uh explain sorry
okay okay
perfect where did you pick that up
uh anime i mean
i see i see so you do learn some things
from anime i thought
you don't really learn stuff if you only
watch anime
whoever says that is a liar
people that believe that media is media
and your brain is a sponge you're going
to pick up stuff no matter what media
you consume and if that's
anime and you're learning language from
anime good for you
because gosh darn it okay sorry
okay next one this is this if you use
this in your stream
japanese people will think you're very
smart
do you know how to say shark fact in
japanese
[Music]
fact almost you got half of it right
i would personally say i would
personally say some
shiki it's like knowledge
but i think it comes close enough so it
says
yeah so
if you if you're on stream you say i
have a
ski
mask
say whatever you want to say there the
the kanji for that it's very difficult
but
written out it's just
wow very difficult kanji very difficult
especially after seeing what the
hiragana is wow it's okay
you don't have to the good thing is if
you have a japanese keyboard installed
and do you do you i do not okay
so you probably don't know how this
works but if you type japanese you write
the hiragana and then
you uh it already starts like
recommending you
whatever is like it could be
and often there's several options for
what it could be especially if it's only
one letter there's like a million
um and then you just choose the one
that's how japanese people write on
their phones or their keyboards they
keep on choosing
the kanjis that they want sometimes it
does it automatically sometimes you have
to uh correct it
if it's the wrong one that your phone on
your pc chose
yeah yeah can you imagine a keyboard on
the pc with every single kanji
uh no that's then
i have a i have a japanese keyboard and
it has the romaji letters on it
but also for each romantic letter
there's also a hiragana on it
but now this is probably some
information you don't really need but um
oh this is gonna be hard to explain
anyway whatever so anyway
you have everything on the keyboard but
no kanji it's just hiragana on the
keyboard itself but
uh when you write on your pc or your
phone whatever it just uh
um transforms it into the kanji that you
want
and if you write out tishiki on your
keyboard
the right one is actually this one is
the only option it gives you anyway
so you wouldn't even make a mistake i
think
yeah oh okay so i can't wait to use that
yeah my big brain now you got that
you're welcome is uh probably something
you also heard before do you remember
how to say you're welcome
[Music]
ah yes yes okay
very polite this way
if someone says um
[Music]
thank you if you say if you say to me uh
thank you for the apple
lingo
you can also say i guess dozer
and i i don't i don't really
hear it that much used that way dozer is
more like um
um there you go
[Music]
i can i guess you could say it but yeah
let's go
and then for example if you want to go
to a place in minecraft
for example a village you could use this
phrase to
sound again like a smart chuck you could
say
let's go to the village do you know how
to say that
yeah well okay that's the that's uh that
the
informal way of saying that uh
let's see we can say we can totally stay
informal that's no problem
but for example mura is village
[Music]
is the polite way of staying let's go
somewhere
nanda then we have to repeat all this
you did a really good job on this one as
well go down but let's see
let's repeat this
[Music]
by the way there's a more uh rough way
of saying that
um girls usually don't say it more like
the men said i
actually also say it sometimes but yeah
people say
speak more like a girl you could say
yeah but that's not not a very girlish
way of saying it
girls usually say
but sometimes i say haraheka give me
some food give me some burgers
and you're hungry and hungry as long as
it gets the point across yeah
yeah aggressively
[Music]
actually that that was probably not
exactly how you wanted to say it but
it's actually also
uh it it does mean something my show is
more like
let's start eating now
but you probably want to say let's go
eat that's more like taban
[Music]
myself uh it's okay we gotta
have some confidence right i have
confidence
okay and sami
yes i noticed something about your
japanese pronunciation
it's really good you you um kind of
silenced
the eye in chi right now
she you said uh no uh in in she
and she you silenced the eye you said
that's amazing how do you know that how
do you know you're supposed to do that
i'm mimicking you
my my fluent teacher you have a good
teacher indeed
yes the thing is for again you don't
always have to silence it it's okay if
you don't silence it but silencing it is
a it's a very correct way of speaking
japanese society
[Music]
um
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
i can't stop i can't stop there we go
next one
a little bit more than half time all
right so
next slide before we get into the bad
words
oh okay so
these are some good words to end the
conversation or end a meeting
and uh like for example if you had a
date with kiara sensei
at the end you would say maybe these
things okay
so for first of all i had fun have you
ever heard of the word for fun
yes
[Laughter]
you caught me off guard and yes
so uh if you want to say i had fun
do you know how to say that the past
tense of a word like tanoshii something
that has
she at the end of it
[Music]
and also senpai oh i'm looking up from
uh sometimes nice yeah i can imagine
them saying that sometimes
so tanos by the way tanuscata
is written with a kanji
that's that you read also as uh
and it means fun but also can mean
for example if you say um
that was a piece of cake you can say
laksha
raksha and that has the raku in it as
well
it means
[Music]
fun and easy win so you say
at the end of the game you say
also it's like gigi oh yeah
that was a random ah actually
never underestimate a bird okay bird
brain
hmm so you say foreign
example uh phasmophobia
right hi hi okay
do you know how to say let's meet again
don't feel bad about not being able to
see it
i don't know okay no problem you just
say um
the informal way is mata
and the former way is
[Music]
and then there's some two two ways of
saying
bye-bye um maybe you know the exact
maybe you know the difference so um you
probably heard of matane
hi you probably heard of sayonara
all right the difference between these
is sayonara you expect to not meet that
person anymore today at least or maybe
even for a long time
oh so i think farewell is the right word
for it in english i wasn't sure
is that do you use farewell in that kind
of way
farewell that's that's very serious that
seems almost dramatic
like that's what you would say uh in a
movie
if you know somebody was going away
forever you'd say farewell you can't
you can definitely use sayonara in a
very dramatic way as well though you can
be like
sayonara my dear lover i will never meet
you again
something like that but yeah it doesn't
have to be that serious but
you get it
[Music]
yeah okay so maybe if you weren't going
to see somebody again for a long time
you say
yes but even also for it just if you
don't see them again today
if you don't expect them to see them
again today or the whole week or so
it doesn't have to be a super long time
it just has to be uh
not anymore in the in the very near
future
you also can say that if you don't see
them anymore today it is
it's okay as well you just say if you
expect to meet that person at some point
again
you say again directly translated it's
right ah
okay again ain't it
again ain't it so the ammo way to say it
okay and then the last word i want to
uh really um i want you really to
remember this one you probably heard of
it before but this is a
if you work with someone yeah or
anything you use this so often
do you know it
[Music]
yes
but you don't only say that uh at the
end of something
um
what's good just made up something for
you to use
what's called a style
but okay so you say that for example
um at the beginning as well though for
if you greet someone
uh you say uh uh
like like you always
tend to say this out of like it's just a
it's just a way that is
it is a phrase that always makes itself
into a conversation
you can say that at the in the beginning
of a sentence
this or at the end of the stream at the
end of a
class at the end of the email or not
for emails it's at the beginning sorry
that's a weird thing
yeah but you you always say that it
makes you so polite
and so respectful
[Music]
though can you say
i would usually start off my message
with
uh senpai
ah just out of respect because i know
pekula senpai is always working hard
and i'm disturbing her in her peaceful
time
so i say what's going on i'm sorry blah
blah blah
i want to talk to you
this is if you know this word you
everyone
thinks you're amazing you know japanese
manners you know what you're doing there
is or past tenses
okay yes
let's say we're saying goodbye to each
other
yeah i made something up there i said
today was fun
[Music]
yes
perfect perfect by the way for everyone
in the stream we're not leaving yet
please
stay it's not over yet it's not open
class is not dismissed get your butts
back in the chairs
you have earned yourself another apple
yay single get how many
[Music]
but i know what you're trying to do
there because young the number four
can be read as for er
as she sorry my brain
it can be read as she um but depending
on what you're counting
uh it it is either
wait is it
yeah uh so normally if you count you can
often say it's nissan xi or it's nissan
yeah i guess so but if you count
something with ko
then it is
okay now we get um excuse me everyone
um i shall teach
my little shark some words in case she
gets angry
during a game or something actually
classes are rated now guys
yes listen up let the pens out here we
go it's gonna be on the test
there we go i don't want to teach you
like super bad words to be honest um
i i don't even know like super super
super super super super bad words i mean
maybe i do but
i just let's just say i don't but i'll
teach you some that are acceptable i
would say
okay these are acceptable
[Music]
acceptable i see yes
okay let's see let's see what what we
can do here well let's see if you you
probably know a few of those as well
yes do you know how to say crap
yes yes
i mean no i don't know how to say that
i do you but actually um is a part of
the nickname that kelly
likes to give me sotori shitbirds
but only cali is allowed to call me that
so don't don't
don't don't you use it
but yes yeah you can you can use saw in
so
many ways actually you can even use it
positively
[Music]
oh it's like saying ah that's damn good
hell yeah
hell yeah crazy
uh yeah i actually also sometimes just
out of reflex
uh i say just so when
when i hit my uh
actually no i say it for hurting uh but
yeah you can say
in any in any situation positive bad
situation
anything now these are two ways to say
idiot you probably know at least one of
them
[Music]
that's that's one very cute way of
saying it but there's one more
er which
[Music]
and by the way there's um for baka
uh the kanji is really difficult um
[Music]
very difficult you don't have to
remember that you can just write it in
katakana or even hiragana it doesn't
matter
for these swear words it actually really
doesn't matter they uh japanese people
write it in many ways they write it in
in
hiragana and in katakana and in kanji
okay now i teach you a phrase i wonder
if you can
remember this uh eventually
uh but i i like this phrase um
okay don't don't f around with me i
would personally translate it to
[Music]
actually it doesn't it doesn't have the
f word in it in japanese
yeah but it is like uh yeah but it
pretty much comes out the same way so um
[Music]
sound more intimidating to assert your
dominance
oh
[Laughter]
is like seriously or for real like
it's um it's it's a good word you can
use for it also for
mati or sheen like for real that's so
tasty
[Music]
it comes from the japanese word sorry
i'm writing that here right now but it
comes from the word majime
which means serious seriously
and uh yes people uh abbreviate it
as magi
okay
[Music]
i mean grammatically it's a bit weird
because you said no
ah it's like you don't even have to say
that particle to make it easier for you
and it's still correct you can just say
that
[Music]
hawaii
but actually you don't only use it for a
shut up you can say for example if
uh if music is too loud you can say ah
or if the traffic is too loud you can
say also
oh so it can be kind of polite like yeah
it means
quiet it actually means noisy
oh yeah so you as again you can use it
in a good way as well i mean not
necessarily cool way by
it doesn't have to be um yeah you could
[Music]
it is quite condescending quite um
angry but if guys usually always say oh
my to each other
then in that case it is not
condescending
wait when do you use all my oh my i mean
as a girl
you usually don't use it unless you're
angry
or or way way way too friendly with
someone
like if you're really friendly with
someone you you i guess you can't say oh
my but
normally girls don't use it but men uh
like to use it
to everyone is it is it just like a wait
wait how to get somebody's attention
right no no it's uh
it's you it means you oh that's right
[Music]
exactly very famous phrase that
we all know okay
and one last one uh i'll kick your ass
um well personally i would translate
that to
uh uh
it's actually like i'll send you flying
something like that but yeah it's like a
class but
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
i guess you could also say
uh it also means i'll click your ass
yes
[Music]
so that people will forgive you
oh yes okay let's repeat these and sound
really really angry okay
[Music]
ahoy
what
you got that you got the rolling r down
really well i actually can't do that
[Laughter]
actually um i would have ended it here
but i thought um we maybe need some
[Music]
we maybe need some
sorry i had to i just had we need we
need some reading practice now i
actually don't have the
hiragana for that so i'll read it with
you and i want you just not
to not think just trust me here okay
just dress up um
and read uh like
repeat after everything after it's quite
long
it's um it's a poem that i prepared for
you
okay hi repeat with me
[Music]
oh
i have officially recruit everyone
in japanese
japanese and i got kula's voice for it
so now we can remix it
ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's what you're doing at the end you
were singing it at the end i didn't pick
up on
it i was trying i was trying it was a
bit hard because i had to stop
for yourself ah i was so focused on the
words i was like is she singing
although the japanese lyrics uh i think
they they don't suit the melody that
well it doesn't fit that well gotta try
to really make it fit
there for anyone who wants to try
remixing it
[Applause]
well i just i just it's my personal
feelings to you i just
i just want to tell you how i'm feeling
i gotta make you understand yeah
[Music]
never gonna make you cry never gonna
stay sayonara
and hurt you
it's such a good song isn't it yeah
we should cover it together someday oh
yes
can you imagine me doll um holding my
chicken drums actually it's like
actually the perfect pose
uh cheeky drumsticks for the synth drum
dance my hand is cutting up there at the
end of this oh
when we are in 3d we gotta do another
dance you know how fancy he dances there
oh yeah around the microphone yeah
such a good dancer
so smooth so i hope
you um maybe like remember i few
things uh let's see how much the shark
brain remembers maybe there will be a
part two one day maybe or i'll teach you
german
instead uh because i don't know as some
people know my first language is
german and gonna actually turn the
deutsche
is so cool wow good actually took some
german
uh before apparently yeah
and the first time i heard it i
absolutely fell in love with it so i
think at some point i have to hear some
more japanese
german from you
[Music]
hi
actually you deserve one more apple for
that
let me put one more last apple there
there we go
and now how many apples
[Music]
oh
you were such a good student even uh you
weren't even like
sitting still the whole class like i'm
proud of you
but i mean you were kind of looking out
of the window but still because i'm duct
taped to this chair
the zip ties they hurt release me
[Laughter]
sorry i will release you now so um
everyone thank you for
coming to watch my classroom my lesson
was good on my private lesson
i think we'll continue to probably
listen a little bit behind the curtains
thank you good i had so much fun with
you you're such a good student
you're such a good teacher i learned i
learned a lot
i was actually worried about that
because um well i taught japanese myself
i didn't have a teacher for that
uh so i don't really know how to explain
things
very detailed and very logically
but the basics i can totally teach you
so
that's incredible that's really
incredible wow
thank you thank you but i i just i just
had a lot of time to communicate with
japanese people
so i think if you if you try to do some
communication and maybe one day
you can do a really really scuffed
japanese only stream
really scuffed one and that would
probably help you with your
communication skills back
in japanese well
maybe one day a few more lessons with
kiana sensei
and then yes oh yes i will prepare you
for the big scary
world out there one day one day we will
maybe
all meet together in japan and
and for that i have to prepare my little
student
so at the end of my streams actually we
say in german
uh auf wiedersehen do you want to say
that one
yes please of course you even you
probably even uh remember that word do
you know
[Music]
okay everyone thanks for watching today
i'll be
back again i'll see you
so guys bye-bye
[Music]
you