learn chant with
K now we're going to do like K-pop style
chant the ketchup remember is
like if you have light sticks in your
hand then just hold the light sticks and
you go
like there's also a variation of that
where you
clap while doing it clap you can do that
in the beginning
ooh and then basically everything that
is blue you're going to scream out loud
with me the pom pom ponga is this PCH
PCH PCH he clap clap clap hi at a
highlighted moment like the chorus when
there's a little bit of a gap they go
like that's it you just have to learn
the lyrics that's all you got to do then
let's listen to this from the beginning
[Music]
going
under I still wonder
[Music]
I'll do you I'll do
you okay okay
[Music]
okay don't this mess
my
[Music]
Mir Escape my
way perfect I know
okay okay I'm ready I'm
ready oh no you I'll
[Music]
[Applause]
you don't live this mess
my
[Music]
Mir on
on here we go
[Music]
don't win
this My
[Music]
Mirage me me me me
yay nailed it