​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​Lately,​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't help but feel like I'm being watched...​ ​​
​​​ ​It doesn't matter where I am.​ ​​
​​​ ​Out shopping, working,​ ​​
​​​ ​at home alone in my bath...​ ​​
​​​ ​I can feel someone watching me.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey... I've been wondering...​ ​​
​​​ ​Have you guys felt anything​ ​​
​​​ ​weird lately?​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you mean?​ ​​
​​​ ​Like, more weird than normal?​ ​​
​​​ ​Like...​ ​​
​​​ ​Like the feeling of being watched.​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you forget that we're idols, Bae?​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course we're being watched.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's the point.​ ​​
​​​ ​No, not like that...​ ​​
​​​ ​On stage, yeah, we're being watched,​ ​​
​​​ ​but it's not just when we're performing.​ ​​
​​​ ​When I'm alone too, I...​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know,​ ​​
​​​ ​it just feels like someone is staring at me.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, having so many of us living together,​ ​​
​​ ​it would make sense, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's not like we're ever really alone.​ ​​
​​​ ​If this is about the time I walked in​ ​​
​​ ​on you in the bathroom, I'm sorry!​ ​​
​​​ ​With her around,​ ​​
​​ ​I can understand your pain.​ ​​
​​​ ​How many times have​ ​​
​​ ​you walked in on me again?​ ​​
​​​ ​At this point,​ ​​
​​​ ​I have to wonder if it's intentional...​ ​​
​​​ ​Noooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's not intentional!​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't be ridiculous!​ ​​
​​​ ​Suuure, IRyS, suuure~​ ​​
​​​ ​You don't think it could be someone​ ​​
​​ ​staring through the windows, do you?​ ​​
​​​ ​Like a stalker?​ ​​
​​​ ​No... It's not something like that...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's hard to explain...​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe...​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe it's nothing.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm sure it's nothing, Bae!​ ​​
​​​ ​Try not to let it​ ​​
​​ ​get you down before the show!​ ​​
​​​ ​Right, thanks.​ ​​
​​​ ​Why are you watching me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Who are you?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey... Sorry to interrupt...​ ​​
​​​ ​The driver's waiting outside.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh, yeah, just a minute...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, Bae?​ ​​
​​​ ​Is everything okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​You don't have to hide it from me...​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh, yeah...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's...​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know...​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like I'm going crazy...​ ​​
​​​ ​Even right now...​ ​​
​​ ​It feels like someone is watching...​ ​​
​​​ ​Not you, someone else...​ ​​
​​​ ​I believe you, man.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, if you want to​ ​​
​​ ​cancel the show tonight, it's okay...​ ​​
​​​ ​I can talk to our manager and...​ ​​
​​​ ​No no no,​ ​​
​​​ ​it's okay...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's just go...​ ​​
​​​ ​How do you style your hair with these horns?​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't.​ ​​
​​​ ​Remove them for me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ehh?!​ ​​
​​​ ​You want me to remove them?​ ​​
​​​ ​First of all, I don't even know how to do that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Second of all, you should be happy to have​ ​​
​​ ​such great weapons attached to your head!​ ​​
​​​ ​Weapons, hm?​ ​​
​​​ ​I never thought of it like that...​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, I guess I'll keep them.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can I wear one of your hats?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oi, I need these!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here, I'll give you twin buns.​ ​​
​​​ ​Something cute for IWyS~​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiwawa~​ ​​
​​​ ​Ladies, it's time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Already?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's do this, girls.​ ​​
​​​ ​Calli... What happened?​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't want you to​ ​​
​​ ​worry about that anymore...​ ​​
​​​ ​Everything is going to be okay now.​ ​​
​​​ ​H-Hey, are you okay?!​ ​​
​​ ​You're bleeding!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, this?​ ​​
​​​ ​I...​ ​​
​​​ ​I just wanted to make sure you'd be okay...​ ​​
​​​ ​That you wouldn't feel watched anymore...​ ​​
​​​ ​What? What did you do?​ ​​
​​​ ​I got rid of them all... For you...​ ​​
​​​ ​Why are you still watching?​ ​​