so
do
[Music]
hello
time game for both of us yeah yeah
never played it it looks like a co-op
did you ever play club
before quack quack
or quack quack quack quack i think
i think i i think i have a feeling that
i know
what you're talking about it's like you
have to control every
limb with like a different keys with
q-u-o-p
it's something like that qw yeah
a bit similar like in this game you
can not move many limbs actually the
only thing you could maybe move is like
your your knees so you can jump
[Music]
but mostly you move like your body has
like
one face yeah you will see okay
wait yeah and i think in co-op mode we
have to work
together or yeah better
oh okay together okay so we're in the i
think
am i you're the one that's picking the
thingy there's story and then ah
yeah yeah i think we have to start with
this one
oh okay i am so
let's get right into it first the first
time
in a long time
i was like one of those things where i
was like it's gonna do something before
we started but then i forgot
i just got to give bubba a treat
ten seconds okay hold on a second yes
yes
giving bubba treat for people who don't
know i also have now pets with me i
moved
back from japan to australia uh
which is not really australia i guess
many people here don't get that joke
uh i'm in europe now and i also have
cats and they also get lots of treats
but but they already got their treats
but yeah i want a treat yeah i can give
me
one
ew i don't think you like that those
kind of treats they're kind of
disgusting probably for humans you have
chicken
you have chicken no
actually i don't i don't give them
chicken treats i don't i don't even know
what that is
a mix of like fishy stuff oh yeah i
don't want whatever
cats eat weird drinks but but dogs too
but they also eat lots of normal stuff
too don't they my dog likes to eat cat
poop
sometimes they'll do that that's like a
common thing dogs will just go
into the cat litter box
oh my god but it's perfect then because
you have a cat too right so
yeah but i know they haven't done that
in a really long time yeah
okay okay not in like three or four
years or something yeah
oh my god i wonder what's so tasty about
cat poop
nutritious maybe i don't know
i think there is a scientific reason
like if they're lacking vitamins or
something they'll do that
yeah yeah they eat arteries
[Laughter]
dancing at the end of your stream what
dance moves
wait you don't see it no you see those
two bunnies dancing
no you don't what do you see on your
screen right now
a little island is spinning in a circle
and then there's clouds behind it
do i press it right now oh yeah yeah do
that
oh uh do you see the dancers dancing
bunnies
oh yeah now i see them oh yeah it does
look like bubba
yeah the 3d ending dance you know
actually today
so we somehow got to the idea in my
stream that
um the way that you have that 3d bubble
dancing ending the really cursed one
oh my god oh my oh my god i got it my
cats just jumped on me
yeah we got to the idea that maybe
someone could make that the same thing
with my cats but i was like no please no
that's too crazy i don't want to see
myself like that
doing something different like a
different type of dance move but
something is similar yeah
no the dancing is fine um but the
the the body that your dog was made into
that's something i would not like to see
my cats
okay okay well it fits your
your dog but yeah what are you trying to
say
i don't know yeah are you
wait you're you're yellow oh yeah you're
yellow no i'm pink
okay i'm yellow yeah yeah i'm here
so if you want to go up there oh goodbye
no we can help each other i guess thank
you but you can also jump with w
oh okay uh it's a bit difficult
but let's let's the first few levels
should be easy
let's go
wait we can grab each other this is wait
this is
easy oh yeah oh yeah grabbing is with uh
the left
side shift but yeah i never used it when
i played alone i
i i played like one level and i didn't
use it i played a lot
i i'm i'm pinkie how do i what would i
grab you for oh
oh we're like in the circus right now
like that oh you got my feet okay now
we can do like a like a like a wheel
oh oh my god oh my god
because you fell no i i was just trying
to jump as much as i could
and then i didn't think i could do lunch
to the left side of the screen careful
first one
[Laughter]
[Music]
we're bunnies now isn't it nice to be a
bunny did you see you're surrounded in
whole life english you're pretty much
surrounded by weird animals oh yeah you
can never feel like you want to be an
animal too
yeah i thought about it my my chat asked
me if like a
if uh we were all animal i guess because
you're kind of already animal themed
and only me and callie are animal themed
i guess oh yeah kellyanne
ever i guess yeah yeah that's true i
said and maybe it'd be a hat
oh thank you
can i take that nice you gotta be
you gotta go go with your hands not your
feet
oh difficult very hard you could store
it somewhere maybe
take it with you yeah maybe it's like a
bonus
what conclusion did you come what kind
of uh oh i got it but it's like
well callie would be like a raven themed
oh yeah and then i know i didn't really
settle on one for mine i think i said
like uh
maybe a hyena or maybe like a beaver
because my teeth i mean i think a beaver
would be good too
that's some interesting choices so
really original choices
bye-bye bye-bye
[Music]
well i can't help you you're too far
just let go i like those two oh we both
let go
oh i thought you would say something
like something like dog doggle like
don't go like yours yeah but we already
have oh you know how i where you gotta
go
i guess okay you wanted to be something
original huh
i have a big beaver tail beaver huh
that's kind of cute did someone make
like menard out of that they should make
something out of that
yeah give me a big tail and then you
know beavers like when they slap stuff
it's like
yeah that's so cute
what the hell it kind of you kind of
have to die too
oh wait oh we i see or you make it alone
maybe
maybe that works too if you okay over
there alone
that's quite the distance you don't have
it
maybe we have to go together okay let's
let's try although that level existed uh
in solo play as well so oh it should be
possible alone as well oh okay
what you get that's what you get my dear
detective
okay i'll try to do it on my own i'm uh
i believe in independent bunny
i'm an independent bunny i'm an
independent bunny i don't need no one
gonna light it up line it up
line it up
[Music]
i'm making a bridge for you
i tried to push you down wasn't that the
same spot where you died before
yeah okay okay okay so you want me to
get in what kind of pose please tell me
exactly what
that pose just like that yeah but maybe
a little bit closer to the edge
yeah i was gonna recommend if you tip
backwards and then jump
you like spring up i think you're
thinking
very deep about this don't fall down i'm
in
do i have to help you
thank you
i don't think you wanted to do that did
you want to do that i wanted to help you
i didn't want it sorry
i couldn't help it you can do it
so uh it back yep that's too far
oh wait wait
when you're coming back down i think
that oh
[Music]
i don't know what i'm doing
um
maybe you try making it over there okay
i'll leave it to you now
wow she got those
damn show me what you got show me what
you got
oh that was pretty good
i think we can only i think the ending
is there but i think it only is there
when we're both
alive maybe oh yeah
really maybe i think so
okay i'll make it this time this moves
damn
okay so why did you do that again i
don't know
oh okay we can grab each other
okay wait stop stop for like
relax relax
here we go again we could have made it
no sorry
okay oh wow i'm sorry my cat i had to uh
talk to my cats
she i have to answer them you know do
you also
always answer your doggle i do yeah i in
my kitty cat yeah sometimes he'll he'll
meow
and then okay wait be careful wait
okay like this and then when you when
you're
on the way back down then you jump
uh-huh okay so
yeah nice i didn't differently but i did
it
yeah wait okay now i have to do it
i'm scared i'm scared
wait hold on you can always you can
always
time travel back and redo it
don't worry we got it yeah i think
thank you i think nice to meet you maybe
since you can do it then you have to
like uh
you have to help me like kick me over
there now i have to help you
now i have to help you weren't you the
one who was like i know i had to do that
move i i'll teach you i don't remember
how i did it
is it short time memories yeah it's
because it takes yeah i have that
problem yeah yeah i get that too i get
like really
short time memory problems oh my god
again
probably from all the reviving i have
memory issues and you have my
orientations
from all the time traveling damn we
should probably stop uh messing with the
time zone
time and time
true you don't play around with that
stuff
oh okay here we go again wait
um kick me over
okay
[Music]
hmm will we ever make it yes we will
this time this is the one this is the
right one and i feel it
i feel like my bones don't feel
filmed
polka senpai has been real quiet
watching our circus dance moves
you're here talking anymore oh oh oh
sorry
please sacrifice yourself this is
okay sure last time we worked together i
shoot you over there but then yeah
i was oh my god what the hell is that
[Music]
okay this is a good practice for me okay
you started right as i was supposed to
play
okay just died uh
we'll get it eventually sometimes you
have to admit your defeat
in order to not suffer anymore
oh this part is easy okay now here we go
again okay
maybe you go first door i'm scared
okay i'll i'll go maybe
i'll catch you if you follow oh that's
so romantic
yeah we'll make a bridge across okay
[Applause]
is
next door okay let's see what we got oh
no spike
i would die with you romeo and juliet
did you hear my cat just now oh yeah
it's cute
with me okay i'm professional
come on come on come on my sticky keys
no sticky keys you're having sticky key
prompts thingy yeah i feel like some
attack saving person like yeah you would
have already turned that i know i
haven't turned it off yet because i
usually don't i don't need to
i don't usually press shift that oh that
was my fault this time
oh my god you need to turn that off
i know i could do it right now but i
don't want it okay
yeah what can you do with it on the rest
of it you think you can grab it oh i got
it
oh yo bonus points
but yeah someone shifted it we can't
clear that level right now
you couldn't do anything about it it was
very surprising
okay oh
nice nice nice
you you can do it you can do it
one more time did you see that long jump
wow nice cats
nice okay let me grab you okay let's go
together
[\h__\h] that carrot we don't need it
[Laughter]
yeah let's check
one more jump keep jumping backwards
nice jump i guess it would be here i bet
okay yeah look into it this might be
the last like section of that level oh
okay
i feel like okay let's go maybe
um should i should we should we grab
each other again or
uh damn it
okay i'll die right here i'll die i
if you need help
[Music]
i can't hold it anymore
you know what i mean you're pretty cute
bunny though i'll give you that
[Music]
oh i didn't die from that oh a little a
little blob is okay oh
that was too much blood i'll go with you
does that hurt i feel like that's that
might be like a good uh
oh oh oopsie yeah
that's that might be a popular massage
um
oh yeah uh acupuncture yeah
i want to try it have you ever tried no
i haven't
i don't know i'm alive
i totally would have made this if you
hadn't died
that was the one i really want to try
acupuncture
punch
okay
[Music]
you want the carrot no why not
[Laughter]
okay you better not mess this up amen
okay
i definitely won't if i can get
[Laughter]
okay good job now don't don't die
just don't fall into the spikes not that
hard okay good yeah
okay grabbing you okay nice we're so
busy now that nothing can stop us yeah
yeah
nice juice
only a minute 30 seconds first try
first chat yes oh no this time oh cause
the carrots
feel this world oh oh my god
oh that's a big hole be careful
[Music]
yeah maybe because there's more spikes
over there ah oh wait there's more
okay i think i have maybe we should go
down yeah they'll need the character oh
my god that's some t-shirt oh
no no no no no no no no no no
to make it less painful for you you know
it takes me down
i see you oh oh oh you need help
you need help i don't think i can go
back up actually i don't think i can
alright can i come back from that no
no oh a
nice snack okay
ouch ouch
are we allowed to show that blood on
stream yeah
it's not blood it's ketchup oh
nice okay careful here there's spikes
down there right now they're like way
far down
really oh yeah i'm scared okay okay okay
oh yeah how do we do this we have to
jump
we gotta jump real good though
okay i'm not doing anything you kick me
on your own
[Applause]
the first step you know i'm usually the
one who does the first step
oh okay really close yeah you got it
yeah
nice you got it okay that didn't move
anything
hmm oh okay can i kick you
oh yeah but then what about you
i'll figure it out
wait no practice
[Music]
you made it alone you gotta make it
together this is uh this is teamwork
training for whole live english members
oh yeah oh wait why am i on top oh i
look i was looking to the ground oh
you're bleeding a lot okay i'll go
that's good practice
your toes don't need your toes
oh your head now this is hard you need
to go to the hospital soon
oh yeah it's really difficult oh
okay that would be so hard to get right
yeah
um
all you need is luck mm-hmm
okay
it's two bunnies on a on a what what the
what uh
on a spike what's the bunnies in this
bike
grilled bunny um
cuddle okay oh okay okay okay wait
no no wait you didn't die
oh oh i guess i didn't it's good
practice for you
okay look i'm playing with your dead
buddy
[Music]
and then yeah okay don't stop in front
of it but
yeah just go
hey
[Laughter]
i don't want to punch you into that all
right you going to go first let me get
over it
[Laughter]
stop
trying to get go first
[Music]
okay uh
stop
moves
[Applause]
why does it not go to the front oh oh
i don't know skills
pro gamer skills
you know you want you want to know what
makes me such a pro gamer ah
your heads i got something i i got some
some
really cute things um gamer girl things
like i got a pink
uh razor controller
now that's funny like a good investment
but you know
one other thing that i really questioned
myself why i got it is like you know
that
pink razor um headphone stand
oh yeah it costs like 80 bucks
but i don't know why i got it like i i
didn't even need a headphone stand like
i got my headphones but like
why why spend 80 bucks
80 bucks to like put your headphones on
that thing i don't know man i got it
yeah i guess so also it has free usb
slots so basically i'm just paying for
three usb slots
but it looks cute all right i got it
this time i think i figured it out okay
even though you think you're figuring it
out you didn't make it last time
um i was
i don't show you game glitch
yeah nice wait are you still alive
[Laughter]
[Music]
i couldn't even do anything pretty
magical
really looks like you're doing like some
nice
[Music]
we ran out of time i think did the clock
stop ah it's because
[Music]
[Laughter]
my what your your butt
outside i'm trying to just
why can't i go no
i keep going backwards physics
don't hurt you guys so much yeah yeah
just make it quick and short
like okay it does it
it wants you to try at least maybe there
we go
now this time all right guys since you
can make it across you should kick me
across and then
you can go okay i'll try okay
[Music]
but don't die right after that okay okay
wait not yet wait let me let me line
[Music]
i think what we learned from that though
is that even if i kick you it might just
kick you really straight
uh yeah i had to line up we had to yeah
okay okay oh yeah
use my body
ah you you are your body is just so
useful amen
because i'm soft and springy
nice damn
now i'm just gonna wait for you here
oh [\h__\h] oh no hey
[Music]
okay so i'm gonna line up like this i'm
not gonna kick me
it was a good try we should have been
closer maybe for that one yeah
that was a good try
what if we go on the top what if there's
a way easier though on the top
okay you know what never mind oh there
is it okay there's that oh yeah
oh wow that's a lot of work
okay
okay thank you for that very helpful
you just led me the way to to revival
thank you i know how to revive myself i
know
how that works i'm a phoenix
okay this is exactly how our 3dw is
going to look like
a lot exactly the movement i'm going to
show everyone okay yeah
okay okay no don't really want to lie
down
okay should we maybe get a bit closer
okay all right i need to
not i'm not on the right side
[Laughter]
okay okay okay
i'm now i'm ready wait i want to move
closer to you though
david not too far away okay okay perfect
okay ready yeah
i think that way you're gonna die in
that angle
yes smell my feet
i don't think that would work all right
kiara now it's time to show off your
skills
okay okay i'm gonna go a bit backwards
and then yeah yeah yeah
oh okay oh oh
oh oh i don't know how to do
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's okay it's okay yeah i'm gonna
start over there again because um me
getting over there
is just a matter of luck and
skill right but you getting over there
is a matter of
how how well kiara throws
[Music]
this is hard maybe there's an easier way
to do it
no no okay no no
you cannot escape
oh sorry sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay i'm ready and that's kind of looks
dangerous but okay you ready
yeah three two one
[Laughter]
okay maybe we should try individually
again let's just get the uh
we'll just get the strategy down okay
i think people are getting frustrated
looking at us
it's fine i want to see them try they'd
probably be pretty shitty
yes yes tell them tell them i like it
when you do that
you guys suck no i didn't mean it i like
bossy no not because i can boss people
like
like i don't give a [\h__\h] about you
amelia
just stay there okay okay
okay
that was close
it's hard to do alone wait hold on
the skill of throwing you over there but
hmm
maybe i should maybe i could catch you
like if i'm
no i think that physics like if i were
like this
and then i grabbed you and i went
[Music]
that sounds like something that you can
do in your fantasies but not in reality
okay i'll just go pale myself on the
spikes
but the moment when you want to do it
then it won't let you do it there we go
there we go oh my god
i love the way he held though he was
like
no why
oh
i wanted to go like yolo and hope that i
hope that i would just make it oh my god
i'm just lucky
maybe we can't use the momentum from the
the thingy
okay if we jump at the right at the
right time yeah
okay you go first okay um
i really still don't really know how
just how to jump to one side though okay
oh wait okay i'm scared how did i do it
first
okay thank you thank you now you gotta
make it
okay uh okay and you believe in you
have confidence
yes have confidence ah no not your butt
precious butt
okay careful we both have to concentrate
million percent now okay let's go
oh we could run over okay okay grab you
got me i think that will go wrong
but okay okay let's go let's go then
okay
[Music]
at the same time you think we were
synced up yeah
just just get to the edge get to the
edge yeah you go one more time roll
stop yeah and now tip forward and then
when your
body is tipped forward jump
[Applause]
the feeling of accomplishment is
immaterial
it's really nice
[Music]
okay they'll probably be more later in
the level
yeah oh what's here why is it where is
there danger mark
i'm gonna die oh hey that makes it
easier
okay oh not better okay not
bad oh that's what's up there
oh no now grab me
[Music]
oh ouch oh okay i can do it
well then how to use the physics in the
game
um
did you know that um i was actually
supposed to be last year
the reason why did you ever know that
ryan was actually in japan last year
no i was supposed to be the
olympic torch oh oh
isn't around you know on fire and all
that yeah
i was supposed to be me and i was
waiting
[Laughter]
that was the spirit from the olympic
george there yeah
yeah anyway my dream was kind of crashed
this olympic never happened and who
knows if it's going to happen this year
um they're still deciding on it if they
decide to make it happen after a while i
might go back to japan
to be the olympic 2021
eyes tokyo die
yeah that's pretty impressive i didn't
know that we were
you know in halloween yeah
you're famous for my fire so they they
hired me to be the torch
wait isn't the olympic fire that has
been going for like a really long time
yes i'm always on fire oh okay by the
way i died
we can do it we can do it just believing
in your power are we in a new level by
the way i feel like we
we skipped one level no this is the same
oh
yeah no we did it remember okay oh yeah
with the power up little torch
yeah i'll help you yes please i'm gonna
go knock me down
stop stop
okay i think i'm happy
[Laughter]
[Applause]
yeah i think you gotta maybe give up no
oh it's fast oh hey i'll go back
[Music]
um
time is the essence or something like
that right
um is it oh yeah time is of the essence
that's the phrase
oh there we go you know remember that
yeah remember that phrase i had i am
timeless
i am timeless yeah
and you had it's elementary in it it's
elementary ain't it
you know now that i'm in australia i um
people are asking me to speak in an
australian accent actually an
alien without the wing um but like
you you are obviously the master of uh
you teach me accents to do an australian
accent mate
oh [\h__\h] um
yeah you say good day good day
uh good day mate good day mate good
[Music]
hey you day you wanna put some shrimps
on the barbie
you wanna put some shrimp for the barbie
we got a ciggy we're gonna go down to
the arvo later
hey you wanna get my you
does that wow i'm gonna be so funny does
that really sound like
uh australians viewers please tell me
does that sound accurate and when you
say no
you gotta say no no no no
no it sounds like a cat in pain
it actually exactly sounds like a cat
like when my cats are like in pain
now okay
no no no no
no wait can you say it again no
no no
[Laughter]
how do you say yes
um okay
yeah yeah nah that's another thing that
i'll show you guys will say
oh my god that sounds so sexy
i like english accents my favorite one
is british though
oh yeah the british accent oh
i love british accents it makes me quiet
i'm quite excited pointing
out
[Music]
oh my god please amelia don't mess up
now
i mean i saw that coming so yeah
i thought i had it
[Music]
that was such a pro run honestly
we're never going to do it again that
well
as i'm struggling right in the beginning
oh no oh no not again
oh
noise okay now
concentration once again we don't wanna
we don't wanna use up too much of the
patience of our viewers
otherwise they're going to go insane
into back seating mode i think they're
already i think they might already be
there
i made it
[Music]
it's okay
i'm trying to die as fast as possible
okay this is the run
i feel it i feel it i feel it in my
veins
i feel it in my pocket wait what
different was that what
was that something if i feel it when my
veins are filled in my pocket
i'm sorry i can't help you too far away
save yourself
save yourself don't give up i'm in
i can't see
no no banana
come back there i'm going to kill myself
let's go
nah i didn't die first that's all that
matters
oh you need help you need help what's
wrong you want some health care
i just tried to come to you
whatever
you said what was that thing you said
before about oops
when you have a thing and a thing and
then it's a sandwich what did you say
i have no idea what you're talking about
and i think in the most [\h__\h] collab
and i was like wow how impressive
up lean back okay
i don't know what you're talking about
cheese before cheese cheese and cheese
cheese it likes a sandwich oh my god
that was so bad
like a big chunk of cheese
what is the definition of a sandwich
does it need bread
because i've seen some actually okay
good question let me
let me wikipedia
sandwich wikipedia
uh do you want it in german or in
english i know that only comes up german
for me
can you translate it for me
english one second english or espanol
now let's go with english
a sandwich is a food typically
consisting of vegetables
sliced cheese or placed on or between
slices of bread or more generally any
dish
bread serves as a container or wrapper
for enough you need the bread almond you
need it
it's a must i've seen before people like
with burger they put
the lettuce in the they put the burger
in the lettuce
i mean i guess that works dude no that's
that's like a vegetarian type no wait no
a gluten-free yeah okay yeah that's the
option oh yeah
oh hey now that we cleared the sandwich
thing up let's clear this thing
this level oh my god oh my god i made it
i made it
okay you're chatting okay stage is yours
okay show me your magic show me what you
got amen
[Music]
yeah indeed maybe oh maybe you need like
a like a powerful sandwich too
i might yeah the power that you need
just eat yourself all the way over there
i'm just going to die over there yes
please
i died
[Music]
who survives in the end it doesn't even
matter
all together dramatic oh
yes
i mean
having some complicated feelings in this
collaboration
now that i'm far away from cali it's too
dangerous to
to you know have such conversations with
someone i have to stay
faithful for myself
okay i'll try not to tempt you
[Music]
well now with you oh yeah
you know i gotta wait in this show i
gotta think about it
we gotta oh yeah i think i yeah i guess
so um
how high am i on the waiting list oh
you're pretty high oops
[Laughter]
on your way up just grab me i'll try it
okay now tip backwards nice
wrestling
[Applause]
come over here come over here that's me
okay hey you didn't even need me you're
you're strong enough alone you're an
independent woman oh it doesn't bounce
for me
wait i can't do it
okay now your turn okay now i will
probably feed
him back up back up back up okay okay
yeah back up and then go
ahead nice
keep going nice
and nervous now that it all depends on
me i'm too nervous
i know how it feels free i hate it
okay i'll go all the way back here okay
oh [\h__\h] okay
it's a good strat because you'll need
more momentum from the
bounce as you go forward if you can make
it mm-hmm
true yes [\h__\h] any minute what did i get
myself into here
um okay stop okay
tip four yep nice okay keep going
keep going keep going
don't lose momentum nice
[Music]
it's just because i wanted to spend more
time with you
but this is oh my god i'm just not i'm
not even doing anything the zone went
automatically
didn't even move a finger the game wants
me to succeed
live once only winners get a treatment
like this all right
[Laughter]
it will be difficult for me to kill
myself here
now you go practice yeah
oh this is gonna be a problem
i think this one might be um because
it's already 1am for me so this might be
the last level so we got to make this
one
okay oh that is really easy we will we
will arm it
okay but don't doubt it just belief
i'm scared i'm scared i died here don't
be scared
we died everywhere many times doesn't
matter we always in the end
we succeed okay we're winners
oh i didn't even need the trampoline and
now i go
and now you made it now can i yes you
can
come on come on a few more times
nice perfectly on time because now it's
one a.m okay nice yeah
we can do it yeah we should continue
it's really fun
this there's an interesting intention
that i would
like to explore further
okay
[Music]
can i um use this moment to
say something um to your viewers hoping
that there might be some
viewers of me no talk actually don't
don't worry
serious talk yeah do it
shadow bamboozled for one week and i
feel like many of my viewers don't know
that i've been back
streaming for a few days now and
nobody gets notifications and i don't
show up in subscription boxes so if
there's any kfp
viewers in inside of amelia's viewership
in here who didn't know that i've been
streaming the past few days
then now you know um yeah uh youtube
doesn't like me
youtube has wiped over yeah
now we have to protect her we have to
protect her
and raise her up and
so motivational so inspiring
if i'm lucky then maybe tomorrow things
could be back to normal but it's been
for
like this for a week now i'm really
pissed off so
i would appreciate a little bit support
thank you sorry
i'll give you support okay thank you
thank you let me let me let me listen to
your
accent accent english accent collection
privately later okay
yeah yeah i got it yeah
all right it was fun being a bunny with
you
yeah it was really fun thank you kiara
for uh inviting me to this club and also
for making the thumbnail and being
yourself
don't worry so hot that's so teddy
that's so wholesome
thank you thank you for having me thank
you for letting me
letting us do it on your channel because
my freaking channel is shadow band no
one would watch it if we would do it on
my channel
[Music]
goodbye
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
do
kick it again