P.Y.M.K.
Note, the
[song]
helper, I can't sing, I'm going to be stunned, I've never seen it before.
Sleep, Mom knows, but I love you so much, I must show my love.
Oh, kid, you go back home and play in Thailand. I have your grandmother's number.
Masita, who was leaving me, met me.
Eases the bird, who was shocked, and this is the
house of Sadhana. She has ears like that, which she has heard.  I've
known Khanakarn since she didn't come to the office.
There, Ee will look very loving now.
Madoremi's heart is looking at Korat. Mata can't get it.
Shu, Ebola has different powers.
[Song]
She's okay. I just met her. She said that Jejo Kido, who got hit by
Jai Dan Lo.  This block is less CU but it will have a bird's foot.  It's
up to you. It's your heart. You'll
say, "I love you."
This one, look at it. It's up to you. This one, I love you.  I
like it, Nadon, you'll
[song] I
like it, you'll look at me, I'll look at you, I love you, I love you.
Just now, I asked for a greeting from where we met. Order to
show the
little bird. Where is she?
She said, "Chicken since she was
a child."
She's just us, her name, who only has a face.
It's cute and sweet, okay.
Okay, she even this by referring to
[Song]
Doni,
this little one will collect this money by herself.
Doraemon,
time the timing from the eyes
[Song]